[MUSIC]
Last time on Gun City!
Our heroes were attacked on the train by a seemingly endless parade of Ken Bone guards from Gadsfield.
This insurmountable fight grew increasingly surmountable once Leroy Peanutbutter and his gang of roving Ken Bone hobos took the opportunity,
provided by Sullivan's flubbing to stage a train revolution.
Thinking quickly, Blowtoss Pisc teleported the gang above the train,
where they were greeted by a very angry King Gad,
whose mech was poised to obliterate the group.
Knowing all he loves is improv and musical theatre,
the crew sang and danced to the best of their ability in a desperate plea for their life.
Rolling a natural 20, Sullivan the Frog was like a regular Ricky Martin,
and King Gadd spared them if he could quote-unquote have Sullivan. This, as a
successful rebellion from Leroy's train hobos, meant the group could successfully
arrive in Who-town, not to be confused with Whoville.
Bloatoss Piss had a somewhat existential crisis, realizing he was just one of many
Who's, but not so existential that it prevented the gang from meeting with the
The Ku-Guru suck-ass shit.
They sang the sacred "Kiki, do you love me?"
chant, leading to a panoramic vision of all of Tamagotchi Empire's history.
By the end of it, they knew the temple was through the Christmas jungle.
Barreling through said jungle, the boys plus Snoochie Boochies bullied penguins with VR
headsets attached to their heads until they arrived at the incredible sight.
At last.
the sight of the template of the Penguin of Dune.
And so you guys are standing before this massive golden penguin.
It looks like the golden penguin statue you had, you'd gotten from the land caves.
And it also has a similar vagina front, despite Joey's amazing drawing.
I should have told him that detail, but I didn't want to I wanted to make sure the poster could be you know on things
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, so and also got the staircase
Yep
And yeah the the and the the
The temple itself is like massive, you know
It's like 300 feet by 300 feet probably and the outside is like shimmering gold if goal had any
Admit any value in gun city. This would be
Worth a whole army of wild stray dogs
The light sky reflecting off this massive structure could blind you and will actually make way ray william johnson take 1d 6 damage for
that he stands. I really wish I hadn't brought that up out of nowhere for no reason.
Me too for your sake, pal. You do. Your favorite thing is to make yourself take damage.
Okay, one. So yeah, the light reflects off of it and like sort of crests across your chest
and you take one damage. Okay, I start standing behind Solomon.
Every time Caleb's character takes damage, his heart pumps one pump worth of blood into his penis.
that is true
are just excited to see me or
why aren't you covering me you're too small
you could
track i mean
blowtoss is like
pretty much a ten-year can you just get bigger for once
well it's all in that stretch him out i'm gonna stretch you out like a lot of
the
well i don't know
sullivan way to help you out before we do
Before we do anything that relates to the quest we're on or anything, I think that a lot of the struggles we've been having with Sullivan would be solved if he was just normal size.
So I think we should maybe leave this temple and go find a wizard or a plastic surgeon.
Oh, the stretcher! I saw the stretcher back in Hootown!
Yeah, exactly. So I think we're gonna go back through the Christmas jungle, back to Hootown.
They have to have like a bigging machine there, right?
the
a
a lot like mary poppins doesn't it's really about it
it's a little bit of a little bit make it worse
everyone in this
temples gonna think he's fuckin mary poppins i don't want it
i want to start talking as can be for three wishes do that i want that shit
exactly how mary poppins was still a quick to get the which it was and i'm
not a very popular for damage of
in about a minute
all right
uh...
all right so i'm gonna get bigger my just got a bug in died
well i think you can take me to the stretcher
you and you can take a look
i know which way i'm leaning
all in favor of the stretcher
i and irish like it
so
let's do it now
now this is what let's do it
this time
I'm gonna destroy it. I'll see I look at the temple and I say I'll see you later. It wakes at you. Yes
The stretcher in more ways than one if you think about it stretches the story out too. Yeah, it sure does
Back through the christmas jungle
You see like the penguins just like
Like watching you all like leave
Stoogey Boogey's like just is sitting there waiting for you while the four of you go back sort of like a it's in a quest at a video game where all the people will just wait there for you to start the quest and you go back into the town to finish your last side quest to go to the stretcher.
You see this building that looks like a Whoville building, right?
But it's, which stretching makes sense, right?
It's sort of got the, it's kind of like the convex, it's got like a convex roof.
It's like a really small, it's like a ranch house almost, like stretched out.
And you see a guy walk out of the front door, who, it's first you see like his profile,
and then as he turns around and he turns out, he is like 10 feet wide,
and each eye is on each side of it.
And he's like, "I'm the stretcher!"
Okay, I think I've changed my mind about seeing the stretcher.
I don't trust this guy at all.
This guy is really weird.
Do you guys wanna... who needs to be stretched?
Hold on, do you do vertical stretching or is it just horizontal stretching?
Oh, hold on.
And he goes back inside.
And you see another thing. It looks like the top of someone's head.
And then when they bend up...
uh... higher there are a lot of people stretch it out with my brother had a
little bit like this guy a lot more and it's got to have a little bit of a
statement you let you can have a swag
yes all done just a quick question
do you want to do to do you want the diagonal brother
no not the fact that nobody's really we need to do it do you do you have like a
grower or something in there
You do have like a bicycle pump or something?
Which of the two green ones are you trying to stretch?
The little one.
Why not both?
Wait, now that we're here.
No, I'm fine how I am.
Wait, no.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Let's get the horizontal stretcher back out here on Patrick.
If we're fucking asking this guy questions,
if you're gonna stretch me, I get to ask the fucking questions.
I'm slipping the stretcher guy some money to stretch Patrick.
Okay, wait, if you stretch me, am I gonna be two-dimensional?
No. So what will happen to you is that you will be an average height for a creature,
of, you know, regular-sized creature like your two other friends here.
Uh, this will lead to you suffering some ability changes.
Okay, I'm not gonna get stretched, but maybe we'll stretch Sullivan.
Can you turn me into a square?
-Yeah, wait, can you make me smaller? -That would be...
No, that's the shape in our next door.
The Squishers are next door.
They're a family of four.
And they love squishing people.
If you wanted to squish, you can go there.
Well, can you just like, is there any way that you could like,
lock the proportions of our frog friend and stretch him kind of both ways?
To be like, kind of the exact proportions of me?
You want this deluxe stretching.
How much is that going to run me?
Of all three of us combined so he can kind of shade all three of us also
Could you make them less of a useless piece of shit?
So I'm trying to get a discount if you do if you do
Stupid frog
Look I have to admit that there are side effects to all stretching sexual side effects
Trust me. That's not gonna affect them. So
I got some statue this campaign
I need him to survive dude. I had to wear him like a like a snuggie. Oh
You want him to be now that I think about it? I could probably just get a snuggie
Is there a snuggler there's an outlet mall right next to this place
It's got an s-scene on TV store. Yes. Everybody there is shaped like stores
You know what we'll just squish this little kid
it
now you keep it
now we give it to me
you know or not my ass
and i can't do that
but
i can stretch your ass so it looks like it has a horn
does good
it's got a hurt
uh... i love that
Okay, what if we just do that and go back to the temple? Yeah, that'll be good enough. Yeah
Solve all the problems kind of run really fast into the temple
Okay, let's just look at how much money. Do you guys have let me think I
Have every Xbox game if I trade I am
Let's see. Hold on. He's taking the trade
Right what do you know what I have every Xbox 360 game
Mmm. Wait a minute if I remember correctly didn't you shoot them all out the guy driving the car?
How do you God?
What the fuck wait now that I'm looking at my inventory - I'm realizing is there maybe like a guy in this town that can turn?
lizard skin bones and penguin into a guy
That will follow my commands
I think this guy can do it.
Like if you like squish them together like and make like a guy.
Do you take... Is Minecraft Steve here?
Do you take American Express or Huge Worm?
I forgot you took a penguin.
I have lizard skin, bones and a penguin and I want to make him into a guy.
You need to go find Victor.
Victor von frankenstein.
Frankenstein?
Yeah.
It's an old hat, but you know, it still fits.
Is he living in this town?
Sure.
Cause if you say no, I'm gonna go to the other town and I'm gonna derail this even further.
Oh, I know.
Okay, so about that butthorn.
or
can i introduce you to the ipod touch
it's a seven hundred and fifteen xbox games
uh... and i thought touch would be more than enough
okay willing to be two words
okay you got it the pal so he takes you into the uh...
the place and you see
the long
him who's the the this vertical stretcher you see harry the horizontal
stretcher
uh...
you can't
see donnie the diagonal stretcher he is uh... deliberately hit
uh... news very fucking weird
uh... any brings you onto a table
and he you lay down your stomach
and he sees the computer on your back is is do you want this stretch to adjust
the s just the s today
you've got it
pals and uh... i like our for her new friendship
pretty cool is that a great eating
he starts needing your ass first
you know we heard for just the run tire time it is good to be seen
each cheek up
like in making like little spires out of them okay
and then he takes like a blowtorch
and like just fires them down
in cases them in something freezing cold
and now you have these two hardened like fucked up tumors coming at your ass
uh...
that you can use in the game, I'll say.
You should find creative ways to use it.
- I think I will. - It's a little harder
for you to walk, but it doesn't really affect
your total run speed, I'll say.
- Nice. - But yeah.
- Sitting down is probably a no-go, huh?
- No, you can't sit anymore.
- All right. - You're never getting
fucked in the ass again. - That's fine.
- Yeah. - Well, that's why I got it,
dude, is protection.
- All right, thank you.
I'm gonna go play with my iPod.
- Can we redo this scene so that I walk by a storefront
that has a mannequin with two asshorns in the front and then I see it and I get an idea
and then I walk in and then I walk out with the asshorns.
Can we just say that's what happened?
Isn't that exactly what happened?
That's right.
Okay, cool.
Can I just leave my penguin and skin and bones with you and just come back some other time?
Why don't you just make the guy?
Do you want me to look after them or?
Just make a guy.
I mean, it shouldn't be that hard to make a guy.
you
okay
i really fucked up your plan i feel like okay so now i have a really good guy
now there is there a net romance or is out of the future you can use
but he's a good argument to a double and bring it to victor
you know you're going to call it a lot of the year
can we bring victor here
the public does he do i have to add as you do house calls he's in other
service he's not i'm not affiliated ok i just called him and he said he'll be
here in one minute
okay let me go call victor to prevent any more of this. Oh i called it.
Oh there he is! Hey Victor!
This far no further i'll go call victor
and he gets on his PSB
and he calls up victor
and uh...
we see come down is like a
uh... uh...
ages very handsome regular looking
like blonde guy
in a later host
and he uh...
says
my name is the there
do you have strange things for me to combine
i give him uh...
uh... the lizard skin
the bones in the penguin and i also see in my mentor and analogy in water bottle
from the get that you into it is the
how that like factors in
i've got a point in my ass and i say uh... but you can buy this with the
frogs that he's uh...
uh...
okay i need to frog to consent
i was legal guardian
he can't spend
okay let me get the frog to any graphs frog in you
and you as soon as his face touches my ask about what the fuck are you doing
so i would be a problem i had to tell my as you discussed it but i know that
other guys supposed to be different sounds a little close to your voice
your freak maybe i'll come back to him and change it
and i'll run
hold on
he's dot so i think he sounded too much like the son of in some always sounds
like these
okay let me take your penguin sing
he takes the penguin
uh... uh... lizard skin in the bones
uh...
and algea water bottle
in algae water bottle
bottle any uh...
He goes up like a hill that looks like sort of the Grinch Hill like in Whoville.
And you see there's like a tower up there that looks like a castle.
You see lightning strike and you see him through the window and now he looks like Victor Frankenstein.
He looks completely different.
And you see his face like exaggerated combining these things together.
And he comes back down and he gives you his creation.
and he says, uh, ZZ is something that I, well, what would you like to call it?
And he shows you, it's a penguin that is a lot like broader shoulders now, from the bones,
covered in like lizard skin, and then it has this water bottle, um, that is like melted onto its forehead,
That holds a brain inside of you loading yo, I'm gonna call you Sullivan the frog
All right, come on Sullivan, let's go back to the temple
It's follows you around so be while Sullivan's there. Hey, wait, could you please call him just something else?
Oh, that's my name. I
I don't hear him.
Oh, shit.
Okay, so you three, four, five people, things, have this interlude, and you head back to the temple.
William Johnson, I guess you're using Solvent's Umbrella at this point?
Like, how are you protecting yourself?
I'm just running really fast.
Yeah.
I'm trying to get into the... I'll take whatever damage is necessary.
I'm just trying to get into that hole. Okay, so let me roll for whatever damage that would be so it's probably several minutes
Mmm. I'm very fast actually let's see well. Let's say it's at least I turn on my turbo mode
Let's say it's at least eight minutes, right?
That's 28 damage
Put the umbrella
I'll hold the umbrella over him.
Okay, all right, I make fun of the temple.
Look at your goofy ass.
Yes, umbrella.
I trip him.
So he falls face first.
Oh, okay.
So yeah, you make it back to the temple.
And yeah, it's the same as it was when you left.
That was so inconsiderate inconsiderate of you guys to take that huge detour.
or we were just about to get into the temple.
I wanted to go in here the whole time.
- Yeah, you guys, that made no sense.
- Who is that?
What is that?
(imitates frog croaking)
- That's Sullivan the frog.
- I thought this one was Sullivan the frog.
- No, that's Kevin the frog.
- No shit, don't, don't call me Kevin.
- Okay, wait, wait, wait, we'll solve this.
I point to the penguin.
You're Sullivan the frog one.
And I point to Sullivan.
You're Sullivan the Frog too.
You know what, I'll... shit, I'll take it.
We'll just call you Crud for short.
Oh shit, fucking hell.
Shut up, Crud.
Yeah, Crud, what are you doing?
Go into the temple, Crud.
Yeah, Crud, you go first.
Sullivan, you're chill. I like you.
He gives you a shaka brah.
So yeah, so the temple itself is surrounded by this like massive moat almost, like it's
on like an island and then there's this moat of like really, really, really warm water.
They say that there's a secret star that died 3 billion years ago and its heat death creates
like a single beam of heat on the planet of on planet
Ibom in the soy waste and it's this pocket is where
it's somehow miraculously form.
You see also all the penguins like like over a hundred
of them are holding hands doing a kiki dance around
this big temple and you see a snitchy-boochie says
they do the dance of my people the kiki dance.
They respect me greatly.
But before we go any further, I must know.
Uh, this Pennsylvania Jim and his Crayola, do they know where we are?
Probably, I don't know.
They probably do.
Why don't you ask them?
Yeah, they're right over there.
(laughing)
- No, no, don't do this.
- I was just pointing to a group of penguins.
- See one of them just looks at you with the gym face.
Like, holy fuck, that looks just like gym.
- Yeah, as you make it through the warm water
that surrounds a small sandbar,
It's it has like a restorative warmth.
It's like a heated pool at a hotel though.
Not like a natural hot Springs.
It feels weird and and as you walk towards the temple one of
the VR penguins turns around and squawks at snitchy Bucci's
like rock up and up and Suchi Buchi says they are saying that
the
I'm not gonna say it if that's what you know. No, not to say the word. That's just sort of like a
Long like a long joke over the whole thing. It's not nobody should say the word. Yeah
It's kind of ready to go into the temple Caleb don't
Yes, yes, yeah, okay
The first thing you notice is that there's a 15-foot vagina in front of you though. Mm-hmm
and it is dry.
Oh no. I'll take care of this.
I start rubbing my ass horns on the sides of it.
Yeah, you like that you big stupid golden bitch?
Nothing happens. I huck a loogie. She loved it.
You huck a loogie. That kind of...
you see it sort of stir a little bit from the loogie.
the
acting that was a that was a positive
which doesn't do anything
dot are a it
credit
you there
uh...
and i think you can you read well
it's your name
okay uh... it always has been by the way
i've seen you it was a before the technique that we love something to be
desired and i wasn't trying to how about you
give it a shot
come on you got this all day
you banged her sister
bring it up
and he's is that
the help
all we have
girls love that
okay uh...
uh... my friend pushed my head into your sister's vagina
indians start going
going at it
uh... unit
all it doesn't quite work you see it's sort of getting
a bit loose but he still can't push your way through
it's still like to talk
matter shooter way out of this was
uh...
uh... you can do an investigation check to to see if there's something you're
missing here okay i'm an investigate
you know i will tell also twenty one
there we go twenty seven she's not my great
ten okay plot us is just enjoying his new friend too much
patrick you know that and uh...
really johnson
you noticed that
vagina does have something at the other gen it didn't have which is realistic
but not
completely realistic
which is that it does have
something that looks like a clip
that clinton looks like
something that is maybe with that twenty seven dot
it's about the solvent sized
which one
the carrier recovery solvent yet right
okay and
to that correct size
yeah can i reach it
uh... you can almost reach it
you can walk across maybe if you like jumped you could probably right i'm
gonna need to stand on your head
I can't hold you up, there's no way!
Do I-
When have I ever gave a fuck about you?
The entire time I've known you!
Okay, that's a good point.
Alright.
Get right there!
Yep.
You got it.
I get on his- I put my feet on his head.
Alright, he's gonna have to roll a strength check to see if he can hold you.
Which is not gonna do well.
He's gonna be able to do it.
He just collapses immediately.
Like...
I throw him up in the air at it.
I throw up.
Wait, you throw who?
Crud.
Okay.
Yeah, you throw him at the clit and he's just holding onto it.
And the, the, the door is just start to go like, they just vibrate a little bit.
Oh,
start peeing on it.
Go nuts, dude.
I don't have to pee.
Make your, sorry.
I'll get you some water.
Wait, let's go find some water.
We leave.
Yeah.
There's a, wait, there's a moat out front.
We get a, we get some water.
That's not clean.
We got to go back to town.
what
don't move
*laughter*
wait can we go to the bucket store
you guys
I'm gonna throw a pail of water
maybe peeing isn't the way, let's think about this
hmm
bite it
I've got an idea
and he bites it and it shudders again
but it's not like
there's something about it
didn't quite work to bite the click
just something do something crazy
uh...
and he just starts laughing at
and this starts to work a little bit
uh...
you start to see a bit of juices
trailed down
from the door
and go directly into
the moat insert to realize
the moat
in the juices
and you start to realize
there one in the same
uh... this time i actually throw up
yes
yeah
and i you know i'll take a point of damage to yeah he's gonna punish yourself
so that is that's horrible
yeah i wanna
uh... it's all of them can you just be back
whatever the fuck that thing is okay and he starts is he slapping it
uh... and it's blue blue blue blue blue blue blue and then it's just like
fuckin more that stuff comes out
and then it's finally just
like flooding the mode almost the penguins are like
panicking a little bit
but then then uh... uh...
the the click like sort of not solving off
and
you can walk through these
stimulated doors
the work road
great job great job credit really
you're going to go through for the team is to the building he says was that good
for you
what's a
uh... no not
knock it off knock it off credits that you're not going to be a girlfriend i
was trying to make a alright
last time i try anything like that
and uh...
yeah you guys can walk into the temple
uh...
and uh... you do with stitching beaches in tow
We go to the first part of this temple.
The first part.
It's a massive room and it has like this like below you is like
this sort of a almost like sickly green.
Like cobblestones and like this mud and and it's sort of this
like mixture of terrain. But yeah, you can't see too far ahead just yet just because of
how dark it is in here. But yeah, that's what you're seeing right now. So what do you guys
one
to
on purpose because how could you be so foolish?
Well no because I texted the group chat that we were recording tonight and I asked him
what time he ordered it.
We're recording at 7, he knows that.
He ordered at 6.45.
Yeah but sometimes he just does something on impulse and he doesn't know.
That doesn't...
I know, I know it doesn't make sense.
You don't need to...
I'm close enough to kill him now.
Right.
And he should be more aware of that.
I'm gonna pause this so I don't have to edit through all this stuff.
Yeah that's fine.
Yeah, that's fair.
Alright.
the
You saved that in order, 'cause you just threw away all of your food.
Sometimes, sometimes with Pat you're like, "Oh, he's just sort of a scam."
And he does shit like this.
Yeah.
You're like, "Huh."
He's actually an evil person. I'm not evil.
He's got, you know what it is?
Spit out the fry.
It's, he has like a, he does have a selective thing going on, and then he remembers
that it would be funny to do something, and so then he does it.
And then it's sort of like after the fact, he's like, "Oh."
that was a part of the other thing they were mad at but it was funny
again
and i think i guess that's just what i think i'm just it's a good thing to do
and i think i could like a year and a half
for the
well this is that we don't know if if if if now you're in new york i'm gonna be
able to send you a lot more because i'm gonna see how you interact the city with
its people
when i see how you you handle things like taxi cabs
you know you know
and uh... yeah
park is my best friend
i was second in the arc
right now we're gonna we're gonna go back to the episode madrid electronics
that's my bodega
the
the good oxford i'm a statement but yeah
so uh...
you guys are
in uh...
uh... good you're in the temple
uh... i was saying what do you guys want to do so you're looking at it's got the
sickly green
cobblestone with the most of it is dark yet
you know it's a bit starkly nasty you'd have to wait for
wander your way through to
a crime or what it is
can you get flashlight you can you just can you just like run around the entire
map and reveal it all
can we have you on fire and then throw you into that dark area
i'll just i'll start walking
that uh...
so i'll have uh... solomon or a_k_a_ crud
is using a little crud from now on i think the accurate
crud manages to walk about this far
and uh...
he walks around i should say
uh... which reveals a bit more than that
to you guys
and it seems like that we're sort of seeing crud do that one more time
a bit of more of a kid since early
atrium
couple these wheels here
and large staircase and as you can see the walk through
c like a big
fuckin egg
in the middle of like a
stone nest
uh... what's a tomahawk she isn't it
you know
it is he's that is what the seas
uh... i'd love being an archaeologist
the
book of different kinds of terrain kind of
mashed up in it
uh...
okay
uh... okay we're going to see if you get eighteen fourteen so
uh... as you sort of wander around
uh... patrick you know that and uh... ray william johnson
you also are able to see that there are these two
uh... very pretty windows
that have uh...
outside of them he's like glass
uh... boxes
uh...
and they have these numbers on them as you look outside the windows he's class
boxes seem to be
uh... suspended
in air and beyond those class boxes you see like
a giant like
room filled with water
and like some sort of
long
iron bridge
extending out from
a door that's behind the a and leave
and that is right over here
between these windows
and that door is
sealed shut
and glowing blue
uh... but
you see these glass boxes extending from these windows one has a number five on
it the other is a number nine on
so there's just two of them
all my god this is where we're still five nine lived
uh... the wheels you see so far i turn the wheels to five and nine
uh...
so the wheels are not they don't have any markings on
they don't have any number markings on
uh... which we'll do you turn
the five-mile direction
and uh... and
as you turn it you feel a notch change
and like a like a sh
And as you feel change, which direction do you turn it, by the way?
Clockwise.
Okay.
As you turn it clockwise, it goes from five to six.
And let's get everybody in the positions that they're in.
So I know you're here.
Blow tosses here.
That's never a good sign.
Crud is here.
Where's Sullivan?
Yeah.
Do we have solvent is solvent is buried his head in the ground.
Okay, and is eating eating something looking good.
Sullivan.
He lifts his head up.
You see like a dead rat in his mouth.
He gives a thumbs up.
Keep doing you buddy.
I love you.
Got style.
Oh, yeah.
I love Sullivan.
Oh my God.
This new Sullivan is so sick.
so much cooler than the whole thing.
He's like a minion dude, he's the best.
Wait, wait, wait, can we ask New Sullivan his real name?
Like a Grogu situation, can we?
Can we do one of those?
No, we have to wait a few episodes for that.
Yeah, we gotta reveal it.
I have to make a character sheet for him.
[laughter]
Cause this guy exists now.
I warned you multiple times I was going to be making a guy.
Oh, you did, you did.
Yeah, this is on you.
He says a lot about you as a DM.
Honestly, I didn't believe you and that was my bad.
I should have known you would try to make a guy.
The last time we'll probably play this, you're gonna try to make a guy.
So, roll a dexterity saving throw...
- Blowtoss. - Easy.
- 13. - Okay.
So, some of the ground beneath you, some of that weird mixed terrain,
This like snowy muddy rocks like kind of forms together into a wave and
knocks into you
You almost get out of the way you almost sort of spidey sense it but not quite and it does
Seven damage knocks into you seven as you knocks you to the ground
And you see a stoogey-boogey sort of runs over to you and he says there's something going on here these numbers
These things the ground it is responding to your actions. Obviously, I
Fear that this is the n-word pass I
Should tell you what it does now that we're here
The n-word pass can remake reality
in
and it it's imaginative he make wishes almost with it so many celebrities white
celebrities use the n-word past in the one way that it would suggest it should
be used which is to let them say the n-word and preserve their career for
example Gwyneth Paltrow she used the n-word pass she's fine
Kramer didn't have the n-word pass you see what I'm saying you can you give us
any examples of celebrities that like we would know instead of ones from like 200
years ago and he gives like a recent example yeah yeah you know like space
Kramer sure space Kramer use the oh my god now I get Jesus Christ I remember I
remember space Kramer at the lol factory oh yeah I remember when that first
uh... dropped on space d_n_c_ i lost my mind
the are ever him on space and pat a man
yeah i don't know what i think i don't know what i would do not was crazy but
space mckee stanfield who's white
didn't use the end of the past
and look what happened to him
career over. I remember that. We all do. So anyway, but this is not the only thing the
N-word pass can do. This is just the way that people have used it. If you use it beyond that
though it has dangerous side effects. But if it's just to do something like, you know,
people forgive you for doing something very stupid, you know, that's reality you could
remake with little cost to yourself.
So what I am thinking is that the N-word pass is remaking this room.
It is doing something to it.
It is making it react.
Maybe it knows that we're here.
So wait, we have it right now?
No, we don't.
We don't have it.
So we can leave.
I mean...
And go back to town.
If that's really what you want to do, this is Dungeons and Dragons.
You can do whatever you want.
What?
Hold on.
Let me talk to the narrator real quick.
You mean Space Dungeons and Dragons?
Yes.
Oh, okay.
All right.
By Space Gary Gygus.
Yes, I knew that.
Who is Chinese, as we all know.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, but yeah.
So I'm just saying we must be cautious.
So you're saying somebody wished for these wheels to change the numbers on the glass
boxes?
I'm wondering if somebody made this whole puzzle from the work pass.
Oh, so Pennsylvania Jim was here.
Perhaps.
He said perhaps.
That means it's true.
It's though at the same time, it does resemble the Tamagotchis.
Maybe the Tamagotchis made this before they vanished.
Maybe it's a trick.
Maybe.
I do not know.
But we must discover this puzzle.
I think we should talk about tricks.
I know that's right.
What are some two digit numbers that we could make with this?
23, Michael Jordan.
Well, it's on 6-9 right now.
That's true.
69.
So I will say though, just because you're in this giant room, some other things you'd be able to see is that there is also some sort of pathway this way that looks like it goes completely black as you go further into it.
And then there is a bit more of a pathway this way as well.
Okay, we should split up. I will go check out the right side path. Somebody go check out the other one.
the other one. I'll check out the left one. Okay. I'll go with Ray William Johnson. Oh,
I have to work with Crud. No, you get Sullivan too. You can balance each other out pretty
much. Yeah. Honestly, Sullivan kind of more than makes up for Crud. He's like two times
as cool. Easily. Easily. Okay. That's all right. Got it. Loud and clear. Who are you
talking to? Sorry, Craig, did you say something? Oh my god. Did anybody hear a fly say something?
Buzz, buzz! That's right, that's right, Sullivan. That's f*cking right. Oh yeah!
Oh, I thought we were talking about that fly we met on the way here. Sullivan,
I just love your catchphrase.
Yeah, and he sort of wanders over to join you Patrick Yoda and and you
So Cameron's just me me crud
Enjoy me crud
Having zero debilitating effects on my brain, I'm fine
It's easy. Are you crying?
Me crud
Meanwhile, you two and Snoochie Boochies goes over in this direction.
So you guys see it's like a long... so let's do a... oh goodness.
Let's do the Sullivan-Patrick path first.
So yeah, you guys walk into this big room and you start to see that some of the snow effects of the N-word pass grow in size.
So it's a, the room's like colder almost.
And you see actually another one of those windows and you would know, you don't even have to
roll investigation, you would know that that the window has a number behind it.
This time it's the number three.
Um, okay.
Is there, is there like a switch in this room?
So that's a good question.
There's a few things in this, in this larger sort of room.
So you see the same musty green cobblestone and you see also a couple corpses of dead
adventurers from the past.
You also see a computer and a couple of servers.
The computer and the servers are off.
They don't seem to be functioning.
And then you also see a pedestal in the middle of the room.
A pedophile?
Nope.
There is one in that room right now. Yeah, it's crud. Mm-hmm. No, I'm not I can hear you
What I can hear I could stop stop drawing that don't I'm moving around
You can't him. This is really good audio
Moving around from the drawing of the word pedo. You're putting over my characters head
And you see there is a the in the pedestal
Yeah, the pedestal has sort of like a, it's pretty funny. Sorry. Okay. Sorry for everyone at home.
You see that the pedestal has sort of like a convex sort of a, or concave sort of a part of it where something could maybe go inside of it and then you see this computer and these servers you see this window that says three on it.
And so that's what's in this room, from what you can tell.
So I'm gonna open the computer.
Okay.
Uh, you open the computer and it shows a, like a grayscale pixelated version of a grave
with a ghost flying around it that looks like you.
(laughing)
- Hey, Sol, hey, Crud, come here, is this bad?
- As you see Crud walk over and look at the grave picture,
you see a ghost that looks like him.
And he's like, "Uh, this is weird, if anything."
- I shouldn't touch this then, huh?
- I don't know if we shouldn't or should touch it.
I'd like, hmm, I mean--
I'll check it out.
Oh shit.
Okay, wow, okay.
So, you're examining the computer and you're seeing sort of its, what is it, what does it do?
It's sort of confusing you.
What you start to notice, I mean with a crit on that investigation.
Yep, that's right.
You start to turn away from the computer and you see out of the corner of your eye,
are
you see him moving his head around and you watch his ghost
get smaller and you watch it get bigger even as as the real
Sullivan is like just like slapping the ground and acting
like a fucked up penguin is he looks at the you swatch his
ghost appear and disappear rapidly as his head randomly
turns towards the computer and also with that crit.
I will say that like you notice that when your head turns
away from the computer like when all your heads are away from it you hear the
turning of a gear
ok I should investigate more because I have no idea what what that could do
well why don't we we try
Okay, why don't we try all turning away from the computer?
We already are!
So when you turn back...
You fucking moron, we already are!
You see the number go down to two.
The minute stops.
It's like a Mario ghost.
Get it to say one!
I'm gonna go type one on the computer.
[laughter]
It doesn't do anything on the computer.
Okay, so I move, um, Sullivan and Crud away from...
the computer, like we all turn around.
Yeah. You hear it go-- you hear that crank go again.
Do you turn around?
No.
Okay. You hear that crank go again.
And when you hear that crank go that one more time,
you see uh...
the pedestal
shoot up
something in the in the middle of it
like a little hole it shoots up and it goes back down
and then you hear that crank again
is someone looking at it
is what are you fuckers looking at it right now
no
if you look at it
do you look at it
you gotta look at it sometime
what are you trying to get it to do
He's playing mind games with it.
Does the pedestal pop up again?
No.
If you stand there though-
Yeah, no, not yet.
Okay, then I'm gonna look at it.
It's now at nine.
What?!
It looped around, dude.
It went down to one and then you let it go again.
Fuck.
Is that bad or good?
I don't know.
I don't know either.
Are they all supposed to say nine?
You picked the wrong group of three people to do a puzzle like this.
Oh yeah!
[Laughter]
Two patches and one match.
I meant the three of us, but that's true too.
I mean, unless you know the solution, Caleb.
I've already figured it out.
Really?
Yeah, I have.
Hey, Ray, can you come here for a second?
No, I gotta figure out... I haven't even walked down my path, dude.
- Yeah, dude.
- No, we already finished the puzzle in here,
so we'll be there in just a second.
We were doing it off screen.
- Okay, then I'm gonna leave this room
and then wait for you guys.
- Sounds good, buddy.
Just give us a minute.
- Okay.
- There's a lot of numbers involved.
I'm getting very flustered.
- Okay, so you guys, you guys look down the pathway
to where you're going.
You can't see where it leads.
So you start walking down it
And you guys roll a dexterity saving throw.
YOLO, that's the motto.
18.
Patches is trying to kill me before I can one-shot his puzzle.
Big time.
Dexterity.
16.
Okay.
You both start sliding down a like mud slide
and you manage to stop yourselves in the middle after you fall about like 40 feet down.
on
you
uh... put pull up a will uh... your flashlight at
well if you're flat slide at brady william johnson
uh... or website
with its own i don't know what you're doing your brightness up i'll go to the
website for those on the
may you go to the sun sunday com
and uh...
uh... yeah
you see down you see that the it's like this moist like muddy
slick
to your end
and
You also start to see like little bugs like flying around like swamp bugs flying around
This better not be the butthole. I
Don't think it's easy butthole then lick it
Really prove prove yourself
Just cuz it's not a butthole doesn't mean I should lick it
Lots of things aren't buttholes and I'm not going to lick them like what?
dirt
Why not?
Yes, no one tastes good. I'm not saying it's gonna fucking taste good
Yeah, okay, but you just you just want me to prove it's not poop. Just put your tongue on it. You got to do it
Okay, I like put the whole tube like behind my face sideways
Some okay. Yeah
It tastes like mud
It's a fucking butthole what the fuck you lied to me I did I did no such thing. All right
And I'm gonna investigate the bugs, okay
Yeah, roll investigation
They just look like real bugs
Wasted that one. Okay. Can I can slide down the rest of the tube?
Yeah, you could try to slide down it. I'm gonna go for it. Yeah, you could just sort of jump and slide down
I do that.
Yeah, you slide down.
You must slide down like another, like, like, it must be like a mile, it feels like.
Okay.
You guys can't hear him anymore.
And you land, plop, in like a big fucking swampy mud pile.
Way down, must be way below the cave.
And you see actually another one of those windows.
And you see another one of those glass boxes.
And you see this sort of like muddy
swamp room in front of you. You don't know how far down you are.
Can I ask you one question? Yeah. Is this the last
number? Yes. Like there's only four numbers?
Okay so we need it to spell "leet"? Yes.
It's gotta be
He's not gonna he's ice-cold
Which the fact that he's not currently crying and getting so mad at you means that it's not Lee. No it is
No, it's Lee. It's Lee. It's either leader boob. It's not even boob. It's
Fuck. Okay. One second. Let me I got a Google something funny
Funny for numbers. It's not funny
Okay, serious four numbers
What are some of the most intriguing four-digit numbers
Let's think about okay, so it could be five one seven five is it that this is this is just becoming a hot about list episode
Mysterious number seven six seven one four that's the name of the number. Okay. I'm gonna roll an investigation check
Hmm, it looks like my little hole that that whole room is there stuff to the back of that room
That's a good question
Let me walk on over there
As you begin to walk over there you start to see
Heads rise from the mud. Oh
Oh, yeah
And
They ain't
Friendly are they smiling? Oh fuck. They are smiling. I'll show you what they are
They seem friendly something smile and not be friendly. What do you mean? Yeah, what you ever see the worst DM ever?
Oh my god, he was thinking
The Joker isn't really not friendly. He was if you were also a clown
That's a man. You were the also the Joker. He's like the friendliest guy of all you see these heads
Wow, why is up with this fucking tool?
the
Let's fucking go!
You see first a zombie Yoda
Do you guys see that? Yep. Yeah, okay a
zombie who and the zombie computer hack demon
The best I could find and you see them all staring at you
my friends and me
Roll for initiative.
Can I speak?
Well you don't know that this is happening because you can't hear me.
You can certainly try to scream.
I'm not a girl.
You aren't.
He involuntarily screams and I slide down.
No I do not.
I will roll for initiative.
Roll a save.
I got a zero.
(Laughter)
Caleb has to roll a wisdom save
or else he involuntarily screams.
is
you're definitely not going to go first. So why?
You're going to die. Say something, do something.
Uh, Hey, is it, can anyone hear me?
No.
You try to climb up the mud slide and you're having a hard time.
Yeah, no, I'll go down and help. Help.
Wait, I have an idea. Don't come down here yet.
Okay, I stopped halfway.
We'll have to be down here at some point.
So he can hear me when I call out for him?
He heard you when you said, "Can anybody help me?"
I said, "Can anyone hear me?"
You know what I mean.
I felt the free meaning of your words.
I decided if I need help here.
Okay, I'm sorry.
I heard the fear in your voice.
The friend link has given us...
Alright, I will allow him to come down and help me now.
the
I don't have a friend link with you.
I am just Christopher Lambert.
- Maybe, how did you know?
How did you know we were thinking about a friend link?
Maybe you do have one.
- Oh my, maybe it's the most powerful friend link
of all time.
- Hear from the distance.
Oh yeah.
- Wait, get Sullivan down here.
- Oh yeah.
- Yeah, come on.
- Wait, no.
- He sprints out of the other room
and just belly slides like the Mario penguin.
the
like like hello yeah if I leave that room without effect the fucking thing at all
I'll get down here will that affect the puzzle you'll find out it was fine
before you went in there
yeah alright i'm gonna run down leave leave his belief grief crowd upstairs
that we've got a red eye
he's got a rare is gonna be a total bummer
okay how i'll watch the egg
uh...
uh... just solving
the crowd
solving the crash
is just watching the egg
uh... for lordly
as you patrick you know the slide your ass down there too
uh...
all of you guys role initiative
so i get to rewrote not have so little
no one
all right
sixteen
nice okay
well it's not to go first
all right uh...
let's see here
which this one that's close to me is which was that
that's a zombie computer hack team
i'd run up to it
i'm gonna hit it with my arm
my uh...
dual pipes
mhm and i have advantage because i have my assassinate
as i'm going first
uh...
so sixteen
yet it's rover damage
and that's it
critical hit
sometimes to
nice well i don't know
yeah
uh... you just are fucking wailing on this thing with your pipes like boom boom
boom boom boom boom boom
uh... and this thing is like any beat up it was not expecting you to slide down
there just are feeding the shit out of it
ray william johnson
you take eleven dammit
ho ho
that thing still takes twenty-two but really doesn't you take eleven damage
oh shit also these are analogous
is our doppelgangers
are in the audience
for her
the but this letter was a it dot
that that what i had a you know that
these are now that we have to do that is the name of the that is their creature
name
yep they are the italic eyes
in
okay what i meant i take eleven
yet you feel like the girl who is a little edge
you
uh...
uh... be you apart
okay
yet you have another attack to
locals
don't get that one
it they did they know that
and don't do that
come on
when it looks like it's not maybe maybe the analogous will
i've run
i can't move again so i guess i'll shoot
you could move again you'll just opportunity
Okay, well I'll just shoot my analogous
It is nice to have something to call
Skeletons, yeah, that'll be so boring
14 it does sound like a creature so 14 does not hit
So you just shoot it and this zombie who?
Deflects it with its own like
Bone pipe 14 doesn't hit and it glares at you like it okay stares you down after that and that is my bonus action
I'm gonna teleport back just so I'm out of melee range. Okay, cool. Nice
All right
Patrick Yoda, it's your turn
I'm gonna try and talk
Okay, I'm gonna try and talk to it which line to me, okay
What do you what do you say?
Hello
That sounded exactly like the Minecraft zombie
That's pretty good
Fuck you
Okay, you can understand me
What do you need down here?
Do you need snacks are you hungry?
You see it rub its stomach oh he's hungry okay, and then point at you I
Know it's getting hot in yes, uh-uh
That's not gonna happen. What if I get you?
What if I call a delivery? What if I get something delivered here?
And you eat that instead and you
Leave us alone
You see it go like like maybe what about a pizza party?
And
You see it
Take a bunch of mud and like put it on the wall and start drawing
Pizza with mud and sticks and twigs and it has your face on it
No, what about a cheese pizza
His name's cheese, by the way
You see him like look for something like yellowish or whitish and just put it on the
the my pizza
so you would accept that she's pizza
i started a really hungry when i see them but pizza on the road
and what about a pepperoni and she had a next person's turn
and then wait no that
i think i think it's distracted and i go for a pokey surprise okay so you gotta
run
of him
So how far are you?
35 feet.
Yeah, but you're, you could be within five feet of it.
Okay.
I think, yeah, right up there.
If you move there.
All right.
That's a cool.
Holy shit.
You got a grit 28.
You're going to kill yourself.
Yeah.
Okay.
Hit, hit, hit him.
Hit the crit.
18.
Nice.
Yeah.
So it was like, it was like gesturing to the pizza drawing it made.
you see it like it was like putting his hand on his chin and just sort of
assessing like oh maybe a little bit this look you just run up to him and just hit
him with your fucking sandwich in the face and it takes a but I say eat this
bitch yeah and it says you're it's a good one and it just takes in the face
you don't take any damage from that you just get a new it in the mouth okay so
So what happens to the zombie creature?
He's hurt bad, you fucking like spun his head around, but he's still alive.
Do I have another move?
You have another attack, absolutely.
Alright, then I'm just gonna hit it again.
24!
Yeah, that hits.
Roll for damage.
For 7 damage.
Nice, yeah, you just like jab your sandwich in its gut after knocking its head around
its neck.
And it's still up, but it's not looking hot.
I flip it off.
like weekly tries to flip you off to
the zombies turns is is
so uh...
that who
first is going to uh...
uh... take out its it's uh... it's cringe gun it has
and should that you uh...
uh... the william now
no no really amazing
what the hell little old me
yet nice try mister skeleton but if you hit him you're gonna take damage
uh... you know i'm using deception
antiquating the you know i'm really got a i got a one
he had got a career on the hits so
that's pretty bad nights
bad for me
yet poets gonna be
more than bad for you
not afraid what's worse than that
very bad
well don't even that's
accounts here
you take a look and then it's
it's not that are you you made that sound way worse and he it's
kiss attack again
okay well don't detect me friend
okay
he hits you again
now looking to hot
and
he does six damage
well and i know one one damage
Okay, now the computer hack demon is going to
Take out a sexual grenade of its own and it's just like this nasty like rotten nutsnack
And it tosses it right at you blow toss to hit all of you
Okay, can I jump on the grenade all of you roll?
dexterity saving throws
The three of you blow toss and
Okay
Okay, you didn't have to Patrick go to your phone
Okay, you're gonna take half damage cam
Ray William Johnson you will not you will be taking
Full damage. So let's see. Let's see how you do
hopefully
You live
How would I live I have one health oh you won't go no, it's not gonna go
It's not gonna totally kill you though. So you'll be fine
You do take however ten damage and you take five
Can I kind of convince myself that I jumped on the grenade to say yes, Sullivan
Yeah, yeah, you see the new Sullivan and he's just like posing in the back and just like Sullivan
I I did this for you
Yeah, baby
I love you kid
He goes oh, yeah, and
You just yeah, you're knocked out
You're gonna start doing death saves you see what happens. All right, that's annoying wait
That's really not good cuz now if we kill try and hurt
Caleb skeleton one
Then it's gonna kill him. Yeah, nobody else can hit it
Mm-hmm
So we're kind of fucked
You got a heel Caleb next time
me yeah cuz you're the one with the heel oh right unless snoochy-boo cheese or
Sullivan where is my heel it's not in here for the other four skin so yeah
where is it it's in your spell section oh right all right I mean also techno
slime does heal people - oh no it's when no it doesn't I forgot it doesn't I'm
sorry I was like if short rests okay I was thinking of how short rests also
partially recharge techno slime and I got confused I'm sorry well you said I
did so I feel no no not how no no no oh no all right it is now the zombie Yoda's
turn it's going to use its own dark side force ability and shoot lightning at you
blowtoss this.
Oh, let's see how it do.
Holy shit, it got a crit also.
Oh my god.
Okay.
Are we gonna all die right here?
Maybe.
Does 19 damage to the tower?
Yeah.
What if it doesn't do that?
No, it does.
Can you hit me with a Borat Knot right now?
When I, also I have an ability, when I take damage I turn invisible.
Mm-hmm.
So you turn blurry, yeah, you're invisible.
So, now, it's back to the top of the order.
Your turn, Blotas.
Okay, um... - These doppelgangers are no joke.
Do I get bonus damage if I attack from being invisible?
Is that like a sneak attack thing? - Yes.
If they don't see you, then you're gonna add... I will let you, because you're kind of a rogue class,
add sneak attack dice. - Okay, I vaguely remember that from reading
the players handbook in fourth grade.
Yeah, for sure.
You're gonna have to explain that to me.
I will.
Okay, I'm gonna go to the guy who's me.
Okay, so first do a stealth check to see if they...
but like with advantage, because you're invisible.
Yeah, thank God.
That was a close one.
Yeah, it was a crit one otherwise.
Okay, let's see how it does in perceiving you.
What's your...
perception?
Okay, yeah. It does not seem to sense you. It's like trying to find you. It's like looking for you.
But it can't find you. So, for you, you're going to add 3d6 to the damage you do right now.
Okay, do I get advantage on the attack?
Oh yeah.
Okay.
I'm going to use my dual pipes here. 23.
Oh yeah. That hits, baby.
the
So yeah, you have another attack obviously still.
Yeah, I'm gonna just use my dual pipes again I think.
Do it.
26.
Yeah, that hits.
15.
Fuck yeah, yeah, you just beat the shit out of it even more and it's not looking good
either.
All three of them now are not looking too good, but particularly Zombie Yoda and Zombie
Who.
I also I'm gonna teleport I think
To further away from everyone else so that they can't hit us all with a grenade again. Mm-hmm. Okay, you're up
Patrick Yoda. All right. Well, I'm just gonna beat the shit out of this guy
You got a heel Caleb. He's oh, yeah, I guess you could do this first. How many years you need to move?
To act to to attack actions you can do so if you use a spell then that's like the only spell you can use
is
are
that up with Crud or Sullivan. Sullivan. Okay. Yeah, you have to teach him how to sight. How
to fight. Do it very quickly. Yeah, well, he just watched me just do some. He's a very
fast learner. He just knows how to pose and have good time right now. I love him. Don't
make him. No, yeah, I'm not mad at him at all. I'm smiling as I'm dying. He's doing
He's like a silly little dance, he's like "ohhh"
I'm just like "huh huh huh"
"huh huh huh"
As I'm bleeding out
I'm like just "huh huh huh"
Cause I'm looking at him
I'm knocked out, I can't see him
But then there's a dream bubble that pops up
And he's doing the same thing in my dream
Alright, so
Should I use the foreskin first or should I just do Hoagie Surprise?
I say do Hoagie Surprise just to get this one out of the way.
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
Fourteen.
Bad hits.
For six damage.
Nice.
Yeah, you whack it again in its side.
But yeah, it's still up.
You have another attack, obviously.
Okay, so that attack would not count for my spell.
No, but that's your action then.
So you can't then do a spell.
So the way 5e works is it's like, if you have an extra attack, you can attack and then do an extra attack, and that's using your action for that.
Or you can use your action for a spell.
Okay, then I'll use the... So, wait, do I even need to, or is Caleb healed now?
Caleb is not healed.
You can't do an attack and a spell. You can only attack or do a spell.
You can only attack or do a spell.
So you have to... Just attack. That's all you can do.
Okay, then I'm just gonna attack.
the
and
bad.
What?
No, no, no, no, the zombie looks really bad.
It's it's like near dead near near, you know, near undead
folks, but it's still up.
Now, Stoogey Boogey is going to spring into action.
So you see him dash like pretty freakishly quick
towards the zombie Yoda and he turns to you, Patrick Yoda,
and he says, this is gonna hurt you.
Okay.
No, don't hurt.
Why? And he just says that and then gets a hit and does.
Yeah, it just snaps to Yoda's neck.
And you take seven damage from that.
But it's dead.
Damn.
Yes. Sorry.
He could not rescap it, I believe.
Ow!
Yeah, yeah.
Fuck!
Your neck just like, like whips around and then comes back.
Yeah, and that's, that's Stoogey Boogey's turn.
now it is the who and the the zombie who in the zombie computer hack demons turn
the zombie computer hack demon is going to turn around
to face you patricota and snitchy boochies and it's going to use matrix
beam or it's evil matrix beam where the
numbers are not zeros and ones but every other number but
um and so you two roll a dexterity saving throw
6.
Dude, this is so bad.
If you die, I don't have any healing.
Okay, and we're gonna have Tsuchibuchi's roll 1.
Okay, and let's see how much damage we do here.
Okay, alright, not bad.
We got a pretty bad roll.
So you take 12.
Fuck.
fuck and such a beauty six six so he is
you know what do you have patrick twenty-two
uh...
okay
now
it is uh...
uh... the zombie who's turn
and it's gonna run over
to you patrick you know and read it to you
i flip it off
it it double burdens
it doesn't even
notice it hits
I
the
*slap*
You're down.
You're knocked out.
Oh no...
Dude, I don't have any healing!
I believe in Sullivan.
*laughter*
It's like just, like,
putting its finger on its nipples and just doing little circles.
*laughter*
Like, "Oh yeah! Woo!"
Its brain is just bouncing around in the water bottle on top of its head.
*laughter*
You- you funny.
the
Let's go!
Alright, and back to the top of the order.
Blotoss, it's your turn.
Okay, has any damage been done to the RayWilliamJohnson skeleton?
Yeah, you beat the shit out of him.
You're 22 to him.
Oh yeah, okay.
But if I hit him, it will kill.
Alright, so I guess...
And I don't have anything that can heal. Can I...
Is there any way I can heal, do any healing?
Can I do like a medicine check to heal somebody?
You can do that to stabilize somebody.
Okay.
Well, I guess for now I'll kill my skeleton, because nobody's going to be dying for three turns anyway.
I'll have time to stabilize them, hopefully.
So I'll go up to my skeleton and I'll hit it with my dual pipes here.
11.
It's a miss. It gets out of the way.
I'll try again.
That hits!
19.
13 damage.
Oh yeah. Oh!
And that was after you did...
the
to it. I'm gonna die too. Straight up next turn. Okay. Um it's it's looking pretty bad but you did
a good number of damage to it. Um now Stoogey Boochies goes. Okay and it does land a hit on
uh let me see. Does it? Yeah lands a hit on. I was getting I was getting nervous there. It lands a hit
on uh... does not be a
uh...
and it says no it does not do prove
has rolled a twenty two proof check
uh...
routine
he killed his head
you know that you know you have a look in your diaper right now and i think
that i would have to do it
the expanse of the
the your hope will protect
it's fine to check you like it
this fine
uh...
however
the uh... he manages to do some like fucking like insane
k ratae
and just fucking uh...
uh... of beat this guy down
uh... to to death
uh...
that's on the news going you take
uh... you take eight damage so what i said i'm at eleven
uh... and now it's going to run over here
and try to hurt the computer hack team in as well
uh...
see
And it tries to hit the computer hack demon and it misses
um
Uh, it misses though. Okay
and uh, it has another computer hack demons turn and
It's going to whip around and use its dong blade on uh,
on uh snitchy boochies
Okay
And it connects with his head with the dong blade
uh
and
uses his fine but he's just doing like this people
uh... and then he's a whip with the sort back around here you can
how i'm invisible
i'll show you right you are
is that you trying to go after him that's right i thought i forgot
kill that n_p_c_
you know who hits again
home and
these guys are too strong
yet and his fault is that
the
Nope. Nope. That's a win. Anything over a one is a win. Yeah.
No! That's a failure.
Alright, cool. So, next in top of the order, Blow Toss.
Well, I can't... I can't hit the Ray William Johnson or
he's gonna die. Or how low does his health have to go before he dies?
It'd be negative his total HP. So you should be good. I'm at negative nine right now.
And my total is 35. Oh, okay. Yeah, I'll sneak attack the
And I only get half damage, right?
Yep.
Okay.
Yeah.
Okay, I will roll my dual pipes with advantage, maybe?
Yeah, with advantage.
Because I'm invisible? 21?
Okay. Hold on. Before you do that, I want to make sure.
I was double-checking the ruling for hitting someone while they're unconscious in D&D
and
It instead I forgot to write D&D so I just googled hit someone while they're unconscious
And
We don't follow D&D we go by the real rules here
Okay, yeah, and I don't know about in real life but in D&D yeah, they automatically fail one death saving throw if you do that
What no, you didn't tell me that no, I'm learning now. I don't want to attack them
Because that's two and two he'll just die he could possibly just die. No, he only has one failure
Yeah, and then if I hit him he takes another failure and then at the end of the turn order he's rolling again
I'm not gonna hit him if it's gonna get a death saving if I
Just do it, dude. I'm gonna teleport over to him and no balls
balls
right there. No, I didn't. That's why I was like, he was like, no, he won't die yet. He
wanted to die. Caleb, you remember that? I'm going to never forget that. And I said, no,
I'm not going to hit slander. And I'm lucky dude. I'm I'm a, you can, I'm going to stabilize
a, a, okay. We're just going to hit him anyway, no matter whether I do or not. I'm going to
check 10. Perfect. That's exactly what you need to stabilize. What does he do? You're
just
still
I guess.
Uh, no, because, oh yeah, you will.
You'll be-
I'll come back for you, dude.
I'll come back.
Thanks, brother.
I'll get you.
Yeah.
Thank you, brother.
Okay.
So, Stoogey Boochies is gonna try to hit this guy.
[laughter]
And he misses, so kinda lucky you.
And he's gonna try again, though.
And he misses again.
So he just like, [makes a noise]
And this computer-hacked demon is just parrying every blow.
And now he's gonna go and he's gonna swing back at the stoogey boochies again
and he misses
But he's gonna try again a lot of parrying just going on here and he hits god damn
Jesus
Soochie boochies is just is hanging on. He's not looking too good though
And now Patrick Yoda and Ray Williams Patrick Yoda death saving throw
15 nice, baby. All right, you're doing okay
Alright, I'm just like
People when you're on God just you're whining
All right blow toss
I
I guess now that Patrick's so close to stabilizing, I'm gonna hit...
I'm gonna sneak attack...
- Do it. - ...the skeleton.
- With my dual pipes. - Do it!
- 17. - That hits.
- Do I get sneak attack damage? - Yep, add that 3d6.
19 damage.
Yeah.
- This guy's dead. You killed him. - Yes, dude.
really is not a no-no it's the area you have you so you just like
you like
in theory after this grueling fight to start
bailing on this guy like
uh...
with him he will be with me in johnson is over the side like
weekly just like anybody else
is not the graphic of the house
the beginning it also
and this guy's dead
as soon as you kill this guy
uh... obviously really johnson you take a death saving throw uh... your
your you you you have one
negative you don't seem to know but you guys are about to have infinite medicine
checks basically we have a failure
uh... you guys are alive again uh... well well not quite we still have to do
health
we still need to do initiative stuff to to resolve the medicine check so
uh...
first thing is to keep it is is going to run over
to you ray william johnson and try to stabilize you
he does he stabilizes you
patrick you're all noticing them
fourteen you're stabilized
yes yes and you two are both stabilized
and then you you turn blowtoss like you're like
pop panting exhausted and you look over you see
uh... sold in the frog doing his little dances and stuff
and here through the window you see he's dancing in front of the point all year
all haha
and watch
as it one
turns to a zero
and here's something
from like
way way way back up
a crowd what's going on over there
can hear you
cried
well if you could hear it before
growing halfway down the slide crowd
crud
we're doing like a great thing
i guess i think i hear you it
yeah you know it's a little
uh... what
after that fight i'm not i think every inch i can get it here
what
what's going on up there is a
uh...
not nothing
and i've been up there
he's been a role investigation check
uh... no
now he's pretty good at either the other system
I mean, I can't make this fucking up.
Like god damn.
Oh my god dude, this is the most evil session of the game we've ever played.
I hate crud so much.
Oh my god.
Dude, this roll 20 is punishing us for going to the stretcher.
Yeah, definitely.
Okay, he's like, "Oh, I don't know.
I'm sorry.
I don't know really."
What?
I don't know what's going on.
What do you mean you don't know?
I don't know what's going on!
Do you have fucking eyes?
I'm coming back up there!
You try to walk up, it just keeps sliding down.
I hoverboard up.
You guys should like rest and restore some health too.
I'm gonna hoverboard up and then rest in the living room here.
Yeah, I don't want to rest in this nasty mud.
Yeah.
What do you mean?
It's comfortable.
You're right, I rest.
I lie on top of of Ray William Johnson like a blanket. I die
against to. Okay. I'm resting too. Okay. I don't think we
really had the option to rest but I do it. Yeah, it's fine.
I'll let you guys rest. That was pretty that was pretty tough.
I just meant like a short rest but if we could take a long one
uh well that's 8 hours. We sleep through the night in the
mud. Yeah. I love the dungeon. Yeah. Are we not supposed to be
able to short rest right now? I thought we well so no I'll let you guys short rest I think that's I
hate that rule uh there's like a rule where it's like technically you're not supposed to short rest
like when you're um because short rest is like down time and so if you have to be conscious to rest
but if you're unconscious and you rest theoretically you should be like getting better
is how I see it. I guess it's not as realistic. Like maybe you would say, oh, do a short rest,
but like take like only a quarter of the health you get back because it's not as well rested,
or I don't know what I would do, but I'm just going to do. It's a short rest for you guys.
It just counts as that. So what do we get from short rest? So you get to use spent, spend your
hit die. Yeah. You can choose how many. Oh yeah. Okay. I will use nice as many as I want. I'm at
Zero HP right now. Yeah. Mm-hmm
Okay, I'm gonna have mine
Suchi buchi sand is as well. Yeah, I'll go up to 24 HP off the floor hit dice
Okay, nice, which is just getting a lot of help back how many did I just get off it's just two rolls
and
i spent five
it does i want back up to forty two
union to get those back
how do i tell you how do i roll what you're doing
uh... she hit dice but none there at all got it okay
Yeah, yeah, alright. If you spend all of them, okay.
So you get 14, 22, 30, 39 back.
Got it. Nice.
Okay, so you spent 5, so
take 5 away from your total of hit dice as well.
Okay.
All right, so you guys rested in the mud for about a very after a very grueling fight with your doppelganger
The analogous the analogy
And you saw that thing turned to zero and you also what you didn't notice before you notice now
You see the wall over here
Which was you all thought was rock and mud like everything else so far in this temple you hear it go
And it opens and you see like a long staircase down
And
You see snitchy-boochies he's his eyes light up for a second he's like now these these I
Was confused these doesn't look like Tamagotchi that looks like Tamagotchi
We were in advanced people, but these all these rock
the
that
haven't seen this something like this it's like this chrome staircase but
it's like this with this gold rose gold hint to it it's quite pretty even though
it's like very dark as you look down further in there and and yeah I mean
that's really it. That's all you all you see so far.
Let's walk up the stairs. Do you do you mean down the stairs?
No, we'll go down and then walk back up. Okay. We'll try to
find some ups. Oh, okay. I think I I'll just start walking
down. Yeah. So you start walking down you guys as you walk
down the stairs. So as you guys walk down the stairs and you
hear your feet echo. You hear solving the frog echo is doing
his little dance moves and shaking and it opens up into
like this gorgeous. Vista of a city that is underground a
dilapidated city. It looks like a chrome like 60s like Sid
mead painting, like massive, like beautiful spires like that are just like buried in time
and decay.
And you see Tsuchi Buji says, "It's Tama Town."
Tomato Town?
No.
Yo, we're in Tomato Town, holy fuck!
Oh my god!
yo we're in tomato town holy fuck oh my god
[Outro]