Last time on Gun City, a broad city, the Uncle's Falcon. Our boys finally went into the Matrix 2
with all of its splendid second life type perverts, its vaporwave aesthetics, shifting architecture and
landscapes, the posts and the vibes. But before they did that, they visited the Mad Suckler with
John Carlo the Bullfrog in tow. They sucked on some fingers and they made a deal. Take care of
Jeff Tiedrich, the king of posts in The Matrix 2, and then they can use his The Matrix 2
ports whenever they want.
The detectives agreed, and after belittling a pig, they strapped in, sucked on a binky,
and became the selves they always dreamed of being.
Ray William Johnson became Jack Black.
Blotas Pits, whoops, Blotas Pits became Caleb Pits.
And Patrick Yoder became Caleb Pits 2.
Upon entering, they received a call from Mommy Goodlegs, telling them to go track down freaking
Carol Baskin, an associate of hers, and a message from an unknown sender saying "he knows."
They went into Dematrix 2, sponsored by Teen Vogue, and began to make some noise.
They went into Jeff's pagoda on top of Mount Paul and embarrassed him with sly trickery,
disguises, and good old-fashioned posting your dick and balls on the internet.
Sufficiently beaten down, physically, emotionally, and financially, after his entire V pagoda
was destroyed, Jeff T. Dritch and his Totemo Warui Itto, or "Very Bad Men," got the message,
and the gang was free to pursue their next lead, courtesy of the mysterious mommy, freaking
carol basket, who lives up on sway lake.
So, blow toss, reminders for the session.
You have no techno slime points, so you might want to recharge.
If you do, we'll have to roll to see if you OD and shit.
Also, you have a monkey.
I used the monkey last time.
It's so funny that every time you have to remind him that he has a monkey.
I remember I have the monkey now.
just takes a while to get used to having a... it's like having a third arm.
Oh yeah, you had a third arm all the time if you had one.
I would never forget.
You would forget it all the time.
I would know... I would use that shit.
Everyone else would remind me.
I would use my third arm like every day.
It's like if you had a pet dog, you wouldn't feed it for like months on end.
You'd keep forgetting about it.
Okay, alright, maybe... maybe that'd be the...
Oh yeah, also, did you have to feed the monkey at some point?
Yeah, this monkey is malnourished.
I feed it you.
I feed pieces of you when you're sleeping.
I didn't make it a feeding mechanic, but we can do that if you want.
- No, it doesn't eat.
- It doesn't eat?
- No, it likes it better that way.
- To the Lord.
- No, dude, he likes it.
He loves not eating.
What are you talking about?
That's what I say to everyone.
I look at my poor malnourished monkey.
- Just sad, a sad monkey.
- Yeah.
- No, dude, he looks awesome.
He looks like the Slender Man.
Ray William Johnson, you still have disadvantage
on dexterity saving throws for the day.
- Let's go.
- And if you take techno slime,
You have to be careful because you risk becoming fully addicted because of what you've done.
Not worried about it.
Uh, Patrick Yoda.
I wrote, "Oh, great job last session trapping Jeff Teejers inside your weird hoverboard house."
Okay, yeah, that's basically all I wrote for you.
You're fine.
Do you have anything nice to say to me?
Yeah, what about us?
I did the best.
I guess I just liked that.
You don't get to dole out MVP awards, dude.
Okay, all right, all right.
I have something for all of you.
Lotas's Jeff Teder's disguise was inspired.
I would have to say.
- Okay.
- Ray William Johnson,
I believe you were the one who posted your dick and balls.
I think.
- Sounds like me.
- That was pretty good.
- Yeah, you all think I would do.
- I think the bit was that only one nice thing,
but you guys are kind of children.
So I was good.
I'm glad I, yeah.
- I feel better now.
- Yeah, yeah, good.
- Yeah.
So right now you guys are outside of the Mount Pole.
just humiliate fucked up Jeff Tiedrich. That's right. And that's sort of where you're at.
So you can go to Soy Lake to meet with freaking Carol or you can do whatever. That's the game.
That's what's happening, baby. Whatever. Hmm. Damn. Do you guys want to open a restaurant
and do that for a few episodes? That sounds like a knockoff idea. Oh, that sounds great.
great for me. We're going to open a restaurant that takes three episodes to build.
Patches is literally a thousand yards staring directly. He just can't believe it dude. He
can't believe that we do this to him every week. There are, it's just like there's a
lot I'd let you do, you know. There's a lot I'm open to. I'm even open to that. Just have
to figure out how to do this Bob's Burgers subplot I guess.
Alright guys, here's my idea.
Hit us with it.
Tall burgers with tiny buns.
Tall burgers, short prices.
That sounds great.
What about hot dogs at cold temperatures?
I think we're gonna try it.
Let's call it the opposites restaurant.
Let's call it cold dogs.
And we give you hot mustard.
Wow.
I don't know why.
Hot soda.
Let's start a hot soda restaurant.
Freezing cold hot dogs.
It's called the hot soda shop.
And boiling hot beers.
Oh this is perfect for a Yoda like me.
all right is anybody know how to start a restaurant
actually i guess we have to go to college for it first okay
first we're going to need two years of college
okay yeah so there is a uh... is that i did is my idea okay okay one of us
handles culinary school
the other one handles marketing
and then one of us handles
met restaurant managing
okay those are the three things that it takes a restaurant luckily that that
they just started this semester
on that little and and will continue to be college well if they just started
we're gonna be late
white registration
the guys can probably go online and registered late for that because of
covid nineteen's covid nineteen
uh... and we just say can we say we open the restaurant
and then we go do whatever we can just come back to check in and absolutely
and other related to a rather head you know what yeah i want that we don't need
no fancy
culinary degree
or a restaurant managing soon after the kid
we just
this is a story it's just a bit of a so you guys are the rest of your guys are
the restaurant yet you guys start the restaurant in writing a matrix to where
there's like no
we can't deal with your being billed like minecraft right yet for a bit like
minecraft minecraft okay i'd build in all dirt restaurant yet you've got an
altering restaurant minds are as hot soda
and and call hot dog have it all for a little bit of a mustard it's our first
customer
uh... shit solvent uh...
though it's all of it
you are a very good
one of those paper chef hats because I'm just a big fan of Sullivan the frog
that's all I am oh what's your name so we can write it down on your burger
we got your hot dog so I can write your name with mustard on the hot dog my name
is Gary C enterprise Gary C by the way compliments to your parents on naming
you what can we get you today at cold dogs and hot soda are those so it's
exactly what the name is so one of each in that case all right what kind of soda
would you like I just want to let you know there is a shortage on dr. pepper
right now right okay well good well then then I'll have I'll have a in W a W
group here is a and w a dot a w root beer comes where we're all out of time
here okay yeah we only have a okay I'll just have the aid root beer then is that
all right here it is yeah it's boiling hot it burns his hands yeah I'm gonna
roll a Constitution saving throw for this guy see how he does Gary C got a crit 20
he loves it he loves hot yeah i thought i had so that all my god i think there is
this to make money
we use this to make more money on the side of the only how much he's enjoying
this right now
gary yeah you here's my proposition
are you are the number one fan of the restaurant so far correct
yeah it's i like a pretty good
how would you feel
about taking over the family business
uh... role persuasion check
if you say yes or give you free cold dogs for life also
located here within the image
sold on with advantage to the a_b_c_'s helping you
twenty one did nice yes
he's like i got a finesse going on high didn't couldn't even come up with a
different character voice
and all right gary
Welcome to your kingdom. You're going to watch over this restaurant while we are gone. Okay, if you say so
And then here's the keys to a new Porsche
Yeah, he's like, I mean, I know these can be just generated. So it's and here's two keys to that Porsche now
We're talking and there we go. I got a spare. It's the new Porsche dual ignition system
You have to turn it at the same time like starting a nuclear attack
that
are
Remember, the soda is hot, the hot dogs are cold.
I know it can be confusing.
Yeah, it's just because it's the opposite.
And let me tell you something, if this thing goes under,
I'm coming to your house and I'm going to break your kneecaps.
I will kill you.
It's not a joke.
You understand.
You have no idea what you've gotten yourself into.
Oh my god.
You have just made the worst mistake of your entire life.
But you already said yes.
Treating me exactly like the character I sound like.
Oh god.
that's right here and come here get closer so he's been on your face
okay very far yes sir
yeah I'll hold it
I'll yeah right I'm a powerful to the
correct I'm this yeah getting him I hit the
I hit the stove so you guys go to the soy lake
yeah as as we leave as we leave the restaurant turn and say
we could be back at any time this literally any moment
you better be here
you cannot leave
this restaurant
dude, patches, this map is so good
you're the master
Soylake, the virtual waters of the matrix 2 are ever-changing, shifting with
code pushes
and perverted user content with the exception of a few major landmarks
Goatsy Cave, Knockout Game Highway, Little St. Homestuck
are just a few of these famous locations in the matrix 2
sponsored by team vote
but few have as much traffic is so i like
upon the nineteen side of the twenty sided world
the lake is white as lotion which i couldn't
finance that's for but that was the best i could
with almost the same consistency
but the virtual allows for wonderful things on the two of by by team votes
corporate rules sponsored by h_n_r_ block
as you arrive at the lake the faded blue virtual road you're walking on digitizes
into a sandy beach
filled with citizens previously obscured from view people of all shapes sizes and
species are playing in the water lying in it
eating some of it
you see families enjoying the synthetic lakeside breeze young men and women
chatting and waiting in the water some are sorry and twilight's playing
volleyball and a couple of massive she's throwing a regulation to matrix to
softball back and forth
couples are clipping through one another as they try to embrace and a group of
old men dressed as sonnets you are fishing
pull up epic means is screaming pockets at full volume
you also see the massive east is so in the heads with their bushy beards will
be parker rims and perpetually open mouths spilling the white lotion into
the lake
it's a beautiful site the behold
and uh...
everyone uh... role the
perception check
i got cheated
on the i got a crit one by the i said disadvantage on rules are
No, just on just on dexterity saving. Okay, so you're gonna get 22 nice, okay
19 so
Blotas you you don't notice because you're -
You're having too much of a sensory overload right now. Yeah from all all the different
In the ocean. I blink and my eyes get stuck closed and I go. Oh my god guys the matrix shut off
We have to get out of here and I'm right in circles
so i don't know what he it's okay the ocean where you're from is always frozen
it's been who built always frozen
you're both does you just died
don't tell me that i did you're dead tell me
uh...
i was a little bit that for his screaming
you too
uh... patrick yoda and every william johnson
he's written it
that all the people at the lake leaks the
kind of in pockets
turn their heads towards you.
Not like, whatever it is, could be their heads, right?
And not all at once, but every once in a while.
And they have this blank, vacant stare as they do it.
And both of you guys actually, roll a history check.
- Finally.
- Yeah.
- I've been waiting so many weeks for this.
- For the history check.
Nice, okay.
- Dude, 24.
Yeah, um, uh, yeah, Patrick Yoda, this, this, this all doesn't,
this all feels kind of new to you.
The way that they're looking at you, the way that they're.
Motioning towards you, Ray William Johnson, you start to sort of, as you, as you see
how obviously they're sort of looking at you all with their vacant, strange stairs,
you start to recall that as you've been walking through to matrix too, you've
noticed that actually quite a bit that people seem to just turn their heads
towards you three, stare, and then just go back
to what they're doing.
And you also start to notice that some of them
walk towards you a bit, cock first, and then just stare.
And then they almost like snap out of it out of nowhere
and go back to doing what they're doing.
- It's the cockulous riff, dude.
- I think, I think I might be a celebrity.
(laughing)
I think i may be famous wow.
So this is what it's like.
What do we do now boys?
Well you can look a bit further down and see that there is the house that is carol baskins house.
You can obviously tell because it is completely painted in tiger stripes.
Well we gotta go there.
Let's go kill that woman.
Yeah, so I think you guys anyone first you can do every one big
There's a big map set up here with a bunch of different guys on it. Can we come back?
Yeah, maybe what we'll say
Is that the coca-cola polar bear?
Yes, that is the coca-cola polar bear and we talk to him. What's up? I'm also a celebrity nice to meet you
Oh god, it's hard walking out in public. Uh
Yeah, the polar bear turns to you and says
All right, buddy, I'm gonna be honest. I was not ready for that voice. I'm gonna leave this conversation
It's just my avatar who says I'm the coca-cola polar bear. That's fine. That's fine your voice
Fucking terrible man. You gotta do something about that. I'm trying I'm going to vocal lessons
Yeah, how much you pay for one of those you can sign saying it myself like
Yeah, let's let's hear you sing. What do you guys want to hear? I want to rap God rap God
I'm
is
have to keep going you know why? Because you're going to Hollywood. Roll a deception check.
Okay. 23. I'm so good dude my rolls have all been above 23. He 100% believes he's going
to Hollywood. You're going to Hollywood straight down the crane. I'm giving you the golden
buzzer. Where should I go? How do I do it? Hollywood listen. It's under the lake. Yeah.
he
like about 20 more people on this beach.
I think we might clean up nice today, boys.
- Okay, yeah, so you guys,
you guys wanna do that to somebody else?
You guys wanna talk to somebody else?
- So I see on this map,
there are two spiders around a campfire.
- Yeah, and there's one in the ocean.
- Can we talk to the spiders?
- Yeah, sure, go talk to the spiders.
- Okay, my rolls have been great,
so let me try this first.
- I'll move you guys over here.
- All right. - Thank you.
- You ready? - Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
- Hey, what's up?
- Yo, man, what's going on, dude?
you're going to hollywood
uh... for all the sections that that's what's going on here and they've got
uh...
the l_p_f_
you have a good idea of their failed
dot com
what you have a huge booger on your nose and i think i saw it touch the mike
i don't have a booger on my nose to i'd just saw it
it's not on my nose
some i handed it
i thought i was being recorded so we'll we'll check nobody nobody will ever see that
and i don't have a bugger on my nose
and uh... one of them says
who i don't
what's up dude i don't think i'm just a spider man hollywood california ever heard of it
it's in the ocean go check it out
i'm not
no i saw what you guys did to that polar bear i've been hanging back
uh...
and i'm like not part of the two of them and i walk up and i'm like
Oh, hey, I don't know you guys.
Uh, hey, spiders, you're going to Broadway.
[laughter]
New York City.
What are you-- don't talk to me, I don't know you.
What? Me, the spider?
No, I don't know this weird robot demon guy.
I just thought you guys look like you're gonna be on Broadway.
What? You mean the guy who looks like Jack Black here?
What's up?
Which we established, I guess, last session?
Yeah, Jack Black, the computer demon.
What about this are you not understanding?
*laughter*
Look man, I just came here to chill with my spider bros
and just smoke some loud, okay?
I don't know what you guys are on about.
Alright, well-
Alright, forget this! We're not gonna get them to drown themselves in the ocean!
We'll leave you alone, spiders.
But I ask you this.
Do you know of anybody on this beach who is extremely gullible?
Hmm, so the spider starts looking around with all the question I have a question. What's up?
Have you seen the spider that hides from gay people
*snickers*
no
*screams*
*laughter*
oh my god
wait hold on
if i were you
i would kill myself by running into the ocean
i would jump in the ocean and stop breathing
he does he does
i made these NPCs
so you could kill them all
what's the deal
I see in the on this map in the middle of the ocean there's a giant dragon and also a giant
worm.
Yeah, those are just people hanging out.
I yell from shore, "What up, worm?"
The worm swims over and he says, "Hey man."
"Hey man, you should go on land."
Okay, and he just does.
Oh, shit.
Oh, no.
all right i guess you are never going to hollywood he starts doing
and some out
and he's just like uh...
i turned out the other two and i say guys i do
what are you guys up to?
i'm trying to talk to my friends what are you guys up to? and you go back in the ocean?
if you must know we're trying to kill as many people on this beach as possible
okay sounds cool
wait hold on i got an idea
what's up? what are you guys up to? do you have like a saddle on your back?
or something like that?
i can make one
you know that's part can you make three
yeah i can make three titles are right i've got a great idea you guys to
everyone join my server
i have a answer yeah let's do it
well it's like
we guys want to go first of lately well we were planning on going to
freakin carol baskins house
but as of the house that's up there
yeah i don't know how much it takes us for a ride up there and you've been
okay yeah you've been doing more faster
yes sir i guess so
well let's let's do it
okay so you guys and all right so yeah you guys get on this uh...
visitors
you guys get on this words back
yes yes
pocket is a very warm heavy campaign yeah i'd i'd did not realize it was going to
be uh... you guys go up to
freaking carol baskins abode
uh...
so
let's do this shit world
well
out here
a were released
thanks for your hangout for a little bit
yes sir dick and i can just tell you
yet dude
yeah i think you'll hear that or
okay
we have to investigate some stuff you guys are cool
thanks benjamin and i think you know i think or a worm
today
man i can't get anything out of this is not the
so you guys walk into carol baskins place
uh...
and uh... freaking carol baskins ranch style home
looks like a rejected boogie nights location
covered head-to-toe in gaudy seventies decor and tiger stripes covering every
surface it strains the eyes to get a sense of where the floor begins in the
walls and
the other thing about freaking carol baskins ranch style home is
carol baskins freaking dead
You see the unmistakable visage of the glassy-eyed psycho laying dead in a pool of her own blood.
The stench is bearable.
Must have only been a couple days.
You see some choice bite marks as well, meaning her tigers have perhaps been well-fed during
this time.
There goes your contact.
Oh my god, husband's revenge!
Wait, she was our contact?
I thought we were supposed to come kill her.
Was I just not paying attention?
Yeah, I think so.
Alright, that makes sense.
I don't know how to clear that up.
Shit.
You guys have full access to Carole Baskin's vast home.
I'm a tea bagger.
Yeah, you tea bagger?
Yeah, a little bit of BM.
Yeah, you tea bag her. That happens for sure.
Describe it to me.
You're Jack Black.
I'm Jack Black.
Tea bagging dead Carole Baskin.
Yeah, I tea bag her and I use her like Mr. Krabs uses the big dollar.
all
little dark in here so i turn on the oven to make it
uh... i'm
since i had inside and looking around for clues okay i i i have an idea it
would not go ahead
obviously you enroll in investigation check
sure yeah
uh...
pull this up
seventeen
and will resolve and second k
uh... i have
they have an idea i uh...
well we need a figure it is a book active crime scene we need to figure out
out some clues we have funds and looms
here i'll try
i'll trace smelling the body
which i get a pro-conservative person if
here all i guess
a perception check for that
okay
perception but i get
reasons and it's okay so that's pretty
the other side it would be a lot of us
you still a lot like my dick in my balls and
that's all you get out of that
uh... i'd like to let me try
yet
i wrote the fourteen
okay yeah
so you smell something other than her dick interval his dick is ballerina
so it may be said that there are
is taking balls
and uh...
You smell, obviously, the smell of, you know, some sort of awful musk that that real-life woman probably has
from just hanging out with tigers all day.
But you also smell that... you also smell, I would say, with your extra-sensitive Yoda nose.
There isn't... she hasn't been, like, visited by anybody.
Or rather it hasn't been anybody outside of here
Okay, the killer is in the house and also Cameron with that 17
As you're looking. Oh, sorry with the Yoda nose. I also smelled the Gats in the oven is getting really bad
Yeah blow toss is just like his eyes are just bloodshot he's just like
(laughing)
- Head just in the oven, just.
But with that 17 investigation in the kitchen,
you do sort of see behind the oven,
you like take your head out for a second
and you look behind the oven
and you see a series of ledgers tucked away,
of cyber ledgers for past businesses
that are tucked away in there.
Okay, I turn off the oven.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, good.
Yeah.
Well, I already looked inside the oven for long enough,
so I think it's okay to turn it off.
And I turn it off, and then I just fall over
and chip my tooth on the table.
Yeah, great.
And then I pick up the ledgers,
and I walk back to Patrick and Ray William Johnson.
Yeah.
Hey, guys, I found it.
What happened to your eyebrows?
Uh, yeah, yeah.
They're gone! It smells like fucking burnt hair in here!
You have, do you have alopecia?
What, did you just lose all your hair going through here? What's going on?
I was hanging out in the kitchen.
What did you do in there?
I was looking around.
Did you do something with the oven?
What's in your hand?
No!
I smell oven!
You know I can smell things!
I turned on the light, that's it.
Everyone perception check
Ted
All right, Patrick Yoda notices that the worm is gone
No house dust. Oh
Crap, where'd he go?
I'm right here. No the worm where the worm go. He's pretty good. Investigation worm is gone. Thank you
Do an investigation? Oh
Okay. Yeah, you go over to where the worm was and you notice a struggle. Oh
the
that
yes
the
That's right. 19, dude.
Okay. So, Ray William Johnson, you at the sort of site of that struggle, realizing that that happened, you wander a bit more through, and you end up in the living room over here.
And what you start to see is what looks to be a iPad of some sort.
And it has no password on it.
And you're able to open it and see a few messages on it as well.
You realize that this is freaking Carole Baskin's iPad.
Yeah, so you can definitely check the history.
I'm going to scroll through the messages for a minute.
Yeah, you scroll through.
So you start to see that she had like a pretty hefty correspondence with a number of people that you guys kind of know.
One of them is a good old mommy, good legs, which makes sense.
She was her contact.
you see that they had a sort of a back and forth sort of complaining about
Papi Chuko and it seems like that they might have both owed him some sort of
money or something at some point and then it just sort of ends with her
saying mommy saying we'll talk but not here XO mommy and that correspondence
and
Jeff Tiedrich? No, you guys let him out. You see that they were probably, they looked like
they were kind of lovers at some point and also kind of colleagues. Like they kind of
would try to basically having a group DM to workshop posts kind of thing. And also you
see that at some point he was asking her insistently to send her tigers after the Sucklo's drug
Runners, which is kind of consistent with what the sucka was saying
But that she was kind of refused she was not interested and the last message from him was I
Know Carol that you're being a bit difficult, but we have a fucking tiny brain freak running his techno slam garbage across my realm
Yes, my wrong fuck face. Sorry. We need a bigger piece of the pie for us
What kind of psycho ass fucker shit do you have to be to not get that?
Whatever China if you're listening, let's get freaking Carol on board with the plan and that was sent like two months ago. I've had nothing
You also scroll a bit further down and you see a correspondence between her and Haseki tsune
It seems that they were like pretty good friends
And then it seems like there's a falling out at some point and they're kind of talking around
What seems to be maybe an affair between Ma between them?
Carol and freaking Carol and Sean and it kind of ends with Hussie the last thing she said
OMG Carol you're being so annoying RN literally done with you and him for good can't believe you do this to me
lol, I'm going to deal with this myself literally by
Then it ends
and that's kind of all the messages you could see that she has.
Actually, you know what? Roll another investigation check.
Okay.
19 again.
You can see that she has in her contacts, she also has Papi Chuko,
and she also has Sean McElwee.
But all the conversations for both of them are deleted.
I have an idea.
I've been reading over...
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Before you do anything.
Mm-hmm.
Caleb...
Ray, plug your USB penis into the lightning dock.
But I just have Jack Black's penis. By the way, Jack, nice.
[laughter]
Crap!
I've been reading these messages over Ray William Johnson's shoulder
and he only notices it because a giant splatter of drool falls onto the screen of the iPad.
I'm gonna text Sean.
Do it.
I'm gonna message Sean you text Sean. So what do you say pretend to be Carol say something sexy?
sub
sub sexy
That I message blue bubble sends
But you have like it's a red the red exclamation point with the circle around it. Oh
No, that was my only idea I
I have an idea.
We prank call him.
No.
Oh, okay.
Well now I forget my idea.
I think your idea was to prank call him.
Well I was gonna
borrow the iPad and go to the bathroom.
No, come on man.
No.
By the way,
you just reminded me I do have to go to the bathroom here I'll just bring the
iPad with me I'll see you guys later no way you go to the bathroom I draw a nice
hot bath okay yeah you just the only bathroom item I had so in my inventory
my inventory of assets hey Patrick Yoda do you want to smoke some techno slime
while we wait to clear our heads. You do. Patrick and I smoke techno slime. I don't know. Yeah,
you will. You do. I don't know. I'm not feeling too well tonight. I just need- I shove it into
Patrick's mouth. Okay, both of you roll constitution saving throws though. For techno slime. I got 18.
Nice.
Oh.
Wait, did I?
Did I?
I didn't do constitution save.
Yeah, alright, fine.
Reroll it.
Oh, you got three of them.
We got four.
Alright, so, looking at the Techno Slime addiction system, you're good to go, Cameron.
Alright, so I just refill?
You refill five Techno Slime points.
Oh, five?
For one pint, yeah.
Okay.
Uh, Patrick Yoda, um, this is your first failure, so you only get three.
Uh-huh.
You have disadvantage on the deck rolls for the next in-game 10 minutes.
- Shit. - So, just for the next 10 minutes.
So while you guys are chiefing a sweet techno slime,
and William Johnson is, as Jack Black, is, I guess, splashing in the tub,
I need you two boys who are outside the role of Perception Check.
- 18. - Nice.
Okay, Patrick Yoda, you hear like, sort of, some sort of scratching going on in the bedroom.
Some sort of scratching and like scuffing noise.
Oh.
Oh, no.
I don't know if it's just the techno slime right now, but I'm hearing some shit in the
bedroom.
Let's go.
What?
No, no, no, no.
I
You try to grab him by the scruff of his neck and he...
-uh, shakes you off. -I do a tuck and roll.
Yeah, yeah, you roll.
-Alright, fine. -I have a plan!
I have a plan!
What's the plan?
I'm gonna knock on the door.
No.
No, trust me. I'm gonna knock on the door and see if there's an ask.
-Can I peek under-- -If anyone's in there.
Can I peek under the door?
-Is it closed? -Yeah, you can peek.
-No, yeah, it's closed. -Hold on, I've got a better idea.
Will you shut up?
And I hit the-- I hit console commands.
Okay, and then what happens? I want you to describe it.
I do the console command, I do a wall, I do wireframe mode, I type in the wireframe code,
and now I can see the whole house in wireframe.
Okay, it doesn't work. What you just described doesn't work.
That's the worst thing I've ever done as a DM, but I did it. I finally did it. I finally just said no.
I'm sorry, you're not making any goddamn sense.
I peek under the door to try and see what's going on in there.
Okay, yeah, roll a...
Stealth? I mean, yeah, stealth first of all, because if you're trying to peek, that's a good call.
And then I guess an investigation?
Alright. Insight. My stealth is 20.
Alright, yeah, and then just roll an insight check. I guess I'm just trying to get insight
to what's going on there.
- Crap. - Ooh.
- Holy shit, wow, okay.
Let me just, one second.
- Yes.
- Unless they-- - I'm about to solve
the mystery, guys.
- Yeah, so you are going under and look under the door
and you don't see anything at first,
but then you catch a glimpse of a shadow.
And as you sort of move your who ass head over,
you notice that it looks like
strange looking tiger
uh... is sort of like
white as a ghost
in the corner scared out of its mind
uh...
okay i
you should talk to him
yeah with that insight check to you with the crit you can tell you doesn't seem
to be
any threat to you you can size them up pretty quickly i i open the door very
slowly and I go hey we're not gonna hurt you we're not gonna hurt you I promise
please please I didn't do anything please I just thought it was okay it's
okay I only took a nibble of her she was already dead I think it's okay I did too
it's okay oh really why does it look like that oh god yeah it's this hearing
hearing this raucous outside I yeah you're already my scrubbing down tell me
What's going on?
You're scrubbing down.
Well, I was playing with my ding and using the iPad.
So I'm going to get out of the bath.
I'm going to dry off and I'm going to head outside.
I put a chair under the doorknob so Caleb can't get out of the bathroom.
No, you haven't done that yet.
I did that already.
No.
I'm out.
I'm in the bedroom.
He's in the bedroom.
You guys are in the bedroom and you see this funny looking tiger.
He's looking real scared.
He's like, "Please, please!"
please please like
he's like shivering
calm down and tell us what happened
*gibberish*
that, okay that's not helpful at all
just got it, got it, see you later
*laughter*
who, who are you three?
uh, we're
your worst nightmare
*laughter*
oh man, roll an intonation check
are
My name's uh, my name's Tigger. Um, I'm here what?
No, you're not gonna do that
Well, I already made a pact with myself that no one was gonna do that this session
My name's Tigger, um
and I I am I I was a freaking carol's assistant, but um,
um, since she's uh, uh,
Been dead. I've I've been I've been hiding
Tell us what happened here.
Well, I was just cutting up those cucumber slices for her, like she likes, and if I get it wrong, she hits me.
So I was trying to make sure I got it right, and then I went to go bring it out to her, and I said, "Oh, freaking Carol!"
And then I go into the lobby, and there's blood everywhere, and she's dead, and there's a slash across her neck.
and oh that's then I I just I I panicked and I took a bite out of her and I ran
away in here and I've been in here ever since
wait freaking Carol Baskins is dead this place really is much all of my imagined
This place really is heaven.
What?
This place really is a dream.
This place really is the hall of my imagination.
What does that mean, dude?
This really is the hall of my imagination.
No.
Wow, this really is the hall of my imagination.
Do you think this was called the hall of imagination?
What the fuck are you talking about, dude?
what
okay to your listen up
and listen good
is there anybody
that you can think of
that may have wanted carol dead
all of these uh...
uh...
and he starts a bank
uh... he says
well
uh... well
towards the end of the carolers
sort of uh... police from i can tell you shouldn't
cuny on everything but uh...
she's trying to help uh...
mommy was something i i didn't know what it was and
mentor
we were working together on
uh... mean but i i i don't know how they well i guess just the bridge didn't
really like a very much after she refused and uh...
uh... i'll see i guess with mad to wind and so he did it
uh... who
I forget.
Oh God, there's so much.
Why is the floor the same as the wall?
Patrick Yoda, go get in the bath.
I forgot to drain it.
You might want to hold your nose.
The iPad's in there.
I left it on your favorite page.
Oh, great.
Patrick Yoda goes into the bath.
What's your favorite page, Patrick Yoda?
I just go through the photos app to try and find something.
Okay, yeah.
You do that.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
page
so
you ever see a man by the name of sean mcgill we around the house
all my gosh on the a_b_c_ used to be here all the time
they were shagging and i have to wipe everything up that was my job
uh... when was the last time that you had to wipe everything up
well let me think probably about two months ago
shall was always here
he was always talking about
uh... her relationship with copy was always trying to get more information and
i think she really loved them but i mean i hope it makes on the cali's
he's like the most popular guy in gun city
of course i am
ice cream from the bathroom because i found a video of shots in the mood
and carol baskets having sex
yeah you just hear like carol baskins like deadpan for
uh...
going yes shaw and uh... yeah uh... they're like glassy eyes no expression
with back
yeah she says he says that yet turn the over now shot it's not any clearer
the whole it's time to which
her head stays in the same place
yeah it's not clear
uh...
okay one one more question
do you have any
any idea why the people in this
in the matrix to
might be pointing their penises at me
i think it's maybe cuz i'm a celebrity so i wanted to know if you've heard of me
maybe do i look very familiar to you
at this uh...
uh...
triggers face
kind of contorts for a second and he looks at you
uh...
and all of sudden he looks
really really fucking scared
uh...
and he starts stammering again.
He was just starting to calm down.
Now he's like, "I know who you three are.
I know who you three are.
Oh God, oh God, get away, get away from me, get away."
- We're not Alvin and the Chipmunks.
He's not Alvin and the Chipmunks, okay?
(laughing)
You get that all the time, but it's completely different.
- I know there's three of us,
but we're not Alvin and the Chipmunks.
- We all dress in different colors.
there's a tall one, and there's a fat one.
- Of course I'd be Alvin.
- Alvin!
(laughing)
- And roll, okay yeah, not roll anything actually.
- I scream Alvin from the bathroom.
- You guys get a ding on,
you get a little ring on your PSPs,
and it's Sullivan the frog, who's calling you right now.
- 'Sup bro?
- Yeah, and as you guys pick up the phone,
or whoever does, you hear a lot of fucking background noise,
like a huge fight.
Like your crashes and bangs,
gunshots, lasers.
And you hear Sullivan sort of trying to cut through it.
Hey, guys, sorry to bother you,
but it seems like the suckers den is getting raided.
I don't know what's going on.
You're like another crash sound.
Turn that movie down, Sullivan.
Yeah, we can barely hear what you're saying, man.
"Ahh, it's on the move, you guys! It's real life!"
"Ahh, the pig is dead! I can't come in to see you guys!"
Serves him right.
And, uh, you see that the tig- the pigger is getting, like, more and more scared.
Uh, and then, all of a sudden, you hear Solvin, um, you hear a huge crash on the other line.
And you hear Solvin go, "AHH!" And you hear, um, a thump.
And then you hear some muffled voices over the phone.
Roll an insight check, Caleb, to see if you can hear it.
It seems like you're the one who answered the call.
- I've been so good with my checks.
- You're drinking it.
- Yeah, I can.
- It's not bad.
You can kind of make out some of the voices.
You can make out Sullivan whimpering softly,
like he's in a lot of pain.
And it's hard to tell though,
because meanwhile the the tigress is also freaking out the same time it's just like oh god get
away from me it's like this all this crazy shit and uh you hear a voice you think you
recognize on the other end of that but you can't quite make it out can i use my yoda
ears uh i'll have you roll roll it roll it inside because you have yoda ears and we kind
of established that early on nice that first one yeah yeah 19 you got the first one let's
the
bag the frog bag the frog and you hear then you hear a voice that you definitely recognize
um and it's uh it goes well you could just finish him off at this point it's poppy chuko oh my god
and then you hear some breathing on the other line you hear solvin crying in pain and then you hear
it hangs up and now all of you roll a um actually wait let's confirm where is everybody right now
No.
Oh, where is everybody?
I and Patrick are in the living room or the bedroom.
No, that's me.
Oh, you mean the camera?
Me and Blutos are in the.
And in what way are you?
Are you a lie? Are you?
This is where you guys are standing.
Yeah, I'm standing in the doorway and I'm still in the.
Caleb's hugging and kissing.
Take her. OK.
All right. I'm right there.
I'm like one step past Blutos at the doorway.
And this is definitely where you guys are.
And then and this is where you are Patrick Yoda.
Are you are you running out of the tub scared?
I'm dunking my own head in the tub.
Okay, cool.
Okay.
You see the call hangs up and then that exact when you hear
Papi Chuka's voice and in that exact same moment,
you guys hear a squish and your heads whip towards Tigger and
and you see a
and sticking out of the skull
and all allies my gosh when you realize his whimpering stopped
and he slumps over
and all you guys role a perception check
i never found out what i was famous war
eight months that's performance uh...
perception six fuck i got a twenty five perception
Um, ooh, actually roll again with disadvantage just because you're all the way in the other room.
Me?
I just realized. Yeah, because I just-
Fuck.
What's about to happen?
23.
Damn. Nice, dude.
Whoa.
Okay.
Um...
So...
Wow, that's pretty impressive.
So with your extra perceptive Yoda ears,
you are able to make out
something lurking in the distance that then
fucking crashes right the fuck into the bedroom.
Somehow, Patrick Yoda was able to pick up on it.
And you see a sweaty, one-eyed, ink and dirt blotted, hulking freak of a man, with sinister,
curly black hair.
His devilish pointed teeth peek from beneath a mouth too wide for his strange knotted swirling
head.
His hulking body dawns a reflector vest.
His legs are bare, completely black, and his toes are talons.
His eyes glare mockingly at all of you.
He looks like he might draw something really fucking edgy right now, like cow and chicken,
but one of them has a fucked up eye, and the other one is so crazy that he might hop right
out of the drawing and just like fucking kill you.
and the figure just looks directly at all of you.
And he says, "I told Poppy you lot were no good.
"Now I can finally finish you off.
"Here comes my dirt and ink!"
And everyone roll for initiative.
- Oh my God, you put Kai in the game.
(laughing)
That's so funny.
- This is going to be a little DM secret.
This is gonna be your toughest fight by far.
Wait, we should all probably just say our initiatives. Yeah, I got a six. Yes. I got a nine
I got a 31 you got a 10 you had you got a 10
10 and Kai
Unfortunately, the killer Kai Klops goes first. So no
All right. Let's do this. So
Oh boy, this is gonna be kind of kooky. Okay
All right, cool. So because I guess because yeah, this is gonna be he's fucking all those noises make me really worry
Yeah, okay. So Kai burst through the window after just obliterating Tigger
And he runs
He sort of like tries to sidestep you
Ray William Johnson and he takes out his his massive
Landscaping shovel and he makes an attack on you. Let's see how he does. Oh, yeah, that beats your AC for sure
fuck
no, and
Dude, I'm gonna be dead in one hit
Yeah, I think I only have like 21 HP right now. Okay roll a also roll a strength saving throw right now
Oh, dude, it's I got it
Seven
That rocks, okay cool. So here's what happens
Hi, one second Patrick don't eat into the mic
The last episode we edited you ate chips through the whole intro and it was insanely loud
Stop eating. Okay, terrible. I can't believe I just caught you doing that. Stop eating for the rest of the episode
No, don't take a dinner. I don't care. You should have eaten dinner. That's not our fault
Okay, well that's your now you have to do now you have to deal with the consequences don't take another bite of french fries
I'm saving a punch for you when I see you on Friday
I'm literally charging up a Falcon punch and when I see you I'm gonna punch you in the face
Don't put another goddamn fry in your big mouth
Say yes, sir
So, here's what happens.
Kai sidesteps over, catching you off guard, Great William Johnson.
He goes like, "YEAH!"
And he whacks you in the fucking head with a shovel.
Dealing 12 damage to you.
And then, as you're falling over, just as quickly, he whips around the shovel, fucking
like Ip Man style, and scoops you up and tosses you.
like he would toss fucking dirt. And he tosses you over his shoulder out the fucking window.
What the fuck, no. No, dude.
And I use my reverse time ability. And I go back in time.
And you take another five points of falling damage as he fucking knocks your ass out.
Dude, I have three HP. Can somebody help me out?
And you're not prone as well. Now at this point by the way, you look over and you
look in the tree and you see that the worm just is like pinned to a fucking
tree with like ten ink pens inside of it. And you get a buzz now in your
pocket, your Jack Black pocket, and it's a PSP buzz and you see a text that says
go to the basement and Carol's from that from that mysterious non number that
you saw before and it says go to the return pods underneath Carol's home and
that's all it says and now it is Patrick Yoda's turn okay hmm how tall is Kai
I
Let's take a look at this ruler, handy dandy ruler tool.
You're 45 feet away from me.
Okay, wait, hold on.
If I'm 45 feet away.
You have 30 feet of movement.
30 feet of movement.
So you have- Hold on, hold on.
Let me reconsider my move.
Peace for Yoda, peace for all.
You're going to do it?
Yeah.
All right.
That's a good move.
Okay.
So this is a very broken ability that Patrick Yoda smartly took.
Patrick Patrick smartly took.
Here, I put it in the chat now.
So what it is, is, "Peace for Yoda, peace for all.
Patrick Yoda creates a realm of mental stability,
instantly calming any conflict he is in for ten minutes.
This means a fight can be stopped and turned into a conversation.
Not everyone will be friends, but everyone will refrain from violence
until the peace subsides. You can use this ability once per long rest.
So, what... oh shit, yes, what you'll have to do is you'll have to roll a resistance to that.
Let's see if he can resist it.
Okay, it's +2, alright. You might be able to...
Where's your DC? No, no, Patrick Gunn might pull this off.
I'm so sorry.
No!
Your DC is crazy and he still beat it. So here's what happens.
You reach inside in your counselor
Jedi ways and you find the inner ability to
cast peace and you watch it wash over this dirty
inky man and you see he starts to consider what it would be like to just
sort of hang out and play crunker with the boys and maybe just have a nice
conversation about things and then you see he starts imagining and then Eddie
like sucking each other's dicks and having like something like that or maybe
the rug rats just like biting into Timon and Pumbaa and he just gets crazy again
and you're unable to calm him down.
And I also lose 7 Techno Slime points.
Damn. I thought you were going to beat that too.
Well that would have been too easy. We like a challenge.
Yeah. We all want to die.
Sounds like everyone in the game loves a challenge.
But you still have your movement that you can do too.
you can or you can also take a I guess you have another action but you can take your
movement still okay so I can't attack him now that was like your that would've been
your attack action so that's your action so now you can do your movement I go outside
I so yeah there is guys abandon me again I I stand I stay I hide under I hide right here
under one of these crates.
Okay, um, you can't technically take a quarter-to-quarter hide action.
I hide, I crouch behind the thing, but he can still see my ears.
Yeah, so I'll say that you'll have three-fourths cover,
so that means he's gonna have disadvantage on ranged attacks against you
'cause you're hiding behind this box.
Um, and now it is RayWilliamJohnson, it's your turn.
You got fuckin' party rocked.
It's gonna take half your movement to get up,
but you still have the other half.
You have ranged attacks, too.
to
- No, you know what, I'm gonna stand and I'm gonna,
you know what?
- To note, you would all have gotten
that same message, by the way.
I was just illustrating it that he got the message
'cause it was--
- Oh, true.
- Oh, so I could have ran to the basement?
If you wanted to do that, I'm sorry if that wasn't clear.
- Or we could kill the guy.
I think we can kill him.
I think we can kill him easily.
I'm gonna use--
- You can always run, so just letting you know.
- I'm gonna use hacker mode.
- Do it, fuck yeah.
let's go to the moment at this mother fucker
it's what i would
all you got click attacker mode
okay let's take a look at that so
hacker mode
uh... cost three tickets i gotta make that cost more
uh... so you uh...
yes intelligence saving throw
he can watch your computer into him
take control of him
for up to ten minutes as crazy i have to nurse stuff i think i'm not a saving me
right now. We're gonna lose this fight if you nerf any of this stuff.
Okay and it's intelligence, what's his intelligence? Where is it? There it is, beautiful. Alright,
let's see how it goes. Alright yeah, it failed. You got it. He's too fucking strong, you made
Strong I
Pretend to be dead
Yeah, okay
Roll a
try this
Roll performance check. I'm a natural performer
Get 18 yeah, he thinks you're dead. I just rolled for him. Okay. I like my tongue out
know
a
I don't have any fancy tricks I can do.
You're explaining this to him?
I didn't do it in the voice, so I wasn't.
Use your brain next time.
I don't have any powers to fight you, but I'm going to try my best.
I use my sickum ability to throw my monkey Patrick onto Kai's face.
Which costs 2 Techno Slime points.
Mm-hmm.
Uh, "Bloodthirst Monkey grabs onto an enemy's face or face equivalent,
blinding them and dealing damage until they can shake the monkey off.
Enemy needs to beat DC 12 Dex at the end of their turn.
On a failure, the monkey causes disadvantage on attack rolls and deals 1d6 damage.
Then an additional 1d6 damage per turn, the monkey stays on the face."
Hell yeah.
So it looks like it is a Dex thing.
He's probably gonna beat it, but let's see. Maybe he won't.
He's got pretty good Dex.
let's see maybe he'll fucking fail
fingers crossed guys
the monkey you throw the monkey at him
and kai just fucking bats him away with the shovel and the monkey just
flies right back at you. you have another attack though
yeah
what should i do
are we gonna try to get to the basement
uh... i
should we try to beat him or should we try to get to the basement?
it's up to you man, I'm pretending I'm dead
where's the entrance to the basement?
yeah, where's the entrance?
yes, good question
it's right, it's under, it's a trap door right under me
it's under each of you, yeah, it's under each of you
each one of you, uh no
that's sick
the basement is, uh, the entrance to the basement, like in all homes
is right in, uh, right, where did I put it?
Oh, here, yes. It is right, uh, like here.
Oh, okay.
Oh, I can get there pretty easy.
Yeah, well, I'd have to, okay.
I guess I'll fight him for now to let
Caleb, to let Caleb get back around there.
Cause if I run away, then Caleb's fucked.
He's sacrificing himself.
I'm not sacrificing.
I would never sacrifice.
I'm sacrificing.
Listen, he doesn't want to, he's being modest.
he's sacrificing his life it's just so i want to know you because you know you'd
rather just let all your friends die so that you can do a funny marriage scene
he's sacrificing his life for another man and buddy that's us
i says pause when he realized that i just run straight to the basement i don't
know how to wait on how to get back i'll help you take it back
the event
take a look at the i don't have a good idea i read it as a i don't think that
that you know that it's just
okay
you could almost get there with the right i go almost there yeah i got right and
then i see that uh... kyle with my grinch gun
from the stage
yet do it
twenty one nice and it's role for damage
eighteen damage
no i wasn't a damaged uh... i would like to write the wrong thing sorry i was like
seven damage. That makes way more sense. I didn't know you could do 18. Still pretty good.
Yeah, you shoot the... yeah, you like start sprinting away because Ray William Johnson's
calling you gay and you shoot the Grinch gun. You didn't have to say anything in game, I could just
sense that he was thinking it. Yeah, you could just sense it. And you shoot the Grinch gun.
He set his status on the PSP discord to thinking Blowtoss Piss is gay.
*laughter*
And it pierces Kai right in like sort of the upper like collarbone zone and
He just like breathes it in like a freak like
Like madder at you and he really wants to fucking kill you now. Oh no weird, bro. Yeah, that's even more sus
Yeah, do you see my discord status?
Yeah, okay, and that's the end of your turn so it is now Kai's turn
So first I'm gonna have him do is I'm gonna have him with your performance check
We have a roll against it again to see if he notices
That you are pretending you're dead
He still doesn't notice he keeps he keeps he runs over here and
he aims a
website a certain dart for a Patrick Yoda and
the
patrick it'll it doesn't hit
was not
movement it doesn't hit
we don't know yet
we just don't know how you have a bad a cf regard does not hit regardless
outside our yes cover yes covered as i'm covered that's true he does have covered
i do have to roll with this damage
it doesn't hit
doesn't it doesn't it didn't hit it did not hit it hit so let's let's go through
a couple other things and there's a couple of things gotta happen now I need
you to roll a constitution saving throw 16 nice good okay so he slings a dart at
you and it does get you right in the neck and dealing nine points of damage to you
And you start to see the dart shake while it's inside of you and what's spewing out of the
top is another pen tip and it starts to form something like in the space and the ether
around it, but you sort of resist it.
Something inside you tells you to resist that and it just swallows back up in the pen and
the pen falls off.
So you still take the nine points, but nothing else happens.
No, I don't.
I'm gonna I will I will just make it happen. I took the nine points. I will make it happen.
Okay, thank you. So now it is your turn though. Okay.
I don't have enough to oh I can't even try Yoda's calm mind again.
How fast can I just make a run for it to the basement?
Absolutely can try okay go for it. What would I need to roll?
Nothing, you just gotta move
Yeah, so you are in
The basement. So here's what we're gonna do for that. I'm just gonna move you
Just like over here to show that you are tip right now out of range of Kai
Which is what's happening?
But you are sort of running down the stairs to the basement and as you run down you start to hear echoing
like as you're running like it's like you're kind of entering like a not just a basement but like a tunnel or a cavern of some kind and
If that's all you do it is now
Wait, can I do one more thing? Yes, absolutely
You need two more things. Oh
Okay, you can only do one more thing I'm sorry that's gonna confuse you I should have been careful with that
There's got to be
Can I have a you can I shoot at him with the needler while I'm running away?
All out. Yeah, actually bro. Just roll in athletics check to see if you can know actually no
You don't have to consider it like you're in mid movement. You do some of your movement and you shoot it go for it
That's right that hits baby, that's the 22. Yeah, nice. Yeah. So yeah, you're running away
Patrick Yoda and you do some I'm running away, but I'm just like I'm spraying the gun like yeah
And
Kai is just like a couple of the needler bolts getting to side of him and he's
Like burst him out, but he still did nine damage. It's quite good
Okay, which means he is at that I'm out of HP
Just say it. Just say the number.
I can't say it. It's illegal.
If I roll a natural 20 right now, will you say the number?
Yes. Let's do it. I'm a gambling man.
What do I get as a reward? You need to establish that.
Nothing. Yeah, alright.
I got a 2. You will never know.
You won't even know your own HP.
That's what we're doing.
But, you know what, it is Ray William Johnson's turn.
I thought it was your turn, but it didn't.
Okay, I...
So Kai thinks I'm dead.
So my plan...
You could do a stealth.
I messaged him on Discord and I said, "You should sneak."
Thank you, Mettatoss.
for messaging another man i_m_ i'm going to
trying crawl about about here
uh... is that yet that's a refit
no it's not so well here's the thing if you used to use both your movements you
can do sixty feet
okay i use both and and make it to the estimate
uh... well let's see because here's the thing to do you have to like
so imagine like okay forty here
and then like you have to walk through the house
i don't make it to the basement you can make it like a rat like here
uh... wait sorry like here
and you can't stop the role stealth
and again do it at stealth remember
eleven follow yeah so
you do make it there
but he knows
you step on you can i can i rule another step so i don't care about it
Yeah, you step on Carol's body like 10 times.
And he was like the wet bunch of bones.
I gotta give her a little, you know...
If he sees me, can I do another performance check?
Yeah, with disadvantage though.
Okay, alright.
Alright, just I'll pretend...
Yeah, you tricked me!
I'll pretend to be dead again.
Okay.
Hold on.
Did it go?
Dude, I kinda...
Okay, I rolled...
I rolled with disadvantage.
1, 5 and 1, 23.
but
I
All right, I'm gonna shoot him twice go for it. All right. My first shot is an 11. It's not gonna do it
Alright, then my second shot is a 16
It's not gonna do it. Damn. Yeah, dude. All right. I jump I jump into the basement
Yes, you just shoot twice and Kai
Like Dodge is the first one it knocks the other one out of the way with the shovel and you're like and just yeet into
the basement as they say
uh... seer you're way out of range now
of himself so you're like an over here
down on
and now it is christ turn how does it feel
good actually like it
so i do like being alone
so he's going to use uh...
uh... no
these blocking the entrance now
he's gonna come after you re william johnson
decided yeah he slings his dart at you
way if you die in a matrix to do you die in real life
only a
uh... man
you know i feel like that
uh... that doesn't raise last and it was uh...
that doesn't have to have peace swings a dart at you and and uh...
uh... here
he uh... for some reason thinks you're dead again and just like
throws it at something else, throws it at something else,
and is like, "Wait, no."
Remembering that you're-- - He just hit it, Carol.
- Yeah, yeah. - Dead body.
- Yeah, she just, like, moves a little bit.
A bit of gas comes out. - He couldn't remember
what looking alive looks like
and what looking dead looks like,
and he mixed them up with his head. - He got very confused, yeah.
Okay, yeah, it is now Patrick Yoda's turn.
- So I'm in the basement now?
- Yeah, you're in the tunnel area in the basement.
can I use my needlers light?
shoot, wait you should shoot
Kai from below
ohhhhh
okay
if you try to shoot
if you try to like shoot him from down there
almost in like, I'll have you
um well no because you're kind of like
of
is
yeah
it
rare
Dude, this is nothing to me.
Yeah, you have some pretty badass moves, too.
Yeah, that's why I'm trying to use one.
Can I go in front of Patrick in the tunnel just so like, uh, Archie Patrick can go behind me?
There we go.
Yeah, can I move behind Cameron?
So that if Kai comes down I can tank it?
Yes, you can.
Okay, I moved myself.
Mm-hmm.
Cool. Now go. Sorry.
I use my dong blade.
You're gonna fucking charge his ass?
I'm gonna get a melee.
I jump up.
I attack him.
Fucking hell yeah dude.
Roll that.
Five.
Fuck dude.
I'm gonna die dude.
You just are like, "Uhhhhhh."
I also think Carol is who I'm fighting.
I run at her.
you
I
range
uh my duel pipes and try to hit Kai. Do it. Fifteen. It's not enough. Alright, I'm gonna
try again. Do it. Sixteen. Not enough, right? No. Yeah. Not enough. Alright. Yeah, you just
like do that and he at this point is like ignoring Ray William Johnson and you guys
are just sort of like literally like dueling shovel and duel pipes just like fucking Darth
Maul and um Qui-Gon's Jinn and you're just going off. Okay. Um. I yell, I yell, Patrick,
ahead find what's down there okay and it is now Kai's turn and he is going to
kill me if you're gay
he turns to you and he thinks for a second there you go real think about it
long time big guy wait I'm not gay that's right I'm not gay I'm not gay
Then don't kill me
Starts sucking it. Yeah, pretty gay, buddy
Yeah, he he's gonna attack you with this
Fifteen minutes thinking about that. Yeah, that's pretty good. Uh-huh
Hey, man, it might not turn out so fucking well for him. Let's find out. Oh
Yeah, he gets you. Oh
Oh boy, let's see what happens. He'll probably
He's gonna kill me did oh
fuck
I'm so afraid to die. You got very unlucky that he just jumped out and fucked you up first thing
Yeah, he fucking just like you say like like what you said, which is if you kill me or you're gay and
Chi our friend says I am gay and just hits you over the head with the shovel
And you are like seeing birds. You're knocked out cold
Holy crap. Yeah, you got some death saves coming up for you brother. Hey, dude first Patrick Yoda. It's your turn
All right, so I changed my mind shoot the needler at him more
So Patrick it what do you do by the way before for
Do I see now I don't know cuz now I'm down
So I'm halfway in between
Finding out what's down here. Oh, yeah, and then I'm depending on what you do. You're gonna kind of move into a new sort of situation
the
But if you go ahead and leave the Matrix, then we can't rescue Caleb.
Right.
He's pretty low, I'll say that much.
Didn't he say he was beaten up?
I said yeah, he's bloodied.
Dude, let's go.
Alright, you know what, I'm going up.
That means he's under half.
That's right. Very good.
I'm smart. I know the D&D words.
That's right.
He's, yeah, we can do this. You shoot him with the Needler a few more times.
Yeah, I'll do the Needler.
Do it, Pimp.
Alright.
19.
19, yeah!
I pop my head back out.
You're fucking...
I just start spray firing the Needler, but you can't see my head, so I don't know where I'm shooting.
Is this your second successful Needler attack in a row?
This is my third.
No, in a row, in a row. Oh shit, it is.
Yeah.
Oh my god, I'm sorry. You should have been doing extra damage. So let's do that now. Whoa
Wait, no, dude Patrick MVP. Yeah, so just like in real life the real needler life
when you do a
You do extra damage if you get multiple hits with the needler. So right now you're gonna do
Because it's we missed one you're doing 8d for fire damage extra right now. Okay, so just roll
Just hit the needler explosion thing needler explosion. Yeah
Ten holy shit and then hit it again
Seven Wow
Fuckin holy shit 25 damage just now. Yeah. He's Wow cuz he kept fucking hitting him right in a row, which is Wow
Yeah
This man shit Kai had so many cool abilities, but that's - that's the name of the game folks describe your kill
So I don't see what's going on
Just I'm under I'm in the tunnel and I'm just spray firing a bunch
And so so many need like I'm hitting like direct hits
This must be this must be just some of my force power, but I I don't know and I'm just sitting there and I'm like
Yeah, I don't even see my kill
the
Caleb killed himself. I mean, oh
Jesus Ray William Johnson killed him so good that he killed himself
Yeah, I must it must have been all me you can't talk. You know, he's
Let it be revived. There we go. Yeah, I basically yes like no
No in order to be revived you have to sit through a 30 minute wedding. Sorry
To come back. Sorry blowtos. Did you did you come up to like kiss me or something?
I step on his face.
Why are you talking?
No.
It just happens.
Yeah, that could have ended very... Patrick Yoda had
literally the best roles he's ever had.
And that was...
That was Patrick Yoda just on maximum power
right now. It was impressive.
It was fucking rocked. Yeah.
And the Kai...
[gurgling]
And he just like...
sort of like dies and lights on fire
explosion and he just sort of collapses in front of you. Pour one out for a real one.
Yeah. R.I.P. Kai. I take Caleb's supplies of techno slam and start pouring them on the ground.
You can't take these.
So yeah, that's the fight. You guys want to go into the tunnel?
Let's go the ladder and I fall down also, I'm too excited. I just go like well
Hey you guys kill Kai
Our friend and you walk down the stairs and you once again
Once again you find another basement layout this time it leads to way out of here
You know weeds to a way out of the matrix to the tunnel to the exit pods
As you traverse the strange crystalline tunnels, the darkness overwhelms you.
This is maybe the first time you've been without the cold comfort of those hellish lights that permeate Gun City.
You also notice as you traverse through that it's getting colder and colder, not drastically, but enough to notice.
Then you start to hear the echoes of laughter and play from above.
You see a gentle light at the very end, almost like a floor light, white and eerie.
The tunnel opens up to a vast room where that light creates an strange glow that rises up
And colors the rest of the chamber
There are dozens of pods meant for leaving the matrix - they're all shaped like Lincoln town cars and 401ks
Which if you didn't know are shaped like a pinwheel
as you look above you see young men and women and
Who's and Shreks and dragons and worms and dogs and furries and Ron Paul's?
Diving into what must be Soy Lake, but as they enter it
They merely float just above you clipping through you. They must be experiencing a different reality from you
They think they're swimming through a vast ocean of soil and motion
But they seem to be to you floating in space not aware of your existence entirely separate from you
But somehow within the same area
as you all crawl into your Lincoln town cars and your
in your 401k pinwheels
That they begin to turn you turn the car on and the spin wheel start to spin so rapidly
It's creating a gyroscopic effect. You feel your digital selves disassemble and enter into the negative space of that tubular
Transportation zone that you were in before the massive holographic Cortana greets you once again
Thank you so much for visiting to matrix to be sure to come back soon to check out husky
Tsune live in concert featuring immortal hip-hop legend and genius pedophile 69 and
Suddenly Cortana's face that's a twitch error error like from before his voice sounds like Zordon
Do you guys remember what Zordon sounds like from the power rangers? There we go
interception interception interception
interception the massive holographic
Quatana ages thousands of years and collapses onto itself. The blue tunnel that connects you to the
real world from the Matrix 2 and vice versa dissolves all around you leaving a black void
and suddenly that sensation of falling becomes all too real. You fall through the inky black space,
gravity the only thing assuring you of some connection to the physical world and then
thump you land one at a time on top of another like in a cartoon in a strange laboratory not
Not unlike the one you saw in the abandoned porno factory yesterday, a voice from behind
you calls out, "At last!
We finally meet, fellas!
Good to see you!"
Oh my goodness.
Guys, I'm so excited for this next one.
This one is going to be the eye of your life.
Patches, I think you should write a book.
Yeah, I think you should write a book.
This one is going to be the eye of your life.
Patches, I think you should write a book.
Yeah, I think you should write a book.
[MUSIC]