[MUSIC]
Last time on Gun City, the Temple of Tepanguin of Doom.
Our heroes attempted to avoid the gamers who slept in their weird apartment complex inside of the land caves by traveling along the internal river on their Mass Effect raft.
But they were far too noisy, and the nasty gamers began to do a sinister crane game,
picking up our heroes, even though Ray William Johnson did an excellent performance of being dead.
After their best attempt, they got scooped up, tossed into a terrifying dark maze of
Pac-Man variety, and became the prey of gaming. After collecting the four elements or element-like
sort of things they needed to to get out of the cave, or get out of the maze, they took a magical
Willy Wonka elevator up past where all the land parties were happening to the main control
area for the gamers who have since colonized this cave. The giant Xbox. And now they are
face to face with the great gamer, the winged gamer, who stands before them. And if you
remember the gamer said um uh would you like to play a game and uh i thought it was saw
i thought it was the saw gamer no he's just he just said that as a little not um not to
saw it's saw he's trying to fix my mic playing with your microphone did i show you guys i
got this what is that is that jimmy carter oh it's donald trump and my pants trumpets
is
this
Caleb, you get one thing to add.
These two?
Nope, one thing per game.
One thing per round.
I don't have...
This is a good mechanic.
I don't have anything in my room.
You don't have anything in your room?
Nope.
You can add this to your inventory.
I add that empty jewel pod to my inventory.
So you add Patrick's empty jewel pod to your inventory.
Thanks for the spot, Pat.
You're welcome.
know
Then Sullivan will take the empty jewel pod.
So yeah, the winged gamer beseeches you, you know, says "Would you like to play a game?"
And he sort of, you see the little gamer who is, you know, sort of going
[gibberish]
Sort of like looking towards the four of you, gesturing towards him.
And Patrick Yoda, you'd be able to understand what the little gamer is essentially saying
is "Play the game and you'll get the prize."
Um, yeah.
What the fuck is he fucking saying?
I believe he's trying to say, "Play the game and you'll get the prize."
Oh, so you can understand him. Okay.
Yes, I can understand all my games.
So now, now I don't have to be the one that he talks to.
Yeah, you can just like come around with us after whatever happens between us here in a minute.
You can just like come with us so we can understand this game.
Yeah, but you can understand.
We'll pay you.
Well, the little gamer here, like, would you say pay me?
Yep, that's what I said.
Do you have any interest in an iPod Touch?
Do you accept negative money?
I don't accept negative money, but an iPod...
It's a huge hit up on the surface.
An iPod Touch is a pretty rare relic.
Okay, wait, hold on.
We don't have one.
Okay.
I do have a...
I have $100.
I mean, look, I'll take your money to help you if you need, but the little gamer here, he's not going to be traveling with you any longer.
And he sort of, he sort of like goes like in like the little gamer sort of scurries up to him and the wing gamer gives him like sort of like there's like a little like up, up like with a dog with food, but it's like with a Game Boy advanced and eventually he drops it and the little gamer grabs it and scurries away.
away. I say before the little gamer leaves I say, "I hate you too." Which means, you
know man, I mean I've only known you a couple minutes in this game but you feel
like it feels like you're a real best friend to me and I was sad to see you go
but you know I know that we'll always be friends and I always understood
everything you were talking about. He looks at you and he goes "WAAA" which means F-Zero
for the GBA and he just looks back down. And he just goes back to playing. Alright so Wing
Gamer it seems like maybe we figured this whole thing out, like maybe you can let us
into the next room or if only well first of all this is the last room okay the next level
like okay a little bit maybe if this is the last level we could go to the next world maybe
like world two level one yeah like the desert one because this is like
what map oh yeah map yeah we could get another map yeah maybe he's a multiplayer gamer fellas
You don't need to do anything of the sort.
Please, approach my machine."
And he gestures back to his, like, giant, like, game console PC thing.
He says, "This is called the Void.
We were going to enter it, after which we will play a game.
And if you defeat me, you will receive a gift from the temple.
Something left by the Tamagotchi people.
It was once told that true gamers would come
And seek out a relic and help the world.
Perhaps something related to, I don't know, the gamer word itself.
So, I have to obey this prophecy as you four have defeated Gaben.
Please, come forth, enter the void.
I'd dive in.
Okay.
Can I take a bite of that cosmic brownie first?
All the cosmic brownies here are yours to have.
Alright, then I'll just wait until I come back.
Yeah, I stuffed my pot.
We'll share, you know, don't...
You don't get any.
Don't what? No way.
Yeah, we're gamers.
We're gonna play this damn game.
How about you just give us the...
How about you just give us the relic and then we can sit here and eat cosmic brownies until the timer runs out.
I am unable to get the relic. The relic is inside the void.
So go in the void and get it for us.
You need to defeat me.
I'm waiting.
It's a ritual.
What if we- I've got an idea.
Repeat that?
I've got an idea.
You need to-
A ritual?
You need to defeat me.
It's a ritual.
Oh, I knew it.
I fucking knew it.
This guy.
What?
He's trying to get us to fight him all along.
No, no, no.
It's not a fight.
It's just a game.
You wanna fight?
Come here, you piece of shit.
No, I don't wanna-
Fuck.
I spit in his face.
Oh my god.
I'm not putting them up.
Please.
Let me at him.
I've got an idea.
- Why are you doing that? - We're crazy.
- Why don't we put him in there with a mirror? - I'm straining like a dog on a leash,
but there's no leash. I'm just pretending to hold myself back.
You don't want to bump my homie over here. He's loco.
Okay, I think evil is good.
If you... How about this?
Oh, what's that? Is that the... Oh, a sub voice.
If you beat me in this, you'll also get to level up.
- Ah, what does that mean? - Get into the void.
Okay, yeah.
I grab Pat and throw him into the void with me.
So what happens is actually,
because there's no, it's like there's this giant machine here
and as you approach it,
your vision begins to get like kind of fuzzy
and the edges of reality fray
and like vibrate a little gently.
It's sort of like you're on a you're like tripping and you
also get to melt into something else like some other world and
it's must be where the winged gamer lives all the time and he
says he says to you and his voice is now sort of like echoing
and has like a another tone below it.
That's so deep it like sort of like rings in your head and
he's like the void is able to project the sine wave that
corresponds to the gamers.
I if you stand too near for too long you become like us.
But this should not be a worry for you all.
You must step in and you guys kind of step a little bit closer
and the sensation you felt before happens again, but now like
sort of louder and stronger solvent as well.
The you look up at the top of the Xbox sort of thing you're
in and it now begins to open up into like a black sky punctuated
by these like little stars that seem to streak along it echoing,
you know, their echoes like lingering along a horizon where
You see like crystal mountains cutting through an endless
expanse radiating colors refracting from nowhere.
And then suddenly the wing gamers before you again, like
you're sort of like shook by this vision and then you see
his face is like perfect face and it devours your field of
view and you hear his voice again and he doesn't even seem
to be moving his mouth and he says tick-tack-toe.
my god.
And you see before you just this like, like, massive, like, beautiful, like, lit up tic-tac-toe
board.
And the gamer...
I'm gonna wait for the console to commence.
The gamer says first, "Best two of three," and puts an X here.
Why do you get to go first?
Yeah, wait, hold on, that's not fair.
that
we
I got it. I play smoking now Patrick you do you okay? Don't do that
Alright, so Patrick's is there and then I'll put mine right next to yours
For the listeners Caleb did not complete the three in a row. Okay. Well that round doesn't count
We're also learning. Okay. Okay. We'll redo it. All right, you can go first this time
Okay, I'll put mine right here, okay
Put yours in the top load each I did to put down
You're so okay. Now Ray William Johnson
I put mine right on bats
Mine not bites in the corner. Okay, I'll put okay. I'll put two
Okay, so now we have four in a row stop. Nope, that's not
That's not how it works. It's easy Sullivan starts to draw like a triangle. This is do
Okay, wait just just one more time I'll nominate all right third match point
No, I'm gonna take one of you to be champion and you can't nominate Sullivan because that what happened
You have to read everything you just said
Just nominate one of you to be it be the champion who will challenge me
I know I put I put Patrick on my shoulders and and and then I climb
I'm a nominate this guy roll roll that legs check as you're doing that. Okay
Just you're able to keep Patrick on your shoulders, but Patrick just starts to tip over
Cameron
uh... okay just let's let's cut this out for a second just one of you
versus me
okay i'll go first
okay
that's fine at this point alright
i don't know
well that's like a
you can have it all across three of them in a row but i don't know it's a little
energy look at it
it's a word with anything it's not an old
okay can i go again
yeah you could try again
no that's not you can't roll i know i'm clear
nope
the whole thing
it's a case in five different spaces
that's not yet you know that there are over the whole board this is not
you know i was hoping this would be too long to the lot of the humor is visual
the
it seems to be that's what you enjoy most
okay
i will go first
again
pay the board just moved to know it's not a i don't know how to read the
election bought i'm actually moving it back a little bit he bought
hold on just
your aid in the screen at us
okay
i'm drawing my ex now one of you draw it all
but like in one square
load us it's all you
no not on top of the x that i just wrote a act i'm putting one in the middle
okay
all right now i will draw in x
as well okay no
nope you do you have to wait for me to draw the experts okay
this is a little options here in the middle no i'm trying to
nope okay five years of speed around now okay how do you like that
what are you doing so you know it is that you just cheated
no you can't get a huge it out you know i i i i don't like to know i don't like
x's on all these. This is my board now. There's a ghost in the machine. I think we just lost
the version. If you look at the board it kind of looks like four X's. How do you like that?
He's just drawing X's everywhere. And then uh, uh, uh, you guys. A laser comes out and
disintegrates him for cheating. You guys are suddenly forced. You're forced out of the
void with him and somehow you're able to stand near the machine now the void is
locked and he says I've lost I became red nude and mad I rage you have made me
rage that was the plan all along you are the better gamers and the void opens up
up. Yes, dude. The machine the void carefully planned strategy
worked perfectly opens up and reveals a sort of gnarled
wooden Eldridge Bop it. And it's sort of like floats towards
you all and it gets right up to you all like floating like and
and then just drops on the ground.
I catch it.
Yeah?
Okay, roll an athletics check.
16.
Yeah, you catch it. You catch the bop it as it falls.
Okay, I drop it.
As you catch it,
as you drop it,
it lands on the bop it button
and
when it lands on that
it goes like a
"Oooh, lock-o!"
and then it starts like all the like different parts of the bop at the
twisted to flick it they're all they all look like this dark obsidian wood and
they all start like they all start like glowing intermittently like the bop at
the game and you hear it go doh-la-co and like the twisted thing lights up and
then if you don't do anything it just goes and it's like gotta I think we got
I think it's saying touch it.
You first.
I don't want to touch it.
I already touched it.
I caught it.
You catched it?
You what?
What?
What did you do?
Say that one more time.
I caught it.
Can we run that back?
I dropped it.
Run that shit back, Turbo.
You mean I dropped it?
Is that what you guys are talking about?
So you guys make me record everything as part of my punishment and uh, he said catched it.
I did not say that.
I think he said that.
I don't remember saying that.
You kicked the bop it?
Yeah.
It goes "Oolaco" and then it goes "Oolaco".
I don't know what that one means.
What?
You can say other shit.
Just kidding.
on
middle. I spit on it. Okay. You like that, Bobbit? I pull it. You pull it? Okay. It says
"Polako" and then it goes "Sulako". I slap it. Oh, I Sulako it. Yeah. Okay, I change it.
Okay, okay, hold on, hold on, hold on.
What?
What's he doing here?
Well, you said Sulaco.
Looking at the ceiling.
You said Sulaco, and that starts with an S. So I don't know if that's spinet.
I'm trying to remember what the functions of boppet are.
Boppet, twist it, pull it.
I tickle it.
Yeah.
It's just like a...
Don't tickle, don't fucking tickle me.
fingernails feel weird don't tickle it uh you look at it and you could see like it has a traditional
bop it structure of bop it twist it pull it flick it spin it um uh it has all um
unless is there yeah no it has all five of those on it um and if you press the bop it button it
goes oh and then like it the light up starts again to let you know that the game is starting
I've been a song plays, but it's like a it's like a like a very very slow sludge metal song. That's playing as
You get to choose like as it lights up again
I look on the back of it and I see that there's a language switch and it's switched from English to scary and I
Okay, yeah, yeah, it's which is right back to English yes, dude, that was so easy. Yeah
Doesn't but yeah, you can you can press you can like just play with it for now
Okay. Yeah, I just play with it
I just have fun. Okay, ooh lock. Oh and it goes door lock. Oh
And I twist it lights up. I twist it. I twist it. I twist. Oh, okay. Oh lock. Oh, I pull it
Nice. Yeah flick it
(laughter)
I pull it again.
No!
(laughter)
Fuck you!
Come on, dude.
(laughter)
I've been playing Bop for an hour.
Starts again.
Ullaco.
I chew it.
Okay.
No, I Bop it.
Pullaco.
I pull it.
No, I'm playing.
You guys are in the other room.
No, we're all playing.
I'm playing.
No, we can't all play.
player you're like walking around the room try to hold it higher than the
house i've got a lot i rub it
it has to say pass it and then you can play
you know that
i read it
can i have brought you know what you guys you you guys handle this one i'm i'm
talking about him
is all you do
okay i would have been immediately
will not go by pass it
okay
and
thirty-two how would it know if i passed it
i would assume just a time around now
interesting doesn't seem like it took very long but i am
okay i just
i knew how long it was going to take the department shut up
try again
okay i bought a lot go
okay yet starts up
adore local i twisted
flake it
I go to lick it but then I flick it.
Then it says
"Pass it!"
Okay, I throw it up like I'm passing it
but then I just catch it.
I bop it.
Which one's Sulaco? Spin it.
This goes on for another 45 minutes and eventually you guys figure it out.
Pretty you guys got it. I'm not worried about you getting it. And as you do,
it says it starts it once you like complete the Bop It sequence, it then you hear and
And like a little disk drive pops out.
And you see the amulet that Marie and Rex gave you.
That was from Leo. Start to glow a little bit and like sort of move a little bit in the direction of the Bop-It.
So you can keep it away from that thing.
I put the amulet in.
Okay. Yeah, you put the amulet in, you close it.
Like it's hard to close because there's like string around it,
but eventually you get it to close and as you do
the Bop it the Bop.
It says like please move away.
Please move away.
Please move away and I hand the Bop it to the winged gamer.
Yeah, and he's like fuck just like tosses on the ground and
it starts to the Bop it starts to like like sort of like like
It looks like it's both like growing like the gnarled obsidian like wood of it is like sort of
Growing and twisting around until it makes like a weird like
Egg shape and then you hear
And it like just just sort of standing or sitting in place
It's like egg and then you start to hear like a little sound like a tinny sound that sounds like a blizzard
uh, like whooshing by and the sound gets louder and louder miser and
Then the egg bop it in all its like
Weirdness it pops open like it cracks open and it reveals like a solid gold penguin
with a really realistic vagina I
Thought it was gonna be snow miser
and
What is this fucking bullshit?
Fuck this thing. I thought this was gonna be fucking snow miser. No. No, I think I think that's a clue
I think that's supposed to be a clue. I don't care
Sullivan are you think it's do you think that thing is sexy?
No
Everyone knows I'm
Talk to her
Sullivan say this word for word. Hey bitch. Are you from Tennessee? Cuz you're the only 10 I see it'll work
Go try it
You're only interested in that thing cuz it looks like a frog
What I push Sullivan up to it
Tennessee
You're fucking it up Sullivan. Oh don't sing Tennessee arrested development. Don't sing that I
Don't I'm not I'm not cool enough to know anything like that Patrick Yoda
and you hear from
beyond the a
A little bit beyond the Xbox area that you're in, a familiar voice say, "Well, that's all
I needed to see."
And it is none other than Pennsylvania Jim.
And he says, "You would have thought that you three Dwights would be able to figure out
what that means by now."
Don't call me that!
I thank you for that.
Hey Jim, is this thing your girlfriend?
Oh!
Yeah, watch this.
You know what he's about to do to it.
eating the statue's pussy right in front of him.
"Yeah, you like this? This is your girlfriend. Oh yeah."
Yeah, well you sure own me, Dwight.
"Tastes like a water fountain."
I'll tell you who's gonna own you now, and he...
[laughter]
Fuck.
He snaps his fingers, and then nothing happens,
is
out with so many children.
It's because I have a loving wife and we have three kids together.
Are these your three kids?
You're putting your kids up to battle us?
No, these are not my kids.
I'm going to go.
I got what I needed.
You're going to go fall in love with a kid.
Nope, not going to do that.
You're a pedophile, Jim.
That's what the P in your name stands for.
Nope, it's pretty clearly Pennsylvania.
Nope, Peru.
Pedophile Jim.
Yes, that's what the P in your name stands for.
Nope, it's pretty clearly Pennsylvania, actually.
Nope, parole Jim, for pedophile stuff.
I'm on parole for being a pedophile?
Yep.
[laughter]
I stopped him from leaving.
Yeah.
Alright, you wanna try to stop him?
Yeah, I grab onto his leg.
We get into a circle and we just kinda like, we put our arms together.
Can we get him on the map, though, for real?
Oh, shit.
uh...
your ability to do it about a good down
so that you better stay away from this guy 'cause you're short he might mistake
you for
the younger person
yeah
right all gone
what about me with this means all of it in the same height
uh... you
a patrick you know you should go you should go to stretch it
yeah okay to lift up your jet i wrote books
uh...
a pennsylvania jim i'm gonna go be sexy over here
i'm not a
not a pedophile point
and what do you know you're going to be a
all no i'm doing some maryland monroe stuff over here
is this a very useful
all god
and to describe what you're doing what find this as well
i found a hair dryer and i put it
I do the ultimate Marilyn Monroe thing and I take a bunch of barbiturates
it's
Everyone roll initiative, and I think because Jim's not expecting it, you guys can get a
round where you try to stop him.
Oh dude.
I got a 13.
I got a 11.
No wait, yeah I got 11.
Oh I got 20.
20 from Pat, let's go dude.
Nice dude.
Okay, yeah, okay, I also, I forgot, I wanted you guys to level up after you solved the
Bop It.
So, um, uh, see ya.
See ya. Yeah, just give us like yeah, five minutes
Just don't do any pedophiles it over there. It's one thing. I respect. It's RPGs. Please level up boys and
So yeah, I'll show you guys your you remember your things
Your weird trees I made for you
I did some tweaking on some of them because I took away some abilities and gave you some others
And retooled them a little bit
But things are largely the same
For the most part
So what you can do if you look at the your your thing you get two points per level up
So you can obviously save two points also
Or just use one point now to unlock a subclass and get the bonus
But right now so Ray William Johnson has you have an unlock in bazinga
You have an unlock blow toss in shadow who and Patrick Yoda you have an unlock in
counselor
Yeah
Do I wait I still have the smoothie ability
Got about that you can now you can now unlock the yeah ignore that the tree
I didn't edit the tree the abilities the tree is mostly correct
But the abilities that I described are did I even have the smoothie and
Uncle's Falcon you had the smoothie.
You didn't really use it.
You had piece for you to piece for all which I fixed.
I'm not completely broken this time.
Because last time it was like basically like a realm of peace for
10 minutes, which is crazy.
I don't know what I was thinking.
Why why change that it was perfect.
Metric also never used it.
It's true.
Yeah.
So wait, it costs how many?
We get two points, it costs how many to-
Yeah, you get two points.
It costs one to unlock one of the subclasses.
So if you have a subclass unlocked, like you already have Shadow Who unlocked, you could
just spend your two to finish getting the abilities from that class.
Alright.
Versus, if you, once you unlock a subclass for that level up period, it then costs one
additional one like it costs two then to unlock another subclass so if you saved
up to this time you could spend three to unlock two subclasses how do we know
what we have well I probably I have three because I just unlocked a bazinga
the first time and that was my first subclass right yeah you actually have
yeah yours are actually stacked yeah you have three cool actually do I have you
You have two.
Where do I see that?
You don't see it anywhere.
You unlocked Counselor last time.
And I retold your abilities so you're, even though you didn't quite keep some of the same
abilities from the last level up, I made you, I kind of like made you a bit stronger to
like make up for that.
Okay, well I'm gonna, either way I'm unlocking Dark Yoda.
Okay, and Dark Yoda is under Sentinel.
Okay, so you unlock Sentinel, which means...
So when you guys level up also, your Technoslime increases by 25%.
But for you, Patrick Yoda, now it's going to increase by 50%
because you unlock Sentinel, which is the Force user subclass.
And Dark Yoda is... Dark Yoda is very cool.
It basically gives you additional abilities when you use Use the Force.
Okay, the whole Sentinel subclass as I made it is supposed to be like you have that used to force ability and that's that's gonna be so it just stacks on top of that.
So when you have dark Yoda patch Yoda embraces the dark side giving him these additional abilities when he uses the force Yoda's mind now can cause psychic damage upon entry into the mind.
So if you try to read somebody's mind, you can also do a shit ton of damage to them now.
Yoda's choke. Yoda can choke enemies grappling from afar with a wisdom check
against a disadvantaged strength check and will be undetected unless the target succeeds on a perception check against Yoda's sleight of hand.
So basically, you can choke somebody and they cannot know where that's coming from.
And then you have Yoda ultra lightning. Your lightning is now superior and can attack more than one person at a time.
a strike of lightning or a stroke of lightning forming a line 100 feet long and 5 feet wide blasts out from you in the direction you choose.
Each creature in the line must make a dexterity saving throw, they'll take 86 on a failed save or half as much,
and also the lightning ignites anything flammable that's nearby.
Um, so, and then also you get, um, also, oh no, yeah, Foreskin Ultra's actually a separate ability.
So you just get those, those, those three up top there.
Um, yeah.
Oh, so this, if this, you didn't update the tree.
Yeah, I didn't update it.
This were on the tree, so it would be like Dark Yoda would be like one thing and then it would have like a bunch of other branches?
It would be no it would be like a sentinel like it is in dark Yoda
But then dark Yoda the abilities would make would you would see the abilities there rather though. You did update it. Okay. Yeah
Yeah, but if I had a better tree would be a better tree. Okay. Yeah Plotas. What do you want to do?
What are you thinking? Um, so yeah, I unlocked the shadow who class and last time I got master disguise
So I'm just gonna get the two other abilities from it. Nice. Yeah, which is who's there - there
where after I take damage I can turn invisible and then sneak attack people.
Gift of the Lorax, which it says I can pick one of these spells.
Can you explain what these spells are?
These spells are like 5e psychic damage based spells.
Mental Prison, which means you can basically trap somebody inside of a mental prison.
I'll send you the like actual like spells. It's basically like you
Give they are inside of a prison that only they can see
So they just like think they're inside of a prison
and then they take a
That they take like a shit ton of damage
In there like to take 5d 10 psychic damage while they're in there and they can continually take damage it's pretty crazy
So you have that ability
And then you have
Phantasmal killer is the other one you could choose
We get that one up to
Fan there. I'll send you these actually
So phantasmal killer you tap in the nightmares of creatures
You can see within range create an illusory manifestation of its deepest fears visible only to that creature
The target must make a wisdom saving throw on a failed save the target becomes frightened for the duration at the end of each
Of the targets turns before the spell ends target must succeed a wisdom saving throw or take 4d 10 psychic damage
I'm going to choose Mental Prison though.
Unless Crown of Madness is really really cool.
Crown of Madness just puts a crown on their head and it makes them crazy.
I choose Mental Prison.
Gift of the Lorax also lets me teleport.
And also Gift of the Lorax lets me teleport.
Yes. Yeah.
So you're basically like, you fully embrace sort of the aspects of Whovian culture that deal with dark magics.
Yeah, and you're fully maxed out there.
And it gives me intelligence too.
Yes. Yes, you get +1 intelligence because your spells are intelligence based.
Now, RayWilliamJohnson.
What are you leaning towards?
I think I'm gonna tailor my level up for our specific enemy and I'm gonna go with
I'm gonna get to are we computer subclass and I'm gonna unlock child porn upload -
Okay
Yeah
Which I don't even want to know what that is, but I am unlocking it. Basically. It just means you can use
Oh shit, I think I I changed that slightly
Yeah, I'll put it back in. Yeah, basically what it does is it allows you to
Attempt to upload child porn on onto five people max
Could I hypothetically upload five times the child porn to onto one person? Yeah. Yeah, you could try
It
It makes the porn the children are five times the age
It does cost so that's actually that's that doesn't work out doesn't help at all. Yeah
If you if you upload the thing it costs
10 techno slime points to use. Okay, so if it doesn't work, I mean you're out but you have I think you have refills
So yeah, I have to risk addiction
But yeah, go for it
Child porn upload to so plus one intelligence and then
And everything after a level of everything's like refilled, right? Yeah, you guys are refilled anyway as it is
so yeah
But let me find the
I'm gonna make sure I have child porn upload - you're making sure you have child porn uploaded. Nope
That's you and that I have to stop making that you have to stop making sure that you guys stop you guys stop
Not putting words in my mouth, but like, you know, just sort of mixing around the words that are there.
I'm not denying that they're there to make it seem like I'm a bad guy.
You want to put one word in your mouth, child.
Okay.
But yeah, you guys are all leveled up. You also all, again, you gain 25% of your Technoslime points.
Okay, do we get to round up?
And Patrick Yoda you get 50% because you chose Sentinel.
So that means your Technoslime points are now...
100.
Yeah, 102.
Oh, okay.
How much health do we gain?
Oh yes, we have to do that as well.
So you guys are now technically level 6.
So, that's cool.
but roll you can you just have to hit the uh... okay
person to get it's not a hundred combat
uh... you said a hundred and two was
just josh and man
was it was a little bit of signified that you were josh in
i was just a scenario eighteen
uh... that's pretty good
that's very high amount of techno sign points uh...
yet round up for you guys yet
yet all i want to have less techno sign points
and i'll take 'em
I wanna grind for my shit.
For you guys in your character sheets, hit your hit dice.
The hit dice button.
And whatever that is, just add that to your total HP.
Cool.
Where's it?
It's under hit points.
Four, bitch!
I got 410.
Nope, I saw that.
Come on, man. I'm right here.
here. Come on. You almost got it past him that time. Yeah, he almost believed you, dude.
I have three hit points total. Oh my god, he fell for it, guys. Yeah, whatever you need
to say, I guess, to me to keep yourselves entertained. And so, yeah, I mean...
It's your turn.
So what do you want to do?
It is?
Mm-hmm.
Mm-mm.
My apologies, sorry.
Patrick Yoda, it's your turn.
How do you want to try to stop Jim?
That's what I asked this turn for.
So are we still-- what are we doing?
Are we still doing the-- what we were doing before?
Yeah, let's just kill Jim right now and just get--
What the fuck is going on?
I don't think we should kill him.
What did you do, Caleb?
It's none of your business, actually.
What were you doing?
Nothing.
I think he fell down.
kill him. What did you do Caleb? It's none of your business actually. What were you doing?
I think he fell down. I did not fall down. Caleb fell down. Okay I'm gonna be honest with
you guys, the door to my bedroom is broken. I asked Janna to turn off the TV and said
she closed the door and now I'm locked in here so I had her roll a beer under the door
and it was very loud. It was very loud on my floor. So are you guys happy now? Wait how
How did you get a beer under the door?
My door is hung poorly and there's a giant gap in the bottom.
You have to know just everything.
I didn't, I've seen it before.
What about when you have to go to the bathroom?
Great, and now the fans know. I guess I'm just gonna fucking not pee, cause I'm stuck.
Okay.
You should kill Jim.
Yeah, so I think what I'm gonna do to Jim...
Oh, read his mind.
Uh-huh. I'm gonna read his mind.
Wait, wait, wait. You should read his mind after I upload porn to it.
I'm gonna read it before. No, because I'm gonna read it before.
He might save me some trouble. There might already be child porn in his brain.
Right. So I'm gonna read his mind.
Alright, so you wanna do Yoda's mind.
Vanilla Yoda's mind on our boy Jim. Dark Yoda's mind.
You wanna do dark Yoda's mind? Yes.
So for that, first you have to use the force. And I have an advantage.
Because we snuck up on him, you said?
No, no, no. The advantage is that you're all going to get to go right now out of turn order before anything.
I thought we had an advantage.
I'll get an advantage for going.
Just do your turn.
So yeah, you spend 8 Techno Slime points now, and you start charging up, and you have this Force abilities and your Dark Force abilities.
It's all happening around you. Now, for Yoda's mind, it costs 5 Technoslime points to do.
So, wait, so I took away 8, you said?
Yeah, to get the dark Yoda's mind.
Okay.
But now you have, now you're used to force. So you have the lightning shit you had before, you have the advantages on abilities that you had before.
it gives you that super power up.
Oh, so I have five techno slime points now.
Yeah, but you have the ability to recharge it and you have used a force for,
let's see, how many turns?
So about five turns.
So you still have it for five turns.
Yeah, that's going to do it. We're going to be fine.
Yeah, so your AC goes up by two, your movement speed is doubled,
you have all this, you can move shit with your mind now,
and you have lightning abilities.
Okay.
So, but you're gonna use Yoda's Mind. Okay.
So, with Yoda's Mind, he has to resist this now.
And he can't.
No, he can resist.
Against your Wisdom save, let's see how he does.
And I roll a Wisdom?
No, it's just against your Wisdom save.
So, your Spell save, rather, which is 16.
he did beat you. No! But you still roll 3d8 and he takes half of that damage still.
Oh. Because you still like tried to penetrate his mind. Penetrate? Come on.
You're rolling all these d8s individually? Alright, cool. Nice, yeah. So you did 7 damage to him.
the
your
I'm gonna do chill. Yeah, so first thing what you should do is roll a sleight of hand check to see if you can sneak the wire
Up to his brain
Okay, I rolled a 12
Okay, and that is going to be against his we don't have like a wireless fucking
There's no not a little tooth not for child porn. Oh, I
Guess that makes sense
Yeah, so that is against his his passive wisdom. Yeah his passive wisdom. Yeah, so he sees the wire coming
She's he's able to like stomp on it and sort of like send it back towards you. No my child born. I mean
that was
There's my wire dude
But yeah that that that costs you like 10 check no techno slime points
But I mean, it's also like a one-shot kill. So oh it was a good kill
Well when you upload child porn to somebody the gun city government immediately
Tracks down and swarms the person that would funny just kill
They would have been bad
Good maybe for me
Blotus you're up. It does mental prison. Does that involve an attack role?
No
Mental prison is it? No, it's a save. It's a save. Okay, so they have to make an intelligence saving throw
So your spell DC is 14, so he has to beat that to not get that.
Yeah, I'm going to continue the streak of just using new abilities and I'm just going to use Mental Prison on him.
Yeah, so that's 5 Technoslime points to do that. I should make that cost more.
Now that I've heard that, I'm going to be using it every single fight.
uh...
okay yeah he does
managed to uh...
uh... okay he does manage to beat it
but he still takes 5d10 psychic damage
alright
so he momentarily thinks he's like in a prison
yeah can i describe do i get to choose the prison? yeah describe it describe it
so he looks around and he's in
the familiar office
uh... because uh... he goes up to the front desk
he sees he sees a beautiful head of hair from the back
and he goes of him i love you any walks up
she turns around you know whose face it is
well no
it's the white house also she and then he screams and he takes thirty one day
pitch
uh...
thirty-nine one bro
yes
he's like
like his eyes like only exploded bleeding and reform again like a car to like
but he's got fucking like
his mind was just fucked uh... i mean he's
he's uh...
like final final boss material so you guys did a good job but he's gonna
slink away to get off
pocket kill you three
okay to it
well
shop any slinks away
he says no just go
he says what
the
it would be a little bit
what did you just say
you don't know that there is a week out the past yet that we have a tough
that you can't say it
good news good news morning news show only good news is a tricky back and
forth
talking here today because i was a little early holding the child porn upload
wire and i said
your take this health wire
is like put it in your brain
is he says
you through your fucking dad
i'm gonna do something bad to you
worse than what i did to roll it
and uh... home
you notice or a you notice that he has that his hat
had he's wearing
has is made of royce skin
and he slowly six okay
uh... didn't have like is like uh... is like
facial features on the head
Yeah, yeah, you just didn't notice before yeah, it's made of his ever-rose entire skin so like the arms and legs are still
Yeah, you guys did a good job there there will be both rewards and consequences for that I'm afraid but that was sick
Damn, how will there be consequences?
Cuz he's mad we need a fight him at some point. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. No, no consequences
I mean, you know, it's in the story, you know, yeah, it's not like you kick the cop or something
But yeah, so now
We're back to the top of the order actually so the ninjas don't get to go
Yet cuz I was like all just like first round like you guys saw Jim and just like tried to fuck him up and you
did
But now we're back to the top of the order. So Patrick Yoda, you're up. All right
So now we have to fight these three ninjas. Yeah
What colors are they? Yeah, they're yellow green and pink from what you can see
The pink one has like a bo staff of some kind and she has like sort of like a cartoonish
cartoonish looking like a
rocket like a little like bomb like it looks like a like a if you've played a
Enter the gungeon books like the little bomber gun in that
and then the green one is there and
And he doesn't have any weapons, but he's just like dripping green all the time and he just looks kind of nasty, even though you can looks like a ninja and he's just green, but you could be something's emanating out of him.
And then the yellow one has like her just also has nothing equipped to her that you can immediately tell but there's like kind of electricity crackling around her and she sort of like stands at the ready.
But yeah, that's a three that are there.
So yeah, what do you want to do, Patrick Yoda?
Patrick Yoda, you also used a force, which you have four more turns of now.
Oh, okay.
So you're super powerful right now.
There's a lot you can do.
All right, then I'm gonna...
So I roll with advantage?
Not for everything.
Okay.
Some of the things you can do, though, with...
Use the force is...
Hold on.
So yeah, with... Use the force...
Yeah, you can move objects though.
Like if that's kind of what you're asking and you have,
you can automatically move objects that are tiny or small.
If they're medium size, which is what these people are,
right, it's DC 10 generally,
but then like they're gonna resist to some extent.
But then also you have the ability to shoot lightning
out of your hands now and you can shoot lightning
with a phone set.
That's the first thing I'm fucking doing.
Okay, so you can also try to set it up
so that you line them all up for a dark lightning attack.
- Okay.
- Or you can do just a regular lightning attack.
- Okay, all right, so I'm trying to set them all up.
I say, "Hey, conga line!"
(laughing)
- Yeah, I'll let you try it.
I'll literally let you try a persuasion check.
- Okay. - To see.
- 14.
- No, yeah.
If you got a crit, I would have absolutely let that happen.
That would have been very funny.
Okay.
So yeah, you can still,
So you have like 60 feet of movement though, so you can pretty easily at least get a couple of them in a line
Obviously, well, okay 60 feet. What if I just went right here?
Because are these two in a line?
Yeah, they're about yeah, cuz if you turn over that's five feet. That's what
You can get the pink and the yell in the back. They are just moving everything around on this map
Okay, okay. I move right here
Okay, and then I shoot lightning
in
Describe your dark lightning as I roll.
Um, I have...
So, I run over to that spot.
And then I go...
Wait, how do I... How should I find out that I have it?
You're not even just running, you're doing the force run in Battlefront 2.
Like, kinda shit.
Yeah, so I'm just like...
Yeah, you're like bounding over there.
and uh...
i trip over
these cheese poofs here
there's some scattered snacks on the ground and you definitely dodge out of the
way of milk duds but the cheese poofs get you for sure. I get the cheese poofs
and then i roll on the ground and i get up because i stub my toe on them
i get up so angry
that i shoot brown lightning out of my fingers
uh... when they see that it's brown their first reaction instead of dodging it is to go
Oh
But yeah now they're going to roll some do some DX. All right, they're pretty they're pretty dexterous, but let's see
You're not
Okay. Yeah, okay, and then I mean they still take half damage. So even if they yeah
They both like are able to like get out of the way of like the largest part of the blast, but they still take
You know half damage so roll 8d6. Okay, so just forward slash our 8d6 and then half of that
Well, I can't can I do it my way you could do it your way if you want to roll each one at once cuz it's a
Little fun for you. I mean you guys are now where'd you guys go on the map?
I don't know where you are on the map anymore. Oh
They ran away blowtoss. I didn't really Johnson. Where are you guys on the map?
Someone disappeared I promise I did not move us
What did you do Pat?
I disappeared you.
Where did you put me?
Are we under Patrick?
I don't know where you guys are.
I'll get your tokens back I guess.
What happened?
Nope, he's back.
You're a bitch.
What is going on?
How do you like it?
(laughing)
God damn it.
All right, let me get you guys back there.
You guys didn't delete Sullivan, did you?
- No, he's still there.
- Okay, good, he's just freaking out.
(laughing)
- Oh, where'd they go?
Oh my God!
I can't do shit!
- All right, you're back.
Okay, cool.
So yeah, they still take 16 damage.
I got a 31. Yeah, they take half damage. Oh, right, right.
So they take 16 and you still have your bonus action that you can do.
Should I just shoot more lightning? If you want to.
Alright, I'm going to do that again. Yeah, go for it.
28. No, no, it would be...
Oh yeah, shit, I guess we gave you two attacks. That's crazy, why'd I do that?
Um, yeah, so, uh, yeah, they take 14, uh, from that as well.
Um, so yeah, they're just like getting like, they're like, you're like,
*mimics lightning*
And you're just like completely fucking them up.
Um, and now you also still have a bonus action for more lightning damage.
Uh...
I have more, I have another attack?
Yes.
Oh my god, dude.
You guys are crazy strong now.
31.
Well, not that one, not, not that, that much attack.
You have like a bonus action you can do.
Oh.
which is so basically it's like you did your two attack actions
and so you have a little extra action you can do that you can see here in the sheet
it's a 2d6 as a bonus action. That doesn't change even with dark lightning
Ok, I think I'm going to roll, so I can roll 2d6 for lightning
Yeah, just roll 2d6, yeah. 4. 4. Ok, yeah, so they're only going to take
two of that. So you did, I mean you just did 32 damage
so, or, it's not bad, 32, 33 damage. 32,
the
back to
next
in our turn order though
is uh... the yellow one
so after getting like fucking fucked up by that shit
uh... she sort of like uh... real brief
you know
recruits
and uh...
jumps just like i runs over here
ignoring you at this point
and she opened you see you see like
uh... uh... out of the top of her ninja
visor
you hear like a
like a loud high-pitched scream and like these like sonic waves coming out of it
uh...
as she's doing like a sonic wave kind of attack or something
uh... which uh... she's gonna try to hit you guys see who your AC is
by you guys i mean uh...
she ran up
to you know patch good to go to read william johnson blowtoss and so i'll
uh...
so her
or attack
okay yeah
think that only is going to hit sullivan
uh... now all your a_c_s are higher than that
uh... as my soul that's got us are getting out of the way uh... or so
uh...
so she does
uh... okay
array
doing the damage from that
uh... hope shit when i saw
that wasn't even before you know how much it was damaged it does
yeah that's basically how much it is information
okay cool
uh... yes holden takes six points of damage so he's on the four h_p_
uh...
and now
she's going to uh...
uh... after she does that
Sullivan also has like a yellow mark that appears on him,
like some sort of like yellow smudge.
He's like, "Ah, ha! You can't get it off!"
And then she's going to...
suddenly like she's gonna like kind of vanish for a second,
and then appear like on the other side of you guys,
and you're all spinning in place like cartoons.
And like she moves so fast through you guys that you're all spinning in place.
And you're all basically dizzy and she now has advantage.
Anybody has advantage on attacks against you guys for one round.
And now she's going to do her sonic thing again with advantage.
And probably, possibly kill Sullivan.
What? No.
Yeah, she hits all of you guys.
uh, and nice. Okay.
And she has another six damage.
Uh, uh, just six damage to you.
Three, um, Sullivan blow toss and re William Johnson.
So the sonic thing comes out and like pierces your ears and like
shakes your head.
Just feels crazy.
I'm solving just head and Sullivan just like passes out.
He's just like on the ground passed out.
He's gonna have to start rolling for him.
Can we throw?
So can we throw Sullivan under a table or something?
Yeah absolutely.
I'll let you guys deal with that so it doesn't become an escort mission.
But yeah now it is Ray William Johnson's turn.
Okay.
I'm going to attack the yellow ninja.
Mm-hmm.
Actually, you know what?
Maybe I'll throw--
I might throw my sexual grenade in between the green and purple ninjas.
Nice.
Yeah, I'm going to do that.
All right, do it.
Right here.
Well, I can't.
You can just hold it down like that.
Yeah, there you go.
Perfect.
All right.
Yeah, that works.
I rolled a hit of 16.
That hits both of them.
both
nasty ooze and lights em a fire. That also costs you, how many Technoslime points is
that for you, is that two I think? Because it's like sort of like one of your base attacks.
I think I gave it two. Let me see. It's either two or three. Three. Three? Okay. Yeah, but
yeah the pink one's not looking too good after that. Yes! So, yeah, you still have another
attack to and your movement. I'm gonna just do it again. Yeah. Yep. 14 that time. It doesn't
hit this time. Fuck you! Yep, alright. So this time they just manage to get out of the
way. They kind of know what to expect. Alright, then I'm gonna move over here and hide behind
the mountain dew. Wait, bring Sullivan with you. I bring Sullivan with me. Yeah, yeah,
you run. I'll let you pick up Sullivan. He's pretty light. And just run over with him. Just
pick 'em up by his leg.
Yeah, just drag him.
He's banging his head against, like, controllers
that are scattered on the ground.
Palming his head like a basketball.
Yeah.
I'm pulling him, like, by his, like, upper lip,
like, all the way.
He's having a sense, memory, in his, like,
passed-out state of a terrible bullying experience
that, like, he went through.
Which was also me.
Yeah, it was, like, also you.
Yeah, we'll do Gun City Babies.
you all went to preschool together
uh... yet so now it is
the uh...
pink ones turn
and uh...
they're going to
turn into some sort of weird gaseous mist
we're gonna go home
and uh...
i've learned to say they're going to go home
that's not what i said
said they're going to do it and it is going to turn into a gash
and uh...
float like over here
and then reform
and then shoot at you blowtoss with their like weird little bomber gun and like
he's like damn it
pink sparkles come out
of it when when
she shoots it
and yeah it doesn't hit you
uh... I knew it
and she's gonna try to shoot you one more time again with that
oh no actually
you know it would be more fun
Is if she does something cooler like
Yeah, she does she starts to like convulse sort of what you saw when you saw the blue ninja do this back in the day
and these like
Like crazy like lines come out of her back almost like tentacles run up to wrap you blow toss
enroll a
DC roll a deck safe
Okay
16.
Nice, yeah.
Okay, these things try to wrap around you, but you remember seeing Patrick go to deal with that last time,
so you're able to like get out of the way of it.
Um, and now it's your turn, Blowtoss.
All right, so the only ninja that hasn't gone yet is the green one, right?
That's the Mountain Dew ninja.
It's a Baha Blast ninja.
I'm gonna run up right next to him, and since I get advantage and extra damage against people
who haven't gone yet, so I'm gonna use my dual pipes.
is
That's not true. The green one got hit by a sexual grenade by Rueben Johnson.
Oh, okay.
You did pink and yellow.
But I- but because I hit- any hit I- I score against a surprise creature, it counts as a critical.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, so do I roll damage twice? Is that it?
Um...
Yeah, just count it twice, whatever you roll. We can just do that.
20.
Oh, Jesus fucking Christ.
That's the highest possible damage, I think.
Oh shit, we're gonna count that twice. You just hit 40 damage.
Yeah.
Maybe.
So this guy just like hasn't moved and like just got burned a bit by ray william johnson, which you did 13 damage to them. Jesus
Yeah, and you just like start
Like beating them senseless
Um, and they do not look good. I got another like shit. Yeah, go for it. I'm gonna do it again
26 that hits
14 times 228 damage. Yeah, you just keep uh, oh no, it's not crit this time. I think right because
Oh, no any oh, right. You're right. Yeah
Fuck yeah, you just like brutalized this guy.
He's more or less out of commission.
Like like it's going to be his turn, but I don't know what
he's going to be able to do.
So yeah, it is.
Freaking cry on me.
Yeah, and he is just like a mess.
He looks like he's been beaten into a pulp and you watch him
slowly melt into himself
and turn into like some sort of like slime puddle
uh...
and uh...
uh... he's able and uh...
you start to sink into the ground
uh...
blow toss
uh... and he moves away as a puddle
like past you
uh... and turns back
and uh... uh...
uh... you blow toss you're going to be able to move next turn you're like stuck in this like puddle
uh... but otherwise he's gonna try to you
uh... with advantage
and we did you is you can go
he's really just concerned to you with
out of his visor similar to the pink one
is gonna shoot something out of your
so the l one except it's gonna be like
with it
i think this green slime vomiting out of his ninja hood
uh... c_e_o_ he does
he is crying on the end of it
you're not crying
he's crying what's going on here i a he's crying
you're right he was crying
and he just said that
what a fucking baby
you can't even cry out loud
and uh... yeah that's all he's able to do he's pretty fucked up
so we're back to the top of the order
aka Sullivan's turd he has to roll a death saving throw
oh he's dead?
he's getting there it's one failure. Is this like the third time he's been dead this campaign?
yeah
yeah pretty much. God he's unlucky bro. He just has to sit in a backpack
yeah yeah you there's a you can find out what it's all
you can find a way to solve for this i would love to know what what you do to
protect yeah we gotta keep in like a safe or something yeah
so solvent is like inching towards uh... uh...
doom
to be fair this this solvent almost death is the first one that like isn't
our faults that we did not on purpose i don't remember what the other answer
yeah uh... and it is your turn patrick you know
uh... this little boy
yeah i'm gonna go on the hill sullivan
you so far away though
yet but i have jet i'd speedy a sixty movement so you're here
pretty good yet because i have exactly fifty feet some ago there and then i'm
just gonna
my fort my four skin
is uh... better now right
now i know you didn't get the force can upgrade it's still good though
uh... but
but you do risk obviously
your force can upgrade allows you to trap enemies
and deal damage to them under the force can and not trap you
well you'll you
but this one just traps you heels you right now
okay
uh... and i can use it on sullivan
you can use on solving you can make it so that it doesn't get really johnson
and it's like just the very tip of it
on sullivan and like everything else is just like a little bit of sullivan a
bite of my hoagie
Well, that counts as food, so that would heal him, right?
I would let you do that, but then your hoagie would lose a little power, probably.
What if I give Sullivan the Mike Pence coin?
It's psychic damage, instantly.
Ah, fuck.
Alright, then I'll do... then I'm focusing on healing Sullivan.
Okay, yeah. Um, so that costs techno slime points wise to three,
right? Three, I believe for foreskin. Yeah. Yeah. Um, and so
yeah, you create this like giant, like thing of this giant,
you know, your giant foreskin sort of thing you generate. And
you basically did it. So it's just like around here, more or
less. So for so solvent's fine. Now he's healing. You can roll
the
at seven. Yeah he's fine he's like... and Ray William Johnson you're just still holding
onto his lip. He's just like "you let go of my lip! Let go of my lip!" Yeah and it is now
whose turn is it? It is the Yellow Ninja's turn. The Yellow Ninja is gonna go after
you
the
I thought it was you for a second. I thought he said Ray.
No. Yeah.
Damn you look cool as hell now.
Very similar words.
She attacks you again and she does hit again.
Ugh.
And uh.
Stop.
That does 10 damage to you.
And now you have like more yellow marks.
Hard to know what's happening there.
What do they look like?
Damn I look even cooler now.
(laughing)
They look like when a kid smudges crayon on something.
- Okay, I wipe them off then.
- You try, you can't wipe them off.
And now it is Ray William Johnson's turn.
- Okay.
- Oh, it's my turn?
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- No, don't do this to me.
- I'm gonna throw my nade again, dude.
I think I have enough, Techno.
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna throw my grenade between,
This time between the yellow and the pink.
Yeah, go for it.
Alright, I'm rolling...11. God damn it!
Okay, yeah, it's a dud.
It just like...
It just like plops there.
And just like leaks.
It just stays there for the rest of the fight.
Just a nut sack on the ground.
Yeah. Okay.
You can do it again.
Yeah, I do it again.
27. Yeah, that hits.
Yes, dude.
on damage.
Ooh.
Uh, yeah, this like, is a particularly, uh, ripe sack, and it just like, lands on the
ground, splat.
Um, and, uh, the green guy is just out of commission.
He just falls to the ground.
He's done.
We took down the green goblin.
Um, and the yellow one looks pretty bad now.
Um, uh, she's like, burning.
Hey, you look like shit!
Um, go home!
i mean she sort of like speaks back in the language that you heard the red in the
blue talking in my corner or or or or
like uh... what they were talking before
uh...
the other green was out
uh... yes i think you can move in shit to if you want to uh... i move and i
shit and move around here and i can't take a shit
okay yeah you shit right on the wing gamers like oh oh my god
it's just a very clear no i do it is noble
uh...
and uh... yeah now it is
uh... the pink ones turn
and uh... the pink one is going to
uh...
takeout uh... is going to go after you
blowtoss
and
to get a stop sign after me
uh... the other ones are hiding behind mountain dew i've literally never did
anything to any of them in my life
you beat the green one
that wasn't me
uh...
does my twin
and she misses the post ever you deflected with the pipes you just like
like not not in my house type of shit
uh... but that she's gonna go for you again
uh...
yeah you deflected again
but and now it is your turn blowtoss and
the yellow marks that are on your body you feel them sort of like
sees and like sort of like crackle and like
like we plug in something we put out unplug something it is for shocks you
except it hurts a lot
come on court yeah and you take six damage
from my god's on you I'm
in I read your turn the pink one standing right next to me so I'm gonna
just gonna do all pipes
yeah do it on the pink one 24
the
again
You just like slap it across her face. It's like boom, boom, boom with the last one and like her head spins around like
And she's just like classes on the ice and then i'm gonna use my new ability. I'm gonna teleport away
Nice, I can teleport 30 feet I think
Yeah, you can
So i'm gonna go up by the mountain dew
with my friends
Yeah at that, uh point, um with two of them knocked out
Um, the yellow one kind of scurries over to them
and sort of gets them to like move barely and they start to stack on top of each
other like you saw the red one and blue one do before
and they start to do Naruto ninja signs and shit
and they vanish and they're gone and uh in their place
is a plate with a big pile of jello on it and what looks like a note
inside of it. Yum! I threw the jello away. No!
There's no trash cans here. What the hell man. You look at the note in the jello and it says
from Jim to Dwight, a parting gift.
And then suddenly the ground around you begins to shake
and you look up at the siding of the massive Xbox you're in
and it begins to, 'cause you start to see it
like sort of shivering and shaking
and you hear like the plastic,
the very hard plastic shaking.
You start to see like the shelves that are up
that have like snacks on them
and the mom bot is like freaking out.
Oreos and Snickers and Mars bars and Nerds
are falling from the sky in this gamer's paradise.
The fridge, the giant fridge in the back is wobbling around.
And then you start to see from behind the Xbox,
pieces of stone and rock that were made of this land cave
back where the Tamagotchis found it, falling to the ground.
You're all struggling to keep your balance.
The wing gamer's like, he blew up the cave.
It's gonna collapse.
You must run.
i'll protect my people
and he just puts on a v_r_ headset and then a rock crushes him
not
uh...
but yeah so the can we have seen do we have the golden penguin
uh... yeah you can snatch it okay yet will that's the first thing we do is we
take the golden penguin
the second thing i do is i teleport out of the case
me too i tell him that i grabbed his leg
and me and so i grabbed cameron's layers float us is lakes
okay yeah so uh...
uh... you only move thirty feet at a time you teleport so the way this works
is i teleport thirty feet forward like a hundred times
i just run up to where they just teleported to
i kinda had a grasp of it
yeah cause you have the same move speed too
so it takes the same amount of time
you guys start by running out of the cave though oh no it's a whole
sequence to get out of this cave
uh oh
it's not going to be easy
is it is collapsing around you this is not easy
yet
uh...
so you guys uh...
teleport out of their uh... uh...
uh... pretty easily
uh... and you end up in the uh...
the land cave room over here
uh...
where it's like this massive beautiful waterfall
uh... you start to see like these like wires and monitors flying around all
these gamers. Some of them are still trying to game even while the whole place is collapsing
around them. While that's happening, I just take an Xbox from one of the gamers. Yeah,
he doesn't even notice that he took the Xbox and his game stopped working. He's still clicking.
You see an Xbox 360 whiz by, you hear a headshot echo as it connects with the skull of another
gamer, like it's going crazy.
And then you guys see a bunch of monitors falling.
All of you roll dexterity check to see how you do on dodging this shit.
Holy shit.
Oh no, eight.
Okay.
17, yeah!
Guys, we beat it!
Yeah!
Patrick Yoda, an Xbox falls on you,
and you're going to be moving slower as you try to run away from this cave,
and also you have to get this Xbox off of you.
It's just like a very big Xbox that is too big for Patrick Yoda.
A blowtoss, you just get knocked in the head by a Wavebird controller.
Ray William Johnson, you find a way to just deftly move ahead,
head and now you're kind of further ahead in the cave
carrying Sullivan and the penguin Patrick Yoda. How are
you going to get this Xbox off to you the force? Yeah, you
can sort of blast it off of you using the force. Yeah. That's
very easy because it's a tiny thing. so you're able to do
that and move ahead your head's kind of ringing a bit as this
happens though. Okay. Yeah blow toss. You're able to catch up
though fairly easily and as you move out of this waterfall
part of the cave the floor beneath you collapses all of
roll
surprised you as you fell to the ground back into the labyrinth where Gaben was.
Gaben is now just spinning in place and just going
"Bah, bah, bah, bah, bah, bah" like freaking out.
You see the lava and the slime from before and like the acid, the sand
are just like sort of like shifting around. This is almost like a tilt-a-world
effect. So yeah, lava is like coming at you guys.
You're able to get around most of it. At this point, your combined damage
and
like a giant dome up there, the elevator is fucking not working.
How are you gonna scale the walls, how are you gonna get out of here?
What's your plan?
How tall is the wall?
I pressed the long button on my keyboard.
Tall is like 50 feet.
I jump on Sullivan's back because he's a frog.
And I say...
Jump, froggy, jump!
I can't, I'm not good at jumping, I was never good at jumping!
You're a fucking frog for Christ's sake, jump me out of here!
i must say excuse for a frog i know
i've been told this before right well i throw sullivan up the wall
i said
okay it that you're you're gonna try to a longboard thing we get ready with the
night i a hit the white button on my hoverboard so everyone can get on it
okay yeah i like that it just gets really wide
uh...
you have to i think it's a role in a place like to try to catch all of them
of
- Yeah, go for it. I'll let you try. - 40 feet is pretty much quite a bit, right?
- It's pretty hard. Let's see what you do.
- Nope. - Five.
- Yeah. - All right.
- Just like it's tossed like 15 feet.
He takes... - No, no, we catch him. We catch him!
- I'll let Blowtoss roll an Athletics check to see if he can catch Sullivan.
- He kills Sullivan again. - 11.
- Just not enough, man. He just tossed him.
Like...
- Okay, he only takes two damage this time. He's okay.
But yeah, you just tried, you just both missed catching him completely.
In my brain, I'm coming up, my character's coming up with like a new sport when I get through all of this.
Where someone is like a ball involved.
Yeah.
But yeah, so I'll let you try to fly up with the hoverboard, Patrick Yoda.
As you do though, it's sort of like a bullet hell as rocks are falling down.
all
animal handling and I got an A.
Okay, yeah, you are getting like knocked back a little bit.
You guys take like five more damage from that.
You can try again though to get up there.
I'll let you try that again,
or you guys can come up with something else.
- How high up are we on the longboard right now?
- Yeah, you guys are about 20 feet.
You have got to teleport the rest of the 30 feet.
- Okay, I teleport the rest of the 30 feet.
- Hey, it's not a long, it's a wide hoverboard.
It's not a longboard.
- I teleport the remaining 30 feet.
- You teleport, you all manage to grab the ledge
right when you appear and climb up.
That was a good move. That was a good move, Blotas.
Blotas is able to teleport you all up.
And you're back over in the second room now.
You're back on top of the building.
I love that we get to see all the old stuff we drew on the map too.
We wrote coins with a heart on this one.
Yeah, you're able to...
Oh wait, no, that said cousins.
Oh.
Yeah, you're able to like run and like to like look like aim for the bushes kind of thing
jump off these these like weird buildings what you see are now all the apartments inside
are destroyed you see some of the gamers have like their heads caved in from the things
collapsing around them you look beyond you pass the river and you just see that like it
is
the front entrance of the cave thoroughly beaten up and you appear at the entrance
and the screen is getting fucking crazy
you just have to take screenshots so that we can give these to people so they
They could know why I stop in the middle of what I'm saying to say stop doing that
So you guys now like sort of tumble outside the cave
You're you're all very bruised battered you made it through though you didn't fail too many times
But you lift your head up to notice that
that
Oh yeah, look at the map.
Oh, we were in there for too long, weren't we?
Our pass expired.
Fuck!
Oh no.
Mm-hmm.
And, uh, you see, uh, uh, uh, the King Gad.
And he says, "You abused my trust, and now this cave is destroyed and your pass expired?"
Um...
"It was Pennsylvania Gym."
Yeah.
"Pennsylvania Gym did all of this, I swear!"
you're under arrest.
- Okay, we did a couple of the--
- Literally, literally hook up the lie detector to us.
It was Pennsylvania Jim who made us take too long
and destroyed the cave.
- Here, you have to take the lie detector test first.
Put this wire in the back of your head.
(laughing)
- You see-- - We gotta test it.
- The wires, hissing wire things
are now like kind of crushed by the rock.
You hear them like hiss and you turn your head over
and you see three mopeds unattended.
Pssst.
- I think we should use the mopeds.
- I say as loud as I can, what mopeds?
- They turn their heads over and see the unattended mopeds
and they start to make a move.
- I just book it towards them.
- Yeah, me too.
- Okay, you guys get on the mopeds.
These are all the mopeds, the Walmart kind of,
they're a Walmart vehicles, they're mopeds.
There's only, they only go max 30 miles an hour
because they don't want anyone's stomach to get hurt.
But you guys are able to start going
and you hear the like Ken Bone cops are coming up behind you
and you're riding down this crazy mountain,
which leads us into our chase sequence.
- Wait, whose moped is Sullivan on?
- I was gonna let you guys decide.
I was gonna let you guys decide.
Okay, I tie him to the back of my moped like when married people tie cans to the back of their car.
This is gonna die. He's gonna die.
I do that first and then I put him on my moped.
Alright, we're done with it? You wanna say a cool line at the end or no?
Let the chase begin.
Why don't you say it instead?
Uh...
Clean take.
Let the chase...
What?
Hold on.
I kind of messed it up anyway.
I had like a weird crack in my voice.
Are you ready?
Let the chase...
Chase...
Begin!
There it is.
Cool.
I'm sorry.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
I'm sorry.
[LAUGHTER]
[music]
[MUSIC]