"Last time on Gun City, the Temple of Tepenguin of Doom, our heroes went for drinks at the
popular Gadsville bar, the Gadfly, where they celebrated, along with friends Rex and Marie,
their victory in the arena, the Octagon, and their assurance to a no-hassle visitation
of the land caves, where they will find the next clue to discovering the Temple of Tepenguin
of doom in order to obtain the infamous N-word pass.
Make sure we got all of it.
Ray William Johnson robbed, unrobbed, and then sort of re-robbed the establishment, while
Patrick Yoda played hot scotch and vomited all over himself.
Lotus Piss absolutely crushed with a tight five that involved calling everyone frogs,
and later Marie gave them a strange amulet from Leo, a blank DVD with a string running
through the center like a necklace. After a night of merriment our gang headed back to the that's
what she said inn where they locked the owner of the establishment inside of a supply closet
and slept in the arcade. Ray William Johnson explored his feminine side and the boys reignited
the once lauded profession of arcade repairman. The next day our heroes headed back to the gateway
Gad Cow, where they were let in with no issue by beautiful Simon, the Gads' attendant, who
led them straight into the Gad throne room in the hollowed out cow.
Despite deep suspicions, Baby Gad kept his word, and goo goo gah gahed his daddy into
allowing the boys to have a one hour pass into the land caves.
Approaching the caves, Ray William Johnson almost killed Sullivan the Frog by throwing
him directly into a pile of deadly hissing wires.
where he immediately lost a lot of blood and passed out.
Thanks to a lucky roll, and because I am a generous DM,
Sullivan does not remember this happening.
Patrick Yoda made quick work of the hissing snakes
with a clever use of his foreskin,
and the boys made it into the cave.
The cave entrance was filled with runes, a DDR pad, NES controller, an old PC...
I don't really want to talk about this part.
I'm still reeling a bit.
I feel like perhaps I've become less of a DM in the eyes of the listener.
I'll do everything in my power to win you back, and I'm sorry.
So now they're on a raft that looks like the ship from Mass Effect with a little gamer creature
in tow, attempting to avoid what strange traps lie ahead left by the ancient Tamagotchi civilization
and vicious gamers alike.
So yeah, you guys are inside of the Land Cave, where the gamers have sort of colonized this
space that once belonged to the Tamagotchi civilization.
And you're on this raft that looks like the Mass Effect ship after something weird that
Caleb did earlier in the game.
And so now you're on this river of Mountain Dew.
You're on this raft in the sea of Mountain Dew, Baja Blast.
As you float casually down this cave, it's almost completely dark for most of the ride
and dead quiet, I called it.
You can hear the occasional Falmer noise that the gamers make, the "Hrrr" in the distance
and the sound of controllers being thrown against the walls.
And there's a lot of rolling going on.
So okay, cool.
You're Michael Dangerous now again.
I should not get distracted.
I have to not get distracted.
Yeah, so in Sound of Controllers being thrown against a wall,
you pass by a number of hovels and strange carvings on the walls,
like sort of more of that the Tamagotchi lore, along with,
you know, stuff being smeared with gamer crud.
There's bats and things that are adjacent to bats and,
you know, they sail past hissing and but now on your left as you sort of come
into a bit of a larger opening in this weird windy Mountain Dew Cave River.
There's like, I started talking about this towards the end of the last session,
but there's like three kind of small apartment complexes that are kind of on
your left where the gamers are gaming, masturbating, and generally being foul
things. The little gamer that is with you tells you, Patrick, you gotta go.
And which basically means, you know, this is where the recently turned gamers live.
So gamers who left civilization to go join the gaming, the gaming, you know, clan.
And and so they're they some of them almost look normal still, like they haven't completely turned into Falmer.
You know, they still have their eyes.
They still like don't have totally blue skin, but they have a lot to prove to be given access to better games like Mario.
Yeah, I say
Which translates to what the fuck is he saying
So you you okay, you're just being deliberately obtuse. Yeah, so he says - he says also
Which means like stay silent. We have to be quiet as you float down this river
However, it seems you know, he doesn't say this but like he says we have to be quiet
He said earlier like, you know, my big brothers aren't as you know, friendly to strangers as I am
but
Essentially he's saying is that we have to you have to proceed with caution
but it also seems like before you guys were kind of drifting down the river in this raft, but this is basically kind of like
Where the it becomes still waters, right?
This is where you would dock to go into your apartment complex inside of the massive gamer cave
So it's - you have to try to find a way to paddle across safely without
alarming this like giant building filled with gamers these like
three sort of like
Like small apartment buildings that have gamers in them
So yeah
Mmm, what's happening?
Let me check my inventory
See if I have a paddle. I
Have I have two pipes we use those as paddles. That's a good idea. Can I use my sword as a paddle?
Yeah, you can use the USB blade as a paddle - okay. I hop to the front and I just start I start fucking
Paddling away, dude. Okay, so I
Will I will remind you that he said to that you should probably try to be quiet
Are you gonna try or are you just gonna go? I just want to let you know in case you didn't remember
Yeah, I'm just gonna go
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, I'd be quiet. What are you doing? You're killed Sullivan wait
I tie up I tie up
You guys my character or you?
Characters because I'm gonna paddle right? I've had a lot of hard as I forgot that friendship means nothing. That's true. That's a good point Caleb
I completely forgot about that
it
I'm
a
- Okay. I was trying to figure, I was trying to unfriend you.
- So, there it is. Everybody.
- You already had a friend request from, oh that's...
I got a friend request from Nick Disney.
- Nice, that's great.
I'm gonna try and, so before Cameron can tie me up,
I jump to the front and I go Winklevoss twins on the...
- Before he can do that, I tie him up.
- So, there are ways to resolve these things in the game, yeah.
Caleb, how about you just do a quiet row?
Can we just do rock, paper, scissors for once?
No, I'm gonna use my strengths to overpower you.
I'm gonna use strength and I'm gonna wrestle you.
I yield.
Okay, I tie you up.
Yeah, I don't just tie you up.
You can't, people are gonna hear that.
I quietly place him into the water and drown.
(laughing)
Okay.
You shouldn't have yielded.
Wow.
So I don't put him in the okay.
You can't take back.
I let I put his I put his feet and I put his toes in the water.
That's cold.
Okay.
Yeah, I want to start to hear what is happening now.
Okay, so I go over to start wrestling with Ray William Johnson and he just
instantly goes limp.
And I use I give up why go on I use my cords that are coming out of his body
to tie him up.
This is fine.
and then i said i'm on the edge of the
boat or the ship or whatever it is a night
dangles toes into the water do you know if you're still here do self check while
you're
tying up your friend
i'm a funny story with my own eyes yeah you do it pretty what do you do
i'm a couple of my hands and i start drinking the water
okay yet is like mountain dew about our last
well
does it heal you randomly
you know it randomly
taste like mountain dew but i have said
it's pretty rare and does not need to heal you in real life yes
but
here in a lot of
here a lot of nonsense and sometimes i have some it turns over
i mean you're you're yes so so so can't we're gonna sit here until cable
apologizes
well we're gonna be a role in that there is come on we got a little
or you know it's our business your game so that we gotta go
I'm sure he's sorry, you know.
Are you sure?
I'm...
I tape his mouth.
Don't do an inside check.
I'm pretty sure though that you're sorry.
Nope.
Okay, yeah, so you can start paddling with the pipes.
I would say roll...
Let's do athletics first to see how well you do it.
It's pretty hard to paddle with, like, pipes,
but let's see what you can do.
25. That's really good. Yeah. So you're able to do this pretty easily, but now let's also have you roll stealth for while you're doing this.
11. That's not so good.
I rolled stealth too.
So here's what we can, I'm going to play out a little bit of what happens and then you'll have opportunities to potentially do something.
What happens is that you get decently, like, with that 25, even though you were only like an 11 on stealth,
you still got pretty far just like right away without being noticed.
And with that 11, you start to hear inside of the apartment complex, you see a light turn on in one of the windows,
and you see one of them start to look out the window.
so this is your opportunity if there's something you have in mind that you can
do
i would say like you would all kind of be aware of that like
uh... load house wasn't quite quiet enough i act like a statue
who have kept
you continue to stay still yeah
uh... i'd i laid down
how how do you business
is this like
this is shaped it's a raft that shaped like the mass effect yeah it's it's just
like a a flat raft
okay
- Yeah, let's jump off the raft,
like slip into the water and hold our breath underneath.
So it looks like we're going to roll out here.
- Yeah, could I do that?
- Yeah, I'll give you all a chance to do that.
- Can I take Caleb with me?
Can I get a, so he doesn't get spotted either?
- Yeah, you'll have a slight penalty
just 'cause you're carrying somebody.
- Yeah, yeah, but hey, I'll do it for my friend.
- All right, so this is still about another thing.
- About what? - So what do we roll?
- So everyone I would say is gonna roll still.
So, Sullivan, the Baby Gamer, all of them.
Sullivan as well.
Oh, I have a character sheet for him now.
- Where was that roll, Cameron? - I got 8.
- Oh, where's that roll earlier? - More statuette, whatever.
- What? - Where's that roll earlier?
- You got a 22. - I got so many good...
I got good... My first two rolls were really good.
You should have tried it if you don't want my rolls.
I did. I got a 16.
Okay, let's go, Sullivan. Go, Sullivan.
- How did he do? - He got 12.
He did okay.
So yeah, you all sort of hop into the water pretty stealthily.
Baby Gamer does fine himself, the little gamer.
And though obviously with that eight,
even though Cameron you're doing pretty well, or Bloodtust you're doing pretty well,
there's some activity that that one in the window sort of starts to notice that
and looks a little bit closer.
um and uh Sullivan also is is is drawing their attention it's sort of in line with you so you see one of them you see it look in the window and when you see the lights go off in that window again and you see the baby givers are which is basing run I mean swim swim um so I untie I untie Caleb yeah I just
You float face down when you're trying to convince your brother at the pool that you're dead.
[laughter]
And I'm just kind of holding my breath, hoping somebody does something.
Yeah, so you see that gamer rush away, and now that that other little gamer has screamed.
I'm going to have all of you guys do just a--
We're going to just basically do your--
much of your movement speed. So like just do everyone move up like I guess like half of
like it's going to look like 30 feet like not 30 feet though like go go like 15. Everyone
like go up like you're swimming in the direction like you're trying to get out of there. At
this point the the the baby is sort of like running up on here and jumping back into the
the water and the little gamer I should say.
And you look up now, you hear a noise, you hear more footsteps and like as they climb
and you see them and you start to see their heads, all of them poking their little heads
over the roof.
It's like kind of this eerie sight as you're looking up and seeing them.
It looks kind of very German expressionist-y.
And then you see their heads all disappear.
and then you hear...
[hissing]
Oh my god, they got a Hitachi wand!
[laughter]
Yeah, you hear one of them come,
and then you hear...
which, I don't want to know what that sounds like, folks, you know?
And, uh, you...
you also start to see something,
like, kind of like, start to form
on top, like a, of, like,
Voltron-y, like,
uh, a massive
metal crane.
*sigh*
that is like just with the quickness shooting down to fucking like scoop you the fuck up
um with like an insane like level of speed it's like and you start to look you also see
in that same instant like all the gamers like in the windows basically it looks like they're
all playing a crane game um in sync with one another um so all of you roll dexterity saving
throw. 15. 23. 9. Okay, and now I gotta do for my main man Sully. Sully, what up? Oh,
it's not the right one, but it would have been whatever that is anyway, because it's
just he has zero on everything. And then he's the most average character ever. And then...
say that. Sorry. And then, uh, I'm really sorry about that. The baby gamer. Uh, um, that's
cool. This is very cool. Actually. Patrick Yoda, Cameron or blow toss piss and the baby
gamer. All of you are able to sort of deftly get out of the way of this crane and me too.
And Ray William Johnson. I forgot to mention Ray William Johnson. Ray William Johnson is
and
top of the roof where all of the the guys are all of those gamers are who are
waiting for who are there thank you yeah and you see that they haven't like
they're not doing anything two of them are just standing in front of like the
door to get down from the roof but the rest of them are still focusing on
trying to win the game to win this crane game in their minds but it's it's like a
as you guys land and you take from that landing
oh no no damage not too much zero damage
I only have 10 health
I chose to game that one night
I'm so smart at this game
I'm gonna play dead
ok yeah immediately
roll performance
ok I'm gonna stick my tongue out
I really quickly grab a sharpie and draw x's on my eyes
is
amazing performer. Sullivan is like NOOOOOO! My talent is wasted in this one moment.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
with
killing it there's tapping into something and being a demon where or
also maybe like you're literally shutting down like you could go into
sleep mode because your computer I think it was the shit in my pants personally
shit in your pants yeah brother yeah yeah so I'm see I see him playing dead on the
top of the roof and I'm like reconsidering everything like I'm like I
never should have tied him up this is all my fault I'm doing a backstroke and
I'm just drinking the water.
[laughter]
So you can all move up, you know, another like 15 feet on this map,
and the crane is going to try to get you again.
Hmm.
Alright.
Is there anything, um...
Or yeah, I mean, there's other stuff you can do. That's like...
Yeah, is there any way that we could like, uh, just kill all of them at once?
Yeah, we have a nuclear bomb.
Yeah.
i mean you could check your inventory i don't think i did uh... don't add into
your inventory now
i'm look i'm staring at your inventory i think i'm missing some stuff in my
inventory
i don't think that's true
stop i'd see what you're doing i can see what you're doing what if i okay well
what if i put one hundred dollars in the crane
yeah i have one dollar to
we could put a hundred one dollars in the crane with a note that says this is to
to
both
in
at pockets i guess to get out your hundred dollars your sticky wet pockets
and this crane just fuckin
scoops you both up and a little gamer
and you all go on the roof
there was a way you get past the guys are
you just doing okay but yet now you're on the roof
uh...
or a jump off the roof back into the
manned air
role a uh...
because it was gonna happen there's a goal line of them in front of you
so you can try to like run through the right try to run them down
uh... wait i can i can speak their language
yeah so if you want to try that you can to okay
also also i guess both of you role
inside to see if you think really on johnson's dead
or if you can tell the six eighteen
okay at that you can you can probably tell the rewinding of the income i'm
poking in with my hoagie
the classic frank i'm still not moving to them so that the uh... but i'm not
hospice you are pretty sure he's dead
yeah
i say i don't move it don't uh... be dead if you get a
i continue to be dead because it is a strong resolve and i'm gay
uh...
but he sees all of this still like trying to be dead he's just like shivering
crying
the yes so there is uh... they're all
wind up on the roof
so
I go up like Chris Pratt in talking to the Raptors in Jurassic World and I have my hands out
And you're clicking
Do you do any bloopers too since like
He's anything funny and that says yeah, what did all that say it said I love you
to
completely lost. Okay let me try again. That was my blooper take. Should I just roll persuasion?
And then yeah they nod when you say let me try again that was my blooper take. They get that.
You said something about their mothers, their brood mother, you know, or about Zoe Quinn
that made them all really angry.
Wait, I've got an idea.
This is my fight song!
Take back my life song!
The crane whips around and just like opens its maw and pushes all of you off the roof
off the other side.
What about me?
Oh no.
You too because you're just caught up in the scoop but you're just like dead.
I thought that they would freak out because I sang the feminist song.
Yeah, they're, they, and as you guys, you guys are basically falling now like, like
tens of feet probably.
Ugh.
And uh.
to
start to see some weird glowing neon below you, you can't quite make it out, and you
crash land onto something really, just really freaking out there.
Sullivan, the baby gamer, all of you.
So let me get all of you in here.
One second, I also have to think where...
Do we take damage?
Oh yeah, no, we're going to resolve all that fun stuff.
not
now you can't feel like the kid who has the teacher what about the homework okay
don't remind him about damage
and he would have forgotten
i'm getting your set about it so
and it looks like kind of complete
uh... blackness around you
uh... you can all kind of c in front of one another and then your eyes
uh... begin to adjust
somewhat slowly
so let me uh...
you can you see now a little bit more
near
yes so what i'm doing in the map by the way it's all these
to all you uh... uh... listeners out there isn't doing a fog of war
setting on roll twenty
'cause they're in this very dark area
and slowly to reveal the map to them as they walk around
uh...
uh... merit so someone's trying to write on top of part of the matter of the
the
a weird black stone in front of you. You can see that there.
And then also there's a door and some white stone on the other side of you. You're in the
hallway it looks like. And below you is a strong clear glass floor. And below it is
an endless sea of stars oozing and flowing through. It looks kind of like
When you clip through a level in an Unreal game,
and you see like the sea level below it because the devs leave that in,
that's basically what it looks like below you.
You don't really know where you are except that you
are actually on top of something right now on the map. There's also a pedestal in
front of you, and it has like sort of four
little spokes in it. They look like it has these like sort of
gems in them, but they're like almost sucked of their light, completely dull.
Hmm.
We see something weird.
Can I touch the pedestal?
Yeah.
I touched it.
Yeah, you touch it.
Nothing too odd about it.
As you look at sort of the four gems, you see that each of them are like, one of them
has like, like a symbol on it that looks like sort of like swirling sand.
of them has like a volcano, one of them has like a what looks like a like a
like a glacier, and another one has what looks like some sort of like a like a
toxin right like a you know triangle with like a skull in it in each of the
four gems. It's Pokemon! I continue to play dead. I solved enough puzzles in this
fucking dungeon. Oh yeah. Puzzles. Puzzles. It's called a puzzle. Also, uh, oh yeah, you
guys have to take some damage. Damn it, I was hoping you would forget about it. I mean,
I'm gonna be generous since they tossed you down here for a reason. Just kill me. Oh, you're
dead, for sure. Yes. Yeah, that's a solid 11 damage to all of you. Yep, I'm dead. Yeah,
I'm
like like it's like a black giant slab of stone it's like a wall that that you
could see like the edges of it glowing almost so that you can actually make it
out among the blackness and then you see a wall in front of you and then like
metal doors that has like a symbol on it that matches the symbol on the pedestal
like the symbols on the pedestal so can I heal them before anything yeah
Absolutely. Okay. I'm gonna use my four skin. You're gonna use your four skin. Yeah, so you create this massive
Foreskin that can heal people. So that's another three
Techno slime points for you. Okay that you used so you should be
This should be actually at um, she used it already. It should be at seven
It's um, yeah, and so roll you can roll now the
roll 1d 10
for
a
play dead. Okay, roll a performance check again this time. Because you have to sort of replay
dead. 21. Very good! Everyone's pretty sure you're dead. Yeah. Well, since he's dead,
I guess he won't be needing anything in his inventory. I'm dead, brother. I don't care.
I mean, go ahead.
You're not fooling me into waking up.
I'm going to take something.
I guess he won't mind if I tickle him since he's dead.
You're like a little hum for my body as I'm like already kind of laughing.
Yeah, roll a constitution saving throw.
Ray William Johnson.
Let's see, constitution.
11.
Yeah, and Blotas, roll a slide.
i guess
slight of hand i guess the tickling
nine
them
you know
uh... he's able to sort of withstand uh... you're tickling you still hear
that low hum though so you know he's you know he's fucking awake like you know
he's been
but he's not able to use burst out laughing
uh...
well i guess he doesn't want a ray william johnson snack after all
wait what?
do you seriously have a ray william johnson snack?
no
where am i?
you look at your passes by the way and it says forty minutes on it
is this bones to the right of us on the ground?
this is so weird. can i take the bones into my inventory?
you have to be good take as many as you can carry
uh... because i i i have uh...
i have a lizard skin in my inventory still so i'm planning to make a guy
just want to have that
uh... the last i just need me
the last thing i remember was
was fucking blow tosses mom
that didn't matter i did not remember i remember doing that no it happened
and i think that
yeah i don't remember that
i think it happened
you see the little gamer he turns to you patrick you know that
uh... he says basically uh...
this is the uh... this is the
the lap the lab rentals
the lab with the of gamers do
we have to get out of here we have to get out of here he's coming for us
essay
and i think that i think that i had been
I
And that means and somebody get a fucking translator or something
Fuck this guy's been saying to me this whole time the jet do the gems come out of the pedestal
Yeah, they do actually good instinct. I take all four. No, I asked so I already have them
Okay, um rats
So roll a perception check
by the way blow toss
10 never everyone can roll it actually that's fair
Oh my god a 22. It starts with a P. I'm extremely good at. Okay. Yeah, pooping. Pussy. Pussy being.
Ray William Johnson. Mm-hmm. You could hear from the south a...
a like something approaching I think there's something approaching I will
tell you that every action you take I'm counting towards this thing's movement
what the hell does that mean that means I'm I am basically looking at all the
stuff you you do and try to figure out how long it probably takes and then this
thing is moving okay what are the different doors that are around us there
are no doors around you I thought you said there was no sorry there's one door
around you there's one door in front of you it's like this metal door what
symbol does it have it's like over here it has the four symbols of all four of
them the stones yeah all right let's go through the door wait did we take the
stones? Yeah. You can't open the door. Can I hold one? Yeah, I'm guessing that this is a puzzle.
I give Patrick the toxic stone. I put it in my mouth because he's toxic. Wait, honestly,
what if all of us have to hold a different stone? That's what I've been thinking. There's four
stones. Yeah. And there's four of us. Okay, I give the stones a round. What are the colors again?
it's and
poison
volcano and ice i think
yeah there's no colors in them right now can totally volcano
yeah you take volcano all take
uh... ice 'cause i'm cool
and i'll get sullivan said kiss
you know you know
noise is getting louder
removed johnson
uh... that was not an action
handing out a little bit of a lot of the night
I think it's getting louder though, because you believe it's getting louder.
And, uh, yeah, so, so, uh, you, the door, the stones in the door, it's not like a thing where you can slot it in, it doesn't look like, you know.
Yeah.
If you investigate the stones, you guys can probably see something just because I was gonna say you're basically are investigating it
So I'd want you to just roll it roll investigation to see if you you
At this point because you're kind of 18 17. It's all very
Pretty good 15. Yeah, that's all pretty good
Wow, okay
Blowtoss as you hand out the stones
To to everyone
They start to, they have like a diff, they start to glow a little bit with the color.
But, you notice, what stone do you have by the way, Blotas?
I have the ice one.
Okay.
As you walk towards, and Patrick Yoda and Ray William Johnson, you kind of all notice this, but from the stones.
As you walk towards Ray William Johnson to hand him the lava stone,
You notice your ice stone, the faint, the faintest blue that is glowing in it,
like ice blue that's glowing in it, starts to die out.
And so does the faintest red of the lava stone.
And when you walk back to give a hand to something to Patrick Yoda,
it starts to glow brighter again, those two.
But Patrick Yoda's, the, what Patrick Yoda, which one did you get?
I had poison.
Yeah.
Yours, you notice that yours, if you move to your character's, when we're looking at
the screen, to your right, it glows a bit brighter.
And to your left it gets dimmer.
So lava, ice, glows brighter as you go to your left.
Poison and sand seem to glow brighter when you go to your right.
Okay, so me and Sullivan are going to go to the right.
Yeah, I mean ray william johnson go to the left
Okay. All right. Yeah move your characters where you want to move them and just yeah, let me be cautious. But okay, cool
Now that's fine where you were patch go. No, that's one. That wasn't I was in the door
All right. Okay, and let me uh reveal a little bit more of the map to you. Oh
Okay, I'm starting to see stuff
Yeah
So as you're moving through the neon glowing of those stones you start to see them more
uh... you see purple ones you see green one you see white one you see a bit of a
red one so then and uh...
patrick you know that
you also now
solvent in patrick you know that
you hear the something now
i hear something that it's quieter for you it's quiet it for me
no known that's why
and spider for her family dot sand blowtoss this
but it's louder for you and it's louder for me actually
And so you, you're, um, but yeah, so, uh, and,
and the stone is glowing brighter. The, the, the,
the stone that's glowing brighter now is the, uh, sand one,
the poison one isn't glowing as bright, but it's,
it's glowing a little bit brighter, but not as bright as the sand.
One is glown. Um,
same for you blow toss and Ray William Johnson,
but the ice one is glowing brighter. Not as much as the lava one.
Okay. I'm going to run over to the red, the little bit of red that I see.
I'm gonna go like over over here. I feel like it's a safe bet with lava. Okay.
Oh this is getting tough. Okay. I see hair. From the bottom of the fog of war. Is that Gabe Newell?
That was gonna be my guess too. Yeah. Wait can I... can me and Sullivan hide behind this?
I'd
shadows
this
just
fact i think it's
making your own
group is a little
uh...
and it's like this hero in case it looks like the old woman from uh...
uh... spirited away
this life massive ghoulish face
start to come out of the shadows
uh... really johnson's pressure is you're running by to go to that red area like
across the door
you exceed on your right
like you know your periphery
and stand patrick you know that you see it obviously in just dash behind this
uh...
and as you begin to see this space
you hear a familiar to
uh...
that
you would recognize as the
pac-man
game star
and then of course you hear
but uh... but uh... but uh... but uh... but uh... as as i was saying
is approaching closer to you
uh...
uh... quite a bit i think that i need to jim
and it makes me eat gabe newell
he's a huge if i need it's like the big dot impact man
uh... it does not do that if you need it okay it's not about that i would you
could be a little bit of half will figure it out together
as a group in the room now and i'm gonna get a greater that
can the room get brighter now that i was gonna say the room does get a bit
brighter now
uh... and you start to hear
the sounds of
and you see the baby gamer like the little game early looking around
uh... and everything
uh... and you see these like lights flooding in
you see these massive we're whales below
like this weird news
and you look up and you can see
scores of of will of gamers
having a land party watching you all in this maze
uh... while they play halo at the same time
uh...
are they like they're like directly above us or are they on like balconies?
they're like directly above you watching you from below. like through like glass? yeah
it's like a dome
yeah
okay so obviously the volcano thing is in the the left corner so that one i'm
closest to poison
right now so should i
how many
So yeah, we're gonna we're gonna we're gonna map that out. So
basically you're going to be similar to the what we were
doing before with the swimming where you move 15 feet.
Gabe moves 15 feet.
If you come into contact with Gabe, there's a chance that you
could get hurt pretty fucking bad and we'll roll for that when
that happens.
So each time each of you moves 15 feet is when Gabe will move
do his movement
uh...
i will tell you now
that's putting up was actually a pretty good idea uh... that was i was like
pretty surprised i was like
is that i you guys are sick together uh... because yet only one game in
there's
five of you little ghosts
uh... caleb
yes sir i think you want to the wrong place second c love the right here and
- No shit, I head towards that lava.
- I'm just telling you.
- Okay, so I think sand is top right,
poison bottom right, lava bottom left, and ice top left.
- I think ice might be in Gabe's mouth.
- When I, I'll go there then.
When I put this, when we put this up on the Patreon,
I'm also gonna include the map
so everyone can follow along at home.
Because it's, it's, yeah, and bless you as well, Caleb.
so uh... yeah but i won't let one now
but uh... c_n_n_ up to hopefully this is making sense that you are basically
there in a giant okay so i'm i'm gonna move fifteen feet this way
patrick you know you're gonna tell solvin where you want him to go
uh...
or would you want someone to follow you
left to protect him now he's got low health
should what do you guys think i should issue that protects all of inner
uh... welcome
the
I have a feeling none of us are going to be able to kill Gabe.
That's just the vibe I get from this.
So, I'm going to push.
It's better to just get to the corners.
So, Sullivan goes here and then I go here.
You can move 15, Patrick.
Well, Sullivan's not moving.
We're just running at the same time.
I'm going here.
And then Sullivan's going to go up here.
Perfect, yeah.
Okay, so, Patrick Yoda, you're going to go a bit more south.
a bit more south. Sullivan's gonna go where he is now. So a little bit more north towards
the sand. So you're on sort of that tail of where that whale is. And Blotas, where are
you gonna go? And then the little gamer is gonna do his, the little gamer is gonna just
dart up towards the sand as well. Basically, sort of understanding instinctually that Sullivan
is the weak link here, and maybe he can help.
I'm going here.
Okay, cool.
So, um, now...
I'm gonna do a little bit of secret rolling.
How about you do some public rolling?
He's disappeared back into the shadows, as far as you can tell.
Ice cream.
[laughter]
You can't get ice cream right now.
[mimics buzzer]
The rest of you, let's reveal a little bit more of the map.
right of nice
cameras right there
resolve them
for you patrick you know that you can do the map isn't revealed a little anymore
for you really
while in that
uh... just cuz of where you are you have some of the map arty reviled the second
has been for you every william johnson
uh... in a little gamer has a bit more than that the revealed
uh... which should help
so you guys are like dashing through you see all these glowing neon like bricks
around you, you hear the thumping of Gabe, you hear the like "WAAA" from above of the
gamers, as this is sort of like this ongoing sort of event, this Pac-Man sort of thing.
Now it's your turn to go again, everyone. You guys can move again.
Okay. I move 15 feet.
Yeah, I move 15 feet. Towards my destination.
i move into the corner with the ice
okay we're gonna resolve that too
solomon is gonna go
we are like i'm only five feet away from the uh...
the poison center
can i just throw the thing or do i have to hold it
so uh... yet let's let's talk this through so
uh...
as you sort of can start to see it's it's the pedestal you were able to see a
a little bit beyond the corner because you can see it's a little bit behind a wall Patrick
Yoda, but you could see like past like the neon green.
Yes, you approach this sort of like acidy thing.
I also want to note sort of what you guys are experiencing
like around you so Patrick Yoda
or I should say actually start with let's start with a blowtoss
piss because you're right on top of the ice
as you like continue to walk like goosebumps form on your skin.
you know, you begin to see your breath like there's just like sharp cool wind like your teeth begin to chatter like the air is frigid like and now it's like snowing on top of you.
So like where you kind of went into like a little biome and you see in this large frozen pond there now that you're on top of this ice.
We're going to have you roll an athletics check.
the
I'll let that that's a good argument roll again. You can roll. I think that's totally for 22. Yeah
You're able to hold your ground. This is a you're who you've were you're from yeah, whoo-hoo bill
This you've been wearing ice skates - yeah, you've been I have been the entire campaign
Yeah, you've been on a lot of ice. This is the slipperiest ice you've ever like been on but you're able to hold your ground
very easily
despite that. Ray William Johnson, you also feel because you're sort of in the area of the cold,
you feel a little bit of the cold. When you were by that red, you felt a little bit of like an arid
climate. You know, you felt like you could kind of hear the sounds of desert sand, like whipping
around you. Patrick Yoda, and you're because you're approaching this acid area. It's like,
it's like stinky. Yeah, yes, exactly. Like it was like a sizzling sound. You can hear like
bubbling sizzling nastiness you could you know you could see yes very good
yes sort of like they go Bob but if it was like dark day go so so suck a buck
about where I'm from yeah yeah a skeleton you could see like skeleton and bodies
around you they're like half this all this is all making sense yeah cuz
William Johnson's a demon so he's from lava and Sullivan's a frog so he's from
the desert makes perfect sense.
Yeah.
Yeah, and like the smell of rotten flesh sort of like you can smell
that and then something worse and also rotten your uvula like a
speed bag.
You want to vomit so bad.
It's done enough of that already fucking awful.
Your eyes start to sting a little bit.
It's like this horrible acid swamp and solving the frog is in
this like kind of desert area.
he's like the air is kind of dry and he's like a little bit uh a little bit uh
beswept by it i can smell the acid corner just a little bit from where i am
i'm like jesus christ badger gilda what you doing over there
oh my god damn nothing and now that you've all moved
can i do something in addition to moving yeah you can do an action for sure
now you're gonna i want to try i want to i want to see if i can shoot i want to
to see if I can break the glass dome.
It got me Patrick.
You want to see if you can break the glass dome above you?
Yeah.
Okay, yeah, do an attack roll.
And shoot it I guess?
You're right, you're trying to shoot it.
Yeah, with my gun.
14.
Okay.
You shoot it and 14's not really enough.
It's like pretty, it's like tough.
It's like, it's like the floor below you.
So it's not, it's not unbreakable, like there's no, it's glass, but it's like thick glass.
So a 14's like not quite gonna cut it.
But that's like your action you could do for this round of like weird tactics game we're playing.
And now, it is the Gaben's turn.
You hear him creep around the corner.
Oh and he dies, oh my god.
Moving faster. And he's like, "Cake is alive."
He's right in front of me, bro.
Epic gamer Gaben. God Gaben, epic.
He started weird man as he's approaching you ray william johnson
Luckily luckily he just took his second turn and since it's Gabe and we know he's not gonna be taking a third one. Am I right?
You solved another one of my fucking puzzles Cameron, I'm so mad about
That's right. He's gonna not do anything this turn any third turn. He won't do anything. That's right. Yeah
a
man.
Fucking cunt.
Weird man.
Fucking weirdo man.
That's what I'm gonna put on it.
Go weirdy.
Please don't piss on, don't even fictionally piss on my map.
As you're sort of approaching it, you can see that it has like a hole, like a slot for
or stop fucking making those eyes.
You know, a slot for--
- That's what I'm talking about.
- For a slit. - Ooh, a slot.
- No, we've been doing this for a while now,
and there's a lot of stuff I tolerate, but.
- I see the slot and it triples my speed towards me.
(laughing)
- Yeah, so you guys have your movement,
and you're all within range.
I think you can do a movement and an action to get it in.
and
that have to go in things after this it's over
so very have a dirty mind that you don't have a fuckin night well i was gonna put
a quarter-pound quirky and kinky and quirky i was gonna put my quarter inch
urin there
manhattan
that's great you got a criminally small dick that's right you and one-quarter
incher
she's come on
patel exactly two-quarters of an inch or
that's what you guys want to
uh... it seems like i'm gonna die
So I'm gonna play dead again.
You're gonna try to play dead again?
Yep, and I'm rolling a performance check right now and I got a crit one.
[Laughter]
So...
Yeah, what does that look like?
I'm more alive than... I accidentally take a Vyvanse and I'm just like hopping around.
Hey, you guys want to watch a movie? Let's watch a movie.
You paint a target on your stomach.
[Laughter]
Come and get me, Gabe.
That's your action. I'm gonna say you still have a chance where it's like that didn't work and you could run
Okay, so I will do that now do your and I will run
I'm about to outsmart him
Okay, so everyone else what are you doing? I go to the right of him
So
Obviously, it's an acid pool right? That's right. So
It doesn't none of I don't get any more
Like the fog doesn't clear up. Oh, sorry. Yeah, I thought I did that. Yeah, I didn't see where the pedestal is. Okay
Yes, you could see it and you could see this you could see that it's like so if I touch the acid does it hurt
me
You could try you find out. No, I'm just I'm asking
Eyeballing it you're like this would hurt me. Okay, so I get on my hoverboard, but you're green and it's green
Yeah, regardless I get on my hoverboard because this is exactly I used to skate around the swamps of Succo Focobar
Hell yeah, this is second nature to me do an athletics check. It's not too hard to pass. It's a good move
Wow
And classic classic Patrick Yoda fashion. I step on the hoverboard too soon and I just start spinning in a circle you
let's do that
the hoverboard flies away from you it is
now on like the pedestals area
it is now like it like slung out from under you kind of thing
and just like glided towards the pedestal
so now the pedestal which is on that little stone island of that lake of
acid
that's where the hoverboard is instead of with you. ok then i haven't used my movement yet
so i'm just gonna
i'm just gonna try and
get to it
you
kick off of this wall, but half of you is kind of falling into this acid now.
My toes are touching it?
Yeah, your, your, your, your, your leggies, your little leggies are.
Oh, no.
Um, so...
Would it count as a movement if while I jump I throw the thing onto the pedestal?
No, because you already kind of did the hoverboard action, so...
Okay.
Yeah, so you're, you take like 11 damage in the acid...
No!
you up as you crawl onto the stone pedestal area.
But you're there. So you can definitely put that in
like next turn you would be able to put that in. Sullivan, meanwhile,
is going to approach this sand area here.
And as he does, it of course
starts to sink. No!
And so our young man is like, "Oh God!"
but the little gamer's there to help him, right?
Mm-hmm. That's what he's there for. Okay, so Sullivan is gonna roll a
Yeah, it's really an athletics to try to or strength really a straight strength check
See if you can deal with it
Nine is pretty bad. He is sinking into this thing
He's got a couple more tries before he sinks in this quicksand. He sees like halfway down
There's like oh no my pants lose bottoms and you see the little gamer
starts
He starts bounding over to give Solven a hand.
So, next turn, Solven's going to try again, and the gamer's going to be there to assist,
give him an assist on the Strength check.
Though the gamer's also going to have to resist this quicksand now, too.
So the gamer's like...
The gamer's like running on the sand, and he's like sort of slowly sinking in with each step a little bit.
He doesn't want this to be another Artax situation, he's getting very distressed.
Um
But he's also sinking in too he actually did not do great on that athletics check
So they're both kind of sinking in but they're going to try to hoist each other out next turn
Now blow toss piss. What are you thinking? You're by this ice area. It's freaking freaking cold around you, man
Yeah, so I can move within five feet of the pedestal. Um, so i'm not right next to it
So I see i can't get the thing in from yeah
Roll another athletics check because you have to like go back more on the ice. All right
And with advantage again, because you're you're a frosty boy. Oh, you're fine five. Yeah, whatever you get you're fucking fine. All right
um
Can I toss the thing onto the pedestal?
You can try it's gonna be hard
um
Hmm, I probably won't do that then i'll probably just wait till next turn. Yeah, I could also try it
Sorry, yeah, what is what can I say? You can see that the stones are glowing now super bright like you're at the right place
All right
yours ray william johnson has gotten dimmer as you moved away obviously
uh...
on the try to shoot at the dome again just as i have an extra action
yeah go for it
fifteen
that's pretty good you start to see that it's it's it's a little bit more
it's getting something something's getting there
as the damage stack
uh... the attacks don't necessarily stack unless it's like he does like a few
impressive roles in a row but i would probably
let that stack
but uh...
But right now you can see that like he's getting somewhere the gamers aren't noticing it either
They're just rabid and shouting and gaming and pushing each other
um
meanwhile
Gaben is here
so gaben like
Like sort of like fucking like creepily like moving robotically towards you ray william johnson. Okay, so i'm being attacked by gabe newell
And yeah, he's not being attacked roll dexterity saving throw. You can't do that trick on me again
Dexterity saving throw
14 that's not very good. It's it's it's it's a it's okay
So he goes to bite you there's a couple of tiers of attack that he does. It's all mouth based
He goes to chop at you and you're able to sort of like dodge back like sort of like just jump back a little bit
mm-hmm, but as he's like
chomping down he like whips his tongue out a bit like
and just like
Licks you with this massive tongue
He's like this giant head with this tiny body and this massive tongue just like
whomps you in the chest for
Think I'm dead again. I've damage. Oh, I'm alive. Yeah, you missed the the
the
around you sink into the ground.
You see it fall into the amorphous sort of sea below you
and dissipate and you're free to move.
- Okay.
How many movements can I make now?
- It's still gonna be 15.
- Okay, I'm gonna go, let me see.
I'll go here.
- Do it.
Yeah.
Now, I'm gonna have Sullivan and the little gamer,
they're gonna try to help each other out here.
So they're both kind of halfway sunk in.
So it's a strength saving throw with advantage,
but they take a bit of a penalty.
Okay, it's not too bad though.
They managed to hold their ground.
They're like sort of holding each other up.
Like Sullivan's like, "Aah!"
The gamer's like, "Wah!"
And they're just like holding each other up,
making those sounds together in concert.
But now it is your turn, Ray William Johnson.
Gaben is in front of you.
He looks nasty, mean, nasty.
- And I'm covered in his tongue goo.
- His nasty tongue goo, yeah.
- Oh, and I hate it.
If I don't do a movement, can I do a double action?
- Yeah, I mean, you have two attacks you can do.
So if you wanna do that, you can do that.
- Okay, I think my, honestly, I feel like my best bet here
is
for
Yeah, yeah that reaches the ceiling and you start to see a bit of the glass like
Shadow, but start to fall
You have to roll dexterity saving throws as glass falls, but so does Gaben. Okay
15 that's fine. Yeah, you managed you broke the glass above you you broke the glass
Okay. Oh my god. I'm so good
So I mean not the only being on for women like you broke the glass a little bit but oh
all
the
going to happen to Gabe Newell?
No, no.
You're saying you're going to do this?
Unless he does something?
You're saying that when they crash into the glass ceiling, he's going to kill Gabe Newell?
No, I'm not saying anything
of the sort.
So, that's enough of that, right?
And you see him vanish back into the shadows.
He vanished back into the shadows
to hide for a second
and recharge, because that did enough damage to him
to have them want to go back into the shadows.
Yeah, but yeah, that was pretty smart.
You can still move too.
Were there gamers on that glass or no?
No, I mean like the gamers are like looking down on it,
but like they didn't fall through necessarily.
They like sort of saw that happen though.
So they're now a little bit more aware of like the side thing you're trying to do.
Okay, I'm gonna go over to the right. I can't see Gaben right now.
Mm-hmm. But I'm gonna move into this right here. Okay. Now, blow toss. Yeah, I'm
gonna take a step forward to get right next to the pedestal. Do I need to do
my athletics again? Cool. No, that was like five feet. Alright, yeah, then I put
the thing into the pedestal. Yeah, you see it go in there. It's it does a similar
thing. It sinks into the pedestal. You see the ice around you like like the heat. It
starts to get a bit warmer around you and then suddenly it's normal temperature.
The ice is melted away and you can walk freely through. I should also say
about you go to the smell went away too around you. Nice. Since I only move
five feet can I move ten more feet? Uh yeah yes. Okay I'm gonna move I'm gonna move like go around
the back of the pedestal to try and get away from Gabe if he comes after me. Yeah okay that was a
good move because now that Gabe has been attacked and uh done enough damage done to him that he
resets he's coming for you actually. Uh oh. Yeah now again so Patch Kiyoto what do you want to do?
the
a
room area in the middle where the ghosts usually are in pac-man but something else is in there
if Caleb goes in there will he heal because that's where the ghosts heal
yeah there will be healing in there if you go in there but you have to get in there
whoa
that's where the door is
oh shit
ok I'm gonna throw my gem to what's his name
go deep
25 feet. Yeah, athletics check. That shouldn't be too tough.
Oh, do it. Ike. And then I just fucking toss it, dude.
Athletics check, you said? Yeah, but it's not too hard. This'll be easy.
20. Ooh, perfect. That was close.
Because last time something wasn't too hard, something awful happened.
So, that's fine, though. Just beam him. Yeah, you just
knock him out cold. I throw it too well. Yeah, when someone throws you a football
the
So, uh, cool. That was your action. That was nice. You still have a movement you can do.
Move into the fucking thing with the...
What? The door's closed, dumbass. We're trying to open that door.
Open it! Go help Sullivan.
Johnson, when you look at the door, you can see now that the ice is glowing on the door,
like the ice emblem, and the acid emblem is glowing too.
Okay, then yeah, go help Sullivan.
Instead of helping him,
I am looking at my inventory and I guess I still have my huge worm.
Yeah, I guess I keep giving that to you.
Okay, so this time it's actually going to leave my inventory and I'm going to...
It's okay, man.
Since I just beamed Pat so well, instead of moving, I'm going to try and throw my worm
at Gaben.
Okay.
You're going to try to entice him with a big worm?
Or just annoy him a little bit.
Okay, go for it.
So another athletics check?
Yes.
Okay, I'm about to catch this worm, Gavin. 14.
Uh, yeah, you throw the worm, it kind of lands like over here.
It's huge, by the way.
It is huge, so I'm gonna roll to see if he's distracted by it.
Do a little wisdom check for him.
Gotta crit one.
Ooh, not wise enough for this worm.
Goddammit. I hate this fucking game.
It's too easy to beat you, dude.
So he...
He is...
Why this like worm is like a fucking menace to me.
I was like oh this will be a wisdom check, I'll throw him a bone, he'll do a wisdom check,
he probably won't.
And he gets a fucking one.
As soon as he, as soon as Gavin is like visually distracted, I like to get the worm back in
my inventory, I like get on my knees and start patting him, come here boy, come back to papa,
I'm gonna need you again later.
Okay,
you see the worms like
like like the Spongebob worm where it's like a dog and it
like, yeah,
it's at the rush up towards you.
You see Gaben's like we're
he starts to try to follow it.
I'll give you a chance to do something about that.
Papa Papa's over there actually and I point over to Sullivan.
I
the
Okay, it starts to sink, it's like halfway sinking.
It's like...
Will Gaben follow it?
No, Gaben's just like watching it sink.
He's like...
But if we get him into the sand, will he sink?
Uh, Gaben? Maybe.
If you put Gaben in the sand, what do you think would happen to him?
I think he would get halfway stuck.
Yeah, me too.
That's fun.
So, um...
a
No, it's just halfway sinking. It's still there. All right, so Sullivan sees Gabe and he's like
Like the baby gamer the little gamers
Let's see how they do they try to help each other out again nice. Yeah, they're able to get themselves out
And the the and Sullivan starts to move he moves he manages to move like five feet up here
uh the little gamer
Uh follows in tow to try to continue to help Sullivan
uh... and now it is your turn still but what i see the last one ago to skin can
already went
yet that were in tactic
on johnson
i'll move
towards the sand area
uh...
kit do i see it can i get as my vision clear up at all
yes sorry we do that for you c_n_n_'s are to see a little bit more of
everything uh...
yes it also say that like the vision around the the vision around these areas
should like it like a much brighter now because once you clear it up
can i see gave been over these little of the stone creates a greenish glow
around this corner of bluish glow around the ice corner
can i see a bit of an over the walls as he taller than the walls
uh... you could
maybe see a tough to pair a little bit but not really it's a hard the walls
are really a plan to say
ten feet tall you can link you collect
s like
do a little scale a little bit like get a little bit i'd over and look at c_n_n_
but not really don't really have line of sight. No.
Hmm. How, if I scale, if I scale, instead of moving,
if I scale the wall instead of moving, that'll give me a line of sight, right?
Yeah. Okay. Can I do that then? Um, okay. Instead of moving. Yeah.
Yeah. Let you do that. All right. Yeah. So I'm do, uh,
do an athletics check. Cause this is sort of like, just like, you know,
smooth stone. Yeah. 10.
I'd say you're able to climb and you're able to kind of look over it.
So you're gonna have disadvantage on your shot.
Okay.
Yeah.
Um, hmm.
Can I see the ground around him?
Not really.
All right, I'll shoot. I'll try to shoot him.
Yeah, go for it.
Disadvantage.
Yeah.
Nine.
Okay, yeah. It's, uh, it goes a little bit wide. You have another shot.
All right, I'm gonna try again. I still have disadvantage, right?
Yeah.
Oh!
17.
that hits
well for damage
three
nice yeah uh...
uh... the bullet was seventeen just barely hits it grazes the top of his
head
is really unlike sort of faces you for a second
uh...
uh... you know he was sort of intrigued by the word now it's a little
little angered by the uh...
he's a little bit
and he's like sort of looking towards you a little bit uh...
but now it's a nice round
again
uh... this time gable go last again just because now he sort of in this like
spot where he's like kind of close to
solvent
uh...
but i a f first patrick you know it's let's get you going to write i'm just
gonna
he moved out
the acute move it was a lot of uh... uh... makes all sense to me
uh...
uh... rewind on somebody wanted
i would like to stealthily trying hide opposite the wall that
that gave in his uh...
Mind okay right here. Perfect. I try quiet enough that he can't he doesn't on their role stealth role
Okay easy for me
Mm-hmm and
A 17. Yeah, great. I mean like he's pretty you know, there's a giant worm. There's a delicious frog
There's a gun being shot at him. So with a 17, yeah, you're pretty much
You're not on his radar now. Yes
You're you're you're hidden
Sullivan and the little gamer make it to the pedestal
And they put the sandstone in the sand goes around away
Which means it's easier to move through it. Uh-oh
Um, gavin's gonna kill him my worm back. Sullivan's like, oh, yeah, you see the worm like flopping around on the ground
um
Uh, sullivan sort of moves into the corner a bit
The little gamer also they're sort of uh after putting it in they sort of like firm up there
like kind of been like a we'll figure out what to do when he comes for us.
Okay.
Back to back.
Worm, come here.
Oh, come here.
Come here.
Don't put my backpack.
Yeah.
I'll let you do that.
Yes, he doesn't hear it.
But roll, you have to roll a, you have to roll stealth, you have to roll
persuasion because I'm because you're kind of out of turn order, but I want
you to do that because I like that idea of the worm as a slur.
Stealth.
Nice.
Okay, so you're quiet enough.
Persuasion.
Mm-hmm six. Oh, yeah the worm the worm like is like like just looking at you like how a dog
What you'll be like come here come here. They just like look at you
Why didn't I teach him how to speak?
And you're like, why are you just looking at me um
Botox piss, okay. Mm-hmm
What's up? Am I on the wall now?
Have I you can use you can use like like a bit of your movement. You're on the wall. Like all right
Yeah, you can finish climbing up there
I'm just gonna I want Gabe and to come toward me. Okay, you solve it alone. So I'm gonna I'm gonna shoot him again and I'm gonna
I'll probably yell like a you know
Like a voice line from like the sniper from TF to like a thematic one if I could think of one I would so just like
Imagine I'm saying one of the voice. I'm imagining it. Yeah
What about thanks for standing still yeah, I'll say or like the one yeah something like that and like where that funny accent
he has. And that funny freaky accent that no real life person has.
Yeah, with that 11 though, it doesn't quite hit, it goes a bit wide. So you obviously
have another attack still though. Yeah, I'll try again. Oh, a 7, oh no.
Yeah, it goes wide again. You can even still take note of that, that you made that weird
I
and
away. But let's see what is it gave us given able to get given
will be able to reach him this turn of somebody is not
something. So Caleb you got to do something you got to attack
you got William Johnson. You're you're very in range of him.
He doesn't know you're there. I'm going to throw my sexual
grenade at him. Okay, go for it. You can lob it over the
side. I'm going to kind of you just pop it over. Yeah. Yeah,
you have you had sight of him before that. So that's totally
fine and I hear him. But okay. 18. That's a good that's a good. That's a spicy. That's
a good. Yeah. Yeah. Oh yeah. 15. Wow. I'm so good. Yeah. You throw this like pulsing nutsack
grenade over the wall and it crashes and you can see over the wall just like like fire
come just like like just like blow up and light his hair on fire. You see him like eyes
is
uh...
so now it is your turn uh...
patrick you know
just gonna move another fifteen day keep going
going over there
when i go here
okay cool
and blow toss you're up as well yeah uh... i'm gonna i'm standing on top of
the wall
news gonna walk
uh... this along the wall
so i just have a better vantage point of stature
Okay, it's the next turn.
Little Gamer...
Oh, actually, wait, shit, sorry, I have to roll for Gaben.
'Cause he has a thing he does
when he gets reset.
Yeah, he cries like a little baby.
Okay.
Sullivan and the Little Gamer
peel out of there, they're like,
"Ha, ha, ha!" like running out of there.
Okay, uh...
Oh, that's so cute, they're friends.
Your turn.
- I am gonna, 'cause I know Gaben is over here
in the shadows, so I'm going to try and run away really fast.
- Okay.
Go.
- So I'm gonna go here,
and I'm gonna get closer to the door.
- Okay, cool.
Yeah, you can see now, but the sand one is glowing as well,
as there's one more left.
Patrick Yoda.
- Do I just move again?
yeah and i would say that this point like all that you sort of like
because enough of like this like slow movement i think it's fair to be like
you're kind of in within reach of the lava
and so i was so let's say what you want to hear you
yeah like what you want to do about what i got to try the hoverboard again
yet go for it
well we do it because
i know i rule athletics
sorry i i i i don't know the hoverboard
now concerning have now considering it like a national court
i guess six
yeah you uh... start uh... hoverboard over it
and uh... like i get over here
except for my under you again
and you're just not having is this not your day
uh...
roles even abrasions up between these two walls
the whole athletics again
or acrobatics or whole fuck
uh... i'm not one of the five
You start to sink into this lava. You take, you take five more damage as you are burning on this lava and it's going to make make your movement, you know, slower.
To heaven health now.
Yeah. I'm going to have Gaben go so you can sort of decide what you want to do, Blotas, based off that.
So what you see, Blotas, you're able to see this because of like where you are.
so reveal this a bit you see gaben go into this like bright light in the
storeway
that looks similar to the one where he's where he's gonna come out
he's sort of a yeah he walks off the right edge of the screen
yep and goes right back into the left pack pac-man matrix
matrix pac-man dude I know my pac-man I've seen pixels yeah
yeah it's a it's a gag classic
um and gaben's coming after patchy kioda
Gadsdor piece
Can you guys help me yeah, I'm gonna help you don't worry. Yeah, it's a blow toss you're up
Can I
Can I jump from this wall to this wall?
The blue wall to which wall to this gray wall right here
Yeah, athletics check or acrobatics, but it's not too hard for you. Yeah, I'm gonna do an athletics check go for it 26
Yeah, yeah, you look fucking sick, dude. Oh, yeah
It won't drag me onto it, right? No, it's not gonna drag you onto it. Perfect. All right, you're on. Okay? Yeah
So now I'm a little closer to Gabe in and towards the door
and
I'm just gonna try to shoot him again
Yeah
You have advantage because now that you have like a total line of sight of him and you're up above
And you're that close get you get advantage like you can't like be that high up and not get advantage on an attack
19 that hits for sure
Do damage seven damage? Yeah, you shoot that it gets to his fat fucking neck and he has the valve thing on the back
And he started to turn around a little bit and it scares me yeah, he turns around he looks like the
Yeah, he looks like the freaky witch
Mr. Freeman wake up, but he's just like yelling
In this dark deep bass baritone voice and you also look up we see the gamers now
They're looking a little bit more like they're stopping paying attention to their gaming and they're more gripped by this
Because you guys seem like you actually might fucking pull this off when you look up you have another attack, too
I'm gonna be gripping them soon enough. All right, tell you what?
I'm gonna attack him again
Go for 18
All right. Yeah that hits
10 damage.
yeah, that's that's enough where it's like he turned around and you just like fucking got him in the fucking eye and
He's like
I'm gonna reveal the whole fucking map to you guys at this point. Yes
So all of his all of his movements have disadvantage now. Yeah, that's right Patrick. No, you know Patrick is that
No, I'm sorry, yeah, that's me to me. No, it's not how that is
No, it's not quite cuz he kind of just like regens and just like retreats
All right, so that's kind of like imagine like his eye like blows up and then he just kind of like hides away
But now this time you can all see him like there's no fog anymore
He can't like disappear into the darkness like it's gone too far at this point
So you can see his eye starting to reform while you're drowning in the lava. You can kind of see that
happening
But yeah round restarts Patrick Yoda
Well, I gotta get to that fucking
in
to
I'm
again all the lights are up at this point at this point everyone can move 30 feet
now so does that mean the door opens yeah the door is now open so everyone
everyone can go now blow toss you're up all right I'm gonna stay I'm gonna let's
see here oh shit I want to stay on top of the walls for now just in case I need to
protect
run
fourteen
uh... and i'm just gonna shoot at him again
uh... work do i still have advantage for being above him yet
who create double-headed shit all the way out
while
uh... well for damage
uh... thirteen damage
yet uh... he fuckin
right is his head you can roll again for another attack
uh...
c_f_a_a_ it's
the senate's three
yet that's enough for he's like
i'd be split sort of like running away
now he's a kind of extra scared
uh... with everything it's a strange or is patrick fuck
uh... run the other way
we can add to that is in my turn yet
yet your turn okay uh... i'm looking at my inventory i have twenty five like you
have a huge or her man i a
the
uh... i have twenty five the huge worm is away right he's still
not now he's like
you need to do to call it he at this point probably came back i don't like
them a risky and so i have twenty five quarters and i'm just gonna throw them
well i like it
and just try and make some noise
I'll probably work on Gabe and right this guy loves money. Yeah, he does
Okay, go for it enroll a um
Hmm, let me think of what this is just gonna try and distract him a little yeah. Yeah, I'll roll
I'll see if he can able to resist it
He's not very wise. Yeah, I mean we've established that yeah
No, he's not that distracted by these quarters. Ah, it's just like a mess a quarter you hear
Hey, man, try throwing some steam points at him, you know, I'm saying maybe try throwing a hat or two that might distract this
If you don't want free money, that's on you brother. I
Get free money every day. Did I tell you to talk please shut up? Okay
Yeah, it's all that I hide in I get in the room
Yeah solving the little gamer kind of ran rushed out or running back to you now you go in the room and it's just like
you hear immediately like a Muzak again, like a Muzak version of a, like a fucking like Super
Mario ass kind of shit.
Some video game soundtrack.
It's like an elevator, it looks like.
And there's like one button and it just says "To the Gamer Room."
Okay.
So you're in there now.
Yeah, just kind of like looking at my watch and patiently waiting on my friends.
I
the
what?
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
you totally able to do that
you like run, jump off the wall and fucking dive
and then like land over there
here's what we're gonna do at this point
we're gonna like fast forward a bit
because it's really just gonna be Patrick Yoda and Gaben I think
everybody else is gonna be able to get into this safe zone over here
the
So go again, Patrick Yoda. Or go go blow it up first.
I'm just going to I'm going to shoot him again. Go for it.
Oops, I rolled three times back, but that's a 16.
OK, yeah, does not hit, but the 23 will hit.
So for that second attack, 10 damage.
Yeah, he's like hurt by that, but like he's still OK.
Patrick, you can move now.
OK, I run over here.
Okay, nice, okay.
Blotas.
I'm gonna shoot again.
24.
Yes, sir.
8 damage.
Yeah, that reaches his cap again.
And he, uh, retreats.
Let's go, we're safe.
Yeah, he retreats again, so you guys can all get into the elevator.
Yeah.
What the fuck took you so long?
And we heal in the elevator?
Yeah, you're all gonna heal.
Yes.
You feel like this aura around you, like,
*mimics the aura*
Like you're coming back to life.
like you were a blue ghost that was eaten or something.
And you see that button that says "To the Gamer Room" and you see the little gamer who's like
"Why did you bring it?
Why did you bring it?"
pointing at the button.
He's saying "Don't press it."
He's saying "Guys, I understand him."
He's saying "Under no circumstances would you ever touch this button."
Yeah, fuck that little kid.
Yeah, the little gamer runs up to the button and slams his head on it, like just in frustration.
And yeah, you hear this elevator going up, this chute.
You see the other gamers in the land, who were having that land party, watching you all,
like kind of in awe, for beating the Gaben.
You go up, actually, and...
You ignore this.
Wow.
And this beautiful waterfall.
And you guys travel up this beautiful waterfall.
were
waterfalls
that looks pretty strange
i would say
uh...
cd you appear in this elevator
uh... willie walker style after defeating gaben
uh...
you're in this room it's like group made of like almost like green and black
plastic all the world history check
who create
holy shit
well nicely only i did get a good role
fourteen's not too bad but the credit
uh... cameron you have like flashbacks
to like an idea to cast memory of like
of of uh...
of dissecting an xbox
in your uh... are going to be granted xbox
you're in this massive xbox
uh...
uh... you could see the the power box
you can see the cpu in the graphics are all that is there it's just all that's
like the size of a minivan plus
uh...
you see a lot of advanced consoles like the super secret
like amazing terminals that you've never seen before
were two gamers a piece apiece it on couches
and they're only playing the most elite titles ever like yick or yick to any
extra heat
they're like giant cosmic brownies that your friend's mom has
uh... cheetos gummy bears fruit roll-ups all the fucking best snacks
mountain dew
there's a fucking giant ass fridge inside of it is uh... basically poggers
uh...
and uh...
uh... it's it's amazing
it's in short a gamers paradise
there's even a mom bot who goes around and you can yell at her
and make your other friends were over uncomfortable as she brings you snacks
uh...
you also see a massive console even bigger than the other ones
and a winged gamer
and he turns to face you all and he looks kinda like he's got the handsome
squidward face
uh... he's like a handsome falmer
uh... this winged gamer with like these white eyes like raiden, these like awesome
white eyes
and you see him like extend his hand and like do like a come hither
and you see the little gamer pile out of the elevator
and he like bows down and goes
like he's bowing down to this gamer
and he gestures towards you all
and you understand him Patrick Yoda, he's basically saying they've bested the
Gaben
uh... you must give them a chance
uh... you must give them a chance and you see the uh... the
badass looking fucking squidward winged gamer
look at you all
and he gestures towards his giant console
and he goes
would you like to play a game
and that's where it ends.
Whoa.
Are we fully healed, by the way?
Yeah, you're fully healed.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
(dramatic music)
[Music]