Oh, God!
My leg!
You have to move your leg.
You have to move your leg right now to get it out.
I can't move it.
Well, hold on.
How can he move his leg if it's over there?
Okay, wait.
Ray, get his leg.
We have to put it back on.
Oh, shit.
Oh, you call this a leg?
Oh, God, this thing's ugly as shit.
Oh, no, that's his penis.
Okay, his leg's over there.
Sullivan's back in heat.
No, no, no.
What am I holding right now?
I think that's an arm.
Okay, so he lost his penis and his leg.
Oh my god.
Freeze!
No, you freeze!
I move!
Yeah, we were just getting some second.
Our friend lost his leg.
Okay?
Guys, can we focus up for a minute?
If we don't put him back together,
how are we gonna get through the Sullivan body scan lock?
That's on the vault's door.
Very good point.
Does anybody have any glue or spit?
What limbs does he still have attached to his torso?
His mouth.
Looks like pretty much an eye and a mouth.
Those are not limbs!
Okay, then nothing.
No!
I'll use my Kemp arm to disfigure the rest of him, and I'll each take one of his limbs and puppet him through the scanner.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
There are dragons flying into the room, guys.
There's dragonflies in the room? Sullivan would love to eat those!
I can't really talk, I've been very disfigured.
I think we should just put him out of his misery.
No, please don't. Please.
But the only gun is inside the vault.
*laughter*
Okay, so we need to put him into his misery first,
scan his body, and then get into the vault so we can kill him.
Gary B, do you have any kind of like reverse bomb that would put somebody's leg back on their body?
No.
Aw, shit! You know it's a lot of soul!
Shit!
Wait, wait, wait, Gary B, do you have any-
Do you have any glue to make a bomb?
No.
What?
Ow!
I just killed all the dragons.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you very much.
Yep.
You hear a voice over the intercom.
"It seems you've all fallen into my trap."
Oh, no, it's that guy.
That's right.
I thought we fell into the trap minutes ago.
Is this a new--
Why has he exploded if we haven't hit a trap already?
Yo.
Uh-oh, looks like there's more dragons.
There's more dragons and gargoyles now too, coming into this drinking room.
Luckily I have my gargoyle ray from earlier in the mission.
No, no, you don't have a gargoyle ray.
And I'm gonna go to the bathroom real quick.
It's right over there, it's the second door to the right if you walk down that hallway.
Oh, they only have a girls bathroom. You have to go in the girls bathroom and there's little girls in there.
NOOOOO!
Wait, I think we're losing Sullivan. Oh my god. Oh no.
Sullivan, is this really happening to me?
Yes, and it's very, very bad and you're going to die.
I bet you're wondering how we got into this mess.
Well, it's a long story and people usually tune me out if I start talking for more than
a couple sentences, but I'm the only one left alive to tell it, so I guess it's gotta be
me.
Uh, well, right after we struck it rich from our last adventure at Te Tempola Dune, my best
friends, Blowtoss Piss, Patrick Yoda, and Ray William Johnson went their separate ways.
I still worked as their assistant, although I don't recall being paid, but I managed their
affairs after they got so rich from the last adventure. I tried to call them, but they
must have been really busy because they never picked up, except for one time they called
me and told me they were all hanging out and I wasn't invited. I saw them hanging in the
Matrix 2 one time too, I think, but when I said hi, they told me that they were just illusions
and I never knew them and I should probably go to an insane asylum because I seem so crazy,
stupid and ugly.
So I did my own thing for a bit.
I became a producer for XXX Contacion, formerly known as Husky Kitchener, and made enough tokens
that I could afford to move back to Gun City and rent a 5x5 foot luxury condo in the Lockheed
Martin District.
After about a year of living back in G.C., I was invited to a charity event for the Papichuco's
Techno Slime addiction treatment and recovery center by my cousin John Carlo.
He done well for himself since we last saw him.
Partnered with Garry's Enterprise on a huge expansion of Hot Soda, Cold Dog's restaurant.
It felt like giving back after being a Techno Slime pusher for so long.
Of course the charity was under Papi Chuko's Techno Slime Corporation so I didn't know
how much good it could do but I figured it'd be nice to go to an event.
Maybe I'll make some friends.
The event took place at the Belle Delphine Wonder Bread event space in Palantir HQ district.
So it was a bit of a drive for me, but boy did that venue impress.
And the venue itself is a single floor venue with a well kept lobby area, warm and red
in tone, with sparks of sleepy golds and yellows, contrasted with a super linoleum flooring
that spills out into the main event hall where things get interesting.
Sheets of neon shoot through the floor, creating dimensions and liminalities as you move through.
Colors gently shift between Pantone favorites, and you hear tinny high-pass versions of inoffensive
music snake up through the floor.
Different tracks loop at different points in the venue, sort of like you're moving from
the restaurant floor to the restaurant bathroom, a Sade joint fading out as the sounds and
smells of Uptown Girl fade in, but it's all in the same open space.
Otherwise it's a pretty fairly standard, you know, architecture for a venue.
High ceilings, baroque chandeliers, simple stage, raised, red curtain.
There are worm servers and chefs that move quickly in and out of the kitchen,
dressed in their party-down get-ups, taking the traditional abuse they deserve.
Sullivan walks in and is barreled down by a few of these worms,
but he recognizes the catering company to be Jamal the Worm's Wormhole Catering.
The program for tonight is as follows.
Keynote speakers, John Carlo the Bullfrog and Gary C. Enterprise.
Followed by a performance from Cream 3, the Jeff T. Dridge, Filipino Mr. Bean and Ray
William Johnson's Worm Band.
Followed by closing remarks from the head of the charity, Fatima Von Kissyface.
Yeah, you remember Cream 3?
I'm just remembering it.
And my worm.
and my worm. I forgot about the worm!
Oh man, I should have done a re-listen to get the lore back.
Oh fuck. Someone make a wiki!
Someone made a wiki, they have to update it. I'm not updating that.
Someone made a wiki, yeah. So Sullivan goes to walk around to try to make
friends. He doesn't really notice you guys yet. I'm not sure why.
But he doesn't. So he gives you guys an opportunity to tell me
Why you why you at the charity event?
How are you guys doing? Where have you been? It's been a year since our last adventure. Ah
Well, you know, I
Love charity so much. I
Think probably after space skateboarding
What a hoverboarding I love I love space charity so much
Basically, I'm only here I
mean between you and I
I'm really only here cuz I got addicted to space cocaine and my dealers here
Yeah, I know I'm your dealer yeah, what's up
How you doing? I'm good, man. I'm trying to keep a low profile. We go to the bathroom real quick
I really told you not to come to this
Why did you I told you I needed to pick up? I I know I said wait till after the charity event
And I'm not buying a ticket.
And then you said I'm buying a ticket.
And then you bought a ticket.
And I'm not wearing a wire.
Alright, so...
You're putting the emphasis in the wrong place.
I'm just letting you know.
I'm not wired up.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
Because of something I did,
I'm not wired up.
I never got caught
with a lot of space cocaine
at the Terry Shiver Memorial Gate Park.
And that's not why I'm here
Okay, I'm gonna go to the bathroom. Okay, I'm gonna follow you to the bathroom to purchase space cocaine
That's not what's happening. Can you walk off and you're saying that he keeps saying that that's not what's happening
And the yeah, we camera sort of whips around to the next one of you's guys
Wherever you's are in the charity event hall
My name is Blotas Piss. I'm a master con man. I've been in this dirty biz ever since I was little. When I was a baby
I was stealing candy from myself. I've played important roles in hundreds of highly successful Christmas heists throughout my life.
I was the teleporter when my team stole every bottle of Mrs. Claus's
1945 Burgundy eggnog from her nog seller.
I was the teleporter in the great art museum heist when we stole Pablo Picasso's Christmas list.
And my teleporting skills really came in handy when I helped rob the Santa's slots casino blind as the teleporter
Yep, I had a particular skill set and I knew how to use it
I was one of the baddest in the game and I was and still am rich as hell
But that all changed except the rich part when my child came along Sullivan
Not the frog the cool one half penguin and half water bottle Sullivan was the light of my life
Once I started spending time with him, I realized I didn't want to be a teleporter anymore. I wanted to be a dad
He made me want to quit heisting and be a better man
I co-parented the little rascal with Ray William Johnson and it was a great experience
Now that my little Sullivan's all grown up and headed off to college. He's all I can think about
I'm sure Ray William Johnson feels the same way
And did you guys go to the event together?
Yeah, yeah, I got dragged by blowtoss and
Ray William Johnson is in he's in the kitchen of the venue right now. Mm-hmm. Yeah, like hey boss. He can't be back here
Boss, what are you doing back here? Just ignoring this guy completely and talking to himself under his breath says
One last job. That's my promise to myself
One last job before I retire the mark a turkey sandwich
But first I'm gonna need to put a team together. I'll start with my right-hand man mayonnaise
We've seen all you can't grab that. We've seen it all and he saved my ass more times than I can count
Hey Mayo, remember gas station tuna? Yeah, we were both so damn coked out who else?
Well, we didn't exactly end on good terms, but American cheese is the finest delicious expert in the entire fridge
After our last job, he went Hollywood on me, but I bet I could convince him.
Of course, no sandwich would be complete without tomato, a master of disguise.
Put him in the right situation and he convinced even the keenest eye that he's a piece of smoked salmon.
Next, my brother from another mother.
Pepper. I may be a computer strapped to the back of a demon and he may be food,
but his black ass always has my back and you know I got his.
Then I gotta get the twins of course top and bottom slice to help her out the crew and of course the big man
Salcito turkey clock again at nearly 899 a pound. He's heavyweight rough and tumble spicy
Which is the right amount of sweet?
This is gonna be tough because I don't think they have knives in this kitchen, but let's do it boys
Okay, we did it now. I'm gonna eat sandwich also me and blowtiles raised a kid
*laughter*
After you reached for the mayonnaise during the speech and you started to mention cheese and were walking towards the fridge,
the other guys were like "just make the sandwich as he's saying it so he doesn't touch anything"
and they just made it as quickly as they could and gave it to you.
I, as I'm, they hand it to me and I took the pieces apart and put them immediately together in the same order so that I felt accomplished.
the
down a bunch of money on the bathroom counter.
Look I, he's in the stall, you could just see his feet, he's like, "Okay, well, that's good,
I'm glad you're not doing that, dude."
And he's not selling it to me, right now.
Don't have anything on me, we're at a charity event.
What did you think I was gonna do, sell you cocaine here?
Yeah.
*knock knock*
Uh, can you uh, open up?
This turkey sandwich is really running through me.
Oh, who's that?
*knock knock knock knock*
Why does it matter who I am?
I'm trying to take a shit in the bathroom.
Because I'm not buying drugs in here!
Who cares what my name is?
Just let me shit.
Coke dealer like pulls up his pants and like just
washes his hands and walks out, opens the door
and yeah, Ray William Johnson, you and CokeToyota.
Oh, it's a multi-stall. Don't let him leave!
leave. As he walks out an alarm goes off above the door that says didn't flush.
Guards run over and grab him. I think that Patrick Yoda is telling me to stop him because he didn't
flush so I also aid in, I tackle the guy. I'm innocent, I'm innocent. No brown bandits getting
away at this dinner party. Oh thank god I needed that, oh my god. They had me on,
They were gonna book me for fucking ever
They're gonna throw me in jail. I bought I hid so many fucking bricks of coke in the terry shifo memorial skate park
One day some fucking little shit hits his head through the through the through the ramp
It was made out of wood and I don't know why he was ever boarding on a wood ramp. You're not supposed to do that
Yeah, his he went full speed through the ramp
Showed off my whole fucking stash. I don't know what the fuck. I I I got I got so much trouble
Anyway, how have you been?
Uh, can we catch up after I shit?
Yeah, do you got any blow?
You got any space blow?
I'm in the stall with him.
As you guys are doing this, I walk over.
Blowtoss talks over us like,
"Oh, we having a little reunion, are we?"
And then instantly my face does the fish from Spongebob thing,
because I smell the poop that the guy didn't flush down.
[Laughter]
the
It's nice to see you man, whatever, you need to go flush that right now.
It smells horrible.
As he's running towards us, I quickly paint a photorealistic portrait of all three of
us with welcoming arms on the front of the toilet stall that has the shit in it so that
he runs directly into it and into the stall and his face goes into the poop.
Oh somebody's gotta flush this and then I flush him down the toilet.
Blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah
Okay, okay.
Well, how you guys, well.
How you guys doing?
What's that on your nose?
My eyes are really stinging.
Sullivan, what the hell is wrong with you? You got shit all over your damn face.
You look horrible man since the last time we saw you
Wait, is your name still Sullivan or is it nothing or poop?
I think it's poop. I think it's poop because of what's on his face
I don't remember
Are you guys, are you guys here for the, are you guys here for the,
I guess you're here for the charity event, it's a stupid question
I was here for, to not buy drugs
Because I'm still not wearing a wire
If you have any
No, I don't. I don't even drink tea.
Oh, that's code for I have space blow.
Officer, I mean, duh.
Shirt, Sullivan, you're talking to your shirt, right?
Sure.
My shirt, you guys give me all kinds of
days shirt now.
Long time, I'm glad to see you've reinvented yourself.
Your name's Shirt, you have poop all over your face.
His name is Shirt, he's covered in poop.
Oh, and you're on the ground.
And I kick his leg out from under it.
[LAUGHTER]
I see you walk on four legs now.
Very interesting.
I like it.
I missed you guys a lot.
We all sit on him like a bench.
And then we look at each other, and we all say--
I miss you guys too.
(laughter)
- I just need to say that.
You hear a little like, ding, ding, ding, ding, like chimes,
but the event is starting.
You see John Carlo, the bullfrog,
not John Carlo the frog, all right,
so those keeping track of canon at home,
appears on the stage at the podium,
and he says, "We'd like to thank you all for coming.
It's an honor to be able to host an event such as this alongside my business partner Gary C. Enterprise.
I remember him.
The work that is being done by Papi Chuko's Technoslime Addiction Treatment and Recovery Center
is nothing short of phenomenal.
They have managed to save 17 addicts this year alone, up from creating 17 more last year.
How about a round of applause?
And you see like sort of a smattering of applause, you know.
You see Jamal Da Worm is sort of like,
I don't know how work how he applauds. He's doing it though. He's
He's hitting his head against yeah, but yeah, you see the worms are
Doing that they're just dropping the drinks. They're trying to serve. It's a certain clapping and just dropping shit
yeah, and he says
Now
Cold dogs and hot sodas is all about giving back
You know, the idea came from Gary C's interactions with three kind strangers who gave him the capital and the inspiration to build this Empire
That foundation means we're all about paying it forward. So they have any cold dogs here past things to my colleague here to give you
Some exciting news
Excuse me. Harry. I'm raising my hand. Yes. There's a worm a worm comes over. Yes, sir. How can I help you? Holy shit?
You came at me too fast
You need to slow down. You'll back off back off man. Get out of here. I'm okay. Give me like to try again
Try coming towards us at a slower pace consider the energy
That you're putting out here, right? Okay
hmm
Hello, sir. Do a crazy avoid American accent American accent. Yeah
Midwestern voice Midwestern. Sorry. Hold on. Let me try to
Hello, I'm not very good at the Midwest. Okay, do a French guy doing a model. It's Fargo a fire fire goal
Dear one. Okay. Yeah, that's not bad. All right
But with that voice, I kind of want you to come at us really fast because you're like pretty inviting
Hi, sir, would you like anything from?
Well, what the hell you doing the old one? Oh, okay. So go back to the fog. Oh boys
Sort sorry. Sorry about yeah
You like any treats yes, yeah
Okay, we got what do you got well we got cold dogs and shit cold dogs and hot dogs and hot sodas
Is that how they see it? So I don't want any of that. Can you go into the kitchen and get me a shrimp cocktail?
Yes, right away sir, and the worm sort of slithers off with an identity crisis
And
John Carlo continues or rather Gary C enterprise walks in the stage
Thank You John Carlo and hello all Gary C enterprise here
What if I told you that cold dogs and hot soda was making enough money that we could devote a significant portion of our earnings
detective slime recovery
And what if I told it at all? Oh
the
I've fallen on hard times
Shut up
Why?
If I told you we'd be willing to pledge that for every cold dog or hot soda you buy we will give one token to the
Recovery Center. How about that folks and people clap clap clap?
It's an honor to be able to work with Fatima and her team
I only hope things can grow from here and that the tax write-offs make this all worth it. So thank you all and
In a little bit. We'll have some entertainment for you. So, uh, you know, it's that fun, right?
"Hey, it doesn't have to be all stuffed shirts, right? Let's get pumped!"
And you know, people clap, yada yada, the sort of blah blah music resumes.
You see Cream 3 getting set up in the back.
You see Jeff Tiedrich and Filipino Mr. Beat and Ray William Johnson, your worm, getting all set up.
Who's still in my inventory, I might add.
Yeah, still in your inventory, but this is what he does on the side.
Oh, I didn't realize my inventory reaches that far.
that's pretty cool
yes so we have what he does when do you mean is
use jim all the worm is here gary c
uh...
uh... well as john carlo
so i don't friends all faces you can see here
you guys want to chat with them i want to share with gary c enterprise i want to
chat with gary i said at first
okay final double jet
i'm just talking to any already
to try and get all right ready to go we're gonna double check
and got one to three hello what's up Gary the enterprise
well so what's up with you not just Patrick's here
I got the whole gang I get the the poop frog guy here to that's good
yeah I am doing what's his name again yes sure
shirt shirt now shirt that's good it's good
how you fellas doing you looking to donate today we're very happy to have you
here I was actually looking to ask if I could get a gift card
and
the
a
You could put 10 million dollars on it.
Could you put, what's that amount that's like two of those like Christian fishes put together?
Is that a gogoplex?
No, it's like a sideways eight. Oh, eight! Yeah, so like eight bucks.
Yeah, so I mean, it's, you know, that's not going to be any actual money tied to it, you know, but I can give you guys copies.
It's a gift card, so it would just be gift money.
Yeah, sure I can I can I could get you guys some gift cards. Yeah, I'm gonna go up
I have a few other until there's a gift card. That's right. I'm gonna nail your foot to the ground
Okay. All right. All right. That's that
Baby mama like that
And uh, Gary see enterprise or smiles. He knows you guys at this point. He does your your whole your old stick
And he which is what?
You're mean to everyone
Yeah, anyway see you Patrick it says I don't got coke
I've I've been I've been walking around in a circle asking for gift cards. You talked about gift cards just then
yeah, and
Yeah, you see now
Creamy give me a fucking gift card cream three getting set up on stage
You see Jeff Tiedrich and Phil Filipino. Mr. Bean and and the worm
They're playing in the in the in the diaper room
Which which goes uh?
In the diaper room I am certain I need changing and they just started singing about that they need that
the singing sunshine of your love 300 edition
It's about it's about the movie 300 but to the tune of sunshine of your love
Yeah, they're crushing it. Everyone loves them. Everyone loves a few bars from that. I only have a couple lines
Do you want to hear it? I need to yeah, I need to hear this. Yes. It's getting near done. I
Fight with 300 guys
I'll soon be with you my love
300 other guys
Wait, wait, so it's kind of it's it's 301
Shit yeah
should be fighting.
29 other guys on stage.
Yeah, so those are the two songs that they play and everyone loves it.
And then finally, the woman of the hour Fatima Von Kizzee face takes the stage.
She's kind of got like a big sort of like Sia hair do.
It's all white.
She's kind of like a prim lady, a bit older, and she says, "Thank you all so much for coming.
She's just been a wonderful event.
We're all so happy to have you here.
And I'd just like to say that I thank you for the three men who showed up.
These are the people who are responsible for our charity's independence.
One of them, I think it was the G-man, he punched the head off Papi Chuko and the company
Sort of dissolved and we got to have our independence. So thank you you three
Did she say the G man that she man the she man you can't say that nowadays
She says
And did she say a big announcement we're going to make we were renaming the charity to make an out
What I can't understand a fucking word you're saying that voice is called the independent charity of underprivileged persons
That's right. We are going to be servicing not just people who are
But everyone in gun city, hey, hey blowtorch spell it spell spell it okay
INDEP
DND
ENTC
HR I T
Oh
My god short
You hear a lot of rumbling about this. This is a big deal. There has not been a charity in
Gun City history, but has ever operated independently that cold dogs and hot sodas has given enough money to this charity
That they can operate independently is a big deal
People are going to be interested in that most charities are exists solely to be the arm of another corporation
This is one that is at the very least a tax write-off, which is a big deal
And she she says now we're going to be going around with donations
Please put down whichever number you think is you're comfortable with but just know that like we need a lot of money
so thank you so much and
let's have cream Shri play us out and
the
It does there's a lot of
Zero zero
I know you're smart shirt. Okay. All right. Yeah, I think so. Okay
shirt I yeah
Let me let me talk to you for a second. I there's I probably like six different credit cards and
like a bunch of
Look, I don't know
the
No, no, just just give just give him your credit card. So he'll pretend to like put out a donation
Oh, yeah, all right. Hold on. Let me just let me get out my Bitcoin wallet real quick. Okay. Hold on. Well, definitely. Okay. Hold on
Whatever you do, please just just don't use this one specifically
don't use this card I
Okay, um, yeah just don't use that card
And write the same amount that they did so which card should I use?
the use
the
The show is brought to you by the members of the audience at the top of the
I guess I could just don't tell him and you'll get real mad at me. No secret safe with us
it's very generous of you and
solvent comes back and
He's like, okay. I took care of it
All right. You have my cards. Yeah. Yeah here
and he's like
Wait the card you didn't want me. Hold on one second. He runs back and he grabs the card
He you didn't want him to use and he gives it back to you. I'm so sorry. I left it at the table
So, uh, okay
Yeah, you guys wanna go get drinks or something Jamal the worms wormhole, let's go hey, yeah, well, yeah, I'm out we donated
I'd say a million dollars of drinks on us right now, sir. Yeah
That's out a huge amount by helping us not actually donate any money right there
On them, please. Yeah
Okay, let's let's walk over to the bar
You guys walk over to Jamal the worms wormhole and you see Jamal the worm
He's sort of cleaning up after a big catering gig and sort of gives you guys a knob
No, I'm gives you guys gives you guys three Pibb Cosby's on the house
My friend but I you know what this shirt finally didn't fuck something up
So I'm gonna give you my card and I'm gonna pay a million dollars for this year Pibb Cosby
the
Did you give him my card?
No, it's my card.
Oh, thank fucking god.
Look, there's a picture of you on it. It's my card.
Wait, did it go through, Jamal?
I have a picture of you on my card because you're my best friend.
No, it didn't, uh...
Where's the picture of me? It's like the whole potter's at the corner.
It's both.
Oh, fuck.
Was it in Bank of...
Was it in Bank of Craymerica?
What?
the
It's my card from Bank of Graymerica. It's a real country.
*laughter*
In Gun City.
*fart noise*
There's the extra money alarm again. I'm tellin' ya, we're too rich.
Hold on, did Sullivan give you guys my fuckin' wallet?
He says, "I'm sorry guys, it's not a..."
"Nothing's going through."
SHIRT!
Uh, but, what?
Did you give them my wallet?
Nah, I didn't give anybody their wallet.
What are you talking about? We're clearly using our card.
You're acting crazy right now, and you're ruining everything.
*laughter*
I don't know what could be going on with you guys cards.
I think you just put it on my head.
Listen, if the cards don't work, I'll just walk over to the ATM and make a withdrawal really quick.
Oh, I found my wallet. Sorry.
I'm not sure what you were committed to.
I like having cash on me too. I'll join you at the ATM, baby girl.
Let's all go to these three ATMs right next to each other and query our balance at the same instant.
I'm definitely gonna check mine.
It's kind of impressive that they're all at our exact heights too.
Yeah, Sullivan starts to like protest and he doesn't want to go, but he just appears there with you guys.
He's suddenly like, "I didn't want to go!"
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
At the same time, guys.
One, two, three, four.
Oh, what the hell? All my money must have been lost after Sullivan, or Shirt, fucked it up.
And it wasn't before, and it wasn't before I didn't have any money.
the
the bank and take it out in person.
I think we need to go to the bank.
Here, let me try to do a withdrawal real quick.
I don't know what bank would be open at this hour.
I try to withdraw 100 million tokens
and a fly comes out of the ATM slot.
It's a fly where--
I don't remember depositing a fly.
You see a fly comes out.
It has like a cup and it's an expiration.
That fly must be worth 100 million tokens.
Grab it.
OK, I got it.
I'll put it in Shirt's mouth for safekeeping.
Oh, wait, he's a whole rock.
He likes that.
*laughter*
You know what, jerk? I'm gonna call you "Wallet."
I put the fly in his butt, and then I bring him to the bank.
Okay, you guys go to the bank, um...
We're in line, we're in three lines next to each other, going up to three tellers.
Okay, guys. Now we're at the bank.
*overlapping*
They're all different heights to match your heights.
Alright, guys, let's all say our pin at the same time. Ready?
ready
There's your pits yeah, we're in yeah
So mr. Teller I need I need I
Need a hundred million tokens right now now that I've told you my pin. Oh, yeah, sure. Let me let me take a look
I went I thought tell it didn't speak
Sorry
Yeah, immediately a news bulletin turns on to the TV
That the pen has killed himself
The secret has been revealed
You see the Ken bone does a
Love actually card that says
I'm sorry to tell you this next card, but it doesn't look like you have any money and it's like call me and the lake
They each of them do that for all three of you
It must have been an accident from earlier and not when I went to the charity
This is a charity must he must have picked up the wrong set of cards
We'll have to talk to the president of Bank of Cray America. Definitely. We need to go to the office right now
Yeah, we gotta fly over to Cray America real quick. Yeah
Okay, let's get in my private jet and I I didn't have to sell mine yeah
Private jet you guys get to a pretty private jet you fly in instantly to cry America and you see the the president of America
Bank, oh
What do you what do you guys want? What's what's what's going on? What are you or again?
What walk in the door again? We we got it. We came in after you but we want to see you do it
And his body just like starts fucking retching back and forth and he's like just jiggling around and he's like
See why I like to donate
Jerry Jerry what's going on? He calls all of you Jerry
Okay, listen Kramer. We have a problem. We think that your your bank might be stupid
And he just stops himself keep going we think your bank might be stupid as shit and forgot that we had
millions upon billions of tokens in it
Okay. All right. Let me I mean take a look one second and he just
*laughter*
*more laughter*
the
and talk to God.
And this happened, this token thing happened
just recently for me.
And you guys are in a private jet flying to heaven.
Which heaven has to exist because I'm a demon.
Yes, true.
And you see, you can't see God,
but he's everywhere and he's white.
And it's a man, no it's a man,
are you fucking kidding me?
No.
And he's a...
I'm not on my podcast, let me tell you.
And they are looking down at all three of you and they say, "You did broke."
Oh fuck!
Nooooo!
Damn, and this is a recent development for me.
And then we fly back to Kray America and then we fly back to the bank and then we fly back
to the charity event to find shirt.
that the charity event
and uh... the crazy just happened and i'm i'd be my need your help to figure out
how this might have happened
yeah and it's probably your fault
why are we back at the charity event?
jerk i must be in some kind of dream
maybe and now it's lucid you should suck my dick
i still see the shadows in my
uh... you guys remember that?
Yeah, from 5,000 years ago? Yeah, I remember in Zeus World.
Sir, let me tell you something. All of our accounts are empty right now.
Yeah.
Are you happy to know anything about this?
Uh... well, when, um... uh...
I seem to remember giving you a card and telling you to write a certain amount.
Yeah, I'm concerned that maybe you're too fucking stupid to even do that right well, yeah, I wrote down one zero zero
zero
You wrote you wrote four digits and then a comma
No, no, I wrote one and then a comma and then I wrote three zeros and then okay
How many zeros?
It's gotta be more than 12 if I'm being real.
And did you swipe my cards?
Only one, the guy made me do one of them.
But it wasn't the bad one, right?
It wasn't the one you weren't supposed to.
Was it the Kraymerica card?
The one with his face on it in the corner?
Yep!
The one with my face on it in the corner
Dear oh
Fuck I'm ruined with my bad. I just want to be ruined. Okay, tell me
This okay for the
one and I kept paying for the other ones with with credit cards that I kept buying with all the other money I I
I tried to make it a cycle of cards that I kept paying off with other cards, and it didn't fucking work!
It didn't fucking work!
Church, look at me in the eyes and tell me, for the love of God,
that you did not do, on my account, the same amount as blow tosses plus one fly.
Then he flashed back and he's, the guy says, "Why don't you just add a fly for fun?"
[laughter]
Oh my god, Jerk. I'm sorry
You fucked us all. I'm sorry
We might as well kill you right now. Please don't please don't please don't I'd have to because I know why shouldn't we
Sure, I'm gonna give you a good reason not to pop your little head off like a frog's head jerk
I'm gonna kill myself with pills and alcohol and it's your fault
We can just get the money back
the
Give me an idea.
One, two, three, four.
We--
Oh, one, two, three, four.
Maybe there'll be money in there.
Try it again.
We run over to the ATM.
We all put one, two, three, four in.
Yeah, you see two flies, and they're
having like a coy date now.
You're starting to get to know their life and their--
My flies.
Yeah.
Okay, guys, listen, I have an idea.
Alright?
Simple.
We start our own charity,
and we ask for a donation from this charity
for the same amount.
I've got an idea.
I've got an even better idea.
What is it?
I forgot the idea.
Can we...
Can we try something else?
Maybe.
Hmm.
I'm trying to think.
What are we good at that might
that might lay itself out for the future.
It could be archaeology.
It could be detective work.
Well, some of us are good at buying drugs.
Wait, are we elementary school kids who found a leprechaun?
I can't remember what our thing is.
No, no, we're here because we won a contest to become chocolatiers.
Oh, I think it could be that.
That could be it.
Wait, are we a bunch of, are we like pets that like escaped and were like lost?
Oh, he's a frog.
Wow, that's a good point.
You're a frog.
Hmm.
He's a frog.
I kind of look like a frog.
I am hungry.
Like a frog.
When is that shrimp cocktail?
Um, I don't want to say it.
Don't.
I don't want to say it.
I thought anyway
No, go ahead listen shirt, yeah
I bet you have a great idea after you got us in this fucking situation you fucking idiot
What if we also you have a little poop right here? No, thank you
It's really gross his poop was really bad. Yep. Yeah, he was on drugs. Thank you. Oh was
That guy listen. Oh, yeah, tell us your idea so that we can forget it
Yeah, I want to make fun of it stole it back stole it back. What if we stole it back?
I just thought of that
Yoda that is genius. What if we deposited shirt into the ATM and see how much he's worth
I
Deposit him into the ATM and it says
One fly
Okay, wait, well that's got it worth it I'll take oh
My god, there's a fucking machine need to be restocked. There's no flies
All right, whatever we'll take the frog back
Okay
All right, so you guys don't like my idea I guess so
Oh, we're gonna do Patrick's idea.
Yeah, that was a good one.
What was my idea again?
I came up with it earlier and then I forgot it and then I remembered it and then I forgot it again.
Oh, damn, wait, we all forgot the idea.
Oh, well.
Oh, we're gonna deposit shirt into the ATM!
Oh, that was it.
[laughter]
So as you guys are about to put it, put shirt back into the ATM.
It's half as much as before and then it says in parentheses "damaged."
His leg's sticking out. He says, "I think Patrick's idea was to steal the money back!"
"Hell yeah, that was my idea!"
"How are we ever gonna do that? There's only one, two, three, four of us. Wait, that reminds me of something. I'm gonna check my ballots on this ATM."
Okay, all right, I know a guy who can help us who knows his way around pretty much any
security
Anything that we could need to do to steal it back from our cup
James Barry Gee
And if we just go there
You talk to him and then maybe he can help us steal it back, okay
Just please stop whatever the ATM machine and I'm sorry about your money. I was very confused
Go back in the ATM machine. I think he did. All right
So you guys should have solvent back the ATM machine and as you
Smash him in there that we smash cut away from that to outside Barry G's mansion the next morning
You see that we bury these mansion has looks kind of like a Scarface replica mansion
It has sort of the massive staircase leading up to a white gate
You have a driveway on the east side of the mansion
But yeah, you guys can there's two guards out front of the gate and then on the east side of the mansion is
There seems to be some sort of wandering beast
That's probably also under employ by Barry Gee
but
You guys can try to go in through the front Sullivan seems to think he knows Barry Gee
If you guys want to try that or you guys could try to sneak in and try to talk to him
Mm-hmm. Am I feeling sneaky?
Yes
Okay, yeah, I might try to sneak to I think I'm gonna walk in the front okay, oh
version. Clever. Yeah, I'll walk in the front. So you guys sneak in and let me in.
You and Patrick, Patrick and Sullivan walk up the stairs to the front and see the two guards
who say, "Hey, what are you doing here?" "What are you doing here?" "This is Barry Keyes' property."
"This is my property." "What? No, I'm a guard." "No, I'm a guard. You're the owner."
Roll persuasion
Wow our first
Guys like the guy pulls out a gun is like you guys stop talking sense cuz I'm getting really fucking confused
I better start talking sense. Yeah, I should
In front wait, uh, what do you mean? Does that we're here to see Barry G?
See Barry G and I'm here to guard the tower and you are gonna own the building one day
well persuasion with disadvantage
Okay, take that for
All right, you guys better get out of here we're not seeing anybody today
So you may well have Johnson and blow toss piss. What are you guys doing?
Knowing I am at least yeah
Exactly Scooby-Doo tiptoeing. Yeah, okay cool, but the tiptoe sound is very yeah, we're tiptoeing and I and
Just to give you guys a
Into the house is the staircase a long staircase
There's like a fence and then there's like sort of this greenery around it and a driveway
Further off that you could follow to a side entrance, but that has
as a roaming beast. I'm tiptoeing directly towards the beast.
Okay. As you get closer and closer to the beast then...
Oh wait, I can become invisible. Hold up. I'm just going to cast invisibility on myself.
Yeah, you should do that. Okay, I do that.
Okay. Who's there?
You turn invisible. That's what it's called.
Yeah. Who's there? So you can turn invisible for one minute.
Okay, that's more than enough time for me. Yeah, so you can dash...
Wily little me.
Across, and what you see, the beast there, it is a Clombo, which has emerged recently.
Oh my God.
And it's said to eat just about anything.
Is there a special treat that they enjoy?
Yes, but nobody knows what it is. It might be a part of this adventure.
Okay, my character has studied Fortnite-ology, which is a really important field of study for
the past few thousand years.
When Fortnite became real in 2050.
Yeah. Well, that was what the Matrix 2 started as.
Yeah. So you guys know, well, you guys, you would know that it's a clomberry,
but there are no clomberry, nobody's found a clomberry in years. They said there's one
in the world.
I just think to myself, I know that thing likes clomberries.
Yeah. And you can walk right by it. I mean, if you're turning invisible and you get to the door.
So just you inside now, you see, it's a pretty dark
the
So yeah as you walk by some of the guards
You realize that they seem two-dimensional
And that they are actually cardboard cutouts of regular guys
as you walk further into the mansion you see a
living room where a man a man made of magnets or tiny little magnets is
Sitting on a couch
My name is Barry Gee. I became
proficient in in the field of bombs making and reviewing and
testing
Mostly I
Test bombs the way I saw would test wines
So I blow them up in my house
Reaction to how strong they are and then I post my reviews online
So I did that for a couple years until I became very heavily invested in stocks
And
Stuff like that
So now I'm a huge business mogul magnet, and I'm also made out of magnets like in the new matrix
So yeah you blow toss
I'd say like you've kind of been you're kind of at the tail end of your invisibility
You're probably gonna return to visibility like in the next 10 seconds
Yeah, but you see this guy sitting on his couch and that is the Barry key as Sullivan described him a older man made of magnets
I mean, why is there anything really expensive I can grab and put in my pocket before I turn visible again
Barry geese or anything really expensive inside your living room. No, it's very barren and also it's very dark in here
So you can't really see what's going on
Anything but my face eliminated by my phone
My favorite social media this year of the future is a m2
Inspirational business posts or for several hours. Mm-hmm. Okay. Well, then I don't take anything
I'm dealing with a beast.
So if you'd calm down.
Oh, the guard tower?
No, he's outside.
My grandfather died there.
Damn it.
Come on.
Damn it, you got the joke right.
What did you say?
Your uncle fell there?
Stupid ass.
Yeah, I mean, so we can cut back to Pat, you and Sullivan.
[laughter]
Stupid ass.
Um, yeah. I mean, so,
we can cut back to Pat,
you and, uh, Sullivan,
with the guards. They're about to start a fight
with you. Okay. Um, but also
Ray, you're...
are you sneaking past
the, um, the beast?
I'm trying to sneak right under
its legs. Okay.
Oh wait, it's a clombo. It's a
the
legs like a clumbo. Roll stealth. Okay. Hmm what is my stealth? You're going to need to
get a critical. That is still not good enough. You were trying to sneak underneath a guy?
It's a clumbo. It's an enormous creature. Yeah. No. No. But what if I just did? Patches
if an ant snuck between your legs you would notice it?
This is not...
I notice every ant.
Clombo's size to people's size is not me size to ant size.
Don't say anything about me being short.
Your ant is about to be fat.
Your ant would be way too big.
You would be sneaking under the ant.
Okay.
The Clombo...
Fucking...
fucking
combo like notices you sneaking underneath but with a 17 like notices
you on the later side of it and starts a sniff the air and sort of catches I see
him oh what's that smell oh my god do you smell that man yeah um roll
initiative. Oh my god I have to kill this fucking... Just run away. Just escape into the house.
I got a three. Ah shit. Clombo's gonna roll for initiative. He got more than a three.
Clombo's gonna go first. Yeah, no way. He's going to shoot Clombo breath at you. So you're
you're gonna need to roll a dexterity saving throw.
Does he not speak English?
No, it's a combo.
Oh, pretty fucking good!
Nice, yeah, you're only gonna take half damage.
The combo breath shoots at you, and you are going to take...
Did you write combos before Fortnite put them in?
No.
What do you think?
Yes.
You should have fucking said yes, you idiot, we could have sued them.
Yeah, they would have believed that.
get
stream last night yelling about combos.
(laughing)
- That bond doesn't exist.
- He's missed me.
- Yeah, you take 12 damage.
- God damn it.
- But it's your turn.
You could use your full movement
and probably get away from this thing.
- I'm gonna do that.
I don't want the smoke with this combo.
- Yeah, so you use your full movement
and you run into the mansion.
You crash into one of the cardboard cutout guys.
the
My friend I'm the God here
All right. I'm I'm just gonna step away Pat and he wants to fight both of you. No
And I guard all the all the crap in there and I and the guy
I'm a good guard the guard now takes out his phone and he calls you
Barry Gee and he says
boss, there's a
There's a some sort of like deficient Yoda
Here, do you want me to I'm not deficient. I'm big-boned
Do you want me to do something about this or what?
Yeah, take him out to dinner
And I hung up and I don't explain
And he looks at you and he says
Do
I'm just gonna give you my number and he starts to write down his number. Oh
Okay, the number that he writes
Yeah, he says let me find
Cameron's number
Contacts here it is
one
It doesn't three four
And he gives you the number and he says uh, I guess just call me when
If you want to get dinner sometime, I'll take you out. Mm-hmm. You're gonna let me in to the building to God everything
Yeah, fuck it. Okay, just like open the door
And lets you in and yeah, you all at this point can come meet Barry Gee
Famous
Bomb expert slash Instagram entrepreneur
Old magnet man. He's a V folk by the way, so that's he's an older model of V folks
So before they could fully just be in the real world
But just face your things they were kind of like these magnet looking guys
Yeah
So and Sullivan kind of goes up to you very good. Hello, mr. Gee. Oh
Hi Sullivan
Yeah, that was
Lying the whole time no, why would I lie this guy this guy?
I've been investing in all the things that Barry G's been telling me. It's been going really well
I think what kind of things does Barry G like to invest in Sullivan or shirt?
well
Barry doesn't really tell me but but he says I'm
Numbers are going really far up right Barry. Listen our latest
Latest product Barry bombs is doing really well in Southeast Asia
We don't want to talk about it much but the numbers are up and that's all you need to hear it be in Sullivan
Yeah, see that's what I'm talking about
Anyway, Barry Gee, we're trying to rob a charity
really
Why?
well
You don't like it, but if you like it the three of us came up. Okay, who are any of you?
I'm I just took 12 damage from your combo. Thank you very much. Oh
So well, that's nothing. It's not mine. It kind of just emerged and he eats everything on its path
Really? I've been told it wants some special treat, but I don't know what it is
Is it a new season at the Barry G
Mansion
Twister towers just came back to my kitchen
Anyway, we need your help
Yeah, I don't know pretty experienced con guys there in high skies, you know, they're pretty talented. Yeah, I do a lot of cocaine
He does a lot of cocaine
Alright, I need to hear this plan out. Tell me your plan. What are we thinking here?
the
So I'm gonna stop you right there Sullivan all that is bullshit and crap, okay, it won't work
Okay, you need is I have no buddy
I think he's some sort of chimp. I forget what his name is. I met him 20 years ago
He's the only only guy who could probably crack this this sort of job. They're trying to do
Do you mean Travis ocelot?
Yeah, he means Travis. Oh what yeah, it's a
Mm-hmm. Oh, he oh he was right. Oh, no. Well, okay. So where do we find this Travis ocelot guy? I
Forgot
As long as we don't have to go to some other planet
Chimps or something
Oh god.
Alright, okay, wait, so.
But uh, yeah, you would know that Travis Ocelot is a former, like, CIA type of guy, part of
the Bureau of Mean and Nasty Spies, and also a prodigious shot, known for disabling security
systems with his dual Golden Deagle technique.
Um, as of now is whereabouts are, um, known to be only to
Barry Gee as earth, um, where he is on a mission, uh, infiltrating
chimp geopolitics.
Um, and that's, that's what you would know.
Uh, um, Barry Gee.
I just said all of that.
Yeah.
And you also want to go meet my, my, my friend Tyler too, at the airport.
He can see Tyler too.
Yeah.
I would also be able to give them, uh, the, the one of Travis
Ocelot's golden guns, the other of which you lost, he lost in a job.
Um, which made him swear off doing heists.
Wait a second.
Barry G what's that there golden thing in your hand?
It's a golden deagle made for awesome shots
Can I have it for no reason no
Whatever she's name was this champ
We go give it to Travis ocelot ourselves
And save you the trouble unless you want to come along
You're suffering from
9,000
Over 1 million so I can't really leave the house. I
Take that and I put it in my fucking mouth
They were all for damage
No, no, no, I don't want to kill you unless you actually want to do that I didn't put it in my mouth
He didn't let me
No, I have 41 hit points so I'd be fine it'd be like the end of Fight Club
Well, yeah, you guys would be giving that information
Jubio, thank you for being a good sport. I know you've got covered 9,000, so a million,
covered 9 million, 1 million. So thank you. And you guys would head to the airport where
you would meet... Tyler 2.
Oh God. Say it again?
I have it written down. Tyler 2.
So this is this area would be a it's sort of a field surrounded by low level like hangers iron and asphalt. It's kind of barren
Uh, this place is dedicated to interplanetary travel, which is not really that popular in gun city. It's kind of a bunk investment
Um, there are no really other planets to go to besides earth and earth kind of sucks
Um, but there's some general tourism interest and some people just shoot themselves skyward and see what happens
um the
interplanetary travel in gun city
at least this facility is run by Smith and Wesson.
So what you do is you go into a bullet, you go into a gun container,
but you get shot out of orbit.
And then the pilot pilots you in the bullet to, in this case, Earth, which is like the only planet there.
So you get there and you see a five foot three orc named Tyler Two,
who's bald and wears a tank top.
And, uh, Barry G what would you have told them about Tyler to his personality?
So Tyler too, he's a very short guy.
He has a weird shape head as well.
Don't mention any of this.
Don't call, don't call him short.
Don't call him shorty.
Uh, don't mention his height.
He's going to bring up the fact that he's six, four, just go with it.
If you want something from him, if not, uh, you'll, you'll get on it.
And it's bad side is a very temper temperamental guy.
You don't want to do that.
And so you see, you see, as you're approaching this area,
you see, hey, my name is Tyler, too.
I'm six foot four.
Nice to meet you guys.
What's up, Shorty McBald Smald?
Hey, short snack.
Hey.
He runs at you guys head first.
Little snack of pancakes.
Roll initiative.
Kill Tyler, too.
Nine.
OK.
The 12.
I'll blow it to us.
You go first.
OK.
the student
okay go for it
we're going to read all of the great failure
so much better
i'm issued again
yet that it's a very rich
i should have returned damage
they should pretend that it was
i'm sorry
andy uh... he immediately stops by the you guys
what do you need
i don't remember
which posted fly in your bullet to earth
Oh, your friends have a...
Barry Gee sent us.
Yeah, Barry Gee. Okay.
Alright, I can help you guys.
Um, let's just get inside the bullet here.
And he's like limping and bleeding out.
And uh, uh, you guys can get some...
Do you need help or anything? I mean, are you okay?
I'm like 6'4", so it's pretty easy for me to navigate a lot of things.
Oh yeah, a lot of love is on your body.
6 inches, 4 centimeters.
*Screams*
Roll for initiative.
I shoot him again.
*Laughs*
Okay, roll.
Roll to shoot him.
Okay.
21.
Alright, roll for damage.
8 damage.
Okay.
He, uh, yeah, he would shoot him again and then he would roll for initiative.
He's got, he's pretty low, he might die soon.
Um, so, he's like, "Ah!
I'm sorry!
Okay!
Alright.
Let's just, let's get in the bullet.
Let's get in the bullet."
And uh...
Just before either of us say anything else, just input the coordinates to where we need
to go right now.
Because I can't...
I just need to make sure for no reason that this ship can operate without you.
Yeah, of course!
And he puts in the coordinates.
And he's like, "Okay!"
Now I'll just press the start, the go button...
Can you reach that button?
Might have to go on your tiptoes.
AHHHHH!
Roll for initiative.
*laughing*
kay
I got a 20
alright everyone roll
okay Patrick Odie you go first
alright I'm gonna fuckin smack the shit out of him
*laughing*
kay
you can roll for damage
*laughing*
dude describe your kill
10 damage
*laughing*
so
how tall is he really?
5'3
oof
on a good day
and way smaller than him.
I think we're all for the most part small.
So I fucking I mean, you know,
I'm swinging it like I got it like like how Rod Carew used to.
Yes, I have it in bunt. Yeah.
No. And I just go down and then up,
up right into his into his balls.
And because that happens,
He throws up all of his organs, right? Like it's like a garbage pail kid. It's like inside out kind of yeah
Yeah, it all all of his organs. It's like that part in that
And nobody's gonna know that movie. Never mind. No, what's up?
I do not support what he's been doing with the CDC. Okay
the
that 27. I now have a Tyler 2 hoagie. It's just a little guy that I swing around with.
And he's dead. He's dead. Oh, a five dollar foot long. You see your hoagie starts to sweat,
it's getting angry, it's starting red. And yeah, you guys fly in this bullet towards
Earth. So, for most people on planet E-Bomb, Earth is a footnote in your textbooks. Once
the third cataclysm took place, all the poor people who were too stupid, lazy, or just
too damn ugly to mean anything were left to fend for themselves, while all the beautiful
rich people escaped to planet E-Bomb. Because the people who remained on Earth were so poor
and stupid, the entire global human infrastructure collapsed in a week. Billions died and billions
more were isolated from one another, clumsily adopting whatever remaining technological
advancements allowed them to hydrate and feed themselves with some regularity, fend off
especially harmful diseases, even cobble together the occasional urban center. Most of all,
they fucked rapidly and indiscriminately with both man and animal and plants and objects.
The interest in earthen affairs wavers on E-BOMB, with the powers that be generally
airing on the side of "Why bother?" but not for the gun city bureau of mean and
nasty spies. They've been targeting Earth for centuries, using it as a guinea pig
for any ops that they want to do, they can't get clearance for at home. And so
we arrive in a dense jungle of somewhere Earth where a chimp clave was under
intense study. Chimp claves are formed all across Earth. In reaction to the void
of intelligent and important people, chimps have risen up. Nothing substantial,
but since there are no other nations worth disrupting, chimp geopolitics are
all that remains. Whether the valorization of Chimp Claves is based on an actual observation
of some semblance of organized political will among primates, or just an intergovernmental
psyop courtesy of the Bureau and constant need to justify funding, no one can say.
And as you guys land, you see this Chimp Clave, Mr. Travis Ocelot.
I have built a perfect killer primate society. An outer haven for psycho apes, guarded by
My 20 Gatling Gorillas, 200 sex-starved bonobos toil away in my 50-acre terraformed outdoor
Xanax plantation, synthesizing dose after dose of high-octane alprazolam for my super-chimp
soldiers to keep them disoriented and confused and ready to snap.
My harem of eight orangutan wives work all day stitching and stuffing tickle-me-elmo
dolls because soldiers need something to fight for. Soon our troop will disfigure,
unthumb, and chew through this whole rotten world, and the title of dominant
species will once again belong to the hairy knuckle-wobbler, and the upright
tower of bipedal man will tip over. You guys arrive at this chimp clave, and yeah
Travis, Ocelot, you see them as they land.
Um, what do you do?
Uh, I guess I recognize them faintly from my old life.
But I still, I still bear my, uh, my insignificant canines.
In a chip display of aggression.
One of your, uh, uh, Gatling gun gorillas says,
"What do you want to do, boss? Should I shoot them now?"
Let's hear what they have to say.
Hi!
He's smiling up there!
Hello!
Hi!
I love you!
He's smiling bigger.
Hi!
What a cute smile he has.
I love you!
We have a guy!
He's just- Kosolin's waving around the Golden Deagle.
Bring it in!
Oh, so the light of the- What was he saying?
I'm saying.
Hi!
Okay, so I guess the light of the gun is now glinting in my eye, and maybe there's like
a faint recognition.
*laughter*
Rubio's trying so hard to distract me, he's trying to get the banana filter.
Is- is Barry Ghi or- is he on the-
No, he's not with us.
He's got COVID-19 down.
He's fuckin'.
Alright. Um.
So yeah, I guess now I definitely recognize the gun
because my human arm, my left arm,
is still clutching my gold desert eagle,
although my right chimp arm is completely empty
and tense with curdled anxiety.
- Sounds like you need a Xanax.
(laughing)
Okay, so yeah, I reach over to the plantation and I pop a single Xanax in my...
I get like the eyes from Naruto briefly.
Yeah.
You see one of your orangutan wives who's like,
"Honey, I told you! You don't need Xanax! You have to stop!"
I lift my chimp arm as if to say, "Relax."
And then she goes back to nursing four ape babies.
(laughing)
She has four breasts.
She's like, she has the breasts of a four-legged mammal.
- She agrees.
- Yeah.
I tell the gowling gorillas to put their guns down
and I gesture for the trio to come onto my temple steps.
Sullivan's supposed to-
Can I-
I'll stay here. I'll just- I'll stay here.
I'm still waving.
I'm- I'm just going-
Hi!
I love you!
You guys, uh, approach the temple.
Um, what does the inside of your temple look like?
Um...
It's decorated with the impaled heads of, uh, anyone who would ever, uh...
Discontent or anyone who would ever be discontent with my society
And there's also a few used diapers
Disemboweled tickle me almost yeah, I'm waving to those two
Mr. Asa rot
We were sent here about Barry Gee we need your help. We've got a big heist we have to do and
Only you and your golden double deagle trick shot is that's the only way we can do it. I feel like
Hi
Golden double dick you're that Travis awesome. I thought you were a different guy. I remember you
Oh, oh the one with the giant chip fortress. Yeah
It just all making so much I just processed it. What's up, man?
What's up, hi and hi I love
It's true many years ago the nation's Federation
Began work on the list three months terry the project designed to create the perfect soldier
Travis the chimps DNA was recovered to create two clones
solid Travis and liquid Travis
Hi, and Liquid Travis 8 saw the Travis's face in the test tube.
And now Liquid Travis lives through me, through this arm. The man you called Gold Deagle Ocelot no longer exists.
I have no affinity for that tawdry and gaudy weapon anymore.
I love you! Why should I bother? I love- I- well, hello.
Why should I bother with a measly firearm when I have a chimp arm?
You think this hand would be more useful if its fingers are made to tangle about the handle of a gold-plated handgun?
Chambered in 50 action express my hand must remain empty and open
So that I may mangle about the faces and thumbs of my enemies now
I will show you Travis's power hold out your faces at hand so I may rip them off
I hold out my face in my hands
Me too.
I guess I'll do it.
This is the first time I've ever seen such instant fealty.
No one has ever...
Do you like this?
I love you!
Hi!
I now am remembering the friendship of these individuals who I've gone on many heists with.
I've never seen actual hairless human faces in 30 years.
And my fused form face factor is-
Yeah, no one else can hear us!
Yeah.
I just thought about it.
Fused form face factor of my brain is
undergoing the same transformation as, like,
as it would under an
ayahuasca trip.
I remember who I am all at once.
And my eyes-
Have we got ice cream?
I- Now I'm remembering I got ice cream.
*laughter*
After a yoga.
Um.
And yeah, I guess now my eyes
are just sort of fixated on the on the golden gun. So what do you say? My
chip-bomb starts to vibrate. What do you say Travis? You up for one last job?
Question mark?
So now I pick up the gun. I remember this feeling. The balance. The ambidextrous
union, the akimbo stability, the pure shiny symmetry of the dual-wielded weight. I remember
my time as a special operative trickshot expert, my across-the-map bullet drop kill on JFK
at Dealey Plaza, my reload-canceled triple headshot on Paul McCartney, Avril Lavigne,
Dave Chappelle, my double 360 no scope with two gold plated heart attack guns on Bernie
Sanders.
It's all coming back to me.
And it feels right.
And then I remember we got we got taco tacos.
I do it over the shoulder juggle both desert eagles while I remember the taco truck.
That was awesome.
Yeah, that was the only chocolate truck I've ever seen that had ice cream tacos
Is it gonna be hard for you to say goodbye to your kingdom that you have built for yourself here
uh
the magazines of my golden desert eagles extend into
infinity and I
instantly do gun kata on my whole chimp tribe and
I killed them all in three seconds
Whoa!
That was so cool!
Now I remember why I like you.
Cause you kill monkeys!
Yeah, and he did that to the taco truck on us too!
Wait, is there any monkeys involved in this heist?
I can't remember.
Are we like attacking a monkey chariot?
I don't think so.
But you should be okay.
Yeah, I'll figure it out.
This is a magic- when you get nervous, close your eyes and imagine everyone's a monkey.
Don't- please don't do that.
Um, are you in?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, sounds fun.
[laughter]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I'd burn it probably.
[music]