[MUSIC]
Last time on Gun City, the Temple of Tepenguin of Doom.
Our heroes finally made it in to the...
Wait, hold on.
They didn't make it into the Temple of the Penguin of Doom.
They went back to town.
They talked with three weird guys.
And they made a new Sullivan, who has become a fan favorite, and maybe already has a three-picture
deal with Paramount. Then they went to the temple. The actual Sullivan, Crud now, helped eat out a
door. So sort of continuing the theme there. And then they were let into a large atrium with
strange stone and other material on the ground of various, you know, origins.
And they saw a large egg of some kind. After doing a bit of exploring and attempting to solve puzzles,
they realized that they should do matter over mind and slid down a mud, little mudslide thing,
and ended up in a room where they fought their analogouses.
*laughter*
Right.
After a near-death experience with probably the most brutal fight our heroes have ever seen,
they ventured down a secret passage through a staircase and discovered the lost city of Tamatau.
Yeah, I mean there's a bunch of other little things in between but that's a broad strokes.
I think you guys should be up to speed both the view list the viewers the listeners at
home and the listeners on the zoom call.
But yeah, so Snoochie Boochies obviously seemed completely elated and excited seeing this
sort of vast town or city of some kind.
It looks like it's under a cave.
And I believe I described it a bit last time,
but just in case, I'll give a little bit more description to that.
But first of all, actually, I should say,
because you guys were knocked out cold,
and I was reading over some of the rules in the game,
and it's pretty clear, I mean already I fuck with the rules all the time, but I think it's pretty clear that you should be able to do a short rest, like half an hour, get one HP back, and you're up and ready to go.
I thought we rolled hit dice.
Yeah, we rolled hit dice for that too. No, I guess I was, this was saying this mostly for me, I think.
Oh, okay.
Like, ah, the rules are, say, I'm sorry.
[laughter]
Whatever.
But yeah, in case there's some sort of missing what it was called or what it looked like,
it looks like this Chrome 60s sci-fi, when there was sort of a utopian vision for the
future in the early, during the 60s and 50s kind of thing.
almost like a like translucent floors that you can see computer wires in it
despite all the grime because this is sort of like a city underneath like a
cave or like a city in a cave it's like underneath the temple you can still see
sort of like what its former glory would it would have been it shine and I think
I said this last time it looks like a Sid Mead painting which I suggest you
guys look up Sid Mead you'll get a sense of what I mean it's like a grimy Sid
me
pretty old. He looks like he has like powder all over him or something. Is this a guy from
Devils Rejects? Yeah. He's got a blue nose. He does have a blue nose. Why does he have
a blue nose? Look at this guy. What the fuck? Everyone at home look up Sid Mead paintings.
Church Sid Mead fappening.
A lot of good stuff here.
Um, but yeah, uh, uh, Snoochie Boochie is sort of like excitedly looking things over.
He's sort of like, "This is, this is the town I remember.
This is what I remember from my childhood.
This is the kind of place, this is what the Tamagotchis were capable of."
And, and you guys would see, like, all these, like, beautiful buildings, um,
But also like you'd see really incredible like artifacts probably worth a lot of tokens.
Digital clock radios, Google Wi-Fi devices, Alexa's, like laser tag toys, Palm pilots,
techno robot dogs, you know those robot dogs.
Even massive things like a huge animatronic Weird Al commissioned by John and Hank Green.
tanning beds. There's like a bunch of tanning beds to around.
So it's a little bit eerie down here.
Obviously, there's sort of like a lot, you know, a quiet is it's
pretty obviously abandoned.
You can sort of faintly hear a Furby singing.
Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, like way in the background that
kind of makes it a bit and a Hulk smash from like a Hulk glove
somewhere else like you hear sort of like the ambient noises
of devices past but you guys can obviously investigate this
place or look around or see what it is.
But I'm going to try to imagine like a massive beautiful utopian
city that sort of a grimy and filled with rock and mud.
Yeah, and it's designed by a guy that looks weird.
All right, investigating people can't choose the way they look.
I got a 14.
Okay.
Yeah.
I mean like depends.
What do you what do you I guess I said investigate but it's like
what are you looking for?
Do you want to find a way back up?
if you wanna find an artifact.
- Yeah, are we supposed...
Is there something down here we're supposed to look for
to open the egg?
- Hey, is Snoochie Boochie with us?
- Mm-hmm.
- Hey, Snoochie Boochie, what's the deal with this?
- What do you mean, the whole?
- Well, I mean, this is like your city, right?
- Yeah, what's the deal with this?
- So what's going on here?
What's the deal?
- Yeah, what the hell is all this crap?
Okay, alright, that's fair.
Well it seems that the temple is the only thing that is standing from the city's past
and below here is where the city was.
So perhaps there is another way up through the city, because we are sort of in a cave,
but as far as what we might be looking for here to help open the egg, I don't know.
Oh, look right there. There's the elevator from Willy Wonka.
And it's an egg key that opens eggs.
Oh, it's shaped like a key for an egg.
It's shaped exactly like the keyhole that was on the egg.
Oh, you two must have hit your heads on the way down here.
Oh, I can see right there.
We did it on the rock that makes you see the truth.
It's right over there.
I would like to play with Sullivan.
Hey, hey buddy.
Wow.
You want to play?
I'm taking like a thousand pictures of Sullivan like you do when you like hang out with your friends in middle school like when you just got a baseball.
I realize he's just one of the rabbits from Raging Rabbits.
I love him so much.
Sullivan, let's go!
Can we have a dance party with him?
I would like to boogie with him so badly.
Yeah, you guys boogie. Do you want to boogie a bit?
Yeah, I boogie hard.
I'm spinning on my head.
Yeah, roll a performance check to see if you all boogie.
he's like inexplicably in a bikini.
Oh yeah.
I got 22 dude.
Fuck, I'm tearing it up.
Nice, yeah, all of you did really well at boogie.
You're all having a really good time.
I look at Suji Buji's like, "I'm impressed."
Yes, actually.
All right, so we did our part.
Now you figure out how to open the egg.
Okay, well, let's go towards where the ceilings are.
it's lower in the cave. Perhaps we can find something there.
Because perhaps there's a way out. What about those stairs over there?
Those are the stairs we came from. Well, can't we go back up the stairs?
I mean, there was well, there was the slide. Look, let's just let's just walk forward.
Okay, fine. Yeah, I mean, you guys can also like do a
a bit of a a you can do like investigation checks to find your way through this place
or like a history check as well.
Yeah, it's a city history first.
Okay, I'll do a history check as well.
Do a history check to see what you guys can recall about this place.
I got a three.
I got a 24.
I got a yeah.
Your archaeological prowess, Ray William Johnson, is really crazy.
You understand these cities pretty well and how they're structured.
Oftentimes they have sort of passageways that lead to some of the more utility buildings,
things that involve turning power on and power off and could help probably have different
pathways to get to a higher level inside of this kind of location.
pretty familiar with like the architecture and structure and sort of getting a sense
of the cave. You imagine that there's a certain like basically like a little bit more West
and like what you are thinking of as West because where you're facing is North. You
could probably find a way up. I would say with that kind of check. Okay, I I pick up
Sullivan and I play some I kind of like carry him on my hip with one hand and I start heading
in that direction. Whoa. And I feel like I said like tickling
his chin with my left hand finger. Ha ha you awesome.
He's learning a lot of words. You're getting a little too.
Oh they grow up so fast.
And yeah, so yeah, you guys walk a bit further
down in that direction. You start to see all these
beautiful sights and of the city of lost past you see sort of like
these monuments to other time got cheese they've come in past ten much I'm
in my chief
members the other names but they're there and
I'm role a perception check all you right now
25 shit 14 forgot you're too good at perception
mmm just like a real life
in yeah I'm
1616 with a 25 Patrick Yoda you see you notice something sticking out of the ground.
In some of the rubble of one of these beautiful buildings.
A bit further in the distance a little bit off course from where the where Ray William
Johnson's leading you, but not so far off course, but you see something that that catches
your eye.
You see an N on it, actually.
What does it stand for?
One day that will work.
Yeah.
I'm going to go investigate it.
Yeah, sure.
Head over there.
You start moving away the rubble.
You find an N-gauge.
I pick it up and I open it, I open the phone and I start going through it.
It's like dead.
It's battery, it's like I take my battery out of my PSP and I put it in the N-Gage.
Yeah for sure.
Okay.
Yeah you put it in there and the N-Gage which takes double A batteries which also the PSP
takes, everything takes double A batteries.
you're able to start to you're scrolling through the context and it's written in like an ill
like a language that you you can't read at least right away.
Yeah like the Mr. Saturn font.
Yes exactly like the Mr. Saturn font but it's for Tamagotchis.
You can roll an intelligence check to see if you can read it.
Okay.
It'll be history.
Yeah.
19.
That's good.
Um, yeah, so you get the sense that this belonged to a like
businessman who used to live in the Tamagotchi town.
I go through his email and I find out that he's the Craigslist
killer. Yeah, you find out he's a Craigslist killer.
The Craigslist killer was in the Tamagotchi town.
You would also recall I would say that this was something that
Leo, the collector, was looking for.
He's never been able to get an end gauge.
I pocket it and I don't tell the rest of them.
Okay, cool.
Alright, yeah.
Okay, so you head back, join the rest of the community.
Well, I pocket it, I pocket it, because I think it's...
Never mind.
I was trying to think of a motivation for it, but...
Whatever. I'll have no motivation for it.
It's kind of funnier that way.
Alright yeah, you pocket it, and uh, as you're walking back, you hear a...
Hey, hey Pat, what you got there?
How the fuck did you get down here? I thought you were up there!
Yeah, well, woah, what the fuck? Woah!
Oh, sorry, I forgot he was up there.
Go back up there right now!
Are you a genie?
I rolled a perception check for him and he did so well, it was like, oh he probably noticed, but I forgot he was upstairs.
he's israel's sorry he just like floats you know it's not a good story the cave
floor
i think the rest of the
the and that guy's all right now let's carry
now let's figure out how to get back upstairs
so i think i have
you know if you guys are not going to keep walking
yeah yeah you guys keep walking towards the uh...
the direction rewind as we need to tell us that that's where we're going
Yeah, yeah, I know I was wrong.
And you reach and you reach a a large building that is is
weirdly like square shaped compared to everything else.
You've seen his head all these like weird angles and smoothness
to them and likes like all very nice and sculpted and this
one's sort of just like a fucking block, but you also see
that the top of it is completely flush with the cave floor
and you see Stoogey Boogey's and he says that's our way up.
We can get to the top of this building and blast through.
We'll probably get to the other side of the back to the temple.
It's cube shaped.
You said how tall is it?
Is it purple?
It's about like it's like 60 feet.
It's a pretty fucking big building.
So even though it's like a like a cube is a purple.
It's not purple.
No doesn't have a handle.
does it have it's a gamecube on it
now
is it a gamecube
maybe
uh...
okay i go inside
i have an idea
way
yeah there are there at what are the windows look like
uh...
they look similar to the windows you seen where they're just they're kind of
like uh...
these uh... they have like uh...
like a half uh... oval
with like at the top of the or like uh...
one two three sides it's sort of like the top of a hexagon on top of a half oval that makes sense
and how many floors is it how many floors is it it's about four floors does it have so okay so
i just teleport to the out of out until we're the top floor you want to above the top floor just go
out oh shit i have to i have to stop you can you bring me with you do it on the fly just just just
nerf him say bro I did this is I have to live with this I have to live with this
wait okay but I stopped for long enough I stopped for long enough to hear what
the puzzle yeah no because I want to I might want to save it for another
another thing now but I have to personal next time I got a fucking nerf this I
have to figure out other internal logic because here's the thing because I've
thought about it and I was like, "Well, I could, to stop him from teleporting, I could
do this, but it's like, no, I don't want him to just like spawn in the middle of a rock.
That's not fair to him." And this is a big enough dungeon as it is. I've thought about
all this, but you still find no fucking way to teleport. So I can't stop you. I'm not
going to stop you. That's being a fair DM who's learned his lesson about letting somebody
teleport every three seconds.
You should, uh, you should nerf my worm, too.
It's getting out of hand.
Yeah, I'm...
I have literally said to you, I think, like, a few times, like, "Yeah, I don't think your
worms in your inventory anymore."
Uh, I'm actually looking at it right now, so...
Yeah, no, I'm sure it's back in there.
It says...
It says one.
Actually, it says two.
I have two...
Two huge worms now.
And if you keep talking, it's gonna be three.
So I will say that what you just skipped was pretty cool, but it was also a whole thing.
So no, kudos to you, this is how the game is played.
Cameron, can you take me with you?
Yeah, I'll take everybody.
Oh yeah, take everybody.
No wait, I'm not going to take anybody so you guys get to see the cool puzzle.
No, it's, yeah, I'll take everybody.
It won't be good for them to do alone.
Oh my god, damn it.
This is real time watching a DM fuck up, so I hope everyone appreciates this.
It's like those videos where the developers watch people speedrun their games.
And they're just like, "What the fuck is this, dude?"
Did you feel a dawning sense of dread when I asked how tall the building was?
Oh, yeah, but I knew it had floors.
That's what I wanted to cut.
I didn't want to say, like, "It's 60 feet, and also there's no, like, it's a big gymnasium."
Like, I can't say that. It's a building.
I was too concerned about it being a GameCube. I wanted to ask every feature. I wanted to
know if it had the Game Boy Player.
There was a Nintendo stuff in there. There was...
It doesn't matter. I'm saving it. I'm saving it. I don't want to spoil it.
You're gonna see like a cube in another arc that we do and it's gonna be like, "Oh, and
it says no teleporting allowed. If you do, I'll kill you in real life." It's weird.
So yeah, so you guys make it back to the top.
(laughing)
- And there's another cube that's twice as big.
- This beautiful city, you get past it.
And you know what I should do next time
is say you can only teleport to things you can see,
which I think is the actual rules of D&D,
but I did not specify that.
These are all things I'm realizing now.
- That's like the first rule,
like first nightcrawler rule.
- I know.
(laughing)
I would just shoot my gun upwards and I'd be able to see through the bullet hole all the
way to the top and teleport.
Easy.
At least that would create sound.
You can't.
Maybe I could do something with that.
No, you can't keep me down.
You're gonna try but it's not gonna work.
I'll just figure out how to get rid of it.
So you're back at the fucking top of this place except now you're back in the temple
except now you're on the other side of it.
that
is
I'm going to
the egg. Yeah, can I have the remote from click? You can't have the remote from click. You
could try to teleport inside the egg. I just want to see what's in there. You should try
to see if it's hollow or solid, probably, in case it's not hollow and you just teleport
into meat space. I knock on it. So yeah, you're back on this side. You knock on it, it's hollow.
I teleport inside to see what's up.
You see a fetus.
Oh my god.
Of a tamagotchi.
Yo!
I take it and I take it and teleport back out.
She's gonna die.
Yeah.
Sullivan is like, Sullivan sees you just appear with a fetus.
He's like "AHH!
What the fuck is that?!"
I don't take the fetus out.
I don't want it to die.
Okay.
Hey guys you made it back!
Shut up Crud.
Alright.
I think there's a really cool puzzle downstairs.
In this giant cube that I think you might be interested in.
Oh, okay. Should I slide down the slide?
No.
You know what, Crud, I've been thinking.
You know, maybe, maybe Crud.
What's happening?
Maybe Crud is not...
Maybe your name shouldn't be Crud, you know?
Really?
Yeah, maybe you just shouldn't have a name at all.
Oh, that's so much worse. Yeah, you're just gonna be like nothing
Okay, okay nothing yes, yeah cinnamon we're gonna call you nothing now
That's what we've been calling you the whole cinnamon the frog that's your fucking name
Right, right you guys that's what that was his name before yep, and now we have this new cinnamon I thought it was Suleyman
on
the i don't know i don't even remember it
shaughnessy
shaughnessy the frog
what but you you've been calling me so i'm i'm i'm just gonna
set the record straight
did somebody hear did somebody hear nothing just now yeah i think i heard
nothing okay alright i was a lot of it
i was walking away at all i was gonna walk away from the situation
where were the fucking day i'm gonna walk so while we're here yeah well he's
walking away I check the computer to see if the number is going down. We're in that room
that I couldn't figure out. You look at the computer and you see your ghost flying around
a grave. Is that it? Uh huh. Is that it? Do you guys remember how to do the puzzle? So
So from last time, what you would remember is that when you looked at the computer, you
got a really high roll.
Yeah.
When you looked at the computer, you'd see a ghost of your face basically flying around
the grave.
And when you looked away from it, you'd hear like a "ka-chunk, ka-chunk."
And then when you turned back around, you'd see that the numbers changed.
Well, let's get the number back down to zero.
Can I, okay, what if I take out the, because I still have some of the Xbox games in my inventory,
right?
I don't think the solution is Xbox games, I'm going to say.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
the computer right? Yeah. You have to have your back towards it? Yeah. So I give everyone
an Xbox game so we can use them as a mirror. Why, we just know how many clicks it's going.
Oh it's not, I thought it was a person. I thought, because you guys said it was like
a boo for Mario. So I thought that we would need something. Yeah, you look away from it.
Yeah, you look away from it, but I thought there was like somebody coming towards me.
It's a computer. Yeah, but I thought there was like a ghost in the room or something.
a
right now for the listeners.
Yeah.
You listen for all nine clicks.
And then leave the room,
I guess, or turn around.
Okay.
Yeah, you turn around after nine clicks.
You see the pedestal
shoot up again.
And you see it sort of
go back down.
And yeah,
nothing else happens.
What's the number on?
It's going back. As you're leaving the room, you hear "kachunk".
And it's back down to 9.
So was it 0 when we turned around?
It was at 0, but then it went back to 9 when you left the room.
What if we...
Oh, so just one person needs to stay here and look at it the whole time.
Okay, Crud, just stay... just...
We get it back to 0 and then I say, "Crud, you have to stand here and look at this computer for the rest of your life."
Yeah, 'cause you're kinda nothing. Like, it won't even probably register as, like, a thing.
the
that the golden thing on the pedestal
do you that golden i'd to do we have a whoever has it
to ever done i have it
somebody does it probably solvent does it
so i was a thing that's about his size and puts it on top of the pedestal but
is it
of self-invite
uh...
please tell me it's like oh yeah or a baby here and i think i guess you're
it's uh... it's uh...
while he's always
and i don't know what i'm talking about these learning everyday i'm so proud
and uh... yes and swear words while we're here
the penguin
this gold penguin which was a bop it
which became an egg which became a gold penguin
its mouth opens all the way open in your income
and like a beam of light
shoots out of it
uh...
uh... yet it turns a zero
and uh... it turns a zero and you can look through the window
and you see again that giant room filled with water
and you see a bit of light in it now piercing through to
we supposed to turn the
i think we turn them all to zero 'cause that's what the journal said yet term
although zero but the is the beam of light going towards the egg
i'm just trying to figure out like what how the puzzles work
just going out towards the room point ok
i think we should get the models here and then see what happens and then we can
figure out from there
because that's at least a thing to do
and so yes going what to do
yes you guys walk to the wheels you turn them all
to kitchen kitchen kitchen to zero
uh...
and uh... you see a beam of light
coming out from the a towards those windows
you see the room behind you
you see that we are door it was in front of you the couldn't get through it
seems to be like magically or technologically sealed
uh... you see it's a deluxe sparkle glow
and
you see the egg
start to shake
and
you see it's a to shake
a little bit harder
and you see
non
other than
all baby tamagotchi hot like catch out but it's also a huge it's like a giant
baby tamagotchi and you see like suchi bujji's go
whoa wait that's not a real tamagotchi and you see the baby tamagotchi just
like bloop bloop like hop out and like just
crash through the door that was there into the next room
and yeah you guys figured out how to reset the kombu gachi clock
Let's go!
Easiest thing I ever did in my life.
Yeah.
I think a big part of why it was so easy is that we got to skip.
Probably half of it.
Skipped a lot, gave some hints, yeah.
But you guys figured it out.
Okay.
Yeah.
I'm gonna dive into that hole with that little baby.
Yes, you go into that next room.
Hold on, pause, dude.
What the hell?
You're gonna dive into a little baby's hole?
And you see...
No.
uh... the baby time i got you again but this time now looks
he sees room filled with water is massive room
uh...
and
you're on what's like a metal platform
and the door behind you that just blew open
like just
shots that similar magical force field kinda comes up
and
he's had to realize that they're like these
mine carts on top of this pedestal on top of this like sort of conveyor belt
the overhanging this giant pool of water you're about fifty feet above it
and you see that those are filled with like
indiscriminate food pellets
uh...
and then you start to feel
the ground beneath you move
a_k_a_ the uh... the this metal bridge in front of you
uh... everyone role a uh... constitution check
saving throw I should say rather.
18.
20.
Nice.
Yeah,
like it moves so suddenly but you all managed to stand up and
stay up and then you watch as these mine carts start to funnel
into this towards the baby
and the baby's mouth just eats them
and then the
the cart the thing below you starts to go faster and faster
and faster.
and if you don't start running in the opposite direction you're going to end
up in that baby's mouth
uh...
and then
while you're doing that
uh... which you can react you could be characters that i shouldn't stop you
the
she
what
well i don't know what happens when you get you may have to figure that out
uh... and uh...
then you see that you see these cannons up top
that about like a whole lake and now policy
refifty feet up
basis room yeah about lakes there about seventy feet away
and another fifty feet near
you see them
point towards you
and
you hear them start to start up
and then
you see
them start to fire
what looks like
food pellets at you but these time this these times
they look like a little
uh... tomagotchi treats
sushi
burgers
all the little delicious tomagotchi treats
from the tomagotchi games that one's too big
the
I think I have a pizza one.
Okay, can you add like spaghetti?
I don't have a spaghetti one.
Can we get like multiples of each one in case multiple people want one of them?
So we don't have to like split it?
I mean you're going to have multiples of each one because they're going to be shooting out
of a cannon towards you.
And the street is real?
You're going to have to roll deck saving throws for that.
Deck saving throws?
I'm going to chop that shit.
Uh yeah, you can certainly try that too.
You can do like an attack roll.
Wait, so are we supposed to make sure that the Tamagotchi eats it?
I think he's not going to tell you everything, Pat.
Oh yeah! Party time!
Sullivan, get behind me! Okie dokie!
And he just sort of, he like jumps over you like Mario or Luigi or something.
No, he's perfect. He's himself and we're not going to bother him.
And, uh, okay, yeah.
you know that okay yeah yeah what do you mean yeah yeah say it back Wow
come on Sullivan you could say it back I pick up Sullivan to protect him from
from Ray William Johnson cuz I don't like the way Raymond Johnson's acting
around him right now I'm sorry I let I know I was moving a little bit if you
want
you guys hear anything? Oh my god! And yeah, roll for initiative you guys. 7. 4. Stellar.
Jesus. Oh my god. Wow, those are some really good initiative rolls. 7, 4, and 2. Those are
actually bad. What are you talking about? And so, yeah, and then I'll roll for Snoochie
Boochies. Uh-huh. What did they get? They got a six. Fuck. They did really bad. That's really
bad for them. What did nothing get? Uh, nothing got... a nat 20. I'm not kidding. I'll take
another screenshot. I'm not kidding. All right, man. Oh my god. Yeah, he just like is the only
paying attention I guess, so, makes sense.
Anyway, so, yeah. So, suddenly you see,
as this food is coming towards you, guys, so,
this is the order that you're in.
First, I'm going to need you all to make
dex saving throws as these foods,
these foodstuffs are coming towards you.
I got a ten.
Fourteen. Five.
Okay, with that, with all those, you all just get like fucking pelted by this food.
And you don't manage to like catch it or anything.
So it just sort of like gets pelted at you.
And you're now you the you.
Yeah, and Sullivan again.
No, I just was trying to remember whatever.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, yeah.
is
that
close to the mouth now.
Do I take any damage?
Of this baby that's going like, "Gom, gom, gom, gom, gom."
Just open him out.
You weird.
It's like Pac-Man.
Fuck it off.
You don't take any damage from getting hit by the food.
Meanwhile, I'll probably get in there too.
Suddenly you start to see rubber duckies start to appear in this massive pool of water.
Just like, "Boop."
the
they're not real rubber like nuts how far away are they
are you know what i mean?
nope that's canon now they're not real
they're not real so i don't have to worry about them
i hope they shut the fuck up
but they're floating right?
yeah they're floating in the water
ok and the water is toxic or no?
i don't know
i can't tell you that
he's so stupid he doesn't even know and he made it
yeah exactly
how close is the rubber duck in relation to the water
in relation to me.
Let's take out your measuring tool.
Oh right.
40 feet, 50 feet.
Ok.
Because I was thinking if I'm
in danger of getting eaten by this tamagotchi
I could just jump in the water and go
onto the rubber duck.
Because it's a big rubber duck.
We should test if it's toxic
first by throwing crud in.
the
move up a bit. But if you use your full movement, you'll be able to stay in the same place.
So Krud is just going to use his full movement to stay in the same place. He's just running
in place. That's all he's doing. Now, the cannons are going to go again. So they're
charging up their food and they shoot them towards you guys. So let's do either, you
know, you could do a dexterity saving throw or you can do like an athletics check if you
want to try to catch it
this year athletics
all all of us twenty
twenty-one all of you
okay i would do
i guess it is what it's it's better
uh...
uh... what do you know how many
okay
so yeah uh...
uh...
blowtoss and patrick you know that you managed to like snag
some of the food you catch it
uh... pretty definitely
uh...
Ray William Johnson, you got like knocked in the face.
Cut by a durian.
Yeah.
A metal spiked ball just flies out.
Where the fuck, who the fuck put that in there?
So you're like knocked prone at this point.
Which basically means like it takes half your movement to get up.
Okay.
So that's where you're at.
And now the rubber ducks are gonna go.
and they're just sort of like moving
towards you guys a little bit
so they are animate
well they have
directives
but they are not
they don't have souls
yeah they don't have souls
so I could take damage from one of them
is what I'm trying to ask
I mean I just took damage from a fucking
piece of fruit. Well that makes sense it was a projectile
yeah these things are projecting
towards you brother watch out
if you roll initiative and then something starts moving towards you, you should be afraid of
it. That's my personal rule of thumb, I think.
But now, looking at the initiative order, it is your turn, Patrick Ciota.
So I caught the food, right? I throw it in the tamagotchi's mouth from where I'm standing.
Yeah.
And roll athletics.
No, you're pretty close. You could just toss it in. It's got a big maw. This baby tamagotchi's
Like bomb bomb bomb and you throw it in there and you for a second it goes like
Hmm and it just keeps going on Dom Dom after that
But it seems a little bit satisfied
So we have to satisfy it. And so yeah, you see snitchy boochies and he says
Yes, we must feed the time. I got you. We love to eat food
We need to eat food to live. How come we can't fucking eat normal. I
Don't know. I did not design this game
So I know someone who did yeah, yeah
I'm talking to him an awful lot in my head. All right, I forgot you sort of established that
Mm-hmm. You have a psychic connection to God. That's right
God is a little I don't know about God
All right. Well, yeah, I think God's too much. Yeah, that's a
Little too much. Ah, yeah, I get it. Maybe maybe that narrator should check his ego. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, I'm God
God.
Fucking Bruce Almighty over here, what the fuck.
Oh man, if only.
He's so cool.
He is cool.
Alright, yeah.
Well anyway.
Yeah, that's your action.
What do you want to do for your movement?
Probably stay in place, I'll use my full movement.
Yes, you'll run.
Unless, I don't know, I kind of want to see what would happen if I jump in the water.
Maybe like put your toe in first.
the
up to about where we will be johnson is uh...
i stayed in place you know because
is using your full movement your full movement is using both your actions to
move out fuck okay yes that's danger yeah
uh...
so i hate danger
yet it is now stitching beaches turn
so uh...
Snoochieboochies is going to jump off this bridge.
Oh, can he reach?
No, he can't reach.
He can't reach that.
So Snoochieboochies is instead going to just sort of like run in front of you guys and
try to see if he can stop you guys from tumbling into the mouth of this thing as best as he
can.
So that's what he's going to do.
Now it is your turn, Blotas.
- Where am I on here?
- You are way in the back.
- Am I under Sullivan?
- You're over here.
- Oh, okay.
I have one of the, I caught one of the foods, right?
- Yeah, you did.
- So I throw it into the--
- 'Cause of your distance,
you will need to do an athletics check.
- All right, that's nothing for a guy like me.
- Mm-hmm.
- 19.
- Yeah, yeah, you fucking knock it out of the park.
And you see the baby Tom I got, you go,
Hmm.
These foods that are next to the conveyor belt.
Are these just are those actually like floating in the water there?
Oh, no, those are just assets.
I'm going to be using.
All right.
Yeah, and yeah, and it it you see it get kind of excited like go
and then you see it's transform
who into
a uh...
kid
sit on the dot g
and it lays down into the same thing works when i'm done done done done
uh... the outwardly now
i'll keep dole keep running away
and really johnson is your turn now
Okay, I'm gonna just desperately try to stay in the same spot. Okay. Yeah, I'm sorry. I'm just moving you over so I can see cool
Yes, you get up that takes half your movement
Then use the rest of your movement and you manage to stay in place
Using all of them. Well, you managed to move a little bit closer to like where where stoochie boochies was
So you're sort of protected by him, but you're pretty close to getting into this this teenager's mouth
Which is your own thing you got deal with?
Now we're back to the top of the order and you see this teenage Tamagotchi thing just go like oh
No, he's jacking off
That you do that in your bedroom you do that away from us if he's doing anything
He's there there's some shipping Jack for sure. It's just jacking out of his butt. He's pooping and this poop
That's how you jack off you freak
the
water as well.
And they have their own
initiative.
What the fuck?
That boy got brown come send him to the doctor.
All right.
It is now
solving the frogs turn.
Sorry cruds nothing's turn.
There we go.
Take you a minute.
So I guess it's nothing.
I said nothing happens.
Nothing.
Yeah, pretty much.
I mean like he's just trying to survive as usual.
I look at him and I'm like "Uh, nothing, are you gonna help?"
"I'm trying!"
"Sorry, did you hear something?"
"What the fuck?!"
And uh, yeah, now the cannons shoot more food at you guys.
So, what do you wanna do?
Catch it. Catch the food.
Did you have to use such a realistic poop image?
I thought that was good.
Oh, I got a 7. Oh, I got a crit 1.
Yeah, you did.
I get distracted by the poop.
the
this
turn
uh...
as
below tosses your turn actually is really sorry
uh... okay
uh...
and my
there
can i try and climb on to the one of the ducks
the one that you certainly can
i'm gonna try to do that
okay a role of clinics
another crit one
all my god you try to climb on the dock you just fucking slip and you're just
like stuck underneath it
like in the water or after all for that your next heard you know some of the
world will be more than slightly not doing well right now
uh... it is now uh... snitchy buchy stern
and he's gonna see the
the he's gonna try to
use all his might to like drag
uh... really johnson further from the stomach out she
so we have him role
just uh... role strength check and see what he can do
it's going to be pretty hard to do
you do to well he just tried to drag you really johnson's didn't work
uh...
he's like i'm sorry you're
it's not you know it's not that you're too heavy it's you know i'm strong i'm
no i'm i'm fat
you can all your at that all don't say that
he's a just let me dot wall
warrants all of them you're up there i said me but
while we
nevermind yours
yeah he's he's doing a little dance and he's uh... shaking his bones
in the bikini again
if i die now i die happy
that is the only way what you know what the hell always first sentence let's go
home i can't even be scared of that i'm too impressed all yeah
and uh... yeah it's now your turn
uh... patrick you know
uh...
so it's fifty feet
right at a worse was your turn first but does the uh...
yeah you know what i just let you do that
thank you
and so i'm
okay
should i jump off and then try to swim to one of the ducks
but do you think a really caleb
uh...
and why do you think is that if you jump off you have a really hard time getting
up
yeah we're also doing
will
like the rest of the the sort of floor of this giant like pool room.
Is it a valve?
No, why don't you ask you could just you know, I'm going to investigate that.
Yeah.
Later right now.
I'm going to try and save Cameron.
Yeah, unless if I have enough movement.
Yeah, you do.
I mean all you do is jump.
So, okay swim still.
Yeah, I'm going to swim to Cameron.
Okay.
Yeah, I mean you swim at half speed, you know, because can't walk as fast as you
swim.
so
not really you're sort of still like ten feet off from the this big rubber duck
which as you approach it it's like had like
like all the fuck i thought it was an animate
uh...
we would you think inanimate
what and he could be an animate i didn't think it had a conscious or anything
like that
we could just be are yet i guess it's fair about and uh... yeah it is now
ray william johnson's your turn
all right
uh...
i will
i wonder if i can give them
my worm
and see she is his
it hunger
or even they can grow to an adult who can be reasoned with
uh... i will give them a worm
do i have a hot but big hot dog bun
uh...
all-out with
all right will take out my soul
world
okay yeah
you throw it and it is able to start like chewing on the hot dog in the worm
on our mom mom and it's like
but you can roll over
uh... but i don't
the world is perfectly intact it was just small
are
thinking
the
a
that's the
and a few words.
Yeah.
Yeah, you can see Sullivan in the distance going, "Oh no!"
Like dancing.
It's good to know you care.
Oh yeah!
And yeah, it is now back to the top of the order.
And you see the cannons are coming out and they're shooting more food.
the
it uh goes to peck at you with its beak um and it just whiffs it just like misses and hits the water
um this other one meanwhile its eyes are glowing red and it charges a beam at sullivan
as in nothing what the fuck
and it misses though it like shoots a beam at sullivan's almonds like it's just like
like blows up in super eats water right next to sullivan
uh... or nothing
and uh... yeah and the poop meanwhile sort of continues to gamble and drift
sort of lazily in the water
it is now
your turn patrick you know
uh...
i'm gonna use
by animal handling to try and talk to the duck
go for it we would be trying to do i'm trying to persuade it to let us right
it's back
cargo for
twenty-two
okay what do you say
how you do this
who will be shipped
doing like a dad doing a donald douglas you know it
uh...
tomahawk
you know the dot you see the dot makes a look at you quizzically
and then lower its neck down
yes
rights i get on its back
okay yeah you're on the stocks back
it is still a way that i i yeah i think i had a lot of the people who have
camera
yeah
you see the dot kind of a cost you could stupid stupid it's just like
swims lazily out of the way
appear
uh... blowtoss you can agree with the like you finally breathe again uh...
uh...
nothing would have been able to help or something
some bullshit anyway uh... and it is now
uh... i was pretty does pretty pre crafty in his head i can i ask the duck
for help
right now can i ask can i have a strategy of playing with the duck
yelich and do that okay so i go
I'm not gonna do it again, but I'm yeah, I got you
Kim I basically I asked the duck if it can catch the food in its mouth for us like when the food comes out the
cannon mm-hmm it goes like
Is that I guess I don't know
It nods - okay
And yeah, it is now
Snoochy-boochies turn and
He's gonna try to get you out of there
Ray William Johnson, so he's gonna like reach his hand in there and do a text check to do that
Okay, he's able to safely like figure out a way to reach grab your hand and now he's gonna do strength. Oh
Shit, and he yanks you out of there nice
Well, he yanks you out of there. You like sort of tumble next to him. You're covered in like
Tama got you saliva
And he's like, are you okay?
No. Okay. All right let's keep running. And yeah and then it's going to be blowtoss.
Can I shout out to him and tell him to jump in? Yeah. Hey! I figured out how to
talk to the ducks! Okay and I care why? We can ride him like a boat. You want me to
Jump in that water. Maybe later
You see
Jump in man. It's the police like all the way over the frog
So when the frogs in a one-piece bathing suit he jumps in he's got like a little glass
And he's like, yeah, yeah, like it's a party animal. Oh
Well, I guess the water actually seems super cool you see some bubbles come out from underneath it because oopsies
Yeah, okay
Blow toss your turn
Okay, I'm so I'm out from under the duck now. I'm saying mm-hmm. Oh, yeah
Can I and the duck is gonna do our bidding right?
Can I miss that one is well I could do I get it is it easier for me to climb on it now?
Yeah, you can absolutely climb on I'm gonna
Like check it's not gonna shake you off. Okay. Yeah, Patrick Yoda can sort of give you a little help. Yeah, it's fine
Extend my hoagie. Mm-hmm. I don't know what else to do. I guess I shoot the poop
Okay. Yeah
Yeah
Roll an attack roll with the Gritch Gun
22 nice roll damage
9 nice. Yeah, you see part of the poop like shave off
Yo, he said you shaved the poop
Holy crap
And
Yeah, it is now
Ray William Johnson's your turn
Okay, I jump in the water. Okay, I know my friends and our party
This whatever side Sullivan jumped in on okay, he jumped inside with the rest of his friends
Yeah, see Sullivan, I'm cool too. Look at me and I tried to fart and I just shit my pants in the water
You make it harder
Yeah, you see Sullivan go Oh
stinky
He's learning so much in here, oh, yeah
Yeah, what do you want to do now that would you shit yourself, okay
Wait, I I have actually, you know
I'm gonna swim over to my hot dog worm and I'm gonna I'm gonna hop on I'm like a surfboard
Okay, yeah, so you swim underneath this giant metal bridge and you hop on your worm and
you're able to like float on it pretty well.
It's a big giant worm.
You're able to sort of stand on it and get your bearings.
Let's say roll a athletics just to see how you can balance on this worm.
All right.
Sorry about getting all this shit on your back, by the way, worm.
21, dude.
Nice.
Yeah, you've ridden this worm before.
That's right.
you're good
you're able to sort of perfectly see you're like kelly slater
this is easy
it's the only surfer i know
is that the bitch with one arm?
no
kelly slater is a guy
but his name is kelly
yeah it has
it is now
back to the top of the order
the food is shooting at you
uh... snoochy boochies is
able to
a
the
of this teenage tamagotchi.
Um, see how it does.
Nice, yeah.
Goom, goom.
It's like nom, nom, nom, nom.
And it's like, mmm.
And it's like, pretty happy.
It was pretty happy.
You also see another poo-poos come out.
Oh.
Look what you did, Ray.
And now it's your turn.
Uh,
blow no
will
that
like wow wow wow like right underneath Snoochie
Boochies on the bridge. Um so she sort of nods
affirming what you had said earlier about like
forget the bridge just jump on the ducks um
and now it is uh
blow tosses turn no sushi buchi's turn actually so she just jumps on the duck
the
and
as it becomes
and adult
uh... is adorable
and you watch it that's the cutest adult of the receipt of my life
you see it's no longer uh... uh... eating like going on on on now it's a sort of
moving its head back and forth and smile i'd throw my food
it's like that was off of its face
since
uh... the yeah and then another proof comes out
so we have to clean the poop up somehow
they take care of it on the gachi
i realize this now
mhm
uh... yes i wish i realized it earlier
well tosses your turn
uh...
can we can we ask snitchy butch is to talk to it
uh... what we do see
I wanna-
Hey, Snoochy Boochies.
You're a Tamagotchi, right?
I know you are.
Oh, wait.
How do you- how do we clean up the poop?
Because, I mean, I could just shoot it,
but I feel like there's maybe an easier way.
Hmm.
I'm reading here, it says "Press the B button."
[laughter]
Well, we could find the B button, if there's a B button in this room.
There is a B button, it's under the thing!
I go down to the B button-
the
down under the tomogachi
you dive down you see
uh... underneath the tomogachi
i think uh... the letter b
attached on top of a
plug that is plugged into a drain
uh... good so i uh...
i'd
unplug it
yeah you roll a strength check to pull that out
it's a pretty big fucking plug
fifteen
okay yeah
you pull that up
and you see the time ago to go all
all in like spin down into the drain
uh... no
you see the poop
and the water all the same
all flow all the way down into the strain
and as you do you start to realize that what you're seeing down there was some
other things and as it's all so he gets revealed
you see this like
beautiful lake
floor
of like a modern civilization so much of that area you saw underneath the city
and you see these like giant tomagotchi devices
and you see is that all the water drains in the rubber ducks are like plot
to the park
like the of the one that was like angry at you to sort calm down it's just for
their both dislike
non-sensual now
uh...
and that's the word i meant
it's not a bit
but the i think it's a and uh... they were really said she and i there if you
like
this
to
he's like underwater almost like and uh and it sounds almost like he's like being like been
auto-tuned so much that it's just like like he's trying to talk to you but it's like wow
get out of the [ __ ] pod so we can talk to you jesus christ and he gets out he goes sorry
before he gets out i want to feed him like 20 times yeah you hit the feed button he's like
This over and over he's like he's really fat he gets out. He's just like he's like three of him wide
He's like oh boy
Hold on and he's just like punches his stomach a couple times and it like goes in a little bit
Not all the way. He's like, oh shit
Hey, hold on and I pull out a thing of Tums
There you go, man, this is this'll fucking save your life
He takes the Tom's ik I I got it he goes back into the top of God's your room it just fills it with shit
and
He points down to the B button
Yeah, okay cool, yeah, it cleans up the poop and he goes down he's like I don't know why we we let ourselves
Sleep in our filth
We did that
Money
Yeah, well, there's only one door left and a head should be where the inward pass lies
Are you already I'm gonna use my last hit dice to heal up do I have another hit I
Have one left. So I'm just gonna use that and try and get to oh I have none. Okay, I didn't get to full
I'm at 45 now. I have two left. I'm gonna use them both. Wait, it said I'd well, I'm at 39. I'm still good
Okay, all right guys, let's go shut up somebody
Okay
see you guys walk through this door and
It's this beautiful silver door and you opens you up into this final room
A picture of it for later at the post
If you see these these four magnificent staircases and you see these massive
statues of
Celebrities gone, you know celebrities from the past who?
Have used the n-word pass in its most rudimentary form like suchi puchi said earlier
He's like these people were revered for taking advantage of realities shifting powers of the n-word pass
And as you sort of walk by each of them, you can hear like a little tidbit like a radio, like a fucking Disney fucking hall of presidents thing.
You guys want to check any of them out?
I want to hear them all.
You have to say them.
Every single one.
Okay, we'll start from the... yeah, you guys walk past the Jennifer Lopez one.
In 2001, when the Puerto Rican singer used the n-word in her hit song with "I'm Real,
Murder Remix," she was quickly condemned for her lyrics.
"For anyone to think or suggest to say that I'm racist is really absurd and hurtful to
me," she responded to the criticism.
The use of the n-word in the song, which was actually written by Ja Rule, was never meant
to be hurtful to anyone in any any way.
And you really think they'd have done it?
Second, you didn't get that one.
Yeah, she didn't.
The DM copied these from a really bad tablet website.
You see, she didn't even have to apologize.
She basically just said, well, the black guy wrote it for me.
That's the power of the N word bass.
you guys walk by the uh...
tim allen one
home improvement star tim allen stirred up controversy after he openly talked
about why he should be able to use the n_ word
i've had this argument on stage a million times allen told the temp pay times
i do a movie with martin warren's and pretty soon they're referring to me
hey my
uh... cameron can you please be used for this
i'm not gonna say it in real life but i've
people make this better i think
maybe not only that i don't think you want i don't know i don't know i was
headed that it implies that he said it though you're probably just christ
patches what the hell is that man
i do a movie with martin lahr it's been pretty soon the referring to me
hey my and words up except he says the word
so i'm the n_ word if i'm around you guys but seven feet away if i say n word
it's not right
it's a very confusing to the european mind how that works
*laughter*
oh fuck
uh
you walk by Gwyneth Paltrow's statue
the goop founder can't seem to avoid the
oh i'm trying to do the voice
the goop founder can't seem to avoid the faux pas
Gwyneth came under fire last year
when she tweeted a photo from backstage
at a watch the throne concert
with the caption
n words in paris for real
after
after unleashing a fury online
the
Yes, they're not like a more recent guy who did this.
So I'm kind of like space crab or something.
Yeah, you walk by Lenny the space crab.
There is I remember that one.
Yeah, it was just patches.
Who's this guy?
Please, I have one for each one of them.
Oh, never mind.
That's no Gibson.
the
of Quentin Tarantino, the king of the N-word pass.
He was able to say it as many times as he wanted.
He can make anybody say it.
The only white man to ever do it.
And you see hanging on him like a lanyard is the N-word pass in all of its glory.
This pass is going to...
You know, this power is maybe too great for most.
But...
I will be able to use it every so often, just to restore a few members of the Tamagotchi civilization.
There you go.
Okay, I just...
Thank you.
We will not seek domination, I promise.
You got the pass.
I grab the pass from him, and I say,
would never betray you and I turn to nothing and I say and we'll have a talk
about this when we get home I didn't do anything so if Sullivan didn't do it and
nothing didn't do it the double agent must have been Jim oh my god Jim you were a
bad guy the whole time um sure sure yeah I mean so you admit you're bad I shoot
Jim in the face before before he has a moment to do anything.
Okay,
we're on this attack 1819 nice.
14.
Hey,
not bad.
Yeah, okay.
All right.
So I would say that you don't get him by surprise.
He's kind of expecting you to attack him just because of like
where you're
You know what I mean? It's not like he didn't see it coming.
He got a 22 on his initiative roll.
So let me get him in here.
Give me one.
He's probably pretty easy to kill.
Oh shit.
Well, we got him pretty good last time.
He's just like a guy.
Where is he?
Yeah, wait, how did we get him last time?
I'm going to use that same ability again, dude.
Just you wait.
All right.
I'm going to.
I trust you.
I'm gonna fuck him up.
Take him down, dude.
Mmm, shit.
I thought I had him.
Where'd you go, Jim?
Looks like you don't even exist, Jim.
Jim, you exist less than nothing.
I win by default.
Nope, nope, I exist.
Fuck!
No.
Yeah, what if you don't, though?
Yeah, what if you didn't exist?
Yeah, prove it.
Prove you exist.
Tell me one ability you can do.
So he runs towards you, Blotas, and he takes out an office pen and, let's see how he does.
Yeah, that hits you.
Dammit.
You got 21.
And he elbows you in the gut and roll a, he basically like elbowed you in the gut and
is
just to see if you can or slight of hand maybe even.
That's fine.
Yeah, either way he's able to grab the inward pass from you
and you see bursting out of the another side of the place now
is the five Crayola ninjas and you see them them all stand on
top of each other and then all of them like to form and they
they start to glow and you see Snoochie Boochie's like, oh,
the
It's not colored in but it's really sick. And that's what the they turned into. They see Jim with the inward pass. He says
See now I can remake reality
it's going to be
I'm gonna be the boss now and
Not see him. Is it not? Oh, no, she got check this out
You should check this out. You're closing my eyes. You see him like scream
And your sound goes deaf.
You can't hear what he's screaming and you see the suchi
buchi's go.
No, like his mouth is silent as he's yelling it and you see
Jim scream and then like nothing happens and then he's like
I've been like anime like when you like the heartbeats again,
he's like the echo of themselves kind of thing and he's like
what's what's happening to me and you see him like he's like
transforming and he said he wished he wanted to remake his reality so he could
be the boss but he is a mere mortal he cannot handle such things you see him
like transforming and and he's like growing bigger and bigger and his arms
he's like breaking through his clothes he's butt-naked now he's like 10 feet
tall and then you see like more clothes start to grow on him and it's like weird
it's like coming out of his skin and it looks like some sort of brown suit and then a yellow
shirt underneath and his head begins to morph and change.
Oh my god.
Out of his cheekbones, blood, bloody glasses pop out of his head and his hair, his wonderful
lacrosse player flow just like recedes and becomes like this square cut on his head and
is
call him a Dwight again for psychic damage. Shut up, no! I'll let that do psychic damage
the first couple times. What do I roll? Just roll 1d4 and see how much you do. I like that.
4. Okay yeah. Shut up! Shut up! No! Bears, beats, Battlestar Collect, no! He's like trying
to
for
and
the
you can't really get around all this feed you can't really figure out how to tie
it together it's like too big it becomes like a conceptual exercise to imagine
tying something that big you're not really able to do it that's what your
action for the turn you get some move since he's that big I'm gonna just like
jump on his leg okay I'll be wrapping your movement I'm gonna grab his leg you
You can like jump onto his like foot I would say.
Okay then I do that.
Okay yeah so he's like that big.
So you jump onto his foot.
And now it is the uh, it is now your turn, Blotas.
Alright, um, I'm gonna use the same spell that I used on him before.
I should say, by the way, N-word passes.
It's like, just really tiny compared to him.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm going to use mental prison on him.
Nice.
Okay, describe, put mental prison in the chat and describe it.
Describe what your prison is.
Let's see what mental prison is.
I can't figure out, there we go.
Yeah.
Do I read, should I read what it says?
No, I can read that.
My mental prison is because he's still freaking out that he's Dwight. This is the only prison I need, right? He's just in a room and there's a mirror.
Damn.
Yeah, it's deep.
Yeah.
Okay, and it is a Charisma, a Spell Save DC of 14 against his, I think it's his Charisma, right? Let's see.
Intelligence.
Is intelligence? Yeah. All right, cool
He's pretty smart. Let's see how he does
He's a Dwight
Yeah, no, he's able to save
But he's still 5d 10 damage, yeah
It's a roll for that
20 is it 5d 10? Yeah, I'm a successful. He still takes 5d 10. Yeah
And so he sees the mirror break briefly and then it shatters in front of him
And he's still very fucking mentally hurt by that
Do you know how much techno slam that cost it doesn't say on my thing. Oh, whoops. That's it's that's for one
or
Fucking bastard
Yeah, okay, yeah you guys are doing some pretty hefty damage to this also I'm gonna move away from him
and
Ray William Johnson.
All right. I start thinking of ways to prank him.
And I'm like, do you have like a like a like a toothbrush
and like some hot sauce or something?
What are you talking about?
Where do you look?
Could you like fall asleep for a little bit?
No, I'm I'm a perfect animal.
I never sleep.
Oh, wow. You really are a Dwight.
No, no. Yeah.
If you're if you're not Dwight, then fall asleep.
Oh, oh, shit.
payroll persuasion
easy did
fourteen that's not enough
it's almost it's pretty good
but it's not enough
he like starts to like close his eyes slowly
no no no no you're trying to trick me
and only twights get tricked
i'm not a twight i'm a jim
you sound like john goodman
i'm john goodman
wait i thought you were jim
this is the life of a mind
wait so i can still attack right
a
one come out of your hand and just fall on the floor.
[MORE SAD MUSIC]
Um, just doesn't work for me.
I vomit to cover up how bad that was.
[LAUGHTER]
[VOMITING]
Oh look, somebody needs to clean that up, that's nasty.
I'm not touching that.
Yucky!
[LAUGHTER]
Okay, yeah.
Please somebody draw a Sullivan.
[LAUGHTER]
is
more like a PS2 cold Kush kind of animation of him is really what I want
to say.
Okay, it is now.
Okay.
Yeah, it is now the Crayola's turn.
I forgot about this fucking guy.
Yeah.
So the Crayola ninjas transformed into a Crayola Zord and they're just
going to go right for Snoochie Boochies.
They throw they'd like their they lift up their hands, which are these
like drills with these different crayons on you could see the heads
of the Crayola Ninjas now.
Now you can see them without their Crayola map, their Crayola Ninja gear.
So they just were like, and you see it spinning around and it creates like a colorful wax
ball and he tosses it right over here.
So all you need to roll a deck save.
That's colorful balls or crashes down.
Eighteen, thirteen, four.
Dude, I fucking suck today.
What the fuck?
Okay.
All right.
Oh boy.
Okay, let's roll for damage.
That's a good aye aye aye?
Yeah, it is.
Sullivan aye aye aye?
Yeah.
Sorry, I have to also roll for Snoochie Boochies.
So uh, Blowtoss and Snoochie Boochies, you both take 14 damage.
I do?
Patrick Yoda and Ray William Johnson, you each take 28 points of damage.
I have 1 health.
Oh my god.
And you are covered in Crayola marks.
Fuck dude.
11 health.
hell
and
John does it's a jump rocks ha it's a jump no no frog okay call leapfrog
He got for actually Pat he actually got my ass I was trying to protect you yeah, and I respect that
But no he's right. It's a jump attack
Gun City cannon frogs are the only things that can leap
And let's see
How he does for damage to start keeping track of the cannon and making sure it all makes sense yeah
and
and he does...14 damage. Yeah, he does like...
Just a pretty good fucking hit on this guy.
It's still standing, obviously, though.
It is now your turn...
Oh no...
Wait, no it's not.
It's my turn, right?
No, we're...oh wait, no, what'd you get?
I got a 19.
Oh yeah, no, sorry, we're back to the top of the order.
Yeah.
And it's now Dwight's turn.
What?
the
he uh...
he starts a vibrant shake
michael
and like this reverberating like
ray of michael scott's just as like fucking shooting out of his body dislike
insane panorama that doesn't make any sense
All of you rolled dexterity saving throws. This is coming towards you.
There's no way I...
Oh, I got a crit one.
[laughter]
16.
17, yes!
Okay.
Dude, I'm dead.
-No. -Probably.
You're fine.
He said probably.
Uh...
He's okay.
Okay.
Yeah, Patrick Yoda, you take 20 damage.
I'm dead.
You're dead.
Uh, you two take 10 damage.
I'm dead.
Okay, I have 21 health.
You got this bro, clutch it out!
Oh fuck.
Easy.
Why didn't you give more than one of us healing?
Right, what the fuck?
Yeah, it is your fault, you gave us all that teleporting and the worms.
Why didn't you give us unlimited health?
You asshole.
Inside that puzzle was a bunch of health potions.
Uh, yeah, it is now, uh, well, let's actually start with you, Patrick, you had a death saving
throw.
What do I roll?
Just hit death save?
Just d20, yeah, hit death save.
18.
Nice.
Let's go.
It's a victory.
Okay, it is now your turn, Blotas, right?
Or, yeah, yeah.
Uh, alright, well, I'm just gonna use mental prison again.
Because it does a lot of damage.
So he's going to try to resist it.
He doesn't manage to resist it.
You made Pennsylvania Jim OP.
He doesn't resist it.
Yes, dude.
Describe it. What do you do?
This prison, he's in Jell-O.
And he can just see a giant eye looking in at him.
He's like, "Blech!"
He's like screaming as he looks in this.
So he is like completely trapped. His brain is trapped in it.
He also takes 5d10. Yeah, he takes 5d10 and he is perceiving himself to be inside
of this jello and he can't really, there's nothing he
can like sort of perceive beyond it.
If he tries to move beyond it or make an attack through it,
you know, or reaches any of his body through this illusion
perfectly encapsulated by the jello
He takes 10 d10 damage
Yeah, baby, which is pretty crazy
Can I yeah, what's now that I cast that spell? Can I also try and stabilize?
Somebody or is that like no, that's your that's sort of it. All right. Okay, so he's now I mean that was a fucking killer move. Um,
Not killer killer, but he's he's looking he's pretty fucking killer
All right, you drew... all right, I'm just not even gonna say what that is.
So, uh, it is now, um, your turn, uh, Ray William Johnson.
- All right. - Uh, roll Death Saving Throw.
Death Save, let's go.
This is easy for you, dude, come on.
- 16. - Nice.
- Nice. - Yeah, you're saved.
Okay, cool.
It is now the Crayola's turn. It's going to try to use its Crayola drills
to drill into Snoochie Boochies.
Okay, it hits and it does a not insignificant amount of damage
Okay, so chibuji's is looking okay
Uh, but he's gonna try to attack sushi buchi's again
with the drill
He no, he's not and that hits as well
And that's another bit of damage there. So you're looking fine. He's looking pretty bruised though as he's fighting
Uh, the his civilization's mortal enemy the crayolas
uh...
and
we are uh...
back to the top of the order
on a way to do this goes for it
so you're going to try to fight back basically
so students at once
nice okay you got the dot
uh... two hits in there
nice to that's going to be a little
who
not bad
nice yeah he's like fucking like search like
who can't do like finding the weak points on this robot
uh... you could hear like a crayola crayons like rattling around inside of
it
well i like the way when they shake me shake a box a crayola crayons like
bing bing bing
he's just like fucking
beating the shit out of it
uh... you did a pretty good job but uh... it's still looking strong
uh... we're back to the top of the order
it is now
uh... jim's turn again pennsylvania jim
and he is going to strike at you
blow toss
uh...
he's gonna say uh... bears and he's gonna try to like a lot you
and he misses so he expresses bear swipe at you is giant like and
and you're just able to get together way
he's got a beats
well does it look at him
doesn't this make him take a lot of damage
all shit to it sorry remove let me move back from this actually he's in his
mental prison
on his turn he's freaking out inside of the jello
and he is trying to climb his way out
role for damage
i say because that's actually what would happen
he would be screaming and crying and trying to climb his way out i know he
will be screaming crying
right let's see here
tenty ten
noon sixty two
holy shit
well i think it would look like that's bill is so strong
uh...
and
probably shouldn't give you that's the idea i don't feel that i think that's
i think she killed patrick and caleb twice in a row right now
uh... describe your kill
i did
usually correct his brain open and what he tries to climb out of the the jello
yeah and he just
he doesn't look up when he's climbing and he climbs right
into a state where and it just staples into his head and kills him
speech
you watch as his head like like just indents and punctures as if a stapler was in there
like the sheer his sheer belief in that happening and psychic pain made him feel like his head just
like got stapled and he's just bloody on the floor and you watch his body like shrink back down the
normal size and you see a dead pennsylvania gym with an n-word pass in his hand run over a night
to
me die. 8. Ok it's a negative. Fuck it. Perfect 20. That counts as 2 wins. So you're stabilized.
Fuck me. Just let me die. Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah. Nevermind I have to live. I need to
see him grow up. I'm sitting here just like. Unconscious and still doing that. Making that
a
Watch your language.
Okay, yeah.
That hits him, and he does it again.
And...
That does not hit him.
So he shoots a rainbow beam at him and it, like, sprays him a bit.
And then, uh, he shoots it again and it misses this time.
Suchi Buchi fights back.
And this is sort of just like epic battle, epic toy battle going on over here.
the
I have just what he needs.
Okay, yeah, well it's your turn.
I'm gonna use Mental Prison on it.
Do you have enough Techno Slime points for that?
Yeah, I have enough for one more.
Oh my god.
Alright, go for it.
Okay, the Mental Prison
for this one is a Crayon Box.
Alright, he's gonna resist it.
It's a Crayon Box? Okay, let's see if he can resist it.
Yeah, he's gonna use it in a box.
Alright, we're all learning here, folks.
I'm learning.
uh... if i didn't have this we would lose this fight
there's no question all yet did
he might have
is perhaps a little you mean you might have that they would have done enough
damage to be like in the first to kill me then
in this chance that i mean
means that could have done me at pat pockets sucked it we lifted
we have like the worst characters in the world how you try to tie issues that
at
the
to
How do you want to kill like I mean this is not gonna end well, yes, he's trapped in the box
He tries to get out of the box
What happens dead gets out of the box?
He climbs out of the box and he looks around he's like wait a second. Where am I? He's in a microwave
Melts. Oh, yeah, he his will and his mental belief in this makes this giant crayon robot melt
And yeah, I'm just standing there just like with my eyes bloodshot just drooling
Yeah, yeah you guys he wakes you guys up you wake those guys up do I have to roll another death save
Yeah, you should actually
Okay, blow toss it's your turn I'm gonna stabilize him I'll do a medicine run a medicine check
12 okay, you stabilized him. Oh nice. They could have been bad
Yeah, I don't get up I get up and I just go
Like I shoot black bile all over Dwight's dead body
Yeah, and it's acidic can it burns through his head yeah, and he's just dead and the Crayola's dead
We did it we all three and I teleport away out of the temple
The
Whatever the ending cutscene is yes, noochie, butchie starts to say something about the Edward Pass and at time and and what it means
To you know take pride in your people and what is?
But not in like a creepy way not in a nationalism way and like a sort of a what is pride?
What is oh wait? Are we giving him the?
Pat wait, yeah, no, no, no Cameron. We you should stay because there's like the fourth thing and I'm not okay
And he says
We did it. Well, I'm blow-tossed it. What were you did it really? What was?
What was that? We keep losing my I keep losing my voice. I'm trying to do
What's his name from Highlander?
lamb air the lm bear
mixing it up with solomon's voice
he's not the good
uh...
we did it
give me the past
i will make a forgery for you
one you can bring back to your leo
uh... okay
yeah okay you can the past
uh... he crafts a forgery
using a his time got you billy's and does look pretty similar
to an hour pass
and uh... uh...
he has it
he seems in the middle of the temple he says
hold on a must meditate
and he meditates for a bit
and you see him shake and shiver
he see the past glow
and you see uh... you hear that silence again
you see light shine
you see too
little baby tomahawk cheese appear next to him
And you see his eyes well up with tears.
He's like, I need to feed them right away.
Guys, it's another boss fight.
Come on.
Say, I cannot thank you enough.
It will take me another few months, probably if I ever forever me to create more.
I am.
You see that he looks, you can't really look thousands of years old, but
he kind of looks it in this moment.
He looks just like drained of his health and life
after doing something like that.
Life begets life, you know.
If I am.
I lose my immortality from this, it will be worth it.
Thank you.
You've saved my people.
We will sing songs of you.
We will do kiki dances in your name.
YOOOOOO
*GASP*
Oh my god, all my fucking bones hurt, but that made me feel better
Um
Yeah, I mean I'm just gonna stay here you you guys can go there's
There's lots of you know, you can go down. Okay. Bye artifact. Okay. All right. Yeah, I got a little one
Myself and I pick up I look at and I look at
Rarely does I say we have a little one to take care and then I hold his hand
I also say and I have a little one to take care of and I pull my hoagie out
Okay, all right, no I get it I feel good about this
we did it we just gotta go back to Leo now and I
Guess show him this lie
You better not fucking squeal I won't squeal I'm not trying to squeal man
I know I know this began with me working for Leo it explica be but
do
But now I'm your guys friends forever
Well, you guys hear something. Yeah
Just hope the next campaign, you know, it just gets a little bit better cuz I feel like I'm pretty cool
the
to
like the odyssey giving him nothing right yep like nobody's you know but we're
still gonna become a slave to them we just change the name did nothing oh yeah
well yeah it's going to have sex with nothing okay well all right hand over
the inward past and your freedom is guaranteed okay and I put up the end
and
I I am
I roll deception check
Six
No, I definitely told you I wanted the inward pass no, I think you wanted an engage
This is he said that you guys this is quite amazing though. I remember that
Both of you roll deception with disadvantage Oh
Two crits
There's gonna be different next time
Everything's gonna be everything. Oh, you're just gonna make his rolls shittier. I don't know what I can do
Okay
He's like
Yeah
Maybe maybe I maybe I did. Maybe I did say that it was a bit
Maybe yeah, you just had a headache. This is fine though. I mean, maybe maybe that's maybe maybe as you misinterpreted
Well, I said this is an end gauges. It eluded my grasp for so long
I'm so happy
Thank you. Thank you boys. You see him put the end gauge in a mantle next to a Nokia phone and
Nigel Thornberry and
the other end thing I could think of and
He says to you all um, we all freedom is all but guaranteed
You know, so you could do what you want now as free men. What do you want to do?
to
I
help raise Sullivan but I will have my money also.
Wait, wait, well I didn't realize...
Okay, I'll take the money too then.
No, you already, we already shook on it.
I don't remember shaking on it.
We did, we shook on it.
I know we didn't.
Are you serious?
Yeah, we shook on it.
I totally remember shaking on it.
18.
Yeah.
18 deception.
That hits.
it's
k
business secrets going you didn't know
is no uh...
and i'll i'll okay so you
each would have gotten
five hundred thousand tokens apiece
old baby
i have a million oaken war
so you have a million
on the millionaire
and it will do the epilogue for the other characters uh... all the epilogue for
that
but for you guys
we're gonna have to figure out what happens next campaign
when it's the uh... richie rich
gun city rich rich and ray william johnson is a single
johnson
what do you mean a single mom on the one who made so i want a divorce
uh...
okay then i get it
keep the kid because it's mine and not even yours at all.
Even like a little bit.
I have nothing.
We can go to court if you want.
I have absolutely nothing.
And yeah.
I unplug myself.
I don't have a dramatic ending for this one like I did for the other one.
I don't really have one.
I think this one was too crazy.
So I go outside.
I go with him.
We all go outside, I look for the first white guy I see walking on the street, and I hand
him the counterfeit n-word pass, just wink, and then vanish.
Thank you.
It's Robot Kramer.
And scene.
No, what's up?
I knockout game him.
Yeah, you bitch, you thought.
Not on me.
the
not on this island
for the
the camera
heads out here
for the
it's really a cheap
the
That's right, that's the whole adventure of Gun City and the Temple of The Penguin of Doom.
Pretty unsatisfying ending, wouldn't you say?
Well, here's an epilogue that will be a little bit better.
With their newfound wealth, Ray William Johnson and Blotos Pishav married and decided to raise
New Sullivan as their son.
Ray William Johnson is a deadbeat dad who keeps trying to buy New Sullivan's love with copies
of Gran Turismo 4, and Blotos has become a relentless career woman and supermom who just
wants to have it all.
They rent a studio apartment, a luxury in Gun City near Tiananmen Cube, where they spend
their off time bullying teens in Dematrix 2 and laughing at New Sullivan's antics.
When the call for adventure comes again, will they rise to the occasion?
Meanwhile, their old pal Patrick Yoda uses some of his tokens to build a huge hoverboard
park under the Terry Shivell Memorial Cyber Highway.
He tricks the city into thinking it's for the community, but he's the only one allowed
to enter.
The rest of his money is used to purchase a sandwich.
They occasionally get together and talk about their time as adventurers and detectives, hoping
they never have to do that kind of thing ever again.
And who was that other guy that was around?
Probably nothing.
Speaking of which, Sullivan the Frog, aka Crud, aka Nothing, left the adventuring assistant's
life for stardom in Gadsville, where King Gad employed him as a court idol.
After experiencing a perfect blue type of scenario, Sullivan decided that Idle Life wasn't for
him and he worked instead as a producer behind the scenes, producing hit songs such as "Kiki
Do You Love Me Riding" and "Santoria" as performed by Haseki Tsune on her latest record,
Back From The Clink II - The Kawaii Desu Experience.
Baby Gadd meanwhile left Gaddsville to go to Bullet Town, where he hopes his desire to
be a great fight promoter will be more appreciated.
King Gadd was devastated at his loss.
you know, of his son going somewhere.
"Leroy Peanutbutter and his 300 wives rule the rails and the soy wastes.
No business ventures have been able to grow out there and it once again becomes
an abandoned wasteland
where freezing,
poisonous soy pollutes the air.
Suck-ass shit and the other whovians do their best to survive without this
once profitable train rail."
It's now, you know,
now it's Leroy's.
by establishing a trading relationship with Leroyder, where they give him a new wife and
he gives them Lunchables.
So far there has been no issue.
With the endgage acquired and no one questioning his motives throughout the whole campaign,
Leo the Collector was free to invade Sky Island, where he has since enslaved leprechauns who
live there.
Leo's goal of conquering all of the Sky Islands above Gun City is nearer to completion, and
with Poppy Chuko and the Mad Suckler under the way, it'll be easier than he even imagined.
Or so he thinks.
With Gary C. Enterprises' hopes of opening a hot soda and cold dogs restaurant in the
soy waste, or a cold dogs and hot soda, I don't remember the order, the lad returns
to Dematrix 2 to expand his business.
His partner, he partners with John Carlo the Bullfrog, who's only grown in power since
the last adventure and the business expands throughout Gun City but without our hero's
involvement. Stoogey Boogey now lives in solitude in his temple of doom where he hopes to regrow
his civilization. The VR penguins have become his new countrymen while he slowly rebuilds
the once great Tamagotchi people. The ramifications of such a thing, who can say?
The god of Popo died.
Lurking in the shadows of Gun City, however, are new foes and old foes,
and old friends who've become foes, and also the other way around where the foes become the friends.
What lies in wait for our heroes in leisure?
What of Tullateralis and the Order of the Penis,
and the mad Suckler still licking his wounds?
Only time will tell.
But I will say this.
"Cameron will not be able to teleport at will."
It has been driving me insane how I wrote that rule.
So I thought it would be like as a bonus action in combat, right?
Then you get to teleport.
But I then remember moving it because I was like, "Okay, well I don't want to move that's only usable in like a combat state."
"I don't really like keeping track of that state in D&D."
"It's a TTRPG, right? So things can be more fluid."
"You know, role initiative is not strictly for combat."
So I just was like, "I don't want that to be tied to that."
I'm
I'm really tired and I'm so horny.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC]