[Music]
Last time!
What the fuck?
What's up?
[Laughter]
I'm sorry.
No, no.
That's staying in there.
Yeah, I'm leaving it.
[Laughter]
Last time on, uh, Gun City.
[Music]
The Temple of the Penguin of Doom.
Alright, now I have to find my fucking notes again.
I got so surprised.
There they are. Okay, cool.
The boys watched half of Employee of the Month before being whisked away from the hotel,
that's what she said, to the massive Gateway Gad Cow,
where beautiful Simon led them through a corridor of confused Ken Bones
and a Gattaca of sorts, where they took another elevator up into a lobby.
And then they saw Pennsylvania Jim
And Pennsylvania Jim was like very rude to them. It's just bullet points today
And they
Just Pennsylvania Jim was very rude to them and they went inside of the right they went inside to meet with the king of the
Gads Papa Gad who said to them that because they are
Gun city types and they lie tried to lie like seven times. They were not allowed to go into the
into the land caves
So then the baby dad told them
Well, I have another way that you could maybe do that if you go into this fighting ring
and the octagon which has but I think it had five sides instead of
What was it was six sides with six sides had six sides and so thank you. Yes. Yes, I didn't finish listening re listening
and then... Oh, am I looking at it now? Yeah, okay, I can see it now. It's right there.
Yeah, it has six sets.
They fought three enemies. They saw Snoochie Boochies, who was the mysterious masked fellow from the...
or mysterious hooded fellow from the auction.
Then they fought three guys. They saw Rex and Marie, who were there cheering them on.
They accidentally involved Sullivan in the fights, which almost led to his death again.
Ray William Johnson cleverly used his worm, no not that one, to trick another worm
into falling in love with it, and they killed that worm. Hmm, that's about it for the notes.
And I think that's literally what happened though. There was a hand too. Yes, there was a master hand
type of thing that shot bugs out of its palm which I liked. And it like pooped or something. I remember
it pooping. Did you make it poop? I don't remember. I didn't get to that part in editing yet. I just
remembered something about it pooping. Yeah. We could make it poop. You could add like a fart sound
in the edit. It could also not poop. There is one fart sound already. I posted this on Twitter but
I found a sound effect on Freesound called "relaxing fart" and it's just in the description was just a
a
is
dad
is you want to make sure he was stay true to his word
uh... but you didn't get a chance to your freedom found out
uh... but you guys basically as far as you know you wanted this tournament
you uh... are going to be a look at the passes tomorrow if you show back up to
the dads
uh... gateway cow
uh...
and tonight marie and uh... rex invited you guys out to get celebratory drinks
earlier on
so uh...
uh... we can come right to
uh... the bar in that case let's do that skill
or we can go
uh... no you're not
'cause it's only been
you can get like a short rest so we could do that where you can get a little
you know i don't know what not to do is going to drink will wait until we're
still working to get happen
yet nobody i'm not fights at a bar now
come on let's go to a bar and it's a good enough right now i'm i'm i'm going
to drinks maximum let's go to take a nap and you guys can go on ahead and then
and
level 5 in this one. So what that means is you have 5 hit dice you can spend per long
rest and you can spend those during short rest. What that means is that, see in the hit dice
area, Patrick in your character sheet, you gotta look at your character sheet.
We haven't done this in so long I forgot about the character sheets.
That's fine, just a critical part of the thing.
It's not.
It's fine. Definitely not for your experience.
Stop freaking out at me.
[Laughter]
I'm sorry, you've had a lot of that this week. I should ease up.
So, what that means is you can basically spend up to five of those hit dice.
And then you, whatever rolls you get from that, so it's like, you have D8, so you could spend like,
up to five during the short rest, and add that to your, to recovering your HP.
Um, so, you know, there's kind of like a, if you know you're not gonna have a long rest for a long time, there's kind of a strategy around that, right?
Where it's like, "Oh, I don't know if I want to spend too much, 'cause maybe I'll need it again."
Um, but, um, yeah, so you, I think you have D8, I'm pretty sure, uh, Blowtoss has D10.
So I just roll a D8 while we're walking?
Yeah, and then you'll subtract one on your hit dice part of your sheet, yeah.
You can roll up to, up to five if you want, so.
so but then we can't use the ones after for a long rest yeah well you just can't use them until you
get a long rest once you do a long rest it all replenishes yeah i'm gonna i'm gonna spend i'm
gonna spend three of them i don't even care me too i'm gonna do two i'm just gonna chill all right i
got a six i got six and seven okay cool so that's you can add 13 back so you're back at 30 that's
pretty good you might not want to spend another one just because you're max 34 you're gonna you're
You're gonna do blackjack?
No.
You already got locked in with Hit 'Em.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, 18 back.
Yes, you're at 27 now.
Nice.
Yeah, cool.
That's just what I needed.
So yeah, the walk is particularly relaxing for you too.
Bray William Johnson though, you're just walking going,
"Ugh."
Just trailing behind.
Yeah.
Yeah, what, yeah, would you, do you, do you, that,
You guys are trailing behind breathing weirdly.
Ray William Johnson, do you chat with Rex and Marie?
Do you chat with them on the walk?
No, I have a I have a paddle ball and I'm trying to beat my record
and I'm really focused on it.
Just keep me from sleeping.
What's your record?
Ray, I.
16.
Ray, it's a good good show in there.
It's really good.
Can you shut the fuck up?
I'm trying to hit 17.
Just like just like when we were dating.
Are you still vlogging?
Nope.
I'm just going to talk to Rex.
uh...
here
you guys can
on either side of the inky morning so it's like by normal beacons
all
there we go that were a great uh... you know i i i i tried my best out there
but i think you may
okay sure what's going on
yet and i'm back
will get your back to the government's not on his back
come on get my back okay i'll i'll you're walking he's like trying to like reach your back you're
like walking he's like he's like he's like about your height so it's kind of okay because you're
yoda but it's still like trying to massage someone's back he's touching my lower back
while I'm walking. Sorry! Sorry! Oh god we're getting looks now. People will talk.
Go higher! Get higher on the back. Okay I'm trying to get higher. So you had to bet the bar.
Ow! It's too fucking hard! The bar is called, I think I gave him a good name with it, yeah
Yeah, the gadfly. It's a very, yeah, it's a very popular bar in Gadsville.
You know, it's got a, you go in there, it's like a very classic looking bar, like a real New York style, like you're in a New York style bar.
And there's a guy trying to do his tight five in the back to an unenthused crowd of Ken Bones, like three or four.
and
but it's also 'cause it was
jet you know this is like a bar you go to after a big thing and there's just a
fight tournament you see people giving you like appreciative nods like hey good
job in there
things like that so it's nothing
nothing too rowdy
i wanna get on the lineup for the stand up
okay cool yeah you get on line there's like there's three ken bones in front of
you
you look you look over their shoulders
they're all going over their index cards and they're moving in the exact same way
a
Okay, all right. Well, I'll check that off the list. No darts for Patrick Yoda.
No darts. I think I'm going to see what the indoor hopscotch is all about.
Yeah, for sure. So there's like a little nook. So it's like the darts. Picture a bar where it's
like you got the bar, you walk in, bar on the right side. In the back you have like a little
tiny stage where people can do like their poetry or stand up or whatever and then you have like a dart
board then you have like a pool table this is as you're going further left and then like in the
back in a corner where you'd maybe have like an arcade game or the bathroom you also have like an
indoor hot scotch hot scotch hopscotch scotch hot scotch just what they call it hot scotch it's like
a
I walk up to the bartender and I hey man
Hey, how's it going? Give me the money?
What can I
Give me the money in the in the drawer
You want the money in the cash register? Oh, yeah
Yeah
Roll the timidation check
This is better be so cash did
22 yeah, he at first is like this guy is kind of weird and I don't think he's serious
He thinks money's in drawers. I'm walking serious as shit. Put it on my card. I hand a card
Put all the money on this
You see him. He's like, oh, okay
Man, it's all right. I have to I have to clean myself
I'll get somebody else to help and so he starts to walk away doing a little
Squatty walk and somebody goes and takes your card and they say what can I get for you pal? I
Dope what the money I fucking told that other guy. Oh, you just wanted the money on the card
Did you pay here pay for something here? No, I yeah. Yeah, I paid for all the well
How much money's in the drawer right now the cash register? Let me check
we got about
About one $100. Yeah, so I'm gonna need that on this card pretty soon here. Okay
And you see the other guy who's like shaking his head like like scared. He's like, okay. All right. All right, calm down
So what?
And you want this to buy drinks or no, I just I are you brain dead, bro?
Okay, you are robbing me fucking robbing your ass you honky. Give me that money. Okay. All right. All right
All right. All right gives you $100 from the cash register. He says just please just
You good you good now. I don't want any trouble. Okay, so it's still cool if I like hang out in the bar though, right?
No, fuck no, get the fuck out of here!
Well, okay, you'd have the money back.
[laughter]
Okay, weird prank. Weird prank.
You sure? Or do you wanna...
No, you can just take it, man.
No, 'cause now I feel weird about it.
My friend's about to go up and stand up.
I snapped at you and now I feel bad.
No, you were rude. You kinda ruined my whole...
my whole robbery, but it's alright.
Yeah, roll... roll persuasion on him.
14.
like
he gives you like five dollars i'm sorry
i'm sorry that's on the house
and he gives you a jacket coke
cool i put on indoor sunglasses and i head over to the front
we call that the art of the deal
yeah that's called a win
as soon as that ends
as soon as that ends i leave the hot hopscotch room
just immediately
i immediately throw up on the ground
oh fuck
Oh my god.
Everyone's like, everyone's like, "Whoa, it's a guy who killed the worm."
I can't believe how fucking hot it is in there.
Oh god.
You see a guy in the hot hopscotch room who's just like,
like you see flies buzzing around his head and he's just staring.
And he's just like, is in there all the time.
It smells horrible.
the
you know you see somebody you see somebody but you know the by the door
like became a deal to heat stay out
i thought people
and uh... you know we got to the the stand-up set so
the can bonus finishing his last joke
and uh... that's why i have no pregnant women i'm i'm telling you they look like
submarines
okay all right everybody had sold for the new man
it
really like your said dude
you know they're thanks
you know what
here's five bugs
of get out of town thanks pal no problem as it is that it is that put my hand on
the stage they just throw up next to the state
it's a
you see a you see somebody who's like you see like one of the barbie heads is
like a play coming over the like a record week we
help you out ur you know i have just taxes is projectile
and he's like
and uh...
you're not clear that's what they're wrong
well i got all that was just being covered in about a inch deep of vomit
for the last year we don't we nobody goes in there was a few quiet is that's
still open
people love it
why he
fifty-five
what's wrong with everybody here
you see solvent city in the audience going
yet go to our stars
so yeah is this uh... i get i get on stage
and i'm i'm like to happen the mic yeah everyone's everyone's cheering for me
because they love me
uh... unlike
that's my for a a guys uh...
my name's split us this year probably be here a lot of that
spree soon
uh... let's see let's see what we have going on tonight and i think of my
little notebook and i i start looking at it i flipped through it for like a full
minute
and then i just thought i was older
look at this
gay as little frog in the front row
i think
anybody where you first of all
what
i'm trying to cheer about and i i hope you like i hope the mike and up to sell
him
where you from people's stupid for public
well i i i come back
I'm from Gun City, Blowtast. We hang out sometimes.
Oh yeah, of course. Of course you're from Gun City.
Look at this guy. You'd think he's from a damn lily pad,
the way he looks. Looking like a frog here tonight.
Am I right, folks?
Roll a persuasion check with advantage.
Because it's always with advantage if you're doing crowd work.
Yeah, frog.
Everyone's like, "Ha ha ha ha."
They're like pretty into it, but
a
can go that you gave five dollars to hear a billion johnson is like yet this guy
rocks to
and uh... yet meanwhile marianne rex are just like at the bar just like what it
rex is like what it what are they doing
reason like my boys
uh... and what
but what do you do it and you know these two your friends right here sitting next
to you this demon in this in this year
yeah i was right now you know that the
characters
yes we got it
the
uh... that
the you know that this you know right here looks like a frog and so it is
and
the world is
what do you guys live in a pop-up
the
we do we do it with a little persuasion with advantage again because i think it
You got, you have three people now.
- 13.
- Yeah, yeah, people are into it now.
They're like, "Man, he's roasting those three.
He's got those three.
He's got their number."
- I'm from the damn bond.
- You got me, you got me, you got me so good, yeah!
- Yeah, and what, everyone who's laughing at them right now,
you think you're safe?
No way.
Hey, you, Ken Bone, right there.
How long is your tongue?
I bet it's really long, like a rock's tongue.
- Four guys turn around.
the
uh... for kyle yet for guys sitting next to each other what he said not to log
guys have been
of a recent night this is not going to hopped off the law is true it's true i
said a lot last week is true
on my god you can make this stuff up
the overall
all at once every can both says and no you can't
try to start another standing ovation
and then it's not like step down from the stage and i just slip in patrick's
vomited hit my head at the same alcohol
mid-seventies you wake up you hear like echo we've always liked
the product
not that's a good slap slap slap
not that's
but i think
they love you you're like you're like jay letterman
the hybrid of jay leno it's a little and then they made
yeah i'm time i'm unconscious so i don't know
the
so i have a it would be out of character to respond to that
now you're absolutely right so they drag your body to little table that rex and
marie got a gun food at this point for you guys and i could put
for patrick there for patrick you know that is that like tom's like
like a bowl of tom's eating
i'm eating a bowl of pepto-bismol and i think it's good spot here
you're blowing on it it's not
and uh... yeah you see a uh... marie says
that's quite a showing up there boys and now you guys can fight like that
start your archaeologists
now that was a fighting i was a stand-up set
well one at a time please
you should always a fighting that was a good set
work
uh...
organelle cargo
yes
you you are you should order me
some flies because uh...
i'm a frog now i heard all about that for over here
Everyone in the barn's here.
So they hear that.
I'm actually a... yeah I'm a frog.
Hey guys, comedy...
Frog comedy's gonna be really taking off soon, guys.
Sullivan's like, "Oh boy, I guess it's my time to show up."
Shut up!
Alright, I could've walked right into that one, I guess.
You're such a human.
Pretty much what the shit?
No way, I'm a frog?
He only started talking about frogs because I'm a frog.
I don't even remember him talking to you.
uh... organs stupid as you're talking to the guy behind you sullivan
all-out hate you know i don't know i never roast you
uh... probably
i'm being gas lit again
this is
this is what it's like being a woman in the twenty first century is a nightmare
uh... man so uh...
in a recess uh...
use from stand up to fighting you fellas are quite impressive have to say even
rex was impressed with with some your chops
frog joke was funny
and uh...
she says uh...
now we're just stopping actually over here 'cause uh...
uh... apparently there's a uh...
massive uh... so i get it up at the frozen waste of soy we think it's
guarding some batman beyond burger king toys so
we're gonna head out there tomorrow morning but we were gonna stop here and
actually a courtesy of uh...
your friend
uh... nisi as she takes out a uh...
something uh... out of her like uh...
chest pocket thing that
ventures have the
you know the shirts and the apartment
and she says uh...
and it looks like a she says that you would and it's like a blank cd-rom
like with a piece of string around it
uh... tied to it and she's like
this amulet uh...
leo said it's going to supposed to help you guys are you in the cave or in the
land caves and
to be honest i'd
does also something else i want to tell you fellas size giving this to you and
she slides the amulet over
and she says uh...
i wanted you to let you guys know to be
careful about jim
and you see rex nodding a bit more
pennsylvania jim specifically
okay
and yeah because before i i they could have been jim sturgis and i'm not jim
brewer
yeah uh... well-made
he's gonna be nice i do
i thought what would happen is that
jim brewer would be talking
and i would think it was a cdc guy
because he's so good at that impression i mean i'm on a roof
come on he sounds just like him
yeah i'm not familiar with this work but uh... you know i have you heard a look
at you have you heard jim brewer story about norma donald garner griska dandy
while all it's great
that's not like what he said it would lead to a story but i'd like to listen
to but
has a go
i don't know how the story and i don't know if you're going to talk about
something
and he spent ten minutes recalling this jim brewer bit incorrectly yet is
fucking it up. I think that Chris Kattan called Norm McDonald.
Or something like that. Yeah, but yeah, she says,
so when we, after everything went down back at Leo's Place,
we searched around. Rex and I were curious about everything going on, about
what happened, how the ninjas get in there, and we started to search around
the place and we found this. And she puts on the
the table a
uh... what looks to what looks like a uh... ninja star
trapped in jail
and
she's like
uh... he's the only person we know puts things in jail
thinking i've had something to do with the ninjas
and just as likely to which they did not sound
do you remember from
yeti you remember
is a miser and he was there about a day ago in the in the fiction
you remember
i thought it was just a lousy he'd myself
no wasn't snow mysore he'd miser was two ninjas who's a little is not what it
was it was a good mon and the mon from the team on our network and i remember
it the d_n_a_ told us that
it was a red and blue from halo
now it was said that already
bark
who were the one of these guys
we don't know who they were that's the thing there are two of the hungry
hungry at the place here you meant pop culturally who were they
okay no
of the day you've you wanted to know how to get school i want to know their
identities
that's exciting uh...
uh... you see rex starts to talk
i've worked with the group like that
that similar powers
beckon
that my days when i was a corporate agent
he takes a swig from
there were five of them
red blue
yellow
green
well like spongebob
just like spongebob
but i don't think it was much fun
i don't know
that's a little bit is friends to me
they were uh... of pretty interesting unit
as an m_n_n_'s
that's what i thought at first to but
i thought you said you thought that it was spongebob
that was just joking around
in the slash i don't know how i can see our best kids
i'm taking this was seriously
you take all of his questions serious but none of mine that's not
who is the who are you addressing patrick you know
you
and the public to humane the d_n_a_ rex
i think you never listen to me rex
talked about three times probably total
well you know i you're not a very good you're not active listener well you know
it's something that's between me and my dad as far as i'm concerned what's your
god
uh... the frickin spying spaghetti scott sir
okay
disorderly that i have a fair amount of
Sorry
Yeah, don't ask me to repeat that
He said one love to you yeah, and I say to each other as well as well to you
So they were called that's what I thought - they thought they were M&Ms. They were called the creo the Crayola unit
They were five adorable little crayons skittles
All right, so I'm giving you the answer now
as a gift
waiting to be there crayons
their crayons
uh... i mean i don't think so but it would have a lot say i guess
it doesn't this doesn't add up
now so there's a heat myseryn up
goldman
what will play out of the heat mysore touched it it's not just the story is
stupid dude
uh...
they're not they're not a heat mysore or snow snow mysore
that we thought that
they're literally
named on the island with us
note that was not those were two members of this creole a unit
that have since defected
and there are at least three others
so you're telling me that snow mysery and he'd mysery were in a crayola kids
unit
now i'm not telling you anything close to that
you are telling you that
is you know who is telling you something getting mad
and uh...
you see uh... you see now uh... somebody uh...
the summary sort of go like a
okay okay we're getting a little bit confused here the point is
is that there are at least of a group of people that we think are
coming after this we think jim
could be involved or he could be stopping it but the point is that he was
at least aware enough to start trapping
or at least putting ninja stars inside of jello
and we just think what about putting
no that's that's no jello not putting jello pudding
now patella putting
now and now i just don't i don't under can you repeat everything
that we were just talking about i don't remember
and she repeats it verbatim
and and even with the disagreements in the mid miss hearings
the way i said flying spaghetti monster
uh... it's all being repeated back to you
okay so putting
you can't
and sorry can you repeat that one more time
it is now three a m
you you you can repeat that over time you guys go back to the bar you go back to
the hopscotch but it was said
what really doesn't rob city can and then on ron's and then re-run upset
uh... the night goes on you guys get drunk you have a good time
and uh... do you guys at the end night
you wanna go back to the uh...
to your hotel
go back to the hotel that's what she said i go to the arcade
at the hotel
yes definitely there's a good kids kids arcade
units it is like four a_m_ when you get back
so it is cruising
it is blocked no
it is locked is nobody in there
uh... you could try to like picked a lock if you want to have an idea
on my sleep in front of it
i'm a little bit of a lot
was in all get you in
on the i'd call the front desk
you call the front desk and uh...
you hear the voice of uh... the worm
uh... like uh...
allow it's a front desk from that's what she said hotel what do you want
they there are some of the log out of my room
okay sorry one second what's your room number?
um a okay so r sir
c sir so we have the room i left all my video games in here i really need to get
in here so the room numbers start with numbers
okay so it's one a r so c
No, it's so typically--
Okay, wait, I lean over the receiver.
Try, try, try 4RC4D3.
So it's three--
Yeah, that's it, that's it.
Is this a prank?
No, it's three numbers.
It's three numbers per floor.
101 would be one room, okay?
102 is another room, okay?
Listen, okay, listen, this, I'm sending,
I'm sending a pin right now.
I'm sharing location.
Okay, thank you.
Just drop a pin.
Okay, so it's the hotel.
That's good.
Yeah, so can you just unlock every door in here?
[laughter]
Okay, I'm gonna hang up now, alright?
This is getting a little ridiculous.
Can you pick the phone back up?
[laughter]
She hung up.
The arcade is like, you know,
it's not too far from the front desk,
so you could just go back.
Okay, I got it.
No, no, guys, guys, guys, guys, guys.
wait wait no no guys guys i got this
we go one door down to the front desk
guys
i need you to trust me i have this one okay
it's all the first floor
i use my disguise
ability okay
and i disguise myself as a
arcade repair man
a thing that exists
and definitely would show up at this hour
yeah so i go
sneak outside of the hotel
and I walk back in. Okay. I go up to the front desk. Well, hold on. Double, first check. Stealth check
to sneak out of the hotel. For sure. No. Okay. 16. Okay. Yeah. You get out. You, you get out pretty
well. You, you find like a window that's unlocked. You're able to sort of slip out pretty stealthily.
Uh, and then you can walk back in. You look like an arcade repair man. Yeah. Could you describe
what that is to me? I'd love to know what that looks like. It looks, it's like a, it's like a
a mechanic combined with Mario.
Okay, so it's just Mario?
You're dressed up like Mario?
Okay, but I have a toolbox though.
Okay, so you're dressed up like Mario, you're carrying a toolbox.
Not fully like Mario, it's like a Mario hat, but with like, you know, a mechanic's...
Yeah, with like overalls and a red shirt.
It's like Mario, but not color-coded to be Mario, you know what I mean?
Oh, okay.
Right, so just sort of a real working stiff.
Yeah.
real blue collar mechanic type you walk in
uh...
and she's like
uh... the the warm at the front desk is like eight can i help you sir
and uh...
i'd hands the arcade repairmen and i am
here to fix
is indeed the idea games
and i need
is there are a kid he didn't get the industry door
let me go
get my dad and said he doesn't have to
and you see like a uh...
uh... gruffer older worm
uh...
sorry my my uh... my
daughter said that there was a arcade repairman
Hello, I'm the Arcade Repairman and I'm here to fix your machines.
That wasn't the accent she said it was, but she could get that wrong.
Yeah, roll Deception.
I guess I said you should get it with advantage.
Because I'm obviously an Arcade Repairman.
At the very least...
I love Dungeons and Dragons so much.
Ten.
Okay, I'm going to roll his inside against that.
Can you roll a dice with zero numbers on it?
Hmm.
Oh, homie got an 11.
Oh no!
So he's looking at you up and down and he's like,
"I don't remember calling an arcade repairman."
Wait, can I turn the corner dressed up like an arcade repairman?
And I turn the corner dressed as a French maid.
Okay, here's what I'm gonna do because you absolutely do not have any of that fucking shit with you
I have a sharpie and I just sharpie black on myself in the
What I should let you do I should let you because you are like part computer
you should be able to like
3d maybe you could 3d print outfits for you guys very quickly 3d print everything and I want you to roll but I do want
you to roll a
Because I think your spellcasting is is governed by your charisma. So just roll a straight charisma check
So just hit and just see yeah, I got an 18 8 16
Yeah, so yeah, you print out a very nice-looking
French made outfit for yourself and a pretty convincing
arcade man
Arcade repair man outfit for Patrick Yoda. So yeah, I turn the corner and I look at Cameron and I go
Hey, this guy's impersonating me
The arcade repair man, oh no you found me
And I run I don't run out of the hotel I just run upstairs to the
You see the you see the worm who's like, all right, I gotta get that guy now
When he starts going slithering up to find you.
Okay, and I just kind of disappointedly look down at my French maid outfit,
realizing I never got to use it.
So I go behind the counter and I get the arcade key.
Nobody's manning the desk now, yeah.
Okay, I sit in front, behind the desk.
In my French maid outfit.
Okay, I get the arcade key and I go, I play Galaga.
Yeah, you play Galaga.
Meanwhile, Cameron, you are running away from the person who's-
I turn it staying at this hotel. I turn invisible. Perfect. Yeah, you turn invisible. So, um, uh,
what I will have you do is roll a stealth check to see if like you turn invisible without him
noticing you turn invisible like when you turn a corner or if you do it like right in front of him.
Do you know what I mean? 14. Okay. Yeah. So you turn a corner, turn invisible. You hear like,
you know, worm slithering noises and like he looks or he's like, what the hell? Where did that guy go?
And I lock him in the bathroom.
You lock him in the bathroom.
We're in the bathroom.
Describe the process.
No, no, the bathroom is, I'll say the bathroom is.
Where are we right now?
You're on like the second floor of the hotel.
Like just in the hallway?
There's no public bathrooms really in the second floor of a hotel.
So there is probably like a supply closet, but it's probably locked.
And there might be, I'm thinking of rooms that there might be on the second floor of
a hotel.
the
it. Okay, I'm really bad at performance. 15. Holy shit. That was my yep. I was gonna say
he's bad at it. But if he gets 15 or bubble, it happens.
So I make it sound like I'm going, you'll never find me in here.
Okay, I'm gonna have a roll. Now I guess you know what I really gave that performance. I have to
just let that happen. So he goes, he slithers over to the supply closet. He's jangling fiddling with
is
He opens up that supply closet door and he looks in there and he's looking in there you have like
You have a moment in there. Okay
Roll athletics, I would say okay 19. Yeah, you fucking deck him. I
Heard him. I just want to push it. He's fine, but he's like he's thoroughly in there. Okay, and I locked it
Yeah, I mean the door is locked like yeah you you
Yeah, you it's like one of those, you know, it locks all the way so he's just locked in there. Hey somebody let me out
of here
Somebody let me
Go downstairs to the arcade and I go guys we're gaming all night tonight, but I forget I'm still invisible and it scares the shit
The daughter comes out to the front desk like dad, can I help you?
Aren't you that guy who's staying in the second floor?
Um if you're not gonna rent a room, you're gonna need to leave the
building. I have to think about the safety of our guests before anything
else. And so the the the that's all folks kind of a
silhouette closes in on you and it opens back up immediately and she says,
what are you doing here?
I'm gonna go play video games. I don't need this bullshit.
So I storm off and I start playing Frogger and then I
kind of remember earlier ago
i'm so tough for all go well
it's all good
on such a damn fraud
meanwhile solvent like went to bed
but he was not a part of that at all
uh... yeah
so it's the uh... you guys stay there all night
in the arcade yeah i don't i'm not long resting i i do not sleep
i'm in a long rest i'm gonna i'm gonna play for as long as i possibly can
And still long rest so it depends when you want to go there. So a long rest
I usually say is like eight hours, right?
So you can if you want to get your full your full eight hours and you can do that
And then go to the god. I mean, there's no time limit on when you go to the
Cow place except the next day so it can be like the afternoon so you can play from like it's like four
Probably 415 now after all the hijinks so until
until whenever
Yeah, why not?
Yeah, I got so many coins dude you go to bed like to your room or do you sleep curled up in front of the arcade
machine I
little cat
There's the what's that game?
Yes
No, okay
The fast and furious car. Oh, yeah with the seat. I fall asleep. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, I sleep in one of the like Jurassic Park ones that's like a whole Jeep and it has like a curtain
So you can like go inside and curl up in there. Yeah, and yeah, Ray William Johnson uses his
Being a demon and a computer probably just makes you
Just insane when you play video games you just yeah, you're in it cracked dude. Yeah. Yeah
So yeah, like six hours go by
Then eight hours go by it's the next day
Luckily you see like now that there's like there's like just children in the in the in the arcade room
You guys are sleeping in there
And they're just playing whatever games they can that and haven't been you see one of them is like poking you Ray Willing
Johnson's like it's my turn
No, I want to play. This is a game for frogs by frogs get the fuck out of here. Not a frog ribbit
Yeah, and
Is my health back up now?
Yeah, you two have full health, full hit dice again, full techno slime points too.
And I'm really good at Frogger now.
Yeah, you're not really good at Frogger.
That'll come in handy later. I made a smart decision.
So yeah, you guys can go if you want to the GAD cow.
So yeah, we should go to the GAD cow.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you go to the guide cow before as you're leaving you see the the worm woman
daughter sort of sitting at the desk and she says to you guys, you guys came in late last
night right?
It was all this commotion with the NF you heard all the commotion or whatever, but there was
this weird guy who came in here his name he was calling himself an arcade repairman and
I'm still wearing the French Bias.
Oh I've heard of those, that's a legitimate profession.
You're still wearing the French Bias.
I'm still wearing it and I go, "What are you talking about you dumb bitch?"
I literally saw you and also like we're so over that now.
Okay.
It's 22, or 2246, 7? So we're so done with that kind of misogynist kind of talk.
Anyway, so I was just wondering if you'd seen my dad anywhere so he just I just haven't seen him this morning at all
I'm getting a little worried
Oh
I would just say like
Keep your ear to the ground and you might find him. I have my fingers in my ears
All right, well one of you was cryptic but at least a little helpful so thank you
What he was mean the other ones Yoda, I guess
That's the classic the classic good cop bad cop Yoda
And yeah, so the four of you with solvent, you know
Trailing behind head over to the Gateway cow
Takes you a little bit longer to get there because you're not riding in beautiful Simon's sweet Walmart
vehicle
uh... but you get there against what sort of the outskirts of gadsville where
there is some of the
you know more space for things like uh... uh... you know people who land planes
there are women skydiving serb prior you guys and yours
you get to the cow
uh... the hoof
uh... opens up
and uh... before it opens up i should say biometrically scans you three
for also solvent
and uh... let's you and i don't wish to consult a solo three-star dinner you you
You are like the same height as Solveig.
I'm still holding him up.
He then holds you up. He like switches.
You guys have to switch.
Yeah, so you guys all are able to get in there.
You see beautiful Simon's face like pop up on the screen inside the elevator.
And they're like, "Welcome back, fellas!"
And the elevator starts to go up to that floor.
You walk down the long hallway with all the Ken Bone technicians.
and
to the lobby and this time there's no waiting for the king
You see a beautiful Simon in in person as much as a V fo can be in person say
You're all welcome to come in whenever the king is excited to see you
Okay
Alright, well we could just move on. Okay, so you guys go walk into the
You're giving us too many opportunities
stuff on the i guess i'll do that uh... and it's you know the room is sort of
like at least part of like
the cows body so it's like this massive like airplane hangar looking kind of
room
with like just a
dinky little weird thrown in the back
and uh... the king you guys go up to see the king in c_e_o_
solvent bows right away says we have a busy to pop a topic
propagate
and uh... you uh... uh...
the propagandists you uh... all
well
welcome back i didn't think i'd see you before again but
my son
uh... managed to convince me he said that you four should go check out the case
how you should be allowed to he said that he really likes you guys and you see a
that you see the baby dad
who you remember it like sounding like a
tough chain smoking
type of guy he's like looks like a goo goo right now missus like nodding in
like making a big wet eyes
uh...
uh... big web baby eyes and uh...
if not
he's like uh... the
propagandist
so i will allow you
access to the land case it will give you the passes that you so
you know desire
it only be for one our any sings it to these josh gadd
he says i just can't have to be done city people going in and out of their
okay
i mean we're literally not from gun city i feel it did not have any other day
that my you know i don't know anything
pushing your luck how about two hours
now and a half
three percent
mister dad one-year
propagate we stand only
where we stand only before you ten minutes
okay you're back into an hour fifteen minutes with that humbly we stand only
before you one
grinch hunter
or whatever
and three frogs
he's two hours
okay back down to one hours as you seem to be suffering from some kind of
houses we can do it in five minutes
i'm gonna hop on you
mhm
so they get these four out of my sight before i change my mind um... uh... six
hours
and uh... one million our
uh...
a_c_ beautiful side with uh... is sort of politely like shuttershut for you
shuffle you all away
uh...
and uh...
you guys are sort of shuffle out of the uh... the hall
uh... right here oh yeah and uh... he says says
before you leave
one more thing
i heard that's the four of you participated in some sort of fighting
ring
last night
you we have this the rumor going around
and i say now you're weird
you weird as hell
new weird world deception
cfd's weird
all of us
yet just all of you will see
for how to can we add it up
absolutely not
but they like four liars at a time it all twenty one did
yeah okay uh... that's pretty good but the other two are pretty bad concerning
the five
so there is a sort of uses like he says like
i don't know if it's true but let's just put it this way to get his voice back
if i hear anything else about that
you're gonna be in for a serious world of trouble
we'll tolerate that kind of time for a catsville
okay you still we had still
and then you know you're gonna fly on your head
them among great
where he's like feeling around to get that fly off you
I shoot my frog tongue at his head and I grab the fly.
You don't have a frog tongue.
I'm straight up a frog right now.
And then I hop away.
Roll to see if you're a frog.
What do I have to roll?
Just roll whatever you want, man.
Alright, okay. I'm gonna roll a D100 and if I get more than 5...
Yeah.
Dude, 54.
and
There's still more game left.
There's still time.
So you guys are sort of ushered out of the room.
He sort of gives you a little warning about the fighting ring.
And yeah, so you can go to the land caves now.
So they are sort of at the edge of town, where the wall is,
or the wall between the town itself of Gadsville and the soy wastes.
So there's a vast sort of plateau.
There's a Yeti there.
There's a Yeti in the soy waste deep in the soy waste.
That's where Rex and Marie went.
Can I call out to the Yeti?
It's so far away.
Can I like
like get a
can I make it loud?
Can you make it loud?
Can I make the Yeti call loud?
You know what you could do?
You do have Marie and Rex's number.
so you wanna hit them up in their p_s_p_s and ask them if you can talk to the
yeti
here you call them
uh... respects up
yet what's going on
and can i talk to the yeti
we'd we'd just left we're still on our way runaway there
but you when you when i see the any before i kill you want me to
but you in touch with it
is there any way i can call out to the yeti
i mean if i slept out of this
by c_n_n_
and within you know hundred feet of me or so is there like a uh... uh... yelp or
like a scream i could do
to make the eddie i'm like it you could do a scream through my phone
through i_p_s_p_ when i'm within a hundred yards of the eddie
and it's not a compromise but my position
i will call you back
well can take all that don't get to it right now
i'd just i'm just
well i want to talk to the yeti right now
i'm on route to the yeti
okay well you say on route
yeah what do you say
in in
in route
alright well shit
because i'm just a big asshole
i don't get how he can do you
wait did he just say he's in route to the yeti
damn you're weird man
look look
look last night was fun but i i get this is this again all silly alright so uh...
when i hang up but wait wait
when he's
can i please talk to the eddie
thanks uh... he's a good idea
uh... so i think christie
so uh... yeah
uh... you guys we're going to answer what i think iraq
I'm
an elevator there, you guys can flash your passes, it opens up, it lets you in the elevator,
it brings you up pretty far up the mountain. The only other way to get there would have
been to basically jump from the top of the cow, which would have meant you had to get
on top of the cow. So as you go up, you start to see the cow come into view, you see the
head of the cow is pretty near you, and when you get out there's a little ledge, you can
walk along and get to the entrance of the caves. And in the entrance of the caves, though, you
You see there's like sort of a number of these like metal sort of like like perfectly like
cube ish like prisms almost sort of similar to a drawing that the drawing that Joey did.
If you look at the mountains in the background of it, that's basically what the land caves
look like.
He he got it.
He got it.
He got it in one.
And so what is coming out of those land caves are these wires.
like wires that are a bunch of different colors and they slither around and they're like hissing
and like a little bit like a little bit of sparks are coming out of it. So, these are like wires
that like sort of act like snakes almost and attack anybody who walks by which is why people typically
don't go into the land caves unless they're a little bit crazy. So yeah, you guys are about like
the
What's the Eddie call sound like?
So sort of like Chewbacca.
Yeah. Yeah, man. It's weird. Everyone feels a little weird about it.
It happens. It doesn't affect the like the wires don't like react to it.
They seem to be sort of like their own kind of sentient sentient like non sentient thing.
their own kind of sentient, sentient, like non-sentient thing.
Oh, fuck my ass. I fucking hate Roll20 sometimes.
Uh, yeah. That's what happens, though.
Nothing else, though. What do we got, you guys?
Sorry, game. No, that's not... Come on, you don't have to do that.
I'm gonna gracefully dance through the wires.
Ooh, that's cool. Yeah.
the
is
is like, you know, he's a frog.
Did I throw a frog 40 feet right?
He's not a frog size though.
He's like Patrick Yoda size.
So you could probably get him like a good you could probably
throw him like 30 feet.
Now I think about it because you are a big strong demon.
Yeah.
So if you want to you can definitely try to throw him
into that.
Okay.
So I also just remembered we're supposed to get his his the
results for his DNA test.
i guess i i pick them up and i say
lesson
who knows what's gonna happen in the next couple seconds
well you know it was a little bit
okay
before whatever happens happens
for a very long
yet what or ethnicity are you
what
what's up i'm a frog
what's your d_n_a_ what
what at what it was the results of your d_n_a_ test
this there is a member there is that you know this is to say he was going to give
us the results only a
uh... shit uh...
farc do i have to do i have to give you the results right now
okay however can and here it comes iraq i'm i'm so excited
it's
became back
And it said it just said I'm a quarter Cherokee nothing else
Well as your people say hasta la vista
three
Throw him like 11 feet you just throw him like on the ground
And he takes
Some damage oh no, dude, he's gonna die
Takes three damage. She's okay. How much HP does he have? He is 10
the
You could probably throw him about 30 if you get a successful throw.
Because he is a little guy and you're a big demon.
If your throw is successful.
I think I'm going to pick him back up.
Okay. He is absolutely at your mercy.
He's like, "Oh, God, my head."
He's like, trying to figure out where he is.
It's a concussion. I'm going to throw you to a hospital. Just close your eyes.
As you get closer to the land cape,
you can hear the hissing sound coming from the wires a little bit more.
more it sounds like it's a hissing but it's also like
sparks. It's like a you can see the wires there. They're not
small like they're pretty big like they're kind of like
anaconda size and you sort of get a better sense of that as
you move closer and you throw him to roll roll roll on the
shrink check.
13. Yeah, you got it. That's a success. So it's just above
10 to just throw him successfully. Okay, you just launch
solve in the frog and he's like and just like lands admits the wires.
Let's see how he does here.
He's going to be fun.
There's no way he dies.
So first he's going to have to take some damage.
Which I guess and someone can tell me if I'm I know that in DND,
it's like 1d 6 for 10 feet of falling damage, but I'm considering
this
He only took 5 more damage, so he's at 2 HP.
He is in trouble, and he's among the wires.
Let's see how he does dodging the snakes.
Why is he at 2 HP? Wait...
He's a civilian, basically.
He might...
Okay, let's see...
They do... How much damage did they do again?
Did you kill Sullivan?
You might just not know
So he did not make the dexterity saving throw
The snakes just the snake wire things just went after him. He is knocked out cold
He's knocked out cold, here's what I'll say we're playing real D&D
You are 30 feet away. You have 30 feet of movement is in like in like a single round of yeah, right?
The way death saving throws work the right wires aren't gonna keep going after him. He's dead, right?
so the way that this works is
You know for every you know round of combat that he's passed out. We do a death saving throw
So we're gonna start like we're to consider like like initiative is started quote-unquote
But your goal is to revive Sullivan in time
So you're gonna have to get over there in the 30 feet of movement avoid the wires
And you're 30 feet away. They're 40 feet away
so
Everyone roll initiative. I'm gonna roll initiative for Sullivan as well. Okay
For I got six
It's only gonna bet 20 on initiative. Yo, let's go
That's
All the death roll fast. I'm gonna get you out of there Sullivan
All right. So first solve it's gonna roll his death saving throw. Oh my god, dude, you killed Sullivan. Okay, it's a success
It's one success one success. So he needs three successes or he can get three failures and he'll die
Yeah, and so he's still he's so successful now Patrick Yoda. It's your turn
and
sure
uh... where can you draw the wires on here yes i will be drawn them
yeah i think that's what i'm gonna do for sure
so they're sort of like this
okay
and what happens and what stabilize them basically
so stabilizing them while you're waiting for these wires and instantly attack
anything will probably lead to you
getting attacked instead of an ultimate attack and what what happens if solvent
is hit now that he's already knocked out
uh...
so if he is uh...
for the technical rule the actual d_n_d_ rule is but the rule i do
is that if his h_p_
drops below
uh... like negative
his total, he's dead.
Oh, okay.
Mmm.
So, and these things, damage-wise, yeah, they do 2d8 damage.
Oh, okay.
So they could kill him if you force pull him out of there.
Absolutely.
Thanks, Caleb.
Can I hoverboard attack all four of them?
So yeah, here's what we...
There's... so what you can do...
I'm imagining like a cover for this episode that's like the Batman like death in the family arc.
[Laughter]
You can... here's what I'll say, there's a couple of things you have.
So first of all, you obviously have used the force.
So that is a way where you can get like, you know, you're able to like fly at that point
and your movement speed is increased as well.
Wait, can I shoot a foreskin?
It's 30 feet, I can shoot foreskin. So can I shoot the foreskin at
Sullivan? That's not a bad idea.
Oh yeah, because it shields you. And it heals for HP.
And so what it can also do, I will say that it can also force
these wires to make, probably strength checks to move as effectively
because they will essentially be caught in the net as well.
I think that's totally...
You're a genius, Patrick.
I think that's a totally viable move.
So yeah, cast Foreskin.
Okay, cool.
So that's gonna be 3 Technoslime points here down to 10.
Okay.
But that's okay. Just wanna make sure we can track that.
And yeah, roll 1d10 +4.
the
the D10 and it's 4 so...
Oh shit yeah you're right I'm sorry yeah he's at 8 HP
so you hear him underneath your weird
four skin thing
you hear him like *gasp*
and like um
he's like starting to like move around and scurry
and you see the wires underneath start to
move around too to try and...
Don't move Sullivan stay still
Wha-wha-what?
You don't have to say what I literally
it was a very easy instruction
I pull up the flap and I just go
"DO SKELETOR!"
"YOU CAN'T DO THAT!"
"I LOVE YOU GAY!"
David Thoreau, Patrick Yoda.
Four.
Yeah, okay. So why you open it and you start yelling your weird thing and one of the wires like whoosh, like whips out, because you're underneath it now, so you're sort of in...
Oh wait, I didn't know how it worked.
Oh yeah.
What?
You don't want to do that anymore?
No.
Okay, yeah.
I thought it was, okay, I thought that the foreskin was my penis skin. I thought that I had a really long foreskin.
and
of
on
is
uh... from the game football right
all right so you have to do that you have to
poem at the foreskin though too
so it is carried a foreskin with us
i mean just based on what i what i believe is true in the game okay
it's tough to have to basically have a happy with the political
those cute so you'll have to sort of bunch it up
business is like thirty feet of foreskin that is how it's not going to be
like thirty feet by thirty feet of force could you allow a lot of
but just to cover the whole kate patrick just use that just use the disuse the
force to lift his little for skin pod and move it and i'll give
people
dude with patrick has got this
patrick in a safe so i wouldn't know what what do i roll for that
that's uh... uh...
so use the force when i have uh...
of your dinner you used a force urn just use the force area are used to force for
for
the
the wires try to start to reach at him.
But where where is he in relation to the wires now on the map.
Sure. Let me do this for you.
Okay, let me throw this.
So he basically was more like over here actually saying we're Ray William Johnson.
Oh, you guys see I've had him there.
So yeah, if Sullivan was here you threw a straight shot put Ray William Johnson in there.
So he now moved a little bit further into the cave like imagine halfway between that
but I can't and the wires are also a little bit further back,
but it's like the same ratio basically,
but the wires are also kind of like just still there because
they're just these super long wires.
Okay. So yeah, there's not too much movement,
but he's a little bit further into the cave now,
which is away from the active wires,
but what I'm going to have happen now because we started we did do initiative
and I kind of want to go back to that.
I guess because now we're sort of back to this.
We're kind of back now to this. Let's do Caleb. What do you want to do?
Ray William Johnson, sort of waiting to figure out how to help solve in here.
Or not help solve.
The wires are enemies that can be attacked, yeah?
Yeah, you can stun them basically by depleting their HP.
Okay, I think I'm going to use... they're all like in a line, right?
Yeah.
I think I'm gonna use matrix beam and trying collateral all of them and destroy them so easily. Yeah 15 that hits roll for damage
17 nice. Yeah, that's fucking gnarly. Yeah, so you shoot out this super impressive
do you have matrix code that shoots out of your your hands and
just
Sort of like knocks it to these wires and it sort of starts to like
Like jitter a little bit. I will say that they are stunned for like around and
so you can run in there, but no more than that because
Like they're gonna be able to come back so
You can run in there if you all like choose to run now instead of doing anything else. I'm gonna run with that. I'm running
Yeah
Yeah, okay
Yes, you all run in there and then and then I'm gonna say you have to make an athletics check
to pick up Sullivan like a football, whoever's doing it,
before the, uh, uh, the wires come back.
Who has the highest... Okay. I got 16.
So you pick up... A football picks up a football and just like...
you just like... you just like use the force to like open up the foreskin
and, uh, just scoop him out and like are holding him up
above your head, running as the wires are starting to like get unstunned
and start to fling around and flail
and you guys manage to get inside of the cave
and make sure Sullivan doesn't die.
Good thinking with the foreskin
because that might have killed Sullivan.
You see Sullivan is just like, "What?"
- Hey, Sullivan, I know you definitely don't remember
what happened because of the impact,
but remember that Yeti that we were talking about earlier?
- I'm gonna see if he remembers what happened.
- Yeah, so anyway, the Yeti, he came
and he threw you into those fucking wires like a football.
pretty fucked up dude
anyway i saved you just then he got a
i was rolling a d_-twenty i was like please solve a remembers higher than
ten
lower lower than ten
uh... you know i have a ten year members already doesn't get a crit one
so he's just like
and i'm laughing in his face
that's seriously what happened on saturday
he's a girl made out of it on a yeti you're eating flies and living on a
a
the colors like that blues are now green right now.
He's like kind of like he's got like a headache like he's all
fucked up.
He said corny is messed up.
But you guys managed to make it into the the first room of the
the the cave.
You walk into the mysterious land cave.
I mean you remember from you know discussing this with Leo,
You know, it's it's this ancient cave is from but it's from sort of the tail end of the Tamagotchi civilization.
This is one of the last places that they existed, but you would also start as you as you're sort of walking in it.
You start to look around and notice that it seems like the cave is occupied by somebody or something.
So, all of you roll investigation.
See what you see.
Nice.
16, 13, 20.
Let's go.
You guys sort of notice the weird gnarled, clawed tracks on the
ground and some of the scattered wave bird controllers.
And you quickly assess that this cave has been colonized by
gamers.
Gamers essentially look like the Falmer from The Elder Scrolls.
[laughter]
Me and Gamer are looking this up.
Yeah, yeah. I knew Pat would get real good.
Yeah, they've gamed so much their muscles have basically atrophied.
their diet subsists of something called gamer pellets, which has a snack that killed thousands
of people a few years ago. And it makes them experience constant epileptic seizures,
but they still game, they game on. They live in a-
What's the Bosmer equivalent of a gamer?
A Bosmer equivalent?
Like there's the Falmer and the Bosmer, right?
A bosmer like like what kind of I guess they play jonathan blow games maybe they play
They play is that what is that what you're going for? Maybe i'm missing. I don't know
I'm, just saying i'm just trying to like fill out the lore, you know
Oh, I see what you're saying. Yeah, okay
Bosmer or wood elves actually just remembered right? Yeah bosmer the wood elves. Okay. Yeah, so they
They play uh, they play uh, uh the best indie games of the year
uh...
you know they play uh... they love the best in the use of the year they love
haiti's in love uh...
uh... they loved everyone they play started valley still
yet they're still playing started alley uh... in the year two thousand two
hundred and four
yeah
here like almost done i guess marrying all the women's and i would like you to
hear you farm in you make a look make a deal with the almost figured out they
almost caught a fish or something i don't know they love the sims the boss
the
Yeah, yeah, oh yeah, what are the other ones? I can't do this. So there's, yeah, the Falmer,
yeah, and the Falmer do love fucking like competitive shooters, they love competitive
fighters, they love those types of games. They live, exist in a lot of caves on planet E-Bomb,
and people don't know, some of them are, from what you can tell, like some of what people
people know it's like they've they've sort of evolved to not have eyes for some reason from
living in the dark despite gaming and so some have been around for like as long as anybody would think
anything has but some of them seem to be like you know people who live on planet ebom who defected
and sort of started lurking in the cave started gaming got addicted to it and just sort of slowly
You know
You know into saying hillary rodham clinton
So, um, you notice there's like cheeto dust everywhere there's uh, freaking uh,
There's freaking wave birds. I said that already
Yeah, so they're here. They're here. You can kind of get a gist of that and also what you see in this room
Is aside from all the like sort of gamer detritus that's everywhere. You see these like beautiful runes
Inscribed on the walls and these are from the Tamagotchi civilization, you know, they have like feces and and and
Hot fries sort of like smeared on them
But you could see sort of like this like this was a place where the Tamagotchi civilization lived
And what you also see in the middle of it sort of like jammed in there almost
looks like a a like
Computer like a like a old old sort of computer and a DDR pad
And NES controller attached to it and
Yeah, and so that's what you see in this room you don't see any doors to go to the next part of a cave
But you know people probably come in here so what do you guys want to do hmm I
Okay, what I when I see the get when I see the gamers
is
I
here
they seem scared of me because i'm a feminist
yeah i thought they would like attack and i was trying to know i think i will
hear it here here all of
yeah i'm a totally a feminist
i think i sort of depression quest
yet
that's my favorite games he is small turd roll out from under the rock
uh...
i
What would you do if there were two?
Are they gonna try to attack us if the DDR machine...
Okay, then I'm gonna save this in case it happens.
Okay, you can do a quick save.
Hit F5.
Okay.
There's no way you just let that happen.
Alright, let's go to the DDR.
Real quick, I give Sullivan the turn. And I say, "This is for you."
Wait, yeah, I heal can I heal Sullivan anymore? Sullivan this is food on this planet. Don't waste your point
Sullivan's almost full
Yeah, I got it. That's right. I am
I keep trying to step forward to go to the DDR pad and getting distracted by one of those
Yeah, you go to the DDR pad
You see it's like hooked up to the computer which also has like a USB port where the NES controller is attached to it
And yeah, when you step on the DDR pad the screen lights up on the computer
And it says like like DDR and then a list of songs comes up
Caramel dancing
that
can go back to the menu you're not dancing you didn't hit can watch what
I'm dancing blowtoss is dancing right I'm dancing to caramel dancing okay yeah
you're doing like you're dancing the caramel dance a roll performance check
okay can it be athletics instead yeah yeah I'm doing a very athletic a very
I mean, GDR, yeah, that's fair.
I'm doing the hands over the ears like really fast.
It's like really athletic and I'm working up a sweat.
Just like a pear-shaped 15 year old at the arcade.
You're killing it.
You do it really good. You get like perfect, perfect, perfect, perfect on all the fucking shit.
I'm singing along to whatever weird language that song is in.
Go white boys.
the
and uh...
and
group
here in the total you only get through three letters so it's just a lot
no it's too already it's like a lot of read what you finish writing it it just
confirms that i wrote by the because that's i think it was spelled
Okay.
Okay, good.
Yeah, I turn around I go guys.
You see the funny name.
I put in.
Oh, yeah, like you're a grandpa like pop.
Yeah, because and I'm like, yeah.
Yeah, because I'm thinking I'm imagining a grandpa pooping and
I'm like, yeah, exactly.
And so at this point when I should mention is you guys can
look at your passes that you all have and you see on it that
It says 54 minutes and 36 seconds 54 minutes and 32 seconds, you know, it goes down by four seconds
You know, I was just figuring how long it took me to say that. All right, so
uh, uh, I wanted to let you know not to be a rude dm but to remember to hold myself to the thing I set you to
um, so yeah, uh, uh
At that point your passes will expire that doesn't necessarily mean you get kicked out of the cave
It just means you are would be officially trespassing. That's all. Yeah
a
out what's supposed to happen when i win the game
do we just play d_d_r_ for nothing
metal was a very highly for nothing
i look at the time ago all suite fifty four minutes of dance dance revolution
uh...
uh... yeah
so you also have that in the lead to by the way
that we are eager to hear your god
uh... and you know you can also do a little more investigating your stupor
in the room
to to figure out figure out what's uh... what's happening here i like your first
incidently d_d_r_ though not a bad one
out
no way we just
twenty-two you are
the
uh... and i and i put the the amulet into you said it's like a cd-rom type
thing right
can i put it into the the
game slot
into the computer yet there's a deep uh...
the
this
was to general on okay with you know i i'm gonna talk to this gamer
neutral dot on an attempt to make it may be a rare
yet talk to him
still there it is your a ms t
and then do you know what is there like uh...
is like the only room in this damn day what's up
user crawls out from the rocker
for looking at you
uh... to lead a tribal beautiful
uh...
he uh... his eyes are almost like on his like one of those who's like
almost of all the noize but and just as almost noize
uh... really tiny dots
first of your eyes are fucked up second off
do you speak
do to our blessing grace
i'll be back
he tries to mimic your
i've got an idea
he turns to you and goes
"I'm going to go to the zoo!"
"I'm going to go to the zoo baby!"
Okay, here's all I have, YouTube.
Let's have, you know what, you guys are archaeologists, so let's say this language is pretty hard to come by,
and, you know, because it's pretty insular, it's among the gamers, not many people are able to interact with them.
so role a uh... role on
uh...
let's do history check
from your studies uh...
both rewilling johnson and patrick you know
to see if you're certain i got a nineteen holy jacob you got a natural
twenty actually got a little and
that's still not bad but
you got natural twenty so you can understand him
really clearly
uh... as far as you can do which is like you get like the gist which he you get
the he's saying like
well are you making fun of me
are you making fun of me
and uh... is you're making noise to you assume and then also when he was saying
to caleb was something along the lines of uh...
of uh...
uh...
only only we can get out of here
there are no rooms and let you solve the riddle
we gotta make him play d_d_r_
way there's a there's also an a_t_s_ controller
i press it
okay you press the start but i i i i present really hard
you start but still comes up uh... start menu c select songs
different things that i put in the kona me code
you know is
yet i'm so glad i thought it's my own i can't tell
that was it yeah you got it
i saw a parking lot
so you're angrily pacing around and i don't know what you're talking about
it
fucking mad
okay
all right
all pop
down down left right left yet no
well
that's a little more
opens
there's a door? I didn't see a door. I'll explain, I'll set the...
I'll set the scene. Hold on, I'm gonna cry.
God damn it dude.
I feel like a controller in my hand. I feel like such an asshole.
Good game buddy.
They'll never get the Konami code.
alright whatever i thought it was fun
uh... so here's what happened
i like the idea of me alone they'll never get the konami coat
no way
what's that? you'll never figure it out?
luke hangover
they'll think of so many things before the konami coat
so the uh... the rock there's like this like looks like a rock wall
walk rock wall but instead like a an outline sort of like appears like you
hear the like you know stone sliding against stone sound that you hear in
fucking mystery things when you're you find a hidden door and it slides open
and you actually see you actually also see the ship from fucking what's it
called from a Mass Effect.
Except it's like a miniature version of it.
Looks like a raft almost and you see this at beyond the door.
This long just dark like waterway of some sort and you see
the little gamer like the little scary and scary up to the
little way the raft and he's like and he's like sort of dancing
on it a little bit like kind of excitedly and I can understand
You can understand he's saying like, "You got it, you got it, damn, you got it!"
Um...
Yeah.
I say back, I go...
[unintelligible]
What does that mean?
That means...
What?
[laughter]
Uh, yeah, and uh...
Is there an NES controller in this room?
In the next room?
Yeah.
Well, you'll see the next room.
So you guys jump on the raft and you glide down this like dark cavernous river and
uh god so no I'll tell you guys about all the ideas I had and uh and um uh as you do it starts to open up a bit and you notice to your left um suddenly like it starts to get brighter and brighter and the the cave starts to open up a bit and uh you just see these like
And you notice to your left, suddenly it starts to get brighter and brighter and the cave starts to open up a bit.
And you just see these weird rooms on the left side. You wouldn't be seeing this as top down.
But you're all riding on top of the Mass Effect ship and you see these rooms and they have...
And you see in the windows these gamers like in these rooms like like just playing games or sleeping or jerking off or just hanging out
One of them's in the bathtub
You see them there
And you see the little gamer turn to you Patrick and he's like
He's saying he's saying those are my brothers they're not so nice please be quiet and
That's and
That means what?
Yeah, we could end it there oh
My god, so there's like runes on the wall
He read the world. There was a there was a I had a riddle if you walked into the computer
There's forum posts, and riddles, and oh my god, there's all this fucking shit.
[Music]