Long, long ago, the world had no Christmas.
Toys would be made, but never be presents.
Children were good, bad, naughty, or nice, but no coal would be given.
No checking lists twice.
But one day, that all changed.
For Santa gave birth.
The son of Santa, king of kings, such merry and mirth.
but this would not happen without three wise men. This is their story from
beginning to end. I wish I wrote my intro in rhyming now. I hate that rap crap.
Yeah, me too. So who are these three magi, these three wise men? Let's start
on my right here. Okay. Well, I didn't figure out a voice yet, so I'm gonna
just say the first sentence and see what comes out.
My name
thing good like
of the candy kingdom. It's pretty good. I am a wise M&M sage, the wisest and
oldest in the land. The king of the candy kingdom relies on me for all advice and
policy, but now I wander the desert in search of the son of Santa. I have been
commanded by the candy king to bring the son of Santa a gift, the gift of
chocolate. But these sands are harsh on a 98 year old M&M. Oh, how I long for
the comforts of my candy kingdom. It's chocolate spires and chocolate archways,
roads paved in chocolate and chocolate everything else as well.
nice and I'm I'm an ancient M and M from before from B. C. Times, so I look
like a normal M and M, but I made out of antelope hide. That's I saw chocolate on
the inside, but it's animal, animal skins and it's really dark chocolate,
a hundred percent cocoa nib type chocolate. Yeah, that's really good, but
I still have an M. I forgot about the present. Can I change my present or do
you have written? You could change your present. M is for Mesopotamian. It's for
My name is M. And so you're and so you you are this wise sage M and M who old
old, old and wise.
And you
just disgusting. That's all they had back then. They had discovered vanillia.
Frankincense, myrrh, sage. Disgusting sage. And you're travelling with a couple
of other wise magi. Let's go, let's give him time to think of what he's gonna say
and go right to Caleb.
(clears throat)
Hold on, bitch.
I'm holding on.
(coughs)
I come from the Elf tribe of the North Pole,
where for thousands of years,
my ancestors have been barely surviving in the harsh cold,
living off of the rancid flesh from dead animals
washed ashore, and sometimes, each other.
My father fell in the cold last winter
because he thought he saw a strawberry.
There's little to do except look for food,
where I come from and look for food where I come from
and wait for the cold to claim those closest to you.
We mostly pass the time by having ice eating competitions
and also making Xboxes and OLED TVs,
even though we don't know what those are yet.
One week ago, I saw a bright star in the sky
and heard a voice that told me that a child
might give my people purpose in 17 or 1800 years.
So I'm an elf on a mission.
My name is Harold and I'm on a quest to save my people.
and I'm going to give him
massage chair
massage here for the sun. Yeah, I love that Griffin McElroy. Yeah,
he sounds like an out
well. Just do Griffin McElroy. Yeah and X boxes and L a TV.
So we have an old M and M traveling with Griffin McElroy. Yeah, well Harold,
but you're old McElroy the elf
and yeah, you're from the North Pole, but there's there is no Christmas. So
it's just this cold, harsh, confusing place. We don't know why we're there,
we don't know where we came from, we don't know where to go.
There is another elf kingdom, a sister kingdom that you will visit. Sister?
Holy crap. Also make a ton of toys. Oh, shiz. It would be nice if
something could be done about that. And make a ton of toys. Where is it,
China?
Well, a lot of the elves are being... Hit that zombie nation.
Hey, you actually got it on the second try.
A lot of elves are being replaced by China.
Yep.
And yep to that is what I said.
Okay.
Okay, who is left?
Hello, bitch.
You all remember me from our previous campaign?
Bitch, it's me, Pikachu.
From the Valentine's Day campaign we did two years ago.
You remember that?
remember
fans have been begging for this character to come back.
People have them. We remember this character. We will be my
member about him is I remember I'm a member. I'm popped. You look you should
have been a member Barry. You're dressed up like one.
I heard I heard that there was a baby that was immaculately conceived and I
wanted to see what the vagina would look like.
I don't remember this character at all. I remember he was a power sunrise. He
was supposed to be like Pepe Lapu kind of, but then you that was fun. We
accidentally made him Israeli and now I don't think I should really do that at
this time. I don't think it was an accident. I think it was a thing. I
think it was the first thing you thought of when you thought of the
character. I think maybe that's true. I have we listened to it two weeks ago
when we played this
anyway, I bought the baby X dark temptation body spray to turn them into
a chocolate guy to walk around and have women. I'm going to teach him the game
like a mystery who will not be around for another couple of hundred deals.
Two hundred two hundred deals like it's like right. It's like we're at zero a
D yeah we're a good zero yeah bro. By the way, I am at every single time
really like Dr. Manhattan. He was only in one time period. He can. I guess he was
he saw everything you say. I will see I'll see everything. So I will teach the
baby about Tindale
and what they think apps are like. So for you to so I got a good sense of that.
You have advised the M and M can I'm wise by beyond my beyond my years. I'm
ninety eight years old. I'm still wise beyond my years. I'm an old soul. Do you
elf Harold, do you advise them on building the OLED TVs? Like what do you
what do you do? Like why am I wise? Yeah, yeah. Because I'm the only person who
hasn't thought that there was a berry out there that I could find. All my
family has died looking for a berry. You got a 23 in your ACT. Yeah, we have ACT's out there.
We do unfortunately have to take standardized testing. If you get lower than a 23,
you're like you're berry prone. Yeah, we'll keep you away. You are looking for a berry.
I think exactly I come from I come as an elf. I cut you got a twenty three. I
think so. Yeah, is that isn't that good? I think that's bad. I think a third. I
think is like good. I thought I think twenty three is like remarkably average.
It's like a right. It's kind of right in the middle. I think it goes up to thirty
six. Yeah, so it's like we think that it says it's above the current national
average. It's a strong makes you a strong applicant. Look at you man. Many
universities. You're above average in the United States.
Not really saying much. What's wrong with the US?
That's
amazing. You're Israeli. I dropped out of community college. And then you went to
a normal college. You went to a normal school. And then dropped out of that.
I dropped out of every single college I've been to. Yeah, every single one.
You're wise, I guess, because you're a Pikachu. I'm wise because I know game.
you live forever to and I also know game. That's the most important part about
now. We know who you are, so all you guys have your get your docs up as well.
Yeah, we're all going to read this poem. I love
yeah, you said Pikachus moves.
Oh, because you didn't remember who this was. No,
you didn't remember that this was just a guy named Pikachu. Yeah,
He gave him the animals. He gave me actual Pikachu. We did do a Pokemon thing.
Yeah. Well, that is true, bitch. Three wise magi traveled through the desert
and saw a star in the sky, one that with all their wisdom and occult knowledge,
they could not recognize. Perturbed and distressed, one of them said, "What
star could that be? What could that star mean?" To which another replied,
"I'm not sure. Where is my cream?" And he looked in his sack and still found
no cream. He checked his robe, there was no cream indeed. He shrugged and said,
"Away to the king we go to speak." And on they traveled, their journey began.
The third one said nothing, his mouth was slammed.
Whatever my dark temptation was in my mouth.
And so you guys are in this
desert, this hot desert right now,
on your way to go see the elf king, the Earl Konig.
And what now?
Earl Koenig.
Earl Koenig, you said?
It's a German for elf king.
Keening.
Oh, OK.
Keening?
You know how to say it, right?
I learned the hard way.
Earl Keening.
You did.
Did you?
[LAUGHTER]
I did.
I-- I'm now millions of people.
[LAUGHTER]
Millions.
Millions is--
And--
That'd be awesome.
You see on the horizon of this hot, hot desert--
I just-- you pointed over here, and I looked at the TV.
No, it's awesome.
Yeah.
That's a power I have now.
you see two men approach you one long one stout the one one round one real quick
heights long again. Oh character heights. How big is an M and M like one
centimetre centimetre less than a centimetre? I think we're all pretty
short, because if I remember correctly, you're an you're not a big M and M.
You're not like I didn't think about it before. So think about it. Think about
it. Are you like the one who hangs out? Well, okay, I'm a giant. I'm like three
centimeters tall. Okay, that was like that's a big M and I was big as in
and I guess the ones from the commercial. I think are three feet tall.
Yeah, I'll be the size of the one from the movie trailer. Okay, and you have
lips
no, I'm a boy. I'm an M. Oh, you have eyes. Yeah, sure. That's yeah. I look
like yes. Oh yeah, you're right. You have white sneakers on. Okay, sneakers
are at least I'm kind of a beige color with a burlap texture
sandals, a tweed rope around you. Yeah, yeah, yeah, and I have a taunt shirt.
Okay, this and I also have a walking stick. That's important to be good for
me to tell. I think if I remember correctly,
the way that I described Pikachu last time was five foot two and I'll dance
with you.
So this time he has electric powers too. Yeah, I mean maybe
he's always had them. Wow, and he didn't use them in a row. All right, and
And what is your look then? Your elf. I look exactly like I look in real life right now.
Okay, perfect. Except for the height. The height is lower. The height is in -- Your
height is lower than the elf's height, is what you're saying? I'm not even -- it doesn't
matter. You can probably guess what my elf height is. I don't need to -- Well, it's taller
than Caleb, right? Like 5'9". For some reason, he looks like Christmas and Link to -- 5'9"
is actually average in -- above average in Asia. In Asia? You're in the North Pole, though.
so is that the Asia? I guess it's kind of Asia. It's not that much. It's not not
Asia, right? It's not Asia. It could be. It could. Move on, move on. So,
these two men approach you, they're all- both of them are- Where are we? We're
in the desert? We're in the desert. You're traveling to the kingdom. Oh, my
God, it's so hot. It's so hot. I'm melting. I died. I'm just kidding, guys.
You can't melt. You made out of- They don't have melting stuff in my body yet.
And you see the long one lift his arm up and go, "There they are, Cain!" And
the one goes shut up able. Oh wait you're right there. They are and then they
wander up to you. What is a bitch?
The old God says you three are through white. Where's there? What old talk
about old
this God is
God is older than you.
Yeah, he's sold
he shut up. You can't think of anything. This is how I this is my own internal
Okay, no quick attack. Oh really good. Okay. I don't want to fight the cane
and able to which one are you attacking 13 13 plus six is 13 year old one.
Oh, which one are you attacking canery attacking the boss cane cane. All
right. So you attack him 19 does hit roll for damage. That's one d 8 plus
four and then we'll roll for initiative.
Nine.
That's not the
you didn't show me.
You didn't show me.
- You didn't show it to me and I just said yes.
- Which was a big mistake.
- There we go.
- Well I would have got six in any universe.
- In any universe.
- What?
- Six plus four is 10.
- So, quick attack.
- The doodoo ranger is hitting you.
- Describe what is--
- The doodoo ranger is hitting me.
- How does Pikachu do quick attack?
- Just uh.
- He swipes his cape in front of his own face?
- Dracula.
- But the swipe of the cape.
Okay, so you hit Kane with that, he goes, "Ah, shit!"
Shut up, bitch!
You shut up!
Okay.
All right, roll for initiative.
Everybody roll for initiative.
All right, bro.
14, wait, wait, 14 plus six?
Why is my initiative so high?
I got a 24.
You made us OP so we don't die in this one.
A little bit.
Oh, I caught you red-handed.
I made you a little bit stronger.
You made me the strongest one here.
It's because there's a lot of adventuring,
And I'd--
- You thought that I was a regular Pikachu,
that's the problem.
(laughing)
- You thought I was a level one Pikachu.
- I got a 20 for my initiative roll.
- And what did you get?
- 24.
- And then what did you get?
- Nine.
- Okay, cool.
- Harold, you're gonna go first.
- Oh yeah, oh yeah, go Harold.
- So yeah, I mean, Kane's not looking good.
You're a little bit a ways away,
not a ways away, like 10, 15 feet away.
You have a couple abilities.
I gave you some bard like ones. You have Borealis Glow. It's basically fairy fire.
You said Cain is hurt, right?
Yeah, you have Bardic Inspiration, which is Carol, which you sing a song, a Christmas
song, but you don't know that it's a Christmas song, but some ancient song that your people
know.
I'm going to go Icicle Attack, but I'm going to do it on Abel.
Wait, if we just kill Cain, then Abel will be at our mercy.
But I have a feeling that Abel is a tank, so I'd like to freeze him.
Yeah, you have a chance of freezing them with that attack.
Okay, I'm going to do that on Abel.
Roll a d20. What did you get?
Well, not so good.
Is that a 9?
That's a 6.
Yeah, so plus 3 is 9.
Yeah, 9.
Yeah, so you swipe at Abel and Abel goes, "Eugh, eugh!"
And you just somehow, you know, he does sort of Mr. Magoo dodges, right?
Okay.
Yeah, that's sort of the end of your turn.
Next is Pikachu.
Can I stun him with Thunder Wave? I'm going to do the exact same idea.
You can try, yeah.
but I will stun him with Thunder Wave.
Cool.
Paralyzed for two turns.
No, you don't roll. He rolls.
Okay.
And he got much higher than a DC14 save,
so he does not get paralyzed.
Crap on the stick.
Yeah.
Wait, then you know what I do?
I'll handle it, y'all.
Let's see what you do.
I mean, you can move too, but that's about it.
And if you move, you will move away from Cain,
who will have an attack of opportunity.
Can I entrance him?
So you...
Maybe a sexual style dance?
You could yeah, you could try to dance. Okay, I start doing
What do you think is a sexual dance?
I I'm in my my Pikachu mind palace and I'm pulling up dances from I'm doing evolution of dance in my head
Mm-hmm, and then I taint it's like yeah, there's only like
I'm doing evolution of dance in my head until I get to
2008 when I see the evolution of dance Wow, and then I just do the evolution of dance at him. Okay roll a
And this is one of your attacks.
Roll a speaking.
Roll mouth.
I'm rolling mouth.
No, this is not an attack, but like a kind of like same.
A talent.
Okay, talent roll.
I'm rolling talent.
He's going to have to do very well for this to do anything at all.
15.
No.
So you do, you dance for like eight minutes.
I'm doing the entirety of Evolution of Dance and it's very impressive, but it's not the
time.
No, no.
And yeah, Cahain looks at you and he goes, "It's just not the time."
but he takes some damage from how cringe it is man. Yeah, he does yeah.
Oof does he yawn? I just take some and bored image. Yeah. Does he open his
mouth really, really wide and so you have an ability? Yes, don't spoil it for
them. We'll get to you in a second. Does he yawn? He does. He yawns. It is his
turn first. Oh shit. Can you make him yawn again at the end of his turn? I
will. So he's gonna attack you. I just bore him. He's gonna attack you, Pat. So
he picks up. He picks up able. He throws a stone in the air and uses him like a
baseball bat to hit you with it. So let's see how we go. Able is short and
squat. Yes. No, it was the other way around.
It's not very good. So he tries to hit you with the stone and the stone just
walks past. You're able to go, oh, and it just maybe it hits my... Yeah,
maybe it hits your cape. It hits my cape. And you deflect it,
like in Smash Bros Mario. Yeah.
You look like Joker from Persuasion. Oh, yeah. With the mask as well as the
and then able is going to go now and able is going to throw up a stone and hit his
head against it to try to hit you with it.
Oh, I get it and he misses yeah, yeah, he misses a last roll. Yeah, they're
doing terribly. All right, any yawns again, then both of them yawn cane and
able then cane. Okay, so cane gets really tired and I run up and I jump into
cane's mouth. I get swallowed by him, so they have to roll it. So here's what
they have to do. So he has a bill called eat me
They have to roll to resist his delicious flavor, and he is a very high
It's a very hard
It's a hard roll to resist and when he does that he goes inside of the enemy and then can beat them up from the inside
Doing additional damage from his regular attacks however. He does take 1d for digestion every turn. He's inside
I didn't read that part, but that's okay. Yeah, you have to maybe just stay in the throat
Maybe I'll just stay in the throat and grab the uvula so you can throw them up
Yeah. But then you would take stomach acid. He does not resist. Who did you want? I was
going into Cain. All right. You see, you guys. Yeah. You guys just hear me go. You know what?
I am getting kind of peckish. I said, I said, over guys, I'm gonna. And then I just get
swallowed. Holy clap. His mouth is so big. He's all that three foot man. Oh yeah. That
is a big M and M and stomach. Yeah. Yeah. Well, I want to see you eat the whole hoagie.
Luckily, Cain is kind of round. It just kind of fills him out, basically.
It's like having...
- Yeah. - Yeah.
So we're back to the top of the order now.
I don't do any damage right away?
No. No, in your next turn, you will.
Oh, I see. I should stay out of it now.
You should crap.
- We're back to the top of the order. - You should crap.
- A lot of crap. - Crap inside of you.
- A lot of crap, guys. - Me again?
- Yeah. - Okay.
So Cain seems to be taken care of.
So I think that I will go after Abel.
Cool.
And I think that I will do my icicle attack again.
Nice, go for it.
Shit.
Yeah.
I suck, man.
We're going to die.
Yeah, Abel's just sort of bobbing and weaving.
He's like going like, "Where'd my brother go?"
You know, and stuff like that.
Don't dwell on it.
He's over there.
Wait, where did his brother go?
I point way far away.
Okay.
He starts to walk away.
Stupid ass bitch.
And you do have an attack of opportunity.
I hit him again!
Okay, roll.
With the icicle attack.
We just killed Kane, this able guy.
And 16.
We don't even have to fight him.
We can just trick him.
Oh yeah.
Okay, roll damage.
1d8.
I know I'm going out of order, folks.
This is fun, though.
Well, that's a 3.
3 plus 3.
So 6.
Nice.
And then DC 10.
Yeah, so he has to try to resist.
Oh, great line.
Oh, this guy's fail is fucked.
So you hit him in the head with the icicle, and he goes, "Hey!"
And he freezes.
He's going to freeze for one second.
and he freezes. He's going to freeze for one turn. Okay, take a picture of where
it looks like I'm humping him.
You could do that in your turn. Pikachu took a mental picture. Oh yeah. And so
now... They don't have cameras yet, man. I'm going... Draw a tablet. I'm going
into my mind palace again. It's just a dance and a picture. Two screens.
There's two things I'm watching, evolution of dance on one picture in
picture window and then the other one I'm watching like the Kodak company
invented camera.
Okay, if we can get
like a film and like all this other stuff, I could take a picture,
but we need, we need to wait a couple of years. That's okay.
The memory is gonna last way longer. Yeah, it's gonna last a really long
time.
Oh yeah.
Oh, it's lasting.
What are you looking at, Patrick? What's happening, man? I don't know, I'm
to see what he's going to do with this turn. Oh, I don't think he knew it was
his turn. I didn't know it was my turn because you were waiting for it. I didn't
either. No, it's not. I didn't go. It is your turn. But I was in that moment, I was
reimagining the moment of him pretending to hump him. Is that you're using your
turn or? You know what, fuck it. I actually hump him. Okay, cool. Oh yeah. Kind of cool
Sullivan. Yeah, I get well if he's already inside of I'm not going to do
that much damage guys. You should still fight. Yeah, we just we said take a
crap inside him. I will. I will able's frozen right crap doesn't damage.
You get a man to eat. You know what? While able is frozen and he's busy
with Kane. I'm going to try evolution of dance again and in this case,
So the goal is okay, maybe you are distracted before, but now that I have
your full attention, he's a captive audience. Now that I have your full
attention, you need to watch this. This could be psychic damage, just roll.
Seventeen plus two, nineteen. So it's not even like you made up an attack,
but I guess yeah, it's just they just both of them just take each of them are
gonna take one D4 psychic damage from seeing you do that. Oh yeah, that's how
Oh my God.
Kane takes four, Abel takes one.
So Kane's not looking too good.
He's in your tummy and he's like, "Argh, I smell."
He's in his tummy.
No, just let it be.
I'm sorry.
I got it wrong.
I just ate him.
No, no, no.
No, no.
months. I love that part. Yeah, I need to do a re watch. Yeah, pull that up.
Don't pull that. Don't pull it. Don't pull it. You'll lose me for eight
minutes. You lose all of us. Yeah. All right, cool. So now it is Cain's turn
and Cain is going to try to
get you out of his body. So he's going to try. I haven't even done anything
yet. He's still happy. Yeah. Oh, I'm so bummed. I ate an M and M. That's him.
Well, it's really hard to do it. So yeah, he doesn't he's not able to do
uses a turn trying to get you out. So yeah, you start to see the push and pull of the mechanic
now. Yeah. And it is now Abel's turn and Abel is frozen solid. It's something he can do.
You're now up. So now I attack and I do 1d6 extra damage, right? That's correct. I'm going
to use my candy punch. First of all, I would drink that's an eight. It's an eight. So that's
not going to hit. Not even from inside. Not even using an extra move to crap. I was going
I was going to say that I was going to want to use a bonus action. Yeah,
you give a bonus bonus crap yeah, but you crap chocolate. No, I don't know
you.
That would be like a crap lugs, human flesh and meat. I
excrement it's just shit man. Everything shits basically the same,
though, as an M and M sand grass
it was going to pass
all right. I believe that
the ferns. Okay, yeah, right, so it's just sort of like just sort of
manure.
He's like, "Oh, no!" It falls out like one of horse poops. Okay, and it
looks exactly like a horse poop. Yeah. Alright, you see Cain. Cain goes like,
"Oh!" And he vomits you up. He grabs Abel and he goes, "We gotta get out
of here!" I take one grossness damage. "We have to tell the old god about
And they go and they start running off shit man riding able like a donkey don't I get an attack of opportunity?
He's running away from me. Yeah, you do. Okay, I'm gonna try and punch him again
11 mm-hmm
And they run off terrified of you guys. I'm going to tell some sort of old God. We're so scary
I thought there's thing old guard
Old God
Testament so you guys we don't know that defeated Kane and it could just be guys named Kane and Abel
Are you joking this could they could be headed to of course their head now?
You beat them for now. They ran for now. These fuckers are gonna make a return
Yeah, you know they are you head to the city of the elves
So everyone pull up their poem
I
Got it bitch. I got it - okay
Leaving us a desert so hot and dry and facing such foes
We're in luck. We're alive another wise man did speak and spoke with concern those brothers were strange murderous
Unlearned but reaching the city was oh such a joy for the city of elves is filled up with toys
the elves do work from morning till night to make balls and dice and checkers and kites and Legos and yo-yos and
Slinkys and clay and teddies and edgies at sketchy hooray
This is gonna be such a fucking struggle away to the king the elf king knows all
But first they wanted to shop at the mall
Remember this world had no presence to give buying and selling was all that folks did and malls are so dope
I love the mall. This will be awesome. Let's shop till we fall
So there sounds good to me. You were a rhymer. I was I didn't know your secret hidden talent
Sucian Sucian for shizu doc D. And
It's so doc T and doc
collecting in the wayfare final hours minutes or left on the sale. So you
guys are at the mall in the elf kingdom. They do sell ball dice checkers
kites Legos yo-yo slinkies clay teddies and that just sketches. They're all
each of those are two silver piece. They also sell health potions worth 10
silver piece. You have 32 say help potion health potions about help potion.
They have 10 so help each of those are worth 10 silver. You guys all have
30 silver. Yeah, each of you have 30 silver is how many silver pieces all
Is that a biblical reference?
Was it? Didn't Jesus get sold out by Judas for a certain amount?
Twelve.
Three?
I think it was three or thirty or something.
You know what?
Whatever you say.
Twelve, I think of the number of apostles.
Yeah, but wasn't it one?
One per apostle.
I forgot the amount.
Why would they chip in?
They all chipped in.
One bad egg.
Tomorrow's the carton.
It was thirty pieces of silver.
Thirty pieces of silver.
Yeah.
It's exactly what he gave each of us.
And what does that signify for our characters?
That is scary.
you know, it's that was that intentional. It actually was not. I wish it was it
was
unconscious mind. Yes, this is always trying to tear down the Bible, even
Catholic by the way in it. I love Jesus Catholic, not a real Christian. Okay,
that I don't want to hear completely true Roman Catholic going to hell more
Christian. Deifies Mary deifies Mary. Okay, well, fuck you. Yep, and we're done.
You know what's scary is the scene in Passion of the Christ where Judas kills himself.
Oh yeah, when there's all those crows bugging at his face.
You guys gonna buy anything?
I want three health potions.
What, I mean, what, there's fucking nothing?
There's toys and health potions.
I'm gonna buy a purple limo.
I'm gonna buy a toy to see how it-
There's no purple limo.
Okay, then I want nothing.
I'm gonna buy a toy to see how it stacks up against the shit we're making back north.
Alright, cool.
What do you want, which toy do you want to buy?
What do you got?
Kites, balls.
Ball dice.
Kites, balls, ball, dice, checkers, kites, legos, yo-yos, slinkys, clay, teddies, etch-a-sketch.
I guess I'll take a teddy.
And there's health potions?
How much is a teddy?
Teddy's two silver pieces.
Oh yeah, fucking throw it in a bag.
Done.
Yeah, and yes, there are health potions.
What else is there?
There's health potions and...
That's it.
Why are you just leaking?
Keeping track of my silver.
I like the idea of like...
Oh you must, where's the rest of the list you have?
Yeah.
No, that's it.
Do you have any secret menu items?
Let's go to the next part of the party. Maybe like a teddy bear that has like...
Oh, there's a teddy bear.
Yeah, but like a teddy bear that like is combined with another toy.
You can do that if you get a teddy bear and another toy and you want to combine them together.
Is this a reference?
No, it's more or less a...
It's a reference to a toy you had.
It's a reference to fast food secret menus, if anything.
Right, yeah.
If anything, you're doing it.
But what about a teddy bear that is also a health potion?
Imagine how big and opaque these sunglasses are. I feel like you're staring me in the
face the whole time you say this. I was not looking at you. I know it really feels like
you are just because of the size and shape of the sunglasses. So you want to pay me?
You want to pay more for a health potion? Okay, so you remember Grandma's Soup from
Wind Waker, right? Sure. I want the equivalent of that where I combine two things, but it's
it's more expensive. I combine two things together, but it's basically two health
potions in one jar. Okay, so you want to play Wind Waker right now? Yes. You can
go do that later, but for now you get a teddy bear. I want to combine a teddy
bear with a health potion and... And you want it to count for two. That's stupid.
The soaking, the soaking up of the... Okay, I want to put a teddy bear inside
of my health potion. This guy's inventing haggling in the year 0 A.D. But he's
haggling with you. Yeah. Why are you doing? Is you trying to play your
character here? Is there something that you think about your character that
makes you want to do this? No, no. I blame the doo doo. Let's go. You go
to the king then. You fail to make a purchase, you get nervous
and start making shit up. You start babbling about nothing. I wanted to
make a... I wanted there to be a creature shop. Yeah. Well, next time
I'll put a creature shop. Maybe I put a teddy bear or a toy. Don't ask
questions. Maybe I give a toy a health potion and it comes to life.
That could have happened.
That's what I was trying to do.
That's not what you were trying to do.
You need to be transparent with us, man.
You can't fucking string us along like this.
And you guys...
That's what I'm trying to do now.
Meet with the king, your old friend.
Trying to string us along?
The Earl Conan.
Yeah, I ruined it.
The king of kings.
Or the king of elves, I should say.
Okay, king of kings.
I know who that is.
Ah, that is God.
He sees you guys.
And he's up above.
Says, "Ah, my old friends."
Wassup, bitch?
"Harold, Pikachu, and..."
Kumau.
M. I've never met you before in my life. Oh, I must have mistaken you for another
friend who is also an elf. And who had the same name as him. Yes, that too.
Oh, okay. It's a good trick though. I guess you do live in a city of elves so that
would make some sense. Yeah, I get confused. Okay. Now I hear tell that you've
you've seen a star in the sky that gave you great pause.
Yeah, it was gay
okay,
nice one is acting gay yeah. That was a guy said all pause no
yeah. We saw a star in the sky and it was around this direction. I just
thought of a joke. Okay, well a let him say his joke and then we'll continue
star in the sky. That gave us pause. What are you talking about a guy seeing the
the moon and turning into a werewolf. Nah, that was a good one. That was good.
No, I
also don't say anything else. When you're going to make him give a help
attack, it's nothing
he doesn't have a heart. Stop worrying about him. It's nothing. See the elf
doctor, the elf doctor, just keep bursting his head out through the way.
Yeah, just keeps like kind of getting yeah, getting pump faked. It's like
treating a heart attack. It's like an MPC. You take an item and they start
hard to put it back. It must have been the wind yeah.
He goes well. Let me consult my astro lab lab astro labia last row labia. It
takes out the labia. He takes out Pika juice favorite thing in the world, a
big old pussy and he consults it and for all I want to get
I pull out a magnifying glass
and he says oh my it seems a great thing is to occur the son of one center of the
North Pole.
Holy clap.
I believe something will begin if you three travel and make a journey and bear
gifts for this son of Santa.
That's crazy.
We were already doing that right.
Yeah, your intros.
I realize that after the fact good, but we'll keep doing it if it's gonna do
something okay, but pretend I was the one who came up with it right
thanks
and as I consult the astrolabe, I have something you don't know oh great yeah,
I believe it.
Well, my name's Harold, the shut well, I don't know even know who you are. I
- Yes, that's true.
- You must follow the star and face trials.
In the valley of giants, you shall help the meek and feeble.
On the river, you shall help solve a riddle.
Across the sea, you must face a great many beasts
and over the mountain will be a great battle
that I cannot foresee.
- I follow the star and I go to the restraining order.
- You must bear gifts though
and recognize the son of Santa as king.
- It was Clay Aiken.
- It is the only way to bring about a new age.
this is what my labia says.
Okay, go forth to the valley of the giants. It's just yonder we had yonder
okay. We have an old timey GPS that says yonder. That's funny. Now, write that
down. That is funny yonder. All right, so
yonder can you my
cubit
A cubits really short actually. Please proceed to the route. Go yonder.
Yonder. Open up your documents. Go yon.
They met with Errol Caining. Errol Caning? Rerouting. Go forth. Errol Caning,
right? Caning. They met with Errol Caning. The king said his thing and his
thing was to sing. Just kidding. He talked about kings, but not him the
king. A new kind of king, a baby king thing with an inch ding a long
pinging his bing.
The son of Santa, king of kings,
king of Christmas, the toys he'll bring.
- I want a ball!
- I want a doll.
- The gall!
These magi were smitten with toys and fun,
but no toys will be had without a journey begun.
Through the valley of giants, down the river,
across the sea, through many a trial,
then a mountain so steep, but from there,
the North Pole, where the young king we hope sleeps.
- Have you guys ever gone to third base?
- It's like...
Yes, I'm a I've had many women in my time. I'm old. That's awesome.
Never been to third base. You the women of candy kingdom would make your eyes
pop out of your head. They're gorgeous. Oh,
even now, as an old geezer, I can't help but I want to see a candy, but
what can this but we don't have but
I prove it to us. I turn around. I got no, but he doesn't. I go right on my
God, imagine what that woman would look like with no but this is what I was
inside came before. When I shit it, it came out of my mouth. Do the girls have
just one hole? Yeah, oh God, it's cool. We'll out the GPS and the kingdom for
us. First base is touching the hole. What second base? Oh, like
holding hands.
third, I guess eating each other is the only one fourth base, but the home run
you guys to
you blow my mind
they have a triangle baseball
in candy kingdom. You come to this realization, you come up on the valley
of the giants, you're like one and you see that the valley of the giants isn't
Valley of the Giants no more. You see the giants are laid dead in the ground,
almost all of them. Oh my god I want to see a giant woman's butt!
She's there, she's dead. There's only one giant left. And his name is poor
Goliath and he's being tormented by these tiny little Davids. Goliath is
he's going like me somebody help me and all the David's going.
Well, normally I'd be on the side of the Davids, but I guess on this eve, I will
destroy them. What are you guys going to do?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, I'll run guys as the master tactician. I've I've crushed
them countless nation states in the candy wars that I've ground infants
my boot. I know how to approach a situation like this. The clear situation is to pick
the side that's winning and side with them.
Okay, so which side would that be?
There's more of the little guys, so why not choose their side?
Look, I don't care how long as long as I get delayed.
And we're a little anyway. I mean, Pikachu here's 5'2".
Okay, alright, we'll be on the side of the... he dances. We'll be on the side of the Davids
then. Alright, I would like to attack Goliath.
Okay, cool. Roll initiative. All three of you, roll initiative.
Fuck me, man. A fucking Nat 29.
- Seven. - Nat 20.
- Nat 20, y'all. - Got a nine, dude.
- Nat 20, y'all. - Nat 20, y'all.
- Nat 20, y'all. Nat, Nat 20, y'all.
- That could be a good song. - 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, y'all.
- 10, 10, 10, 10, plus 20, y'all. - What'd you get? Sorry, one?
- Asshole. A nine. - I was actually asking.
- Oh, what'd you get? A one? - I'm sorry.
And what did you get Pikachu?
Seven.
Yeah, it's lower.
Wait, seven plus six.
Which would be?
For initiative, yeah, thirteen.
Don't make him do it.
Don't bail him out, Patches.
No, I know it's thirteen, because six plus six is twelve plus one.
Bitch.
A little peek behind the curtain.
Piece of shit.
Alright, M&M.
Remember the M&M.
Okay, I'm doing it this time.
This time it's going to work.
you're getting up in his mouth. You're going to get he's huge. He could
swallow me. I'm a normal size. I'm an to him. I imagine yeah he does not
resist. Okay, I'm in there. Yeah, he's well, you know, I mean yeah, yeah, I
keep getting there.
It's going to be a problem. Okay, I'm in there. All right, you're in there.
So
again, you guys hear me just make that speech about how we should fight and
kill this guy and I just climb into his mouth. I was crawling up his body like a
spider. Fuck yeah,
I'm just go. You just he's gone sexual. See the Davids and they're like they're
that guy's a freak and they started out. They like him yeah, I like they see my
I speak out of a certain ego. I go, you know it
what he sold what we're doing is going to be a legal okay in the Bible. One of
the Davids did manage to hit the Goliath and he got wow damn he got a ten damn
okay. So he just goes up to the Goliath kicking his Goliath like oh my shins. Oh
we are we are we is this David's like yeah, fuck you yeah and starts kicking
him in the show. I is such a bitch. Yeah, yeah, I think we sided with the right
people. Real shit. You get your up
what I'm gonna do. I mean, I saw I saw him go down his throat and I've never
seen him go down to like a
I've never seen him get eaten by somebody that was like proportionate to
his size and it unlocks something in me and I have to sit down.
Jesus, give your turn. You will do anything to avoid using these abilities
you've been given. But what happens... That's good, I really nagged him that
time, is... Let me guess, it's a made up attack that's not on your cheek? No,
there's... My cheeks shoot out a thunder wave.
You don't have a thunder wave. He does have a thunder wave. Oh, you do. I
paralyze everybody around me.
Or actually, just the Goliath. They beat it. The Goliath does resist it.
Ah, damn it.
Back to drawing.
(laughter)
- If Goliath resists it, then...
- What do I even do in this scenario?
- You can just move.
- Move your turns over.
- Yeah, but, okay, then I roll around in the sand.
(laughter)
- Sand in the valley.
- I try to get rid of my boner by--
- From the dead Goliath woman?
- No, no, from him going down the Goliath's throat.
- Oh.
- Because it unlocks something in me.
- Yeah, I got that.
- I didn't.
like you guys don't frequent rule thirty four. I not so much I roll there.
We're on a hill right
it's a battle. We crested okay, then I run to the top of the valley. I like a
sardine and then I roll all the way down
to get rid of the boner yeah and you go
different kind of is really right. I'm not is really I'm a Pikachu. You're
it was a character that was is really I never said it as his homeland. I
was saying what's going on. Okay, it was in zero. It was a throwaway joke in
the last campaign. It doesn't have to stay.
Well, you're stuck with it. All right, fine, then I eat tabouli and I eat
hummus and I and that's all you do. Harold, what's up? I would like to
it's really my only thing. Well,
Is Goliath, would you say that he is rapidly running back and forth anywhere?
He could be goaded into doing that.
He could be goaded.
Is he aggressive? Is he chasing the people attacking him?
Yeah, I feel like we should have.
Or has he fully thought about that before?
No, he's going like, "Ooooh!"
He could be goaded.
He could be goaded and we should have maybe allied.
There'll be other times where that move will be used.
Alright, I'm going to do the icicle attack again then.
Alright, go for it.
Thirteen.
Yeah, thirteen total? You added it in two?
Yeah.
yeah, that doesn't hit well. I'm going to take a break. Okay, all right, it's
back to me. Sorry, go live stern. Oh, goliath is going to try to start
smashing the Davids around him.
He does a terrible job. We pick the right side. Everything is such an idiot.
How many? How many Davids are there? How many Davids? Yes, there are three
Davids right now, beating him up. There's only three. I thought there was
way more and it's the only reason I thought there was like twenty. Yeah,
It's the only reason I chose...
There are other Davids around.
There's three right now fighting him.
Three David crosses.
Yeah.
They're telling him that this war in the Middle East is fucked up and bullshit.
George Bush is a cunt.
Yeah.
That is the kind of thing he says.
He smashes two of the three Davids to smithereens.
What?
So there's just one David?
There will be two more coming in.
Okay.
Oh, okay.
You guys are scaring me.
Endless vibes.
could have been goaded and we should have. All right. Is it my turn? Okay.
Candy punch
10. Okay. Does not hit getting not so good rolls. Yeah. Oh, that's my turn.
I'm still just in there. Oh, I guess I have to take damage. Yeah. Take two
damage.
Now it is David's turn.
So two of them show up so they don't do anything just yet. They just show up.
So one of them tries to attack seven. He misses.
Thanks for reading. It was your eyes were over there. Yeah, it's a good point.
You're well your turn. So, okay. So now that there's sand all over my penis,
always in a different, just like a different game. Huh? Keep going.
All over my penis. I've become enraged and I shoot a light,
a thunderbolt at the Goliath immediately. Go for it. Yeah.
Because I'm mad that the, the sand on your penis. Yeah.
that sucks into my penis.
Oh,
that was that was for people not watching the video playing on the edge.
You can roll that on probably could have been an inch of room on the table
that he not fully rolled the entire thing on pretty crazy. The least the
dice has ever a die is removed. That's like it. That was like a genuine role
with that was God's hand. I was crazy putting it. I was about I was supposed
to roll that Thunderbolt. That was real.
Wow. Yeah, roll to D ten
Which one? Almost man. It is this one.
No, it's the one with the nine on it. Yes. Yes.
Okay. 44. That's pretty cool.
So that's eight plus two. So that's 10 damage. Um, and uh, yeah,
it was pretty good. That Goliath was like,
Oh that Goliath.
Cause he's in his mouth. No, no. Why would you bring that up? He's chilling.
No, I thought about that. I was like, I was like, I'm already,
I already gave him some DOT, he doesn't need to have damage also from that.
Unless it's too...
They all standing my penis because of what?
I saw you eat him, my friend.
Bitch.
Goliath is not looking good, by the way.
Okay.
And you're not even looking good.
It is Harold's turn, yes.
All right.
I am going to...
I don't know.
I'm hoping this gives me some kind of advantage.
I know about Goliath.
Not my character, but me as a person.
Yeah.
And Goliath has a weak-ass forehead.
his forehead, one single rock can kill this animal. It's an overactive
pituitary gland is what they say. It must be some kind of third eye
abomination. So I am going to specifically target his forehead. Hey,
okay, I'll give you Bible points.
Reroll it anyway. Thank God. Yeah. Okay, good. Oh yeah. Wow. That no,
leave that dice on the floor. That is, that's a
dice.
eliminate the natural one dice out of the look at
twenty not net twenty but blame me anymore.
Thirty twenty think about yeah. All right yeah that's a that's
that's for sure a hit.
Okay roll God roll five D sixes like five
D sixes. That is one D eight plus three.
But OK. No because you're doing the stone to his
forehead. You are so right. You're doing the Jesus move.
I need book. Jesus didn't do that.
A book. It was David. It was David.
I'm stealing people's dice.
You're gonna blow a lot of David's minds right now.
Five, one, that's six, 16, 18.
Yeah, describe your biblical killing.
Damn.
I take out my ice slingshot or... He didn't use a slingshot, did he?
Yeah. He used a sling.
It was a sling.
It's called a sling.
So it's like a...
I take out my ice sling that I have and I roll it around plenty of times.
And I shoot an ice sickle at maximum speed over 10 miles an hour directly at
his forehead. And I hit it and he shatters into a million pieces. Yeah.
And out you come and now you come. It looks like you were. It looks like you
were wearing him. I'm having a nightmare. Wake up. Wake the fuck up. Come on.
Wake up, bitch. You see the Davids. They can't do you. That was amazing. We're
We're gonna start doing that.
Thank you.
You can't do it because you don't have any, there's no ice, right?
There's something called copulite, bitch, and you cannot steal his moles.
You can't just copy my attacks.
That's right.
Damn it.
Well we thank you for ridding us of the last giant.
Now we can do shit to their bodies.
What were we supposed to do in the Valley of Giants?
Go past it.
To the next area.
Okay, so we're going to go past you now.
Thank you so much.
I think the poem said, "Don't regard any moral."
In the Valley of Giants, you shall help the meek and feeble, was what I said.
So that's tough because...
So meek just like means small, right?
Meek means small, yeah.
Because it's like, "Meek, meek, meek, meek!"
Like a mouse!
Yeah, a mouse's sound is meek.
"Meek, meek, meek, meek, meek!"
But they were not as meek as the giant because the giant seemed shy.
What did he say?
Help the meek and evil?
Feeble, but they were feeble.
I'm pretty sure he said evil.
He said help them meet the feebles and they were actually bad.
Sorry, I only have one hole I hear out of my mouth.
You don't have ears?
I know, but yeah,
no room for you. He is why? Why did God give you eyebrows, but no ears?
Eyebrows are helpful to keep sand out of my eyes. I don't have eyelashes
because I'm not a girl.
We don't believe in evolution yet.
Wait and then I like
that is going to lock your world in two thousand and eight. Where would the
There's gonna be a man called Bill Maher who will walk your world.
So you guys, 2008 is what your fixated on.
Well, they do list.
And so you guys move past, you guys don't even have to take this out for this one.
You guys don't have any lines in this one.
Oh, okay.
Fuck you.
The trial of the giants was hard fought and won.
Who knew freaks so tiny could be such bums?
You know that they're evil, five seven or smaller.
We were supposed to kill the Davids.
It's fine.
just look at women who tend to be shorter
Latinos, Italians, Spaniards are these and don't get me started on the God
damn Chinese, with their big bushy tails and ears so long they trample my garden
while hopping along. You're thinking of rabbits man. Oh shit,
you're really thinking of rap or squirrels. Maybe yeah, that line big
bushy. You know, let me
rabbits have bushy tails, God damn, you have a not big ones. It doesn't
these, though,
But back to the journey of the three wise men,
- Aries, those goddamn Aries. - Cones, Cones.
- Who now reach a river with a curious bend.
Wide and rushing and luscious can be,
how will they go down it?
Oh, we shall see.
- We swam.
- Wait a minute. - There's a riddle.
They said it was a riddle, the river riddle.
I remember. - We make it a loft.
- 'Cause I was excited for the riddle.
- The edge of the river,
where you see an old hobbled man
with a sort of a nasty robe,
kind of tab I knock him out on his I just pick up Pikachu chill. I pick up the
first rock I see and I chill the fuck out. I
old man's I create an ice old man's head and I turn him into a raft. No, I
block it with ice. You block it with ice. Yes, I want to see what he has
planned here. Pikachu. Let's hear what he has to say and look closely at his
body. So now you're talking.
I want to look at this sinewy bobby.
And so this man introduces himself to you guys as Noah.
Alright, I pick up the rock again.
And he says, "I have a problem, if you can help me."
His plate's too weak.
Damn!
No, I'm kidding Noah.
unless I got by his way, he says you see here. I have a chicken, a fox and a
bag of grain and I have to bring these over across the river. Wait a minute, I
know this one, but if I leave the fox with the chicken, not this man, the fox
will eat the chicken, but if I take the chicken with the grain and leave them
there, the chicken will eat the grain. Okay, what do I do? I've heard this
turtle before and here's a question I have to ask you of course. Why do you
need a fox? I have one girl fox over there. I need to add this boy fox to my
arc.
What then?
Oh,
I had one trip and I grabbed the chicken. You said you know this one. I know this
one, but I also have been cook on it. I have a trump card,
which is patches, weak as plate patches, had a weak plate. It thinks that was not
Thanksgiving. I filled it out after and I will give me this
camera. Give me this one over here. Don't don't don't the me
camera. It was weak at the time. I then filled it out after I
just wanted to try a couple things. You don't have to do
the riddle because that plate was this guy's eating crumbs
for Thanksgiving. I only ate crumbs. You would expect if you
got tricked into having a weak ass plate that you would have
ate and some of it. Noah, I'm sorry. You were being you. Noah,
but you are Noah right now and you had a weak plate. It was very now we are
playing, we are doing the shame ray at you.
Okay, here's my solution. Here's my proposed solution. Well, Pat said he
knows the answer to the world. I do know. Wait, wait, wait. Okay, so it's
you bring over
it's you have the grain,
you can only bring one at a time, right? That's correct. It's a classic riddle.
Uh huh.
Oh, fuck. I saw this. Wait, and the fox is gonna eat the grain? I literally
solve this. The chicken needs the grain. Oh, then just bring over Fox grain
chicken. No, the chicken needs the grain. The chicken eats the grain. The fox is
going to start with the chicken. Okay, that's the only possible start. You
start with the chicken because the fox doesn't eat the grain, but the fox is
going to eat the chicken. No, start with the chicken. You know, you bring the
chicken over and then the fox and the you and then you bring one and you come
back with it. You come back with it. Exactly. So yeah, you bring the chicken
across and then you either bring the fox to the grain, but then you also take one
back when you come back, but I don't remember what, but I know that's what
the key is. What you bring
so
yep, time to draw. I just have to think about this. So you start and you need
to like if that's the river bro. This is literally okay. I know that for a fact
that patches saw this on the tick tock game. I don't play. There's a tick tock
game. There's a tick tock game. Forty years old. I don't have never on. I
thought that the weak ass plate would have knolled all of this.
I mean shut me up. I'll give you that way up, which I actually just feel bad about
way. I got it guys. I know how I thought that I thought that I would have some
other world. If you can fit more, how many things can you fit on the boat at
one time? One can only fit one thing in a guy. Okay, one grain, the guy, well,
the guy who's bringing the thing Fox chicken. So you bring the chicken over.
Okay, what should we bring next guys? Wait, so we bring the chicken over first.
Why'd you draw? Well, this look, I just realized this is easy. This is how we
you can yeah, but the you you I know I was saying I
thought you had a solution. I don't have a solution. I know with a step off. You
can't Google the solution man, all three of your role perception with
disadvantage. Okay, bitch,
that's a seven. I mean, our all my God, I got a
reception is brain yeah, it's owl owl yeah, then I got a seven. I got a
eighteen. Is that your low one advantage? They are low, oh disadvantage
Yeah. Okay. Wow. Wow.
So while you guys are puzzling over the riddle, riddle, riddle, if you,
if you solved it, I would have let you solve it.
I will solve it right now. Oh, it's just a actual Tick Tock game.
This is dope. Oh, wait, wait, wait. We'll eat sheep. Hold on. Oh my God.
To restart. You bring the Fox over. No, you bring the sheep over first.
Yeah. It's we bring the sheep over first.
I have a feeling the comments will cook us on this one. Yeah.
They're going to hate. I just solved it guys. No. Why would you bring, wait,
Wait, wait, wait, I just solved it. I just solved it. I literally just solved it.
Look, look, look, look. Bring the chicken over first.
OK, then you bring the fox over and you take the chicken back.
There you go. Then you bring the grain.
Then you come back and bring the chicken.
That's what it was. There we go.
Well, that's what it was.
You did solve it and you solve it for Noah and he's thankful.
But he also says on Thanksgiving that you are over on the other side of the river.
Now you two can solve it.
He said, now we need it. Now we need to do it with us.
I get to be the chicken.
and that why I'm an M and M, so I know I was to the food chain. I think Noah
says now my gorillas and two gorillas. Oh God, come on. We helped him grab
this M and M me who brought over and solve the riddle. I'm going to wait is
Noah in the water.
Noah is not in the war. Noah's on the other side of the river with a jump
across the river, the two M and M. Sorry, the two gorillas, though you might
I recognize them as Cain and Abel wearing gorilla outfits.
Oh shit, we should have killed him.
Wait, we should let them go on the ark so they have to have sex with each other.
That's his brother.
No, don't!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
These are two brothers, they're not real gorillas.
What?
Yeah, look at them.
Put them on the, put them on the boat.
You don't even have gorillas in this part of the world.
I pull off their gorilla masks.
Put them on the boat, I have an idea.
Why would the old god betray me like this?
No, we're trying to help you.
Please, don't!
wait a minute put the gorillas on their boat in them with it. Yeah,
we're one that we used to cross the way. I'll just go ahead and put the
gorillas on the boat. Okay, he does that tell them to go on the boat. I
guess go on the boat. Why don't you? Why do I have to do it? We put the
gorillas on the boat because I have an amazing idea. We'll just tell them
to go on the boat. Okay, you tell me to put them on the boat. He's three
feet tall. Gorilla. If the gorillas go on the boat in the middle of the
say something good will happen. They're not going to do it. If there's
nothing that may be a maybe
not maybe there will be there will definitely be an amazing roll talking
that is a seventeen. They go pretty good yeah, yeah, your perception being able
to notice the gorillas and unmask them and your solid charisma check. They're
like all right, we're sorry, Noah, we're sorry, all right, so they're in the
they're in the river. They get in the boat, yeah, the in the boat and they're
the water. I shoot a lightning bolt into the river.
Okay, roll attack roll.
They're in a boat.
What's a boat made out of? Metal?
Mm-hmm.
Really?
Oh yeah!
Oh.
Fuck that!
Nine.
That was pretty good. That was a pretty good idea. It did not work though.
But I kill every single fish around.
You kill all the fish that come up.
Sentence movie.
And then you hear a rumbling in the back and Noah goes, "My ark! No!" And you hear a "krrk
as the whole arc way in the back of the woods by the river explodes.
You see two by two animals running out.
Wait, because of the electricity?
Wait, I thought this was your arc.
Explodes in the back.
Beefly animals!
No, this was just to get into the arc.
I'm sorry I tried to kidnap you.
I thought the old god was nice.
Beefly all the animals.
He thought the old god was nice.
Wait, why did you even try to kidnap me?
Is there a female M&M on the arc?
Well, and before he could say it,
he gets squished. Okay, thank God.
I don't want a female in a male. And you do get eaten once again,
but this time by a lonely whale. It's all three of you. Jonah.
The story of Jonah. Jonah was a prophet, ooh, ooh, but he really never
got it. Sad but true. But this time, the whale gets it. He gets you
three and you go down the gosh darn river, and you're whooshing down,
and you're rocking around inside the whale. What? Was it a freshwater whale?
from the art could swim up. He had a tank in the I would like to
call on the pirates who don't do anything
yeah. They still don't do anything like the story God damn it. They just
throw him overboard and so he you're going down this river and then you
suddenly feel a drop in your stomach waterfall. You fall all the way down
this massive waterfall, the end of the river to the sea and boom you hit it
and you knock out. That'd be a good theme park right. Is there any
Christian theme parks that do Jonah inside there should be there is a
whale's mouth.
Ken
Russell, no there's this case this this Australian fella Ken something can down
and no he has a Tennessee can see and with a whole have a one to one version
of Noah's Ark. That sounds awesome. It's really silly. It does sound really
cool. I have an all night over money. Yeah, so you guys as you come to
We pull up our poem.
Yeah, I come too.
Wassup?
You came too?
I came too.
You came second?
Into the maw of the great big whale.
Oh, what has happened?
It's so dark I need braille.
How will we make it to the North Pole now?
Inside of a whale, the biggest of cows.
Oh, not so fast, another voice did say.
You're staying right here and dying today.
And out came a man, handsome and strong, with his five lion wives.
It was Daniel the Wrong.
What's up Daniel?
I know you hitting all that.
I know you hitting all that Daniel.
What's up?
These are all my wives.
What's up baby?
Yeah.
All right.
What's up?
Okay, maybe I didn't spare you guys.
These guys are pretty cool.
Yeah, what's up baby?
Watch this.
Hey baby!
Yeah, hey baby.
Baby!
Okay, what's up?
Okay, I'm going to try this.
Oh no, once you get this move.
- What's up? - Evolution of dance!
- I like the way your wives look, baby! - What's up, Daniel?
Let me get at them!
The old guy had said you guys need to die, but...
What's up, Daniel?
Maybe I'm wrong. This guy's got really cool moves and attitude.
- (laughing) - He just Superman'd that hoe.
Holy shit.
Daniel, check that out. Show your wives that, they're gonna fuck you.
Daniel Tiger.
He's a bit.
Oh my God.
Daniel Lyon.
Daniel Lyon, I think.
Lead singer of the
The Evil of Amn Themes song.
Oh, that's true.
So, convince me.
Why should I spare your friends?
I just showed you everything.
Oh gosh, why should I spare your friends?
I'm just like him.
Well, he's a little-
We're basically three of the same guy.
We have to go to Santa's kid and I have to give him Axe Dark Temptation.
No, don't tell him that.
This is the old-
Wait a minute. I give him a little I give him a smooch a spray on the
smell. This guy loves testers. He gets one of his lion wives to smell it and
she goes like that's pretty good. Women love that. Women love
make her smell me. He's made of chocolate.
I want her to smell me. No wait wait.
She cannot resist. She eats you. God fucking damn you dumb ass. Dumb piece
I had this in the bag.
He was literally carrying us for the first time ever.
And you jump in the bitch's mouth.
I'm playing my character.
Okay. So one of your friends is gone.
Now we get rid of this elf.
No, he's gonna be back.
What? How do you mean?
He always comes back whenever he gets in.
Your wife is dead.
I look at his wife and I say,
"You are not skinny. You shall throw up."
(growls)
Roll talking with advantage
with advantage 'cause you sound just like Daniel.
(ball bouncing)
Oh my God! Nat 20.
Nat 20.
All three, all five of his lion wives start vomiting.
(laughing)
That's his second nat 20,
and both times it has not rolled, but bounced, guys.
It's pretty impressive.
Something is up with you today.
Yeah, you come spilling out.
(sighing)
What's your wife like that, though?
I guess I do want my wives to be skinnier.
You make a good point.
And he's just an elf.
- If you can't eat elves, cause of Santa.
- Who's Santa?
- God.
- Nobody.
Actually we don't know yet.
- Actually we don't really know.
We saw a star on this guy.
- We hate Santa.
- Wait a minute, can you make the-
- We like the old God, not the new.
- We like the old God, yeah.
- But the new one, there isn't even a new one.
- There is a new one.
We just call him God.
- You know what I like is sex.
What's up, Danielle?
- Okay.
- I like sex too.
stepping in between the two of them.
I'm hobbling over with my cane.
You know what? I was going to kill you guys, but you seem pretty cool.
You make my wife skinnier
with your meanness, so I don't take the heat.
It's a pretty good idea.
How about this? You come here every once in a while.
You tell my wives they're fat, so they get skinny.
All right. What's up?
OK, Borat. And then he yanks on the whale's uvula.
And all three of you shoot out of the whale's blowhole.
Huh. I wouldn't figure that's how that works.
Into the next part of the poem.
Woosh! The wise men did fly out the blowhole,
and thank goodness they did, for that was their goal.
They went 'cross the sea, while inside that beast...
How lucky is that? I thought we'd be feast!
I think you'll be on food.
I find that rude!
Settle down, fellas. Chill with the 'tude.
Dude, we're now at the mountain, there's more traveling to do.
(laughing)
- The weather was colder, the North Pole grew near,
shivering, freezing from tip top to rear.
In front was a mountain so high in the sky,
the thought did occur we wish we could fly.
But the Magi are wise, crafty and shrewd.
No matter the task, they'll sure make it through.
The newborn son of Santa is finally near,
and once they do reach him, Christmas be here.
And so you guys are at the--
- Could've said is.
- I was feeling piratey, I don't know.
So you guys reached the foot of the mountain.
Hmmmm.
So we're getting back to, I'm from the North Pole, but I'm back home.
I know why I'm climbing all that shit, bitch.
Well, I'm sure I have some kind of knowledge about how to traverse this kind of terrain.
I would say you do, yeah.
So, I'm going to start, well first you set some anchors.
Wait a minute, are those sluts behind the mountain?
There's tons of sluts all over the North Pole.
Sluts?
Yep, sluts all over the North Pole.
Can you play just like a Scooby Doo run sound?
Just like, do do do do do do do.
know
Batman transition sound. Yes, that kind of works. Well, we don't have that
either to do a scooby thing. I mean I can give you this. I can give you this
okay. Does that work? So that works fine. My eyes bulge out of my head and I
turn to you. I turn to you. I was like why don't they have slots be on the
mountain? Tens of slots
That works. That works.
Yes, I'm going to start throwing anchors into this mountain and we're going to
start climbing this bit. Yeah, roll survival, which oh shit, that's owl with
advantage. Owl.
You just rolled a d4.
Oh, you did. 18.
Okay, six. Okay. And would you get with advantage? Yeah, all of you guys, all
you guys go with advantage.
Oh,
23 on the edge. 23. Wow. 23. 30, 20, 18 and 23. You guys scale
all this mountain with fucking ease. This is not there. Sluts be on the
mountain and I ran like Scooby Doo. I had stuff. I had stuff. I'm over
clocking my body. I'm literally I'm literally erasing minutes off the end
of my life, which is you do the inception walk where they walk up
the street and up where it's right. You're remembering like a Normandy style
event. Like you had like a PTSD flashback. Then you run so fast. No
man. I'm thinking about sluts. I'm a horny old man. I think of I
legal honey. My holiness is rubbing off on these old man. Maybe you're thinking
about rubbing off on me. Oh, shit. He's dirty grandpa. Now I'm thinking of my
sisters, man. What the fuck? That's awesome.
In the candy kingdom, we're all brothers and sisters to
north to that's basically how it worked in the Bible for most of it. Yeah, it's
trick. Yeah, I love brothers.
Where you're from
- Pikachu, Pikachu!
- Oh yeah!
(laughing)
- Oh yeah, guess what's up?
- Wherever you're from.
- Which is where exactly?
What are the exact kind of boundaries?
- I am from--
- Longitude, longitude.
- I am from Chocoyellow's kingdom.
From the magic kingdom in Atlanta.
- You're from Atlanta?
- Atlanta.
- Oh, okay.
That actually makes a lot of things make sense here.
outfit is starting to click for me. It must be Sunday.
Yeah, right. I was gonna say. That was church. That was church, Pikachu.
Oh man. I like to hear- I'm just a white guy from Atlanta.
Yeah, and you're dressed up for church. You guys are white guys from Atlanta? I didn't say anything about race, man.
You fucking weirdo. Oh, I'm from Israel. Oh, I'm white. Shut up.
I may have stepped on some rakes. All
three of you roll perception with advantage for this amazing mountain scale.
You have amazing survival skills.
Perception is what?
Eighteen.
Twelve.
Sixteen.
Eighteen.
Okay.
You two.
Sorry.
You must be too focused on leading the way.
Thinking of my sisters getting so fucking horny.
You're thinking about fucking your sisters.
Drooling.
I'm melting the snow on the side of the mountain with my drool.
You two.
Am I, am I, did I'm okay?
You two, so what you two hear is a rumbling from up above and you see.
Is that you thinking about your sisters?
I think that might be my biggest sister.
Instead, it is Cain and Abel once again.
Oh, these fucking cliques.
But this time it's Cain and he's saying, "Avalanche!"
And he's hitting Cable up against a mountain.
Who's Cable?
- From X-Men. - That's you, man.
It's Wolverine's brother?
- No, he's Scott Summer's son. - I thought--
- I'm Caleb. - Oh.
- He's hitting Abel-- - I've known you for five years.
Six years, you--
His name's not Cable?
No, it's Caleb.
Calby?
bro, was your second guess. If you got the cable wrong,
I can't believe how irony poison I am to understand what Patrick just did. Yeah,
he literally just did a pose y'all and it was some kind of letterish
watch out guys. It's a candy lunch. It's a candy lunch of rocks. You to a
candy lunch made of ice
to
roll
deck saving throws with with advantage and I just fucking die. I guess I got a
20. That's ball. It was another bounce or save ball fucking dexterity with
advantage. You balance ball balance 12 man. Well, what'd you get advantage?
You said? Then I got a 24. I got a six. Both of them are six. That's adding
balance ball. Yeah. Oh, she is. Okay. I rolled a four twice.
Oh God. 12 damage for you to you take six. I got a 20. Yeah, but you still
stick half. That's fair. I'm at 12 HP. You guys. Okay, I'm gonna drink my help
potions that I bought that when nobody else seemed to buy anything for even
though I got a teddy bear, bitch.
You got a teddy bear. Okay, how much does it heal? 2D4+2. Okay, I'm gonna
just overhear. And as you're drinking the potions, you see Cain and Abel
scurry off once again, and in their place, a dark rumbling from above,
- Not an avalanche this time.
- It's the thing from Fantasia.
- You hear a familiar tune.
- You're a mean one, Mr. Grinch.
- What is up, Grinch?
What is up?
- It's the old god, the Dark Grinch.
- What is up, Dark Grinch?
- I'm going to take care of you once and for all.
There'll be no Christmas on my watch.
- Wait, I thought we were boys.
- No, I'm the old god.
- You're a piece of crap.
You're a piece of crap.
I wouldn't touch you with a ten-foot pole.
I would never touch you with my long, weird finger.
Y'all.
Well, the finger isn't that long and crap.
You can't touch me with that finger any day.
Green motherfucker.
I'm green.
You green bitch.
Yeah, you know, in the candy kingdom, we kill all the green candies.
Ooh, that's fucked up.
You kill the green M&M?
Anything green.
Don't you ever kill them again.
It's what we do.
We're racist.
This is a beautiful...
What?
racist. You guys roll initiative. It's time to final battle time to fight this
bitch against the old God, the Grinch,
sixteen, ten.
Oh, well, that's plus six. That's an eight.
Okay.
Grinch go first.
Grinch gonna use his Grinch powers. Grinch gonna Grinch. Grinch is gonna Grinch.
Grinch is gonna Grinch y'all. How many is your ACs? Mine is 15. 14. 14. Okay he beats all your ACs.
Well I'm gonna beat him up. He goes MWAH! HAHAHAHA! And he shoots out a Grinch ray from his hands.
I didn't come up with any. What the hell is a Grinch ray? It's like a green ray. It's a green ray you stink.
I think we have once in a while
With the sort of a thing because of the same name same name probably the same type of special problems
All right, and he does seven damage to all three of you. Well guys. I'm at 5 HP, okay
And now it is Harold's turn though
No, she is well. I think that I will do again my icicle attack go for it
Come on, please. I really need to get I'm really high number
15 that's oh yeah nice, and he needs to be a DC 10 for freezing
Oh, yeah, one d8 plus three. Where's the d8? Where did it go the blue one right? No? Yeah?
It's the one that's most triangle. That's a nine
Wow
some serious damage
And he does resist the freezing though.
Piece of shit.
You slice along his Grinch body.
"Ahh! My Grinch body!"
What color is his blood?
It's blue of course!
What the fuck?
What?
Why is it blue? The rest of you is green.
Green or like black?
It smells like fucking shit!
No, no it doesn't smell bad.
You should kill yourself.
No.
You should kill yourself because you smell fucking terrible.
That's the best idea I've heard all day.
like a fucking you smell like you smell like shit Grinch and you should kill
yourself. No one at school likes you. No one. I don't. I don't. They don't. You
should fucking kill yourself. I think you have to get to know me. I've knew
you said I'm not joking. Literally, it would make the world better if you
fucking killed yourself. You're eight years old and you have a beard.
Psychic. Come on, do it. Come on, jump off the mountain. Jump off the side of
at the mountain green bitch green mother. We call you guys green.
You all talk
my kingdom damn
net one mother fucker. It was a bouncer to I was so I have the resolve to live
more than ever. Fuck I won't let you bastard yourself. I will kill myself.
There will be no
Christmas. I don't even know what that is yet, but there will be none of it on
my watch. I do know I'm trying to stop it. I know that because I'm an old God. I
thought we don't need to hear all this bullshit. I was just by turn and I've
tripped myself up. It's not his turn. It is now M and M stern. Okay, should I try
to get eaten again? Guys, I think that you should you have any other abilities?
Yeah, I have plenty go out of order. I mean, I just have I just have attacks.
You should use the plenty then. Oh, I all I have is being eaten or attacked
to attack him. You know what I'll just straight up attack him, even though I
haven't hit a single attack this entire game.
Okay, that's an eighteen hit
that's seven damage. Nice. Yeah, you just run up to him. You start punch him in
the gut where he got sliced and get a blue blood on your white gloves. Whoa and
now it is like a blue and white tie dye Pikachu.
I choose you to go next to take your turn.
Man, it's all on the sheet. You're looking up at the sky.
I didn't get him to kill himself.
Your moves are on the sheet.
So maybe I should just shoot a lightning bolt at him. Or thunderbolt, sorry.
This is the thought process of many high school bullies.
So what I'm going to do is just shoot.
Maybe I should use my powers. He didn't seem bothered by my insults.
Up the mountain like that.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah. Make it hop. Make it hop.
Oh, fucker. I've hit too many good rolls.
Yeah, you spent them.
You spent them on some cool stuff, though.
Law of averages, man.
Pretty good rolls.
It's true.
Karmic Dice.
Karmic Dice turned on.
Karmic Dice is turned on for you.
Your lightning bolts hop over the mountains, and they go past the Grinch. It is his turn
again. And he's going to now...
He's going to attack me for telling me to kill him.
Oh, yeah, he is. He's going to stick his long finger out. Roll a Dexterity saving throw,
Pat.
These be a good bounce.
Oh, my Christ!
Christ you tainted your die man tainted that shit in that ronnie's tooth the critical one. Oh, you're reset wait. You're actually reset
Yeah, you're back to zero. Oh, yeah, anything could happen now your finger goes wraps around your throat you take I like this actually
This is what that I pay women to do take for damage and you're gonna be around
It's gonna be around your throat for a while. I pay women to do this to me. So now you are gay
Now you are gay. I'm not gay. Well then why are you strangling another man?
Why are you strangling another man who derives pleasure from it?
The Grinch is definitely gay. That's why he lives in a separate place.
Yeah. He's been cast out by the Whos. It's a homophobic story.
What do you mean by Greenies? It's an allegory. No, this is separate from my character.
This is something that Seuss baked in. He's fine with gay Grinches.
Everybody's gay in my world. In Candyland? Yeah.
Candyland's on the-- It's called Candyland.
That's why they killed the greenies.
Candy-ass land.
Yeah.
You're up, though, by the way, Candyman.
Okay.
Oh, no, you're not. I'm sorry. Elfman.
My carol, so I sing a song, give someone 1d6 of what?
Of like, they can add to an ability roll.
It's like Bardic Inspiration.
Oh, okay. All right.
I didn't know if that was health.
Yeah.
Well, I'm going to barely use any of my abilities.
It's a bonus action, too, so you can use it.
It's like Bardic Inspiration.
You can just use it as a bonus action.
So I'm going to do my slick sick.
What does that say?
Slick stick.
Slid side.
Slide sickle.
I'm going to use my slide sickle and I'm going to,
we're all up on the cliff now, yes?
I'm going to basically do a border around the cliff's edge.
Nice.
So that anytime that he's anywhere,
if we could somehow get him to the edge of this thing,
he may slip and fall.
Where his house is, yeah.
Yeah, so I'm gonna slide,
What do I have? Thirty feet of trail. I'm going to put a icy border on that.
Now boost my strength.
And I'm going to do the same thing.
What's a carol you're going to sing?
That's a good one, man.
This is how we do it.
I sing that one.
It's Christmas time.
Stockings on the wall in Santa's truck.
He has a truck in the truck. Really? He has a you have one D six. You can spend
a car and it's going in my truck. No. All right. Cool. It is now your turn, Eminem.
OK, you can try to push him or punch him into the ice or something to slip him,
slip off to slip off the. Yeah, I'm going to try and punch him into the ice
to slip all the way off. And I get to decide to add this after I roll it. Yeah.
Okay, okay, that's a thirteen. You're going to want to have yeah
fourteen. My inspiration. No, it's is that the only thing I could have rolled
that would yeah pretty much yeah. Oh, no, sorry.
We're going to my inspiration man. You're up Pikachu
Yeah, push him.
Push him over.
All right, then I'll do a quick attack in hopes that it's a push.
OK, I'll let you try it.
Fuck. So five.
Your quick attack misses.
It's getting the best of us.
The Grinch does another three damage to you.
I'm dead.
Oh, that was too much pleasure.
And he shoots his beam at the two of you.
Oh no, it's over.
Both of you guys roll d20.
Four nine.
I already assume it's balance ball.
Yeah, balance ball.
Nine.
Okay.
Oh, seven.
You both take nine damage.
I'm dead.
You both dead.
I'm still alive.
I'm hanging on with two HP.
Cam, I have an idea for you.
You have to pray to new God.
Listen, listen, listen, listen, listen.
Pray to Santa.
The son of Santa.
What do we know about the Grinch?
Gray, green, stink.
You're getting closer.
He loves Christmas at the end of the month.
He's in the movie. He hates Christmas at first, but then he loves it, but then he
loves it. Heart. Guess what? Guess what's our? Yes. Guess what is on my
body right now? A teddy bear, a toy. He has never, ever gotten a gift. Oh my
god, teddy bear and pleased for the love of God. Give the Grinch. Give the
Grinch a fucking gift. I'm going to do. I want to live man. Yeah. Well, is it my
turn? Yeah. Okay. I'll be the only person who's left. I'd pick up the teddy
teddy bear. What are you doing get away? I don't know what I'm doing, but it
feels right
and I give him the teddy bear. I really slowly handed to him.
Thank you.
What is this feeling?
It's falling over and
it's called gravity.
Oh, I'll get you blue women him
my mortal enemy. Well played my friend. Sorry your teddy bears gone yeah that's
okay. He revives both of you and you guys continue to climb over the mountain
to the next part
of the poem
exhausted beyond measure, battered and bruised. The magi's journey was no
It's Santa! It's Santa! We must meet them both days!
Slow down for a moment! This ain't a race!
I agree. Quieting down, he sees the Magi arrive, bearing their gifts for the
son of this guy.
Ho, ho, ho!
Who are you three who've come to see me and my son? I'd like to bow and
get on one knee. Yeah, I'm also reverently bowing. I'm doing like I'm
being knighted. And I would say, "My name is Harold, and I don't know what
you are." I pledge my life to you and your son as well.
I'm looking for hot slots. Is there something written I'm supposed to be
nope? We just had amazing lines that you would have thought were written.
You thought those are written. That's how good we just do that out. I'm
looking for hot slots of any kind. Also, they have a gift for you.
Oh, please give them give those gifts to my son. I have to make a different
my all my other old man voices. Hold on. Okay, give those gifts to my
please. Oh, we do that. What gifts do you bring for him? You guys go first. I
bring a massage pad that you can put on a chair. Oh wow, so that baby can be
massaged before he has hair. That's a my rhyme damn my rhyme do I twist the
ax thing and I'm just
because when I
and I brought in my pocket. I have some chocolates that I
oh
what and guys the chocolates have been in my pocket this whole time. Oh, the
what happens to what happens to chocolates when they stay in your pocket
chocolate.
No, this is useless. I throw it on the ground and I stomp on it and I say,
but what else could I give? What other gift could I give that could be
associated with this day for years and years to come. Why I'm just an ancient
old man. I barely have anything to offer except for well, I suppose my cane and
guys, you're can't hand him my red and white
cane from the candy kingdom. Oh my fucking God, and I give it put it right
in the baby's mouth. Well done,
and that was my plan all along. Well done and the baby, the son of Santa
who could it be?
*imitates baby crying*
I knew it!
Throw him off the fucking cliff.
I hold the baby's nose open so it's mouth is wide and I just spray Axe all up inside.
Before you do, before you do that,
I rhyme.
The gift so touched Santa and the son of Santa
that the baby suddenly snaps into being.
And he says, "What if we had a day called Christmas
where everyone received presents and not just me
And it could be today, the day I was born, and that this happens.
Maybe, Dad, you could hire the elves who make all these toys,
and they could stay up with us in the North Pole instead of wherever they are now.
You could keep two lists, a gnarly list and a nice list.
Kids on the nice list should get to have presents that you give them based on what they ask for.
However, if a child is not good, they should be on the gnarly list, and you should give them coal instead.
You'll have to fly to every child's house and give them their present through the chimney.
You'll go down the chimney and sneak into a room where they'll have a tree that they put inside.
You put the presents under there, wrap the gift in gift wrap,
but you should also tell people who want presents to leave out milk and cookies
that way you get to eat something to eat when you're doing all that traveling.
You should get magic reindeer to fly you across the entire world
and pull you by a sled that goes in the sky, carry all the toys in a sack that sits next to you.
One of the reindeer is going to have a glowing red nose
and he will help lead the way when it is nighttime because it'll be dark
and that's what we should do, I think.
I'm getting atheist vibes from that.
Yeah, when you lay Christmas out like that, it seems so asinine.
It really does.
It's not what the plan was.
you seem like an a the is not what I was. I'm not trying to do an epic
Christmas. What kind of
a frog fly around the world? No, he was just describing what Christmas should be
and Santa. Here's this wonderful idea and he's so excited. He says, Thank you
son, bye bye and he tosses the sun away and we don't know where he ends up or
where he goes. Sullivan the frog is canonically the son of Santa and his
birth is Christmas. What the hell and he's that old.
he's in all our future. Wait a minute. I have an idea. I will be on the sun.
Oh, come here. You pervert. I am Santa's
and the end of the story. And so that's a story of the first Christmas day.
The three Magi who traveled without delay. Merry Christmas to all and to all
a good night. Christmas is now a thing for all night.
Christmas is now a thing. Okay, for all night for all night for all night.
Well, my friend, you are truly a warrior of Christmas for this.
All right, thanks everybody. One of the most. This is better than that
fucking movie with the BB gun. What's the Oh Christmas story? The worst movie
of all time. Good night, my friends. Good night. Merry Christmas, everybody.
Miss Drew.
Can't see it.
This is also from a little one.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, how sweet is that?
It seems like we've taken a lot of these are a lot from kids.
Yeah, it's weird that we didn't get that many adults in our literature.
It's kind of weird, right?
Yeah, I feel like mostly kids.
I guess it makes sense.
This is from Little Ben.
Oh, okay.
Hello, Santa.
This year, the only thing I want for Christmas is world peace.
Oh my god, that's so cute.
War, disease, social disorder.
How could I sit here and wish for big red fire trucks
or super powered action figures
when some people are struggling
just to afford basic human needs?
What a smart little kid.
It would just be selfish.
And that's the problem with this world.
Selfishness.
Selfish corporate CEOs and money hungry politicians
hogging all the wealth up top
and leaving the little guy with nothing.
little bit all the way at the bottom. He's probably referring to himself or
his family as well. Is he related to Big Ben?
It could be a clock
all the way at the bottom. I just wish I could do something about it. You know
what, Santa? I finally decided what I want for Christmas. I want a voice.
I want a say in what direction the winds of change blow a say in the future that
I'm
Every border of this country will be protected by nuclear bombs and big red fire trucks.
To put an end to you illegally flying over the border, go back to your igloo, you disgusting
red snow pig.
Holy shit, Little Ben.
Little Ben, what the fuck?
I thought you were a little ass kid.
What a turn Little Ben has made.
I didn't know you were a grown man going by Little Ben.
I mean, his first name could be Little, I guess.
Little John.
Little John, yeah.
Little Richard.
Little Wayne.
Actually, there might be more Little Men than Little Hornets.
(Dog barks)