Last time on Gun City, a broad city, the Uncle's Falcon. The boys leveled up. Grinch hunter,
Blotoss Pist, tapped into the mystic powers of the Lorax and learned how to create an impeccable
disguise. Force user, Patrick Yoda, chose the path of the Jedi Counselor and learned how he
he can bring peace in a moment during combat.
Abomination Ray William Johnson chose the dark path of the Bazinga, gaining incredible strength
but at the cost of growing a little boy's haircut and becoming allergic to the sun.
Once they all met with Ray William Johnson's doctor, these hotshot detectives tried to sell
their friend Patrick Yoda into slavery to see if they could make 10 million dollars
off his strong Yoda body.
They murdered an innocent, which caused Sullivan the frog to freak the fuck out and bring them
to his cousin John Carlos, a greasy lowlife who was always looking for some of that techno
slime.
And after some tense negotiations, Giancarlo agreed to help the gang meet with the Mad
Suckler, who can help them get into Da Matrix too.
In exchange, they gave him some Primo Technoslime materials.
To what end will he use those?
Who knows?
He told the fellas to meet him back at the apartment at 10pm.
Afterwards, these Sherlocks tried once more to sell Patrick Yeo to the human traffickers.
an operation made up of three Ken bones and that woman from Matz's Inc.
They defeated the human traffickers, humiliating one of them to death, if I recall, and killed
enough time to head back to John Carlo's place and begin their trek to the mad sucklet himself.
That was it.
That's what happened.
That's what we call a filler episode.
Yeah, it was great.
Definitely a filler.
Wait, so okay, right off the bat, I want to I'm gonna want to talk to to I'm going to turn
to my companions and be like, "Hey guys, while I was going back and listening to my diary
in order to add sound effects and edit it of our adventure, kind of like two segments
of our adventure ago, I realized that maybe we should be a little suspicious of this Mommy
Goodlegs character, you know?
I was kind of thinking about it when I was listening to my diary.
Why?
Well, see, Sean McAlee, right?
His whole thing was he was trying to turn all the clubs into the Matrix 2 virtual clubs,
right?
And that would put Mommy Good Legs right out of a job.
So I just wanted to throw that into the mix because I completely forgot about it until
I was listening to my diary and adding fighting sound effects and music to the beginning and
end of it.
Me too.
Also, what room are we in right now?
Don't know what you're talking about.
Okay.
Okay, so a couple of things.
First, reminders, 'cause I try to do reminders now.
Ray William Johnson,
you have two Techno Slime addiction points
because you failed,
'cause I was also listening to Blow Toss Piss' Diary
and I realized that you did fail once in that session
and that's why you went on a weird sort of odyssey
on the highway.
And then you also drank raw Techno Slime,
which counted as an auto failure.
So if you fail one more time,
you're gonna start hallucinating every time
you take techno slime.
- That sounds really fun.
- And being paranoid and attacking everyone.
It will be fun.
Blowtoss Piss, you have a monkey.
I have that in there to remind you of your session.
- I remember the monkey.
- Okay.
Otherwise, yeah, Patrick Yoda,
I think you've taken, I think, the most damage.
What's the other thing?
Is it you've taken the most damage?
I think you and Blowtoss-- - Congrats, buddy.
So just to be on the lookout for that.
Um, I'm doing great.
I think you're actually lying about that.
Okay.
Don't, no, please.
I've scored the, I've scored the most high score points.
So no, I, I got a slam dunk.
It's true.
Ray William Johnson got a slam dunk last session.
I don't know if you guys noticed.
Yeah.
Recap.
I got a slam dunk.
And Ray William Johnson, of course, got a slam dunk.
There we go.
You could just put that.
It's a clean take.
- Put that in wherever you want to, yeah.
Just overlapping over something else.
And yeah, so where you guys are, which is a good call.
I would say that you are right now
in the human traffickers office
after murdering all of them.
And you guys, it's 10 p.m., so you can go back to--
- So we just hung out there for a few hours
after we killed them.
- Oh wait, yeah, it's 10 o'clock, we have to meet up.
- Yeah. - With Giancarlo, right?
- Mm-hmm. - Brad and him.
the
So yeah, you guys walk outside and go back across the street, head back to John Carlos
apartment building.
That addict woman who was smoking outside of it is dead now and you walk upstairs to
his apartment.
I spit on her.
Okay, cool.
Yeah.
And you look awesome.
I guess he, you know what, I sort of began the wanton cruelty and you just sort of added
the layer.
So it's not, I can't really blame you.
you walk up the stairs to his apartment and uh... the four of you including
solvent knock on the door
uh... solvent says john carlo we're back
and john carlos is good took you long enough
uh...
newton uh... so what do you feel is one of the local fucked up to get to a
scrape so i saw it
i'm fine
uh... are you guys trying to lie about that
we we've got a lot of uh... uh... chair
I guess all of you rolled deception, whatever.
Like...
That's an 18.
Yeah, okay.
Hold on.
Pat got a 5.
How?
I love it.
Okay, so, um, wait, what did you... you said no.
So he believes you didn't get into a fight.
What did you say, Patrick Yoda?
I don't remember.
He said, "I'm okay."
I think he said, "I'm okay."
Okay, so he's for sure... he knows you're not okay.
I don't remember.
for sure he knows you're not okay. Caleb he thinks you might have fallen off a
chair. He's not entirely sure if he believes you there. He's like okay yeah
that's like the result of that. Okay yeah anyway I could take you guys to the
Mad Sockler. You should be expecting my arrival around the next half hour so I
told him I have an interesting crew I'm bringing in. He seems intrigued. Now I
I know my cousin over here can be a real square,
and so I need to know that you detectives won't act like fucking knocks in there.
Especially after I incinerated that body for you. No questions asked.
What do we have to do
for you or to you?
Please do nothing to me. I will do anything.
And I mean anything.
Is this
anything?
Anything.
(laughs)
- All right, well, and he sort of,
you'd get a ping on your PSP and it's his number.
And he's like, "Well, anyway, so let's just go."
(laughs)
- Yeah, so you guys walk down the block
through the slums of Gun City or Guns Titty.
And you see all manner of low-lifing scumbags on the way.
Hardworking folks just trying to get by, not here.
this is the part of the slums where people deserve to be poor
as you walk through the dark winding neon alleys you come across a featureless
black door
john carlos stops
returns around
i need you all to close your eyes or or turnaround or something sorry i i just
can have you knowing how to get it here
uh... abracadabra
but ran up in the door
there's nothing happened i'd not yet
all incessantly i'd i'd say i think warmer
uh... says to me open
do like starts to open the distance and goes on the better of it
as i i cover my eyes
but i but i i unzip the pocket where
patrick the monkey is on my jacket
okay i think i'm going to be really peak out
- All right, do a sleight of hand check on that.
- All right. - Yeah.
- 12.
- Okay, let me see if he notices.
'Cause that's gonna be contested for sure.
Oof, yeah, he notices.
Hey, hey, put that guy away.
Patrick, you see Patrick in the mirror.
(imitates monkey)
- The monkey's, he's blind.
(laughing)
I can vouch for that, he is blind.
- Roll deception.
Okay, roll the straight,
I was gonna say with disadvantage,
but he's sort of helping you out.
So just roll straight deception.
- I, he's blind. - 19.
- Oh great, I got a crit. - Oh no, that's a crit.
- You got a crit.
(laughing)
- Yeah, you see, John Carl was like,
"Oh my God, I'm so sorry, I had no idea."
(laughing)
That your monkey was blind.
- That's okay.
It's a really big issue in today's society.
People just assume that monkeys can see,
and you know, it's something that I've been trying
to raise awareness of, so I'm glad you're so receptive.
- No, if you have any organization
or anything you want me to donate to,
I will do it right now.
Yeah, if you give me like 50 bucks, I can go bring it to the Blind Monkey Foundation.
25.
30.
Okay, he hands you $30.
That's your inventory.
Yes.
I look him directly in the eyes and I say, "I am also blind."
is
also turn around or do you try to also peek? I can't use Yoda's mind
just to hear the password to the door. Turn around!
Okay, you can do whatever you want. That's fine. Yeah, okay, and Sullivan puts his hands over
his eyes. And so, the door, you hear some strange noises, it's like the door is
unfurling. It almost sounds like, doesn't sound like a mechanical thing at all.
It doesn't even sound like a cyber thing. It sounds sort of like something writhing.
and then at that he says okay you guys can open your eyes and blow toss you
look at your monkey and he is just white as a ghost did you fuck the door no no
is that the secret code and here I'll try and then I try to fuck the door
Uh, nothing happens. Nothing happens.
Well, I'm havin- I am-
It feels nice.
Well actually, wait. How do you try- How do you try to fuck the door?
I try to fuck the- the
space between the bottom of the door and the ground.
Okay, nothing happens.
Oh, well, I cum.
Your cum's just on the ground.
Well, boys.
You walk into this place,
and you're just not in it.
Yeah.
Where's- Yeah, I did.
the
because I don't know how to speak monkey. You do. You read the mind of the monkey.
Mm-hmm. So the mind would translate automatically? Just because that happened
in the first gun city so now it's like I guess that I have to allow. Oh I okay I
read the monkeys mind? You read the monkeys mind in the first gun city and
translate it for the monkey. Yeah first of right. Mm-hmm. That's right. So the monkey's
willing so you could just read his mind and the monkey the monkey. Should I do that? If you
want to guys I feel like we're pretty worried about this door right now I just
I just read the monkey's mind oh my god yeah the monkey uh you hear the monkey's
mind and he's trying to describe what he saw he's like he's like a vagina vagina
on the door.
Oh my god.
I'm seeing the door again.
Okay, yeah, how do you do it?
I do this time the top of the door frame instead of the bottom.
Is that all the money says?
Have you tried the keyhole?
That's a great idea.
I fucked the keyhole.
So there's no keyhole.
This door is just like a solid block.
So you just have to...
Isn't it already open?
and
i've come to a slurs is one of the side of the monkey can describe the process
later if you guys need to know okay i did that
but uh...
uh... i had the money has an on deck he's white as a ghost from what he saw
uh... this
so uh... yeah
once you guys walk in uh...
at first all you see is pitch blackness
in the eyes begin to adjust in a faint red light begins to grow
and see the outline of a techno industrial fortress
high ceilings and drop downs chandeliers shaped like guns and have strange lights
glowing in and out of them
and massive screens all along the walls playing looping surveillance footage
everywhere in gun city
with the occasional pornographic images flashing as well
drone music creepily thumps in the background you hear the idle chatter
between unseen women
are they laughing at you
are they laughing at your peepee
They are!
[laughter]
You're in the Suckler's Den.
You've heard stories about this place,
about the debauchery that takes place here,
the riches within, the politicians, businessmen, and celebrities
who've come through here to have an audience with the underworld kingpin.
You notice that even trying to use minor techno-slime abilities is impossible in here.
The whole area is totally nerfed.
Whoa.
All you guys roll a perception check.
Oh.
Now where's that?
10.
21 dude, let's go.
Nice, yeah.
So, uh, yeah, Way William Johnson, with your post-nut clarity, you have heightened...
Double post-nut clarity.
Yeah, you have heightened awareness.
And you notice that around you there are like large worms, like slithering and suckling on things and burrowing into holes.
Like just like so you're walking through and it's like pitch black you see the flashes of red light sort of reveal
But to this to your left in your right there are like these like worms that aren't going into the pathway, but are just like
Like whatever the fuck like just slithering around
And they seem to be avoiding your path so you notice that
I am scared as you walk
The flickering lights on the chandeliers begin to illuminate a throne
And in front of the man of the hour sits the mad suckler himself thanked by beautiful big bitches
huge bitches and
His twin killers two massive cyborgs with terrifying metallic skeleton heads Mary Kate and Ashley Cabrera
Sucklers long muscular butt worm like body is even more slimy in person and his rockabilly haircut
even more gravity-defying
You can't quite make out his eyes. It's like they're two pitch-black holes
large inside his skull
But you'd know that terrifying jagged tooth smile from anywhere as it's often plastered along the slums to remind people to watch out
Or the suckler will get you
So the suckler says
So what's up, John Carlo?
These are the ones you spoke of to me
Yeah, yeah, these are them
detectives
Interesting maybe
Maybe I'm a snake
What I really I am really really scared sir. What are you?
Sure, I'm the mad suckler that's all you need to know about me. Why do you sound like Harvey Fierstein?
He's the scariest man I could think of.
Man, I'm just glad there's only one giant worm in here. If there was a bunch of little ones, I would freak out.
He doesn't say anything. He wants to be polite.
What do these detectives need from me?
Well, first of all, I need to know why you sound like Rv5 Steve.
and
look i was i was raised by theater girls
okay well i i that's all i need to know
we can go to help
uh...
so just kidding
we need to have a million dollars training and a million dollars right now
and we need you to give it to us
please
junk on the you told me these people were serious and john carlson's yet of
course that
the very serious if things they would they want
uh... they were they want to weigh into the the the matrix to
hello
i_b_c_
why do you want to go into the matrix to
there's a mister in there
you see the big bitches are shaking their heads in
there's to mister reason there
now as we were loving respect the which ask you so much
These are all amazing reasons.
If...
Look, I'm not going to stop anyone from going in.
Of course, you can use my devices.
But...
And he holds up a long finger.
It's way too long.
There's one thing I need you to do for me.
Cool finger.
[laughter]
I have his finger in my mouth right now.
(laughter)
It extended all the way out.
(gagging)
Please don't put a zinger in my mouth!
I'm sorry about that.
Does that happen a lot?
It happens so often.
That tastes like turkey dust.
(laughter)
Here, let me try it.
Put it in my mouth.
Okay, sure.
I think I sucked it all off.
Yeah, you did.
Okay.
Now all you'll taste is my slime.
Yeah.
It's pretty good.
[Laughter]
Okay.
Cool.
[Laughter]
What do you need us to do for you besides suck your finger?
side suck your finger.
What I need from you all.
Are you all familiar with Jeff Tiedrich?
No.
I'm familiar.
Ah, that's my old nemesis from around the way.
Yes, well, Jeff Tiedrich, if he's your old nemesis.
Is it Tiedrich?
Because I looked up the pronunciation before.
Whoa, Diedrich, okay, yeah, I do know that guy.
I looked at the pronunciation before recording to double check, 'cause I also thought...
I think it's pronounced "The Third Reich."
[laughter]
That's what we've been calling him.
Yeah.
Well, Jeff, the Third Reich is an associate of mine.
Whoa, what?
Wait, are we entering into a business deal with a Nazi right now?
No, no, that's...
that's wait well hold on because if that's the case I'm gonna that's just
his name that's okay he's just right he's trying to get it changed okay is this
okay to put on the recording or do you guys want me to yeah okay well he's one
of the biggest players in Dimitri X - he funds a lot of the V tech that lives
there but he's also indebted to me. See I supply the cash, I supply the content, he
builds his virtual world but he's been acting up lately. See I have runners I
send through, I sell techno slime myself at discounted rates that Papi Chuko
doesn't want me to be selling but who cares? And he seems to have forgotten his
place what I don't care okay I just wanted you know I'm on your side amen
brother
what do we need to do
almost there all right continue don't let us interrupt you again sucking his
finger he's almost there Jeff is my reply guy nothing more but he seems to think
he's a bit more than that my runners I sent through there we starting to stop
them in them their tracks he's starting to prop them up as captures he's made in
glorious ways of fighting corruption but meanwhile I made him who he is so I need
you if you wish to go into the matrix - I need you to teach him a lesson and send
evidence of that to me I have no problem with that sounds good to me yeah I would
not mind I would not mind giving him a piece of my mind if I'm like perfectly
honest I would like to be his I'd like to beat him half the death please tell me
I want to know now Patrick Yoda your past with him. I know your name. What was
My past with him
well
I'll just say it. He's a prick
You guys were in that band together. Yeah, we had a band together. We were in that band cream, too
Say what you will about Jeff the Third Reich amazing guitarist. Oh, absolutely
We like Clapton reborn he does really look like I loved cream - oh
Wait, is that lady? He pulls up an LP and it's just you with like long hair and
I'm playing it up right base right electric bass and like a handlebar mustache. Oh
Middle school was insane for me
Well, I'm I'm a huge fan as I was 18
It's a Yotus middle school year.
Sounds like a spin-off to me.
If you-- hey, hey, who knows?
If you guys do this for me, you rough him up.
We're all square.
You can do whatever you want in the Matrix 2.
You can come here any time you like and jack in.
But if you don't do this, I'll hunt you down till you're dead.
I'm scared.
Well, you won't need to worry about that.
Yeah, we'll do it.
Yeah. What's his address?
Can you read out the street address in town and zip code
and everything?
Well, no, no, I wish I had that in my notes now, but you
can't miss it.
Jeff Tiedrich or the Third Reich or whatever lives in a
massive Japanese Pagoda in this in the Matrix 2 on top of
Mount Pole.
if we can and we have a sound
do we get to keep his house so we can all live in it?
I don't want you to kill him
I want you to teach him a lesson
what happens if we kill him?
what if the lesson is how to die?
well you don't need to
you could teach him how to die but then
you know be like ok what do you do
I'm just saying it's not
what if we kill him then bring him back to life
that's fine that might be pretty scary actually
do we have the ability to do that?
can I teach him how to tie a knot with a cherry snot?
him out of tie a knot with a cherry stem I can tell him about Lee Ferrickson okay
I need you to I need you to beat the shit out of him is that oh but not kill him
you know you're very subtle for a man who put his fingers in my mouth yeah I was
being insanely subtle just now well now that that's settled so uh hey I have got
a
I have a worm? Yes, you can have one. Oh, if he's getting one, can I have one? Do you have a favorite?
No. All right, then I'm taking this one. I'm going for the same brood, okay. And there's nothing you can do about it.
I mean, okay, I said you could have one, so. I'm gonna put them in my pocket now. All right.
And you're, are you seriously not mad? I'm not mad, bro. This one isn't your favorite? It's totally chill.
Which one is your favorite?
He doesn't have one, he already said that.
I don't have a favorite worm.
I have a favorite worm.
Well, which one would you hate to see go?
Now that's a good question.
Alright, I have a worm.
Probably that one, and he points to one and it just gets lost in the mass of worms.
Oh my God.
You can't like tell which one it is.
No, I have one worm.
Well, that's fine. I guess I guess I have one add a huge worm to your inventory. Okay, I put him in my backpack
Okay. Yeah, and so he says please right this way and you see it takes his long finger
and moves it towards a another door and
You can't see what he's doing to the door, but the door opens
and
You see like sort of a light a floodlight coming in from that door just like a like a light and he says right this way
a
- Come on, come with us.
- He's my cousin. - Drop him, you son of a bitch.
- Don't touch him.
- Oh my God, he's my cousin.
I'm just trying to tell him to be careful.
- I know what you texted to Ray William Johnson.
- Haven't you ever loved a cousin?
- Of course.
- I've always loved my cousin.
- A cousin's bond is unbreakable,
but drop him right now, you fucking bitch.
- Okay, all right, all right, all right.
I've seen what you guys can do.
I'll drop him.
Somehow I've seen it.
And he drops Sullivan the Frog.
we suck people's fingers off
so in the front says uh...
are guys i get it
let's go nasty to mister sarkar and uh...
there you guys walk towards the uh... door
and as you step in
it's a just a
big slidey slide
you start sliding around and around and around and around
uh... for like a solid meaning a half it goes really deep
yeah exacto
uh...
no right this is great and anyway so you can reach the uh...
you reach the bottom of the slide and uh...
you see a large sterile room very similar to the one mommy had in her on the
bottom of her uh... club
and uh... you see three cribs for babies in there
well i'm not sleeping in any of these
are you saying
i'm a baby
i'm not sleeping in a baby's crib i'm not saying only a baby right now i'm saying
you are at you had a race car beds before now this is their cribs that's
all i'm saying
well i'm not a baby
i'm calling you a baby brother
i'm not a baby
you see a pig guy
there
some big fat pig guy who looks like a pig
and he kinda comes up to you guys and says
alright if you guys are trying to get in there let's uh...
why do you look like a pig?
it's the future i don't know
i have been a human yet to be a piece yet
you like shit
i don't i don't look like a
i don't know if you have a giant worm just like one room ago what's going on
now and that's this is a different character
i don't want to have a new i have a room i'm out
what you're going to smell your finger in my mouth got all right i'll do it
these are in his mouth right now it's a singer in your mouth
or more and it's a it's a slight uh... it's a slight
a tuesday bacon
through the and bacon
uh... yeah i mean
uh... the edgy a cramp so
if you climb in here we can get started in the process
alright
all right i believe
the
i'm just a character i don't know i don't know how to go
i don't know page page how much did you did she's crying i don't know what you
all my god stop crying here
it is idiot and i throw my giant worm in his face i think you need immediately
so god damn it
i was saving that
it's so good
it
it out
he's been sitting out
because whatever you say
really you know
what's the answer to the mystery?
[laughter]
I don't... what mystery?
Fuck. He's too good.
[laughter]
He winks directly at the DM.
And I wink back at him.
And then what do you do with him?
And then I give him a little kiss.
Yes. And so yeah, you guys
look at the camera and say
"seems like this guy's too hog to handle."
And then I trip and I fall
into the crib and hit my head and pass out.
out. Yeah okay you're knocked out in the crib. You all do you guys climb into your
cribbies? Yeah. Okay yeah you all climb into your cribs and you guys hear a
little lullaby play as you guys crawl into your cribs. Play some classic rock I hate this shit.
Yeah you guys hear Margaritaville as you climb into the crib. I actually find it
quite stimulating to fall asleep to Pulse Demon by Merseval. Yeah you hear
or whatever the fuck, you know, cool, cool ass taste Cameron has.
You hear that?
And, uh,
(laughing)
- It was a joke.
- I don't, man, I don't know shit.
You crawl up to the crib and you guys all get strapped down
by some like metal fucking things.
Some straps kind of come around you.
And a robotic arm comes out from underneath the crib
and it has a binky on it and it puts the binky
and it shoves it in your guys' mouths, collective mouths.
I love you I love you
I love you
so are we gonna hug out after this?
yeah
I'm gonna hug out after this
are we gonna hug out after this?
since I'm a rascal, are we gonna hug out after this?
are we gonna smash that ball?
*unintelligible*
You gotta suck on the binkies to get in there
I start sucking on it
I've been sucking on it
Me too but in between each I'm telling the pig to suck my dick
Yeah okay
*unintelligible*
You do the sucklers
You do the sucklers move
and you suckle on your binkies and suddenly oh and you feel when you bring
the subtext down into the open yeah I love the pain sometimes really well
developed sometimes it's the only way and you guys start to dissolve into the
matrix - you sort of feel your body's start to I guess you don't really feel
this but you just sort of fall away and all of a sudden everything around you
turns into like sort of a weird, sort of like a cyberspace tube, like you're traveling through
like a crazy tube, and it's like blue and white lights just sort of shooting around you.
Oh, excuse me.
And you guys are all sort of like, like, going around that together and floating through
and all of a sudden you see a giant floating Cortana.
And she greets you all.
says welcome to the matrix - I just have a few questions for you before you enter
hello beautiful thank you first of all I still have the binky with you she's like
first of all what would you like your names to be while you're in - matrix -
Jack Black. Patrick Yoda. Caleb Pitts. Okay. No. No. No. I'm also Caleb Pitts too. No. I'm Jack Black.
Jack Black, Caleb Pitts, and Caleb Pitts too. Great. Now, what would you like
your avatar to look like? Caleb Pitts. Baby. Jack Black. A baby, Caleb Pitts, and Jack
black awesome now is there a name of a person you would like to reach out to
you can reach out to anyone as long as you have authorization
John McElwee no that Caleb patches is not available in the matrix - there is no
patches Caleb it's Caleb it's like has been dead
Caleb Pitts has been dead for thousands of years.
But like how old was he when he died?
Thirteen.
Thirteen? What? How did he die?
Have you seen the movie Benjamin Button?
Something like that. I'm trying to figure it out, how I do this.
Anyway, anybody else you'd like to reach out to?
Sean McKelvey.
Come on man, you're stealing my shit.
You see her eyes do the like scan like they're like scanning for a person
I accidentally say John McElwee and I'm talking to a different guy
And she's like
Sean McElwee status unknown unknown unknown
Okay, you don't have to say it three times what the hell is wrong with you sorry I have Tourette's
anyway
once reid just died i really did this shit kinda went downhill for me for a
bit
what about you
i'm talking to john mcgill we still
uh... okay
uh...
yet i mean it was it was gonna what is john mcgill we sound like
john benjamin
okay all yeah uh...
well my god i don't know how to do it
that i think that it's been that's
uh... yeah down
yes it was a bit though right uh... sound like bob's burger
uh... i got i gotta go
throw a football he's a football player right
my wrong about that maybe a john elway
john i think you've john elway this is just a guy
john mccall we
well if you've got to go through a football that probably has nothing to do
with
n_f_l_ start john elway
to your body
she says is there a location or a person you'd like to see
i guess we should ask your
here i'll talk to you guys
i guess we should ask her about
teacher the third reich
hold on one second
i turn the court on a
to box a core
uh...
sending you to to park shakur
all my
bargain got a new it
and uh... yeah you guys uh... you see that the the sort of swirling tunnel
that is uh...
in front of you
starts to like, you can see that there is like a light at the end of it and it's like fading
white and your vision completely fades to white and suddenly you each materialize.
And Cameron you are, or sorry, Blotas, you are a baby and you have a little top hat on
that says "Happy New Year" and you have above your head it says "Caleb Pitts, 13 years old"
And also the last song you listened to on Spotify,
which is the only music streaming service,
and only way to listen to music in gun city.
What was that?
- "Wait and Bleed" by Slipknot.
- Amazing, yeah.
And so you're this baby, everybody in here, by the way,
it looks like PS2 graphics.
Caleb or AKA Ray William Johnson,
you zoom in, you materialize,
you're Jack Black is your name.
you look exactly like jack black in school for a
uh... julian do we do we do we have a little bit of a little bit to get to
change our voices now
uh... it's
we change our voices to our avatars voices or
uh... no i mean like you're still yourself so it's sort of like in second
life where when you talk to you got it yeah they know we're doing a second life
thing
but now i know
and uh... yet it also says the last time you listen to on yours
spotify age also it's like
how was in school for forty
says that
you know i'm saying to the school of rock soundtrack
okay teachers pet
on as a song
and uh... patrick you know that you materialize as well as uh...
uh... and your name says caleb pits too
and you look like a load
uh...
who uh... is like sort of some sort of lost person from
long long time ago
uh... lost
yeah like land a lot of shocker from what it is a cost here that's a big thing
caleb looks like a really difficult to cover the middle of the past
that's right you look good
i'm right
yet beautiful
uh...
was that
i'm trying to i'm i'm the only one trying not to break immersion like they
are
what are you talking about
i'm doing i'm doing i'm my my character
is trying to sound like the character he's portraying yes
and to the voice again
i think you're
you think that's what i would sound like as a yoda
no that's what you sound like
that's not what i sound like
that's what you sound like dude
no
did so we materialized a two pucks a two puck zone yeah so you materialize
and i think i have to go
a guys i think we should leave here because i don't really wanna
i don't want to make you know the matrix render a voice for him
yeah
you don't know what he said here is good enough for me i'm with you just knowing
he's alive that takes that box for me
the judge of the joke box has been ticked
there's no other jokes necessary
uh... me
But yeah, no, you end up and you end up, you know, you teleport to the player that is,
um, name is Tupac Shakur.
And so you see the avatar of Tupac Shakur, um, with PS2 graphics.
Um, except they like have a good jet pack for some reason.
And an eye patch.
Um, and, and they're saying, um, Hey, what's going on?
That's what's up.
What's up, Pac?
and uh... you look around and you see that you are indeed into matrix to at
last
uh... it's has this sort of uh...
blue sheen around it right so looks like looks like classical cyber space right
let me uh... you know i mean
have some stuff for a new year you know i mean
the matrix to was filled with floating buildings annoying vaporwave aesthetics
everyone looks like the p_s_ two characters everyone's hands have fingers
stuck together and stuff. There are people speeding by with cyber bikes and people
walk up to empty lots and swipe through left and right to generate a setting or
even a video or an event. People walk through their favorite movies, even
YouTube poops and games. It's an entirely chaotic virtual experience where one
thing distracts from the next, making sure that for not for one second you're
ever bored. It all has a shimmery haunting sort of cyber quality to it that
It crowds the sky and the ground.
And it's basically an entire planet shaped like a 20-sided die.
When you look up into the sky, you see posts exploding into vision and disintegrating back
into the ether.
Everyone's feed exists in their every frame of vision.
So as you look around, you see your own feed, you see other posts.
But in the sky, you see where trending topics exist, the big posts, the most popular posters.
And as you look up, you see the mad cycle of posting, very unfair.
techno-slam prices are too high i will sell at major discount to drive demand
economics
ten million phase five million reposts
t-jerk or the third reich replying
you're a stinking fuck stick and everyone knows it
in one day your mommy will know it too
and then you'll cry like a stinking fuck ass because you're a big baby
you
four million phase two million reposts
what was the beat
it was the n_ word or
you see that you see a defensive to call a worm that
uh... i think it's pretty offensive to call anybody
the inward
bloat are there enough
i'm still learning but you know
the all our thirty years old and i never promised to be perfect this is an
anti-racist d_n_d_ campaign
uh... so to put a chicago her
you look at the sky
you see chrissy teigen got canceled for the third time this week for sub
tweeting her slaves
and i appreciate the church of medics went viral once again for saying girls
are gross
you also see quite a bit of posts saying hashtag abolish tax
nash tech all right he's shot
and now your p_s_p_'s there are a million
it's mommy good legs she's calling up
i pick up the phone and i think that's what i think
was going to need to want to pick up some of the i think it is
justin scattershot
this information will get across somehow
glad you boys found a way in i can help you much as i didn't get you in but i
can try
i have a contact their names freaking carol baskin who can help you
She has a number of epic tigers who can help you
on your search for Sean.
They can track him down no problem.
Let me ping her location to your PSPs.
And she pings you on your PSPs, the location.
You could see that she is north of Soy Lake.
So that's somewhere in sort of on one of the sides
of the 20-sided die, but you have sort of a GPS
so you can walk in that direction.
She says, "I have to go now,
"but if you have any questions, let me know."
Um, good luck and she hangs up and then you all get another buzz on your PSP
and it's from an unidentified number. Whoa. And it just says he knows.
Oh my goodness. Oh no, I think my dad knows we're in the matrix too.
He's gonna be so pissed.
Yeah, but uh, what do you guys want to do? You're here. You're into matrix 2 you could do anything you want your own avatars you can
Do whatever or you can you know first find a find try to find jeff or try to find freaking carol basket, you know
Hey tupac. Do you know where jeff is?
What jeff?
Jeff the third reich
Yeah, bingo, of course. He's in this japanese pagoda on the top of mount pole
Everybody knows where jeff is. Can you mark it on my on my mini map as a waypoint?
yet of course no problem buddy and you see he's like walking over to do that
but is like the top half of his body is like
not moving at all in just as legs are moving as he's marking and be it still
mark on your back
he's clipping a little bit through uh... uh... uh... through your head
and he says sorry about that
and here your pain is pretty high
to park
my need to change i_s_p_'s
well it's just hard to find what do you got cybercom castor
yes i have a cyber spectrum i have cyber spectrum
uh... there you go bastard as your problem
you're paying looks pretty low you guys must have gotten on some good stuff to
get in here
we've got either that
yes he my uncle made the matrix to
he starts flossing while he's talking to you guys
do you know how old are you
i'm thirteen
Yeah, meet me too. Oh
I love being 13
I do I remember what it's like and everything and I could reference things that I would think about if I was 13
I wouldn't have some wouldn't have to write anything down for that. I just got a I just got a steam alert that Patrick
Just launched skater XL
I'm gonna kick you off of the call. Yeah, you need to close that
Christ I was just checking
Graphics pack. Oh my god. Nobody would know dude. I saw your little smile as the screen lit up your face
He's gonna like unfriend all you on Steam yeah, I can't believe him
Writes a book for us every week every week Pat is like, yeah, let me see what I can do on my computer while he's talking
God fucking damn it dude. It was Pat's idea to do the graphics pack, but it was not my idea
I said I should do it. Yeah, I said it was a good idea. All right. Well, I did it. So, okay. I'm glad. All right, so
So you're 13 Tupac
Yeah, Pat take the lead
How do you know where Jeff Diedrich is if you're 13
Well, you don't have to be 13 to know that he's just you know
He's the biggest guy in guns in a no, that's not where I am. He's the biggest guy matrix - can you do?
Tupac do you want to join our party permanently and like be another character on this show? Oh
Do I oh?
Boy, awesome. Let's go to park
All right
Said I was 13 when I began this conversation
That doesn't mean you can say it. Okay, get out of here to bug. I'm locked to puck. Yeah, you block him
Yeah, you just see like a giant X over him. You see like a Garry's mod error
Yeah, and he just said he sort of walks away now there goes another great character
All right, we should let's head to Jeff, huh
Yeah, should we do general first? Yeah, I was gonna do Joe we should do Jeff just so that the
Bad suckler doesn't come on us. How about you guys go do Jeff and I'll go do Carol by myself
Yes, but the party do it I feel like we have strength in numbers three
Three people
Wasn't a racist
I think maybe, hey, we could have done that.
However...
Good point.
All right, let's go to Jeff.
At this point...
Okay.
Yeah, for sure.
Let's go to the white one.
All right, so we start walking over in the direction of Jeff's Pagoda.
Yeah, absolutely.
So you guys walk in the direction of Mount Paul, where Jeff's Pagoda is.
You see all different things as you're walking there.
People, like lots of noises, lots of different music phasing in and out.
You see people just changing their shapes and changing their avatars constantly, comparing
things, having a good old time in the Matrix 2, posting in cyberspace.
You reach Mount Pohl and it just looks exactly like Mount Fuji.
Which is just, that's it.
And you see at the very top is that pagoda.
And you see sitting at the front is a young man with a bow tie.
says, "Hi, are you here to see Jeff?"
Yes.
Yeah.
No, we're here to teach him a lesson.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
No, we're not.
Guys, come here, come here.
No, we're here to teach him a lesson.
No, we have to huddle up.
Don't tell the guard that!
What?
We're his tutors.
He hired us.
No, just get--
I'm Khan from Khan Academy.
We don't know this guy.
We don't know this Yoda guy.
Well, look, if you're here to see Jeff, you just have to put your name on the list here
and he sort of a ways is hand up minority report style
and uh... you see that they're sort of a
elicit sat too long and you can actually put it on there
or uh... if you have a urgent business i mean of course i'll let you out
we have we have uh...
knowledge about the mad suckler that he needs to hear now
well there is a great teacher
near our county jim out of all in him even a harder
and and where it were not gonna
where we're not going to get into a big trench coat
but i think
when i get a stack each on top of each other so it doesn't recognize me i would
be absurd
that would be crazy if we did that again
well he hated to do that already
and sort of did that already
uh... he he he
about the crazy if that's a thing that we do we do constantly
and uh... yes it he says okay well one moment here
he uh... holds his hand up in proud style like he's taking a phone call and see a
phone materialize
applauded in product
you're holding it the wrong way you're not just pointed out by our finger
does not have a role
that's not the improv method of something to you c_b_ exactly
he gets on the phone he's having a conversation
uh... he's a recent
i'm an hour
and he had a lot of the
you know that i know you johnny bravo
i don't know how to go on on that phone call
all excuse me sorry one moment c_n_n_'s mackinsey's
jeff will see you right now
night i cool
and so you guys get onto a ski loft other takes you all
the way up the mountain and you reach a massive pagoda that's super frickin high
in the sky and as you reach there you see all these different everybody there is
like wearing kimonos it's all very inappropriate and you also and then you
walk it you guys walk into the pagoda I guess and just sort of a like a sliding
door and going yeah yeah you guys are saying arigato to everybody there yeah
Okay, they're all very very happy to say arigato back to you.
Arigato.
Even though I think, yeah, yeah, that's, is arigato a thank you?
Yeah, they're all just saying thank you to each other.
And as you do.
Whoa.
Whoa, we just got a very cool map for the listeners at home.
Yeah.
And you see you're in this beautiful hall room and you see that he's sitting there on
is on his on his uh by his it's thrown another throne but this time it's him just kneeling
and you see he has some of his uh uh some of his uh his posse in front of him
and he says um he says i want to see jeff's posse
-Origato! -Oh my god, Bazzi.
-Origato!
-Origato! -Origato to you, Jeff.
-Origato you, Jeff!
-We already got you.
-Patrick Yoda.
-Jeff, you bitch.
-I knew when they-- when my boy out front was describing a Yoda that screeched like a weird monkey, I knew exactly who it was.
-Yeah, it was you, bitch.
You, no, it's you, you fuckstick, you ass fuck.
No, it's you, you cromulent.
Whoa, why don't you blow it out my, my fuck ass, you shitbag.
Hey, ass clown, how about I show you.
Yeah, that's your mirror.
No, it's not, it's not my mirror.
You're looking, turn your monitor on, Jeff.
Well, okay, hold on, he turns on his monitor.
Sir, this is a Wendy's.
[Laughter]
Bruh, you see all his henchmen are like
They all love that joke and he said and he says uh
You think I didn't know that the mad sucker would send three goons like you to come after the goon
No, you are good. No you and I listen we all love something awful
Goons here. Let's just relax
And what are you doing here then state your business? I'm Jeff Tiedrich
Came to teach you math
Yeah roll deception
He's telling no, no, he's actually telling the truth, okay roll it again with advantage Cameron
14 okay. Yeah. Yeah. Let me see what his wait. Can I deceive him? Wait, hold on. I rolled a 20
You didn't already talked. No, you already talked you
Whenever you want
What I trick you need to you should go back to playing skater
Yeah
14 is not gonna cut it cuz I know
Like you guys you he let you up here for a reason knows all the scales
He knows all the scales on the guitar here. He's a white. So why'd you let us up here?
Then if you don't want to learn math
As I wanted to see exactly what the mad suck was sending my way and I'm gonna teach you all a lesson
That's right. I'm gonna I'm the teacher here. It's a mind matrix
Yeah yours yeah yours
No, mine. Yeah, you know that's no that's no you're right. No, he doesn't understand how to do this kind of riff. He's like
It's like too complex for him. No, it's yeah. No, it's mine
No, it's mine. No, it's
Rabbit season again, right?
Is that what this is? I dropped my worm on the ground
You got your worm back. I got my yeah, cuz yeah, he got it. I took it out of his mouth. Yeah
Yeah, what what pretty great that pretty cool worm, right?
And then I whisper I whispered a
Blow toss and Patrick guys go go like punch him or something. Oh, yeah. What do you think of my worm? I?
Think is he up at the time wait, wait, wait, wait guys. Wait. All right. Okay. Hey guys, you know what Jeff is, right?
We shouldn't listen to the mad suckler. We should just get out of here and I turn and I leave the the pagoda
Okay, and when I'm as soon as I'm outside the doors out of sight I use my
disguise
Ability and I disguise myself as the the boy from the from the bottom who who had the phone. Okay. Yeah
As a young man, okay. Yeah. All right, and
And I just fucking rush at him cuz I hate him
(laughing)
- Okay, shit, all right.
So yeah, you come back, you're looking like the boy.
- Oh, I haven't come back yet.
I'm peaking, I'm waiting. - Oh, you haven't?
- I'm gonna wait.
If Patrick's rushing at him, I'm not gonna come back.
- Okay, cool, so I'm gonna remove you from this.
So you're ready, are you rushing at him?
- Yeah.
- We doing this?
- I'll put myself right here next to this guy
'cause I assume I'm gonna have to fight
one of the henchmen.
- Oh yeah, we're rolling initiative in that case.
Let's do this.
- Right after I started my cool plan, Patrick, really?
I can turn around. You're also...
Patrick, Pat, he's not worth it.
I run all the way up and then I turn around.
Because while I was running up I noticed there's a fun-sized snicker.
No, that's my worm.
Behind this little thing here. So I go looking for a fun-sized snicker that I thought I found.
What game are you playing at? What was that?
Bomb sorry, you know, well that sounds like the Patrick Yoda. I know that's right, bitch. Oh
You okay
My ideas for our band cream - you never let me do any solos you brick
In the middle of this argument I burst in out of breath as the as the front door boy and I'm like sir
Sir, mr. T drink. Oh my god that you have to come downstairs
is
towards you then you know he's no he's at this point very suspicious so he's
walking towards you so what's up are you letting him leave are you guys gonna do
anything really I want to get him right outside the door right away from his
posse okay cool okay and okay so yeah you walk him out okay so I'm gonna I'm
gonna I'm gonna put you guys back I'm gonna I'm gonna take this map out for a
sec well and I'll move these guys over over here to pretend they're not around
and you guys are now outside okay Patrick it's over there if you're gonna make
mischief at least make it something that like the prisoners can hear yeah okay
a
again.
Okay, I shoot him in the hand.
Woah.
Oh.
Cool.
Okay, do an attack roll with advantage.
Alright.
With the gun.
Oh, yeah, 24.
That first one hits for sure, do damage.
10.
Yeah.
Let's go.
You shoot it right through his fucking hand.
He's like, "AHHHHHH!"
Like he starts to, like, makes a horrible noise, and, uh, "You fuckstick, you fuckburger, AHHHHHH!"
and there will never be a cream three and that's for changing the intro to
sunshine of your love to to be on guitar
guitar you fucking it sounds like shit yeah he's on the ground now he's
bleeding I use my matrix beam on him oh shit you guys are gonna fuck him up okay
oh wait don't kill ya don't kill him I just didn't kill him all right yeah well
here's the thing here's what we can do no you can revive powers yeah so if you
kill him if you kill him quote-unquote if you knock him down to zero you can
revive him so that is something you can do and then also you'll just need to
like do a medicine check and also I can't Caleb you have healing abilities
so true you would be able to do that as well but uh yeah if you want to if you
want to do that though if you want to like the next attack we're gonna like
Roll initiative because the guys in there are gonna be like hearing their yeah. All right, you know, I'll hold off
We got a I just kick him in the head
And yeah, I mean you hear the guys sort of coming in as they're hearing this commotion
so what do you guys want to do like I
Walk it out. I walk back in to the
To the building and I say to the guys. Hey, have you guys seen?
My worm anywhere. I think I left my worm in here
Okay, they're just trying to run right past you no, no, seriously, there's a very cool worm in this room
You could definitely also like do a surprise attack on them for sure. So like I'm just gonna stop chasing. Okay
Mass demon I could I could disguise I could disguise myself again as Jeff teacher
Yeah, you could throw your grenade - those are no disguise do disguise
Okay, guys, yeah, let me see I'll use up all my techno slot. So, okay. Yeah, so here's here's though
The order of events then just to make sure if you guys want to do this, right?
Obviously you have another Jeff Tiedrich that you'll need to sort of apprehend. Yeah to have only one
So I'm gonna give you guys like each of you guys can do like kind of one thing to see how you're gonna resolve this
So, what are you thinking to both? Have you disguise which is one thing you're doing?
And then what are you two thinking of doing to sort of like quiet this this Jeff teacher and like hide the body or I?
Sit on his face. Well, I got an idea not gonna
Get ready could also try and pretend that he's the he's the imposter. I just rolled 22 on animal handling
He is an animal. Yeah
He's part Muppet.
What the hell are you doing man?
I'm sorry!
Yeah, that's not going to do anything.
So do you guys have a plan?
You guys don't have to have a plan.
I'm giving you a chance.
Oh, oh.
What if I put them in my hoverboard house?
So if they do come out...
Your hoverboard house?
Wait, I don't have that because I'm in the Matrix 2, right?
Or do I still have that?
My hoverboard turns into a little pod that I sleep in.
I was trying to sleep in yes. Yeah, I would say that you still have that ability so to do that though
And like to do that quickly
That's gonna be just a straight Dex check
And your thing that you do by the way
Blowtorch not blowtorch. Sorry, um, Ray William Johnson can be like assisting him with that so that he has advantage
Yeah, or or you could do something else too, but I help him out with the house. Yeah, okay
I lock him in my little hoverboard house
Okay, he's like what are you doing now? Now your stupid house. I hate your house. What what I just
Rattled it. He's silent. He's silent in there. He's like yelling about it being art deco and how that's
Trash it's fine. All right, so both you so roll decks twice patch a go though
Try to like stuff them in there as quickly as you can
And sort of surprise him
Oof, okay
Oh no.
I guess it's a contest.
I guess I'm contesting Dex, which maybe this could have been strength, but I think Dex
is fine.
Let's see how he does.
Why don't we add it up so it's a 20.
Yeah, sure.
Why don't we just say it's a 20?
Yeah, why don't we say I got a natural 20?
No, yeah, I mean you can...
Nobody can see the rolls, I mean.
Right.
All they can do is hear them.
It's all 20s.
Yeah, so you beat him though.
You got four 20s in a row.
Don't worry about it.
Every time we've rolled a die, we're just making up a number.
Yeah, I mean kind of these stories are airtight. Okay, everything is planned that you're exactly
No, but you did beat him. So it beat his like Dex check
So he tried to get out of the way and you like sort of grabbed him and like shoved him in
He was sort of already like kind of fucked up because you shot him in the hand
And so you got him in there. And so now the his like men come out of there
Sort of already in formation and they see this other Jeff Tiedrich with you two
blowtoss missing and a hoverboard house and
They're like they're like sir. What happened? We heard you scream. I
Went down to the front gate and I saw the mad suckler there and
he started yelling at me and I told him I was gonna I was gonna bring him down once and for all and
And he went to the mall to start to try to enact a plot against us.
And I need you guys to go to the mall.
Okay, I'm gonna go ahead and find him and kill him.
Because this is crazy.
But like I said, you have deception with advantage because your disguises are so good.
But it's sort of dipping into this is getting, they're like trying to assess what's going on.
They trust Jeff, but they're not, they just want to know what's going on.
So go for it.
With advantage, you said?
All right, so yeah, one of them is a two.
All right, let me see. Yeah, okay. They're like, "Okay, which mall should we go to, sir?"
The farthest mall.
Of course, the Mall of America. And they start running.
They start running to the Mall of America, which is on earth. So they're like not going to be there
for they're gonna go there to travel to the years
uh...
and they start going
uh... yeah
so you guys have jeff you've apprehended him you bring back inside or like to
interrogate well so i could really could just bring him to the mad suckler
i bet i a lot of we did that we have to get out of the middle of my little
there's like a little like slidy window thing and i pull it open to see what
he's doing to my house and he is just he has issues on my new carpet
he's a dentist
"This Japanese thing is fake, I love wearing shoes indoors!"
*laughter*
"You better knock that off right now!"
"Nooo!"
"And I'm gonna post about it too!"
He takes pictures of his kicks.
"Get his phone, get his phone!"
"Get his- ah!"
"I force pull his phone."
"Alright, you see?"
"Would I have to roll a 20 for that?"
"Uh, no, no, uh, roll, roll, shit, I guess you're doing 'use da force'?"
"Yeah."
So use Deforce, which is going to take some Technoslime points. Let me get your...
Yeah, let me open that thing.
Yeah, which is going to give you the ability to...
Oh, where is that? Oh, here we go.
Yeah, so if you use Deforce, it costs 5 Technoslime points,
and you're going to be able to... it's a tiny object,
so you're automatically going to be able to yank the phone from him.
Whether I grab it...
Well, I would say it's a contested Strength check,
but um just because like he's sort of fighting back so um but i'm gonna give you advantage
because i don't think he's going to be expecting it so just roll um just uh actually you know what
sorry what i should do yeah okay it's gonna be a contested strength check so just roll with
advantage um i'll have that force be sort of linked to that actually sorry you should roll wisdom
because that's your force okay which is gonna be better for you there we go i mean either one of
of those. I take his phone out of his hand. Yeah, you immediately take it out. And now,
I have the power. You see he was about to post his picture of his shoes and damn Daniel was
going to be the caption. And he didn't finish writing it. He's like, "Grrr, you!" And yeah,
so what do you guys want to do? You have Jeff Tiedrich. And we have his phone. I sent a
and
a
bit of my penis. You should just no love deep web it just completely all penis
and then he's in the background. Okay then I do that. Okay yeah you sexed the mad
suckla with like a picture of Jeff Dietrich and your dick kind of in it and
yeah he just sends back like a thumbs up emoji. So that's is that good is that
good enough for him do you think? Can we let him go now? I send back a message that
says you like this
here let me grab a dummy try it and i can grab the phone and i said
what up big head
it
uh... the mad cycle calls the phone at this point and so i i it's in my hand
answer hello beautiful
uh... you
the real
s
what what's going on you have just a little nice
and we have jim so again
can you help us out was up
just make sure he gets the picture
and we did the picture to you
did you not get it it was better to do this penis
no that's a little thingy out
that joke ralph always you want another one with his balls in there to okay by
and i hang up on a and i had a phone a patrick
i gotta get my balls and it's a hell of a job all of our photo him in his throne
room so i have a look at the market for a bit
no i have to take the picture from upside down
i didn't hear the picture i'll take the picture
okay you take a picture
all right you can't use then here jeff
you're perfect baby don't move a muscle
okay
take your balls out
uh... they've been out
all those are your balls
just other you just the other people walking behind
like in this sort of courtyard outside is the code of people are just sort of
like
seeing what's going to confuse a a rob rubberneck much
alright better back to your balls
are they seriously that small
uh... i'm a yoda
alright well i guess i'll need to do some here i'll just get the camera really
close to your balls to make it look normal size
yes what do you think you're sending him a picture of your balls now and
uh... our balls
is not our ball
therefore it will cost
the k_u_ send as everyone's walking by i saw i'm still disguised as yet
yourself as everyone what was walking by
hey guys it's me just teacher ake everything in my pagoda is free
yeah
he's the uh... i were
uh... someone sees my word bring him out please
you see everyone go
they hold running side
and they start like tearing up the place
you see jeff is trying to open the sliding window in your home
your hoverboard home like screaming like
what you can hear it in there
uh...
he's screaming though
uh... one guy comes out with just like
with like three golden buddhas
uh... and just like is like holding them
is a i can't wait to bring this to my wife and he's just like walking out
all excited
you see uh... somebody comes out of the worm in hands it to you
uh... though you
and uh... they go through
and they are walk away
and then okay well and then i'd turn to
to great william johnson i go
hey take a picture of me
and i do it comes up
and i and i because i'm still just a trick so
Okay, I take a picture of him.
Okay now post it with the caption. I'm gay
I'm on it boss
Yeah, you see it. Yeah, you look up in the sky and you see that post explode
into frame
Uh, it just says i'm gay and it's a picture of jeff tedrich giving a thumbs up
Outside of like his pagoda being raided
uh
And then I reply to that post with the picture of Patrick Yotis penis and Jeff Tiedrich in the background.
[Laughter]
You see the trending topics have changed immediately.
It has like 2 million mentions, like "Is Jeff Tiedrich gay?" "Damn." "Who knew this?" Like it's just going crazy.
Jeff Tiedrich sentimental emotional coming out. He posted a picture of him and his partner
His partner is Sean King his partner is his partner is Patrick Yoda's penis. Yeah, my penis just looks like a guy
But yeah, what do you guys want to do you guys you guys have like
I've really you guys just really what I would say
To be helpful. All you have to do is let him know that this is what the mad suckler said
- You do? - Oh, yeah.
He's pretty sufficiently...
Like, you've made it clear to him not to fight.
- I've ruined his life. - I pull his pants down.
[laughter]
- Wait, who's? - Whose pants?
- Which one? - Myself.
[laughter]
You try to pick between each, Jeff, and you get confused.
- Yeah. - So I just pull my own pants down.
Yeah.
And I look at Patrick as he looks at my balls, and I say,
you know as much
uh... i don't care size doesn't matter
also as does matter
both sides does not matter at all does that your model
mrs
what
yeah going as well
yeah anyway jeff basically
uh...
the matter of the my pants are still down there
but i'm not is is that
Ray William Johnson's dick is exactly on eye level with the window that Jim Diederick is looking out of.
Basically, Jeff, the mad suckler sent us. He wanted us to teach you a lesson. Do you feel like you've learned something here today?
You see him like nodding. He's like, he's like crying. He's a mess.
Yeah. All right.
Well, we'll we'll get you around then.
The first person to figure out how to explode my pagoda gets a grand prize.
You see a guy whose avatars Ted Kaczynski just run in there.
Start trying to figure something out.
Yeah, what do you guys did you guys just deposit him then on his stoop of his burning pagoda?
I kick him off the mountain
Hey shit, okay
Like cartoon violence style that I know that'll kill him. I will kill him
Oh, man, all right, not supposed to kill him. Well die in the matrix you die in real life
Well, I go like a little I find a very small cliff and I kick him off of that
I'm gonna need you to do or feet. Why don't you kick him down the stairs? I kick him down the stairs
Yeah, you kick him down the stairs he takes
You Larry took one damage he's fine. Yeah, he's like this is fine. I love this is my fetish
And he's like a crumpled mess on the ground and you guys just fucking step over him with your dicks hanging out yes
We're walking away into the sunset and I turn back and I look him in the eye and I say sir
this is a Wendy's you see it you're walking we go that you hear that song
from you know the movie Breakfast Club is playing you guys are on the ski lift
heading back down you see the you see the young man he said my pants are still
down. He said, "Wow, Jeff seems to have really lost it there. Hope I still get paid."
He's a total weirdo. Listen, do you feel like my balls are almost too big?
Um, no, they seem okay.
Now, what about his balls? Do you feel like they're too small?
Proportional, I think, but...
Thank you! That's what I've been saying!
You have no taste.
Yeah, oh I, okay, well, I mean, I wish, wish you would all just, just for recommendation,
you guys should probably put your pants back on while you're in here. There's gonna be some, uh,
this is an NSFW server, so, uh, but. Well, just click it on.
What do you want me to click on? Click it on. NSFW, click it on.
Is Patrick trying to get this, this little boy to... He's not a little boy. He's not a little boy.
He's an 8 year old boy.
He's literally 3 years old.
Jeff Tiedrich calls him boy.
You know how you do that to people who are like 22 if you're a piece of shit.
Yeah, 22 months.
Yeah, 22.
Looking pretty bad for you, Patrick.
No.
You've got tiny genitalia and you're trying to shove them.
Caleb's balls are out too.
Yeah, but you didn't tell him to click it on.
Also, I'm not ashamed of them, I'm proud.
I told him to click on the NSFW tag so that it becomes a non-safe-for-work server.
He's in charge of the server.
Yeah, he says, "Let me go do that, it's gonna take an hour."
And he shoots himself in the head.
And he starts doing that.
Yeah, you guys did that.
So the Suckla messages you all on your own PSPs and he says, it says like good work and
it has a bunch of S's at the end of it for no reason.
And he says do what you must and dot dot dot like a boomer.
It's all good.
Like a freaking boomer.
And you're good.
Oh my god.
Nah.