Here we go.
Last time on Gun City, a broad city, Playtime continue fun.
The guys beat the crap out of a snake, but not before making its heart grow three sizes
with the ever lovely threat of suicide from Patrick Yoda.
The snake, confused, let Patrick go take care of the half leprechaun O'Neil, whose throat
had been slashed by Playtime, the ever rampant serial killer, the ever rampant.
who tried to get his third kill in the same day.
However, playtime failed,
and Patrick Yoda staunched the bleeding.
After Blotoss and Rey finished off the snake,
they took its corpse and went on a shopping spree
where they found nothing they could afford.
Then Blotoss and Rey took the snake back up
to the crime lab for further investigation.
While Patrick Yoda met up with Baby Gadd,
who urged Patrick Yoda to keep the whole playtime attack
on the down low,
that there'd be something in it for him if he did.
Patrick skipped most of the dialogue in the scene and went right to Gaddy up.
I didn't.
BG's chintzy Gadsville-themed bar in the undercity on the Pleasure Palace space station.
The erstwhile cyberpunk aesthetics of Old Gun City reared its head there, and Patrick
Gyora almost felt at home until he saw a very intimidating huge ass twins named Keep Calm
and Chive On.
Patrick set to work reading their minds, whatever was in there, and found some very useful information
that I'll recap in a moment.
But the sleuths up at the crime lab found their own strangeness.
This snake, the second of two monsters that have appeared today, was made of organic matter,
plastic that is in toys, polyethylene, and some kind of synthetic composition that made
up its erogenous zones.
and we learned it was scary to fight it.
- Yes, and scannable.
- And we learned that we were brave for defeating it.
- I'll also remind you guys a couple
of little housekeeping things.
It is probably afternoon-ish right now.
You guys probably got started today,
like at like 11-ish, maybe got to--
- We've already done all this shit and it's afternoon?
- It's probably afternoon, maybe early evening.
Might be 5 p.m. maybe.
- Well now I'm not, I was so scared when O'Neal got killed,
but now I'm not scared at all, it was in broad daylight.
- We were booking it.
It was like 5pm-ish, I mean the Undercity is pretty dark.
I've just been assuming that every single day that we've played this has been a different day.
I've been assuming that this is real-world time.
Yeah, I guess there's no daylight, it is...
The daylight is like, I mean there's like, yeah, the...
Yeah, the artificial day?
Yes, but it depends on where you are in the space station.
They didn't invest in the Undercity.
The Undercity not as much, that was, you know, wasn't the Undercity yet, but...
I see.
...kind of made it a little bit more like that.
And where O'Neil is kind of right on the border, so it's kind of like dusky at best there.
Daylight's been scared out of us.
It's been scared out of here as well.
Just turn the lights on and off.
Holy shit.
As soon as I said that,
that was insane timing.
Can you do that?
Do that again.
Holy shit.
Alright, don't do that. That's too scary.
Wow. Okay.
That was crazy.
That was insane time sync up.
Right there.
So you guys have been traveling around.
- What a coincidence.
- Did he do that on purpose?
- Well, they both turned off at the same time.
- I don't know.
- What?
- No, when I said scared the daylights out of us,
the lights shut off immediately.
- Yes, I agree.
That is pretty cool.
- That was weird.
- I think there's a ghost in the office, you guys.
- So you guys have been traveling around,
going to a crime lab, you know,
and you've been taking the zippy loop for the most part.
You lost a little bit of time going the cool way,
but not that much time, like lost time.
It just took a little bit longer.
So it's like probably 5 p.m. ish now, I would say.
Like, so I guess like kind of end of day for a lot of folks.
And for you, I'll give you some recap
on what you heard from Yoda's mind.
And then I'll set the scene for where we are.
'Cause right now you got the parties like split,
I guess, right now.
So here's what you had learned.
- Oh, it ended with, last episode ended with the--
- With an imagined scenario.
- With an imagined scenario where I get murdered.
- Yeah, get murdered.
Yeah, that was cool.
So, here's kind of what you learned that those twins, so like, are pissed at Gadd for, and as you dug deeper,
failing to kick up like a certain amount of tokens, it sounds like, over time.
And wanted to talk with him about that.
They also wanted to talk with him about the playtime situation, make sure it was under control,
because it happened to one of Gadd's guys, that being O'Neal.
as far as how it relates to you, they're wary of you,
in particular, like you three.
Like, you know, you're not, at this point,
you guys are kind of gun city celebrities, right?
Like you've-- - We don't mean that.
- That's right. - Oh, I mean that.
(imitates gun firing)
Yeah. - You open hot beer
and cold dogs. - We did a hot soda.
- You were entrepreneurs, you murdered
the most powerful man in the city.
- Oh yeah. - You went to jail.
- That usually makes people famous.
- Yeah. - Going to jail.
- Yeah, what about that model guy?
- Oh, for sure. - Remember that guy?
Which Marl guy? The guy who had the sexiest mugshot meme.
Seems like you remember him a little more. I wonder why. He left his long time girlfriend.
And you looked that up too. You looked up does he have a girlfriend. You have not learned how to roll a single die in this game.
But you have made space for that hot guys love life. You don't remember that? No!
Sorry 2014 lay off. He's got a fucking
I'm sorry. You're right. I'm being ableist I guess um so but also we are a list cuz we're a list celebs in the gun
Guys are you're more like notorious like some people like notorious be yo, motherfucker. Yo, motherfucker. Yo, so ultimately
They have big ultimate ultimate Denzel Curry
They have big murals of us on the streets.
You're like, is that Ray William Johnson?
That doesn't really look like him.
Until you get up close, you're like, oh, yeah,
I guess I can see it.
I guess so.
But ultimately--
And they have rap snacks, but they're actually
rock and rap snacks.
Denzel Curry aside, they were most concerned about--
because you went all the way deep and kind of
into whatever can actually rattle around
their minds into their biggest concerns, which
was of some kind of scientist
that they wanna make sure that the activities
of that scientist who works for Hugh Jass-Fax
are not becoming a problem for the
Hugh Jass-Fax's operation in the undercity.
- I didn't get anything else out of their brains, right?
- That was the deep, I mean--
- Yeah, base level, I didn't know about their past
or anything.
- No, I mean, 'cause the mind reading thing
is meant to get their concerns about things,
so you can get snippets of them,
but we talked about, we talked about--
- I can't get their anxieties.
- We talked about getting--
- And play upon them. - Upgrading it potentially
to-- - Oh, right, right, right.
- Into visuals as well, which we'll talk about ways
to upgrade that, but another time, not in this episode.
But also, but all that said, like,
I can say that with that kind of mind reading--
- What, I didn't do anything.
- Ability. - Just let Pat just talk.
- All right.
- With that kind of mind reading, you've, come on.
You definitely get the sense of like,
these guys are like--
- They're both eating pussy. - Why are you stopping
talking? - Yeah.
These guys are like, they're not high up,
but they're thugs, right?
They're not meant to really--
- Oh.
- Like, they're thugs for a gangster.
- Hey.
(laughing)
- They're thugs for a gangster?
Okay, so they sound fucking badass and sick?
- Yeah, I'm not just, all right.
I'm not gonna interrogate what you just put into the air.
- I'd like to recruit them.
- I mean, they--
- You're not in the room.
- So yeah, so that's everything you learned.
You're still in Gaddy Up.
Baby Gat is going to go talk with them now
'cause he told you, "Hey, I gotta talk with these guys.
"I'll be right with you though."
And O'Neal is in there, he's ordering a drink.
But you guys, we're gonna go to there where you guys are.
You're in the crime lab in the Royal District.
- Yep.
- So you just found out that this snake
has like erogenous zones.
The blue gopher told you that from his analysis.
- I remember him.
- Catch me every time.
We put the him.
Yeah.
Really like.
No, put my guy over here.
I really like that his name is the blue gopher.
No, the blue gopher was in the right place.
Yeah.
Sorry about that.
So you fucked everything up.
Uh huh.
So he's here.
And then Peppa.
Ray.
Ray William Johnson.
Well, Peppa's my nickname for Ray William Johnson.
Oh, okay.
Oh, 'cause you're spicy like Peppa.
Yeah.
I like that, actually.
And you're a pig.
And the blue gopher will say, like, to you guys.
Hey, man.
You're the whole hog.
(laughing)
- Yeah, I call you a pig 'cause you're the goat,
and that's another farm animal.
So it's kind of like, I say Peppa Pig
'cause you're like the spiciest goat.
- Okay.
- I call you pork grind.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause I love to eat your skin.
- Spicy goat Jamaica vibes.
- Yeah.
- Mm.
- But you're not a jerk.
- Oh shit, thank you.
- And you're not chicken.
- But when I see you, I don't say ackee.
Like salt fish and ackee.
- You're getting way done. - So the blue gopher
chimes in and says to you guys,
like, this material's really interesting.
I don't know exactly the synthetic parts
where the erogenous zones are.
I don't know anyone who could make something like this.
The composition is hard for me to even track with.
It's sort of making my instruments into just doorstoppers.
Like, I can't even begin to decipher it.
You can see he's like looking at it.
It's like, it's kind of unknown what the composition is.
It's like, maybe it's techno slime,
maybe it's like a some sort of like other kind of material just of the erogenous
feel good if I put my doodle in the erogenous zone of the snake that's a good
question you could certainly try I yeah but you're doodling roll a constitution
saving throw wait would it feel good for who so it's a mouth and then that secret
hole in the bottom I'll try both one by one okay let's start with the mouth roll
or not
that's a net twenty
and you know what
your day you'd you had twenty put it here
here you do the full like the angelo how does it feel
it
galatani
menu for the same
i'm not for the status quo the reason i was one of my cameras out there for that
music videos cuz he's fucking is that he had a hard-hitter
I do want to clarify that one in one out. Yeah, so yeah, no berms one pump no spurting sperm
What if you don't so good you should have you are a complete control
Yes, I'm gonna tell you it feels amazing and you are
You are as it feel though. You are in complete control of whether or not you come
You have like a control that no one's ever had. Can you describe exactly how it feels? No
- Okay, I pull out and then I go...
(laughing)
I go, "Ah, ah!"
- What the fuck is that?
I've never seen cum.
- That's something from inside the snake.
- Oh man.
- It attacked me.
- He's having a seizure.
- The blue gopher goes and he's like,
"Oh, well let me put it inside his kill."
- We need to analyze that.
- He goes, "I'll analyze this later.
"You gonna try the other hole now?"
- Oh yeah, well he's analyzing it
And I'm secretly trying the other hole.
Okay, cool.
Roll another constitution saving throw.
With advantage.
Because you got 20 on the last one, so you know what this is about.
Okay, that's a 4.
Well, this could be a whole different kind of feeling.
And that's an 8.
Plus 1.
That's a 9.
Yeah, you come inside the snake's hole.
Right away.
Pretty much instantly.
Doc, I think there's more stuff to be in this other hole.
No!
I staple it shut.
unplugged something. I remember that being Staples there. He's like trying to analyze
it more closely. He says, "Well either way, what was it from your experiments? What
was the synthetic material like?" I'm smoking a cigarette. I can tell you that it felt
like good in like an otherworldly way. So I'm smoking a cigarette, I go, "Phew, that felt good."
interesting okay that help us at all there's a tear down your gopher that a
huge scientific breakthrough pussy and fucking butthole feels good but as I'm
my shirt up I'm rubbing my belly but as good as it made you feel that's where
it's curious it's something hold on and the blue gopher takes on its hands
running a train on a dead stage.
(laughing)
- I don't think, I think there's a one time
I think I'm gonna not partake.
- Yeah, and yeah, yeah, the blue gopher's eyes
like permanently cross.
(laughing)
He's like, I think I can still see.
Yes, that is not human.
That is not a creature that should,
that's not, thank you, bless you.
- It's a being made completely out of pleasure.
Hey Pleasure Man, am I still on the phone with him?
Yeah, you can call them. You guys can call each other.
Yeah, I don't, because I remember I called him last time, but I don't remember if I'm still on the phone.
Yeah, you just hear like, you haven't been saying anything, you hear from speaker, like a speaker phone.
Like a being made completely out of pleasure?
Yes, something like that.
A Pleasure Man?
there's only one sorry my computer made that sound the test results are in
I actually literally I'm only 90% who so I do need to just one second look like a
grandpa as I look that's not what a grandpa looks grandpa's don't look no
where badass leather yeah not your grandpa yeah my grandpa's grandpa's
named Arnold. You're gonna get your whole identity hacked by saying that dude. Arnold?
That's my great-grandpa on my mom's side, Arnold. Okay well now you're
fucked. And I have a shirt that has his name in it. Arnold. Yeah McDarnolds.
Yeah McDarnolds. Yeah cuz you wear so much McDonald's. Yeah you like McDarnolds.
I work at McDarnolds. Yeah. And you have a burger. He's got a burger in his pocket.
Keep it going, keep it going, Pat.
- And your thing is as big as a french fry.
- Yes, and one of the little ones at the bottom.
The kind that's only the crisp.
- Yep.
- Yeah, those are actually some of the best fries.
- You think his is some of the best penis you ever had?
I'm reading between the lines here.
- The only scientist I could think of on the ship
who would even know where to begin
in analyzing something like this.
- Probably some fucking ho-ass scientist.
(laughing)
- Doctor might be, I think he's about to say Dr. Slut.
- Yeah, Dr. Mike Lit.
- Well, no, I don't think so.
Mike Lit, he died very recently.
- Or Mike Hunt.
- Yeah, or Mike, well, that's a little nastier.
(laughing)
R-rated.
- Okay, wait, Mike Hock.
- Yeah, Mike Hock might be.
- Well, it would be Ebenezer Keech.
(laughing)
- Okay.
- Dr. Ebenezer Keech.
Him and Tool Lateralis were the only,
only ever doctors to work for the Techno Slime Corporation,
Papa Chuka Techno Slime Corporation, and Get Out.
But, and he works here now.
- Ebeneezer Queef.
- Oh, hey, that's not right to say.
- Somebody shut that funny phone up.
- From the pocket.
- If you go to the command center.
(laughing)
- From the pocket.
I'm ripping shit up from the pocket.
You can't even, I ain't even in the room.
- You're just in the bar.
You're in the bar, you're like in a corner,
like, "I'm gonna give a fuck, yeah."
(laughing)
- One ear closed.
- Yeah.
- Finger.
- Yeah, dude.
- I'm tearing that up from the pocket, though.
Sorry, excuse me.
They're moving over as some people move in
with their friends.
- I wanna close my tab.
Oh, snap!
Here we come from the pocket.
So you could--
- And then doing the thing where you hold
the phone speaker directly to your ear
when you're playing a voice memo from someone in public.
(laughing)
- So you could go to the command center and meet with him.
That would be where he's located.
You'd have to go probably speak with Gumby Superior
as he is his personal scientist and member of his crew.
But at this point, I'm out.
I mean, you'll keep bringing me monsters.
I'll keep fucking them and learning more.
I wasn't even a character.
You guys made me up basically.
Oh yeah.
The blue coat fur is now a guy.
So now I think that...
And he works at a crime lab.
And fucks dead animals.
The guy who fucks the dead animals to analyze them.
Well this is the first one that he fucked right?
Which is now he has a taste for it.
Yeah.
Let's see. He rolled an 8.
He fucked 8 before that?
I don't know what that means.
I'll be honest
Way to find that out, but yeah, so you guys can either we'll go back to the bar though
Let's just I guess get some people there, but um
Baby gets here now
Yeah, baby get baby. Well, baby guys in like a back room with the two with keep coming Chyba unless
Unless you I mean Patrick Yoda, did you as baby guy went?
He just went away with them. You didn't care at that point or like, um, you I mean
I was just asking if you like talk to them at all or talk to baby guy before you went away with them
I did so you just had read their minds right after baby. God. Oh, yeah. Yeah, then they went into that room, right? Yeah
Yeah, that's fine
I want to see if you if you wanted to engage with them at all cuz you were gonna hit them
I'm gonna I'm gonna try
Is there I don't have any kind of eavesdropping technology
Not technology, but you big ears big-ass ears. Yeah, I
literally think
We'd almost do that. I know that's a I I literally think there is precedent for yeah you using your big ears
Okay, then I'm gonna put my very open to that
Okay, wait should I climb is there a I'm gonna roll an investigation real quick. What are you gonna?
Do what are you I'm looking for a way to eavesdrop more on their conversation?
Yeah, so I'll also before you enroll
I'll give you a layout of just like there's like the bar and then like a back room that's to the side of the bar
It's actually it actually just teleport you to the back room and makes you invisible when you're there, but no yeah roll this
Because I feel like rolling my ear up to the door would be too too conspicuous
Yeah, yeah roll roll to see if you can find a better way to do this
Okay, and then also you can describe to me. I got a nine wait wait nine
- Nine plus, so that's 11.
- 11, so it's not bad.
I mean, there's nothing, you have a better way of,
like you can see kind of where the crease in the door is,
it's on the bottom, which isn't that helpful,
but you didn't get too much about the layout
that can help you.
That said, I mean, describe to me
how you're gonna try to listen to them
to make this less conspicuous.
There are other people at the bar, but--
- They're in a secret room?
- They're just in his office, in the back room.
It's not like a--
Can you describe what's around the office? Is it one of those bars that it's just a door
that says "employees only" or is it fully in the back? Does it say "Gastropub"?
What you know is that there's an "employees only" - it doesn't say "Gastropub" - only
door.
There's a door that says "Gastropub" though.
In that - through there. No, but what you don't know is that if there's further down
the hall than his office.
know what I mean? Then I'm gonna put my ear up to the... is there a stool
next to this door? Yeah. I'm gonna sit there in a way that is not
conspicuous, but if you were to look at me... Yeah, roll performance. If you were
to look at me, you'd be like, "This guy is clearly trying to listen to something."
Yeah, right. What'd you get? I got a six again. Or no, I got a six now. What'd you get
later. Oh, I know earlier I had another 11. Okay, oh your performance is pretty good.
Uh yeah, I would say you can do this for like enough time
that like you can get that you'd sense that you can't really hear much so
there's probably more space but you know that you can't do this for any kind of
longer than it is to know that before like a bartender will probably or like a
a bouncer will come over and be like, "Hey man, what's..."
- Is it the bouncer?
- What's happening?
- Yep.
- Yeah, the bouncer's like, "Oh my God."
- I don't want to sleep.
- Oh my God, that's Cloud's body.
(laughing)
- Oh my God, that is mostly Cloud.
- Yeah.
I feel like you're missing Cloud's hair for that piece.
- Shut up.
- Okay, what else can I, can I just like sneak into that?
'Cause it's like clear that there's, all right.
- Yeah, so look at your--
- I'm going to assume the role of employee
using a disguise. Do I have a disguise kit?
We're bringing back disguises. You don't have a disguise kit.
The only one that you have is the arcade repairman outfit.
Let's go. You're going to try to do that again? Yes sir.
Okay, so roll a disguise kit check
I guess. This is what would usually be for a disguise kit.
And you can still just put on the outfit.
Do I add anything? No, no, no.
No, he's got six. I mean, you don't you don't have the
the comportment of an arcade repairman for the most part.
But really, this is performance.
So it's like 11 then, right?
Oh, yeah, you're you're you see, but you did kind of walk in here
already as not an arcade repairman.
So wait, wait, did you change before there or did you leave?
OK, I or before I do this, I leave the bar and say, all right.
Is there an arcade machine in the bar?
Yeah, there's arcade.
I just...
I just pick up the hookie, I just...
You destroy him?
I just break it.
I just break the thing and then I'm just like, "Damn thing ate my quarter!"
And then I just walk out and then turn around.
It's like as fast as I left, I come back in, in the arcade.
I'm gonna have you roll Pa Simpson, Gif.
I'm gonna have you roll stealth.
Just to see if you can get away from people who are gonna not.
I got a three. I got a four.
A four.
You run around the corner.
Bouncers are chasing you.
[laughter]
They see your clothes
go from like behind the corner
out in front of them
and then they see you come out wearing different clothes.
Also you're completely out of breath.
[panting]
Hello fellas!
Oh boy!
I heard your arcade machine has gone broke.
What the fuck is this voice?
I'm the arcade repairman.
We know who you are, asshole.
Oh, good.
That means my work speaks for itself.
That means I'm one of the best arcade repairmen this side of Gun City.
Look.
And we're in space, so I don't know which side it could be.
They're already grabbing you, Billy.
here's your going to be j_j_ f_u_ out of the only as well as i have a good side
really good at the age of back or a bark at it is uh... into the parker confused
yeah i was wrong with a lot of your house is that so what's what i think i think
it's a little bit funnier they're literally confused
and they throw you have a good seat doors
They throw me back in.
Well, that worked out.
Why did they stand outside?
Our work here is done.
No, they stand inside the bar to stop people from going out.
Can I roll a performance to--
I want to do something really stupid.
Go on.
Because they threw me--
This is new.
I start rolling like Hot Rod.
I'm rolling down.
I'm aiming it up and going like, whoa!
OK.
What if I roll all the way into the employees-only room?
Wow, I love that so much.
You have to try.
Roll a performance.
all
well you're all enrolled and don't even look at it don't even look at it
like twenty
or was it
dot you get upset only sixteen don't even look at notes were rolled again
you're a little table rules
table rules i said don't even look at it
yeah
uh... the best part of that was a little sixteen of the way
it's not hot it's late in the work
and i said i was pretty fail
so yeah you like you're like
you're trying to do the spit thing, you think you're doing the hot rod thing
yeah but you're instead just like on your back going
whoa in the middle of the bar like a turtle
um here yeah clean that up um and uh as you're uh as you're doing
that um uh somebody else walks into the bar
um oh my god she ain't gonna stand by herself
Sorry, I don't know what to do about the clothes thing. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry a holder of her
Yeah, one second. Let me get back into my
Seat trap yeah, I really tried man shit rolls today. I
Sucked all the luck out. I got a 21st thing
on the most important check
It's true who is this
So we're dressing all describe while he's dressing her the most
Folks listening at home our Barbie is having a wardrobe malfunction
Hey, hey Cedar yes, I can't even be an eye over beautiful
Fran dresher looking
She I don't know if she looks like those close to my head be legs on camera. Yeah
Walks in she's chewing gum
She's sauntering up. She sees you on the floor yelling and rolling around and
She looks at you and she goes
Who are you?
I'm your worst night
I
Mean just roll persuasion to see if it's not bad
Okay
She's like all right. That's kind of weird. I didn't know you were gonna talk. Uh you're Patrick Yoda, right?
No.
Roll Deception.
Well he's dressed like the Arcade Repairman.
That's true.
So that's gotta be advantage.
How does she even recognize him?
He's a famous Yoda.
Also, if we're famous,
probably our Arcade Repairman thing is
pretty well known at this point.
Right?
It's not.
It's not not well known.
That's how you get an Arcade Repairman costume, is you go into Spirit Halloween
have a costume with our picture on it.
At this point, Blotas has like an actual disguise ability.
You need like a new get up.
Because it used to be you two would go in together as Arcade Repairman.
But he could like change his face and stuff.
Those were the days.
You just are still a Yoda just wearing an Arcade Repairman outfit.
Which is not an outfit.
At all. It's not like an outfit.
Well you just made it one. You said wearing one.
Yeah I did. I sure did.
Yes, so she said no. She doesn't believe you. She goes like, "All right." And she like
kind of looks back in the bar and she said, "Did those two big British guys, did
they go back there?" Yes. All right. Give me one second. So she goes and walks
through and goes... I follow her. Yeah. Like I'm floating towards her like a pie on a window. Yeah, I mean she's not even like
paying much mind to that and she's going in and you see it is a
bit of a longer hallway is probably why you were having trouble hearing and then
you get to the door and she knocks on the door and you hear now kind of muffled
yelling like British she kind of yelling I've been like like baby gag kind of
like pleading and when you hear that kind of like stop for a second as they
here and then like baby go get it I'll get it he gets a door and they see her
keep calm and chive on and they go miss sorry and she was like yeah no I think
that's enough dressing down the the baby who runs the bar you guys can go home
now and they go yes miss and they kind of walk out and she goes over and she
like starts like apologizing the baby dad and like daddy yada and they walk by
You to keep calm and shy ma and they kind of like shoulder check you a little bit as they rest you
I'm gonna steal something from their pocket do sleight of hand
This is gonna be a good roll
You're cursed add your sleight of hand seven
Like I had bad ones last they are going to assume you're just trying to grope them and not steal
What's your fucking problem mine?
I'm small and you're so big
You're so much bigger than me
big
uh... he's
uh... it doesn't help with the necessary it's lift you up
it
the
who brought it
yeah
any fully
but
the after the debate
yeah and then uh... you see the one she goes
jive on
knock it off
put down the man
or
and they go, "See you later."
Like he wants to do that again with you very badly.
- Jeez, God.
- And then they keep going and they walk away.
- They leave?
- Yeah.
And she comes up to you and she goes,
"Okay, my name is Janet Blowjob."
(laughing)
- And--
- What the hell kind of a name is that?
- Well, another fun James Bond reference
to Holly Goodhead from Moonraker, folks, right?
- Is that a reference to Holly Goodhead from James Bond?
- Oh my God, how'd you know?
- Wait, so you--
- What? - How did you know
it is a reference? - How is anybody
knowing anything anymore?
So she goes, "Look, my associates can come off a little bit."
- Bye. - He gave me uppies.
I don't care what he does.
He's my good friend now.
- I did see him give you uppies.
that looked fun.
But, if you guys are ever interested
in learning more, probably about,
you're investigating playtime, rumors been going around,
give me a call, and she gives you, like,
her SD card that you then put into your PSP
to load up somebody's contact information.
(laughing)
Let me know, and I can see if we can get
something for you going, okay?
I've got a lot of good friends to help you.
- So you can get me anything?
- Well, pretty much.
Can you get me a piece?
I'll do my best.
And she lifts you up and gives you a piece for a second.
She throws me into the ceiling.
Yes, you're stuck in the ceiling.
And she leaves, you're stuck in the ceiling.
Baby gag goes back, he's like,
(sighs)
"Oh, God, those two fucking guys.
Get out of my ceiling and we'll go back to you guys."
So you guys are in the crime lab.
You were told that you can go to the scientist area in the command center and
you get a call. You, Blotas, get the call. You're probably the point
person for this. From Belinda. You see it's Belinda's contact info is coming on
your PSP. Do you answer it? I answer it. You better answer it. And I motion to Ryo.
I'm just okay. Come here. Come here. I want to look at your phone call. Why do a phone call?
What can't do a fuck? Okay, come here. Come here
Come here. Okay
Go like feel like saying up. He's kind of unlocked a whole thing
Hello
Sorry, I thought I thought you guys were doing
We don't have the technology for that we're doing like we're doing like a yeah explain me
- We're doing like a 90s sleepover,
like he's on the other line secretly.
- Got it, got it, got it, got it, got it.
Love that, love that.
- No toss.
- I'm holding the receiver.
- No toss, you there?
- Yes.
Excuse me.
(laughing)
- No issue.
holding my giggles so hard on the phone
I'd like to order a pizza
I'm... Blotars pass the joint!
Stop!
I heard
that there was another attempted murder in the undercity
And that's Patrick was present for that.
Penis!
(laughter)
Excuse me.
Alright.
How does she respond?
This is always a trouble.
To penis fart, excuse me.
(laughter)
You have to imagine.
I make people, I try to make them.
Yeah, very realistic.
but okay it's now a good time yeah it sounded very sarcastic yeah it's a
really good time you got your voice back I see yeah look so I want to excuse me I
I want you guys to look a little bit more closely into I
Don't want you to how do I explain this I
Don't want you to ruffle any feathers in the under city. I do want you to be careful there
I'm twirling the
USB-c cable right I go. So what do you think of Ray William Johnson?
Formidable fighter and detective
I
Like anyone I
Know you like me but for like I mean like like is there any other information that you you've gathered from being at the scene
Yeah, I heard somebody likes you
Secret
- Tell her it's a guy though.
- It's a guy.
- That's lovely.
- Whose initials are?
- No, shut up.
(laughing)
- Okay, I can't tell you.
- Okay, I'm going to just level with,
I can hear both of you very clearly.
- Excuse me.
(laughing)
- They did this in Anchorman already, by the way.
- Who's Anchorman?
- Still funny.
I'm not going to say it's not funny again.
[LAUGHTER]
All she has to say.
I'll just tell you what she has to say.
No, so-- sorry, let me get--
OK, so basically, she just wants to know
if she has more information, any more information.
[MAKES FUNNY NOISES]
I can't hear you.
We're breaking up.
[MAKES FUNNY NOISES]
What?
You're breaking up with me?
So you do like me?
(laughing)
- Excuse me.
- She hangs up.
- I mean, I guess it's--
- All right, well.
- I dial back.
(laughing)
I like to order a pizza.
- She has a hang up.
- Yeah, a fart pizza hang up.
- Cool, so what do you guys wanna do?
There was other stuff we--
- We went to, we're gonna go to a scientist, right?
- Yeah, we wanna go to--
- Did she just text them that information?
- Wanna go to--
- She just texted, yeah, I would say--
We have a group chat with her.
No, well I guess maybe now you do.
Because you can't rely on--
What was the name of something, quiche?
Ebenezer quiche.
Ebenezer quiche, we're gonna go to Ebenezer quiche
up there, but first we have to go to the command center,
so let's head there.
And we bring the snake with us too.
But I hold it and not this fucking sex addict.
I'm done with it.
All right, listen.
Do I meet up with this?
That's the thing, do you guys relay this to Patrick?
My character--
Patrick is doing his own thing.
Just for some information,
my character has sworn off sex forever
because he washed his wiener in the sink,
he put hand soap on it, and it burned.
- Okay, all right.
- So Patrick-- - He will not be doing
that situation anymore. - Then you carry it.
- So what we can do then is, you guys will go there,
Patrick, Gad comes up to you and he says--
- Oh yeah, I'm still in the ceiling.
- Back in the bar, you're in the ceiling,
you're down from the ceiling now.
You have like a comical bandaid on your head
with some ice and a beer.
O'Neal's there as well, and Gad says,
"Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry about that.
I meant to there was a there was a just a mishap with some business associates
look so all I want from you is just to keep one was O'Neal was a I think
actually one of the I just want you to just keep it under wraps I can kick up
some money I can give you guys I got a wrap on my head right cuz your head was
in the ceiling I can also give you guys some lodging if you don't want to pay
those crazy fees. How about you get me some logic and I start making some beats. If you want I can get you a beat
like a beat maker machine what are those called? An MPC? Yeah an MPC. I'm gonna get
one of those okay I'm gonna get one of those I'm gonna get some lodging and
and and and what else hold on but if I'm giving you this I'm gonna call my boys
up real quick okay yeah yeah no I understand call it call you call the guys
call your friends. So he calls you guys, what do you guys see? Patrick Yoda, phone call,
what does your contact picture look like? I was just making sure. I literally was like
it's probably gonna be that right? Yeah do you guys pick up? We're at a baseball game
together. All in a row. What's up! You guys are on the zippy loop right now, so you're
You're on the train just yelling.
I'm at, I'm at, uh, Gaddy Up.
Gaddy Up.
I went there, um, somebody gave me uppies.
Yo!
I got uppies twice.
We basically had phone sex.
Damn!
Yeah.
Yeah, with some girl I can't remember.
Damn!
And she basically said, admitted on air that she liked me.
She wanted to slobber on his, I don't wanna say.
Well, that's insane.
Pretty awesome.
So, okay, so I'm getting, what am I getting?
I'm getting logic, I'm getting lodging, I'm getting,
oh yeah, baby Gads giving me all this crap.
- Whoa!
- What else do you guys want?
- As for money.
- Okay, also along with the lot,
put like a big chest of money in the lodge.
- Yeah, chest.
And we want it to be a lodge cabin.
- I got you on speaker now.
- Hey Gad, you there, BG?
- How you doing, fellas?
- It's me, RW.
I want you to give us...
Put your pants back on.
Yeah, oh, oh, sorry.
Sorry, I'm getting a fucking...
What the hell?
Sorry, I'm getting a fucking blowjob from a fart machine.
Is that right?
Do you have a guard?
Do you actually have your pants down?
No.
No, we're doing theater of the mind with Baby Geth.
They're really doing this.
I know them.
They're crazy.
So, look, I...
Okay, so lodging, logic, chest of money...
And we want you to capture a fart in a jar.
And a fuck
That's okay. I can do all you can hear me dialing and a numbers over the line for no reason
I'm just going to me. We're doing that to make it sound like I'm cussing you better give us the
fart jar
And a cheat and a pizza with all the toppings
I
Will get you
All of those things just please
How much how much we didn't say how much money was in the field to the brim with how much money you can get in?
I'm out in it. You want us to keep the investigation on the wraps. Okay. Love you. Bye. Bye. Bye
I'm here in the room with you. I'm saying it to them. Obviously
Peace out later player later player
You see after a while crocodile, okay, bye bye
You see O'Neal and like O'Neal's been kind of like happy and like enjoying his time. Oh, and I want this guy to
Fully healed mostly by you. What do you want though before? What does he want O'Neal? Yeah, I
Want all I'd love to have a love to have a girlfriend
That's sad
So O'Neal I don't I will say to you I don't know if that's gonna happen
happen tonight. This would also mean... You kind of look insane. This would also mean,
by the way, because nobody's going to pick up on this, but he's not a childless couple.
He's not a childless couple. So I will note that. He's not a what? Because that's who
Playtime was killing. Childless couples. You're a genius. I wrote the story. Oh yeah. It was
just figuring out how subtle to be with things, but like yeah. Yeah, well there's no way.
- Yeah, yeah, I know. - Now, wait.
If playtime was...
This is supposed to mean something.
(laughing)
I'm supposed to be thinking about all this money
I'm gonna get. - Perfect, perfect.
We're cutting away.
That is perfect.
- He is an orphan.
Playtime's an orphan.
- You guys arrive at the command center.
- Okay.
- And you see right away--
- Wait, where's the lodging gonna be?
- It'll be like, it'll be probably either,
I mean, you'll get your pick.
You can either be--
Oh, I'm going to get my pick.
Well, because you can either live above Gaddyup.
You can live above the bar.
Or he has basically like section 8 housing in the undercity.
I'm going to pick that.
Kendrick Lamarvod.
Yeah, Kendrick Lamarvod.
For sure.
I'm picking that.
So the White House?
Yeah.
So you guys will-- but because of that,
then it's it's the rent is gonna be like 100 tokens and we have a chest full of money.
We have a chest full of money. Hey, we got a chest full of money that is gonna be...
Brim levels of money. He's got to make something out of it but instead of
paying 500 tokens and you're still getting a thousand a day from Belinda
so you're gonna start seeing increases in your money this way. So that's
that's a way to look at it so we'll keep that in mind as you're basically
canceling your hotel stay at the 10 Seasons
and moving into Section 8.
It's a great move.
We're frugal.
Wait, we can't have two like GTA V?
Like GTA V, you could have two if you'd like.
We want two.
But then you've got to pay twice.
It's $500 a day and $100 a month, though.
It's a safe house.
So like--
You don't have to pay him $100 a day for lodging.
That's crazy.
That's our new-- it's our new crash pad.
You will be-- cut that to us.
We want to do--
So you guys are in-- then we'll work out the housing logic
later.
So you guys are, yeah, you guys arrive there
and Gummi Superior is like waiting for you
at the Zippy Loop stop.
- Okay.
- So, and he has his hands behind his back
and he says like, "Oh, you gentlemen, it's good to see you."
- What is he, who's his character?
Can he be that?
- Gummi Superior is the, that's pretty funny.
But I think I had him as,
if I can't find a guy for him,
I think this was him, basically.
- Okay.
- "Well, gentlemen, it's good to see you.
I heard you already had a major way through my my station took a little joy
ride through the through the space launcher throw the snake at him just
just let him just like put it in it not at him but like into his arms right
yeah he catches it you got a you got a little bit of a pest control issue it's
pretty cool yeah oh I see your phone's still on and I just wanted to say you
You sounded just like Buzz Lightyear right then.
Well, thank you.
Not you.
Oh, okay.
Me.
Well, I assume you want Ebeneezer to take a look at this.
Fucking duh.
Okay, well.
Where's Ebeneezer look like?
Oh, we're not talking to him on the phone.
Before.
Excuse me.
And we want a poop pizza.
you talk with Ebenezer I want you fellas to come with me to the command center
just wanted to have a conversation. You said come with you okay? Come center?
Come center? Alright we'll come with you. The command center? Alright let's go.
He hands the stake off to one of the crew members who then takes it
presumably to Ebenezer's lab and you guys walk through the command center you
see all the different like ship crew members working on different things and
Yada yada you get to the main area the command center. We were looking out at all of space and like in your see gun city
You could see like the like sort of like
Luminescent like fog just like of gun city the only like bright spot on the whole planet
And you see ebomb - right and it's just like gray gross kind of morass
That's perfect. I love that and
He says I
I just wanted to talk with you a little bit more about your...
So that's not gonna...
That's gonna defeat the purpose.
Oh, not even visible.
I wanted to talk with you a little bit more about your investigation.
I know you're looking into playtime and I understand why.
He took your boy, presumably.
That's obviously very important, I understand.
But I just wanna make sure...
that there's some clarity as to...
what is probably actually going on here and I want you to know
to help make all this go much more smoothly
okay so go ahead and tell us
am I still on the pocket?
yeah you could be on the phone. Wait hold on can we call our friend
I'm muted. This sounds important
can we call her boy?
And I got a baby named Leo.
(laughing)
Ya ba dee doo, ya ba dee doo.
Now you, I'm a big fan of King Leo.
I like what he's doing here.
New sovereign state, right?
This is a good thing, something to challenge Gun City.
I don't know if you boys are too young
to remember the Vampire Wars,
and you guys were not too young.
You guys were in the Vampire Wars
in the very first invasion.
I remember it.
I go.
That was the one where I were the pig.
We were too young.
That was our friend Colin the pig.
Colin the pig.
Oh yeah, Colin the pig.
But you guys swore to never talk about him or I think or it again maybe because of how
traumatic it was when you lost Colin.
Yeah, we were too young to remember.
Yep.
On my end, where did I lose anybody?
I'm 15.
I'm moving into the new place.
Just don't worry about, he's finishing something.
On my end all you can hear is "Ahhhhhh!"
You're already muted.
I already said you were muted.
Wow.
Wait, who is this guy who's talking?
Is this Evan?
I don't know.
Wow. Wait, who is this guy who's talking? Is this... Gummi Superior. He's the head of the ship.
He says, "The vampire wars were pretty bad. I should know. I was a war hero in those
wars. What I will say is that I think we might be on the precipice of another kind
of war between Leo and Gun City, between the Empire of New England and Gun City.
And why am I talking about this?
This doesn't have to do with playtime.
Well, it does.
Because what's happening here
is you're being sent on little errands
to go take care of a supposed serial killer.
And somebody's calling me.
It's very distracting.
Take care of a supposed serial killer?
I don't think that's what's happening here.
How do I explain this to you?
When Belinda hired you guys, what information did she give you about playtime?
Well, she said she had a crush. She wouldn't say who it was.
But it was heavily implied that it was me.
So nothing?
Yes.
And she said we couldn't have a pizza.
[laughter]
What I think is happening here is that Leo the Collector, or King Leo, has a unique opportunity to build a world without crime.
You see what I'm saying? This is a new sovereignty. He's accepting the undercity
because he has to. Because he feels like he has to. And rather than taking care of
that problem, he draws the attention to this serial killer. I don't think this
serial killer is a serial killer at all. I think it's a sort of a happenstance,
right? This is this is all just a show. And what's happening here is that the
under city is after you boys. Piss, Johnson, Yoda. These names mean something now. You're
not just three nobodies, you are legends in Gun City.
That's fuckin' right.
I think, why would a serial killer who's been murdering everybody take one boy? Unless,
suddenly there was a reason to take the boy, because maybe they wanted people to be interested
investigating maybe certain people want you to go deeper and deeper and dig
deeper until you're just a drive-by murder in the under city just a three
heroes died on vacation they can't kill you when you're I start crying when I
- It's a fancy hotel.
- It's like, I just start sobbing,
just the idea of someone dying on vacation.
(laughing)
- Now, now, don't cry, don't cry.
- Let alone a hero.
(laughing)
- I want you to keep doing what you're doing.
I think it's good work.
It sounds like you're trying to figure out what's going on,
and that's good, but what I want you to think about is,
if you had a chance to destroy the criminal underworld
before it even became a thing.
If we could destroy it in this nation
and not let things turn out like Gun City,
we could create a nation of peace.
We could start here.
All I ask of you is to just,
as you're investigating this serial killer,
let me know what's going on,
because I actually have the armed forces.
I have veterans who fought in the vampire wars
who followed me up here.
And if we get enough, you know,
evidence or circumstantial even,
about what's actually going on down there,
I can bust that whole thing wide open
and slaughter every last one of them.
And you boys would get your boy back
because you know that's where it is.
It's in the undercity, it's huge-ass facts,
as your boy, that has to be what it is.
I hear somebody raising their hand.
- I've been on speakerphone this whole time with Baby Gant.
(laughing)
- He just heard all of this shit.
- Damn.
- Maybe you guys like, whoa.
(laughing)
- Sir, yes sir, we'll kill all the whiteys downstairs.
- No, that's not, no, well.
- Heard you loud and clear.
- I'm saying to get me evidence, work with me,
Don't worry about Belinda, keep giving her bullshit, that's what she's giving you.
I can get you guys your son back.
He's not a part of the crime syndicate.
He's just kind of...
He could relay this information.
He is obviously indebted to them and O'Neal is one of his guys.
There's sort of a like, you're part of a smaller group kind of thing going on it seems like,
but you still have to kick up to the actual larger crime syndicate.
Can I roll insight on this and see just what I can glean?
Yeah, absolutely.
Be careful with that.
Use the six die.
Can I roll glean?
Can I reuse Caleb's die?
Oh my god, a nat 20.
That was a good move.
What do you glean?
Get this away from me.
Put that back in the bag.
I'll trade it up.
Actually, we'll just all use mine.
I'll trade it up. Actually, we'll just all use mine.
I need to think about what you get to know with a natural 20.
All of it.
About his motivations here. Give me a second.
First thing, he believes what he's saying.
Okay.
He's not pulling your leg.
Do you actually believe that bullshit?
[Laughter]
- Hey buddy, this is between you and I.
(laughing)
- He obviously is playing up certain aspects of it
based on hunches because he wants you guys
to help him rid the pleasure palace of the under city
basically entirely, not because he knows for sure
Huge Ass Vax has your kid.
He just thinks that seems way more likely
than some rogue serial killer who he thinks
is just a circumstance of there being a criminal underworld.
It's like this guy is not, he didn't take your kid.
Why would you think he did?
- He has not seen the Giants.
- It was just blamed on play time
just because it was convenient.
What else you got?
The fucking 20, good God.
What else can you?
- He has to know 20 things.
- Yeah.
- I'm just thinking 'cause he, so.
- Okay, with that 20, does Baby Cat definitely hear that?
I mean, that doesn't carry over, but I would say--
- I don't know.
- But he did--
- It makes the story very interesting.
- Baby Gadd did hear it.
You did that, and this guy said okay,
and I did not have him like check on that.
How could he?
He just trusted you guys.
So, what else did you get with a 20?
- Favorite color?
- Blue.
That's my favorite color, stupid.
(laughing)
- You're gonna get hacked, bro.
- You shouldn't give information out like that.
- Yeah, I'm sorry.
- That's a number one security question.
- It's always what's your favorite color
and who was Arnold?
- Yeah.
- You also...
(laughing)
- Who was Arnold to you?
- You also can sense in how he's talking
that he is extremely nervous about his life.
about Huge Ass Facts, not about a criminal enterprise,
but about Huge Ass Facts specifically.
When he said his name, that, with your 20 insight,
you were like, he either has a crush on this guy,
or he's really, really scared of him, his enterprise.
All that sounded like abstracts,
compared to like the kind of stank he put on that.
- He stunk it up.
- Made a stank.
- And I would also say that when he talked--
- He went like, "Huge ass facts."
- He made a base face when he said it.
He said, "Huge ass facts."
- Also when he talked about his admiration for Leo,
that's not true at all.
He does not admire Leo.
He does feel like, from what you can tell,
that this is an opportunity to create a nation
that he would like.
- Okay.
- One that wouldn't have wars, he does not want war,
but what does it mean to basically try to do
what he's trying to do?
- Genocide.
- He's a Hitler guy.
- Yeah.
Leftoid he's a lefty. He's basically he's a lot more a lot more like our stall a worse
Trillions of people that and if you honestly if you don't believe that by the way fucking up unsubscribe right now
That's right. Do not don't say no one else. Do not do not give me another give you like Stalin
Do not give me another fucking dollar. Yeah, also your cringe and your cringe and this
Okay
Um, yeah. And if you like Hitler, stay tuned.
And we'll end it there. We'll end it there. I think we should end it there.
Okay, now you relay all of this to me over the phone so that baby Gadd knows.
We already did it. No, like the info, all the stuff that he said about...
Caleb left. All the stuff that he said about how much he doesn't like me or...
He just went to the bathroom. We're done. Okay. It's over.
Bye bye. Bye family. Bye family.
(upbeat music)
Yeah!