As the end of the week approached, we needed to act fast and get this heist going.
The plan, I thought, was pretty good.
The building sits in downtown Gunn City, the I-Cup headquarters.
It is one of those older models that has four ground floor entrances with sliding doors.
It's a charity building, so there's no immediate security protocol.
That was disabled in a cost-cutting measure back when ICUP was under Papi Chuko's Technoslime.
However, once inside the building, there were certain security and authentication measures
that anyone would need to get past private security hired for the affair.
Since the guys told me girls and frogs don't count, our crew was five people.
That means I needed to get six more.
I looked high and low and pretty much everywhere else as quick as I could, and lucky me, I found
the best heist guys around.
This is Sullivan's Eleven.
Matrix Biedermann, E-Bomb's greatest hacker.
He can turn any security system into an insecurity system, because it's full of holes.
So also into Swiss cheese, that's another way you could say it.
That's right, I'm the most devious hacker in the world.
I was bricking systems since I was in diapers at age 8.
This seems like a tough job, but my skill set will be more than enough to hack into the
mainframe and delete the force field program.
Space Belden. He's an alien who can read minds and control us puny E-Bomb rings.
I'm glad he's on our side.
I am not from here. I am an alien. I understand things you can't comprehend.
JFK was killed by Lee Harvey Oswald. Frogman, I detect you are thinking about pussies.
I will use these powers to read the minds of the guards and find out when they need to go to the bathroom.
Maximum Watson. This guy is basically a living EMP bomb.
He radiates electromagnetic pulses like a...
I guess an EMP bomb is the only thing that does that.
The name's Maximum Watson and I'm the only electronic being on this
godforsaken planet that can deactivate the godforsaken robot security system in
this godforsaken building.
Stand back and let me work or I'll zap ya!
The Class Clown. A man of mystery. Nobody knows his real name or even his
roll in the heist but we all know one thing his his funny ass sends people's
sides into orbit. Alright so here's what we're gonna do I go slap a couple
kick-me signs on the guards after they start kicking each other I get inside
the control room there I will disarm them with my boyish humor and coerce them
into a game of oogie-cookie pants around the ankles racing to blast on a
mrs. Fields cookie I keep in my cargo pocket you know guy stuff that's when
you all strike when no one's looking at the camera.
And please, make sure you hurry up.
I'll buy you as much time as I can,
but I really don't want to eat that cookie at the end.
- The Home Planet Twins, master acrobats.
You might think the count is two people,
but twins, scientifically, each only count as half a person.
- We are the Home Planet Twins.
We come from a planet called Home Planet.
We will cartwheel and somersault our way into the vault
to help steal the money.
That's our job in the heist.
We like candy. We love to eat candy.
And our extra special member of the crew, Drake.
Yeah baby it's Drake. Oh I'm so cool. Listen to my song. Hotline Bling, Spotted Eye.
Along with the rest of Sullivan's Eleven, we were all in position. The heist was finally ready to begin.
Oh no! What's happening?
There's a laser, it looks like, right near the entrance of the building and oh no!
Everybody's walking into it one by one!
All the people who are new to the team are all walking right into the laser!
Oh no, Matrixpeederman, look out!
Try using bullet time!
This laser is hacking into my body and fishing out my guts!
AHH!
SpaceBeldon, what are you doing?
Using my extraterrestrial intelligence, I detect that I am dying, Frogman.
And that Steven Paddock acted alone.
Ooooooh!
Maximum Watson, stop!
You're gonna overload!
Into the laser!
Not the class clown!
There ain't nothing funny about that!
Oh!
It's curtains for the class clown!
Gettin' sent up to the big principal's office in the sky!
twins oh no two for the price of one oh no a laser
and our extra special member of the crew drake
oh no i'm dying i'm dying no no no
oh i i just remembered i was supposed to
i'm supposed to turn off that razor for the uh
for the heist.
Well, well, well, anyway, uh, uh, we got this. It doesn't matter.
This is where Ray comes in.
The private security is, uh, is, uh, automation. It's robotic.
So he would be able to hack in and make sure that any accosting from the security force passes by us.
However, we need to be able to get him into the first floor control room to make that happen.
Barry Gee, lucky for us, knows a guy on the inside who owes him a favor, after inspiring
him to be an entrepreneur. Barry will meet this guy, Goofus Gallant, describe Ray's profile,
and have Ray carted into the security room. Meanwhile, Blotoss will be scoping out for
each of these three identities, Doug Jerk, Stephen A. Smith, and Stinky Eric. These are
The three people who frequented the building have crypto credentials.
Once he recognizes one of them, he will know that he is the one who is trying to make the
transfer for the crypto money so that it can be reinvested.
You have to dispatch of them and assume their role.
Then follow Fatima into the security area where the vault is.
The dispatching of one of these guys is where Travis comes in.
Travis will lead the target away from Fatima, handle it discreetly, and then contact Barry
Gee to signal that they both make their way toward the vault too.
Travis will trail Blowtoss and Fatima through the vents and follow the blueprint while Barry
Gee takes a route through the plumbing in the girls bathroom.
That way when they get to the security section underground, should anything go awry, Travis
can jump down with his dual pistols and dispatch the security system and Barry Gee can use
the love slime bomb to destroy the vault door. Patrick Yoda meanwhile... well actually I wasn't
sure if he'd still have brain damage by the time we needed to do the heist so I was just
gonna sort of have him work the floor and if he saw something suspicious kind of yell ice
cream into the walkie talkie but uh so right now he'll just be working the floor looking
for any sort of variables that could happen.
Mommy Goodlegs will be running interference with Fatima if need be.
She bugged her during their conversation, so hopefully we can get some information from there.
Finally, once we are able to download the money, we have to leave.
If nothing goes wrong, Bluetoss will send a signal and everyone will leave their stations.
And we'll head on out of there.
If something does go badly...
Oh, fuck.
I guess we'll have to figure it out.
and me as always I'm the getaway driver and I was told that if I leave without
them I would have to wear a dress and I don't really want to do that very much so
I'm just gonna stay put until the job is done they said otherwise I'll probably
die so I'll just hang out here so this is it this is the heist you guys have
the
I mean, is that?
Hey Patrick, Yoda, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Okay.
All right.
I'm fine, Bar.
Oh, no.
Okay.
So, all right.
Wow.
That's a little better too.
Okay.
I'm making a new one.
I'm making a note to become like a brain scientist later in my life and try and figure out, try
and study what the difference between the two places I hit him was that caused the ice
cream bar and I'm fine bar.
Can we just try to see, okay, Patrick, what's your favorite color?
I guess green, like my skin.
Okay, all right.
All right, good.
All right.
I think we should probably just make our way in there now
I just are running as fast as I can I'm really okay
See him running and I yeah, I'm gonna be the first one in there I'm just way too fast for you
I'm trying swinging my arms in front of me trying to like trying to happen. It's not working
Okay speed skill
I mean, it's just your movement. I teleport ahead of your move speed. Yeah, I mean you do have teleportation. Yes, I
Mean, are you guys actually are you guys racing? You guys racing to get in there? Yeah
All right, cool. So you guys are racing to get in there Travis and and
Patrick and Barry Gee are you guys just walking in there normally or you guys also racing? I'm moseying you're moseying
Okay, we got a mosey. Yeah, I'm walking walking normal style. I'm walking chill. I'm chilling out
the
I'm in a suit too.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I mean that's up to you.
You can be the suit.
You're still like drooling all over the place.
It's like...
You have two lines of snot that are just going directly into your mouth.
I have snot but I'm aware of it.
I'm aware of it.
So I'm like snorting it, trying to snort the snot back up.
Yeah, that's all in slow motion.
I'm trying to look like a cool
grind set guy.
Also there's stuff coming out of your ears too.
ripping out of your ears.
Yeah, mm-hmm.
So yeah, you guys go inside, and it is sort of as Sullivan described, based on the blueprints.
It has a fountain in the middle that is with this-- right now it has Papi Chuco on it.
There are plans to reassemble it eventually, you know, now that it's no longer under Papi
Chuco's Techno Slime Corporation.
But yeah, it's a fountain just shooting out little squirts of water that used to be Techno
the
Yeah. What? I hope that's just his last name and not his full name.
Oh, me too. But his full name is Gallant Goofus. So you can sort of look through the directory,
you can maybe you have his number. I don't know. How did you get in touch with Gallant Goofus?
I contacted them through the most exclusive way I contact everyone I know,
through my public DMs of my social media accounts.
Okay, cool. So does he know, is he going to meet you down there then? Is that the plan?
Or are you trying to be secret about it? What's your plan of meeting with him then?
Yeah, he can just meet us down there. I'm sure if they bring the whole crew,
they'll be chill and we'll do a deal that won't go down badly.
Yeah, for sure. Bloat toss. Meanwhile, your job right now is to try to scope out and figure out
which of the people with the crypto credentials is going to be working with Fatima. Fatima's
office is on the fourth floor. She would presumably come down to the first floor to meet with whoever
that crypto person is. Obviously, if you want to try to make it up to the fourth floor and intercept
her, you can too, but you might be better off trying to spot who the crypto person is either
outside or in the lobby here, and then make sure you direct Travis in the right direction after
that. So I think that it'll probably go down in the lobby, isn't it? The exchange? I'm going to
to hide in the trash can in the lobby.
Okay.
So yeah, we're going to have to do, we'll have to do, and I'm going to put that my
ear against the inside of the trash can.
Like I'm listening through a wall to make sure I hear everything.
All right.
We'll do some roles for that in a second then.
Um, Travis, I don't know if you have any, I mean, obviously you're sort of
awaiting orders, but I wasn't sure if there was a, anything you wanted to do
or a game plan you had in mind in the meantime, um, I'm whistling.
Great.
And you've been practicing your shot, right?
Do you feel in control of your chimp arm now?
Or where do you think that's at?
Yeah, I've been feeling pretty good about it.
I've been clutching my balls during my jerk-off sessions
and nothing's been torn off yet.
Okay, so this is sort of, yeah, good.
Alright, so I just wanted to make sure, I wanted to see where that was at.
And, yeah, Ray, you're kind of waiting on Barry Giesley here
Because Barry he's going to meet with that guy.
So I guess you're just kind of posting up or is there anything else
you're you're handling in the lobby while we wait for that to initiate?
I'm just lamp and smoking a cigarette.
Love that.
But I'm also smoking.
I'm smoking a cigar.
Oh, I'm smoking too.
I'm smoking too in the trash.
You guys are running.
I'm trying to.
I'm trying to smoke.
I'm trying to smoke, but every inhale that I take makes me throw up.
Yeah, I'm smoking.
I'm smoking a cigar in the trash can.
You have to go ahead and ruin smoking all you want,
but I'm just normal smoking, having a really enjoying myself.
What's what did I what do we ruin?
He's vomiting. You're in a trash can.
What's wrong with that?
Um, so, Patrick.
OK, so, Patrick, you're working for. OK, cool.
So, Bergie, yeah, Gallant Gallant Goofus
does meet you down there.
You can see he's a so he works as one of this
one of the sort of like human security guides,
which means that all his job is to do is to just monitor the automations.
So, yeah, you see Gallant Goofus and he walks down to see you, Barry Gee.
And he says, he says, oh, hi there, Barry.
And he's like sort of like walking out.
He's like super excited to see you.
Oh, what's up, my man? How you been doing?
How's your whole business doing?
How's business?
Well, you know, I still have my day job, but I'm taking all the advice
you said and put my money in a few of those funds.
And I'm really watching some growth and I have a few investments, a few friends of mine.
I really tried to look for the guys who had the same vision you were talking about that go get her spirit.
And I really think that something's going to come of it.
So I owe you everything.
I owe you everything.
Yeah, I'm following memories because I meet so many losers who want to make their own business.
So yeah, you're the, you're going to sell poops, right?
You're going to sell like, like the Amazon of poop.
You're like the Amazon to have poop.
That's what you want it to be, right?
Anyway, I'm here for
And I saw the tell them why am I here for he's my assistant yeah
It's waiting in the car. I'm calling him. Yeah
There are this guy's
Yes, you told me to let Ray Ray into the control booth
for the security drones
In my I'm not on speaker, right?
Yeah, okay
Yeah, I'm sure you'll get your business going. I'm sorry. I'm hanging up on you. Anyway, is there any chance we can get into the
You know your security system without you you telling your bosses just like yeah, of course
That's the whole thing entrepreneurial spirit do it yourself. You'll let anybody tell you no nobody
Yeah, yeah, I got you. You can tell me no you can tell me no, whatever you want
Okay, I need you to shut up now. I got my another young who wants to learn
You know for someone as successful as you it's my friend railway William Johnson. He's a demon or whatever. It's fine
You can just let him in he won't kill you I think oh
Well, how do you do mr. Ray
What's up?
I'm his young. This is my mentor great. Tell me your business. My business is
Well, I'm going to be the Amazon for poop oh
Oh, okay. What a small world.
Anyways, I got to take three minutes at the same time.
Right.
No total deception for that guy either, because he just is just happy to believe
anything.
Um, uh, okay.
So yeah, Mary, yeah, you can, you can now make your way to the bathroom.
Um, um, you know, you might want to wait for, where's the women's bathroom, by the
way?
I know I'm a man.
I just want to know just so I don't go there.
Oh, of course.
It's just, no, I get it.
I get it.
You got to know where everything is.
That's how you stay ahead of the game.
Well, it's towards the back and, and, uh, well, where you, you make a left
and then there's sort of two ways to go over as a women's room and the men's
room, and you're going to go towards the women's room while you're not going
to go towards it, but now you know where it is.
Yeah.
It's so, it's so embarrassing.
I did that once at a sushi place.
I was, I was so embarrassed.
All right.
I'll show you.
I walk away very fast.
Yeah.
Um, okay.
So yeah, he's gonna Gallagher's gonna turn to you, right?
He'd be like, come on, I'll show you where the security is.
It's great.
It's a really nice room.
It's air conditioned.
There's only one other guy in there named Lance.
He's chill, though.
He's awesome.
And he starts leading you back there.
Can I be holding my he's going to holding my hand?
Do you want to hold your hand?
I can't tell where I'm going unless you hold my hand.
My eyesight's not that good these days.
Roll up. Persuasion.
disclosing his eyes.
He's not sure if that's okay to do.
My eyes are completely closed.
16.
I just, I can't see a damn thing.
[laughter]
He's like, "Oh, well, ah." He holds your hand.
He's like, "Okay, well, I guess, just let's keep going this way."
Then he's like, holding your hand and dragging you,
leading you to the security room.
Cool, okay.
Blotas, I want to resolve your hiding in a trash can.
Yes.
if you're doing that now, there are still security bots that are more or less active.
So, can I tell, before I sneak in, can I tell by looking at the security bots if they
have thermal scanners or anything like that? Yeah, what I would do, because we don't have,
I would say that this is kind of a, let's just do either intelligence or arcana, I think, to sort of
assess the the like technical aspects of these things.
All right let's see here. Okay 10. Yeah um yeah I mean you can tell that
they're they're they're not not advanced. They might
have thermal it might not be great but it also might be good enough
for the trash cans. You can't really tell.
It's like but what you know is that they definitely have things that are beyond
just like sensing things right in front of them.
Okay because I was going to try to turn invisible and just walk in and climb
I'm
to have the stealth into the fountain. Okay that's fine. Okay roll stealth.
8. Alright, Scriba you fucked this up. Cannonball into the fountain. The water goes everywhere.
And not only does the water go everywhere but there are a bunch of coins in the fountain
like when people throw it into Wish and all the coins fly out and they catch the sunlight
and they flash in every guard's eyes.
Oh, yeah, okay.
The robots are gonna come over and go, "You can't be in the fountain."
I do.
I'm like, "Hey, get your hands off me!"
Like, even though they're not touching me and I kind of like slink away.
But I'm also, I'm slinking away, but I'm not going straight away.
I'm kind of looping around to go towards the back of the building and hoping they don't
notice.
Okay, yeah, no, I think that's fine.
I think it's more of just, they're just, they're pretty simply programmed.
So it's like an aberration, okay, the aberration ceases, okay.
So we'll come back to that.
Okay, Patrick Yoda, you are working the floor with, right now with Travis, who's also sort of chilling at the floor.
You hear a "tss" from your PSP, and it's Mommy Goodlegs.
And she says, "Patrick, Patrick, come in!"
the
*laughter*
I think that I'm fine.
I think that I'm fine,
but I don't know I'm saying
bar after everything.
Because Cameron, or Blotus
kicked me in the head or something earlier.
And it's kind of like, made me
a little bit loopy again.
Patrick, okay,
I need to ask you something.
This is part of the mission.
Okay?
Eagle legs?
What?
Mom?
Eagle legs?
Okay, can you put-
Is there anybody else on- near you?
I'm here, I'm right next to him.
Oh, okay, the sociopath. Okay, so-
Good.
Um, okay.
Hi.
Hi, hi Travis.
Hello!
Okay, I looked into
who was looking into the building and using the Papi Chuko pseudonym.
I think-
I close the call and I start playing Ridge Racer on the PC.
Yeah, it's just...
Yeah, that just like doesn't get resolved.
Let's go back to Juvio.
Very gee.
So you're heading towards the girls bathroom.
Are you just going to rush in there without waiting for the guards to be rerouted or deactivated
or are you going to wait outside?
I just want to know that.
There's women's bathroom guards in this building?
No, there's just guards in general who if they...
They're not very woke, dude.
And so if they see you going towards that lady's bathroom, they're going to be pretty
PO'd.
Okay.
So you can sneak and you can maybe make it, but I just wanted to see if you were going
to wait to see if Ray William Johnson can turn it deactivated or not.
I want to make an awesome sneak maneuver.
So I'm going to head to where the bathrooms are.
I'm going to get into the male bathroom and as soon as the door closes, there's going
to be a puddle of little magnets that crawl from under the door into the woman's bathroom.
I like that.
I become a man right as I walk in. So I'm still a man in the woman's bathroom.
Cool. Good. Okay. Yeah, I think, yeah, you're able to turn to Slither and then Slither
is going to give you, you're going to have lower DC check on any sort of stealth checks you make.
So I would say roll stealth. So you turn into the puddle in the men's bathroom. I mean, you could
Just go into a stall, just do that.
And hit the stealth button.
You can just do that.
You can just turn into a puddle in the men's bathroom.
You get advantage, so roll again.
Just because you're a slither.
23, there we go.
You kind of make yourself into a very thin strip of liquid and just sort of slide along the wall.
And slip into the girls room.
And do you...
Yeah.
nobody in there right now. It's pretty early in the day.
People haven't started their some of them. There might be
people coming in to do their PB routine, but it's not like
lunch hour or anything. So you can turn back into a man for
now. Ray, you're being brought to the security room. I'm being
led by led. I apologize. Yeah by hand you're in there by a
gals. Goof is gallant gallant goof and he says, okay, here it
is
to the bathroom and leave you two at it."
And he gives you another big wink and he leaves.
You see Lance and Lance is just sort of like, Lance sort of looks like Carl from Aqua Teen
Hunger Force.
And maybe he sounds like him too.
And he's sort of like, "What do you, did you want me to show you how this works or what?"
I need you to show me around this entire place.
But the thing is, I can't see very well.
So I'm going to need you to hold me.
You need to be led by hand?
Yeah.
Okay, yeah.
You're not the first one.
I mean, it's not too much.
We got the control panel over here.
This is where we control all the robots.
Then we got the monitors over here so we can see what's going on.
Can't see in the ladies room though.
I've tried.
And yeah, I mean, that's about it.
I mean, we got a, do you want to, I got snacks too.
Do you have like maybe a a giant like 128 ounce soda?
Yeah, hold on one second
He goes underneath the the control panel and pulls up the opposite. He pulls out a big big ultra big gulp
Okay. Oh, this is oh, this is gonna hit the spot. This is gonna be good. Yeah. Did you want this? Yeah
Yeah, come on hand it over. Okay, you can have a couple sips, but you know, this is my lunch
This is my dinner and it's my lunch and dinner for tomorrow too. As soon as it touches my my hands, uh, it it flies
Because my hands are so so clammy from holding a boy's hand, right?
I was getting so nervous and sweaty the soda flies and the soda gets all over every single piece of every panel
Oh, no, what the fuck? Oh, i'm
I'm, sorry, you make me a little nervous
Oh, no. Oh, I mean you make me nervous too, but this is terrible and uh,
uh yeah all the robots are they're they're going to be out of commission for some time um
can you go get go get gala scooping go go figure figure this out oh god
oh okay all right i'm getting nervous though and he starts holding your hand and leading you over
uh yeah the robots are in uh are in a bad place so you blow toss you can now hide in the trash
Yeah, so I yeah I was I I did the thing where I was circling around the back and I did but
My intention was never going to go in the back door
I was just gonna circle around and try to jump in the fountain again, and I'm not aware that the robots are
So I just jump back in the fountain and then I go inside and I climb into the trash can and I light up a big
Fat cigar and nice smoke is coming out of the trash. I tap in Morse code on the trash can all the robots stopped working
*laughter*
Yeah, you learned that from working Morse Code.
Working for the Bureau of...
I start crying,
because the Morse Code is really scary.
I think it's a robot that's coming.
He's so scared he thinks it's rain.
*laughter*
I think it's the trash can rolling
down a hill.
*laughter*
Okay, yeah, so,
meantime,
um,
robots are shooting at the train.
*laughter*
Uh, Patrick Yoda,
you see Fatima
coming down the stairs.
Um... I take the PSP
out and I hit, I dial *6-9*
because I realize I've fucked up
something. Okay.
*laughter*
Yes, who would you like
to contact? *laughter*
Doesn't *6-9* call people?
Does it call the person back
who called you or is that star six seven? No, star six nine is the anonymous phone call.
Oh, star six seven. I hit star six seven then. No, no, no, star six seven is what you hit
if you want to do an anonymous call. Star six nine I think does call back the person. Not
on my phone. Okay, then I hit star six seven and then I-
Yeah, it refers to last call of turn. You're right. You're right. Thank you. Let's make
sure. It's star six nine and I don't call anybody
because I got the numbers mixed up. You were actually right. It is star six nine.
It is star six nine. Yeah
No, I already said it's different on my phone. So you call still you call back mommy
And she says okay. Can you can you talk now? Is everything okay on your end? I
Said you guys just some trouble
What this is mommy you mommy good legs my mommy
No, not your mommy. Your mommy's a Yoda. All right, I chokeslam Patrick Yoda and
take his PSP.
[laughter]
Hello?
Travis, okay.
Here's the thing.
Fatima doesn't know, but in the security vault, the person who was looking for me, or was
looking for the building, that was...
Sorry, wait, hold on. I want to make sure I get the name right.
I want to make sure I get the name right.
Dr. Toulateralis.
I almost forgot the name.
I thought it was going to be something hard to pronounce.
I gasp really hard, but I don't know who it is.
You might not know who he is. But he worked with the boys.
But he worked with the boys on helping-
FARRRK
Uh, yeah, sure.
Um, glad the chokeslam didn't put you totally out of commission, Patrick.
It actually kinda helped me, a little bit.
*laughter*
Seems like it.
Also, you're on speak-a-phone and everyone around us can hear us.
Alright, I rip his mouth off.
*laughter*
*unintelligible*
He just met his lips.
*laughter*
There's something inside-
I seal his mouth.
Um...
There's something in the vault
besides the money.
He wasn't able to tell me what it was,
but just be on your guard.
That's all.
Okay.
With you right now, what are you?
I'm i'm sort of been listening to fatima. It looks like she's gonna go meet
No, I mean what else what else is going on?
Oh, um
Oh, I mean I had I I I have a I have a son now that was a recent
Good he was born between the episodes. Yeah. Goodbye
And uh, yeah, so Fatima is coming down now so Patrick or Travis you can notify
Up to Fatima. I run up to Fatima immediately
I pick up the trash can and I hold it upside down so that blowtoss falls out. I run up to Fatima and I say
Oh shoot one of the three generous millionaires who gave us so much money it's so wonderful to meet you
Oh, you don't have a mouth, okay, that's funny
*unintelligible*
and uh...
when...
when the trash can got turned upside down and I fell out
I landed cigar first
and the cigar went into my mouth
and I involuntarily swallowed it
and I just instantly turned completely green
*laughter*
and I'm very sick
okay
well you also see walking in
Stephen A. Smith
*laughter*
oh my god
*moaning*
So Travis, you would remember that from the dossiers as well.
Patrick Yoda right now seems to be entertaining Fatima.
So I would say this is an opportunity where you can apprehend Stephen A. Smith,
blow toss, you could turn into Stephen A. Smith and make the transfer of the money.
Okay, I'm gonna immediately turn into him.
Yeah, you guys can kind of like make eye contact and know exactly kind of how this should go
or know that you have to do something.
Okay.
Um...
Excuse me, sir.
You dropped five quarters.
What?
Behind you.
No, I didn't.
Yes, you did.
Roll deception with advantage.
That's fine, but then I will be gone.
I have to roll deception for that?
Yeah.
I mean, it's either that or nothing.
Right?
Okay, fine.
I'm sorry, give me one second.
No worries.
You get advantage on it though.
Oh yeah.
Nice, 21.
You know what, I feel like I had about 5 quarters in my pocket the other day.
He starts looking around on the ground.
I rip his head off.
Yeah, right.
Okay.
(laughter)
Alright, I mean, he is a civilian.
So you will be- and he is also
distracted, so just roll
Krav Maga 2000 with
advantage.
While this is going on, I go over to
the front desk of the hotel and I-
(laughter)
I go to the-
Casino?
Casino!
I go to the- I don't think it's either of those things.
And then I go to a hotel.
Yeah.
He's been at a hotel the whole time.
Every, every, uh, every casino I've ever been to has been a hotel.
So I just assumed that there was a front desk here.
This is not a casino nor a hotel.
We're at a charity event? Right.
Um, so- This is no event.
We're just in a charity building.
Right, charity event at a casino slash hotel.
flash hotel yeah not just like the room the place to the desk that has markers
screen kiosk at the McDonald's I go to the I go to wherever they have markers
and I draw a new mouth on him.
And I walk down the aisle,
and I see the bride.
I draw a new mouth on my face, so I can speak again.
Patrick walks out of the store,
walks out of the store,
is now called the store.
He's in the store!
I don't even know where we are.
I'm so disoriented now.
I was in a casino!
I get a message from Wawa.
He goes to a Staples.
I suffocate because we're in outer space.
*laughter*
Okay, cool.
Yeah, you draw on a mouth.
So Pat goes under the marker room.
The party room of the casino.
No, it's a charity building with a marker room that's a casino.
Charity building?
the charity building
that's a marker room
basically a charity, basically a headquarters for a
for a non-profit is essentially where we are
yeah so there's a lot of markers
they do like markers
at non-profits
and whiteboards
I always be writing on whiteboards
so I take one of the markers I draw a new mouth on
so I can speak normally
what do they write on those whiteboards like uh
how do I not make money
yes there we go
the
The rolling sound oh and roll 20
Looks really upset Caleb's had a rough week. All right. Do I succeed in decapitating? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
I mean this guy's just like a chump like yeah, I will say though that people notice you decapitate
So I you should know that that would happen
Okay, I quickly reattach his head and I hold
on
with his head on his like fully on his body.
- I look like him, but I'm completely green
'cause I'm very sick.
- Okay, so yeah, you can go up to Fatima though.
Patrick Yoda was distracting her
and then drew his mouth back on.
- I walk up to Fatima and I'm like,
hello miss, how are you?
- Oh, okay, this is good.
Before you were going,
you were making pretty scary sounds.
So I didn't know you were.
- I'll go on your mouth now.
Oh, that's so exciting.
Yes, are you from Sky, England?
I'm from... I'm from...
Sucka-fucka-ba.
Nah, I'm from Sucka-fucka-ba.
Oh, okay.
Oh, yes, you're Jordan.
Um, yeah, both of us.
Sucka-fucka-ba-ba.
Wait, now there's two Stephen A. Smiths and one is a puppet.
Yeah, unless you want to dispatch
the other is just green.
Take the puppet one into the bathroom.
Yeah.
carry on his duty.
I'm going to just make an announcement outside too.
Like, you're not far away from the lobby.
Like, you're in the lobby.
Like, you could...
You'd have to still figure out a way to dispose of him,
but it's not like you can't get rid of him.
Alright, we should stage some kind of fight between the two Stephen A. Smiths
where Lotus wins and defeats his doppelganger.
I'm okay with that, yeah.
Yeah, we're gonna do it, yeah.
I can't control that.
I can't control what you do.
"Ohhh I'm so sick because somebody's copying me!"
"Oh, Steven!"
"I'm your evil twin!"
"And I punch him like really lightly and his head just flies off."
"And his head also, it's not attached."
"And people just applaud and say 'Yes, finally, the real Steven A. Smith has defeated his
evil twin!'"
"Everyone watching, both of you roll a performance check."
The effect of this is that people will think like, "Oh wow, security's really good around
here and nothing strange is happening."
I say that out loud.
Because they can deal with threats.
I say that exact thing out loud.
I got a 4 on performance.
11, okay.
Yeah, people are less convinced that you were able to punch his head off.
But they're not necessarily unconvinced that that was the evil Stephen A. Smith.
Because you do look like Stephen A. Smith now.
Exactly like him, but green.
But they do think that your performance of budging his head off seemed like you were
trying to beat him.
But you...
Okay, okay, I admit it.
I faked killing my evil twin because I wanted you guys to respect me.
I've been an outsider since my first day at this job, and I thought that this was going
to be the day that that changed, but I guess not, so let me just get whatever code I need
to do my job and go home and fuck with you myself.
I applaud, I try to start another round of applause.
Roll persuasion.
Uh, Travis.
Both of you.
I beat you for winning.
Zero!
Why did you do that?
Why did you try to clarify?
Why did you
Friend I mean, it's so horrible. It's just like
It doesn't convince anybody of anything in particular, okay, I
Just say just kidding everyone
Yeah, I mean like everyone at this point is like completely perplexed by the scene
But you do look a lot like Stephen a Smith and sound like okay
And none of the real
Is true, but you fail persuasion
Yeah, that's kind of what's happening here, I mean oh man, I mean like nobody believes you
We don't be known what to think about you like you're not you haven't done a single thing. That's made either made sense
You could pretty much say whatever you want
Anybody to do anything ever for you on your behalf
the
just goes to you Stephen, Stephen slash blowtoss and says oh so good that you're
here okay so it's time for us to transfer the money into the market so if
you'll come with me we'll go to the security vault it's going to be into the
basement so please right this way Stephen. Easy for me. I'm Stephen's aide and I
Come with him. This is my younger brother
This this half-chimp man is my younger brother and I need him to help me because I'm so sick
I'm sorry. I just we're only going to have so many
You know the security protocols is it's not going to allow it's okay. It's okay, but your brother
He'll come he'll come
It's okay. I can come I can come inside. Yeah
Instead of me
Well, so I'm just kidding I'm just we to go and you say back
That's funny, okay
So I'll go with you Steven look if your younger brother needs to be or sort of you know
he can come with us at least to where we're outside of the the
Security chamber, okay, and then we'll play by year once more about my older brother and I point to a guy
a guy I don't know.
Guy I mean...
I... uh...
I don't know, I think we'll just keep it with you younger,
but you felt a lot weirder than when we first met.
Um, let's just uh, short term make our way there.
Sick.
And um, yeah, you guys
started to start walking there, Travis you're coming along.
Um, at this point.
Meanwhile, uh,
Ray, you're being led now
to um, uh,
uh, Goofus Gallant
By Lance and Lance is like I goofus
Goofus. Oh, yeah Lance. Yeah this guy. He spilled a bunch of shit on the fucking control pan. What the fuck?
No, this guy spilled all this shit
Every fucking thing in the whole goddamn room. Oh my hand
Okay, yeah goofus goofus doesn't believe you
you
So well, I believe in you
I mean you wouldn't necessarily be aware of it. This is happening. Well, but if you just had it like a motherly instinct
Yeah, he just knew that
I'm not trying to interfere what's happening. I'm just I'm just trying to give him like like a some reinforcement. Yeah, it's fair
Yeah, I'm sure he has like a bot that sends encouragement to
Patches he probably has some kind of bot
My latest post which is a video of me going like you need to start selling off your family members possessions
They don't they're not doing anything good for you. You need to sell them off and I'm saying that to him as well
Yeah, I think goof is I think without you even sending that goof is is trying to remember that you're very good
So well, you know, let's just go to the control panels go to the scene and just try to try to figure out what to do
You know, I think blaming other people that's not that's not that's not the the mindset here
Let's just try to problem solve, you know, let's just try to problem solve right?
I can solve your problem right now. You fucking fire this idiot what? Oh
Don't listen. He's a fucking demon. You listen to a demon
I am NOT gay. You told me to grab your hand, but you said that you liked it
I liked it, but whatever I like a lot of things. Yeah, like like, you know what it's not about who's gay
Yeah, that's right. It's not about
I always build all the soda in the whole room and destroy every last part of the security system
Let's just move on from this and if you can bring me to maybe another room and boy am I thirsty
if I mean I can a
Giant bottle of orange juice
What do you say
Roll persuasion
7 okay, one worse. It was like I think I think we should just sort of let's let's just go back to the security room
And just try to try to fix the problem
And then and then and then I can get you that OJ. Okay?
All right, sounds good, okay cool
They were being brought back to the security room with Lance who's pissed at you. You're you're both going back there now
Going back to you
Barry key, so I don't know blow toss. I assume you've I mean, well who did the robe? Yeah, ray you keep the signal of people
Did you get the signal that the robots were well? No
Travis was able to probably communicate that to people so very key. You can now start to travel through the vents
Travel through the the plumbing. I mean through the girls bathroom
Yeah, so if you want to do that, you can start doing that you could go back and slither again use another charge
To get into the into the plumbing
Yep, I'm smithering. Oh, yeah, so you're slithering through the plumbing and this is the girls bathroom
so one of the big problems is that there's a lot of buildup of a lot of just like the kind of stuff that comes out
of women and
Unfortunately, yeah, no it's attacking you
The girl stuffs attacking you know
Cancel the campaign
Yeah, I'm sorry guys
No
because I thought about it a lot and I was like if he goes to the plumbing like I have to try to be realistic and
trying to like tell the story in an accurate way and
Girl stuff attacks you so roll initiative Barry G. You're being attacked by tampons
You're being attacked by by girl doodoo, which is worse than guy doodoo. Yeah being attacked by discharge
just general yeah and bugs and bugs the only other thing that girls have a
pussy fly the fable pussy fly girl but rat in there - I hate when I see a girl's
butt rat. Dude when the butt rat string pokes out of their shorts. Not for me. Nope. Not
my thing. I said a butt rat traps all over the floor in the bathroom. Yup. So we'll go
back to that so Fatima is leading you now down there
blowtoss with with Travis and she's saying you know
the thing is is that there's there's a lot I want to do with
this charity you know and I think about the the three gentlemen who donated all
those that's money and I think about what that could have done what that did
for us you know that's kind of generosity because
there's not a lot of it in Gandshetti and I think about what we can get done here
And the things that we can start to do and it's very exciting.
So you're going to see a lot of money in this vault and it's very good.
And I'm looking forward to what we can do with this.
I don't know what funds you're thinking of or potentially sort of if there's a particular
coin you're thinking of trying to turn this into.
I know we only talked about preliminaries.
Yeah, there's a certain type of coin that I've been really interested in putting my
money into lately, and it's called my coin.
I'm gonna turn this all into my coin.
Oh my coin, my coin.
What is that? What's that run on?
Me. OS.
Windows ME.
iPhone.
A vintage coin, that's interesting.
I'm gonna win those coins
Yep
Oh man, damn you just won my favor as a dm. What can I say to that? Uh, so that's very good. He's funny
That's funny. You got a funny brother
I hate him. He's my evil brother
We have to kill him
Give him a noogie with my chimp arm
We get into a big fight
*laughter*
um
we're fighting like the- like the- the guys in- in oceans 11
and like when they- they- the balloon goes up and covers the security camera
but it serves no purpose at all
*laughter*
but it is a fight to the death
we're just doing it
yeah
um
you guys are just fighting
uh
patrick yoda
um
what are you doing in the lobby?
i wanna get a sense of where you're at
I'm uh, I'm really just like
At this point I really don't know I
Have a drawn-on mouth. I've been walking around
I know that I have an assignment, but I don't really know what it is
And I'm just chatting people up. I'm just walking up to them. I'm
Pretending I'm the manager. I'm working on the chair. Yeah, and I'm being like, oh you you you have a good time
the
fifth
and
the
the fifth
*laughing*
fuck
you wanna get-
*laughing*
you wanna get your head badgered in yeah?
you talkin' to me like that?
*laughing*
badgered in
i'm listening in, i'm in the vents i'm listening in
yeah, bergy, uh, uh, there's a fly
now, it's comin' at you
um, oh fuck
*laughing*
big sideways, uh, mouth parts
yeah
It's going like...
[Mimics the sound of a cat]
You know, a pussy sound.
And it's attacking you.
Okay, what is your AC?
Oh, your AC is higher, I just realized.
Because you're in slime mode.
So it tries to shoot acid at you.
Um...
And the concentrated acid that comes out of...
So yeah, it misses though.
But it's going to try one more time.
Because it gets two attacks in this beautiful world of ours.
Do I get a million attacks?
You get two attacks.
How about...
...forty?
No.
You know, it does hit you.
It hits you for eight damage.
It shoots its acid at you and it sort of gets your slime...
...uh, body.
Your weird fucked up slime.
FUCK!
Not my slime body!
[laughter]
Yeah.
But it's your turn. You're up.
This fly is sort of blocking your path so you can't plant the bomb if need be.
I kill it in one fell swoop.
the
Yeah
If you depolarize somebody's cells you can mess with their
Diaper I was doing some is that true? All right. Well, fuck well
It's because of it's one aspect of when you depolarize someone cells things you can do to their diaphragm
I don't recall in in deus ex. Is that something you can do it in? I don't know about
7-7 it was just something I was reading about the depolarization of cells. Yeah, I read about the - I'm gonna deploy race all that pussy
I guess.
Yeah, okay. So then hit depolarize inside the attack and spell casting thing. It's in the middle of your sheet.
Oh, I got it.
Oh, yeah, that hits roll for damage. No, no, so hit depolarize in. Okay. Oh, damn. Okay.
I got a 12. When I rolled that,
Oh, he rolled for damage. Okay.
You rolled.
Juvia just hit depolarize inside of the chat window.
I see.
That's a fake one.
That's also a fake one.
It's going up sequentially.
Hold on.
Do it one more time.
Okay, fine.
Do it.
Oh, that's weird.
Okay, you got it.
You got it.
So you got date.
Did you use any of your charges?
I use the you can use one charge to paralyze it for six seconds.
Yeah, I'll just paralyze it and go out of my way.
I don't want to...
So, for six seconds, it means you paralyze it for one round,
which means during that round, you can try to run away from it
and you can get some good distance on it.
You might not be able to totally disengage from the combat,
but you can start to make moves to do that.
How strong is it anyways?
I mean, you can do it.
You can...
Just say a number.
Say a number.
You have a roll insight.
I'll let you do a free insight check to see if you can get a
sense of how strong this fly is.
We can tell it's not, it's not, not tough.
Um, yeah, but it's also a pussy fly.
That's true.
It's not really, it's not really fucking around.
Um, it's, it's fairly tough, but it's not that tough.
Um, like you can take it, but, but we'll kill you.
I'm going to go for the kill.
Like I always do.
So are you gonna use any other charges or you just gonna keep it paralyzed or no?
I'll do the other the three charges thing the drive on destruction
Of course you fuck up this flies diaphragm
So it takes 1d for damage every turn until they long rest it moves at half speed and it's disadvantage on all saving throws going
forward
So we'll come back to this combat in a second we're gonna go back to the Ray William Johnson
Workplace comedy and so you're going back into the security and you see that the I mean the drink is spilled
The security bots are broken because of it and gallus goofins like all right. Well, well, let's just see if we could try to
reboot this
No, listen, I'm an expert of technology and basically I'm gonna need you two boys to suck all this soda up with your mouths
Every last drop. All right. I'm gonna say role persuasion with advantage because you do have a computer attached to your back
Nice. Yeah, you see gallus immediately start sucking the the juice from there
- yeah
And you see Lancy like I I don't know if I want to be sucking this
Sucking my soda from the control panel you are you uh, hey everybody this guy hates soda
Okay, okay he runs over there
So, yeah, you got them both sucking on it, um, uh, you're still able to see the security cameras so you can see
travis and and blow toss with fatima
Approaching one they're one door behind the security chamber where you won't be able to see them anymore
And so we cut into that area and we see you two and you see Fatima she says, okay, so we're gonna go in here
So travis you're going to wait out here if that's okay
And then me and and steven here we're going to go inside
And we're just going to handle this transaction and then you guys can keep hanging out being brothers. That's all cool with me
Okay
fine
Okay, and so uh, she leads you inside steven steven blowtoss
on
the
*sigh*
and then?
and after that
I mean then she, then she um
I, I don't know, what do you, what do you guys want?
no and then?
she gets all sticky
she gets very sticky at the end of it, ok
ok, that's good enough for me
so that
so
what part of that
when the door opens, it lets her, it's gonna let her and
Travis, and Travis
her and Blotas inside
mhm
um
and then I just sort of scoop my foot into the door
You're gonna scoop so I mean it's like it's a kind of door where so I should describe this a bit more
It's a kind of door where it's gonna open. It has like an opening from the center of it and it like an aperture
Yes an aperture 100%. Okay. Wow. Thank you. Um, and
Wow, thank you. And you can see you can uh,
You can try to step inside. It's gonna close pretty quickly. So if you do that, we're gonna have to do a dexterity check
And if you fail it could be you know, it could be bad you all right I put all the valuable parts of my body in first
Starting the penis then the head
Trying to
Yeah, I guess kind of like a cab cow away move to make that work. I feel like um
Okay
Roll just roll straight deck. So if you go into your nice fuck, okay
Wow
Yeah, 19 you slink in there and at this point
You guys don't need Fatima anymore because that was the biometrics man
so
I'm letting you know what that happened because Fatima's gonna be like, um, I just I don't know if
We can have you in here. She's gonna be like that, but she's not doing that yet. Yeah, and it's fine guys
What's she gonna do? She's all sticky anyway
Stick her to the wall
I do a quick perception check on the ceiling of this room
Mm-hmm. Okay
Can I do a quick perception check to check whether this is the real vault or if it's one that they built in a in a
warehouse to trick security cameras
I just want to get ahead of this if it's gonna happen.
I'm gonna do a perception check just because I'm really not sure where I am.
You need persuasion, Pat.
Yeah, see, everything's all going to the fritz.
Yeah, alright, so, yeah, checking the ceilings, I mean, you gotta crit fail on your next perception.
So Pierce, you look at the ceiling and yeah, what you do notice is the gold plated discs
that would need to, that could only be, that would come down and slice any intruders.
They can only be dismantled with the golden guns.
So you do notice that and obviously yeah, they could be activated, you don't know how
or when or why.
know
but you did clock that before you did anything the Fatima
okay
um I guess I rip her head off
yeah she's a civilian you can do that she just wanted to make the world a better place
uh roll an attack roll on her
poor thing
you fucking idiot
yeah roll damage she's dead
You killed Fatima von Kissyface.
And yeah, she just, she said something in her unintelligible, I think I was trying for
Dutch accent and then dies.
The gold discs from above sling down to decapitate both of you, the two of you.
Travis.
I turn invisible.
Travis, this is your this is your shot, OK?
Roll attack roll. With your golden eagles,
OK? Alright, wish me luck guys.
Good luck. Bad luck. There we go.
Well, all of your training, your whole life has been leading to this moment where you
whip out your golden.
Describe to me how you do this.
You got 25.
How did you do it?
So I cross draw for my right golden deagle and both holsters are on my left side.
So I cross draw with my right hand and my left hand I'm also drawing so that I'm fully
akimbo. Fuck yes. I still have a cigar in my mouth, I swallow it, and then I breathe out
the cigar smoke through my nostrils. Sick. And then I squeeze the triggers using my index
fingers. And then of course the slide goes back and then a little bit of exhaust comes
Roll a wisdom saving throw too.
Yeah, why not?
[Laughter]
Okay. You were able to pull this off.
But the amount of control and effort it took to do that, to suppress your chimpness,
has caused your chimp arm, after the deed is done, to kind of go on the fritz.
it is scratching your own ass, it is scratching your balls, it is trying to pick bugs off
of Blotas' head and eat them.
Your chimp barn will be out of commission.
But you will be able to pull this off.
Okay, great.
So these gold disks that cannot be destroyed except by golden bullets from golden deagles.
Blotas, you're gonna be at the vault, we'll come back to you.
I started also I put it I'm putting my chimp fingers in Fatima severed heads
mouth you think it's sucking on it maybe of course
Barry G your combat continues this fly takes one other takes the 1d for of
damage this fly this fly all right name not that much but still did all right
and now it's going to attack you this time with its little fly mouth it's
gonna try to bite at you it misses and it's going to try again it misses again
you're up though you can destroy the fly I kill the pussy you have to roll for
You have to see if you do you have to try
Fucking this thing I guess nice. Oh shit. You got a crit. Okay. Yeah
There you go, yeah 13, oh, yeah, how do you how do you kill this pussy fly I
I
Get it all out and I crush it
with my my my
with your what my my my magnet body i just
hell yeah in a single without even without any effort
yeah you're nag nag nag as you crush it to death
yeah you're able to slide through this pipe now and get to your friends
um uh blow toss oh actually sorry not blow
Ray, they have finished sucking the soda up and things are still not working.
I think you missed a spot.
They both of them are holding their tummies going "Ohhhhhh"
"Ohhhhhh"
I feel like they're just in a lot of pain.
pain.
Okay, well, uh, I'm not- I'm an expert on technology, not on tummy aches.
So, um, I'm not sure how much I can help you two further, but I hope- I feel like I learned
a lot here.
Um, two grown men who can't hold down 60 ounces of soda.
much soda I think I'm just at this point I think I'm just gonna leave roll you
two around for a minute and then I'm going oh it's all fun oh yeah you roll
around for a bit, Gallant says "Tell Barry Gee that I'm cool"
I'll text him on Instagram.
Yeah, yeah, I go "Yeah, sure, of course" and then I text Barry "Your friend is rolling
around on the ground, he drinks so much soda that I think he's going to die."
You need to stop drinking so much soda. You are burning your business by drinking this much soda.
*laughter*
Uh, Patrick Yoda, yeah, that guy's like, "Look, I did not mean to say, uh, F you, you know, I'm trying to understand your culture, I'm trying to meet you where you're at, man, like, I'm not, I'm really sorry about that."
the
Marketing yeah, nobody could say anything that you always can just say marketing. It's true. I just do a cartwheel
Cool all right blow toss and Travis
And I'm looking at him to like like waiting for him to class
Yeah, he's like, all right, can I roll athletic good car wheel claps?
You can roll you can roll performance.
If that was your intention.
He's not impressed.
He's mostly just tiffed.
tiffed.
Using the parlance.
Well, it's us.
This is it.
Yeah.
You got your laptop.
You've got access to the vault now.
You have to get your credentials to get yourself in there.
I open up my laptop.
Travis, did you tell Blowtox that there's something else in there besides the money?
Or did you not tell him that?
I'm curious.
Did I what?
Oh, did I tell him what I learned on the phone?
Yeah.
No, I forgot.
Fuck yes.
Okay.
Um, you've got your password.
Yeah, I'm typing in "hello".
It doesn't work.
one doesn't work hello one two three doesn't work goodbye doesn't work this
is your password yeah my password is hello one two three four I type in
hello one two three four and it works okay cool all right you're in your
laptop I'm playing squirrel bubble shooter on my laptop okay you're not
downloading that swag poop comm slash squirrel - bubble - shooter which still
exists in the future. Yes. Oh yeah. It's the only website from from web 2.0 that
will still exist will be swag web 3.0. We will be publishing NFTs very soon. I'm
looking forward to it. Okay. I download all the money. Yes. With the credentials.
Okay. As you do, I'm loaded into Venmo. And I make the I make the payment memo
poop and it's like a hundred million dollars it's a public the only payment
in Venmo history where you can see the dollar it's also it's the last it's the
only it's the first payment in Venmo in the past like 200 as you do that you
download it from the vault without even having to open the vault and here
banging on the vault door like slamming banging and then you hear it subside and
when you hear you hear like sort of like a warping noise hey what was that
oh classic sound okay oh yeah and that's what you hear oh wait what did I hear
What was the second part?
What
Maria oh
Yeah
Is it Mario or Luigi
That's all that you're left with is either Mario tell me right now is it Mario or is it Luigi can't tell you what that was
Okay. Well also, what did I not go? I thought we were in the vault
No, you were in the security chamber you down outside the I thought we got the biometric
Okay, I go into the unless you wanted to use Fatima's to I
Mean, yeah, I thought we were in the I mean, I'll go into the vault. Okay. Yeah, I'm not afraid of going into the vault
so what you see is a
pedestal
That doesn't look like it fits in with anything
It doesn't look like anything you've seen in gun city. It has sort of weird arcane design
It doesn't look like it fits in with anything you saw in the Temple of Doom, Temple of the
Penguin of Doom.
You see it there for a moment, you see it flash a brief bright red, and then you see
it vanish.
Erm Mario much?
But you get your money.
I say erm Mario much.
I laugh and laugh.
That's the joke that I say whenever I see anything red.
Even though I'm not seeing this at all and I'm in a completely different thing, something
takes me over and makes me laugh just a little bit to myself.
I try to punch it up by saying "erm Elmo much"
I stop laughing too.
I suddenly stop laughing.
An eerie air rolls over my neck.
Yeah, then I say I'm just kidding.
You got the money.
OK.
You know what the gang now?
Uh, yeah, I'll just walk upstairs to tell them.
You know, I'm going to follow.
Yeah, security is down.
Very good.
I'm also just shooting my guns indiscriminately at the ceiling and shit.
The gang people.
Hey, you guys make it to the lobby.
You have the money.
Um, you can go.
Okay, I- in front of everybody I transform back from green Stephen A. Smith into myself.
In front- in full view of every employee.
Everyone gasps. Uh, the second you do that, still in the building, after there is security footage of you going in as Stephen A. Smith and now leaving the place as Blotas,
There is a security warning now.
Don't worry guys.
Looks like they're just letting us off with a warning.
And you see a massive, massive robot sort of break through the back area of the lobby and sort of confront you guys.
I need you all roll initiative.
Whoa.
Fuck.
I'm in the pipes.
I'm in the damn pipes.
What the fuck?
You fall through the pipes.
Yeah.
And you say ow, ow, ow.
You say owie, owie, owie.
God.
Yeah, no, I can't control this.
That's out of my-
And I see you and I go, "Oh, you smell like pussy fly."
I started licking him.
I'm like, "Oh, I'm gonna have to go to the bathroom."
fly I started licking him cool okay let's see we got here oh okay cool let's see
what we got here
it cool sick ass that showing up in the audio you know what you're talking off
no no the upstairs people at the office you you farting no no I can't hear you
farting pep now okay yep okay Travis it much you're up first this is a massive
don't wake daddy bot.
ok.
it is ready for you.
it is pissed that you woke it up.
it looks like all your dads.
whatever that is for you.
ok.
i'm gonna kill you ok?
i say everything's fine.
i mean it's not it's unconvinced.
it's unconvinced.
wow.
try again.
I mean it. Everything's okay.
Damn. Okay. I shoot it maybe with a gun or
Yeah, absolutely. Give that a shot. All right. Well, keep in
mind, I get it. Give it a shirt. We're gonna be doing half
damage, right? Only one. Your Travis chimp arm is going to
crazy mode. Okay, then I roll for damage. Okay, so you only do
four damage here. It pings off of the robot and you seem like
it
the
(laughter)
- Can the robot also fly?
- Can I try to teleport inside of the robot?
- So funny little motherfucker.
- Does it, 'cause I know it's like a mind control thing.
- Yeah, it's not really inside.
- Or, is there maybe a vent or something
that I can see inside so I can physically teleport
just inside of the robot's body and try and fight it from the inside.
Not really, it's sort of just like a compact.
Not even in the bullet hole?
In the bullet hole?
It wasn't like a bullet hole, it was like a slight indent, yeah.
Ok, I'm gonna attack that.
What's an area that I could attack that would make a hole?
Oh yeah?
Oh yeah, uh, let's have you do insight.
Let's have you do insight.
See what you can sort of assess from this guy.
17.
17?
Fuck yeah dude.
Um, yeah, I mean the Don't Wake Daddy bot, you can see that the eyes, the pupil, the
material around the pupil, where the pupil would be, is not as, um, like, robust as the
rest of the material.
Like that was clearly at some point meant to either be like, commanded by somebody and
they were meant to see out of that or something like that. It's not as robust though.
Okay, I'm going to shoot my Grinch gun at that eye area.
Go for it. And I have advantage because it's my first
turn and he hasn't gone yet. That's true.
Oh, why is this not working? Oh, here we go. I don't know. I'm not in charge of that.
Alright. Alright.
Okay, it's a 30-20. Both of those hit. It's got pretty low AC.
I think it's double damage for critical hit, right?
Yes, it is.
I mean, like, typically we do two rolls, but I like double damage better.
It's just simpler.
Oh, okay.
That's fine with me.
I mean, I went ahead and did four total rolls.
Yeah, I know I did that.
Oh, I see what you did. Okay, yeah.
That's fine. That makes more sense anyway.
Yeah, so I mean, it's good. A shit ton of damage.
21 damage? Yeah, you're able to, like, um, like...
If you're concentrating that on that pupil,
*imitates drum roll*
with that intent,
It's like ding ding ding ding and it like shatters, you know,
after like the fourth bullet hits it.
So, yeah, so it's sort of like hasn't.
Cool.
What kind of action is my teleportation?
Is it a.
Oh, that's a good question.
I remember if it's a bonus action or I know I'll just wait until the next turn.
Whatever.
Well, hold on.
Let's find out together.
Let's find out.
Do they're in there as my action?
Yeah, you can certainly try.
He gets in there before me, I'm going to throw a fit.
I get really small.
I just sit there.
I'm I'm beginning to become into a puddle to stay there.
Where's your teleport?
You have 30 feet.
I think it was a bonus action before but I know you took a lot
of it.
I did nerf a lot of stuff from it.
But if it was a bonus action before and I didn't nerf that.
No, it doesn't look like I nerfed that.
So I can't really I can't make a claim.
OK, I go inside the robots body.
God damn it.
Alright, I mean it's just Misty
step anyway at that point,
so that's kind of fine.
I can't really.
Take any blame I can't.
You know, we'll take blame.
I mean, that's what I mean.
Actually, yes.
Cool, yeah, you find your way
inside of the eyeball of the bot,
so you're sort of like
curled up inside of there.
I'm smoking a cigar.
Cool.
the
It doesn't have like cells the same way that organic material does, so it might not work.
Well, I guess I'll just use my mines.
You can use your magnet mines.
Yeah, I'm going to try to use my mines and throw them inside of the robot so maybe it
also hits.
Whoa, whoa, what's this about?
So you have multiple kinds of mines.
You have bomb, you have clown gas, you have EMP, and you have charm bomb.
Can I only throw one kind of mine?
No, so you have three magnet mines, you can use as many of them as you want in action,
but you just like only have three per long rest.
If you want to use all three mines though in one action, you can.
I want to use two mines.
I want to use an EMP to maybe immobilize it and a clown gas to make blowtuffs laugh in
the robot.
So for the EMP mines, it can work on simple security measures or robots, cyborgs, hard to work on more robust systems and computers.
I would say this falls under the more robust systems and computers, but if you use more than one, if you just use two for EMP and both of those connect, then you can do it.
Alright, I'll do two EMPs then.
the
is
seconds and that's and that's awesome that they are they're actually
differently abled is what we say right sorry yes yeah I mean Jimmy tried to run
away from a pussy fly in six seconds and those things are fast I think they get
up there. I will run. Yeah. I'm still, I'm inside it. You can run too. I'm just gonna
leave you, I'm just gonna leave you. I mean at this point, combat is over. It's disabled
for 18 seconds. So what you guys want to do is walk up to the robot. Walk up to the robot.
Connor you look like me father.
Can we all leave and just leave Patrick here?
I will gladly leave Patrick to die.
Is there any buttons inside the robot's head?
No, nothing like discernible. It's like wiring, you know.
Is there a red wire or a green wire?
Yeah, there are wires of different colors.
I think I see what you're asking, but like, I mean it's not like...
It means only so the wire the wires are visible right now to me to him to you
Oh, sure British had s up and get out of here. You'll okay. I
Climbed down the road down the robots throat into its stomach and I get pooped out
There he is boat also you do it down then I run away you guys sprint out of there Sullivan
Yeah, you guys are running out of there Sullivan's in the car he's like do to do do to do
Listen in music. What's your listening to? What's your listen to? He's listening the xxx contassion
Whoa, kick him away digging your pants. Yeah
I'm driving the car away. Mm-hmm. It's slow ride
You guys get away you guys get away with it, um
Yeah, you know we all of it
No, you have to go with the hiding
Because you were very much identified by the end we drive back and we drop Travis at the
Yeah, he did it and he's also a sex pervert
We were Joe we were in there trying to stop him from doing horrible sex crimes to everyone in there
That's the only reason we were on the security footage he's my evil twin
Yeah, I mean you guys got your money back I think it's officially cannon Lee revealed that he is my evil twin
So we did it you got the money split it five ways between the guys and
Then get any since it was all my fault. They said and we went our separate ways
Travis traveled back to earth. So we said and he may have slipped back in the espionage
It's hard to know what that guy but in any case he said he's gonna use his share to rebuild his chimp
I'm Empire. He completely destroyed before hanging out with us
But all the chimps would have one human arm and they would each have their own golden gun. So it's pretty scary
Barry Gee decided to use his share to actually pay off the Scarface house
he pretended to live in, and he started a new podcast called The Mental Heist, stealing
from the mind to give to your wallet.
The three guys each headed into retirement.
It was, after all, their last job.
With a kid in college, I'm sure Blowtoss and Ray have their hands full.
And with all the debt following Patrick Yoda around, he always got me something to do for
him.
But me, I'm doing okay.
It was fun getting the crew together and it felt even better to pull off the heist.
Though I do wonder what Mommy Goodlegs wanted to talk to the guys about.
Nah, it's probably nothing.
It's never anything really.
There's never nothing that really ever goes on for us.
I'm pretty sure it's nothing out of this world.
.
[ Music ]