[MUSIC]
Last time on Gun City, A Broad City, Playtime, Continue Fun.
Patrick Yoda went totally rockstar in Janet Blowjob's room.
He'd been invited as a guest of hers to Lera Fax,
the underground or under-space station headquarters of Huge-Ass Fax,
the gangster who knows everything.
Because of intel he had on Captain Gumby Superior's intentions for the undercity.
Yep, Caleb turned it the wrong way.
Patrick heard.
No, that's worse.
I sound like I'm inside of a small bowl.
Patrick heard something very strange come from the other room while playing Xbox's Shrades
with Baby Gadd.
The sound of metal scraping against metal.
I forgot about the Shrades.
I didn't.
So he burst into Janet's room and began to investigate.
He also met a cool little robot, nanobot, named Scooter, who is now on the team, who tried
to help him out as much as his programming would allow.
Meanwhile, Ray and Blotas left the room.
Uh oh.
He's getting a new cover for the mic.
Meanwhile, Ray and Blotas defeated a ho-ass tentacle monster.
Deep in the guts of the space station, with a greech.
A person corrupted by the poor air and water quality in the depths of the pleasure palace,
palace attached by the crotch, the base of the crotch of this creature. So you guys fell
down the...
Creature's crotch.
Creature's crotch. Afterwards, a Seamus, the leprechaun they rescued from the royal guard
in the first session, met them in the guts and led them to the Boglands, the home of
the leprechauns. The home the leprechauns made for themselves outside the slave courts.
Lotas and Ray also huffed some gas to get +1 on rolls.
The Leprechauns struggle with fending off the Greeches, and more threats.
Plus now Sullivan has arrived after working out in the gym so he could lift the snake.
Now Ashamus brings them to meet Bear McGinnis, leader of the Leprechaun people on the Pleasure
Palace.
Tearing apart the room, Patrick Yoda managed to find very little.
Though he discovered an odd panel behind Blowjob's bed, and after rolling a 1 while trying to
trying to pry it open, his hoverboard was firmly lodged in the wall.
A furious baby gad tried to yank the board out of the wall, but it remains to be seen
if he was able to, because Patrick Yoda soon fell asleep, and a strange dream
that gave him a sense of where New Sullivan is. Still, what is with the toys
they discovered from the victims of playtime? And who sent
Lotas and Rey down the chute to the guts?
And does Gumby Superior really know where New Sullivan is? Well, we know who sent us down the chute.
- Ready, that guy, ready.
- We already know that one.
So can you come up with a different second one?
- Sure.
And who really is Bear McGinnis,
the leader of the leprechauns?
- The leader of the leprechauns, I just answered it.
- But who is he really?
- So, okay, so you just gave us a hint
that he's a different guy.
- Nah, he's not really.
- Play time.
- Well, just continue, you suck.
- And what of huge ass facts?
That's my last one.
What of it? What of?
What of him?
Look, okay, what he is-
Yeah, wait, what of him?
Wait a second, I didn't consider that before.
That's an interesting thought.
Here's what we're gonna do, fuckers.
I wanna make sure we, like, 'cause it's been a little bit, 'cause I got sickies.
Yeah, you gotta remind me what the vision was that I saw.
Yeah, I'm gonna do a little bit of a-
You just did a whole recap.
You were drawing a circle.
I drew a face.
- You're drawing a face. - Drew Patches again.
- You need to stop with this. - He's trying to draw me again.
- He's trying ugly me again.
- Well no, no, no, he didn't say what I saw in the vision.
- Yeah, I'll do that. - Of in my dream.
- We're gonna do not just that, we're also--
- So it's not that I wasn't paying attention.
- It was that, but you just were.
- No, it's not I was paying attention.
- No, no, no, he's right, I didn't say
what was in the vision, we'll do that.
But also-- - I'm right.
- But also, I wanna do a little bit of--
- I don't think you can be right while you're--
- Yeah, no, that's what I was saying,
is it just cuz he doesn't didn't say what you're looking for doesn't mean you
were paying attention I was paying attention you guys are in the bog you
guys know what mr. snitch did or whatever and I was trying and I'm trying to do he
- He hated my last portrait on the back of this,
so I'm trying to make it more realistic.
- Pretend you're in a play right now.
- Pretend I'm in school?
- Yeah. - Okay, here's what I used
to do when I used to practice drawing.
- No, not in school.
- You were pretending you were in school.
You need to pretend that you're playing a game.
- Pretend you're skateboarding right now.
- Yeah.
- Why is he pretending to play a game?
- 'Cause I don't know what I'm doing.
- I'm making art for my friend
and I want him to think it's beautiful.
- So here's the thing, what we're gonna do,
we're definitely gonna recap your dream,
But also, I'm gonna do a little bit of just like
general character, like faction recap,
'cause it's been a little bit.
I feel like I was like, as I was writing this session out,
I was like, there's a lot of characters,
I always introduce so many characters.
- State of the Union.
- Yeah, pretty much.
So, let's start with like--
- State of the Dungeon.
- State of the Dungeon, go ahead.
- You're on the Pleasure Palace, right,
which is Leo the Collector's space station.
- Okay, you don't have to go this--
- Yeah, that's way too far. - We know that we're--
- No, no, no, don't worry, don't worry.
I'm not recapping the whole story, don't worry.
I'm just, I'm going faction by faction, right?
So it's Leo the Collector's space station.
He's the king of the New England Empire,
the only kind of nation that's really rivaling Gunn City
besides Transylvania, which already had a war
with Gunn City a while ago.
- We all know the facts.
- So under him, as far as like,
who's in your purview right now, right,
Belinda Croaks who's sort of the governess kind of of the space station
and also his assistant who has tasked you with doing all this stuff that is now
embroiled you and a whole other bunch of other shit then she's fine right yeah
she's fine for a frog woman then there's jingle Heimer who is the head of the
Royal Guard who you guys had in like the second session and totally abandoned him
but just remind just to remind you who he was that he existed and then finally
in that group of the royal guard of the the Leo's royal crew I guess the New
England Empire group is Blue Gopher who is the forensic scientist I remember him
I remember Blue Gopher yes and then Jingleheimer's the guy that we were they
were on the phone and no okay I'll get you okay so Jingleheimer like was
supposed to like was like basically following you guys around to like
provide help and then you guys just like were like abandoned him by going through
the space by going through space yeah we flew he basically like lost track okay
these are the Royal Guards yeah that's like the head of the Royal Guard so now
that's like one group of people Belinda you guys kind of told the fuck off also
in your own weird way I think we kept trying to they were on the phone with
her and they kept trying to ask her out yeah they kept trying to ask her out
when she was asking for information.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Sounds like this bitch can't take a hint.
- That doesn't sound like something that would happen.
- Yeah, she's a royal, other kind of aard.
- So then, there's, I mean not that she's--
- Lizard.
- She's kind of a princess of the pea.
- So then there's Gumby Superior,
who is like the head of the space station.
- Tard.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- This is the $10 tier.
- Lick Tard.
- And so, yes.
- No, that's my character says that.
I would never say that.
- Tard.
(laughing)
- It's funny that Lizard and Libtard rhyme
'cause they're both reptiles.
- Shit.
- You are basically like a fucking Nostradamus.
- You are based at Igli and Frog Hogs.
- Yeah.
- Gumby Superior is the like,
captain of the space station.
He was a general in the Gun City Army who's retired.
Under him is Michael Quinn,
is like a lieutenant, is like first mate,
who led you guys,
you to to the guts to meet with the scientist who was ebony's ricky
and his assistant
and who was ebony's ricky
yeah and uh...
you're alex baldwin in the departed right now
his name is ebony's ricky
name is Ebenezer Keish. Put the paper away fuck stick. What are you drawing?
Oh no! Come on.
It's even better. I tried my best to drop
patches. You know what would have been actually funny Patrick? It looked like Barret Harkonnen.
If you, after this first one sucked so bad, you can't just do another ugly one. This needed
to be a photorealistic, beautiful portrait. This was
photorealistic. Alright put the paper away. I don't want to ever see you do this again.
- A cousin of Carl from Aqua Teen.
Is that what I look like to you?
- No!
- No, not to him, that's objective.
- Yeah, right, yeah, that is me.
So then, there's Reddy, also the assistant,
who pushed you to-- - Who, yeah.
- The bad, bad motherfucker.
- The bad motherfucker. - Oh, okay, see,
I thought that maybe it was-- - Who we think is in league
with, yeah. - I thought it was Ebenezer Kish,
maybe. - Maybe, that's what you guys--
- 'Cause we didn't see any, we were just looking
of the whole right? A guy like me he's Ebenezer Creep. So what was it? You guys assumed it was
ready. Ready. All right well now I'm ready to get to the bottom. So that's
and that's sort of the like crew slash scientist kind of group that's like working the ship but
isn't explicitly aligned with the Royal Guard but is insofar as that they do run the ship.
Okay.
Perform stuff on it. Now, let's look at the sort of the under city groups, right?
So we have Huge-Ass Facts, who you guys have not met yet, who you're supposed to
meet soon, who is like the head of the under city group.
Yeah, he was going to meet, no, Janet Blowjob.
Yeah, you were gonna meet with him through Janet Blowjob.
Janet Blowjob being his right-hand person.
- Yeah.
- And then--
- Man?
- Well, woman, I guess.
But I was trying to be super inclusive.
- So you went with person.
- I sure did.
Look, I work in corporate America.
He just slips sometimes.
- Dox him.
- Don't dox me.
Please don't dox me.
- Matching Mike vibes.
- Ruined my life.
- Just realized.
- Then there's
Oh, that character you didn't meet.
Oh no, go ahead.
No, since we're listing every, just list every single name in the world.
This will be the, this will be the characters episode.
Where we list every single character that's going to show up or has gone up.
His name's just Resort Manager Eagle Ramirez.
I just thought of a character named Paint Can Peter.
Okay, describe him.
Yeah, because this is about as important as what the fuck he's talking about.
And a paintbrush and Oh paintbrush Paul
Paint can Peter and paintbrush Paul, so they're a team so so let's let's so the painting partners. So let's just restart
Janet blowjob who works under him Kenan Thompson
Who's Janet blowjobs like assistant?
- Speaking of blowjobs, that guy's leaning over on my penis.
- He sure does seem like he is.
He's really trying to push this in here.
Okay, cool, this seems good.
I see why you were doing this now.
And then there's Scooter,
who's one of Janet Blowjob's nanobots.
- Isn't there two nanobots?
- Oh, there's like--
- There was two in the room, right?
- There's like 15 nanobots in her room,
but that was the one that you--
- I thought that I talked to another one.
- No, you were trying to get behind the bed
and then you sucked at it.
- Yeah.
- I mean, it was a hard check.
I didn't expect him to roll a one,
trying to lodge it out though.
- Yeah, pretty good.
- Then, oh, one more thing also underneath Belinda
is Shark Eyes, her sort of like bodyguard guy
who you guys don't know much about.
- Oh, and then the two--
- I know, there's Keep Calm and Chive On,
who are also in the Huge Ass Facts group.
- And then there--
- And then there's Baby Gat as well,
who's sort of like in that, and then there's,
fuck, what's his name, O'Neal.
O'Neal, who was like the shopkeeper who almost got killed.
- Who got almost killed, and we--
- Who you guys saved.
- Yep.
- So--
- Saved his hunky ass.
- Now, lastly, let's just talk about,
our last group is just the leprechauns,
that you, at least of the groups you know.
Which, there's a Seamus, who is sort of the
friendly leprechaun who you guys saved
in the zippy loop train earlier.
And then there's Bear McGinnis,
who you do, who you're gonna meet,
excuse me, meet soon.
- Burp City up in here.
- And then there's Bear McInnes' girlfriend,
Millie Shamrock, who you'll meet as well,
who also works with him.
- Oh, like Millie Rock?
- Mm-hmm, that's right.
Yeah, got the reference I just made.
And then, yeah, I mean, that's,
and then of course there's Playtime, right,
who, we don't know who that is.
- Who's a rapist.
- (laughs) Not a rapist.
- Not yet. - I can tell you right now.
- I mean, there's also, I will also say--
- He hurts people, like it's not that crazy to also say--
- Yeah, I guess he could be a rapist.
There's three other characters, sorry.
- I think he chews his gum with his mouth open.
- John Carlo the Bull--
- And he cheats on his girlfriend.
- What?
- John Carlo the Bullfrog.
- Can we not have a character that does that?
- We'll get rid of that.
- Thank you.
- John Carlo the Bullfrog,
who is the head of Papi Chuka's Techno Slime,
who is also here.
Sullivan the Frog, who is nothing.
And then, anytime.
And then--
What else about Sullivan?
He's like, also, he's a pedophile.
No, I won't--
What's up with you today?
--blue tonight.
Yeah.
What's up with you?
Blue on white.
Blue screen, blue Patrick.
Saying, this guy's a rapist.
This guy's a pedophile.
You would think this is--
And Caleb's saying that looking in the mirror.
No, I literally just said that.
And then you--
I couldn't hear you.
I got distracted.
Stealing flopper.
He couldn't.
He is a stealing flopper.
Stealing flopper.
Continue.
That's what I was saying.
- Yeah, sorry, I don't remember the third character.
(laughing)
- Okay.
- I don't know who the third character was in the end.
- We're gonna start playing.
- Yeah, sorry.
- I'm getting, I need him to,
I need, we need a different route from him.
- I understand, I understand.
- Maybe cutting back and forth.
- So, here's where we're gonna start from.
We're starting from, you guys are back in the Boglands.
So, you, last we left off, you guys ran into Sullivan,
who said he went to the gym, so now he's really strong.
Patrick is not in the Boglands.
- Thank God.
and said he's really strong now
'cause you told him to go to the gym
so we could lift the snake.
He asked you where the snake was.
You guys accosted him.
And now a Seamus was gonna lead you to
where Bear McInnes is.
He was gonna have him meet you guys
to see if he could help you find your son.
That was the third, last person actually I realized,
knew Sullivan.
- Yeah, who says what?
Oh yeah.
- I just feel bad 'cause he's not here.
- Wait, can you, what would he,
so he's off in some other room.
How would he say oh yeah if he was being tortured
by a demon spirit?
- I'm not gonna do that.
I love him. - Don't we get--
- Oh yeah!
- That didn't sound anything like him.
- No, there was some quality that was missing.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- If somebody could like repeat that maybe,
then maybe make it sound good.
- Somebody older and wiser.
(laughing)
- If only there was someone in the room.
So I'm not gonna do him being tortured.
I like him.
- Yeah, you should never do somebody
while they're being tortured.
Unless they ask you to.
- Being dude is torture enough.
- I hate being dude.
- If somebody does me--
- He dude-ed dude.
- Yeah, I bet he did.
- If you understand the word, but--
- If somebody does me,
I don't also need torture on top of that.
I'll already give up my secrets.
- What you guys had seen when you guys entered the Bog Land
was like a massive, let's pound that out.
Let's pound that out, it is about Luger.
- What is up with him?
- This guy's obsessed with rape.
- Yeah, I don't know what is going on.
- I can't stop talking about rape right now.
- Literally you're obsessed.
- What the fuck is happening?
- He may have stopped drawing and his mind started to wander.
- Yeah, God.
- You have to, you're obsessed with rape.
- You literally are obsessed with it.
- No.
- So this was--
- People don't like that.
- Yeah, nobody wants to hear that.
- Nobody wants to hear about that.
- I thought he was talking about S&M.
It's about power dynamics.
- So this was sort of like,
this is like representing like the Boglands,
like the swamp in the middle,
the little village, little town.
Back here, over here, is like a big submarine
that was, or like submarine-like structures,
kind of just like some sort of cobbled together
metal structure with these like circular windows in it,
and that's where Bear McGuiness and his Leprechaun group are.
So, Ashamus leads you to--
- I'm so sorry, I hate interrupting.
- No.
- I just want you to know, when you said submarine,
I had such a like, I like had a gulping physical reaction
'cause I got so scared that it was gonna be fucking Taffy
or whatever his character was.
(laughing)
- Chuggy. - Yeah.
So I'm sorry.
- No, it's fine. - I have to snap out of it.
- It's not Chuggy.
Chuggy's gone. - It's Taffy!
(laughing)
- No.
So let's have you guys over here now.
- Chucky's brother.
- He's not even in this universe.
- Well, that was in the past.
- That wasn't the past.
- So we're gonna pretend I never said anything.
- Yes.
- We're just gonna move on.
- I'm just gonna piss him off.
- Frodo!
- Yo!
- This guy's made of straight up cum.
- You say that every time I bring these guys out.
- This guy's made of boogers.
(laughing)
- Ew, yuck.
- Yuck, I have a gross army.
- It's the Jism twins and their booger brothers.
- This guy's made of--
(laughing)
Can these be the Jism brothers and this is the booger?
- No, these are all leprechauns.
- The Jism twins and the booger brothers.
- These are all leprechauns.
Can you stand that one up?
God damn it.
- Leprechauns. - Just talk your talk.
- I will talk my talk, I apologize.
Right, nobody's watching this.
Everyone's listening to it, I know, I know.
So yeah, you guys arrive at,
and you see Bear McGinnis there.
And yeah, he's a impressive looking leprechaun
as far as that can go, roughly a half inch taller
than all the other leprechauns.
- I thought he was a half inch tall.
- No, he's a half inch taller than all the leprechauns.
- So all the leprechauns are five feet?
- No, all the leprechauns are like three, five.
- Okay.
- And arriving on the other side,
so you see the makings of an army,
it's far more prepared than anything
Gummy Superior had intimated when he was talking about,
like, oh, the leprechauns, like, you know,
they're also trouble, but you know, yada, yada, yada.
This looks like a real militia,
like a real trained militia. - The IRA.
- Something like that.
They're all armed with makeshift shillelaghs
that induce stun and some kind of chemical reaction
along with slingshots that hold glowing yellow pellets
that explode on impact.
So they're like genuinely outfitted.
Hunched over a modest desk looking at analog battle plans
is a leprechaun who is, without a doubt,
exactly one half inch taller than any leprechauns you've seen.
As he approaches desk, he lifts up his furrowed
auburn brow and takes you in.
Without missing a beat, his hand glides over his plans
and they vanish from the table.
So he does kind of like a little bit of trickery.
In tune with their apparent leader,
the leprechauns stop running combat drills
and turn their attention towards all of you.
As the Seamus makes apologetic gestures in their direction,
Bear McGinnis' wild hair more matted nest
than anything gently sort of bounces as he talks.
He's dressed head to toe in dark green armor,
fitted to his stocky frame.
In lieu of bare feet,
most of the leprechauns have just bare feet,
he wears black boots made of solid lead.
As he adjusts himself,
you hear the considerable thud each movement makes.
And he says, "Shamus, who are these three?"
'Cause Sullivan is here too.
- He's not like Liam Neeson.
- He might look a little bit like Liam Neeson.
These were the guys I was telling you about.
They're real nice.
I threatened one of the Royal Guards on my behalf
when I was riding the Zippy Loop,
which I know I shouldn't be doing,
drawing attention and all,
but they de-escalated everything real fast,
and they just killed one of the Greech monsters,
and I wanted to make sure that they could rest up,
plus they're real handy in a fight,
and maybe they could,
- Bear McGinnis is like, "Enough, enough, this is, stop."
And he sort of looks to you two,
and like, kinda like gestures, like,
like, "Who are you?
Like, introduce yourselves."
Yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo
yo yo yo my name is Ray and I'm here to say that the fucking I hate these guys
are made of boogers and these two are gay they're made of cum and jizz and a
penis too and a motherfucking Frodo motherfuck you too man fuck this place
you got tanks and and guns and your bombs and your bombs and your bombs in
in your head, in your head, they are fighting
I fucking hate war
and my name is Blotas Piss and I also want to say this
and I gestured to whatever he was saying
in your head, in your head, they are fighting
it's in your head
let me handle this Blotas, don't worry about it
it's in your head, zombie
What?
Nat 20 performance.
Oh my God.
And by the way, wait, show me the Patches cam real quick.
Nat 20 performance, right?
And I think as the people were hearing me sing,
I got that in real life too.
Yeah.
God, whoever, whatever fucking Aztec God
controls my real body, just rolled a perfect 20
when I was singing "Zombie" right then.
'Cause I have in-ear monitors now.
Bear McInnes crosses his arms and nods.
Normally I hate that hip hop crap.
(laughing)
- But yo, yo, yo.
- That was exquisite.
- You gotta admit that shit was fresh, huh?
- Was like a limerick of old.
- They should do a--
- That's what this guy, he's Lime Rick.
That's what they should call him.
- A remix of Hip Hop Rick and the Gizmo Twins.
- Lime Rick and the Gizmo Twins.
Y'all could be a new hip hop trio.
- You see them considering it thoughtfully.
They're like, oh maybe we could be.
I do look like I'm made of jizz.
Like, um, all right, a Seamus.
Normally I'd be pretty disappointed in you
bringing two strangers to our secret stronghold,
but these ones can rap.
Okay, thank you for saving our friend Seamus here.
We appreciate that and taking care of that Greech monster.
There's not much we can offer in terms of help.
just being as we're a militia
and trying to fight our own battles,
but perhaps we could provide some assistance
if you do one more thing for us.
- We already did one more thing.
We had this conversation yesterday.
And then we got, we saved Seamus.
- What?
- I'm gonna go and roll.
- What do you mean, what do you mean yesterday?
- That's an 11.
- What's your deception, two?
- Three, so it's 14.
- Okay, it's pretty good.
Let's do his insight. He's pretty, unfortunately, pretty crafty.
There's no way I can beat that.
If he gets a one.
Yeah, he got, yeah, he got 18.
I'm sorry, I thought, um...
I was still rapping.
We got taken to a different secret stockhold yesterday.
Art of storytelling.
I understand, I understand.
I was just rapping.
And I'm terminally ill.
I'm mumble rapping.
Alright, well, I know that's a lie. You don't even have to roll.
What the fuck do you want us to do?
Because if you don't say something right now, I'm gonna keep freestyling about all this bullshit you got over here.
I need you to kill the Greech Queen.
Yeah, we got dice, these are nice.
Wait, what? The Greech King? Queen?
Queen.
Oh, okay, that guy. I won't kill a king.
The Greech Queen? Oh, do you think they could do it?
If everything you said and their rhyming skills are true, that they don't take no crap from no one, I think they could do it.
Does the Greech Queen die from hip-hop freestyling?
Can we do like a "Parepa the Rapa" style battle?
Who?
It's the voice again!
He's getting scared.
Um, no.
Yeah, we'll do that shit.
The Queen of the Greeches sounds like a mean creature.
Yep.
Now you keep going.
Now you do the rest.
The Queen of the Greeches, yeah, I got one speech for you right now.
I'm gonna make her black and blue right now.
Yeah!
And then throw her in the sewer now.
Kapow!
Blau Blau Blau Blau Blau Blau Blau Blau Blau
Do do do do
Can I come? Can I come? I'm really strong now
Yeah you can come into these two's room
It'll blend right in because come is their race
Go ahead
Wait hold on, can I come or not?
Hey little frog, you're not part of this song
So do not speak while we wrap this week
You're worse than a dog
I guess dogs are pretty okay in this world
If we're already talking to a fucking frog
Yeah, I'm still, I feel, I guess it's definitely insulting what's coming my way, which is hard
to make a big...
What's coming your way, is that your day?
Damn, drop the pencil on that one.
Alright, yeah, that one I get.
I've heard that before.
Alright, you can come up, but only on one, there's one caveat to you coming.
One condition.
You got it.
I get to tie you to my body like a bulletproof vest.
Okay!
Yep.
(silence)
Okay, let's do it.
Okay, so you tie Sullivan to your body.
He's very...
I'd also like to add...
He's so excited.
Do you guys have any cork or duct tape?
Uh, yeah, of course we do.
We're Irish.
Okay, give me some cork.
Go ahead and break some bottles of fuckin' whatever and give me some cork, you fuckin' drunk piece of shit.
I like you. I like the coat of your jib, computer demon.
Thank you. You're an orangutan to me.
(laughter)
Okay, he gives you cork and duct tape.
Okay, I'd like to stuff the cork into Sullivan's mouth because I see this being a serious problem of being so close to me
And then I will duct tape on top of the cork and I'm gonna duct tape his nose, too
Because I think frogs can breathe through their skin they can so
Yeah, I thought maybe they could they so I'm gonna do that. So now he's fine
That's enough though. You're going into like you might as well be hibernating. You're basically just a piece of wood
You're basically just a piece of wood better than nothing how did you say that I hear another layer
Yeah as much as possible
What I will say
mummify him
What I will say is that before you go you should definitely rest
If you're gonna go to the Greech lair, and we'll discuss plans tomorrow
You're gonna need to sleep. You're gonna need potentially
some more assistance as well as in I would
Try to contact Patrick before you do this quest because you will you will die with just the two of you
Fuck him
Okay, call me. I would decline the quest you decline the car. You know what I
call I
Call him at the same time and our
- The exact same time.
- We cut two, Patrick, your PSP is off.
You are--
- Get your buddy out.
- Oh, blood.
- That's how D&D players cuss.
- Oh, you gods.
- Your PSP is off, but, sorry.
- We have a timer here as well.
- Oh yeah, sorry, I'm making sure.
Oh, is it over there?
- Yeah, bottom right.
- I'm a silly goober.
- Oh wow, I timed it perfectly.
I'm proud of myself.
- What do you mean the time?
- You press start when we started?
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Well it's like to the second, you know what I mean?
- You know what, if you want a compliment, yes.
- I didn't want a compliment.
I was happy.
- You're the perfect timer.
- All right, now I feel like it's a bad thing.
- If you had timed it perfectly with your brain,
that would have been pretty impressive,
but you just used another timer.
(laughing)
- If you said we're at 30.09 right then,
I would have been like, damn.
- Yeah, I guess that's true.
- Human timer.
- I was just, it's stupid, you know what, I'm stupid.
- You're not stupid.
- We're cutting, we're cutting to Patrick.
It is dark where you are, you try to move and you can't.
- Oh my God, I must be at the movies.
It's dark where I am and I can't move.
I must be at the movies.
- It all seemed too good to be true, you hear a voice.
Very convenient intel about a guy we've been worried about for some time.
Confirming our worst fears.
Oh, is this Janet? This is Janet.
And so all you had to do was fall into your trap.
But you slipped up and you got greedy and you see her appear in the light.
I knew it was you, bitch!
You working for someone besides Belinda?
You working for Gumby Superior?
I honestly don't care who both of those are.
[laughter]
All I wanted to do was get a bunch of money and then find my nephew.
Then why'd you go into my room?
I was bored!
What?
Yeah!
She's gonna roll insight on you.
Roll persuasion.
Six.
That's your persuasion.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
So I got an eight.
I mean she's like, "You were bored?"
You had charades for Xbox.
It's the only game we had.
Have you tried to play that?
That doesn't explain why you were so dogged about the whole thing.
Jamming your skateboard in there.
What does that mean?
It means you were pursuing it.
You were just keep, kept doing it over and over again.
You kept going for it.
You jammed your skateboard in there.
Oh, I was bored and I kept doing something over and over again so that I could actually
not be bored anymore. Have you ever played with a, like, a ball on the ceiling and you
keep throwing it over and over again?
No, I've never been to prison. What are you talking about?
I've been to prison twice.
You have been to prison at least once, that is true.
Twice- one time before that.
You did? Okay.
On Suckafuckabob.
And they gave you a ball?
I made the ball. Who is that? Who asked me that?
I need to know.
Who is it? Is there another guy in here?
You need to tell me everything you know.
Chris?
Wait, Chris Craig is in here!
No, no, no, don't even look at me.
Chris Craig! I haven't seen you since high school!
It's not a big deal, I work on the ship now.
Just leave me alone.
You're doing something.
Chris! Chris, can you get the fuck out of here?
I am... listen, I'm gone.
Oh my god, I'm interrogating you.
- Janitor, Chris Craig the janitor.
- Don't talk to the help.
- He's still a janitor, just like you know.
- Stuff didn't go so well for me.
I'm gonna go clean the room next door.
- Chris, get out.
- I'm really sorry, I'm really sorry.
- You should be sorry. - Wait Chris,
do you remember this?
Wait, wait, wait.
(imitates a dog)
- If you do that again, I'm gonna kill you.
- I'm out, bye.
I'll see you Patrick.
- Get out of here, Chris Craig.
- Let's also get you on the interrogation table.
- Chris Craig, who's Chris Craig?
Who's Chris Craig?
- Chris Craig is somebody else.
- No, which character is he?
Oh, here he is.
(laughing)
He's leaving.
- Bye Chris.
- And Patrick, as she moves closer,
you see that she's not pleased up.
Come on, don't do, all right.
As she moves closer, you see that--
- She's gonna suffocate me with her butt?
- You see that she--
- Good way to go for a guy like me.
She has, which you didn't notice before,
'cause before she just kinda looked like Fran Drescher.
- Yeah. - But now she's got freckles.
- She's Sans Dresser right now.
- Oh, fuck. - Yeah, fuck, that was good.
- Oh! - No, no.
Why'd you throw my-- - Just him.
- What was that? - I was going for your hand
and I missed it. - It's rude,
you weren't gonna get it.
All right, continue the scene, I'll pick my dice up.
- And now she has freckles,
and what looks like, in the dark,
from what you can tell, reddish hair.
- She looks a little different from what you're used to.
And from what you can also see,
now that you're like getting yourself
a little bit more oriented,
you're not in the guest room, you're not in her room.
- Oh, I'm down in the swamp with the other guys.
- If you look out the window,
you can kinda see space a little bit.
But what you would've seen where you were before,
but you just know that you're not where you were previously.
- Here on the moon.
- And so--
No fucking way.
Sorry, I'll leave again.
I was just playing a joke.
You're not on the moon.
Okay, bye.
Classic fucking Chris Craig, dude.
This moon joke.
I used to do it all the time in high school.
I used to kill people.
And if someone said, "Where am I?" I said, "You're on the moon."
Classic Chris Craig.
My bad.
You need to tell me everything you know right now.
Okay.
- Four plus four is... - Hold on.
- Yeah, wait.
(laughing)
- Is it gonna be a short list?
- Just, uh, just careful how you phrase that.
- Four times four is 16.
- Stop.
- First of all, I'm proud of you.
(laughing)
I didn't think you'd pull off the multiply.
- Seven times seven is 49.
- Okay, all right.
- 12 times 12 is 144.
- Ooh, all right.
- Now do 13 times 13.
- Is 162.
(laughing)
- Now 100 times 100.
- I can't, Chris, get outta here.
(laughing)
- Oh, that's not my strong suit.
- Look, I just wanted to,
are you in league?
- Are you one of these Irish leprechauns?
- I'm not.
- Your red hair and your red skin freckles.
- Fuck!
I'm not a leprechaun.
Just.
- I'm a leprechaun-vict.
Music.
- Look, I just.
- And you already know.
- Why did you go into my room?
- Bored.
- You really were just bored, weren't you?
- Yep.
God, you are something else.
Uh-huh.
All right, and she frees you from the interrogation.
And you're free to, I'm sorry, I was just--
Where's the bathroom?
It's--
Is his PSP still off?
It is still off, he can turn,
she gives it back to him, you know.
It's over there.
I turn it on and I go on my phone
'cause I'm going to the bathroom.
Okay, yeah.
you can see a missed calls but you have a missed call you get ten thousand
dollars and white that hasn't text from me that are awful
the role it's a family except for the
the means i thought it's a good idea
the sway all those of the way like one of those like nice job
yeah
not even looking at the
which is a hundred coming up with his creative
but the
so i guess i think about
who's not looking at the just on the toilet just hitting the book that night
- I'm not even sending them on Instagram,
I'm texting it to you, I'm copying the link
and texting it to you.
- It's a screenshot and he can see you have a notification
from like the doctor.
- She knocks on the door, she's like, Patrick.
- Occupied!
- Oh my God.
Okay.
- Housekeeping?
- Do that and I'll let you in.
- I don't wanna go in the bathroom,
I want you to go out.
(laughter)
Do housekeeping for Tommy boy
and I'll let you in.
Pat, you need to do housekeeping.
Oh, I open, so I say it.
He opens the door,
says housekeeping, his pants are down.
(laughter)
Oh yeah, you're right, I need to do it.
Oh yeah, you're right.
Housekeeping.
there we go
(laughter)
she starts doing it to like appease me and just be like "alright fine, i'll hook you up with an eye opener"
and we both say it at the same time and my dick is out
and your dick is up on top of the toes that you're peeing onto the floor
that's what that's meant
husky bank!
(laughing)
- All right, what do I gotta do?
- All that happens.
- What the hell am I walking into?
- Chris, you've been in here the whole time
you told me to do it.
- Oh yeah, that was funny as shit.
Okay, bye.
- Okay, all right, okay.
So all that happens.
(laughing)
She says that was one of the worst experiences in my life.
Glad it's over.
Look, all you need to do now is go talk to Huge-Ass Facts
and tell him what you learned.
- Oh, I have his phone number, I'll call him right now.
- No, you don't have his phone number.
Nobody has his phone number.
- Ah, rats. - You don't even
have his phone number.
And just forget what you saw here.
I'm sorry, I didn't trust you.
I just thought that somebody doing that would've been,
they would've had a good reason for it, but--
- Well, clearly after you've seen everything
I totally understand your whole thing. You know I may have some kind of mental disability. You're sort of a savant. I understand now.
What is he good at?
Fighting and killing. Oh yeah. Speaking of fighting and killing, how about you get your sorry ass over here and help us?
Yeah, oh wait.
My phone's not like, been on the phone. You're on call with me.
I can hear it in my pocket.
Patrick, come on.
Oh, oh snap.
What the flip? Let me check my phone.
We have to fight the gleech. Wait, wait.
What can you tell your friends?
Where, where?
Hold on, I'll give the phone to you.
Where are you guys?
Housekeeping.
Janet Blowjob.
I'm naked.
Oh my god.
They're all like this.
Where are you guys right now?
Oh wait, okay. And I pull my pants down.
Ewww!
Wait, housekeeping, housekeeping.
This is our joke.
Okay, wait.
She sort of looks around.
- And she looks around.
- I was keeping, I was keeping.
- She sort of looks around the room you're in
and she goes, okay, she turns to Patrick.
She goes, I can get you there.
If you talk to Huge-Ass Facts,
I can get you there right after, I promise.
- All right.
- Okay.
She looks at the phone again.
You guys are just naked, I guess.
- Me and Bullet Joss are like,
just touching our fingertips together like this.
She just says, "Did you guys talk to Bam McGinnis?"
Who?
Bam McGinnis.
Oh yeah, who were you talking about?
No, but we have to kill some hoe.
I'm with some hoe.
Wait, let me handle this.
Let me handle this.
Go ahead.
What of it?
So you did talk to Bam McGinnis.
I don't know who, what of him.
What was your name again?
Both of you rolled a seven.
Would you say your name is Gleek Queen?
- Was that a roll?
- No, that's not a roll.
- Here, I need a 20 'cause he dropped my d20.
- It was an accident with my drop.
- 11.
- Okay, I had your deception.
- 14, motherfucker.
- Mine is 11.
- I'm sorry?
- 11 with what?
- 11.
- Altogether?
Oh, okay.
Can you give me a d20?
- Yeah.
- You definitely have one.
- Yeah, she got 20 on her insight.
- Damn!
- Bloody hell.
- She knows.
- You should've waited a roll.
- You're right.
- A roll, gods would've blessed you.
- You guys don't know that she knows, but she goes,
okay, you guys, all right.
- Dumb bitch doesn't realize a thing.
- So-- - She's as stupid as a--
- Hey guys, she can't even tell you're lying.
(laughing)
- Yeah, look at how big my dick is.
- Damn!
- She probably thinks it's actually big.
- It's so red!
- Pull that up to the phone.
- Okay.
- Okay, I mean, I didn't--
- Stop happening.
- I'm putting the memoji on it,
I'm making it look like a chicken.
(laughing)
- Whoa, what the fuck?
- Wait, wait, keep it like that.
- Wait.
- Here, I'll get it.
- Oh, my fucking cock!
- Oh, I thought it was real, I'm sorry.
- Oh wait, I didn't remember it on the computer on the back.
- She hangs up the PSP, hands it back to you.
- We're still on the call with each other.
- She leads you to a pod, like a circular pod.
You both go in it.
- Am I meeting huge ass facts right now?
- You shoot through space.
We're on the moon pause and suddenly we're on the moon
While you're shooting through space
you're shooting towards the other end of the
pleasure palace
The end that you were originally at you were on
The bottom you went back to where they're from the bottom where they were now now you're going
Well actually you were back or the way. I had drawn the map you were at the top
So I'm was I was here you were there when you were at a fax layer
Then you were there and now you're going back down, okay?
So okay, so up then I'm down so this is where the Royal Guard or whatever is no the Royal Guard sort of in the butt
Area the back the back the fuck the Royal Guard is like there here
We're gonna hear the Royal Guard is like over here the royal the royal shit touching his tip
This is where stop this is where you were
Over here just now
We're going down here. Yes fax is over here, so I go down here
So you were just now here, and you're shooting back down the huge ass facts and while you're inside this pod
You watch as a
Bunch of little robotic hands similar to the nanobots pop out and start doing
Janet blowjobs makeup and dying her hair do mine too and making her look like mine after Janet blowjob again
You go and move in the way, and you get the same
It's a you both just look like Fred drescher, and she's like oh god and
And you come back I start taking selfies on my phone
Wait, we got a center
Really close to the camera you go like a hundred feet away and look be under it like you're holding it up
Okay, I said it to her
I pull up my phone and I just show her,
look what I did.
(laughing)
I got my friends to send me their cocks.
- That's awesome.
- 'Cause I'm a pretty woman now.
- So you land in the,
back in that part of the Pleasure Palace,
and you ride on like a conveyor belt,
and you pop out through the panel.
- And when I pop out through the panel,
the hair gets caught.
- Your weave gets caught.
- The whole mask just fucking rips.
- So you just look like you again.
- Yeah.
- And you get out and you're back
in Janet Blowjob's bedroom.
And she sort of like dusts herself off,
pushes down her leopard print dress,
and then she goes over, knocks on the guest room door,
and says, "Baby guy, wake up,
"it's time to meet huge-ass facts."
And he gets out, baby guy gets out,
He's like, "All right, let's do it then."
And he looks at you, and he like glares at you
because you had been fucking with the panel before,
but he sees that like you guys seem cool,
and so he like kind of forgets it.
And so she leads you to--
- Wait, what happened?
- Baby Gat was-- - Nothing happened
to Baby Gat 'cause didn't I leave the room
and then just like go to bed?
- Well, he was freaking out that you had done something
to her room. - So nothing happened,
so didn't she catch him in the bedroom and then I left?
- Well, you don't know if she caught him in the bedroom.
- He might have just given up,
and then she abducted you at some point.
- I assumed that I left him to get the shit kicked out of him
by her security guards.
- Um, that's, well, so, and then you see,
you also see Scooter, and he waves to you
as you walk behind. - I wave over,
I say, "Get over here."
- Okay, yeah, he sort of like,
he hops up and lands inside your robe pocket.
And then you guys go into-- - I got a pet.
- The elevator.
Kenan Thompson is already in there.
he does a little bit of like an extra thing
with the like putting his finger down
the Harry Potter ass kinda like thing with the elevator.
And the elevator moves inward.
Excuse me, sorry, I've got a whole thing
written for this part.
I promise it won't be too much,
but it will be a lot actually.
Where am I going here?
(humming)
There we go.
Yeah, this time after pushing out horizontally,
rather than continuing up or down, it keeps going.
So where the elevator last time was going up and down
and then hers, it took you to a secret room,
this time it goes forward and it just keeps going.
- It totally is the Great Glass Elevator.
- Don't even say Wonka Vader, that scared the shit out of me.
- I did not even consider.
- Wonka Vader, idea for later.
- Rather than continuing down or up--
- Charlie Bucket, I am your grandfather, Joe.
though it keeps going.
- Oh yeah, he would be.
- And as you move through the opaque elevator,
like you can't see anything outside of it,
the chatter of members of Facts Gang
and the occasional crackle and pop of machinery
and rushing of some kind of liquid you can hear
around you as the elevator is moving through,
but you can't see, excuse me, anything.
It goes right for a bit, then down,
then makes three more rights, then down again,
then one final right that pushes it further and further in.
- On the back of my phone I drew a crude map.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I'm about to get here.
- And then down again, then one,
you know what actually, roll,
I guess, let's just roll like a general--
- Roll intelligence. - Intelligence, yeah.
It's really just a general intelligence check.
Oh, not bad. - 18.
- Oh, that's good. - Plus or minus what?
- Minus one.
Or was it the number on top?
- Yeah, yeah, the minus one, yeah.
So, all right, cool.
So that's 17, that's very good.
So I will,
I will show you kind of what you drew later.
- Okay. - Like, I will remember,
I'm gonna write a note just to remember
that you drew this well.
- I drew it well 'cause I was bored again.
The elevator was taking too long.
- Yeah, after where the huge-ass fax lair is from.
- That's my savant, that's my savant.
- Yeah, one of your savant drawings when you're bored.
- I'm really good at drawing a map to somewhere.
- So when you, it goes right for a bit,
then down, makes three more rights, then stops.
Kenan Thompson then runs his fingers along the elevator panel
and the yellow doors open and reveals a dark chamber
safe for a luminescent yellow pus bulbs
that jut from the bruised, knotted flesh
you saw outside of the fax layer.
So you remember those from outside the layer.
So let's get you all the way over here.
- I'm looking at a pus bowl right now.
- Let's get up her skirt.
- Oh, gross bro. - Look at my characters.
Look at my characters.
- That is her God-given dribbler
and you'll refer to it with respect.
Okay, I'm looking at her pus filled dribbler. Thank you
Do you mind lining lining this with guys just line the sides with guys as many as you can?
Wants to get up in a guy's intestinal lining. I don't want to stop saying that
So a dark chamber safe for the luminescent yellow pus bulbs a jet from the bruised knotted flesh that you saw outside a fax layer
and in your dream
Yeah, your dreams. Oh
It's though those bulbs that you would saw so when you went to first see huge ass faxes layer
It looked like a like discarded like engine of a alien ship
Yeah with these yellow pus bulbs, and it was like just over a hole so that way
That's what I saw in the dream. This is in real life that it was like this kind of giant structure
That underneath it was a hole that led down into huge ass fax layer
Yeah, and so you're seeing those yellow bulbs again now the ones from my dream. They were also in your dream
Yeah, but they were in like you're seeing them there. You're seeing them here as well
And if you also remember before your dream happened
Your video game console you thought was like flickering
Yeah, like and like losing power almost like why as you were falling asleep, so just make painting some pictures here for you
- Scooby-Doo and the Cyber Chase.
- Yeah, it's pretty much that kind of movie.
- These bulbs--
- Can we do a Scooby-Doo and the Cyber Chase one next?
- We kind of did.
We've done Scooby-Doo and we've kind of done a Cyber Chase.
But maybe a combination of both.
- We could do a combination of both.
- Can we do it both together?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Can we do exactly Scooby-Doo, Cyber Chase,
and no plot points change from the movie at all?
- Yeah, that's fine, we could do that.
- I like this.
- And we're just saying the script.
- These bulbs light a room of--
- That movie is awesome.
- Clean white tile.
- The live action version. - Yeah.
- That gives way to a glass encasing
below which you can see one of the glowing
power cores of the ship.
Similar to what Blotoss and Ray had seen
in the upper guts in, I think it was two sessions ago maybe.
When you guys were in the scientist lab
and you saw the power core below you,
there's a power core here as well.
(laughs)
There's a power core here as well.
So it's like on one end of the ship there was a power core
and the other end of the ship there was a power core, okay?
So, and you can see it below these sort of glass encasings.
Where everything about the lair
had been clean and bureaucratic,
this chamber has an ancient flair.
The bulbs like sort of roomy abscissions.
It's like they're like these old, old things,
like ancient looking things.
Sitting beneath the bulbs, watching you,
Gad and Janet, watching you, Gad and Janet,
as you walk across the chamber are a number of factoids.
Factoids are elite agents in service of huge ass facts.
They're dressed casually, they're all manner of races,
ape, clown, goblin two, fungoid.
The difference being that their eyes glow
with an eerie yellow.
- Cough much?
- Excuse me, yes.
That is, damn dude.
- Had that locked and loaded since the last cough.
- I know.
Their eyes are yellow though,
these people that they're watching.
Yellow eyes, what are they, the lava monster
from Hercules, the animated movie?
No, the yellow, that's not the,
that's the first thing that has yellow eyes.
It's not really as good as Koffmuch, but whatever.
Their eyes are yellow and matching the luminescent bulbs
as well. Are they staring at me?
They are watching you guys as you're walking through.
You're flipping them off, that's pretty cool.
Take a picture to last longer, bitch.
Yeah, the dark eerie sinewy walkway gives way
to a cool steel platform at the end of the chamber.
So it's like this white tile, these weird bulbs,
and these guys on the other side with the yellow eyes,
and the bulbs and the fleshy shit
that looks like the alien ship with the clear white tile.
And then at the very end is sort of this raised platform.
And you see,
beyond that is a large bay window.
So there's a large bay window
that is looking out at planet E-Bomb as well.
Atop this is a modern minimalist desk
and the back of a large segmented chair behind it.
So one of those like--
- The elusive man.
- Sort of.
That's kind of what I'm looking for here, yeah.
So, and, so beyond this,
similar to that, the command center that Blotas and Ray,
so similar to the command center that you guys saw
with that bay window, this kind of like mirrors that,
but it's on the bottom of the ship now.
- Dope.
Where we put the black folder up, that place.
- Yes, yeah, that place.
but it's where instead behind this chair is Hugh J. Fax.
And what you can see is less of Gunn City
and more of the white fog of the uninhabitable sea bomb
that sort of surrounds Gunn City.
- I point at it and I say, "Blow that up."
- You also see minority report like holograms
kind of flashing along the windows,
them like swiping back and forth.
And the segmented chair spins around
revealing a pudgy bulldog of a man
of some 40 odd years with slick black hair and a goatee.
- Oh, that was supposed to be Chris Craig.
- And mesmerizing eyes.
- Here he is, bulldog of a man.
- Holy crap, it's Chris Craig.
- No, it's not Chris Craig, it's this guy.
- Yeah, it could be that guy.
As his gaze settles on, sorry, sorry, yeah.
- You think gays should settle?
- No, hold on.
- They should settle down with their husbands?
- They should settle down with their husbands
- I think things could be a whole lot better.
- His eyes also seem to like--
- Where those guys eyes are--
- Straits could be slaves.
- Where those guys eyes are yellow,
his eyes seem to like shift along the spectrum.
Like as you look at them from different angles,
it's like they kinda like keep shifting.
He wears a sleek gray Zhongshan suit,
sort of like a Chinese suit.
- You wanna try that again?
- Zhongshan.
- You wanna explain what the fuck you're talking about?
- He's wearing a Zhongshan suit.
- A Zhongshan is like sort of like,
it's like kind of like a Mandarin collar,
kinda Mao--
- And it's made by P. Diddy.
- Yeah, you're thinking he did it.
- It's like a Mao suit.
- You're thinking John John.
- Sean John.
- No, Zhang Xiong.
- You're thinking John.
- Jubio, can you pull up Zhang Xiong?
- Big Sean.
- Z-H-O-N-G.
- Sean.
- Oh God.
- S-H-A-N.
- Guys, we're moving on.
- Okay.
(laughing)
With a gold bulbous pin sitting at the top of his collar.
As his gaze settles on Janet,
his eyes kind of settle a little bit in a light brown.
I mean, his eyes flicker towards you, Patrick.
And his stony face slackens just enough to speak.
As he speaks, the bulbs in the room
pulse in time with his voice.
- Janet, you've deemed this diversion important enough
to take time away from data collection.
- Do you have peanut butter in your mouth, bitch?
- Excuse me?
- Sorry, I have Tourette's.
- Well, Mr. Fax,
(clears throat)
Patrick Yoda, who's this loud gentleman here,
and Baby Gadd discovered something very interesting
while conversing with our friend Gumby Superior.
Patrick, play what's on your PSP.
- I was already playing with it.
- No, no.
(laughing)
- Picture of my giant red dick.
- No, Patrick, the recording.
- Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- He's right by the table.
recording me going "uh, uh, uh"
*laughter*
Do you have a recording of your friend
making those noises? Oh I have a recording of my
friend and it's a video of him and it's like him
with like, the camera below
is nuts. No they should have to use the picture of
me with the big red dick to figure out where
they are.
Yeah you're just scrolling through all the text that you've got
since we think that you're the woman with makeup
and it's like me fucking my shoe.
*laughter*
Go to your audio, give me your PSP.
- She takes your PSP from you.
She finds the audio recording,
she almost throws up in her mouth
as she looks at the audio recording.
She finds it, she plays it,
it's Gummy Superior's speech about
how he's gonna try to basically destroy the undercity
and he wants your guys' help and yada yada yada
and those are his plans for it.
And he says,
- It is difficult to get intel from the command center.
And this is vital information if he means to kill us all.
It's shrouded in too much doublespeak to use it against him, but this changes things.
A fact I had not known.
As he says this, he raises his right hand and holds his palm towards the sky.
One of the bulbs near to him pushes out of the wall.
So it's a bulb, it like pushes out of the wall like on a stalk.
He's like, (slurping)
like that kind of noise, you know what I'm saying?
- Do it again.
(slurping)
- Oh, God. - You know what I'm saying?
- Do it again.
(clearing throat)
- Cough much?
- And it careens towards his hand,
and Fax places his mouth on the bulb.
When he pulls his mouth away,
he wipes yellow liquid from his lips.
- Let me get a bite.
- Oh, you can't have any of this.
- I don't actually want it.
I'm just saying everything that comes into my mind.
"Gad, expect a generous cash infusion in your business, continued support and protection.
The twins, nor anyone else in my command, shall bother you any longer,
and you are dismissed."
And you see two factoids come around
to escort Gad out. Gad's like,
"Woo! Yes!
Okay, I owe you big time, Pat!
You can come by any time, you can do whatever you want, don't fuck up with this game."
"Smack him. Smack him right now." "I owe you big time, man."
Smack him.
You know what? Fuck you too!
Fuck you too! I could have done this without you!
No, I was flipping out the other guy!
And just kidding! And I love you and thank you so much and fuck you!
No, again I was flipping out the other guy!
You're being very confusing!
And then he starts, you hear him like cheering and getting all excited as he leaves.
He does that skip where he taps both of his feet together.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, he does that.
Wait.
That's the number one way to do that is figurine.
Yeah.
(laughing)
- And he leaves.
- SpongeBob ass.
- Yeah.
- You, Yoda.
- Do you know where my nephew is?
I'm gonna be point blank.
I'm just gonna ask.
- That's what I wanted to hear.
- That's what you wanted to hear?
- Because you want something more than just money.
I would give you--
- No, wait, hold on.
- Oh.
- I want two things at once.
(laughing)
- No, no, no, no, I said more than just money.
you will be compensated for what you've done today.
- I'll get three things?
- You're going to get 25,000 tokens from me.
(imitating game sounds)
But, if you want to find your precious nephew.
- Drop it low.
(laughing)
- Just like, crumping.
Doing a Fortnite dance.
(laughing)
If you want to find your precious nephew,
everything Gumby Superior said, he's a,
how do I, he's arrogant.
- A bitch.
- And a bitch as well, that's well said.
- You don't have to put the filter on on me.
You know I'm not PC.
- I can very much tell this.
I will not just offer you my most precious gift,
information
i will offer you power
insight and network
late on me
and i don't care if there's a catch just do it i'm lost
let me tell you the catch though you will want to hear this car right then
once i tell you what i want you to do
if you do not fall through with it
or you choose not to follow through with it
i'm afraid i will have to monitor everything you do for the rest of your
life
until...
Oh, there's already someone doing that.
[laughter]
I've already got a few people who do that.
And if you step somewhat out of line in that instance, unfortunately,
I will have to kill you.
But, if you do what I ask you to do again,
you will have access to my network,
and in 24 hours I will find your nephew.
[laughter]
It's kinda hard.
That is pretty sick.
yeah i'm a do it i don't care
his which and if i ask him to kill us
well wait
no
you should do it i think it is a good idea
better ideas whatever you're going to say that it was going to go on a quest
you have to find a treasure
uh... i don't think you know you
it
it is like you have to kill a dragon to find a treasure
You have to find the jade monkey.
You have to level up three times.
You have to raise your acrobatic stat by jumping up in place.
You have to collect 15 turtle shells.
There are seven puzzle pieces.
When you collect them, you'll get to the next level.
Find the location of this painting.
Find where in the game this photograph was taken from.
Spot six differences in this photo.
Like seven daffodils so you can make a new potion.
Here's what it is.
Here's what you'll need to do.
In two days time,
Leo's Thunderland opens once again.
There will be a celebration of sorts.
And there will be an address made by Gumby.
You will kill him in front of everyone.
I will have Patrick Yoda, member of Sullivan's Angels,
murder a war hero in front of the entire space station.
You will then be brought to the brig. You will be put up for execution
And it is here that I will free you
Grant you immunity. Oh if I'm free then yeah, I don't care
And since my research will be concluded by then I will reveal the location of your nephew
Okay done
Okay, you trust me?
No, but I'm gonna do it anyway cuz I'm bored of your talking I
respect that and
And next time, we will have you go join up with the guys
with your new mission of murdering a general
in front of everyone.
- And it will be easy.
- And you guys will enter the Greech's glare.
- The Greech's glare.
- The dojo.
- Greech's green.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- The snake pit.
- Cool.
- Okay, bye.
- Bye.
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[music]