[music]
Last time on Gun City, a broad city, the Uncle's Falcon, our heroes founded a new restaurant that serves hot dog--
wait, no, that serves hot soda and cold dogs, which I'm pretty sure was just called Hot Soda and Cold Dogs.
I couldn't find me saying the name in my recording, so...
and passed the business on to Sullivan the Frog's superfan Gary C. Enterprise.
Convinced a few people to commit suicide, and then, atop a giant worm,
they rode through Soy Lake to meet with Freaking Carol Baskin,
only to discover she was murdered.
The boys dug through her belongings, discovering hidden messages
sent between Freaking Carol and several mysterious characters
we've come to know and love throughout the arc.
They found a terrified little tiger named Tigger,
who told the gang some more info on what freaking Carroll was up to before he was suddenly seized
with terror backing away from the boys and promptly assassinated by the killer Kiklops,
an elite assassin within Papi Chuko's ranks. In the midst of all this chaos, the boys also
received a distressing call from their assistant and pal Sullivan, who seems to have been caught
in some terrible fight at the suckler's den. Patrick Yoda's spectacular ears allowed him to
pick up that it could be Papi Chuko himself who abducted their dear friend. And Patrick
Gilda's spectacular aim allowed him to finish off Killer Kiklops before he did some truly insane shit that maybe I will share in the discord one day.
Following a tip from that same mysterious number that texted our heroes before, our three sleuths traveled beneath freaking Carol's home,
underneath Soy Lake and found the return pods back to the real world from The Matrix 2.
Their arrival, however, was intercepted by a mysterious scientist who stands before them now,
Ready to launch into an absurdly long monologue that will hopefully clear up some stuff,
but will leave just enough mystery at the edges to keep people curious about what's going on.
Um, reminders. None of the reminders are really going to be relevant,
um, because, uh, there's going to be sort of a reset, you'll see.
Um, but, uh, Patrick Yoda, you have level one addiction to Techno Slime,
and Rey, you have level two. That's really the only thing that matters right now.
I would not have that. What does that do?
For level 1 it just means that every time Patrick Yoda takes it, he has a risk of reaching to level 2 addiction.
And also that whenever he takes Techno Slime, he's going to have disadvantage on Dexterity saving throws afterwards.
He started crying because disadvantage was so sad.
I can imagine him having disadvantage.
This has something in my eye.
There's something about disadvantage Patrick's everywhere in the world.
Well, we can talk about that.
But some of that, I mean that will only matter depending on how the next few moments go.
So you guys, just to set you guys up, so you have room here.
You guys fell sort of like a cartoon like blump, blump, blump, right?
like on top of each other. I'm on top. Okay. Nope. I'm in the middle. Nevermind. I'm on
the bottom. I changed my mind. I'm on top but I'm standing because I'm so small. Okay. So
you two fell and on your like stomachs and Patrick you're just sort of like just like
sort of like glided in and is standing. I have the force. Yeah, that's right. And before
you is a scientist with crazy hair and you know, a lab coat that's all dirty and matted
But his lab is like a gorgeous like technological wonder you see, you know test tubes and pipes and all that shit
but also you see like
That fucking like astrolabe kind of shit in the middle that's just like spinning and conducting something that you know
You don't know what it's conducting
uh
And and you also see a giant uh, like machine that looks like some sort of shrink ray
and
Uh, he sort of looks at all of you
uh like a like a real ricky morty sort of way and he says uh uh at last we finally meet i'm so glad
what is it is that ricky morty no my name is dr tool lateralis
Well, from earlier.
Yeah, maybe.
Why would you say that?
I heard your name before.
Yeah, I believe that.
I mean, you said at last we meet.
So, I mean, I think it's pretty fair to assume that we might have heard of you.
I don't know why you're acting so crazy.
Are you OK?
I don't understand why you said that now.
OK, well, I feel your forehead.
Are you feeling OK?
He feels OK.
OK, you're all right.
the area and i will claim the but he has a lot of what he's on your laptop
now that i look at it
the way but i would like my hands on your laptop to i a
i wouldn't have it any other way alright thank you i've got some dirt on my hands
for the better
fondling the scientist i'm gonna stay on the floor
and you know
i have
much to tell you
all that
all
right yeah
skin
no it's just that it's respectful to stand up and you have a laboratory you
respect him in his laboratory
pick me up
dot i think you are picking up
thank you
you do everything for him
yeah what is what i did not realize that one day i'm not going to be then
Why did you tell why are you doing a Boston accent Patrick Yoda? What what changed in your brain?
I've been doing it
You're doing a different accent in this episode
I don't remember the last one I did
He did it for six episodes
You were doing like a how did you forget?
We're gonna do this you're gonna do in that. Hey, I did one of these. Hey, how's it going?
How you doing?
Like this. No, you sounded like a 1930s baseball player and no, ah, okay. I see
i see you there we go we go now it's back
now okay i think i hit my head too hard when i fell down
congratulation yeah i hit my head too hard i became
from boston okay mr tool lateralis seat what's up man it's dr tool
lateralis oh okay look i didn't spend seven days at bed school to not
lie about being a doctor. Anyway, I have much to tell you, please. And he's sort of like,
you see like three like very comfy chairs come up from the ground, sort of below you guys to
like get you guys settled in. I have a very long monologue to go through. When I was a young,
just a young scientist of around 527, I was working at Stakehams Federation of Bodies and Spaces as a
a four-hire chief researcher in the Technical Innovation and Development
Division under the potentially war crime type stuff if everybody is cool with
that department. I'm fine with war crimes. Hey, they were too. There I was hired to
develop the Calculus Rift, an idea that came to then president of
Stakehams, XKCD Musk, in one of his many dreams where Lila Futurama beats him to
death with his father's penis. The vision was to create a way to bring the virtual
people into the real world.
Beginning the process of blending our universes.
I worked on the project for 10 long years and once it was complete, the Calculus Rift had
a slow adoption rate.
It turns out, marketing people to insert a device into their penis when they turn 13
was not as popular as we hoped.
At least not among all cultures or creeds.
The project was almost completely shut down
until Poppy Chuko's Technoslime Corporation stepped in,
bought up the rights to the technology,
my team, and brought in a ton of resources for us.
With his buy one and I will give you free drugs campaign,
Poppy had everyone and their great uncle
hooked on the calculus rift.
V folks and real folks were all intermingling
in beautiful harmony, you know,
and the future looked bright, you know, you've lived it.
One day, Poppy called me into his office
said what I'd been waiting for him to say. We need to go cordless. The Coculus Rift 2.0.
The Coculus Quest cordless experience. This was it. The dream. No painful insertion. No
limits. A satellite based projection of Coculus Rift technology to everyone of all ages, of
all races, even the Polish, throughout all of planet E-Bone.
With the completion of the quest, the Matrix 2 would be able to fully blend with our world.
It would be the end of reality, the end of virtual reality.
There would only be a hyper-reality superimposed upon our collective interpretation of the present.
XKCD Musk's dream of being beaten to death by Leela Futurama, whenever and wherever he
wanted was finally in reach.
I began development for the next few months, working tirelessly, day in and day out, when?
Out of the blue, I was contacted by a mysterious man
referring to himself as S&M.
Our correspondence spanded a wide array of topics.
But one he was keen on learning more about
was the thing I could not divulge on,
Calculus Rift 2.0.
As our friendship grew, we decided to meet in person
in a surreptitious sort of manner.
And it was none other than famous activist, Sean McElwee.
Sean was concerned about something he learned
from an inside source in Poppy's crew
about what the calculus Riff was being used for.
What he described to me was certainly believable,
but preposterous controlling people's minds.
It's been tried, of course.
And it's been tried of course,
by every corporation worth its salt in gun city,
but no one has ever been so heartless
or competent to carry it out.
And not with my technology, certainly.
Well, I took what Sean said very seriously
as there's no person more serious
than activist Sean McKay.
And so I dug into some of what Poppy was up to.
And it was true.
I was heartbroken.
Suddenly the implications of making the Oculus 2.0
horrified me.
Poppy would effectively be able to control the entire world,
getting everyone hooked on techno slime,
suddenly manipulating every facet of our lives.
I began to stall on the project
while Sean and I planned a way to disrupt
Poppy's nefarious scheme.
Sean was Poppy's nephew-in-law,
which is one of the most treasured of relationships.
And he used that and his sly charm and good looks
to our advantage,
discovering details of Poppy's plans,
figuring out ways to sabotage and expose his corruption.
But of course, it went all the way up.
Jeff Tiedrich was aware of it, the Mad Suckler.
All of these big players knew that Poppy
had some control over the population,
but not to what extent, we realized.
If we could get these guys to turn on Poppy,
maybe then we could bring in Stakehams,
which still has some authority, however marginal,
and the public at large to condemn him
and cancel him forever.
A fate worse than death.
But Sean, well, he had his vices.
He would fall out of contact suddenly.
Sleeping with one V-Girl one night,
double teaming another with cyborg David Blaine another night.
He'd go on benders,
just to escape the pressure of his great duty to activism.
My dilly-dallying was starting to frustrate Poppy meanwhile.
He was picking up on my intention to delay progress.
So I was taken off the Cocculus Rift 2.0 project
and relegated to the abandoned porno factory,
where I was under surveillance by his goons
and forced to develop new techno-slime products.
Sean had been missing for a few days now,
but he arrived at the factory to rescue me.
But in my escape, he was captured.
I haven't seen him since.
I don't even know if he's alive.
Before this, Mommy Goodlegs and freaking Carol Baskins
were the only two broads worth a damn,
helping me keep track of Sean.
They were our gals on the inside,
but soon their correspondence stopped as well.
I learned what happened to Carol.
But Mommy, I think she just got cold feet.
So I've remained here in my secret laboratory
underneath Comet Ping Pong 2,
hoping the top 10's tattletale agencies
Investigation would lead you to the Matrix 2.
Praying I'd be able to intercept you
when you transported out of it.
I'd like to think mommy had some idea
what I was thinking and help set this up,
but I don't know.
Regardless, at last, the music swells.
Gentlemen, we meet.
You see, you were the key to our plan all along
because the three of you are Papi Chuko's best agents.
We were hoping to get to you before too much attention
was drawn to your investigation,
nevertheless
To even have you three in my laboratories a miracle
Poppy has been controlling you for years and the last act you did for me or for him rather was to capture Sean McKelvey
You are his kidnappers
What I have been working on is a way to remove the cockula's rift from people's penises and we need to remove them from yours
Immediately so we can escape so you can escape poppies control
Afterwards, we'll set up a meeting with him and he'll think he can control you, but he won't be able to so you play right along
And you know, then you pass but before all that we have to get inside your penises
That'll make sense
And Ray William Johnson, what's your way to belittle that?
that
I love Adam Curtis.
And what are you listening to, Bluetooth-piss?
Just white noise.
You were just talking for a long time.
I was trying to go to sleep.
Yeah, I get it.
While writing this, I realized this is probably going to be a huge turnoff for them.
And maybe even for the listeners.
But it had to get out some way.
Anyway.
This is huge.
my jaw is a gape
so you're saying we were under control the whole time?
well not the whole time
you know you've been acting as if you were controlling us. so you're saying when i
when i fucked my big beautiful
Dominican wife, Cameron, you're saying Bobby Chuko
he made me do that?
no no no no no
not all of the time. yes i think he did
i think that's what he would never he would never fuck a woman of his own
police and i mean i i i don't i don't even know exactly why
you know i mean i don't think that i mean surely are are restaurant cold dogs and
hot soda
that i don't work that it was all of the way we did that
well i know we did that
yeah there's no doubt in my mind that i think you know that never have come up
up with such an incredibly smart business plan.
- We've been thinking of that forever.
- What I'm saying is that not,
you are controlled all the time.
The times you're controlled, you probably black out.
You don't remember.
- I slap Ray William Johnson in the face and I say,
I think I just got controlled.
- Do it again.
- I do it again.
- Nice.
you have to do it one more time i think
yeah one more time i kick patrick
all right you weren't controlled then i know you weren't controlled then
this new voice is really getting me i don't know how you lost the voice
wait if i've been controlled this whole time
because i just lost control i'm not under control anymore and now i'm doing my normal voice
yeah and i'm just a guy
no listen
i'm gonna try doing a backflip
and i tried to act with the night is a small black
no no no role i can't object to truthfully
let's say i would like dungeons address instead
it's kind of my fault it's not just make 'em ups
yes
yeah you know it's sort of like a
you like to the thing where you like to land a little bit too
top-heavy it's easier to walk forward a bit
and you can see it
yeah i must definitely be being controlled is normally i would stick it
perfectly
okay tell it's not let's look
when you control when you're not controlled who's fucking who's
dominican wife
we need to focus
i know it's me to nobody else is bugging my dominican wife
well you know you don't know that yet
and that's how that's one of the mysteries we are we've been trying to
tell it where trying to figure out all these mysteries
yeah i guess the episode still young you could not get the right again
the
are going to have a set of this adventure in fifteen minutes
so
uh... in front of you there's a massive shrink way
well shrink
recruiting for a way
now is a massive shrink way but in front of you
and with with a small quest the wise sphere sitting at the end of the way
gun parted
machine
and since that's just my son
mcgann here
you've a very intelligent son he's hot he's done is so good at reading he's
talking to a shrink
the
well
to the side of that you see three jobs of raw techno slime
Similar to the stuff that Ray William Johnson drank a few episodes ago.
You see I kept busy in my lonesome laboratory under the abandoned porno factory. While I was under surveillance,
I wasn't necessarily under supervision so to speak,
so I developed this raw techno slime blend that when ingested
gives you the ability to withstand my shrink ray without your molecules turning into diarrhea.
I must warn you, once you drink this, we'll have to move quickly.
We'll treat two of you at a time. You will infiltrate the third one's penis and remove the calculus rift within it
It will require some ingenuity and you will likely have to face nanobot manifestations of your inner soul or as I named them
calculus guardians
They cannot be dismantled without confrontation of some kind and while the two while the two are on the inside
They'll be doing most of the heavy lifting
But the person whose penis they are inside it will need to perform the final
Exorcism of the calculus rift through a sheer force of will until that is completed the struggle will continue inside of the penis
you
So this is this is shin megami tensei penis five
You have to be willing to help yourself to get the help you need so to speak
So drink up and then we'll go inside a penis
Say that one more time
You want me to go inside of his penis? I pointed Patrick
Yeah, we can list leave the one on Patrick
Don't do that
Well, it's up to you guys I think it would be better if we all of you are not under poppies control
But if you really want to
Leave
They're gonna go in they're gonna go in my penis. Oh
Hey, man, if I gotta do it, let's do it man, whatever man
Do I still have those two other things of no you gave them you gave them to a junk
Didn't we give just one did we have a huge argument about?
About how many to give him? I
Think wait, let's check you. Did you update your inventory or did I update your inventory?
I looked at my inventory and it just says huge worm
I feel like I think I have one should we listen back like who's that will take so long to find now
I think I think we definitely just have one it would be very funny if someone gets mad about that about the inconsistency here
I pray
But yeah, so yeah, I mean regardless
So yeah, Ray William Johnson, you don't need to drink another one of these because you
Drank all of it that whole one
so
You're already sort of like
Lubricated more. Yeah, fuck it. I'd do it. Anyway. Yeah, of course you do. So yeah, all right, I drink my extra one. Yeah
Okay
- so you all drink it
The same description from last time right? So panorama of colors lights a gnarled subspace floods your senses and all that, right?
You know
Yeah
As you attempt to move your body you feel each cell vibrate and stutter as if you're slipping through a vast
Primordial humming your bones and muscles weaken melt and shiver back together re-render not reform within each moment
Space and time feel observable the seas
Like seas swirling plasma clouding what remains of your sense of self. Is this ego death?
Ray William Johnson
Your vision that you had earlier remains the same you see
As it was last time you see fat bitches falling from the sky out of a giant coke zero can
falling into a pool from chameleon airs cribs
is
that
the who's saying that's like uh... who's there is uh...
you know that one
i don't know what it's called
we've got to do it
i'd just add a little bit
bobby bobbitt
okay so you hear that song you're going to be a good to see this
horrible little
smiles and your ear
and laughable
horrible
patrick you know
uh...
you see your homeworld fuck a sucker pop
it's rolling mists and strange swampy greenery
if you like a child once again
you're playing with your favorite toy
what was your favorite toy
my favorite toy was uh... it was
it's just another yoda
you only have yoda toys on there
that's so sad
your parents approach you in this vision as you're playing with your little yoda toy
and they tell you it's time to go to school
nope
(laughter)
- Do you stay and go to school or do you run?
- I run.
Are you kidding?
- So, the three of you from your visions come to,
your form begins to re, you know, sort of,
you sort of feel yourself reconstitute and realign.
And you see Dr. Tualatareles in front of you.
and he says now whose penis first
my
let's get my let's get a let's get patrick over with
okay and i put it i think i i think that a close spin
i put it on my nose
okay i'm ready
patrick gilda
are you ready
yes penis inserted i'd just said yes okay all right wait penis inserted wait hold on
doctor do all that is not what i signed up for a listen man look i don't know
how i'm going to have a penis
but i don't care what i have an inserted somewhere i don't know about that
ninety i think it's i think what i'm trying to say is
you can have it
just get it all the way it battles here
okay and he sits behind the shrink ray
whips it around
and shoots it
at you ray william johnson you blowtoss piss
and you feel yourself shrink shrink and shrink and shrink until you're like a
pecan
teeny-weeny and he catches you on a little petri dish
uh...
okay pretty fun voices
uh... is here
uh...
patrick yoda
uh... you and that your parents
revealing your penis
and doctor to a lateralis
takes
a needle
puts the boys in the needle
and stabs your penis in on that first and checks them into it
and you boys shoot
to the local on
i don't care how i'm fine with the figure here five with all that
you injected into the penis
and you both of you arriving to a dark
or
hollow cavern
fucking idiot
newton
miss shrouded in swampy
countless shallow lakes and lagoons seem in the distance as well as bog wings
dragon sanks
uh...
butcher bugs slain zvine snakes and swamp slugs
examples of flora include the lady a plant
the yoga plant in our tree in your own seats
but he's there in my opinion and a p
yeah
it it's
yet they go back
of the now trees that emerge from the receding green and thick waters
The once inundated lowlands revert back to a marshy swamp.
The air grows more humid as you walk through this strange penis, until you stumble across
a strange-looking older Yoda man.
courtesy of neutral party who is makes the best maps actually Branson was the
one who you who turned me on to them not he didn't talk to me about it but I saw
that he repped them and I was like oh they're really good but yeah it's a
really good swamp map anyway it's Doug Yoda Patrick Yoda's father he stands in
front of you homework you must do he's in my penis
to a lateralis addresses you Patrick he says no your father is not in your penis
again it is merely a manifestation he is guarding the cockula's rift hey hey
Patrick Yoda guess what I just found in your dick your own dad dude yeah no I
i can't hear anything and i heard a lot of my own way dot he's looking the inside
of it he's not only a little bit i don't know you're you're not in here
yeah you would know what i think you know that you have a post on ebay
just said it's a manifestation it's not real
yeah well it is a man and he's really enjoying it i don't know how he's not
it's not really all of my life but i think i got a man infestation and i
don't have a good infestation you do not be a
Well let's see if you have a man infestation.
Which one?
It's the D20, I'll just see.
Wow.
A Nat 20.
You absolutely do not have a man infestation.
I don't have a man infestation!
You have a woman infestation.
I have a woman infestation.
Okay, okay, you sick.
Also, okay, wait, I, I, I, some, I look out of the tip of his penis and I ask Mr. Toole,
Dr. Tool. Wait, so this is Patrick Spina's?
Yeah.
Okay. I just punched the ground as hard as I can.
Stop!
I keep punching it.
I bet you like that.
No, I don't like that!
Yeah, you like it.
There we go.
It's going to be an L1, dude.
I'm calling it here.
You love it.
you get a little bit of semi job
and that's it
that's just because they were smoking
heard thanks man that's gonna make it a lot harder for us down here
slick the classic uh...
uh... do look at the war and i start sucking him off
and uh... you've got a move
uh...
so why you guys are punching your friends
and inside
uh... i say that like what you guys doing like i didn't put you inside your
friends penis uh...
uh... you see doug yoda
uh... suddenly like just
go
like clench
and
uh... then
duplicate
what that
what the f
doctor to a letter alice uh... addresses you patrick
the meat is they're going up for danger
patrick what do you see it to a form
What did you see in your vision?
Well...
I ran away from school, 'cause I didn't want to do homework.
That's a- a natural reaction.
*burp*
Excuse me.
I keep doing that.
*giggle*
But...
What that means to me is that...
Oh no.
You're going-
Boys!
You're going to need to fight...
Patrick's dad!
You're going to need to confront homework!
Oh, great.
Oh my god. Here I got this. Hey you two should kiss.
That'd be pretty hot. You look like twins.
Homework you must do. They don't seem to know how to say anything besides.
These guys have no sense of humor.
Roll for initiative.
I'm rolling for initiative. Oh my game. One launch. Hold on.
So yeah, Patrick Yoda, while they're rolling for initiative and the conflict begins to grow,
You do start to feel like your penis vibrating more, not in a pleasurable sense.
You start to see visions of math problems and arithmetic floating in front of you and like attendance classes.
This is the worst thing that could have happened to me.
You hear like, "Yoda, Yoda," like you're late for class.
It's a Ferris Bueller reference.
Yeah, if I'm gonna keep--
How I wanna kill myself.
And yeah, you just see like images of like degrees and like, like pictures of pictures of essays is what I said.
Yeah, just everywhere. So what's going to happen is you guys are going to have to defeat these Yodas.
Once you do, Patrick Yoda, you're going to have to perform some a task of some kind.
I'm know if you succeed
It will be exercised the the cockula serif if you fail the Yodas will come back
With not full health, but you'll have to defeat them again. You make Patrick exercise
Fucking luck brother. Hey
Hey watch it. Hey, man
I'm just having fun
So the Otis go first and
They we switch that around please. No, can we have it switched? Can we get that switch? We change that?
Initiative of 16 when we're when we're editing this episode. I'm putting our turn before theirs
And they move up a little bit there's three there's three now
You hear like overlaid like now like, you know for them homework you must do are they saying Homer? Oh
Yeah, I can do Homer
What do you
It is your turn Ray William Johnson, oh
All right, let's kill them no, dude use your grenade on them use your grenade on them
i i i got it's actually my turn so maybe you could wait your turn that's why we
have turned to the first place maybe shut the fuck up or something i think it's
turned away from him
no
i use my grenade
nice of that hits for sure
eighteen
and where do you what point you choose by the way
uh... let's see study for a is from point of explosion
every boxes five feet
the up
uh... canada and right there then
Alright, I'm gonna roll for damage.
Do it.
Nine.
Nice, yeah, you throw the sexual grenade, it's a pulsing ball sack,
you throw it, it lands in the middle of all the yodas,
and it explodes, covering them in fiery demon cum.
And they're like, "AHH! HOMEWORK YOU MUST DO! AHH!"
They're just like, burning.
They're still standing, but they're not looking too good.
Nice.
Uh, you're up, Blotaspis.
are no nonsense i shoot the one of them in the head
right away
go for it
so i do it right away
right away
that's a twenty that's
all right damage for
which one did you pick which one on the far left let's say
yet so you a minute
you a mere your your grinch gun and you should
and you get it right fucking between the eyes and you see
patrick it is dad doug you know that
his eyes roll in the back of his head
and and just go and just say how are you more
room and just like
like just dissolved into
digital
fucking shit
that's right
yeah you have another attack obviously
so yeah i'm just gonna shoot the next one
yeah fucking go line 'em up not come down
that's right
eleven
uh... that you know that was able to use the force and sidestep it
I'm sorry.
- Oh, bitch, dude.
- He's like, "Hmm, you should do homework.
"I mean, homework you must do."
(all laughing)
- Meanwhile, the Yodas are now back again.
Dr. Toul Laderal is like working at the computer,
typing, typing away.
Patrick Yoda, you're sort of just like, you know,
still suffering from this like vision of school
and arithmetic.
And--
- I hate it.
- Yeah. - I hate it.
and roll a wisdom saving throw.
- Me?
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay, 14.
- Okay, yeah.
So you see a math problem sort of come at
into your field of vision,
and you're able to dispel it
with an image of a cold hot dog.
Just sort of vanishes away.
- Nice.
- Yeah.
And one of these Yodas is not gonna be able to multiply now,
but the other two will,
and they're approaching you.
on now
and they're able to sort of dislike float in the air
she
okay i don't know how it's
they're getting close
it's your turn
uh... really in jesse
but i don't i don't know uh...
so they're going to get it right now it's my turn it
it was a really i knew i i knew
to throw the great
you didn't know
i'm gonna throw it on look i'm taking it out right now
every day happy
it's a good thing
yeah that hits
okay
you've got a
seventeen damage or lock
yes okay
so you throw it and it's a particularly
juicy sack
yeah uh...
uh... you see how the it is
you see that uh... but someone on fire in this guy like uh... you know
and just like melt
uh... this one
is gone this one is gone that one
is gone
uh...
and this one is going to do it
yet another one still a guy that's closer yet go for it
down i want to run up to him and hit him
with my a_a_a_ you should run up to him and hit him
how does that feel
thank you i appreciate your advice because i'm a good friend and i
understand you're only trying to help
maybe the problems me
Okay, I run right up to uh...
Yeah, do it.
To the Yoda and I use my dual pipes.
That's a 19.
That hits. Here, that's Rey, so...
16 damage.
Yeah. You fuckin' beat this Yoda-ass dad to death.
Hey, Patrick, I just killed your dad!
That's fine! We're estranged!
[laughter]
And he's gone.
But suddenly, it starts to rumble and you see the swamp open up.
And out comes the granddaddy.
Oh my god!
How many feet by how many feet is that?
It is a massive fucking Travis Scott Fortnite sized ass Yoda.
That is saying "Homework you must do."
Ah. And uh...
Grumpy cat.
And all that good stuff.
stuff and it is its turn and it's able to move right up on you and it's going to
swing it takes a it's it's lightsaber out which is about the size of like like
it's about 30 feet long and so it's gonna try to swing it at both of you so
it's like you see its arm come down so Patrick Yoda you feel yourself like
vibrating even faster as the the massive manifestation of your father and his
phallic saber comes down on your friends when when when the giant Yoda draws his
lightsaber Patrick's penis starts to glow yeah you hear your penis you you like
move around to talk you're wait I just realized I have one HP yeah oh you would
all be fully healed by the way sorry it's like fuck dude this is not gonna be
the
that
a
I'm the best and I'm the greatest.
No, you know it's not good.
You know what's not good though is taking
taking a 12 points damage each.
Oh my god.
I'll let Caleb take all the damage
and I'll just leave.
I'll take none.
Caleb, if you take all the damage
you will be the best guy in the world.
Seriously?
Yeah, if you take all the damage
You think it would make me cool?
Yeah, everyone will love you.
what's twelve damage
all right i took twelve damage
uh... yet
but that's it now it's your turn really johnson says is giant mega dad you know
and it's not a demand you to do homework
that's right can you hear me
what's going on
your dad is big now
tell it
tell them to get small
No, listen, I have an idea.
What?
I need you to jack off.
Oh, fuck it.
Right here?
Right here, right now.
Well, I don't, I don't know.
Jeez.
You, you, you'll eat us, man.
Please, Patrick, it's our only hope.
So we can shoot your dad out of your wiener.
Shoot my dad out my wiener?
Just ignore that, just start jacking off.
I guess you can't really see what's happening.
Just trust me, man.
and
It's not a bad idea.
Look, I can give you privacy, but I think jacking off might be in our best interest.
You have to do it, dude.
Ah, crap.
This sucks.
Please, do it for us.
Come on.
This sucks.
I hate this.
You're, you, you could, here, wait.
You hate jacking off, are you gay?
I looked at blowtos, look, I got this.
You're not man enough to jack off.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
and
you know you would know how about you prove it then big guy I could do it right now then
do it yeah you start jacking it takes me two seconds yeah and when you do that you watch
as the first of all the the swamp water that's around you guys like starts to like drain out
(laughing)
- You got nasty fucking swamp cum, dude.
- And you watch as the Yoda dad is like,
"No, son's innocence."
And like starts to like vibrate a little bit.
- Son's innocence?
(laughing)
- He takes damage from just realizing his son jerks off.
- He takes, nice, he takes,
takes ten psychic damage
well that wasn't even worth it man
no that's pretty good he's like your fucking knuckles push up against me
and i mean
why'd you use your knuckles?
that's just how i do it
i'm sorry
he does it between two fists
yeah nobody jacks off with their knuckles i don't know what i'm talking about
uh...
But yeah, that's like a free damage, so it's pretty good.
You watch as the dad is sort of just rattled by this.
That was just like a free action, so you still can attack.
- Oh, nice, dude.
Okay, all right.
Dude, I'm so smart.
All right, now I'm gonna use my Matrix Beam.
- Oh, fuck yes.
Oh, that absolutely hits. - 23.
- Yeah, that hits mega.
- All right, let's roll for damage.
19, dude.
Yeah, so you concentrate your energy into your USB sword, and you point it at the Yoda, and
this beam of Matrix code shoots out of it, and starts to, you watch it sort of like rattle
its skull, and it's like vibrating violently.
Oh, excuse me.
And it looks like it's almost done.
Like, it looks like it's all psychic damage it's taken, and it's like, it's like slowly
like just like homework you must do like it's like not able to like function
anymore yeah you really fucked it up blowtoss it's up to you I'm gonna shoot
it in the pingas you better all right let's see here that's a crit failure
describe how you fail to me I'm holding the gun backwards I shoot myself in the
the
it was all up to you
uh... is moments ago say you're gonna take half of whatever this damages
because okay
you delighted
i got it
because she shooting yourself was your suggestion
yes i'm gonna let you
take five damage from that
notes because i'm wearing a condom right now and i think that
just in case i need a later
yeah
and appears the brunt of the blow
okay yeah five damage
yeah and so this year and now
we're going to get my second attack also are yes you do it but i don't think that
but not that
how do you even ready recover from shooting yourself
i'm going to do it again to try again i don't move the gun it on still pointing
it
as a twenty three that time
units so i'm still pointing at my at my dick so it it ricochets off the bullet
that's already in there yes it's at here at the yoda
yeah describe your kill on this giant as you know that
so it uh... yeah i'd ricochets off
uh... and it goes in order to damage but like you're gonna
you're gonna comes for them yet yet you are a
it goes right up into his we whole and it goes all the way up into him
i'll get a sense of his and it goes all through his things and his stuff in
there and then it goes up and it comes out of his nose and the asked me he's he
goes eyes
doctor freud i'm paging images
dissolves
uh...
in front of you
and then you feel rumble in the ground
and where that
yoda came up from
the ground that giant doug yoda
outcomes a giant
metallic looking like computer chip
in the shape of a state comes frozen dinner
and I need both of you to roll a dexterity saving throw.
Oh dude I got this.
It's nothing to me.
I got a 14.
No I got an 11.
You got a 14.
Okay.
Uh, both of you get- Please don't hurt me!
Don't get hurt.
Uh, what happens is this giant frozen dinner/computer chip flies out and *woof* *womp* gets both
of you in the gut.
Flies out towards the end of the penis.
You pass by all the weird fog and the trees and the swamp,
and with a now dry swamp,
and you shoot out of the tip of Patrick Yoda's penis,
and Dr. Tualat Aralis pulls a lever,
and as you come your friends,
Patrick Yoda, you watch as they grow in size
right before you.
- Now that's what I call draining the swamp.
(laughing)
and you are no longer you are you've been d calculus rift
well so you you if you
can't cv folks anymore
you can't go into the matrix to but you are free of poppy's uh... control now
okay i
as we stand there
recovering from that uh... from flying out of the penis i pointed out
brown puddle on the ground in front of patrick and i say
and then what's that thing
did you do that you did that when you came out
that's not a lot of it
i don't have a saying that is
policy that was it did you put that there
that's heightening juice i just don't know what
you know what comes out of you when you
that's what happened i don't know what you live alone in a skateboard do what
i like that's what happens when you get tall
all your comments very interesting i promise now making downplayed boston
accidents getting worse
doctor tolerous meanwhile is ecstatic it worked
it worked
it's success
yes now
who's next
who's penis do we get to go into next
yours get over here
we're just curious
uh... we should at least get to see it
let's see it come on he shows you his penis
uh... it's not even hesitate
i don't want to see it now that you can hesitate i'm a scientist
You only want to see a penis if somebody's reluctant to show it to you?
No.
That's what he just said.
I don't know what it sounds like, man.
No, he just did it too quick.
Okay, Yoda CK.
Alright.
Hey, Dr. Tool, you're actually a pretty cool guy.
Look, I'm just trying to hang with the boys, alright?
Alright, now I understand.
That's right.
Anyway, let's get into another person's penis.
Okay.
Who's next?
Okay, fine. If nobody else is gonna do it, my friends can go in my penis and my balls, too.
There we go!
Well, we don't... they do not need to go in your balls.
I think... I think... I mean, I'm looking at my stuff downstairs.
Look, I'll go in there if we have to.
I think they have to go through my ass.
Ah, well, now that's too much.
...on this computer.
That's too much.
Well, looking at my readings of demon anatomy, you're not really wrong.
That is actually the easiest way in.
Let's not do that. Let's go the hard way.
No, no, I think you guys do have to go into my ass first to reach my penis.
No, I'm pretty sure.
That could happen.
I just sit on Patrick.
Drink him. Drink him now.
Okay.
He whips around the shrink way.
it's both of you you both shrink down to a microscopic size and you shoot into
Ray William Johnson's ass it is like a dark cavernous fucking David Litch
that dark oh my god this is awful you just hear like a
I've ever experienced is there a family of dead cats living in here what's
going on
of
been in here that's what the graffiti says. It says "Kill Roy was here." What was that?
In the 40s? That was the 40s. I don't think so. You must be reading it wrong. It says
"El Barto" over here. Did you let a little kid in here? You let Bart Simpson into your
a
the
ask for poop. There's so much that science just doesn't understand. There's an entire like...
They have giant mine carts heaping with poop that they're carting through their city to power their machines.
There's an entire Deadwood series going on in his ass. Like, just like a town.
And you travel through it and you end up in his penis now. And the fires of hell
rest within this penis. It scorches the earth with its demonic cum. Nasty little imps and
devils bathe in pools of lava, screaming in pain as they stab each other in the head for
fun. As you approach what appears to be the main chamber, a chugging, drop-a-dee riff
begins to rise from below. It's too heavy, its skull crackin', it gets hotter and hotter,
to the point that it becomes unbearable to walk through it.
Any traces of computer influence on this demon have completely ceased as we move further
into Ray's penis, just up ahead.
Relaxing in a pool of cum lava that looks just like Chameleonair's pool on Cribs is a computer
robot type of fella with a small wormy demon attached to its back.
That's right, it's the reverse of Ray William Johnson.
Holy crap.
Ryan Higa.
Wow dude, you just unlocked something in me.
Can you say the first half of his YouTube screen name really quick?
I wonder what this guy's YouTube username is, but I don't have very much patience, so I
only want you to say the first two syllables.
it'll let you know that there was no come on doctor to let's not
i can't read again
of this map is even better than the first one
god damn
really has a lot of women
and around the good and around him
are the biggest bitches you've ever seen your life
drinking from massive cans of coke zero
and laughing at all of this guy's awesome jokes
so i says to him and that and that's all i would have done nine eleven you know
okay
who the fuck are you too
uh... would just some guys
don't mind us
who are you talking to there's nobody here
net yet that's exactly what i just said there's nobody here
well i clearly see you too and so do my child like a senator i would have a way
to turn around and i wave my hand in front of his face hoping that it somehow
does something
to make them not see us
what what do you do what are you doing turn around for one second
okay
he turned around
are issued a right
the
Okay, let's roll for initiative.
You get a surprise round.
Me too.
That ingenious tricking me.
You get a surprise round.
So whatever your initiative is, is fine.
You still get this attack round.
I got a five.
Do we roll with advantage?
No.
So what it is, is that Cameron gets a whole round of combat.
And I get my assassinate ability.
So I get a critical hit.
- Oh fuck. - In a surprise round, dude.
- Oh, there we go. - I'm gonna destroy
this guy right away.
- All right, yeah, so do it, roll your hit.
- All right, my Grinch gun, that's an 18.
- Shit, that hits, yeah, roll for critical damage.
- How do I do critical damage, is that just twice?
- So, let's see, shit, how would you do it on this?
So yeah, I guess we should, yeah, it should just be twice.
I forgot that, I have my own house rules for critical hits,
but I don't use them for this campaign.
let's just do regular nobody gives a fuck so let's just do this roll twice why did
I somebody who listens might play do you know yeah yeah so let's just roll for
damage twice all right so that is three plus seven when I can Patrick yeah I
throw my face like a microphone I say amen pretty weak honestly all things
considered. Yeah so you shoot the gun at the guy and at Ryan Higa and it hits him
in the back of the head and he's like "Oh fuck dude I'm gonna fucking kill you" and it's his turn.
No you're not. And you see the fat bitch is just giggling giggling away as he
oh whoops one of them moved. And one of them moves also. Yeah one of them also moves.
Yeah he rushes up to you both and his arms turn into like hand
cannons and he shoots at all of like shoots like a Gatling gun at both of you
it's gonna roll for an attack he's like oh as he's like does this okay oh yeah
he misses he shoots at you guys yeah suckin like matrix it or whatever the
fuck and get out of the way I think he just misjudges your height Patrick Yoda
cuz my face or someone to miss on you and he's like fuck and it's like fat
bitches get them and these fat bitches roll up now oh they are going to all
they're going to try to seduce you all so I need you all to both of you to roll a
charisma saving throw that's a five out of seven oh no both of you have been so
these fat bitches start start start twerking and doing the wap dance
Whatever that could be and you guys are all you guys are both seduced
Which means you get you're gonna get in my world where seduce is the thing you have disadvantage on all your attacks against these enemies
Damn it until you break out of this which you can try to at the end of your turn
Just against the big bitches or against all enemies. Okay. Yeah, so yeah, you guys are you guys like what do you guys do?
Do you how how do you guys how are you guys seduced by them?
yeah oh god like hey big boys awesome my my jaw drops to the floor and and
Patrick the monkey who was on the ground looking for for little snacks it just
crushes him it just hits him right on the head and flattens him to the ground
like a pancake and he and he and he he live has to lift my job back up yeah he
makes that noise yeah like just trying to live okay yeah meanwhile uh Ray
William Johnson with your dick out your demon dick out you are seeing visions of
big beautiful bitches and you see Ryan Higa there as well and he's seducing
these bitches in front of you.
And he says, "I'm everything you're not.
I'm better, smarter, faster, stronger.
I didn't settle down with some fat ass Dominican woman named Cameron.
I never stopped fucking.
Try to seduce these women.
Try to out-seduce me."
And you guys are going to get into a seduction competition in your mind.
In my mind.
Okay, let's go, dude.
So, so tell me.
So roll a persuasion check.
It's going to be a persuasion contest.
Okay.
I rolled a 15.
Okay, what's your line?
Hey ladies, do you want to know how to be ninja?
Ha ha!
And yeah, they're like, "Oh wow, we would love to know that!"
And he's like, "Noooo!
that's my thing
not anymore bitch i'm so mad i'm gonna say the first part of my channel
the director's cut and uh... yeah so
so uh... just like that the fat bitches vanish
you're still seduced by them
you still have to shake that seduction
but they are no longer going to be able to attack you or do anything
uh... you see ryan higa look around
and go
more like how to be loser what have you guys done
uh... and uh... it is now
uh... cameron it's your turn blow toss
so you have disadvantage but at the end of the turn you could roll to get advantage again
alright
do i have disadvantage on using
uh... my monkey as well
if it's like a spell
so if it's something where uh... he has to uh...
where he has to like roll like a saving throw he would just get advantage on that roll
is what I'm gonna do. But all right, I'm just gonna attack and then go for it. I'm gonna
run up to him and I'm gonna hit him with my dual pipes. Go for it. Oh, sorry. I mean,
do that. Oh, God. 21. All right, roll again. Oh, yeah, I forgot. It's Yeah, you're good.
You're good. 10. No, that was the greatest gun. Oh, no. Again, try again. 20. Fuck. Yeah.
Yeah, okay, you hit him for sure.
Alright.
17.
Fuck.
Yeah, uh, you just fucking whacked it.
How do you whack the shit out of him?
I'm interested.
Um, I hit him one time.
Uh-huh.
Hit him two times.
Oh yeah.
And then, you might not believe this.
I'm almost there.
I'm hitting him four times.
Yeah, uh, you fucking whacked the shit out of him.
I didn't think of something funny fast enough.
- No, that was, no, I put you on the spot.
That's not a really a good improv partner.
I think he did fine.
And he, you know, what you really did well at though
was hitting this guy.
He's looking not too hot.
He's just like, like, you know, like all messed up.
- I can hit him.
I can hit him again.
- Oh yeah, you sure can.
- All right.
I'm gonna try again.
That's a nat 20, but a 16 with the disadvantage.
- Oh, damn.
I was really rooting for you.
okay uh... that does not hit yes we are a c
uh...
but uh... dam he has a pretty high a_c_-level it's a really cold in here
all right small he's got a tell
all right patrick it's your turn
all right what i'm gonna do
scum i hit it with the needler obviously
yeah needlers
agree well
don't know i think st
no duty
disa i might go i would never have a good as well
all maybe during combat i know we're all about to die
he and they don't i i hope my hope you surprise has a better bludgeon damage
my attack is better to plus eight
but join the dark slide really haven't done that yet
uh... or you could just kill the guy
i'm gonna join the dark slide
what does that mean is that we're going to where you'd where you pause combat
for thirty minutes and describe something
fourteen but i would have gotten a twenty four uh... i'm sorry yet doesn't hit
but so what you do is you you do your move where you sling your skateboard and
it was around
times he's able to like just deflected
uh... back at you and you
pops up back under your will you defeat
uh... you still have your movement obviously so if you want to do that
okay
uh...
that
not
go over here that's fine all out of it
uh... there it this is exactly what every fight goes patrick mrs in attack and
then runs away and we have other person to die
it's not going to let her alice is like
crunching numbers on his keyboard
uh... uh... and he turns to you really justices is there any chance you could
jacket
in front of you don't know where you know
but if i did it is not a pleasant if you want to do a major golf
you're gonna have to get my wife down here
i'm so proud she's right there look
he's like
okay i don't have many uses by teleportation divides but
i think this one's worth it
and he goes to a cell partition device types in your address which you give him
and any polls the lever
in beams your your wife
your fat ass dominican wife cameron
who is on that
who is in the fad ass
that i'll get you out my bad notes chill and is in the middle of taking a bubble
bath
home and she's like
high on the
hands-free fucking bust on her face to do
let's fucking go
this yet you do it
uh... you put it you bust immediately and you see
uh... all the lava in the in the uh... help it
of your penis
spurred out and i guess
i guess burn your wife's face i guess she's used to it
i guess she has protection i don't know
no she doesn't
her face is repeatedly burned over and over again great as long as you're saying
that and uh...
the uh... you watch as the uh...
he's gonna
he's uh...
ryan higa is like no he's enjoying women
only i can do that
and he uh... takes
he takes out five psychic damage and he's just like
and uh... rattled by the fact that you have a really
i when his whole thing is that
uh... but it is his turn
he's going to attack you blowtoss jerry in front of him
it's a it's not your turn it's my turn
i'm trying to trick him with a lot of
I think you got mixed up man. I think it's my turn. Wait, let me just he looks at the initiative order. He's like hey
don't try that again because I'm
Obviously, I'm easily deceived
Can't blame me for trying to turn around and then you shot me. Oh, you're holding. I think you're holding the initiative turn upside down
Okay, well me let me see
No, cuz now I can't read anything. So I'm trying to you can't read you know, I can read I can read
Brian Heaton.
Ryan William Johnson can read, so you can't read.
You're the opposite.
No, I said everything's upside down here, right?
That's true!
No, don't use my logic.
Don't use my bragging logic against me.
That was just, that was for a-
Okay, well then can I just have one attack before you start your turn?
Okay, fine.
You can't let us do that.
Yeah, he does.
Yeah, he can.
Okay, I'll take it.
I'll take it.
Yeah, go for it, fine.
Oh, I forgot to try to break the thing, but that's fine.
I still have disadvantage.
To be fair, you were insisting.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's not gonna hit.
Okay, that's a, that's a, with disadvantage, that's a crit failure.
Yeah, he just like ducks and wheezes and says, "Okay, fair is fair.
Now it's my turn."
Aw, man.
And he unhinges his jaw and a horrible, like, pool of lava shoots out at your face.
But it doesn't hit.
a
that's gonna be a hit.
The one that doesn't hit just shoots out of my penis
and it's one more just
my wife is screaming in pain
and just one more little
droplet of lava hitting me in the eye.
I gotta pee real quick.
Right.
Alright I'll let you know what your damage is.
I'm gonna wear the time in the pic.
So when we left off Patrick was getting fucked.
Yeah Patrick was getting fucked by some lava
spilling out of Ryan Higa's mouth.
And he was like
Ryan Higa's mouth and you take a 10... 10 damage? 10 lava damage. Fuck. Oh and
Patrick's is weak to lava damage. Remember? Remember that from when we
created the characters? No. He's weak to it. You're weak to it. You take three times
and
it's still disadvantage right?
cause I didn't break it last turn
alright, that's 21 both rolls
OPELAKJAK BABY
roll for damage
nice yeah you fuckin like
beat the shit out of him
he's looking really fucked up now
so go for it
yeah I'm gonna hit him again with the pipes
that is 025
nice yeah
roll for damage again
that is
fifteen
you fucking describe your fucking how you do it man
okay so he's like a robot right
that's correct with a little demon on its back
okay i take out one of his
wires and i replace it with my pipes
and it short circuits his whole body and he starts saying error a lot
and then you know, his computer does the like, the chrome thing where it does page not found
where it has the little x's on his eyes and stuff.
And then you play the dinosaur game.
And I play the dinosaur game for about 20 minutes.
No stop playing the dinosaur game!
And then I kick him in the freaking nuts.
YEEOWCH!
Yeah he just like fucking keels over.
And uh, fucking, you watch him like, you watch his like, metal body fucking like start to
disintegrate and pull apart and fly, revealing a like, fiery core.
Um, and uh, I need you to roll a constitution saving throw.
Eight.
Not bad.
No, it's pretty bad.
No, it's not bad.
Yeah, it's pretty good actually.
Nah, it's definitely bad.
That's an eight out of eight, if I'm not mistaken.
His body explodes and going, "No!"
And like fire erupts around you.
You take 10 fire damage from this.
10 fire damage?
Yeah, and you see now that pool of lava
start to open up where he was bathing
before the chameleon air pool of lava.
and up rises another state comes frozen food some on computer chip
both of you role dexterity saving throats let's do this
eighteen
beautiful
take the first thing to get the first thing to take the first half of
your
amazing for them but if it's very good but to eighteen so wait yell eight
that's a teens though actually i don't know you're good
both of you
uh... fucking like
duck underneath
as the president comes towards you
and you grab onto it you fuckin right it out of his dick
and you see passed by all these demons and ms sucking a fucking and knocking
each other on the heads and stabbing each other i say
cream me up scottie
and
and shootout
and just like that doctor or else
finishing up typing up something
pulls a lever and you explode onto Dominican Cameron's face
uh... and back into full size. Hey you piece of shit that's my wife
and she's like honey I have to go back to being a woman
okay see you in the house
alright peace get out of here. Okay. Get the fuck out of here.
I'm at work right now you fucking bitch. Yo hey
hey save it for the bedroom
that's how you like to talk to maybe maybe i love you please just a little
my friends you know i mean no guys
that's real shit
that's right that's right and she uh... teleports away to bubble path i hate
that stupid picture right guys
and uh... doctor to a lot of ralph's giddy as hell
uh... 'cause you
uh... really johnson no longer controlled by poppy chico
no longer
your flag
excellent
one last penis to go into
are you ready to pass
ready as i'll ever be
i don't think he's ready i think we're a mary full snorkeling gear now
uh...
well i i think i'm ready to
let's let go any
pocket shoots the street great at both of you
shrink down the size
and you go into his curvy swirly twirly who penis yeah
uh...
and
it's got a hook on the unlike a christmas ornament
that's it's your pocket does i'd love that
and as you enter it uh...
as you went to blow taxes strange who penis you see inside it is
quite normal
real regular looking inside of the penis
as you travel through you begin to hear an echoing ryan bounce along the
pulsing fleshy cock walls
and things take a turn for the surreal
the walls drip rainbows they begin to unfurl
the colors pop and excite
while the young who girls twirl
small strange creatures dart to and fro making haste for what?
who can know?
ah! whose dick is whose dick you dicks do pick
these veiny things these ding-a-lings they're semen spilling and creaming filling
Giving rise come the morning sun, you'd to chuck wood too were you so hung.
But this winding dick is like no other, not like your brothers, sisters, or your uncles.
For all the things that make cocks go wobble, are topsy-turvy, courtesy of this here bubble.
And before you...
Wow.
I just have to say real quick, Patches, that was so well done that it made me like you
less.
(laughing)
- I was writing this earlier.
- It's truly upsetting.
- I was writing it earlier and my, my, uh,
- Fiancee.
- Was like watching a TikTok or something.
And I said, shut that fucking thing off.
I'm focusing.
(laughing)
And when I showed her what I wrote after she was,
- She was like, yeah, of course.
- So unhappy.
- Absolutely.
- Yeah, no, I should have shut up.
- And here we are.
- Nice. - In the lair.
this is scary it's pretty cool down there guys right
from honestly yes
it's the best one right
uh... i'm not gonna say that
june one of them was mine butcher
i actually don't like this
uh... the uh...
the guardian here is none other than the blue grinch
is walking guy again all my cat he floats into the sky in a zen pose above
the susan cosmos
what are you to doing here disturbing my peace
often
we just wanted to chill and smoke
you wanna a you down
for real
yet it'll go over your yes let's do it he said who
he floats over towards you guys to smoke weed with you
okay uh...
okay i i put uh...
i take some grass off of the ground
uh... and i stuff it in the barrel of a gun
and i handed him a much do this you check this out all you have to do is
just put this thing in your mouth of the policy this button right here just
that you know i do
and uh... he pushes this button
the trigger
and you know
let's let's make it clear that it's the trigger of a gun
it shoots through his head
but it doesn't seem to do anything to him he's like hey
you are trying to trick me
oh no sometimes people get high their first time
well i have some tricks for you and he teleports back
nope
i have some christmas riddles for you to solve
God, can't we just fight dude? Jesus fucking Christ.
Nope!
I have no...
*laughs*
Not this one!
This one's...
Oh...
Christmas Riddles!
*laughs*
Come on!
Whatever dude.
Are you guys having fun in there?
No!
Yeah dude, you're doing some blast!
Awesome, not.
I will admit, some of these riddles I found aren't really that clear.
*laughs*
It's pretty bad.
Did you just... are you saying you're the Grinch and you couldn't even come up with your own riddles?
Yeah, if you're a Grinch, you're a terrible Grinch.
No, I'm a projection of his worst fear, his inner soul, Blotas'
Blotas, you're afraid of riddles, you fucking pussy?
That's not... well, I'll let him answer.
Are there riddles in here?
[laughter]
I crawl under a table.
You can't hide from your own penis.
*laughter*
If there's anything I've learned, you can't hide from your own penis.
You see Dr. Troll Adoralis, he stops typing, he gets down, he shakes you, Bluetoss, he's like
"Snap out of it, boy! We need you focused, we need you to be able to face these riddles!"
Okay. But only for my friends.
Of course. Only for your friends.
Not for you.
Alright, well, you know, I was, you know, that's fine, I guess.
I guess it's just maybe we can be friends like at it at the end of this there'll be enough
Yeah, we're not friends yet. So not for you. Yeah. Yeah. No, that's real. I dig it. Oh, that's a real shit
It's all I'm saying. Yeah. No, I
I'm just I'm just trying to spit some facts. Okay loud and clear
The Grinch says his first riddle to you guys
You're gonna suck dude
What does this Santa Claus?
Presents what presents does the snow Rudolph?
What does the snowman eat for snack Rudolph
What does a snowman eat for a snack? That's right. We have one answer
Rudolph
carrots
What does a snowman eat for a snack once you answer you're locked in
That's all it takes bad. Well, hold on Caleb Caleb. Yeah, I mean Ray William Johnson. Yeah
I got a question for you. Yes, sir. Okay. So what is a snowman eat for a snack?
I get to see I'm googling it on a screen right now. I know you even care. I
Who who's going on there? Oh, don't I go out googling it on my phone?
Do not you are forbidden from googling it. I'm not googling it for a phone
This would be a problem and I still didn't prepare for it
You can't give Patrick the riddle he
You can see the different colors of the different pages that he was looking at reflected on his face
Don't Google it Patrick
Use your no man's think about no man's snack
Well, what's off your brain? What would you say? What would you say blow? Yeah
Are they allowed to consult me as I know that I know the answer 100% of the I
What
WHAT WOULD A SNOWMAN EAT FOR HIS SNACK?
JUST THINK ABOUT IT! WHAT'S YOUR WORST FEAR?
JUST GIVE ME THE AXE!
THAT WOULD KNOCK ME OUT!
the
in
I rolled a 21 baby.
Woo!
Let's go.
OK, your hint is, it is a real treat.
It with-- hold on, I'm not done.
OK.
With the word snow in the name.
Try a snow cone.
Try saying snow cone.
Hostess snowball.
snowball
yeah you both take 8 points of psychic damage
oh no
my god
it was a snow cone
that's the answer to that
you fucking idiot
mine was more clever
you literally fucking said it dude
to that awesome riddle
mine was more clever
how did we need a fucking hint for that
i'm going to downgrade it to riddles for kids
that's maybe more our speed
I don't know if you...
The one I thought of was more clever.
Not if you can tell, but this old thing was maybe supposed to be two episodes of Mystery,
but it's taken us six.
So...
I come with many...
You might need to go easy on us.
I come with many colors, so beautiful and...
Rainbow!
Snow cone!
I turn so many houses into a beautiful sight.
Oh, I got this.
Do it easy.
Christmas lights.
M.
You got it!
I hate that you got it. Yeah, cuz that one was so hard. How about this?
How about you get Christmas riddles for G? I'm gonna go
Idea, how many go back I sting Christmas. I'm gonna go back to the adult section if you could you keep it up
We're gonna get more snow cone type. No, I mean
I'm so stupid and I have a baby brain a role persuasion check
14.
He's like, "I'm onto you!"
I know your brain's not a baby's brain.
And Christ can fuck off, by the way.
No!
That's right.
Have you guys heard of Penn Jillette?
No!
Don't even say that, man.
Meanwhile, Blowtoss Piss, before you, you see this silhouette of your wife doing some
wifely ass shit and she says to you, "Blowtoss, it's me, your wife. I'm dead. Could you sing
that song for me? The one I used to sing?" And before you do it, roll a performance check.
Okay. Nine.
Okay, sing the song.
Okay. I say, "Of course, Caleb's mom, I will definitely sing you the song."
know
well honey i remember you singing it so much better
uh... hands
the grinch uh...
the grinch as you know what that last riddle doesn't count
uh... come on dude he's a strengthened
by a resolve
I'm gonna fucking die because you suck at singing.
No, that may be.
I don't know the words to this song.
It's off camera, you moron.
I'm googling "who song".
What do you get when you cross a bird with a turtle?
Turtle bird.
Shut up, dude.
Just shut the fuck up, dude.
Oh my god.
Turtle dove.
You got it.
Oh, that makes me so steamed.
wife comes back to you, blow toss. Please honey, try again. And here, here's a guitar tuner.
Try to, I don't know, does this help?
I just remembered all the lyrics to the song.
Roll another performance check.
That's an 11.
Okay, sing the song.
Fa hoo, forest, da hoo, doris, welcome Christmas, bring your light.
well
i do love that song
again though i'm dead and uh...
the grinch the blue grinch is like uh...
you know i only have one last riddle for you too
and uh...
uh... except there can only really be like what for christmas it's just at a
certain point
the fatigue i feel it
so i gotta you know i don't know the blue grinch is chronic fatigue no i
i don't have chronic fatigue out of the blue bridge has chronic fatigue no
dollars read that you know there's a rumor and it's a little bit for that
google doctors that the
you won't be disappointed
the last one
is that dirty riddle for all adults
come on dude
why
and mister and mrs class
childless
because this is clauses all hollow
that's not no that's well we have two answers here that's pretty good pretty good yeah that's not bad
yeah low toss roll a history check okay oh no that's a nat one you can't remember christmas
right now okay ray william johnson what's your answer um because uh
'Cause Santa Claus keeps, uh...
I'm not...
He puts...
...fuckin' coal in a pussy.
[laughter]
I think that might be it!
I think I got it.
I think-- Okay, I'm gonna log in.
That's my answer.
Santa Claus puts coal...
...in Mrs. Claus's vagina.
It's because he only comes once a year!
I don't think that's it.
No, you're-- I'm looking at the answer right now.
I
it's
the
and uh... you want to see this all i should have
i should have just tried to kill you
and you see from beneath the who trees
outcomes a state guns
frozen food computer chip
both of you rolled x thirty saving trail
i'm gonna get it this time did
you're not going to get anything a fifteen for me
it's coming by
uh... i got eight
the patrick you know you're distracted by your awesome eggnog answer
and you just get pocket walloped by this thing
uh... ray william johnson you start fucking surfing on it
you shoot out of his swirly who penis your corkscrew ring around
uh... uh...
uh... blowtoss uh... uh...
you fucking not
out the fucking
weird swirly weird colorful beautiful susie in news
uh... out of the tip of your swirly
dog looking dick
uh... and
doctor tool that arose pulls the lever
and you both grow
uh... and you're all free
the car arafat
am i still in this penis
yet
get used to it and they're big guy
no
here you play with you every night
who didn't you talking to him right in front of them
yeah
and i still in european
uh...
uh... i don't know i think
i gotta say that one of the worst days of my entire life and talk it over and
talk to the lawyer says
and but one of the best days of mine
uh...
all three of you are now free
let's get him on the phone
we're gonna meet up with him
and spinach this once and for all
and uh... you guys for your p_s_p_'s to con car car car contact
okay
doctor uh... no uh... poppy chico
and you see on your phone to say message left for you
from mommy good legs
you play it
can you hear
uh... in the background of her message
banging and clanging and gunshots and jamal deworm dying
no! jamal deworm!
i'm sorry i couldn't tell you everything boys
i promise it was for your own good
you know all that shit
moreover
i'm sorry i couldn't help you more
here's to living
here's to being a femme fatale
and you hear
a what sounds like
a tommy gun
going off
and you hear the phone line die.
- She could have just hung up.
She might not be dead.
She could have just hung up on us.
- Yeah, she's hanging up.
- So you call Poppy Chuko.
He picks up the phone.
So, boys, what are you,
what's going on?
- Shut up.
- We went into each other's faces
and we're all right again.
- Don't tell him that.
- You shut your mouth.
- Hold on.
out
you guys to say anything to Papi Chuko right now.
- Why?
- 'Cause you're gonna tell him that we took the things out.
- I'm not gonna tell him anything, all right?
- Don't tell him that we took the things out.
- I'm telling him--
- I like their penises.
- No, I'm telling him he listens to us.
- We're just gonna hang out.
We're gonna meet up with you and hang out.
- Look, Papi Chuko, I think somebody's
cutting into the call. - You're gonna give me--
- We're just, yes, just meet us at home.
- You're gonna give me 200 milligrams of slime right now.
I ain't gonna give you shit, you little man.
Alright, you know what? Then I'll take it.
I'll let... I'll let Blotas take over the call.
Look, Blotas, you and your friends wanna meet up, then?
Yeah. How 'bout Hussie Kitsune's house?
Perfect.
I'll see you there.
In five.
Alright, he hangs up.
Five minutes!
What? That's... No, we can't get... What the...
Come on!
Wait, call him back.
I called back.
Okay, listen, man.
What's going on?
it'll probably i mean what are we like i don't know where i am in at least
minutes right yes it's gonna be okay so i think that i realize fifteen but plan
for twenty i realize that the right on that
you know i would i wouldn't have been mad
i realize that we have to know what it what you know that not one of these
people like my brother for example just like shows up got a whatever he wants to
write a letter you'd like to know that's not so it's so inconsiderate and is that
is it is rude you know what it is maybe it might quit grab and not everyone's
Operating on your schedule kind of exactly. Yeah, so I don't want to I don't want to like ruin your day
Wait, what the fuck no, he calls you back. I'm just kidding
Honestly, a lot of stuff has been said about you right in the end pretty funny guy
I know you gotta say, you know, I you know, I was I was I was on Def Jam
Really?
and then data that he has been the video game deftly good for you
that was next to method man
in the character so i was he had the case
i don't know that it is a pretty good
okay anyway will see you and i guess that twenty years
right got it
and he picks up okay
uh... doctor to let us is
i'm proud of you three
anyway
go there
and confront poppy
wants it for all
and uh... yeah he supplies you guys with uh... his own ryan dunn mobile
and uh... you happen the car
and
you you drive through out where the lab is a lab is sort of on the other side of
uh...
uh... uh...
the chas area but still within that sort of like ritzy ur sector just sort of
stuck the way hidden
and you get out of it
any drive to the lockheed martin shopping district here
make that familiar right and mister hands boulevard
and go through the laser gates to sean and has he's massive princess peach
style mansion
an uneasy feeling begins to settle in
you pocket car you go to bring the taco bell but before you even can
hiring it
you bring it
and the book
you bring it in by hearing it the door already opens
and he's right now
and you see a Jollibee officer has opened the door to greet you.
"Captain, they're here!"
You look in the back of the foyer and you see Captain Filipino Mr. Bean
is just up ahead with Papi Chuko, discussing something.
Look over to his right and you see Haseki Tsune is under arrest.
"I'm innocent! I'm an innocent activist and sex worker!"
She's shouting and protesting as they're pulling her away,
the poppy chico ignores her cries
filipino mister being addresses you boys
man's nice job fellows
copy told me how you crack this one wide open ingenious stuff
finding her journal tracing the order of the hit back to the cycle it impeccable
impeccable
yeah
yeah we did kill it honestly are guys let's all right now it's not really up
blog
made now i say i say a uh...
captain philip it was to be to we talk to you in the pantry
i'm really hungry
uh... yam
mishar of course
in c_n_n_ you guys walk within the pantry c poppy to go sort of just watching you
guys as you walk with them
uh... you guys are in the pantry with them what's going on
okay
so
to stop me if this sounds familiar
bobby to go basically has been controlling us through the calculus
ribs so that he can take over the one i'm gonna
stop you right there
uh...
uh... well i i wasn't even done but church justin
we got the part
it was has to keep soon a quarter to hit
on her unfaithful husband
okay
good job but no i i'm telling you we don't want to do it and i was a duty
we were told doctor tool ladder that down to the rock told us
that we actually had every two we went into each other's penis is a week to go
to the ships from the state of the federation
and uh... i don't know what's out of the union
he puts his hand both your on your shoulders like has been just right
uh...
he says
great job fellows
he walks away
and probably was the stupidest guy ever he didn't understand
and pop it you go
saunters up to you
if you want to talk further you can follow me
but i'm giving you three now
case closed
your heroes
nobody gets hurt
you'll get your frog back
i mean that sounds like exactly what we were looking for a right now and i think
if we get Sullivan back I don't care.
Okay.
Right this way then.
You can't give us an option like that because we're just going to take it.
Wait what's option number two?
It's a noir.
Option number two is noir?
No thank you.
This is how noirs end.
Unless you choose something different.
Oh my god.
It's the different one.
This is the moral, this is the first time we have to-
No, he's not gonna tell you what it is.
Okay.
Well, what's the option?
I'm gonna look at the other two and I'm gonna say, "Lizzen."
You can follow me.
If you guys want-
No.
Lizzen, shut up.
How about one of us follows you?
Shut the fuck up, Patrick.
God, please shut up.
If you want to hang out with that stupid fucking frog and get some gay little shiny medal to
put on in front of your desk or whatever you to can leave
i have a mystery
to get to the bottom of
i start clapping
thank you thank you anybody else want to clap
i'm not gonna clap
okay well then i grabbed i'd rather do you answer nice are making him clap
don't touch me
all right bobby i see you know
i think we have to take my fist in the patrick's mouth
you see poppy chico
busy poppy chico like you know
but he says
you want to talk more let's go
here wait can we see as long as we can set the meeting place
can we can we do a quick safe
you could do a quick safe
i would have to a quick safe
canada's f present five
okay press a five and then i slap up each of those is a good
okay you should probably press f nine
i press f nine okay you reload the right side
bobby to go listen
i know a great little restaurant
it's a school dogs and hot soda
what a little while ago i'll meet you there
we go down there we has just out like men as that sound
is that the restaurant it's in the matrix to
now it's in the real world you even talking about
yet not even as okay you've got a bit in the matrix to yes i'm a bad liar
okay well then i guess we can be in this is you guys can
show me how you can get in there then
Oh fuck. It's not in there. Fine, we'll go to Popeye's, whatever.
What did you think was gonna happen, huh?
You'd confront me? You'd force me to reveal my secrets?
I come quietly, no ifs, buts, ands, other contractions?
It's a noir, you're lucky if you're alive. Yeah, lucky if you're alive.
I am lucky. After we're done with you. I was mostly thinking we would just probably kill you.
Then do it.
Whoa.
You're right.
Go.
Okay.
All right.
Calm down.
No.
Fuck you.
I'm killing this guy right now.
He's the bad guy, and I'm going to kill him.
It's the end of the game.
Let's fucking go, Papi Chuko.
How do we know he's the bad guy?
It's a noir.
Listen to his voice, dude.
He sounds Italian.
Let's fucking kill this fucking guinea wop right now.
He's in front of us.
We know what he did.
He's been controlling our brains with our fucking penises.
I had to go in your fucking penis, make you cum, just to get out of there, dude.
Fuck this.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay.
How about this?
Why did you say that?
Instead of you killing me, you follow me.
I give you the frog back.
Look, as long as we get Sullivan- Let him finish the fucking sentence for once.
And we can call it square.
That's all.
turn you into a square big guy.
I'm gonna fold you up.
- Yeah, you're gonna become a cube.
- Shut up!
You're not even making,
do you wanna fight him or do you wanna leave, Patrick?
- I'm gonna make him 3D.
(laughing)
- All right, then let's fucking go.
- He just wants to talk.
He just likes to say things
while other people are saying things.
That's kind of his thing.
- You know what I do?
I punch Papi Chuco straight in the fucking mouth.
- Roll an attack roll.
- Where is that?
just role like
your uh...
strength
and at your proficiency
you see a proficient in fiscal efficiency bonuses three yes is really a
strange i role in eighteen
yeah you fuckin slug him
role
rolled the sex
so it's gonna be forward slash are hell yeah baby
the
that's what
yeah i just want you in the book and they've got to do this and i did do
that in the leaf
officers i'm being assaulted and uh... you know i
the jolly the officers swarm
swarm you guys or world
i don't know what he would uh... so i'll tell you what i'm glad to have a
Point out the door. Yeah, it's a big fat guy. He's a winner. We work for you. We're detectives
I we tracked him out the door go go
He's getting away. Hurry hurry
What are you doing you're just standing there get out of here
Get away we have to get whoever did this to Bobby Juco
Bobby Juco come here. Let me fix your face up
and then I'm okay roll another attack roll another 18 okay yeah roll for damage
another okay describe your kill
okay I clean off and then where his neck is it's like it's like a ribeye in a
fucking cartoon you punch his head clear off of his fucking shoulders and it
rolls it rolls all the way down the hill that the house is on everything slows
down the head flies through the air in slow motion the cops rush you three as
As you do what is just for the world, but not what is best for you.
And the camera pans over the scene.
Exterior, Gun City skyline.
A head flies through the air, crashing through a window onto one of the last patches of flora
in this place god forgot.
A lame blotch stains a lamer attempt at diverted prevalence.
Pulling back, this belabored irony loses its poetry and keeps its humor at cost.
The meandering, desperate lives of the denizens of Gun City are accompanied by atrophied streaks
of harsh neon that bandy about, an accent to the ersatz expanse of a place as empty as
it seems.
The end of the collective soul can just barely be heard above the sound of the eternal modem
and the gears of progress.
We are an island.
So it goes.
Kurt Vonnegut.
Another tale in Gun City.
Another mystery solved?
Who's to say?
Can mysteries ever really be solved?
Of course they can, that's an insane question.
But our heroes always tried to do what was right, up till the very end.
And in slow motion, you see like, Ray William Johnson's face like, ahhhhhh, like a head flying
Police officers rushing you three. You're getting fucking handcuffed in the back
and you see the camera sort of zoom out from there and
follow us
into
poppy Chukos techno slime industrial laboratory
And you see it sort of zoom in
to somewhere else and pierce through something really just like blackness darkness and
And first it passes by Sullivan. You see him in stocks.
And he's like, "Help! Help me!"
Um, and as you keep pushing through, you hear more of the narration.
Um, but our heroes always tried to do what was right.
What was just.
Except for a few things.
Some of those things were really bad, actually, now that I think about it, but...
You know, the intentions were there.
And maybe that's all we have at the end of the day.
The desire to seek justice and the camera pushes in forward and becomes clearer a figure starts
to come to light in a cruel strange e-bombs world and the camera pushes in and finally
it's revealed so it goes it's Sean McKelvey frozen in cum carbonite
Epilogue
The Calculus Rift 2.0 project was stopped.
With no one left heading this secret operation, development was paused for the foreseeable
future.
And while there is no more Papi Chuco, there is always a possibility of someone rising
anew and finding a way to utilize this dangerous technology.
Now the man of the hour, Sean McKellie, was unfrozen from the cum covenant.
He divorced Haseki Tsune and began to tell his story about the truth behind the Calculus
Rift and the Cocculus Rift 2.0. In response to this, Stakehams Federation of Bodies and
Spaces now offers the opportunity to have their Cocculus Rift removed for $10 million
and have decided to install the Cocculus Rift in all types of genitalia, not just penises,
to be more inclusive.
Shortly after that, Sean realized that you're better off working incrementally within the
system rather than outside of it, which is definitely what he was doing, and he started
a new firm called "I Allegedly Have a Coke Problem" that lobbies tirelessly to finally
bring back the minimum wage to Gunn City.
They have not been successful, but have made a lot of money for themselves.
Sullivan the Frog is safe and sound, released along with Sean after the death of Papi Chuko.
He is now the head detective at the Top 10 Staddledale Agency, where he works tirelessly
to solve the many crimes in Gunn City.
He hopes to one day reunite with the three hotshot detectives who believed in him enough
to let him drive them around and call him names.
Meanwhile, his cousin Giancarlo the Bullfrog immediately started reselling the Technoslime
vials Ray William Johnson gave him, and filled the void left by a dead Papi Chuco and a shrinking
Mad Suckler empire.
He was able to go legit, and took over the business development division at Papi Chuco's
Technoslime, which is still looking for a CEO.
Dr. Toul Laderalis now heads a covert operation that removes coccylus rifts for free, discovering
new ways of putting things in and getting things out of penises, his favorite thing to do.
He remains in hiding, but has expanded his network of scientists who are obsessed with
genitalia, creating the Order of the Penis.
Like Sullivan, he awaits the return of the three brave detectives who let him experiment
on their penises.
Toshikitsune found herself in V Alcatraz, stripped of her rights to freely move between the Matrix
2 and the real world.
While she did put that hit out on Sean, she certainly didn't imagine it'd come back
to bite her quite this way.
She at least thought her Uncle Poppy would have her back, but lucky for her, her fans
did have her back.
They launched a campaign to get her released, and while she lost a considerable amount of
wealth once Sean divorced her, their tokens helped reduce her sentence to 11 minutes.
Besides continuing her very important sex work, her new status as a hardened criminal allowed
her to pivot musically toward a career as a SoundCloud rapper, XXX Contacion, with critics
claiming that her song-for-song cover of Steely Dance Asia, titled "Ejagao", is "the most
sonically challenging, innovative, and meaningful work by an artist who conspired to murder their
spouse since the guy from As I Lay Dying did that."
Mad Suckler escaped the raid on his compound with his life, barely.
His entire collection of worms was killed by Papi Chuko's corporate military squad, and
most of his lieutenants were disbanded, some falling under his right-hand cyborgs, Mary
Kate and Ashley Cabrera, who betrayed the Suckler in the ensuing fight, creating two
new factions from one, making a mess of his once tight-knit operation.
Meanwhile, the Suckler himself has gone into hiding, still collecting paychecks from loyal
pushes, but with the portrayal of his cyborgs, a dethroned Jeff Tiedrich, and a chaotic scene
at Papi Chuko's Techno Slime, the path forward is less clear for the terrifying gangster than
it's ever been.
Officer Filipino Mr. Bean was disgraced for letting the Great Papi Chuko die right in
front of him.
He stepped down as police chief, got addicted to Techno Slime, and formed Cream 3 with Jeff
Tiedrich, who had that similar fall from grace, and the sole surviving worm of Papi Chuko's
collection that Ray William Johnson took in episode 5.
They have a modest following among sexual predators who frequent DIY scenes.
Speaking of worms, Jamal the worm took over Mommy Good Legs, turning it into Jamal's
wormhole.
It's become a popular nightclub thanks to Jamal's signature drink, the Dr. Pibb Cosby.
Because of the incident with Ray William Johnson shitting on his head, Jamal has developed a
new fetish that he doesn't want anyone to know about.
The all-dirt restaurant Cold Dogs and Hot Soda run by Gary C. Enterprise, famous Sullivan
the Frog impersonator, has become a smash hit.
Or success, you know, a restaurant's not like a hit.
Most of the tokens earned have been donated to Moms Against Drunk Driving.
Gary himself, however, has dutifully set aside some of the earnings for the three gentlemen
who gave him the restaurant.
He also patiently awaits their return.
And what happened to Mommy Good Legs?
Well, Mommy's long gone.
But with her is a Tommy Gun she can call a friend.
A new identity, and the coordinates to a safe house in a town not too far south.
She'll be out of Gun City by dawn.
She hopes the boys made it through okay.
She's sorry for everything she put them through.
But how else could she finally get away from Poppy?
Surely there was no other way.
Or were there other ways?
And uh, the decisions the players made were so completely fucking insane that you just uh...
You know, any possibility of another way was just sort of out the window by the third session, so...
You know, you just kind of uh, went with whatever the fuck was gonna, you know, get you to the end.
Or something... weird like that.
And our three detectives, where are they now?
Well, they're in their toughest spot yet.
The old slammer, where they helped put so many perps and innocent poor people in before.
Patrick Yoda has started meditating for 15 hours a day while in prison, and can almost
conjure a cheeseburger.
He is the prison staff's favorite.
Bloatoss Piss and his monkey Patrick started working out non-stop, and have even started
competitive lifting competitions in the yard.
The monkey Patrick has taken first place in the deadlift competition, three weeks running.
William Johnson meanwhile has joined the White Caillou's.
Who knows when they'll get out of there or if they can get out of there, the prison.
Maybe if enough people want to know what happens next we'll do a direct sequel, prison break
one off maybe, you know, it could be fun.
*school bell rings*
Can you hear that? It's the bell.
It's time for recess.
And uh...
If I don't leave soon,
the fifth graders are gonna get the only good kickball.
Can't have that.
So, you know...
'Til next time, folks.
And remember...
Um, may the force be with you.
Always.
[music]