[music]
After an interesting experience at Room Street,
where the guys robbed a man of his thumb, his virtual wallet, and a lot of his dignity,
we had what we needed in spades.
Quantum crypto credentials for when we get into the iCup facility,
Then we got access to ShinyAndro's crypto account.
Also his car and his house.
Next, we had to deliver that money to Mary Kate Cabrera.
That's easy enough to do. We could send that over our PSPs.
But then we had to meet up with her...
with Goldbeard, who would get us the golden bullets.
Mary Kate said she'd link us up after we did the job.
After that, we'd only need to get the love slime
and potentially a way to perform a biometric scan matching Fatima Von Kissy faces.
I suggested we talk through the different security gates we need one more time.
So yeah, you guys just got away from Room Street after causing some mayhem.
There are a couple places you talked about going.
I mean, obviously you have Shiny X.
- Is he still knocked out?
Or is he locked out? - Yeah, what's going on with me?
- He is knocked out last I remember.
- Okay, can I give him mouth to mouth?
- Can we have a dream sequence of him?
(laughing)
- Do you wanna go inside Pat's dream?
- Can we all be characters in Pat's dream?
- I think to wake him up,
we have to go inside of his mind.
- It's completely white.
The whole, it's completely white except for me in a room.
Only white and you're completely
that's your dream is only white.
It's completely white and I'm eating
just like a big Snickers ice cream.
No, you're not.
So, yeah, you're doing something nasty, actually.
Yeah, you look closer in the Snickers bar is poop.
OK. Yeah, yeah.
I leave or I leave his brain.
I hated it in there.
Yeah, no, you missed it.
He's eating.
He's about to see his father's penis.
Talk to him.
So you missed that.
Yeah, but yeah, so you guys are so you have a couple couple
places you can go.
Obviously you talked about, you know, rating shiny Andrew's
house since you have his key in his car.
I exist to his car.
Now, you can obviously also go back to Atlanta City so you
can make the trade with Mary Kate Cabrera.
and get those golden bullets.
Those are the two main places you would probably go.
But you know, whatever, you can go back to the hideout.
I feel like we've been trying to get these golden bullets for a very long time.
I strongly feel as though we should go get these bullets, boys.
Yes, I agree.
Oh yeah. Okay, cool.
So yeah, I mean, we can do a little handy-dandy fast travel.
As you get back to Atlantis City.
I walked the whole way really slowly.
(laughter)
(singing)
We're walking.
Mm-hmm. And you're walking.
And you're walking the whole way there,
so it was like, what about,
I guess midday, and so now
it becomes late afternoon,
and you're about halfway there. You guys have been walking.
I'm really tired. I want to go take a nap.
I'm gonna go take a nap.
Water break.
[LAUGH]
Okay.
Can I now drink water for about two minutes?
Am I still knocked out?
Yeah, we've been dragging you.
We have a camel that we tied you to.
We've been dragging you through the desert, which I think is where we are.
Yeah, you're in the desert of Gun City.
You're in the desert part of the city.
Yeah, and when you get to the, when you get to Atlantis City,
Cabrera sends you a message over your PSPs to meet her at the,
at De Niro's Diner.
So it's a diner that is nearby the like main casino area,
the conch place in Atlantic City, Atlantis City.
So that's where that's where she told you to meet.
So that's all.
That's all you guys can go there.
It's like that.
You guys can go there if you want or you can go.
We're back in the casino is what you're saying.
No, you're just in Atlanta City, so you're not in the casino right now.
You can go to the basically sitting down at the roulette table.
You are.
You're telling me.
Yeah, I mean, there might be a lot of money or a little might be a window of time
that Cabrera will wait for you at the diner.
What was the name of the horrible game that we played?
Pig.
It was Pig.
You guys want to play round a pig?
No, I have no anything but fucking I'd rather flip a coin than play pig.
Is coin flipping a game at the Atlanta City Casino?
No, they throw you out if you flip a coin.
That's unregulated gaming.
Whoa, no chance here.
Yeah.
Um, I'm gonna go to the meetup with the Mary Kate.
I just, I piss my pants.
Yup.
All right, nice.
You guys walk into, walk to De Niro's Diner.
De Niro's Diner has like a vintage 2097 feel.
So that's when Earth had like a retro gilded age.
Everything's very Baroque.
There's a lot of red velvet, a lot of mahogany wood,
Rockefeller kind of lanterns.
- This place is badass.
- Yeah, it's a pretty sweet, sweet place.
And so you go in there,
you see Mary Kay Cabrera sitting at a table,
you see her posse around her,
and she beckons you guys over.
And she says,
so I received the funds.
I appreciate that.
The thing I don't appreciate is your lack of discretion.
There's a reason why we're meeting here.
My passed out body lets out a huge fart.
Pash, you're doing a good mob boss thing by just having indigestion.
Yeah, sorry about that.
Wait, what did you say? What you said again?
Sorry, we were all a little distracted.
I don't remember feeling to be discreet.
No discretion that you lacked.
Is such that it's coming back to me.
That's fine, I mean, just tell him it was us.
Yeah, I don't who cares?
We got you your fucking money.
Why are you complaining?
I mean, yeah, I mean, hey, I don't.
With all due respect, you didn't tell us to be discreet.
I would have assumed that that would have been a part of...
Well then you were way too discreet.
Yep.
You were discreet by not telling us.
You were being discreet so much that you didn't even tell us what you wanted.
I didn't know we came to meet you in the Discretion Diner, your favorite restaurant.
Oh yeah, I didn't realize we were in Discretion City.
I thought this was fuckin' Gun City, you fuckin' stupid bitch.
Yeah, on this street.
That part.
Alright, alright, alright.
Because we still want the other stuff.
The deal the deal.
And she snaps her cyborg finger and out comes Goldbeard.
Goldbeard who's a... Does he love gold?
He does love gold.
He has... You see him come out. You see first a barrel wheel.
and then you see a head inside the barrel wheel, you see a beard made of solid gold
and uh, two legs, this guy is walking, his beard is too heavy so he carries it around in a wheelbarrow
You wanna talk about being discreet? He's got a golden beard!
I call bullshit on this whole thing!
Do you not want the golden bullets then?
Gimme that shit, yes, of course I do!
Do it discreetly, and don't say gold bullets, use a codename.
Yeah, you gotta be discreet here.
Like normal bullets.
It's a joke.
Okay, got it.
Uh, here are your normal bullets.
Shh, shh, shh.
Quiet.
You gotta be really quiet.
You have to be really discreet.
You never know who's around.
And uh, Goldbeard gives you guys a big toothy grin and coughs up two golden bullets.
bullets. I snatched them.
Nice.
I snatched them with my fingers.
Yeah, really, really fast fingers for that.
He has 10 of them.
Roll 10 times for each finger.
One finger.
No roll 10 times for each finger roll 100 times.
So yeah, you guys get the golden bullets.
That was so easy.
Mary Kate says to you now.
I had another end of the deal.
I promised you guys which was information about love slime. Thank you for reminding us
Just basically general like you just tell anyone the second part of our deal
Yeah, didn't you didn't even check if we were who we say we were before you said that
Are you who are you? We're us continue
Okay
She says, "Now, I would expect your friend over here, the V-Folk, to know this about
Love Slime, but it has not been in production for many years now.
It was made by Swag Inc., which was a boutique techno-slime company.
Anyway, it was too dangerous. So that's what's taken federation by the basis said and so they seized all of it and use it in the server wars now there been leaks since then.
Become sort of a designer drug designer product.
And I know somebody.
Or rather I just know that there's activity where a former friend of mine.
Runs a danger club.
And you guys would know danger clubs are nightclubs where people do really crazy shit.
Like back and out.
Oh like back drinking.
They do backflips they drink.
Oh God, I don't know if we should go there guys.
It sounds scary.
If you go there and you play cool, you'll probably get offered some love slime at some
point.
If you go there and you fuck it up, you won't.
So, okay, then we'll do, then we'll do good.
Fine.
One more thing.
I had to call in a favor to get the cops to stop, you know, asking questions about who
Who were those guys who beat up that paralyzed guy?
Who were they?
We don't know who you're talking about.
Yeah, we're so discreet we have no clue what you're even talking about.
So and who killed those other cops or killed one of them and then removed the lips off
another?
Oh, I don't know.
I've never touched lips.
You just don't know what lips are.
Yeah.
What part of the body is lips?
He points at Travis Oswald.
That guy removed a cop's lips.
Oh, I wouldn't even know.
I look behind me.
There's no guy there.
There's a there's an eight-year-old child.
She serves him right you keep
eye for an eye.
Okay, so
If you aren't as discreet, if I can use our favorite word one more time.
Good.
There will be consequences.
OK, what will they be?
Yeah, go ahead and tell us.
We already fucking ripped a cop's lips off.
What the fuck else can we get in trouble for?
Send people to try to kill you.
What do you think is going to happen?
We're the main characters of the thing.
You think they're really going to hurt us?
No, fuck you.
We're going to the danger club.
All right. Fuck you, too.
Yeah. So you guys can go to the danger club.
This danger club actually is is a repurposed
as repurposed abandoned techno slime factory from the first campaign.
It's been about two years since you've been there.
Oh, I remember this.
I remember that, too.
Yeah. And do you remember that?
Do you guys remember?
They remember.
Not likely.
I was there last night.
You were not.
It seems like you guys are going to be at a serious strategic disadvantage.
We remember the exact layout.
I remember you and Granny.
So yeah, do you guys want to go to the abandoned Techno Climb factory that has turned into a danger club?
Yes.
But first, glow sticks.
Yup.
Okay, you guys wanna go get glow sticks?
Yeah, but we don't have to do a scene of it, we can just have them.
Yeah, you guys got glow sticks, yeah.
Mine's purple.
Mine's also purple, but it's brighter.
No, no. I have two in there. I have four like General Grievous.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, okay, fine. But yours are poison and they kill you if you hold them too long.
[Laughter]
Okay.
On your way there, Mommy gives Sullivan a call.
And Sullivan picks up and says, Hey, hey, Mommy.
Oh, do you guys want me to put this on speakerphone?
Yes. Talk to your damn mom.
No, this is not. Actually, yes, I do.
Put her on speakerphone. OK.
Mr. Sullivan, is that you?
And no, this is Mommy. Good legs.
We've Mommy frog legs.
the fifth
that's her name
the trim of the
fifth
the way both at
the fifth
I'm Sullivan the frog my mom is mrs. Sullivan no I know that's what is your
dad's name. Don't tell me it's the frog.
No, it's Papa Sullivan.
Mrs and Papa.
Yeah, I don't know how this is so confusing.
Is this not normal?
I don't have parents, I don't know.
I don't think you know their names.
I do know their names.
It's Papa Sullivan.
You think it's Papa Sullivan and Mrs Sullivan?
Maybe.
Maybe I should reach out to my parents.
I think you should.
I don't think frogs talk to their parents.
Don't, don't, didn't you just come out of a load of slimy eggs?
This is a, uh, Pierce, I'm gonna say this one time and one time only.
He is a future frog.
Why would he follow the modern frog's law?
It makes no sense.
Do you guys not slime out?
I mean, I still I'm out, but.
Mommy good legs has just been on the phone.
OK, mommy, get to the point.
So I met with Fatima and I was able to get some information from her.
There is one person who is in charge of extracting the crypto credentials.
Now. If I mean, I'm not sure if you guys got crypto credentials or not,
You guys did get crypto credentials, by the way, from shiny Andrew.
You couldn't find them yet, but we're working on it.
Fuck yeah.
Nice.
OK, wait, even if I say nice.
Yeah, nice.
That's got to be advantage.
Give me advantage for him.
Nice. Nice is disadvantage.
No, no. Nice is in like he just remembered like, oh, yeah, we didn't get it.
There's no there's no that it does neither advantage nor disadvantage.
If it's that, if it's this interpretable of a nice,
it's just open to what it could sound like.
Well, they're on the phone.
How do you know?
How do you know she can even hear it?
It's a lower.
So it's a lower.
Maybe he's not because it's over the phone ice to something
else.
Yeah.
I mean, it's a lower difficulty.
Well, I rolled an 11.
So yeah, yeah.
So she says, okay, sure.
Well, you know, let me know when you get it when you get
nice.
Nice.
Yeah, we will believe.
We'll let you know, alright.
Hey, good luck, Oprah.
She bought it!
We're at the mall with our girlfriends.
That's why he's saying that.
She bought it.
She bought a bionicle for me.
She just bought it.
Oh, she keeps buying it.
She says, "Anyway, so I met with Fatima,
And there is one person who is in charge of extracting crypto credentials.
Now, if Blotas gets a good look at them, he can get the crypto credentials from anywhere,
because then Blotas can mimic their identity.
However, Fatima wouldn't tell me exactly who it was, and I didn't want to keep pushing.
That said, there are only three people with crypto credentials who have set foot in the
I cup facility so I'm going to send you those their dossier now and she sends
you the dossier of the three people commit these to memory blow toss and on
the day of you can use one of them as your disguise and then figure out the
rest ask her to spell I cup I'd unknock out Patrick so he can stop typing
Patrick's in like a Stephen Hawking wheelchair typing all of his messages.
I like that Patrick is following the rule of like, "Okay, I'm knocked out so I can't talk."
But I can send secret messages that nobody can hear to my friends.
That's what happens when you get knocked out.
I just learned about the whisper function on Roll20 and I've been sending everyone a message.
Oh, cool.
Yeah, um, what does the dossier say?
Wait, so, oh, I remember everything that's happened up to this point.
The dossier just has like three people's names and their faces as well.
Which are?
Which are literally Doug Jones, Stephen A. Smith,
[laughter]
and stinky Eric are the three guys and their faces their faces
well Doug Doug Jones is a white guy Stephen a Smith is a white guy
well stink yeah and stinky stinky Eric sticky Eric is a green guy
He better be green.
Well he, so he is a, Stinky Eric is a, um, a fungoid.
Which is a type of race in the Gun City world.
They are mu- what, what, what, what do they look like?
A fungoid?
What are their defining facial characteristics?
I can tell you, Cam and I wrote up a whole bunch of lore for this.
So, first name Stinky, second, uh, last name Eric?
Yeah, what's his dad's name?
What's his dad's name?
His dad's name is Papa Stinky.
Papa Stinky.
Okay.
Maybe I need a Papa Stinky after this.
I've been.
I've been in your kitchen.
You've been popping stinkies in fucking Kevin's house?
That's not nice.
Mm-hmm.
You keep that door over there closed.
You can't pop one.
I'm never letting you in my apartment ever again.
Poppin stinkies instead of Molly's a fungoid is a mushroom
yeah they're mushroom... yeah. I didn't mean to get Pat going on that but I was laughing
at it. So Stinky Eric looks like a mushroom kind of
the
Mike and Ike's they look like Mike and Ike's.
No, they look like Mike and Ike's in D&D. I think that's what they were.
Mice and Id's maybe. I don't remember what the race is called, but they're just like mushroom guys.
They are, generally they don't do anything.
So it's kind of weird for one of them to be like a crypto credential guy.
Generally, they just kind of like sit around all day and find ways to collect money.
By doing as little work as possible.
And they are they have like a they're kind of part of money by doing little work as possible.
They try to collect money by doing as little work as possible.
Yeah, I mean, that's that's all the other two guys are just like regular looking white dudes.
Right, who don't try to make money by doing.
They love to work hard.
They work hard. Yeah.
No, no, I like this damn mushroom.
Let's talk about this damn mushroom people for a second.
Look, man, you need a mushroom in your house
where you can rush around and get it all before I see you rushing stinkies.
Oh, I didn't write Doug Jones.
I wrote Doug jerk.
That's actually kind of cool.
There's no Doug Jones.
Yeah, he's Doug jerk.
Stephen A. Smith and sneaky Eric.
Yeah. OK.
So what do we need these guys for? We talked to them about how to...
No, so what...
They are the three people, or the only three people with crypto credentials who visit the iCup facility.
So they either visit it for, you know, consultant reasons, maybe they work for another company that someone wants to partner with,
or they are the people who are in charge of transferring the funds.
Okay, I'm thinking maybe I could disguise myself as one of them at some point.
Yeah, well that's what she's suggesting.
Is the day of when the day of the transfer is happening, right, which is the day you're going to be able to, you could pretend to be someone with crypto credentials who fits the right profile.
So I mean you could have sought these people out, you know, and gotten their crypto credentials, but you guys got crypto credentials.
So instead of doing that, you can just mimic one of them and make that a part of the plan.
Obviously, you can still try to seek these guys out and grab their crypto credentials
or kill them if you figure out which one of them is the person who is actually in charge
of handling the money.
First I think we got to hit the, we got to hit Club Danger.
Yes, no, this is just information she's giving you so you have it to use.
Thank you, love you, bye.
Okay.
What's your what's your mom and dad's name before you go?
Because your name's mommy already.
My mommy.
Or you're like Grandma Goodlegs.
Is that your mom?
No, it's her name is Felicia Goodlegs.
And my father's name is well, I mean, her name is Felicia.
Felicia Day.
Hang up. Hang up.
Miss Daring.
Yeah. All right.
Your father's the only name of your father's good legs.
Yes, yes.
Maurice Goodlegs.
How'd you know?
No, it's Seth.
It's Seth Goodlegs.
Why? What's Sullivan's?
You're not gonna fucking believe this.
Yeah, it doesn't.
Isn't this a little weird?
His mom's name is Mrs.
and his dad's name is Papa.
Stop!
And their last names are his first name
and his last name is just from is what he is.
these frauds are fucked up man
just hold on i'm just i'm gonna figure this out
i'm gonna figure out why this is
just stop stop telling people
basically we're pretty sure he was adopted
i don't think i was adopted
i hate to be the one who breaks the news
i'm pretty sure you're adopted
i don't think you hate being the one to break the news
i gotta really light
it feels good to break this news to you
his name could be like baby sullivan or something
now that i'm thinking about it
that might be the better
Tadpole with no legs, sir.
Yeah, were you- did you grow up with no legs?
Oh my god, Tadpole.
This guy knows everything about fucking frogs.
Just fucking shut up.
Okay?
I know a guy, his name is Tadpole.
If we're talking about him.
We just grow up- we don't grow up like regular frogs.
Dad's name should be Dadpole.
That's a very good point.
I mean that'd be funnier, but...
Your mind will be like, Madam Pole. Nice.
Yeah, then that's how many poles and I don't need
that's too many poles and I don't need to screw in a light bulb anytime soon.
No, they're bad at screwing in my bulbs.
I know. That's why there's three of you.
All right. It's OK. I'll let that go.
All right.
I certainly love the danger club. Mm hmm.
Yeah, I mean, you guys can hop in Sullivan's car
and head over to the danger club.
Yeah, it's in the abandoned techno slime factory.
You guys are familiar with it.
It looks different now.
I mean, at the very least, it has a lot of
a lot of scary looking young people outside.
You see people start to you see people outside of the club
or just, you know, smoking techno slime or injecting techno slime or snorting it.
You know, it's a big sort of club scene.
You see people like smashing beer bottles on their heads.
They're all like challenging each other to do more and more dangerous stuff.
You have to. Is there like a vibe check we have to pass to get in?
No, no, you can just kind of walk in there.
This isn't space Berghain.
No, no, no.
Nor is it the salt salty spittoon.
Oh, yeah, I'm I'm Gary.
Yeah, yeah.
And when I literally you're 16, what?
What I made this in this whole time when I made this I was thinking of Barry G
thinking of Barry G saying he was 16.
I'm 16 I can't go in.
You're all deception Barry G.
Hang on I gotta get my lion boots on.
Barry I've got an idea.
Okay.
All right, so you see right next door to the club
is the Bigington Coat Factory.
the what?
The Biggington Coat Factory.
Why are you moving closer to the monitor?
[laughter]
Are you doing that to hear me better?
No.
You gotta own it.
Biggington Coat Factory.
Yeah, I mean you guys roll insight.
You're the ones trying to believe him.
Or not believe him.
That is your strength save.
You roll, you guys roll insight on that if you believe him.
the
Insight is literally just to see if you believe him or not.
Then you can do whatever you want with that information.
Well, I don't need to roll because I believe that he's 16.
Okay, alright, sounds good.
It's initiative, it's another I word.
Jesus, dude.
I'm ready to fight him for this.
[laughter]
You're still locked out.
No, he's not locked out anymore. He's speaking with lucidity.
You just type in "insight".
[laughter]
the
of
Patrick Yoda was in some kind of severe either debt or...
I'm in debt with every club owner in the city.
Yeah, something like that because of cocaine.
I would say then that you might not know this club owner.
I mean, unless you directly dealt with him.
I don't remember.
To the nights we don't remember and the friends will never forget.
Yeah, sure.
So we can cry if you think if you've owed money to every nightclub owner in the city, we can we can address that when you're in there.
Or we can address that now and be like, you don't want to go in or you want to do something different, because then that could just be a truth that we're we're dealing with.
I take I take a marker and I draw a mustache on.
Okay, cool.
Actually, I already do I already have?
Yeah, yeah, the art Joey made.
I draw it longer.
Okay, cut it.
Draw the opposite of a mustache.
Yeah, just draw green Yoda skin over it.
No, I'd draw it longer.
Yeah, just look like you have a flesh disease.
Also, isn't...
I mean, Barry G is...
You're like made of magnets,
so couldn't you become like...
Can you be like invisible or like slime to go in?
You could become slime and start to sneak around, too.
Yeah, I could do that.
Come on, make 16 year old slime.
[Laughter]
You're 16, you're chock full of slime.
I want to see your 16 year old slime.
[Laughter]
Cool, yeah.
You can just do that, it'll cost you some
techno points, it's your slither ability.
Um...
So you can hold that form
for 10 minutes.
Um, and if you use multiple charges
you can hold that for an additional
An additional 10 minutes after that you have six charges per long rest.
So you have six charges.
You haven't used it yet or you haven't used it since your last long rest.
I don't think if I'm remembering correctly.
No, you did use it once.
So you actually have you'll have you have five charges, but you can use it again.
Now.
He has six charges.
He has six max right now.
He has five.
So I'm saying I'm going to use it once and I'm going to go.
All right.
I'm going to go look for some love slime in the girls bathroom,
and I just sit there away.
Okay, cool.
So we'll address that in a second.
You guys want to go into the Danger Club?
Yeah, of course.
Okay, cool.
Yeah, you guys go into the Danger Club.
All of you roll deck saves.
And I'm looking swagged out.
Right.
I'm dressed to the nines.
Wow.
I'm dressed.
I have a longer mustache.
Holy shit.
failure on everyone's here.
Yeah, well Barry, sorry, you Barry, you didn't have to
because you're Slytherin elsewhere.
Cam, Pat, Yoda, Pierce, so blow toss, Patrick Yoda, and
Travis Ocelot.
You all are able to get out of the way of the swinging axes
that are of course coming down the second you walk into the
danger club.
You, Raymond Johnson, just sort of walk right through it.
I mean, you get hit, but you just sort of just take it.
Well, yeah, I mean, you take some you take damage, but it's
almost like you didn't even your brain didn't really register
it coming and when it's sliced into you.
You take two damage.
That's it.
Yeah, not that much.
It's easy.
Got a low roll.
Can I walk back through it?
Yeah, I mean you can and yeah way.
There's no way.
There's no fucking way.
You got another crit fail?
Two zeros in a row.
Get them all out of the way now before something happens.
Roll it again.
I took another five damage.
Five?
I'm kind of shaking.
That roll was fake.
So now I did walk back out the door.
So I do have to walk back through it again.
There we go.
Crit! Good crit.
Wowie yeah people watch you just like walk through get and get caught up so
fucking bad twice Evan another time walk through and like dodge it like you're
moving through like fucking like you're just moving through anything like it's
like you timed it perfectly and you're immediately noticed I just had to figure
it out a danger to figure out the time it's all about timing I'm doing you
- Do people clap when he says that?
- It's a timing, it's mostly a timing thing.
- People nod and look at him, yeah.
- No, it's not me, it's just timing involved.
- You see Sullivan hovering outside,
he's like, "Do I have to go in?"
- Yeah, and walk really slowly in the entrance.
- It's not about timing at all.
- That's the timing, the timing part is go real slow.
- Yeah, and now I'm not sure about your height,
but just stand on tiptoes when you walk too, just to really make sure of...
nothing.
So the text is of holograms.
They're holograms and they don't hurt.
Yeah, and there also aren't axes, so don't worry.
If you see axes, you're crazy.
Pffft, I got an 8.
Man, Sullivan takes...
how much damage?
Okay, Sullivan takes 4 damage.
He gets caught on the action, swings up into the ceiling and gets caught in the mechanism.
He's just getting swung back and forth like the pyramid ride, the carnivals,
the Egyptian ride, you know the one, right? The Egyptian ship.
Do you guys see that shit?
I know what you're talking about.
The pirate ship.
That's right.
It's a pirate.
Yeah, it's usually a pirate.
It was Egyptian for us.
Where I'm from.
Egypt?
Egypt.
I was in Egypt.
- You got a part of an Egyptian rollercoaster.
(laughing)
- Egypt.
- I'm referring to all the rides as Egypt.
- Rollercoaster, just Egypt rollercoasters.
- Yeah, I went on Egyptian Magic Mountain.
- I went to this crazy Egypt themed restaurant in Cairo
when I was a kid.
(laughing)
- Okay, so yeah.
Yeah, I mean people are impressed with Ray William Johnson.
Yeah, the music is poppin', it's like crazy,
like fucking like lights like it would kill anyone with epilepsy.
It's it's a like insane club like
Dragula to Dragula bites back, which is Rob's obvious follow up
when he was he was revived against his will and forced to make that song good.
And that's what's playing all the time.
And you serious?
Can you write that and record it?
I would genuinely love to write Dragula to Dragula bites back.
Okay, your shot.
Yeah, Cam, Cam, I would need a I want to I want let's collab.
Cam, Cam, let's go.
They can't do it again.
Not anymore.
It's the same song with new lyrics.
That's yeah, exactly.
All this. Yeah.
Um, yeah.
And so you guys are in the club.
So, I mean, you see people like, you know, hanging out, doing drugs,
you people like like pulling, pouring like like
like acid on themselves and like screaming in pain.
You see people like going in.
There's like a little area with a cage with rabid dogs that haven't eaten.
And people are like fucking around with that.
It's like a you know, it's a scary nightclub.
People are going going kind of wacky.
So, I mean, you could try to start to find drugs,
figure out how to get the love slime,
which is both a drug and a chemical chemical component to make bombs.
Before we do that, I would like to nut on a piece of poop.
So we'll do that to Barry G you are slime.
And you're slime and you said you're going towards the girls
bathroom.
Yep.
I'm looking for a love slam in the course bathroom.
Okay, doesn't know any better.
I'm on the ground and I'm going.
Oh, I'm 16.
Can I have some love?
And I'm in the bathroom.
You're blowing your cover.
Yeah, how would you be saying I'm slime?
I'm slim. I have no age and like a real.
Yeah, I'm saying all this.
So where are you going to do that?
What am I?
I'm in the girl's.
I'm I'm 16 years old.
What am I?
Get to the girls bathroom.
You're either going to have to go through the front entrance as slime
or you can start to scale the building and find like a vent or some kind of window or opening.
He's slime. I mean he can go through the crack in the door, no?
What kind of a slime is he?
He can go through anything that has up to like one inch thickness, like one inch of a gap.
He's like a magnetized slime.
So he can really kind of get his toe flat.
That's such a huge gap.
It's a big gap.
It's a really big gap actually. It's like massive.
Well yeah, you can't go through any crack.
Yeah, I would say.
Yeah, I'll go through the vents.
Does it help that I walked in in such a cool way that the women of this club have already slimed every surface in the entire place?
And that maybe he fits in?
If that's... No, I guess not.
I'm sliming through the vents.
Here's an example of it.
Almost just as easily, though.
So he's like Flubber right now?
Yes.
He's a lot like Flubber made out of magnets.
the
>> You're invisible, look at you.
>> What?
>> [LAUGH] >> Look at him, he's not there.
>> Look at him, he's not there.
You're invisible, look at you.
>> [LAUGH]
>> What do we have to do again?
We gotta talk to- >> We gotta get love slime.
>> We gotta get love slime.
We're just trying to get- >> Yeah, we have to make Jubio make love slime.
>> All right, who's the craziest person in the room right now?
Who's the craziest person in the room right now?
That's a good question.
There is...
Me.
[Mimics a loud noise]
There is... whoa, okay.
I mean, you could do a little... I would say do a perception check to sort of...
And then... let's do... actually, no, just do insight.
I think insight should be like, if you're trying to suss out, like, who the craziest person in the room is.
Yeah, it's kind of hard. So you're kind of looking through the crowd and you're like kind of having a hard time discerning who could be craziest. I mean, you see some people like, you know, like, like stabbing himself with knives. We see other people like, like running their head through a wood chipper. And it's like, it's kind of all it's kind of hard for you to really tell like what the craziest person the club is.
Do any of these activities like necessitate the use of love slime as a sort of lubricant?
Are those all of the sexual activities?
Um, the sexual activities don't seem to need to use love slime, but I mean you could certainly
like...
You hear that, women?
You don't need to do anything before.
I mean you could start talking to people too and see what they know, or you can start to
or you can go towards some of the sexual activities
and do a little investigation.
- All right, I put both my guns to my head
and I say, I will kill myself
if no one gives me love slime right now.
- They're gonna like that.
It's the danger club.
- It's a danger club.
- Okay, I won't kill myself.
- No!
- Yeah, people, when you say you're gonna kill yourself-
- Or an opposite club.
(laughing)
- So yeah, you hold the guns to your head.
Some people are like, nice, nice.
It's like they're bobbing to the music
and then like trying to match you also.
Like they take out like,
they got like a machete and hold it to their throat.
Like, yeah, yeah.
It's like, that's how they're dancing with you.
Like, they're trying to like catch your vibe.
- Yeah, and you're cool.
- Yeah.
Yeah, they think anyone who does anything crazy
or dangerous is cool.
- You're a bartender?
- Yeah, of course.
- I go over to the bar.
And then I--
- Don't tell me this bartender is gonna serve a guy
who can only say ice cream.
- I can't, no, I'm lucid now.
He got cured.
Oh, okay.
Cameron cured him.
Cameron cured me because he got annoyed.
I walk up to the bar and then I throw my little Yoda body onto the bar and I, you know, like
the shelves with all the glasses?
Yeah.
I try to drink all of them.
Cool, okay, yeah.
I try to drink everything in the bar.
Alright, roll a few things I guess. I guess let's first have you roll a dex check because the bartender is going to try to stop you.
Okay, cool.
Alright, let's see.
You're trying to duck and weave.
Yeah, they can't do that well.
So yeah, you get around it. You're just trying to drink all the shit.
Now roll a constitution saving throw.
Unless are you looking at what you're drinking?
16. No I'm not.
Okay, yeah. Alright, yeah.
16, okay. You're gonna
start taking some
damage. What?
Because you're drinking poison, some of it.
Some of it is poison. It's a
danger bar. It's a
danger club.
Wait, how much did I get cured?
From the knockout? Because I only had
I only had two hit points.
Oh, so I mean what you can do, well you guys took short rests.
So if you want you can use some of your, you could use, let's actually calculate that.
So let's say you had your full hit die back.
So you have six D8s, so how many do you want to spend?
I'm going to spend two.
Okay.
What's your max HP?
41.
Max HP is 41.
I got three.
Why not just do all of them?
Yeah, okay, I'm six
Yeah - I'll just roll two more 12 you mean four more okay cool
HP back and then yeah, you take you take a damage from the poison I
Had to like figure out how to like take me there's just some poisons that were too strong
But your constitution saving throw was pretty high.
Um, yeah, but people are starting to notice you too.
Um, yeah, they're gonna think you're cool.
Are these a throw up poison?
What?
I'm not supposed to, I'm supposed to be inconspicuous
or I'm supposed to be very cool right now
because I did this so people would think I was cool.
Yeah, there's a, there's a line.
There's, there's, there's, there's,
Mary Kay Cabrera doesn't want you to draw too,
like, to be too
indiscreet,
but what you're doing at this club
right now is kind of fine, right?
Like probably attacking other people is is indiscreet, right?
This is the danger club putting yourself in danger,
even like ransacking the bar is probably fine.
OK, just make sure I thought that we were supposed to draw
so much attention to us that that we get called into the VIP room.
It's kind of like that.
It's actually not a bad idea.
One of you guys should open up your asshole and say,
put love slime in here. I'm crazy.
Yeah. Well, I'm drunk as shit on the bar.
Do you want me to do that on there?
Yes, please.
OK, I'm going to drop my pants down.
OK, cool.
I do.
I undo my pants and I show my little green ass.
Yeah. Off. And I, I mean, I, I
That thing can gape.
Okay, yeah.
You know, you know that thing.
It's gaping, yeah.
Yeah, I forget I, I forget what I was gonna say because
and I'm just standing there and I'm like, I, what?
I forgot what to put in here.
Ray William Johnson, out of the corner of your eye,
you see a familiar looking worm
and you see it slithering
through the crowd and towards Patrick's ass.
Worm? Worm!
You see the worm, it takes a second, turns around and sees you.
You're a worm.
And it slithers towards you.
OK, I grab him by the scruff of his neck.
- Yeah. - His whole body,
which is a neck.
And I give him kisses.
- Yeah. - And then somebody gives me
a kind of a weird glance.
And I say, "He's a poison worm.
Look how close I'm holding him to my face.
I'm being so dangerous.
I love you."
- Yeah.
(laughing)
Yeah, cool.
- We'll go back to that in one second.
So, Barry Gee,
you are now sort of climbing through the vents.
Roll investigation, see if you can like figure out where the girls bathroom is.
What'd you do?
Five, okay.
Wasn't he just in there?
You just follow the girls.
I mean through the vents, I mean.
Oh.
So where's he gonna drop?
So yeah, you drop out of the vents and into, just sort of on the club floor.
And so people are just like stepping around.
So start rolling dexterity saving throws, you're a little slime guy,
try to avoid people there stepping on you.
that might step on you.
- Sit just on here.
- Great.
24?
Yeah, people are like stepping around, glasses dropping,
and you're just like able to weave out of the way
as like a little flubber guy.
- Excuse me, excuse me, excuse me, I'm sorry,
excuse me, I'm sorry.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
And yeah, I mean, now you can sort of just follow the girls
to the girls' bathroom.
- I follow the girls to the girls' bathroom.
- Yes, cool.
Yeah, so you're in the girls bathroom.
What do you want to do?
I'm just hanging out in there.
I'm asking girls where they're from and how old they are.
They're like, what?
What?
Who's saying that?
They're like trying to find out where that's coming from.
Yo, where you from?
Your age?
No, I'm 16.
Yo, no.
They're just like, oh my God.
and
with the worm.
The worm hops out of your hands and starts to slither away and you see it sort of beckoning
you to follow.
With what part of its body?
Its tail.
The main part.
Its only tail.
You know, like, if the head's facing you, you know.
Fuck, dude!
While he's following the worm, you can like, like, there's like cameras following him,
see me out of the corner like on the bar and I'm grabbing a guy by the shirt
collar and I say "put your love slime in me!"
That works. Yeah.
And the guy's neat.
[Laughter]
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, you two, you two are starting to get attention of people.
Blowtoss, are you doing anything in the club or are you just like standing?
I'm asleep.
I was like flat on the floor.
Yeah.
Please down.
Yeah right so you're going so the worm is leading you towards you see like a door back room and the worm you see like slams its head against the door knock knock knock.
And it just opens and it's what is in and six it's a worm tail out and waves you in any see a gesture towards.
like Patrick Yoda and Travis Esselt where they are and go like, you know, one, two,
like, come again also.
Guys, come on. This, my worm, I think it's my worm.
[Laughter]
This, this worm is, is telling us to come in here.
Okay.
Mm-hmm, cool.
So you guys go in there.
I wake up. That was me waking up.
Oh, okay.
What sound did you make?
Yeah.
[Laughter]
That was cool.
Yeah, I love that.
It's a waking up sound.
That's what it sounds like when you wake up, isn't it again?
That's what it sounds like when you wake up like this.
I was like a horse seeing a ghost.
When you wake up, you're like.
You sit up and you yeah.
After you sit up.
But before that you go...
*snort*
Yeah, I didn't hear...
Every time he cuts out, I can hear it through the door.
*snort*
Mm-hmm.
I'm hearing like him...
stopping, and then just hearing like...
*whoop*
*snort*
Barry Gee...
You, uh...
A security guy comes into the bathroom, and says...
Uh, is looking around, and is looking...
He's like, "There's a puddle in here if it's harassing the girls."
And it's sort of looking around for you and he sees this view on the ground.
And he sees like a puddle.
And he's like,
Hello, it's like trying to see if you're said shin.
Just don't say anything.
Playing slime women be crazy.
Yeah, the guard does say that he card goes man women be crazy.
Yeah, he starts to he sort of like sticks is the tip of his his his boot is
bouncer.
I should say not guard sort of towards a puddle of slime and start to
move you a little bit.
Yeah, they are.
I'm going to call bouncers guards from now on.
Roll roll.
I mean, I guess, you know, here's the thing.
It's up to you.
How do you want to play this off?
Like, because right now when he's sort of like nudging you, it is kind of
revealing that you're a little bit more substance than just like some puddle of
water.
Um, but it's not immediately, you know, obvious, but
why would it go? Why would a guy see a puddle and start nudging it with his
boot?
Well, because he was told by a girl that a puddle was talking.
Uh, can I move myself under his boots?
So he loses, he just strips over and false.
Oh, Whoa. Very true.
Yeah. Does he have it? Well, he's all magnets, right?
the
You can also attack this guy with depolarization or I don't want to make a scene.
I just want him to trip over and fall.
Okay, cool.
Yeah, so what you could do.
Yeah, I guess let me think of what you would do here.
Let's just do a hmm.
What's kind of check is this is weird.
It's no real like, you know, I mean like.
Dexterity check because you're sort of like maneuvering underneath his
feet why are some sort of finesse and how you're moving your weird bodily body.
A check so just just hit decks on the far left eleven okay cool so you you can only
get a little bit under his boot and it has a little bit of give it is like huh he starts
to like lift his foot up.
I mean you're kinda like sticking to the bottom of his foot now a little bit.
I mean, I'll give you a chance to react and figure out what you want to do too, though.
I think it's enough time for you to like, have like, figure out either do you want to like...
Because right now, as he's like lifting his foot up, it's like...
It's becoming at least a little bit apparent that something's off with this puddle.
Right.
Um...
Can I just run away again? I'll just run away into one of those stalls.
Cool.
Where you can see me.
Cool. Yeah, I would say like you're gonna move fast enough and take him enough by surprise that like you just get away and go
One of the stalls you think hey, what the fuck and he starts to like bang on the stall
What event he on the floor does that get lapped up on it by his slime body? Yeah that goes into his body
Disgusting I don't think oh, I mean it's up to you Barry. Yeah, I didn't think it there
But what this it's women. It's a woman's bad. I think it gets
You think yeah, you can't have venuses how do how do women pee I don't know I never can I call Sullivan ask him a question
I'm not giving you my mom's number. I need to call her right now. Some guys try to roast me on a spit
Can we talk later?
How does she pee, at least?
I don't know how my mom pees!
Okay, hang up.
You're useless.
Sullivan to himself is like, "Should I know how my mom pees, too?"
[laughter]
Um, yeah, cool.
Uh, we'll cut back from that to you guys in the room that the worm is leading you into.
You see a particularly like, it looks like a normal back room of a club, except it's a little bit more dilapidated, it's the abandoned Techno Slime Factory.
Where people have sex.
Yeah, people fucking. And you see...
Ewww, you didn't have to say it.
I cover my eyes.
I throw up.
Do you guys keep walking? I cover my eyes and hold my nose. Yeah? I hold my nose. I try to cover the throw up with my hand and the throw up shoots out so fast that it gets in my eye.
Okay. What happens after that? I throw up more. Yeah, you tell me. Okay, cool. I get a normal healthy boner. Yep. Thank God, you know. I throw up on his boner.
boner. So you walk, I say, guys, this is
awful.
It's called as you guys are as you guys are walking around and
sucking puke off each other's boners.
What the hell?
Yeah, and watching people fuck you reach a part of the end of the back where it's starting to get really really dark like too dark sort of like in a souls game where it gets like pitch black in like an area and you walk through and it's just a wall and it looks like that and as you get there you hear familiar voice.
Say, "Don't come any closer."
You guys would recognize that as the mad suckler.
Oh, this fucking guy.
Yeah, who?
Yeah.
I throw up on him.
"Don't come any closer." Where are we supposed to go?
Okay, I got a mouth full of cock and puke.
I'm supposed to make a...
I'm supposed to talk to you.
He holds out his inordinately long finger.
I put my mouth on it.
Oh, this is why my damn worm...
That wasn't even my worm.
That was just one of the worms he has.
the
I think Pat last time you sucked on his finger.
Definitely one of us definitely.
That was definitely me, yeah?
He said, oh, I remember this OK.
Yeah, you like it.
You still like it?
No, he likes it.
I hate it.
Watch this and I start walking towards.
Down the finger.
(laughing)
- How far can you get?
- And then I throw up.
- Roll constitution to see how many inches you get.
(laughing)
- Roll constitution, yeah.
- 10.
- You can't even deep throw.
You take those--
- How many inches?
- What?
I thought that was for, hold on, let me roll a,
okay, I'm gonna roll a D20.
- Let me roll one more time.
- How long is the finger?
- Hold on, let me just roll again.
We'll do it. We'll do it the same way
dude
No
Just said you can't you know you got a ten dude. What the fuck you think?
I don't think that your esophagus is long enough
Ten inch we're gonna. I'm gonna roll small Yoda for a roll a d4 and if I get
We'll do it the same way. I guess cuz this has this has no consequences
So yeah
You don't have to roll at all.
Just say that you put it all in your ear.
You get one inch before you throw up.
*Laughter*
Not even fully in your throat, dude.
It just went past your teeth.
At the lips, yeah.
It smelled so bad.
*Laughter*
Okay, and Vansome goes like, "That didn't happen last time, but, um, look, just, I don't want
too many people to know that I'm, I hear you guys yelling about love slime over and over
and over again.
Just take the love slime and go.
Here I'll give you some.
Oh, thank you.
I have some.
Just hold on.
You have to keep this quiet."
I hold onto his finger.
the
the highest investigation
- Nice. - See if this is real live love slime.
- Oh yeah. - Yeah, definitely, definitely, definitely.
- Oh, true. - Definitely really interesting.
- I'll roll to see if it's real love slime. That's a good idea.
Yeah, 'cause Patches would trick us.
- I would. - No, Matt Suckler would.
- Mm-hmm.
- Patches would never, but the Matt Suckler might.
- He was based off of Patches.
- Yeah. - Yeah, he's based off of me with my long hair.
- You got that 26.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, like,
I don't know how much knowledge you have about
Love slime this would be more Barry G's department
but at least from we have the one guy who would know about this is
We can always just go
Where I'm just hiding behind under the stall and someone comes in I just go to the next all over and just
- You're tormenting the bouncer. - You did nothing on this mission.
- You did absolutely nothing. - I distracted the guard.
- I distracted the guard. - We didn't need him to be distracted.
- There's a bouncer. - You don't know that.
- I distracted the bouncer. - He's in full plate armor and he has like a spear and a torch.
- You're a guard. He's like, "No, I'm a bouncer."
Yeah, you mentioned his steel boots, but he has steel everything.
[laughter]
I mean, with the 26, you can tell that, like, it's, it looks like a slime TM product,
and it's definitely not Techno Slime.
And that's like a pretty good indicator that it's probably Love Slime.
I believe you, I just ran a check on this, basically.
And, uh, yeah, you're, we're good.
Okay, well...
If you're going back to marry Kate
Tell her I'm go I will return
What the court?
Well, yeah
The Lord. Hey, you want me to say I will you want me to say he said I will return you admitted fucking act it out
No, don't you don't have to act it out. Just can I paraphrase I
If you have to, if that's too hard to remember.
The mad suckler, he's gonna be swinging on by.
Okay.
It's pretty good.
And yeah, and you guys got that there slime
and you guys did it without killing anybody,
which is good.
Was it discreet enough?
Yeah, you didn't kill anybody, which is good.
That's basically it for discretion.
But yeah, I mean, right now though,
you have to figure out how to get Barry Yee
out of the women's bathroom.
Okay, do I have a humongous, silly straw?
Okay.
All right.
That's all right. I'm teasing.
Do I have a killer clowns from outer space, silly straw?
Or is there one in the room that maybe they used to have a worm
sounding or something?
You have a worm.
Oh, yeah, true.
Can I?
I have worms all around.
Can I worm centipede my worms to create one long tube?
the
What you have to roll is...
Let's have you just roll...
God, everything with you guys do is like dexterity, right?
'Cause it's just your ability to like, put things together.
Intellect! Intelligence!
This is an intelligence thing.
This is a very intelligent thing.
Okay, so a saving throw?
No, just regular.
Regular intelligence.
23.
Oh!
Fuck yeah.
You... I don't know...
You've just had a lot of experience human centipeding things, I guess.
You're and I kind of I like whip it around the entire place.
Well, that's women's restroom.
That's going to be a check or you're going to have to get somebody
to feed it in there.
I want to see him whip it.
Yeah, everybody.
Everybody's kind of looking at me now.
I already did.
I did like the hard part.
Well, you whip it and the the front of it just slams into the door.
I actually, okay, all right, now could you, sorry, would you mind opening that door and
every door between here and the women's restroom?
Yeah, that one too.
We each hold one of the doors open.
My assistants.
We all hold one door open and thread the worm.
Yeah, you guys thread the worm through the club.
I hear a large ruckus, then someone's knocking on the door, so I just leave there out, out
of their
worms.
No, wait, no,
I have one end of this of the worm straws in the women's
restroom and I don't know where Gary I don't know.
I don't know if Barry's in there.
So I just start sucking.
It's in the toilet.
It's in the bigger than I thought he was.
Barry.
Yeah,
it just keeps sucking.
I'm just gulping down women's shits and used tampons.
[laughter]
Yeah, it's great.
And then Harry slimes through the toilet.
[laughter]
Well, you wouldn't know if he came through at all.
You would just like, "I think I got him."
Yeah, "I think he may be in here somewhere."
[laughter]
And I'm just like, fountaining out just different shit.
Just lost earrings and underwear.
You know when women drop the toilets.
Yeah, yeah, perfect.
Yeah, thinking a girl lost earrings and yeah, of course, yeah,
in a pink heart, a fucking Barbie.
Yeah, yeah.
A Barbie doll.
Cool.
I mean, you guys got the love slime.
I'm I say we we chill out there because I think the last one
was a little bit longer.
So I feel comfortable in this one where it's at.
Unless you don't.
I rolled 100 dice.
And I planted a bomb in the woman's bathroom and it blows up and then we run away.
Okay good.
Yeah.
If you could have planted a bomb we wouldn't have had to do any of this right?
I planted a bomb.
Oh shit.
Were you actually planting a bomb?
Uh yeah I did it and it exploded.
Okay.
Yeah, that roll I just did was how much damage everyone in the club did.
Everyone in the club takes 1068 damage.
No, I meant individually.
I meant individually, every person is one of these numbers.
What? What does that mean?
So, some people took crit 1, some people took 20.
Oh!
0, 100, 20.
[Music]
(upbeat music)