[Music]
Last time on Gun City Stories, a broad city, the Uncle's Falcon.
The crew stood before a mysterious door in the abandoned porno factory.
And what they found behind it was hard to believe.
A fully furnished Technoslime lab with prototype machinery and Technoslime apparatuses.
One not even approved by the Stakehams Federation of Bodies and Spaces.
that Patrick Yoda had encountered in Mommy's bathroom.
Ray William Johnson drank an entire vial of the stuff and went on an Evangelion-type odyssey
where his body and soul melted into one thing.
Big bitches.
He awoke from the trance, able to search the room with the aplomb of a truly great detective
like Sherlock Holmes.
Underneath a pile of Maxim magazines he discovered a blueprint which had something called "The
Coculus Rift 2.0, the Coculus Quest, Cordless Experience, with pictures of vivisected penises
on it.
"The name at the bottom of the blueprint said Dr. Twolateralis."
Suddenly, the Iron Guardians burst back into the factory, realizing that they were tricked
by the wily Blotas Piss.
A great battle ensued and Blotas almost died, but luckily Patrick Yoda brought down the hurt
with his hoagie surprise for a devastating blow.
The mess got the attention of the Jollibee police force along with police captain Filipino
Mr. Bean.
He warned the boys to not get too ahead of themselves in this case.
But good job finding those Iron Guardians.
It seems they were, much like the Technoslime Red Eye drugs, not approved by Stakehams and
have been making appearances throughout Gun City and causing mayhem.
They are V-folks, with an X of course, that can actually cause harm to real people, a terrifying
prospect.
The boys booked it out of there before Filipino Mr. Bean could finish questioning them, and
slept at their respective abodes. Patrick Yoda on his hoverboard outside of a tattoo parlor,
Blotas Piss in some kind of endless Russian doll refraction of holiday refuse in the middle
of the park, and Ray William Johnson three and a half inches deep inside his wife Cameron.
The next morning, the boys went with Sullivan to Mommy Good Lakes, where she opined about
the value of the Matrix 2, V-Folks, Beauty, and spoke of her suspicions of sabotage. Our
Our heroes talked about eating poop and had I think canon gay sex with one another and
posted it online to ebay.
I'm not sure if that was cut out or not.
We haven't edited that episode yet so there's really no way to know whether that happened
or not.
Alright I'm making a call right now.
It's in.
(laughing)
- Yeah, it really got towards the end, it got.
Anyway.
(laughing)
- Mommy brought them to the secret Jack In chamber
at the bottom of Mommy's good legs,
then informed the boys of a plan
to check the Jacked In archives and records offices
in the United Health Group Incorporated
in Marlborough District to figure out
when Sean McKelvey left Jacked In.
Once they confirmed that,
Mommy will feel more comfortable
helping them get into The Matrix 2,
and they can go in after Sean,
if he's even in there.
The boys now sit in the secret jacked-in chamber
underneath Mommy Goodleg's club,
debating whether they should do this heist
or see what there are,
see what other options there are.
But before we do that, they have to level up.
That's right.
In this arc, we're going to watch our heroes level up.
Now, everything that's been made for them
is extremely homebrew,
so I've come up with some tweaks of my own
that they can pick and choose what they want
at this level up.
At this point, I think the narrator should stop talking.
Okay, that's what I did.
Things to remind you guys after this.
Patrick, you now have the Needler.
You can check your inventory.
I updated that.
You have the attack for the Needler as well.
If you have any more,
if you want any more information about that,
I have a little note.
- You can go to Needler.com.
- Yeah, you can go to Needler.com.
- HaloNeedler.com.
- HaloNeedler.com/Patrick.
And you'll find what your Needler does.
Caleb. - Yeah.
You have two more servings of raw Techno Slime.
So, um, those-
- Just fucking go.
- Like last time, those will give you advantage
on like every kind of check,
and recharge your Techno Slime points.
But the next day you will have disadvantage
on all Dex tech, Dex checks,
which is what you're going through right now.
So like, you're kind of like wobbly.
Like you can't really like handle what's going on.
If you take it again though, today,
while you're like in withdrawal,
you will be fully addicted to Techno Slime
and have to deal with those consequences
that are in the techno slime addiction system.
- So if you want to take it again, you can.
- I was going to say, I just take both right now,
but I guess I'll allow you to live.
Yeah.
Cameron, a reminder this time,
you have a monkey named Patrick.
- The monkey this entire-
- You've forgotten, even in the first Gun City thing,
you forgot about it.
- I literally made a note.
- It's a quiet monkey.
All right.
He's very quiet.
This entire campaign, the monkey has been inside my jacket pocket and zipped up inside.
He's completely quiet.
But I made that note to remind you of that.
I'm going to try to do that for every recap going forward.
So we have like...
Just tell me I have a monkey.
Yeah, that in particular.
But yeah, so level up, folks.
So, for anybody listening at home who is a 5e, D&D 5e person, I sort of based all three
of their classes off of different sort of, so like Caleb, I sort of based him off of
a warlock, Cameron off of fighter, and Patrick Yoda off of, kind of based off like a druid
mixed with like a fighter because it gave them some like more physical chops and
then from there I mixed around the proficiencies and I mixed around a bunch
of abilities and stuff. Can you pull up that uh that level up tree again?
I closed out of mine. Absolutely yeah and so what I did is I made a like sort of my
own sort of level up system where it's kind of a little bit more resembling a
video game where you can choose a subclass to start putting points in and
and then choose an ability within that.
I'll probably post these on the Discord at some point
to show people, because I think it's kind of fun and interesting.
They're cool.
I used draw.io.
If you guys are looking for flowchart applications,
it's a really good one.
First thing that you guys should know about your level up.
All of you guys, regardless of your...
You're all going to increase your total Tecto Slime points by 25%.
Next, we're going to increase your hit points.
- So... - Better not.
Yeah, it's gonna be different for each one.
All right, Patrick doesn't get to increase his hit points.
- He doesn't want to. - Yeah, Patrick doesn't.
- Don't make him increase his. - No, I want them now.
- I don't. - Okay.
- I do. - So, what you guys need to do
is, again, 'cause I based this off the class that you were.
- So, first, Cameron. - Yeah.
Roll 1d10 and add your constitution to that.
And that will be how much your hit points increase.
All right.
Nice, that's gonna be pretty good.
Six plus one, seven.
Nice, seven.
So you increase your hit points by seven.
Cool.
Patrick Yoda.
You will roll a D8.
Okay.
So like forward slash R.
Nice, hell yeah, dog.
So like, see how it's like three
on the left side of your character sheet?
Yeah.
That's your constitution bonus.
You add three to four.
So you add seven. Can you do that, Pat?
(Patrick laughs)
So I have seven constitution now?
There it is.
No, so you have seven,
You add 7 hit points to your max now.
So now you're at 34 hit points.
Okay, nice.
And then, uh, Caleb, you have, um,
I don't remember, I don't think Warlocks are 1d6,
but I guess I was basing yours off Wizard.
So you roll a d6.
Caleb's a certain type of Wizard.
Yep.
Very high Wizard.
A cool Wizard.
He did very well in that roll.
So now just add your Constitution to that
and then add that to your total hit points.
Okay, hold on.
My constitution bonus of two?
Yes, sorry.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yes.
Gotcha.
So that puts me at 31.
Nice.
Okay.
Cool.
And then, yeah, yeah, your technical points.
Great.
So that's the stuff that needs to, that's just like sort of maintenance stuff.
So now, is I've given you guys two points.
So if you look at your tree, each of your trees, I don't know if you guys, can you guys pull them all up?
Yeah, I got mine.
I'm seeing it.
I'm looking at it.
Good.
I read through the stuff.
Awesome.
Perfect.
So if you spend one point, you unlock a subclass.
So for Blotaspis, your subclasses are,
you're a Grinch Hunter is your class,
is what I've called it.
- Yes.
- Your subclasses are Grinch Killer,
Gun Sniffer and Shadow Who.
Each of these have different abilities
that you can then unlock with an additional ability point.
Once you unlock a subclass though,
it's gonna cost two ability points
to unlock the next subclass.
So you can't really unlock more than one subclass
level up. So, if you unlock Grinch Killer, you're gonna get +1 to your strength. If you
unlock Gun Sniffer, +1 to your DEX, Shadow Who to your Intelligence. And then from there,
we can go into the abilities.
Uh, uh, uh, Patch Gyoda, you are a Force user. And so I based this off of Kotor. Uh, so Sentinel
Guardian Counselor. Um, if you spend one point, you're gonna get on Sentinel. Sentinel, I never
really liked how Kotor did it. They kind of tried to make it like a like like rogue or
specialist. I always liked watching Caleb play with his pumpkin lips. You know, I'm
waiting till it's my turn. Okay, it's almost your turn. So with Sentinel, you're gonna
increase your max techno slime by 50%. Sentinel is basically taking advantage of your force
abilities. Uh huh. And like everything you get in there is gonna increase your when you
use the force which is one of your abilities is going to make that like
really really powerful. Guardian is just going to make you a better fighter in
general so like a Yoda agility and Yoda warrior increase like Yoda agility I
think increases your I don't remember exactly I have to double check that but
Yoda warrior. I can increase my movement speed. Yes. I can deflect projectiles if my AC beats an
attack roll. Yes. Yeah all these buffs are pretty cool.
Yoda Warrior makes you like you can do an extra attack. So
that's fun and Yoda Hawks famous 900 is you do like a
Tony Hawk 900 and shoot out basically a gust attack in 5E
and then Counselor is sort of like game breaking divination
spell type **** So Yoda knows means you get to like actually
contact somebody we can discuss in game what that looks like to
make it work, but Yoda has been alive for 900 years. so you
should know somebody who can help you with something you have
much to learn. Young Jedi uh allows you to I don't remember
what the **** that allows you to do but I wrote it down and then
peace for Yoda. Peace for all is like allows you to literally
stop a fight in its tracks for 10 minutes. Um so again, like
all these things, anybody who's like plays five is like this
**** game breaking but that's why we're doing it. It's fun.
Uh Ray William Johnson, it's now your turn because I'm
making your **** awful faces. So, uh you have two points to
level up. You have are we demon? So that taps into your demon and your demons
abilities. What those can do and an are we computer which taps into your
computer side and then Bazinga. Bazinga is special. It's basically a hybrid of
your abilities. I don't want to quite give you too much information about that
unless you choose it but it involves a curse. Oh my god dude you're really gonna
think that I'm not gonna pick that yeah I mean I kind of you could only you could
only pick bazinga level one at this point I have to wait to the next one
right and then you'll have like an extra point left over though for your next
level up if you do that and what that does it gives you all stats plus one
which is pretty crazy but then I'm gonna pull up a table of curses and give you
some sort of crazy curse and you're also gonna deal with some body transmographic
body or your body's gonna look different.
Oh okay. It's gonna be the first phase of your body looking different. I choose
Bazinga. Alright I figured you you would. Okay so I made my choice too I don't
know I think I might have made mine. Okay so let's start with the order that you
guys announced. So Ray William Johnson you've chosen Bazinga so we're gonna
increase all your ability points by one and we're gonna do that right now. Let's
fucking go. Yeah. Do I need to do that or can you do it? I got you. Such a good
friend. Such a good mom. How could it be in the mom? The best moms increase your ability points for you.
Please fucking don't don't do this to me man. You know? You're the dad.
You're the sexy dad dude. You're the dad and the mom. Look at that extra unbuttoned button.
That's not just a just to show us your dad. It's just hot in here. Yeah
Dads are always hot dads are never never the right temperature. Yeah, it's true
And bazinga you get an armor class. Oh your armor class also goes up, right?
Great. Okay. I'm thinking I made the right choice. So so
Yeah, so bazinga my description of refer it is you synchronize your being a demon in a computer a computer in the demon
What are you? Who are you? You're warring signs become more at peace, but at what cost?
so
this
We have a few curses in D&D that are
Some are funny. Some are like genuinely debilitating. It's like this is in real life
No curse in real life is funny. Fuck is funny. We cannot joke about curses glitter emoji star emoji
Laugh emoji. They are not funny
The first thing I'm gonna describe for this though is how your body starts to change big juicy tits
Back off dude. Worry about your own juicy tits, please
So first thing is that please you please little eye candy for the other detectives
You do not get big juicy tits
Instead you get a a
a very interesting hairdo all of a sudden that sprouts in your head.
Doesn't sound like a curse. It's like my dream. That's the first
first part. It sort of looks like a like very high hairline,
very cropped haircut. brown hair kind of short. And it sort of
makes you look kind of dweeby, but it's sort of the first
Aspect you feel that sort of appear on top of your head
That's the first slavery because you kind of look like
Like a like a little boy almost with this haircut. I look like a little boy now
What's gonna happen though what curse is it I'm gonna roll and pick one of these curses from that still eye candy for Patrick
I guess yes, no
No, it's not even better for him
No, shut up
So let me roll and I'm gonna pick from my list. Okay, here we go. Okay seven. Let's take a look at my list
Might not be so bad. That's the thing not the list. Oh
It's not gonna be bad. It's not gonna be bad. Seven is the Lord's number
The Lord's number is 100 cuz that's how many angels he has
Is 100 angels
That noise wasn't can you dramatically react into the microphone?
That's a good like when you see like a very nice ghost
Yeah
That was a bust if I've ever heard one
Yeah, I busted
Folks, it's you have the curse
Your first curse is day Bane
banging hey man no no I what what was a day Bane you turn it sounds bad the
target takes 1d 6 points of non-lethal damage for every minute of exposure to
bright light. Oh, my God. That's yes. Dude, I'm a I'm just a
vampire out of no out. I can explain this to my wife,
Cameron, the only you're only the bad part of a vampire. Yeah,
cool. I'm just gonna like walk downstairs for breakfast and be
like, Hey, babe, by the way, I, for some reason, I'm a vampire
now don't worry oh yeah I leveled up it's not gonna make any sense to her dude oh
yeah so so how does how does Ray William Johnson react to getting this hair
feeling a lot stronger like freakishly stronger like that's very impressive
okay I go to the doctor because I think I might have prostate cancer okay yeah
okay um oh Ray William Johnson it's good to see you hey what's up doc you're
You're looking well, I like the haircut.
You think I look well?
Well how do you mean?
I mean I look like a baby and I'm allergic to the sun.
Well hold on, we don't know.
And it really sucks because you have an outdoor doctor's office.
Ow.
Yeah, well it's cold.
Well look we're dealing with a pandemic here so.
Ow.
Hold on, let me, so the doctor starts trying to put up a tent.
Hurry up Eddie Bauer.
Okay, how is that?
Who I sound like he finishes putting up the tent now.
Okay, let's take a look in here and he he takes out a fucking
what's the thing you look at when you're looking at fucking
ears telescope. Yeah, telescope. He points it in your ear. He's
like, Oh, interesting. And he sees in your in your in your
brain. He sees a the logo for TBS just printed on your brain.
Yeah. Ah, interesting. And he he he showed he shows you the
x-ray. It seems that you're very funny. Ray William Johnson. Why
thank you. And but because of this, I recommend you stay out
of daylight. This is pretty good. I have DBS in my brain.
Yeah, that's right. I'm assuming so. I mean, I've never really seen anything like this before.
Your vitals are higher, you're running, your heart rate is perfect. You're the strongest I've
ever seen you. Your demon seems under control, but something else has happened to you. And I
don't know what that TBS is, but it's a very rare type of melanoma that seems to be growing on top
of your brain. I knew it. I knew it was cancer. Yeah. Well, it might be benign, but we'll have
have to do further checkups to find out.
Have you seen Bucket List with Queen Latifah?
She's not in that movie.
I don't think she's in that movie.
I thought that was her movie.
Isn't that with Morgan Freeman?
No, that's a different one.
That's any movie with Queen Latifah.
No, Bucket List is Morgan Freeman.
Morgan Freeman and Jack Nicholson.
Queen Latifah Cancer movie.
You're thinking of Last Holiday.
Have you seen Last Holiday?
[laughter]
No, I haven't. It's the year 2245.
How does that movie go?
Uh, never mind.
Continue, then.
Sure.
Well, I suppose based on how you were bringing that up, much
like Queen Latifah in Last Holiday, I would say you should
be wary of of continuing down this path of increasing your
strength and and but increasing your level of curse, which
is what I'm going to call this as the doctor in this scene
that is happening while you guys are in the basement.
You're calling me in.
It's uh, yeah, yeah, yeah. On their PSP. Yeah, of course. Yeah.
Yeah. Alright. Well, I have to go. Um I have to go look at uh
uh pussy gotta go and he uh hangs up and and uh yeah, he
hangs up on you leaving you despondent with your new curse.
So we'll figure out how that looks gun city's a dark
Blade Runner type city. You won't always have to deal with
that but there will be instances where the harsh fluorescent lights of the fake
Sun above does cause you damage and we'll figure out how to do that maybe we want
to get you an umbrella or something we'll see but next Cameron blowjob piss
yeah you said next and then and then we'll go to mr. Yoda but Cameron what
did you pick? What do you think? So out of the three paths I picked Shadow Who. Great.
Shadow Who rocks. Yeah I think this is gonna be the most fun one. Yes and so
Shadow Who. The day was unkind to the Grinch hunter who was mocked and made a
fool of, but the night, oh yes the night, was so much kinder. Your brilliance and
your curiosity led you to seek out, I wrote seek with an A, that's crazy, out
out the forbidden Lorox magics, making you an unstoppable mystic warrior, feared by all.
When a shadow who is on the case, everyone basically fucking shits themselves.
You're in, you're out without a trace, except for the faint traces of mystic death.
Add +1 to your intelligence.
Okay, here, let me add my +1 to my intelligence really quick.
Yes, and now you have three abilities here that you can choose from.
I like all of them, but which one did you pick?
I chose Master of Disguise.
That's what I'm hearing.
That's pretty much the only one.
Yeah, Master of Disguise.
Your deep autism has allowed you to master mimicry of all creatures.
For four Techno Slime points, you can perfectly imitate
and disguise yourself as one person.
If anyone starts to pick up on it, they have to roll with disadvantage on an Insight check,
and your Deception is rolled with advantage.
So, describe that process of mastering, of tapping into Lorex magic.
Is this something you meddled in as a young Who boy?
Yeah.
Or is this new for you?
No, this is, um, I come, I kind of have just like an epiphany one day walking around, right?
I'm walking around Gun City and I see one of those living statue performer guys and I'm
like, "Oh my God," and I drop everything.
I run back to my house and I sit down in a meditation pose, complete silence, and I think
for about ten seconds and then when it's over I'm able to disguise myself as people.
And so what I do, right, is I get up and I head out to Ray William Johnson's doctor and
I disguise myself as Ray William Johnson and I go up to the doctor and I say, "Hey doc,
I need my stomach pumped.
I think I guzzled too much cum last night and accidentally swallowed my favorite toy, but
could you make an appointment for tomorrow for that to happen and please come to my house
and do that to me tomorrow morning?
"Hey, thanks doc. See you later."
And I go back to my house.
- And the best part of that was it was all a dream.
(laughing)
- No, that happened.
- And the whole thing was a dream, and that's the--
- That's the best part of it.
- You know what?
Since this doctor exists in a fake liminal space,
I want you guys to roll contesting D20s
to see if it happens or not.
- I'm gonna win. - This is gonna happen.
- I will win. - This has to happen.
- I will win.
- I got a 15.
- You got a one. - Oh no, I got a one.
God damn it.
Yes.
All right, roll, roll Caleb.
He did, he got a 15.
Oh, you did?
Oh, damn, okay.
So yeah, so here's what I actually have.
You go to the doctor and you do say this,
but the doctor writes down instead,
Dominican Cameron, Caleb's wife, to get her stomach pumped.
So he's still gonna go there.
Pump my wife's stomach, dude, without me there?
That's disrespectful.
Yeah, that's fucked up.
That's not what I was trying to do at all.
Yeah, no.
I wish that I was just getting my stomach pumped.
- Okay, you heard him Pat, just do it, do it.
- Okay, so.
- It's like a cool Rod Stewart thing, you know.
- Is that what's cool about Rod Stewart?
- Yeah, you got his stomach.
I don't know anything else about him.
I thought he was just famous for that.
- Okay, yeah, sure.
We're gonna have it, he goes to you then.
Let's do that.
We'll resolve that when that comes.
I'll have to make a note.
- It happens the next end game day.
- Which is not where I ever saw my life going,
but I'll have to take a note about that.
It happens two sessions from now.
Yeah, yeah.
Set an alarm on your phone.
Dr. Pumps.
Dr. Cum Pumper.
That's his name.
Dr. Cum Pumper just finished looking at a pussy and now he has to extract cum in a toy
from my stomach.
Actually, no, he has to leave the cum.
I want the cum in there.
Yeah, yeah.
He has to just take the toy.
get my toy out. Yeah, the cum was not the problem. And if you touch a single drop of cum. If
you disturb the position of any of the cum. You just said this to him. It's like operation.
He's not like batting an eye. He's like, yeah, of course. Like that's. Of course, the toy
is what's most important here. I will never, I would never compromise the cum in your tummy.
Um, okay, perfect. So you have master of disguise. That's going to be pretty cool. Um, I'm excited
to see that. Now, Patrick Iota, much like the protagonist of KOTOR 1, you are now choosing
between three paths. So, between counselor, guardian, or sentinel.
I'm gonna be the counselor.
Hell yes. Okay, let me find... what the fuck did I write for this?
You should fuck Bastila.
Dude, she's so fine.
the
(laughs)
- Dracula, you gotta fuck Dracula.
- I might.
Don't worry, don't worry, I might.
- The Jedi counselors are the ones who understand
that peace can be the answer.
They build connections, use diplomacy,
and work with the flow of the force
to bring about peace and harmony.
Yodas are often counselors,
using their superior wisdom and age
to build a foundation for peaceful force techniques.
If I say peace one more time, add plus one to your wisdom.
So that's pretty neat.
And now you have three abilities to choose from.
Wait, do I add it to the 20?
Yes.
Oh yeah.
Also in this, which, uh, people in five who are familiar with five, do I type
plus one or do I just make it a 21?
Just make it a 21.
Okay.
Um, is that I, I allow them to go over 20, um, because I don't care.
Uh, I think that rule is stupid.
badass
so
Jedi counselor you have three abilities you can choose from right now
What are you thinking? I think I don't even want to hear what they do
You just want to guess reading what they do
Okay, I just haven't been able to decide so yeah for listeners Yoda
He has Yoda nose, which is that he can basically contact. It's sort of like there's um
I forgot what the there's a background in D&D that allows you to like make a
contact and this is sort of like replicating that except like we're
bypassing a lot of bullshit with that and just letting him contact somebody
when he's in a tough situation. He and I will discuss in real time
like sort of what that looks like. Once he uses it you can't use it again until a
long rest so whenever he sleeps again. You have much to learn young Jedi which
is a courtesy of Ron Donald. Basically, you can forge a telepathic link among up to
eight willing creatures of your choice within range. So this is like, I forgot
what fucking spell this is like, but it doesn't matter. So the point is that
basically he can like communicate telepathically with his friends, which is
obviously a huge, a huge boon. And, but it's not, you're not able to
communicate over different planes of existence, which is true for the
whatever the spell is in 5e, but is like the matrix 2 in this one.
So he wouldn't be able to communicate with people through the matrix 2
should he go in there.
And all creatures who are linked with him have advantage on saving
throws while linked.
So it's a really helpful spell and they have a so I can link to a
character while using it and then like as long as they're willing,
okay, and it's just so that you can talk with them basically.
So it's good for your allies.
If you want to talk if you're in a tense situation and you don't
want to alarm somebody about your side plannings.
So it's sort of like in-game metagaming, basically.
- Okay.
- And then Peace for Yoda, Peace for All.
Patrick Yoda basically creates a realm of mental stability,
instantly calming any conflict he's in for 10 minutes.
This means a fight can be stopped
and turned into a conversation.
So like in games when people are like,
"Oh, I want to like persuade them to stop fighting."
Most of the time when you're in the middle of a fight,
I'm like, "I'm not going to let you do it."
because it's like someone shooting at you.
But in this case, Patrick Yoda can basically just like
use his Yoda abilities to calm everyone down for 10 minutes.
That doesn't mean everyone's gonna be friends,
but they'll basically stop fighting
and he could figure out,
sort of strategize from there what to do
as long as he doesn't like instigate
another fight, obviously.
So three really cool abilities.
Which do you want?
- I'm gonna go, I'm gonna do peace for Yoda.
- Awesome, yeah.
So what happens?
What led Patrick Yoda into this counselor mindset?
Why did he choose this?
- Just kind of decided.
(all laughing)
I look over Cameron, so we're still, are we still in,
no, we're not in Sullivan's car.
- You're in mommy's good legs, weird basement.
- Secret basement.
- So I just, I turn to Blotas and I say,
"Hey, I'm gonna be peaceful now."
I punch him in the face.
And I say, I say, I'm going to be peaceful.
What do I roll?
Yeah, do you want to if you want the punch to face to be real?
We can know it was I did it.
I did it as a joke.
Yeah.
So it was just because it was a joke.
You didn't take any damage.
Um, the prank, like just like in real life.
Yeah.
Uh, yeah.
Okay.
So you guys are all leveled up.
So you're feeling stronger.
feeling more... I'm me dude I'm fucking allergic to the Sun and and bald. You got
all your stats boosted dude. You're strong as fuck. I guess. Yeah and and you have one
ability point left over so you can spend more next time but yeah so now what you
can do is so now here's where you guys are at you're in the basement she
basically told you like I have I talked with with Sullivan the frog so if you
guys want to do the heist you can but that being said there's a lot you guys
can do you know you guys learned a lot of information since then about the you
know about what's going on the techno slime what's going on a bunch of other
things so there's a lot places you can go from here but if you want to do that
want to do a heist you can wait so why do we need why we need money right why do
we need money again? Yeah, so here's here's what's up. You
need you need money to basically to uh uh either a repair the um
techno slime uh uh not techno slime. **** my **** Uh the
matrix two um sort of portals to get in there which mommy would
spend on but she wants to first make sure that Sean is
definitely in there because otherwise it's basically just
like wasting time repairing it. Mm hmm. Um obviously you have
other options. So one of her things is like, okay, I like can help you guys break
into the records office so that you could find out if Sean is still in there. Or
you know, you can ask around, you can, there's a bunch of things you can do. But
this is like the first time where I'm kind of like, figure out what you want to
do. So I can lay out the details once more, some more details too. So when you
went to the lab, it was a tech, it looked like some sort of like makeshift tech,
There's slime in lab
You found a blueprint with dr. Tool lateralis his name on it. You found raw techno slime. You found those weird like sort of a red-eye
fucking a cowboy bebop techno slime drugs you
You
found the V sort of warriors that are like kind of apparently a thing in gun city right now that are like
Kind of kind of scary because the idea of being able to like replicate people who can just
Basically being able to generate people with code who can hurt people in real life is a bad prospect for people
but also mommy good legs has provided you obviously with like a thing that you could do and a path forward but
that requires like more illicit break-ins, so
I
Think I have an idea
the
you want to discuss with us first?
yeah what's going on?
uh... what are you doing with your phone you know you're not supposed to go on
your phone without asking us first
you need a... i can't actually allowed to go on my it's my phone
it's my property i pay T-Mobile every month
no you have a jitterbug phone
me and Patrick don't
you have a jitterbug phone and me and Patrick pay for it so i mean you kinda have to go
to us... oh i'm sorry i'm just i'm calling nine one one which is the third button
besides you and Patrick. Wink wink. Well I'm gonna have to believe him. Yeah why not?
Okay yeah so you call Papi Chuko. I don't know why I'm hiding this from them.
Okay so I'm calling Papi Chuko now. Okay cool. Yeah the ring back tone is the
Godfather theme and he he picks up he says um and I feel like I messed up his
voice last time so I'm trying to make sure I remember how I wanted him to
sound he's a cricket I believe he was Chinese if I'm very mainland Chinese
Because if you keep saying it
Okay
Wait, wait William Johnson. Hmm. Well, it's good that you called me. What's what's going on my friend? What's up, man?
Okay, yeah going
You just are you just checking in or I mean, you know, I try to do a little small talk up top
I'm doing okay. I'm just enjoying my can I but can I sell you some drugs?
What do you mean explain to me all right, I have this stuff right it's super high potency
Excuse me, I'm on the phone.
Well, while he's on the phone, I turn to Patrick Yoda and I'm like,
"Look at this guy's hustle, dude. He's trying to sell drugs to 911."
[laughter]
And I just give, like, a sly thumbs-up to them, like, I'm really working on it.
So I have these two beakers of highly potent techno-slime.
Where did you find those?
uh... room
payrolls role deception
uh... right i mean
uh... but i guess i think i have to help us
that's not just a lie okay fine and i wrote a little bit
not yet i'm gonna let the big room
k you're
pushing it so we can't always a factory it was a few men and sort of weird
I don't really remember. That was over three weeks ago. It was some sort of factory.
But in game, of course, it was...
It was minutes ago.
Yeah, right? Something like that.
So, do you tell him that it's a factory?
Yeah, yeah. It was in a factory.
Sorry, wait. I'm actually rethinking this. Bye.
Okay. Okay, cool. Yeah, so you hang up on him.
I realize that maybe he's not the guy to be giving that information to.
Yeah, what do you look at?
Nah, well, you know what? That was my attempt.
How about you guys give it a shot?
Okay, I'm writing that down.
Your action happened.
Oh my god, I fucked the whole thing up.
Why? Can you just ask us first?
I have an idea.
This is why we give you the jitterbug, okay?
This is why you're not allowed to call people.
That's why you can only speed dial people.
Now I have a great idea. Now, can I borrow your phone, Blotas? I lost mine in the river
when I was swimming.
When were you swimming?
I'm not Blotas.
I'm sorry.
When were you swimming? Why did you go swimming?
I, well, as you know, the shower in my home is broken, so I decided...
I did not know that.
I did not know you had a home. I thought you just slept on your hoverboard.
the
fifth
I'll admit that I have a plan.
You went all the way to Planet Fitness to take a shower?
Yeah, I had to go.
Look, I have the membership.
Are you okay, Yona?
You okay? You have to stop smoking.
I've smoked so much K2.
I don't think I should give him my phone.
I think, hold on.
Once I get past the shower story, I'll tell you what I'm gonna do.
So, I have the membership to Planet Fitness so that I can use my, I don't have to, I can live
remotely like I do.
Anyway, can I see your phone? I'm gonna call Papi Chico back and tell him to disregard everything that he just said.
I don't I'm gonna say no on that one pal. Why I think we should just leave him alone
No
Why don't you go buy a new phone and call him then if you want to so bad?
Well, it's in the river. Why do you go use the phone and I just said I knew one
I bet you want to ask him out. Yeah
I bet you want to ask him on a date. Yeah, you know what? I ask him on a date
You just want to ask him if you can come over and do things to him
No without even the date par for yeah, you want to take a shower with Bobby Juco?
No, I don't I just wanna I just want to talk
Well, anyway I was swimming in the river because
Shower
So you're regaling them with?
Absolutely fucking insane shower river story and
You guys hear some like flap flap flap flap like a froggy foot foot feets sort of slapping on the stairs
I turn around and shoot him
Solve here could be anything solving the frog is sort of flapping down the stairs and he's like, sorry fellas
It's getting hot in the car
Do you mind just being in the car at least I want to park illegally
Okay, listen Sullivan. We came up with a plan
Basically, what we're gonna do is we're gonna sell Patrick Yoda and keep her into human traffickers for a hundred million dollars
No, and then we're gonna steal him
Finish making that no, so if you could
Trafficking ring or Yoda traveling ring, I guess would be more of an apt turn of phrase. But yeah, that's our plan
- So, uh, take us there. - That was not the plan.
- Right now. No. - I guess I could start looking into...
- Don't look into it! - (laughs)
- Don't look into it at all! - Okay, he doesn't seem to agree on...
- I'm just a... Look, I just wanted to help you guys. - He's joking around.
- I'm not joking around. - Hey, hey, Patrick Yoda, come here.
- He's the one joking. - Patrick Yoda, come here.
- What's up? - Come here real quick.
Do you see... Is there a weird bug in the bottom of this giant butterfly net?
- (laughs) - No, there isn't.
The I don't know I think there is I think you need to get closer. There's not one but look are you sure?
Oh, I see it. It's oh my god
That there is it. Oh, it's oh, it's it's beatboxing
You won't miss it I can see right through it
No, but it's a there's a very small. It's an invisible bug unless you're looking in the net or something
There's no such thing as an invisible bug. It's the future. There's such a
This net the inside of the net smells very cool
Nope how does smell this net? How does it how does it smell like a thousand dollars? It's indescribable
I'm not going in there. Which one?
Not going in there. Is it a thousand dollars or it describes it?
I could not describe it, but I guess you kind of nailed hit the nail on the head with a thousand
Yeah, I guess I would have never been able to describe that. Okay, that doesn't sound so pleasant like that's a sounds
Well, it's not really for you. It's more for Patrick Yoda.
Well, I hate that smell! I hate that smell!
While everyone's distracted, I grab Patrick Yoda and I put him in a headlock.
Okay, do a contested strength check for both of you.
Both of you guys roll strength checks.
Me and Cameron?
I got a 19.
Goddamn.
I got a 1.
Goddamn, you get him in the headlock so easily.
Okay, this is not fair!
Put the net over him.
No!
Here, get in the net.
I'm not gonna be sold into human trafficking.
We're gonna get you right back, right after.
Yeah, don't worry about it.
Like a week after.
This sucks, I hate this.
You're already in the net, there's nothing I can do anymore.
I don't know how to get you out.
It's out of our hands now.
Okay, do you want to try to resist being in the net?
Yes.
Okay, roll a I guess roll I'm trying to think I guess roll
strength again because
the history
You know something about nets, yeah
You're trying to keep him in the net then it's contested again. Yeah, I'm definitely trying to keep him in the net. Okay. Oh
Okay, give your baby you got 17 17 fuck me. All right. Um, don't worry. I got this don't trip
I'm not tripping. Don't trip. Oh my god
Even okay. Wait, let's see. Then at this point. We have to just look at your Caleb as the higher bonus on the roll at least
Oh
Yeah, he does. So he does win. That is kind of how yes. No
So you, you, you, Patrick you and you, you give your best, you guys are like locking hands
like the fuck.
Real life Patrick is so upset.
I can see he looks so sad.
I don't want to be assaulted to human trafficking.
You're gonna be, it's happening.
Hey well I didn't want my character to almost die last session dude, this is how D&D works
alright?
That wasn't our fault, that was your fault.
Maybe you should leave Everett Street.
It was absolutely, it was your fault for running away instead of standing in front of me.
So do you guys, do you guys carry him like to the car?
Yeah, we're carrying them across the street to the human traffic outlet.
[laughter]
You guys carry them too.
Yeah, which the humans are us.
[laughter]
To Sullivan's car, at least.
You guys dump him in there, in the net.
And Sullivan's like,
"I don't know if I can actually..."
"Shut up and drive, frog!"
[laughter]
"I don't think I feel comfortable trafficking this Yoda."
"I use my prayer."
Use my prayer to
Pray that the car crashes
So so at this point
Solvent solvent sort of says he goes. Okay. Well while we're in here, I do have some stuff for you guys
Look, I didn't have a lot of time to look over the place that mommy
Good make sent me to but I did manage to drop some diagrams in case you're interested in
Break it in and figuring out where Sean is it's all of in
Buddy, are you blind?
About Sean and I just want to get out of the we are we put them in a net
Yeah, it'll be all mad if we take him out now we gotta go we gotta go
It'll just be like we like stuff will be awkward if we
If we go through with the plan, you don't you don't know how you'll feel about something until it happens
From Pete Holmes
Just try it it's not gonna be that bad we'll get you right out max max a year
You guys are hell-bent on this plan I could take you to my cousin
who might know a way to sort of... I don't really know what the goal is to traffic...
We sell... what do you mean? We want money.
Okay, here, let me lay the plan out for you, Sullivan, alright?
How much money do we need? A hundred thousand dollars? Right?
Ten mil... I think it's ten million.
Ten million?
Something like that, yeah.
So we go to the human traffickers...
We show them this really fine specimen of a Yoda, right?
Aren't you the last of your kind, Botas?
That's a great point first. We have to get him in shape
Blow toss is the last of his kind wouldn't he be more of a rare specimen shouldn't we sell him shut up?
You're already in the net dude come on come in
You couldn't get out of the net if you tried you already tried it didn't work
I'm looking at my I'm looking at my phone right now. I'm looking at that. You don't have a phone and you lost
This is why we're selling you because you're a liar. I found a phone in the trunk you are going
I don't use I am selling you as soon as possible. No, okay, so all right
I'm just gonna start asking people I get out of the car first pedestrian. Do you want to buy a guy?
What kind of guy
He's green. Yeah small green
Yeah, sure. I'll take a look. Okay. Well here he is. I bring the the net
See how he does he's a feisty one
You do really well in an underground Yoda fighting ring if you're into that sort of point
Underground Yoda fighting ring. Yeah, he's sort of a he's like bleeding a bit from his finger. I bite the other finger
Yeah!
See, he's one of the feistiest yodas around.
You can tell that he's just ready to breed.
Okay, well, uh, look.
Ten million dollars!
Take it or leave it!
I unload, I pull the needler out of my back pocket and I unload half of the spikes into
the guy.
Okay, roll an attack roll on this guy.
We really should have taken his gun.
Yeah.
That was a huge overshot.
Do I roll?
So just go to your, go to your, hit Needler.
Oh yeah.
In your, yeah.
Eight damage.
Yeah, unfortunately his AC is a little higher, but now you just pull out a gun and just shoot
it at this guy and he's like, "Oh God!"
And he like sort of swiftly dodges like, "Ah, ah, ah, ah, look boys, look, it's a fine offer,
but this Yoda's too much for me."
And he...
Twenty million dollars.
You're gonna give me 20 million dollars to take this Yoda?
You can buy it for 30 million dollars.
We will give you 20 million dollars to take this Yoda.
Hold on. Hold on. Are you gonna give me 20 million dollars?
Yes.
Okay. Let's see it.
I'm gonna have to... I'll have to write you a...
He hits him. He hits him. Yeah, I mean, how do you kill him?
Patrick rolled another Needler attack.
How do you kill him? He's a pedestrian.
We were this close!
I shoot him straight in the head, two needles go through his eyes.
And then I go and I reach into his wallet and I pull out 20 million dollars.
He didn't have 20.
He couldn't even pull out the tab.
I pull out a thumb drive that has 20 million on a USB stick and I turn to Caleb and I say
uh...
We don't have 20, come on.
Batches, you gotta jump in here.
He was lying to us.
No, yeah, he doesn't have 20 million dollars.
I mean I can tell you that.
Okay, he's got 20 bucks.
Yeah, he does have $20.
Okay, now we just have to do that a million more times and we're good.
No, that's a start.
Uh, yeah.
And yeah, so you, you do that and you shoot him and, uh, you get the 20,
$20 out of it and, uh, uh, uh, Sullivan, the frog's like, Oh God.
And he sort of, uh, takes the body and shoves it in the trunk of his, uh,
Ryan Dunn car.
All right.
We got to get rid of this guy.
Uh, eat him.
- Professor Sullivan, try and eat the body.
- Yeah, eat the whole body.
I wanna know what you're doing.
- Come on.
- That's it, I'm making an executive decision.
We're going to my cousin, John Carlos' place.
You don't know what to do with this.
- All right, let's go.
John Carlos, the bullfrog.
- Maybe.
- And so yeah, he drives you guys.
He's in a frantic.
He's frantic, in a panic.
He drives you guys down to the slums of Gun City.
- And while he's driving, I turn to him and I say,
"Don't worry, I got this."
And I pick up the body out of the truck
and I pop the trunk open.
I throw it out. - So you're in the car.
- I'm in the trunk still with the body.
- You're in the trunk.
(laughing)
- And I look, I assess the situation of us
with a dead body in the car and going to see a guy.
And I say to Blotas,
hey man, have you ever seen Pulp Fiction?
(laughing)
Kind of reminds me of Pulp Fiction.
Hope Giancarlo doesn't drop the N-word.
- I throw the body.
- He won't, you don't have to worry about that.
He won't do that. - I open the--
- I'm worried.
Okay, well you shouldn't be.
I'm in the trunk, I pull that little, that glow in the dark thing
out on the trunk, and then I just toss the body out on the highway.
Okay, roll sleight of hand, see if Solomon notices.
Whoa, Matt won.
Yeah, you just like, get the body, you try to get the body out of the car,
and it's just like, it's just, you're like too little, so it's like, it's just the guy's legs
are just like dragging like flinging back and kicking up
sparks on the road. Yeah. And you guys drive up to uh uh this
like sort of like rundown apartment in Guns Titty which
is the slums of Gun City and and uh um sort of rundown apartment
complex. You see uh you see uh uh uh some chain smoking uh uh
amphibian outside
Uh, and and she she's like, uh, uh,
She's just sort of like just hanging out out there
She doesn't really care and uh sullivan sort of gets out of the car and says come on
We gotta go see john carlo. You know, hi doris. Hi. How you doing? Sullivan?
This woman's chain smoking and he sort of sullivan's just already running up the stairs to see his cousin. Um
So yeah, beautiful
I say that to delores
Name's Doris.
You got it?
Don't always say that to Doris.
You got any Techno Slime?
Alright, Techno Slime, well, bitch, do you have ten million dollars?
Nah, fuck off.
Alright.
I've seen- I've fucked demons before.
Yeah?
Your dicks are stinky.
You look like you have a little demon in you.
I do, and it's called...
Yeah, do you want one?
...addiction.
[laughter]
uh... so yeah you guys right upstairs instead of completing an interaction
and uh... you see uh...
uh... the sort of bulky
looking at
uh... guy
he's playing uh...
displaying halo combat of all the next box
and uh...
he has an eye patch is bulky looking bullfrog
he's wearing a uh... a uh... wife beater or a hate and assure
and uh...
he has the same when you get to know pan style situation and solvent does
and solvents are the out there like uh... i don't know what to do it and i
think that's a part of it and then and then they shot him in the head with me
lord
he's like is a calm down calm down
andy's what he's got a school you guys
and you see just sort of a he takes out of the t_v_ smoking a j_d_ just sort of
uh... he puts it on a window sill
he says i see guys up
and worse i've learned that c_e_o_
I force push the joint out of the window sill.
What the hell man?
Do you want to buy him?
Not after that, I want to put him down.
I force pull the joint back up.
Would you pay us money to let you kill him?
That's right.
That was a cool trick right?
I'm pretty cool looking now huh?
Look, we need to find a way to either get into the Matrix 2 or figure out where somebody
is in there.
I see. The Matrix too.
We also have to sell our friend.
Yeah.
And his dead body.
Do you know any really fucked up human traffickers? Like really depraved people?
Wait, hold on. How much for a dead body?
How much for a dead body? Zero.
How much? No.
Come on, but really.
You have to know some creeps.
No money.
But what about...
I know plenty of creeps.
What about a...
Why do you mean I have to know some creeps?
'Cause you're the guy that knows the people.
- What, okay, what about how much for a dead body
and also two rounds of needle or ammo?
- There we go.
- Included with the dead body.
- And I just found a rubber band in my pocket.
How about I sweeten the deal with a rubber band?
- Hold on. - Tell us.
- Hold on here. - What are you trying to do?
What do you need all that money for?
- Okay, all right.
- I have another item for sale.
*laughter*
What? Wait, hold on, let's hear him out.
What do you have?
He's still in the net.
I've taken one of my Super Mario Sunshine
stickers and I've put it on the eyes
of this dead body
to cover up the needlers.
The needlers ammo. Now what do you think?
I think...
I don't have a lot
of thoughts on this. It's just pretty
alarming. You don't know any
You don't know any greeks who would have
sex with a dead body that we could sell this to?
John Carlos, John Carlos.
Don't doubt how many creeps I know.
Listen, you don't know any rich creeps?
John Carlos, John Carlos.
We're gonna give you the dead body, okay?
And we're gonna give you 10 million dollars.
Alright? And then you're gonna give us 20 million dollars.
And you get to keep the dead body.
That's a pretty good deal.
I hate that deal.
I'm taking my stickers back.
What do you guys need the money for so why'd you bring these guys more stickers?
We need it. We need to restart the matrix -
Yeah, twiddling our thumbs looking down. Yeah, we we have to we have to get in the matrix to do
Michelle we
Need we need to we got a restarted machine. We do a lemonade stand outside your house. I
Mean knock yourself out
But if you're just trying to get into the matrix to that I can maybe help you with
As far as the dead body goes hold on one second and he takes it and he sort of like heaves it and you realize that
Next to his Xbox. It's just a giant incinerator
All right, I like you did I get my stickers back
You see that there's a little like a receptacle on top of the the incinerator that where the stickers were deposited
And and before you take the stickers he puts his hand over it not so fast though
now I
Just did something for you. And now you're also asking me to take you to the matrix - you I mean you
It wasn't that big of a deal. You already had the incinerator. Oh, yeah, you didn't ask us
this
Say in numbers.
No, no, our president's electricity control bill.
Our president's electricity control bill?
What the fuck are you talking about?
It's like rent control.
Look--
All electricity in the city has to be--
Wait, guys.
--controlled by us.
I just thought of how we can make the money in no time.
How much money?
$10 million.
All we have to do is buy--
I thought we needed $20 million.
All we have to do is we gotta buy three microphones
and an audio recorder, okay?
And in a month's time, we're gonna be making the big bucks.
- That's a great idea.
- If you guys want to get into the Matrix 2,
I'd be happy to help you out with that
and put you in touch with the Mad Suckler.
Now, look, I can't be asking him for too many favors
or else he'll stop, you know.
Yeah, it's just a tenuous relationship.
He's a stop suckling.
Well, now, at least on my stop suckling you.
That's you got. Yeah. Look.
Look, what I need from you guys, though, if you have,
I'm going to put you in touch with him is I'm going to need
some of that new techno slime truck,
the red eye stuff.
How much?
Oh wait, is that different?
10 million dollars or nothing!
Wait, wait, is that different from, uh, is that the unrefined stuff or is that the cowboy
bebop one that I have?
It's a bebop one that you have.
Okay.
Alright.
So do you have it?
I do have it.
Um, wait, what, he said he's gonna take us to the Mad Suckla if...
If you guys, if you give me enough.
How much is enough?
I mean about five tubes of that stuff. Yeah, we got five tubes right here.
That is one tube. I think your eyes are crossed. You're seeing
single. He puts on his glasses.
He puts on his glasses. Okay, now I'm seeing two of them, but I'm pretty sure there was
one. He takes off his glasses. Yeah, there's one.
I gotta get new glasses. There's five here. Hey, Patrick Yoda, Ray
William Johnson. There's five, right? Yeah, I'm counting five.
yeah i think you're i think you might just have to be having a problem with
your vision hold on fellas we do know at least one
person who had more than one yeah me i have five yeah it's blowtoss he
has five he's got five look i see it right now guys it's just
okay guys you can't just will reality who's talking here is it patches or is
it sullivan hard to tell i oh no sullivan's having
another one of his psychotic breaks. You can't trust this guy. There's five tubes here. There's five tubes.
Don't think about it too much. There's only five tubes. There's only five.
Go with your gut. That's what Mr. Wonderful says.
Well, my gut's telling me that that's not enough. Okay, how about this? One tube or you say one,
we say five it doesn't matter however many tubes that is
but then how about this that's cool
that's cool caleb you say one i'll say five okay yeah go on
two and then two tubes of this other weird thing that i have no
just give them one just give them one just one we only have one of that you're
mixing up numbers again. No, I have two. I have two of the
weirds. No, you have the I have two unrefined thingies of
techno slime. No, we only have one. Wink, wink, wink, wink,
wink, wink, wink. Okay, I'm gonna need to goddamn. What do
you even have to **** roll? I guess deception just to see if
you can like he's a little disoriented by this. So, like,
roll just the straight deception this is the this is the verbal equivalent of
that scene from now you see me this is just becoming an episode of Ed Ed and
Eddie yeah I got a 15 for deception yeah okay he hasn't picked up on it that he
has one he has two so so proceed proceed so I have two of these things and now we
gotta say really some really crazy shit so do you pull it do you pull it out do
you show it to him? Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Look at these. Yeah. You
show him the raw uh techno slime and it's uh it's prismatic
swirls inside of these uh tubes and uh his eyes glow. He's like,
oh and he tries to he tries to mask it but you guys can tell
that he was pretty excited by that and he's like, okay, He's
thinking about it.
Cool.
If you give me both of those, I'll take you to the mad suckler.
You idiot.
I don't, I mean, I don't.
No, we gotta save one.
What if we give you one?
Yeah, we only have one.
I'm sorry, your eyes are all messed up again.
I think you're seeing double.
Your eyes are all messed up again.
You must have put your glasses back on.
Look, you tried to trick me one time, and I admit, pretty good trick.
And it worked.
And now I'm trying again.
You are wearing a monocle.
No, I'm not.
I'm wearing an eye patch.
I mean, if we give you...
You only have one eye.
Nobody's ever told you.
You are a Cyclops.
You have one eye.
So I point to the...
I point to the...
Not Cyclops.
I point to the eye tube stuff...
Do not call me Cyclops!
And I point to the eye tube stuff and the two unrefined ones and I'm like, "Look, this
is an incredible value, okay?
We're giving you six tubes of Techno Slime."
I don't see why you need to ask for 12 or whatever it is you're saying right now.
I have told you what I'm asking.
Quick sidebar.
With both John and Patrick.
Okay.
Yeah.
Sure, yeah.
You guys walk a few feet over to huddle.
Why do we need to keep two of these things?
Sullivan's apologizing to Conroe meanwhile.
This stuff is super heavy.
I'm getting tired lugging it around.
I don't really care.
I probably know Papi Chuco made that stuff and I'm not convinced he's uh...
entirely truthful. I think we should hold on to it as evidence uh... and
in just in case. You never know.
You know somebody might ask, somebody might say hey
I heard Papi Chuco's making that crazy stuff and then we don't have any
evidence to prove it.
What have we been talking about?
Here, this is what we're gonna ask him, right? I still have that backpack full of snacks
from the first episode of the arc okay I'm sorry I had my headphones in I still
have this Santa clip that I've been listening to an audiobook on. Can we
start this conversation over again? What happened Pat? Did you just zone out?
Yeah, Patrick was watching videos again.
I wasn't zoning out or anything, I just thought this would be funny.
[Laughter]
I thought this was your sly way of saying that you just have not been paying attention at all.
I thought I was... I laughed.
No, we can't restart.
Alright, well...
If we pool our quarters, how many quarters do we have?
We can give him some quarters.
I have 10.
I got 12.
a clip alright this thing is valued at three million dollars it's very rare
it's three million I think I I think I got an idea
listen Giancarlo we turn around we rejoin the the menu yeah what do you want
what about one thingy of the good thingy stuff another thingy of the other kind
of thing and then an mp3 player. Oh no come on it doesn't just play mp3s it plays flac
files too. That is valued at over 3 million dollars. Okay. By this guy in this net. Okay.
Roll persuasion. Roll persuasion? You guys it's like what Neil Young was trying to do
with the Pono except it actually worked it has a great it's a better flat
format.
Alright.
21.
Okay.
Yeah, John Carlos says, "Alright.
Fine.
I'll take it."
Let's go! I mean, of course you will.
What?!
Alright.
I'm not even done.
I'm not even done my David Icke
- I'm gonna get a audio book.
(laughing)
- All right, I take, I reach into the net
and I grab the mp3 player.
- Patrick Yoda suddenly vanishes from the apartment.
(laughing)
- I take the mp3 player, I grab the techno slime
from Blow Toss, I grab my own refined techno slime
and I, and I, I.
Yeah, handed over to Giancarlo. Yeah, transactions made. He's he's like counting it like it's money even though it's like three
Three distinct objects different shapes and weights. Um, he says, all right
Thanks boys
Meet me here again tonight
10 p.m. Are you serious? You're not oh my god. We gotta wait of the stuff back
Yeah, hold on. I'm let me finish. I can't just the suckler isn't just always around
And he's in a twist pal
These are not panties. Okay, these are I'm I see pan I see a panty line not with this it no
I see a line under in your dress. I see lace. I see lace coming out. I have a Winnie the Pooh style situation
Why'd you get a panty tattoo then
and
look we all have to do what we have to do
by
i don't want to hear it
come back here tonight
and i will take you to the man suckler
fine
solvent get these
joke is any okay thank you john carlisle whatever
and uh... solvents are lead you guys out
leads you back downstairs into the car.
- Can I get my stickers back?
- Oh yeah, sure.
He throws them out the window to you.
(laughing)
- Awesome!
- Yeah.
- No, the wind picked up!
We gotta get my stickers.
- Yeah, the stickers fly a little bit away,
across the street.
And--
- I cause like a six car pileup.
- Yeah, you do that.
- I cause a six car pileup. - Yeah, that happens.
And but I get my sticker.
OK, yeah. You cause a six car like a beginning of Final Destination.
Yeah, final destination.
Except Patrick just lives every time everyone else around him dies.
Cool. Yeah. So you guys are back
in the Sullivan Mobile.
We just got to wait till 10.
Oh, yeah. So let's go hang out, too.
Yeah, so this can do.
Let's have a boys day out.
Well, you know what?
We've been so focused on solving this mystery.
Yeah, especially this session.
Yeah.
Ignoring that dig from the from patches.
We've been so focused on this mystery
that we haven't focused on our friendship.
Yeah, we need to do some serious work to get Patrick Yoda
to trust us again after we tried to sell him to human traffickers.
"Hey Patrick, do you wanna go hang out in that restaurant?"
And I point across the street to a storefront that has, um, it has a cardboard sign that says "Restaurant"
that's kinda like hanging askew a little bit, and you can see underneath it, it says "Human Trafficking Hub"
*laughter*
"Ooooh, that one's good!"
"I heard they have really delicious pizza!"
"I'm- I'm gonna roll Perception to see if I-"
*laughter*
"Do it!"
A 10? Yeah, you can kind of tell.
I see the word. It's a new restaurant.
You can tell it's not a great restaurant. Like, you might not want to eat there.
I wouldn't like to eat there. Well, they have the craziest secret menu.
They have those smiley face french fries. I hate those.
- let's go laugh at them
Well gee I don't know
Come on
Just like we used to we can write a hilarious one-star Yelp review
We can go make fun of those french fries and how bad all the food is
And I was stupid that's I come on that signs not fooling anybody everybody knows this restaurant suck come on Patrick
What is the sign say why why is the sign bad because it's made of cardboard? Oh?
See this is God come on. This would be like as a gag like like let's go to the air. We'll make a video
Yeah, we'll make a documentary video that about
Yeah about you eating at the worst restaurant in the world
We'll add some cool sound effects and stuff. Yeah
Right. Hmm. What do you say buddy? Well
Gee I don't know I
Mean can we
There that has a play place, but we know that Burger King is good like this place, you know, it'll be funny
It's like a bad movie. That's it's like so bad. It's good exactly
But does it have a play place is the problem? I'm pretty sure it does. Yeah, actually I'm looking at Yelp right now
Yeah, does it have a play place? I pull out my Junebug
I pull out my Junebug with no screen and I look at well
I mean, yeah, the Yelp reviews all say it's like the worst restaurant, but the best play place
Well, I'm not going into the restaurant. Can we go into the side door that says play place?
Yeah, let's go into the back door. Actually, let's go knock on the back door. That's a better idea for sure
Yeah, you guys go into the back door of this restaurant slash human trafficking. He's the net comfy for you Patrick
It's not comfortable
Okay, so we walk in this yeah, I was so I walk up to the kids at a counter. Yeah, there's a counter
there's a woman there she looks like the
The woman in Monsters Inc. There's like the secretary. Yeah
Yeah, she looks just like her. Yeah, I say just how much how much for a I and I wink green meal
small size
Yeah, she she she
She like leans over and looks to Patrick Yoda up and down
and she says
17 tokens
You see
Patrick has rolled a needler in the chat silently
Okay. Yeah, I
Jump in front of it to save this woman's life. Okay a few things to resolve here
Okay, are you shooting the needler? Yeah. All right, we're gonna roll for initiative in that case
Because these are human traffickers
And so they can fight
Okay, let's do it everyone roll for initiative I
Don't want to fight them. I'm gonna smell Patrick. I'm on their side. Okay
I'll roll initiative. I'll defend my friend Patrick.
I don't know why you guys thought he'd be worth 10 million dollars.
I mean he's cool, it's because we love him. He's cool as hell.
He's worth 10 million dollars to us.
Exactly Patrick, that should make you feel really good.
He's so upset.
You can't needler me in real life Patrick.
You don't hurt me when you press that button. Not yet.
You can't- 22 actually might- that might hurt me.
That might hurt him.
Wait, roll for initiative, Pat.
He did, he got a 7.
No, no, the first time he got a 7.
No, I got a 21.
Also, he's in a net.
No, you didn't.
I got a 21.
He got a 7 and he's in a fucking net, dude.
He's dead.
No, I got a 21.
Because I didn't notice, I'm gonna give him a-
What?
Alright, that's the new rule.
If you can roll something and re-roll it before Pat just notices, you get the second roll.
Fuck off.
Alright, let me make some notes on this battle.
God damn.
We're killing time.
We have until 10 o'clock.
Yeah, might as well kill an entire store full of human traffickers.
I mean we're doing a good thing.
Yeah, we're doing the world a favor.
This was our plan all along, Patrick.
We're ridding the world of this scum.
You win with it perfectly, buddy.
Patrick still thinks it's a restaurant.
This restaurant has the worst service of all time.
You shot at them.
All right, let me roll for initiative for all of them.
All of them?
How many?
Oh, no.
So there are four people there.
There's a secretary.
Then there's one of the beefy guards there who looks exactly like Ken Bone.
And then there is two other guys and they also both look like Ken Bone.
They're triplets.
They're triplet human triplets.
Oh no, the Bone Brothers.
Yeah, it's yeah, they're the Bone Brothers, they're famous.
Direct descendant of Ken Bone.
Yeah, who became a despot in the mid-21st century.
Yeah, he became an infamous white rapper in Brooklyn.
And White Bone is a white rapper.
Yeah, Ken Bone, but like the E and the and the E's in Bone and Ken are dollar signs for
some reason.
It's going to put it somewhere.
It's a euro.
One of them's a euro.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
One of them, he got it right.
Yeah.
Okay, cool.
So Patrick Yoda, actually, that was your turn first.
Okay, that role I missed.
So I'll give you I'll give you like a little layout.
I'm gonna use a samurai, the samurai pack.
Whoa, we got a whole crew smoking samurai pack.
Okay, these are, these are Ken bones.
So they were.
So Ken bone, human traffics and that's real?
Yeah, no.
Ken bone in my fictional world, human traffics.
So Ken bone is a real human trafficker.
No, that's not what I'm saying.
Nope.
And here's the geisha for the secretary.
She's beautiful.
I can't fight her.
Yeah.
Uh, great.
Yeah, this actually, this, this fucking rectangle is perfect for the area.
So okay.
So yeah, Patrick Yoda, you actually did, uh, shoot at her first.
And what did you roll for that shot?
The first shot?
13.
Yeah.
Okay.
No, no, no.
Wait.
Uh, 12.
shoot at her with the needler and she's sort of using her geisha secretary
technique very easily like dodges it and sort of repositions herself but you're
gonna get to go again because you roll first initiative. Is he still in the net?
Does he have to get out of the net? If he's in the net then yeah he needs to
use at least half his just just to use half his movement to get out of it.
That's right. Well can I wait can I do stuff from the net still? Yeah I guess
- Yes, you can.
Yeah, you can technically do stuff from the net, for sure.
- There's holes in the net, if it's a butterfly net.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah, if you wanna do stuff from the net,
you definitely can.
- Okay, so my needler,
well, obviously a needler through a butterfly net
is gonna burn a hole.
- Yeah.
- So I just stick my arm out of the butterfly net
with the needler, and I'm just sitting in the net
with just the needler out of the butterfly net.
Okay, yeah, so what do you shoot at that?
What does Needler explosion do?
I would guess it's an explosion.
Yeah, Needler explosion happens just like with the real Needler
where if you attack somebody twice in a row on a turn with the Needler,
so on one turn of the next turn, then you're going to be able to cause additional damage
and each consecutive time you do it you cause that additional damage.
Okay.
So I'm gonna do, I'm gonna do Needler explosion.
How many people does it hit at once?
- So first you have to, you have to shoot someone
with a Needler first, because like,
without doing, already getting a Needler bullet in them.
- Oh, so did I hit the Geisha at all or?
- No, you didn't, you didn't, she dodged it.
- Okay. - So.
- So I'm gonna hit the guy to the right with the Needler.
- Okay, go for it.
- Yeah, that's a hit. - 18.
hit hit the needler in the chat nice 16 damage holy god Patrick's overpowered
we were really we were willing to sell this guy yeah you so you turn the guy in
the right you uh you sort of like scramble in the net and just like find
your footing and shoot it at him and one of the camp bones is like like he just
like got shot right in the chest stumbles back it's up against the wall
and he's sort of like wobbling he's like toss up a little bit of blood you got
I'm really fucking good. Uh, uh, yeah, he's, he's, he's looking
pretty fucked up.
I call him a bitch and it does more damage.
Okay. Uh, no, you don't have to accept that.
I, you know, I wasn't. So, uh, it is now, uh, it is now, um, uh,
cam. Oh no, it's not. It's actually a, uh, this Ken bones
turn over here. Yeah, no, sorry. Yeah. So this Ken bone is going
to run over and he's gonna try to hit you Patrick Yoda because of what you just
did. He's pretty pissed. He's gonna miss. He's like that's my brother!
What does Ken Bone sound like? That's my brother! That's my brother! Hey man! Hey I
what did he do on reddit? He just did some creepy shit. He just like something
racist. I love pregnant women. They look like beautiful submarines. What did he say?
that he said. Pregnant women look like lovely submarines. He's right. He is right. He's
correct. Why we persecute him? Okay yeah so uh so yeah he has a giant baton. He's a guard
and he's gonna start to swing it at you. So let's see how he does. Okay yeah I think your
a
head with the baton. He says, "That's for hitting my brother!"
Shut up, bitch!
Okay, and now it is Cameron, it's Bluetoss' turn.
Okay.
Cameron, get that fucking Ken Bone away from me.
I'm going to, I'm a good friend, unlike you.
No, I'm a good friend.
That's not something you would do.
We're trying to sell you to figure out the whole, we'll talk about this later.
I'm gonna I'm going to attack the the Ken bone that's attacking Patrick with my
Lead pipes let me yeah, let me roll that
That is oh I have advantage on by accident sorry, so that's a 20 yes, it's the first one yeah, that hits okay cool
roll for damage
nice 16
No, yeah Patrick rolled something. I don't know what the fuck
16 yeah, yeah Patrick Yoda sort of giving you moral support. Yeah. Yeah get him. Yeah, like just like from the net and my
Yeah
Thought somebody else was in the call I was like nobody's dubbing over Patrick video terrifying
My moral support does so well I
Tell Cameron
That I'm sorry, I apologize finally for running away that one time
whoa
While you're about to hit
Okay, my and my apology gives you strength cool. So yeah, I rolled 16 damage
Okay. Yeah, you did 16 - you uh
You beat the yeah you beat the shit out of him you just like whap him on this fucking fat belly sides
I mean just bop him on the head.
That's right.
He's seeing fucking birds.
He's like spinning and he's like, "D'oh!"
He's like in pain for real.
And yeah, I mean, what else do you want to do?
Yeah, yeah.
So then I say, then I turn to Patrick and I say, "Hey, Patrick."
What?
No, not you.
And I unzip my pocket and I let my pet monkey named Patrick out.
I use my my sickum ability to sick the the monkey I throw Patrick the monkey
across the room onto the the Ken bone that's standing far away in the doorway
nice yeah yeah what is it my monkey grabs on to an enemy's face or face
equivalent blinding them and dealing damage until they can shake the monkey
off enemy needs to beat DC 12 decks at the end of their turn okay right so yeah
So throw him and then he needs to beat the DC. So let me and that cost you techno slime points
So I'm deducting that. Yeah, I don't think the Ken bones Dex's are very good. So
Yeah, yeah, so you throw the monkey at him and you get it on his face. Yes
so yeah, it's like and he's like just jumps on his face and like starts clawing at him and
Roll for roll 1d 6 for damage. Okay
For your monkey eyes
six baby yeah uh describe how your monkey kills this kind of what because he
already had a shit ton of damage done to him from Patrick Yoda wait really I was
doing it at the other one the one that didn't have oh this one but hey you know
what I'll take the kill okay yeah this guy I'm sorry yeah kill this guy the
monkey so Patrick the monkey rips off Ken bones face yeah and then he rips off
the muscle and then he rips off the meat and then he it's just the skull yeah
right and then he starts playing bongos like Donkey Kong on the skull okay yeah
everyone asses hell everyone feels awful yeah I vomit yeah I pull the net over my
eyes I like do like a double layer so I don't have to see the whole thing I
I close my eyes under it amazing. It is now
Cameron Cameron, but it is now Caleb's turn. I punched the girl in the stomach
So you just do it unarmed attack you say an old-school punch it right now. Yeah roll a
Roll, uh, this is gonna not be as ideal for you because it's a strength. I'm making a point
Yeah, do it. Yeah, good good point roll. It's roll a straight
Strength so just just roll d20. Okay
Just a d20 or do I click strength? If you click strength, you'll get the same result. So
- - yeah - yes
You like describe how you fuck this up
I walk up I walk up to that stupid bitch and I and I and I throw just all I have
behind a punch but then I realized I didn't walk far enough to where I was
like close to her at all and so I just kind of fall on my face. Okay yeah yeah
so you fall on your face and she just she just sort of like looks sad at you
By the way, you move up to her, obviously, to do that.
And my head is just like laying right at her feet now.
Yeah. Yeah.
And she's like she's like, kiss it.
I kiss it.
Yeah.
She like blushes.
It's just nice.
I kiss farther up her leg.
OK, yes.
I'm going to have her attack you soon.
All right.
Well, I get a couple I get a couple more kisses in before
where she gets to me.
Yeah, she uses her reaction to kick you in the skull,
dealing.
Kill me.
It's not going to be funny.
Dealing three damage.
Just like take perfect.
And she just like what?
It says the girl.
Action girl.
Yeah, it's a girl.
Sound to me.
And now it is.
We're getting some Ken Bone action
where you get double Ken Bone and the secretary.
I would love some double Ken Bone action.
We're actually only getting one Ken Bone
because the other one you fucking killed.
So this Ken Bone is going to come over here and he's like,
I have a crush on her and like try to hit you
because you're trying to kiss me.
Yeah, he's mad.
I pretend to be dead.
OK, I played that.
It doesn't work.
I just won't let you do it.
I won't let you game sucks.
OK, it does.
He's going to attack you.
Let's see.
I don't think he's going to do too hot.
Oh yeah, that absolutely hits you. OK.
Oh my God.
You guys just going to let this happen to me?
Yeah, I'm busy.
Yeah, he were rekindling our friendship over here.
Like you're like trying to like suck on her toe
And he just like fucking whaps you on the head with his elbow.
He just like sort of like fucking like just jams on your head and does like eight damage.
He pile drives me?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
I'm in love with the secretary!
And he just sort of jams his elbow in your head.
Hey, I'm using my perception to realize that that's the first time that she's heard that.
Yeah, yeah.
She's trying not to react.
It's too overwhelming.
This is a Jim and Pam thing.
Yeah.
(laughs)
- They had a Jim and Pam thing going on.
- And I'm like the cameraman.
(laughs)
From the later seasons.
- Yeah, like how the cameraman tried to suck Pam's toes.
(laughs)
- Yeah, like that.
- I remember that scene.
Yeah, now she's like, "Oh, Ken too."
(laughs)
And she tries to kick you again in the head.
See how she does.
She gets to hurt me twice, dude.
She fucks it up, though.
She's too distracted by her, like, confused emotions,
and she just whiffs,
and you just get to keep sucking on her toes.
Man, I'd like a whiff on her.
Yeah, that's good.
Come over here. Join me.
Get this kid boned.
[laughter]
It is now Patrick Yoda's turn.
Alright, um...
Yeah.
I use... how many tech... I have 13 techno sign points.
Yeah, you guys are a way... I mean, these are not...
How many, how many techno, how many techno slime point?
What does Yoda's mind do again?
Yoda's mind allows you to read people's mind.
Right.
It'd be a crazy thing to pull out right now.
It uses like most of your techno slime points.
Just kill the guy.
I was gonna use Yoda's mind to get into the head of Ken Bone 2
and then make fun of him.
Or you could shoot him with your gun that can do like 20 damage.
Hold on, I was gonna make fun of him about his love for the secretary until he kills himself.
Or you could shoot him with the gun.
Patrick, I just have to say, there's a guy right next to us right now.
You have a lot more of two options.
Which is the unfortunate thing.
I just got a notification that Patrick is playing Garry's Mod.
I just got a notification on Steam that says you are on Gary's Mod right now.
[Laughter]
Care to explain yourself?
I'm really not.
What, this isn't enough game for you, Pat?
It says Tim Allen is on Gary's Mod.
That must be a you problem, not a me problem.
All right, I just wanted to, you know.
It's not open for me.
Okay.
Alright, anyway.
So what do you think I should do?
Patrick.
Patrick Yoda.
I look deep into his eyes.
I really appreciate that you apologized to me for running away that one time.
And I'm thinking about apologizing to you for trying to sell you into slavery.
But, if you don't kill this guy right next to us right now, I won't apologize.
This is a very important question.
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to answer it.
This is a really tender emotional moment. The music swells before he answers.
Yeah, the music's swelling. Ken Bone and Secretary are both just like, "HUH!"
Like, waiting to hear what happens.
So then I use my hoverboard, and I'm gonna hit... Can I hit both the Ken Bone?
'Cause if it's like the hoverboard boomerang, I can hit all three of them, right?
Yeah, roll for attack on that.
That hits all of them. Roll for damage.
- Nice, yeah.
You whap, this one, this guy over here is dead
and you hit these two.
She's looking pretty busted.
He's looking okay.
Describe how you kill this guy.
- So I hit, so I--
- Very tender Roman.
- Through the net, I kick,
I've basically just destroyed the net at this point.
- Yes.
the
you wearing it like a leather face
and i can't be i think the hoverboard boomerang through the net and it hits
uh... that guy it kind of just stays
spinning off the guy it's a good case of
such a bad concussion that he dies in the equivalent of a car accident
and i have other to uh...
it just a it doesn't normally
Yeah, the other two ran out of ideas.
Yeah.
Yeah, the other two take some damage.
Okay, cool. Yeah, that guy's dead in front of you.
Uh, uh...
I throw up on him because I'm still not good at seeing dead bodies.
Yeah, you guys have killed two human traffickers today.
That's a good start.
Nice.
Uh, and now...
Shit.
Yeah, you killed two of them, so now it's actually, uh, Blowtoss, it's your turn.
That's right.
Um, alright, I uh...
Aaron, go give him a wedgie.
I'm sorry.
Lotus, go give that man a wedgie!
I look at Patrick and I extend hands to shake his hand and I say, "That sounds good to me."
And we shake hands.
Yeah, you shake hands.
We shake hands.
And then I run over to Ken Bone and give him a wedgie.
Absolutely, yeah, just roll it.
An atomic wedgie. I pull his underwear so far out it's gonna chop his freakin' legs off.
Yeah, roll a strength check and we'll sort of do an opposed strength. All right, I got an 11
Okay. Oh he beat you. So yeah, he is
Industrial reinforced underwear, so you try to pull it up and he's like that the fat between his legs is too. Yeah
Yeah, he's like not today Satan and he
Okay, so then I hit him in the face with my lid
That's a nine. Oh, no, it's not gonna do it. Yeah, you're like
Frustrated you start swinging. He's just suddenly like like just like fucking like it man like fucking dodging your shit
I'm here now, by the way. Yeah. Yes. Yes. That is where you would be
He's like I have the power of love on my side
And now it is your turn Caleb, I'm sorry for my suggestion of the wedgie, it's okay. That's what's friends are for friendship
Um, I I mean again, I keep it old-school. I just use that ladies face like a fucking speed bag
I'm definitely gonna hit it this time guys. Don't even worry about it. I
Mean, it's not 17 roll
roll a
D4 now, okay
Yeah
Yeah, how do you kill her?
had to help. She had she had more. She had she had about
seven seven or eight was what I was thinking because she's
pretty weak. Right and you just like kind of like just crested
it. How do you kill her? I I kip up from the ground. uh cuz I
took two years of Taekwondo and then you just start just like I
said just like on her chin just over and over and over and over
again and I'm like dodging even though she's not punching back.
Yeah, practicing right?
And then I just do one final,
just like knockout uppercut and she flies into the ceiling and it's like a drop
ceiling and she gets her head stuck in there and dangling.
Yeah, that was bad ass.
And then I started stuck in on her toes again.
Yeah. You're now like on top of her under right under her,
right under her. Just like, like a, like a hamster feeding
on her big toe.
(laughing)
- Yeah, you see the Ken Bone is like,
like so angry. - And I also moon him.
- Oh, no. - I left side to him.
- Oh, he is so mad at you. - Yeah.
- He is losing his fucking mind.
So he's gonna come over and try to hit you.
- Oh, I say, "Toro, Toro,"
and then wave my ass like a red flag.
(laughing)
And right as he almost gets me, I move out of the way.
Just oh is that what happens?
Let's find out.
Just sucking on his toe.
You're just sucking on his dead woman's toes.
- Yeah.
- Oh man.
- Run him into the wall.
- Yeah and he's gonna try to beat your ass.
See how he does.
- He will miss.
- He does miss.
He says I loved her almost as much
as I loved human trafficking.
And he tries to hit you.
and he misses though he's too angry he's crying he's got stingy tears running
down
uh... inside knows
and uh... uh...
it is now your turn patrick you know
all right so
i get i'm gonna i'm gonna do what i said i was going to do
with the yoda's mind
this is what he's one guy left
i know but i want to go out there
All right. Well, this fight is already taking like 45 minutes.
All right. You know what, then?
Hoagie surprise.
Yeah, I'm finally I'm finally out of the net.
I pulled my hoagie out.
That's what's up. I hit him with the hoagie surprise.
You do roll the damage.
The remainder of the net is just on Patrick's legs like fishnet stockings.
I start sucking on his toes instead.
They look better.
Yeah, he's so yeah, you whack him right in the skull and his head spins around.
I gotta hit him in the nuts.
You hit him in the nuts and he makes a he makes a soy face in response.
He's excited by it and uh, but he's still standing.
He looks pretty fucked up, but you guys haven't done enough damage to this guy yet.
So it's your turn, Blowtoss.
Oh no, um, we should pants him.
All right, yeah, for my first action I pants him.
Let's humiliate this guy.
Let's just humiliate him as much as possible.
I'll count pantsing as an attack action.
Yeah, so go for it.
We're kind of the bad guys now.
Roll strength.
Strength, roll strength.
He has to have really strong pants.
Let's see, he has a resistance of 22.
Oh, there we go.
Let's see how he does.
I mean, unless he crits, he probably won't do it.
Yeah, no, you whip those pants right.
Oh, yeah.
And he's going to take
the damage.
He's gonna take 1d4 psychic damage.
So he's just like so humiliated and he's watching as his dead love of his life is getting her toes sucked on and
and he's just...
[laughter]
We've done so much to this human traffickers.
He's a human trafficker, dude.
Yeah, he sells people into slavery.
It's like how people end up like working in insurance.
Like, you know, like you could just be a normal guy.
Yeah, human trafficking is just like insurance.
And more so than you would think.
Hey, hey, he's he's crying.
He's like it's so much pain.
He's like, please, please spare me.
I take his shirt off.
I pee on him.
roll
When I take his shirt off, it turns out he had one of those Iron Man type heart pacemaker
things implanted into his chest, right?
But he was so sweaty from the fight that it stuck to his shirt.
So when I take his shirt off, it just rips his heart battery right out of his chest.
It just collapses to the ground.
That's so bleak.
Oh, man.
Hey, that's what happens, dude.
Yeah, you just hear, "Boooooo!"
As he rips it out of it.
He's really upset about dying.
He's swearing up a storm.
And he's just having a seizure on the ground and then just like dies.
Yeah, and then I stand over his body and I'm like,
"That's what you get for letting us walk into your building."
And I think we'll end it there.
Yeah, so next time we'll start, you guys will...
guys will it'll be it'll be 10 p.m.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[Music]