Hi, what's up? It's Cameron. I have some big exciting news
We are doing a D&D live show on Thursday March 31st
It's in Brooklyn, New York at Union Hall
And if you are listening to this episode on the day that it comes out Monday, February 7th
Then tickets will be on sale at noon Eastern today
And if you're listening anytime after that
tickets are already on sale and you're going to want to buy a ticket to this
because it is going to be
swag as hell. I'll put a link to buy tickets in the description of this
episode and I'll also put it
on Twitter @podaboutlist
it's called
"Hopperation Frogtastic Voyage"
and Sullivan the Frog will die if you do not buy a ticket to the show
so you're gonna wanna do that and here's the episode
Well, after an auspicious start, I knew we needed to set a plan in motion in order to
get our money back, er, get their money back. After we convinced Barry Gee and Travis to
join us, we had to deal with the ICUP charity compound. But first, the team.
Blotos Pierce, teleporter extraordinaire. Patrick Yoda, mind reader and force user.
Ray William Johnson, computer guy.
Barry Gee, explosions expert and face.
Travis Asinat, muscle and deagle expert.
And me, Sullivan the Frog.
I think they told me I was the driver, but I don't, I don't, I just kind of did a lot
of stuff.
Um, anyway, the ICUP charity compound, formerly the Papi Chuko's Technoslime Addiction Treatment
and Recovery Center, was a highly secure location, even by Papi Chuko Technoslime standards.
And it seems after getting their independence from the company they maintain that security standard
multiple floors made entirely of hyper-cauterized techno slime
Staffed by elite corporate agents who still are getting paid by Papi Chuko's corporation because of a billing error and also technological security
Concentrated EMP rays to destroy rogue electronic devices biometric scans and ID checks
It's uh, it was it was gonna be a tough job
But the building was large and maintenance doesn't really have that much value behind it, so there were other access points.
Once we got the blueprints of the facility and staked it out, we just needed a few other components.
So we knew that the ICUP had a vault and in that it had donations that were represented as hard digital currency.
That's right, currency you can actually download rather than existing as a series of transactions in the unreachable quantum blockchain.
Most institutions don't do this but regulations around charities that stipulate they do everything less efficiently out of respect is an advantage for us
After about five days time however the vaults contents will be invested into the quantum crypto market
And then we won't be able to access it so we're gonna have to figure out how to do it
The way that the way that what we knew about the vault was that we needed to at the very least get credentials
So that we can as quantum crypto investors so that we can download
The files we had to get inside the vault to do that on the same network as the ICUP
And we needed to get past security including using a double golden deagle trick shot with perfectly weighted golden bullets for that
And we also needed to make sure we passed a pyometric scan that was for Fantima Von Kissyface
we also would need love slime to build a
UOAB, the uncle of all bombs, to open the vault door
So in order to do this, well first we were gonna have to get that blueprint so
I consulted the gang about what they thought we should do
Guys
All right, everyone's showing their credit cards on stream
*laughter*
anything about pulling a heist it's probably there's probably a made up of
several rooms connected in different ways probably a vault that we have to steal
from and there's probably a blueprint that shows it all and if there's
anything I know about a heist it's every step of it and I don't need any of you
and I'll go do it myself well all we have to do is go to the basement of the
charity and look for a blue piece of paper and that should give us a map of
the entire area. We need a blueprint expert. We need to recruit a blueprint expert. A brand
new character. Voiced by a new person. Let's find someone who has the thing we need and
make him give it to us. I think that's probably a very solid idea, Travis. The question is,
I mean I imagine there was probably an architect or something who designed it. Okay, him. Okay,
Yeah, okay him right now
Don't think I'm instantly call him
To the discord call. I mean the meeting I can't well look to get to that guy we I
Can't just find the architect for this maybe
We're in your Scarface mansion without you for some reason I mean, where are you where are you zooming in from?
them. Space. That tracks, yeah. You're in space. I hear you guys need an architect.
I know a guy. I know one guy. Who's that? His name is John Architect. Okay, is he the
architect of the building that we're trying to steal from or is he just an architect?
He built that building.
He built the building too.
Okay.
Well, let's... where can we find him?
At his house.
Wow.
Can you ping us a location?
I will...
C message you
his location.
Do you phone, Sullivan?
C message. Sullivan, you have a phone?
Yeah.
I need to put some parental controls on this.
No, no last time you access adult websites
Let's read his search history. Please don't
Calm adult friend finder.com
Search slash friend
Just trying to spread out the you don't know what a lot of people need friends. Maybe maybe so I don't need any friends
I got plenty
Okay, why are you here a search on Quora - that says how many friends do you how the few friends can a person have before?
they die
Okay, and then I'm going to say a similar search right after where you replace person with frog
All right, you know give me give me my phone please please give me my phone
You don't even have my number in it. Give me give me his phone
Okay, okay, at least that's a more reasonable height. Please give me the phone. Oh you left your private tabs open. Oh
Please please stop. Oh, yeah, but what does he have open hermit the frog butt girl?
Here give me that I take them I take the the phone and I turn around and a flash goes off
Guys, what the hell Sullivan is a picture of my dick and ball
What the fuck is going on Sullivan?
It tabs give me the phone give me the phone I take Sullivan's phone and I dial 9-1-1 and immediately hang up
Okay, wait, let's just not draw attention to the cops
Very key very key if you know where this John guy is I say we go talk to him
About the building maybe he can give us maybe he could tell us about it or has blueprint for it. All right
Let's let's just go to his house while he will say
building
Shit
Who go ahead me go ahead while Sullivan was saying that
Yeah, Barry we can hear you just send over the thing what you say the
Opinion mm-hmm while Sullivan was saying all that stuff. I just bought like a bunch of
That I bought it I bought a print of that I bought a print of Barry G with makeup on his eBay account
using his his Apple pay
Okay, that was
That's so old you have such a shitty phone that still has Apple Pay on it
This is an iPhone 5c. I can call people who cares, you know, that's all I care, you know
Your call history, okay, so there's a call to 9-1-1 five minutes ago. It looks like that's it
Yeah, it's still got a flappy bird on this thing. You're actually
a lot of money
To sell your phone, okay, so first
I didn't pick it up again. It's not
Reflective of my ability to play flappy bird and also if you look at the call history
I've called you guys every week and a half and then I would space it out about a month
Just in case I was being bothering you and you can see a lot of me trying to call you guys
so that happened to
How much you use your phone for something useful and find out where this fucker is? Okay. Thank you
Barry G for sending it and yeah, he finds the the the address of John architect and
Yeah, I mean you guys can head over there if you want to
the
I came with you.
I'm just kidding.
Okay, this is starting to make some serious sense.
Let's go to that guy's house on planet E-Bomb.
Yeah, sure.
Which is the planet that we're on.
Which I think is maybe where all of us are.
Let's stay on the same planet.
I don't want to leave the planet.
Yeah, for some reason.
So yeah, you guys drive across Gun City
city to John Architect's house. It is, uh, it looks like the house in
bling ring that just like perfectly clear box house. Um, yeah. And you
see him. Oh yeah. Wow. Doing stretches, uh, um, completely
clothes. Are those crazy, awesome teens from bling ring in there too?
Nope. They're not. They're not helping him stretch. Nope. Nope. Are
those Ross they are no no they are helping them stretch
your old helping instruction there way more of us than there are patches you
can see there are enough of us now that we can just make the story
slowly becoming becoming us obsolete yeah okay so the teens from from bring
bling-ring are there and they're helping them stretch and we walk up to them we
blast their brains they're 18 years old that's first that's for stealing all
those celebrities fucking shit you pieces of shit yeah you're not allowed to do
that yeah you're not allowed to do that you guys are lower than dogs from
stealing food from fucking celebrities and they explode the most beautiful
people on the world celebrities in what world are we on Pat
E-Bomb!
You guys go in.
Oh yeah, what's up?
I was gonna say "Um, E-Bomb."
[Laughter]
We're gonna get through so much plot.
Alright.
John Architect answers the door.
And you guys I guess are carrying...
Are you guys...
Is Barry Gee zoomed in or no? Not yet.
I'm eating basic combos.
an iPad that we have.
Yeah.
Wait, Caleb, can he be on your computer screen?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, he replaces my Teletubby screen in the middle of the demon.
Yes.
Instead of the normal two green dots for eyes and four green dots for a smile.
Just what you see.
Yeah.
You see Barry G in makeup.
Yeah, on the line with Barry G.
the
I think I'm gonna fuck out of him
If I'm a bit confused so you're welcome to come inside
I'm gonna kill you
No, we need a we need blue we need some blue I'm gonna have sex with you
No, we need some blue from you
We need the blue paper. I'm gonna blow him
No close
I blew him?
I guess I'll have blown him.
I've blown him before.
When we leave here you're going to be saying I blew him, but not right now.
Got it, okay.
So we have some, we're interested in the recent redevelopment of the iCup compound and your
work on it and we wanted to know if you had the blueprints for that.
It's not called a blueprint you idiot it's called a blue piece of paper stupid ass shirt.
Yeah and I blew him? No.
This is sort of like I'm playing D&D alone and we're here to distract you.
I'm actually answering them.
I have like five people just making fun of me while I play D&D by myself.
You're like Jordan Peterson and we're like five Joe Rogans.
Yeah.
Because he's crying.
Okay.
And yeah, I mean, John the Architect answers me and he says, "Oh, well, the blueprints,
Um, I mean I have some
sketches, but the official blueprints I
Like everything it got possessed by
Um black rock real estate and development division. Yeah, he blueprints his black cock
Yeah, why don't why don't you roll roll roll persuasion on that let's have you roll something
Let's see if that made him laugh. He rolls. Can we can we do a perception check on whether or not?
John, architect is a black male
Or not even that, just if his cock is black.
- Well, they all need hair. - No, no, I just said princes.
All of you, yeah, all of you roll insight to see if you can tell...
- It was like the anime needs jokes. - ...if he's got a black penis.
I think Gun City needs a new skill roll called "joke."
And if you make a joke to a character, you have to roll that.
And I think my character has +100.
Mm-hmm.
And I think Patrick's character has -7000.
I'm only 20.
Yeah, you could tell that his penis is the color of whatever his skin is like you can tell pretty sure
It was it is it is white like all my characters
Thank God, yeah, oh and in walks the
Morgan Freeman
Hey just got back from the white surgery store
And yeah, so I mean he says it's in like this Blackrock facility. I mean you guys would know that
Blackrock eventually became more
Aggressive and being a development and real estate company. So they probably developed some or at least contracted John
architect to develop
the the
Facility as you would know it and so that is the place that would have the blueprint
But you know, you can't really just go in there and
Ask we gotta go in there. I asked for a blue proprietary blueprint. Okay, I think we need to break in there
But first we'll need to get the blueprint
Actually, no and we'll need to go recruit two people who are willing to join us on this heist John architect
Do you know who designed the blackrock facility?
I'm not I'm not entirely certain but I can sit I let me I guess I can
For he was British the entire time. I had no choice
I was forced on the spot to make a character and I was like he's got to be different
And so I chose this and he is different from Leo the collector. Oh
Yeah, Leo the collector is very different. Yeah, do both of those voices at the same time. I can't do two voices at once
the
And he lives and he he knocks up one floor right above me
You see David architect who's also stretching in the clear building. This is all so easy so far
Yeah, yeah, and he breaks the glass floor and just comes down and lands on his face. I want to say
Glass floor you must be a very good architect
And he says he says it all it bruv I'll go another British accent for you
And he hands you guys the blueprint to the Blackrock building and then he kills himself
The Blackrock building was developed by by David architect and it shows they have glass floors everywhere we can bring right in
Does not have glass for all floors
It has glass floors and ceilings and walls and doors
Glass that have no door are just a door frame. It has doors made of paper and windows made of water
This is gonna be the best heist ever!
Made of nothing!
There's no ceilings on it either, yeah.
And it's as small as my hand!
It's perfect!
And it's right here!
Yeah, it's in his back pocket!
Okay, no. We're gonna do a heist on that place.
Yeah, you will.
the
But you can see that there is at the very least a main entrance.
And then you know that if you go up two floors, somewhere in that third floor,
there is a computer terminal that contains a full list of the blueprints inside of them.
It's hard-coded in there, it's not replicated anywhere, it's meant to be not accessible except by personal download.
the
you can roll investigation for that. Yeah, go for it.
I'm, yeah, while he investigates that, I would like to case the joint by dressing as an arcade
repairman. Okay, yeah, of course.
Walking into the front door. Very good.
I got a 20 on my investigation. Okay, cool. So,
all right, so, so yeah, I would say there's kind of like a synergy here because,
Cam, if you as an arcade repairman are kind of useful in that you can kind of distract the guards here while he's casing the joint, because it's pretty conspicuous to see a demon with a computer on its back, sort of like observing a building up and down.
So I think we should play out that scene to see if you're kind of ample at distracting them.
Yeah, I used my master disguise ability, by the way, so I have a perfect disguise.
Yes, as an arcade repairman.
Yeah.
All right, so yeah, you're coming up to the to the guards what's going on
Hello. Hello. Hello. What's all this then? I'm the arcade repairman here to repair
Machines
Yeah, I guess let's start with
Yeah, uh, you know what no, it's let's let's play this out and then we'll figure out where you're gonna have to roll
You see the guard there is like I don't remember we don't sorry. Did somebody call you for the building?
The machines are broken!
Oh, you're the guards, you're the guys who schedule the repairs, you're the ones who remember who calls who.
No, no, we don't schedule the repairs.
I tried playing the games earlier and I complained because they were all broken.
[laughter]
I, I, I, uh, just, just, hold on, let me, let me just check at the front desk.
I can't believe this.
Travis, how close to the scene are you? Are you-
I'm shouting!
(laughing)
- You're 20 feet away, cupping your head,
hands around your mouth, okay, yes.
- And yeah, one of the guards goes inside.
- I'm losing valuable time here, okay?
- One of the guards goes inside to check.
- I've never been made to wait this long in my life!
- While the guards inside, I walk out,
I turn the corner in like a guard uniform
that's way too big for me, 'cause I'm a Yoda.
It's like little kid wearing dad's clothes.
Mm-hmm, and I go sit where he was sitting
You see the other guard turn to you go. Hey, what?
While Patrick Yoda's standing guard I walk I would say oh, hey guard you mind if I walk inside
Wait, and I'm stuck out here
Hold on, hold on.
What the fuck is this?
What the f-
Let's do a couple of rolls.
I mean, Patrick Yoda, I guess first do Deception with disadvantage.
Real quick, sorry. How do we do these rolls again?
For sure.
I only got a 25.
So on roll 20, you'll just hit the thing that has to do with whatever the roll is.
So like if you look at the skills-
Open up your character sheet.
Yeah, open up your character sheet.
Yeah, I'm on my character sheet.
Yes, yes, yes.
that
the
Also I'll say with that 20 you also can tell that somebody's been through there recently.
I'm a guard!
I'm starting to do, I'm doing that thing where I like, I hear, I've heard a funny voice and
I start accidentally mimicking it just because I think it's funny so I'm going like, I can't
believe I'm waiting here!
I can't believe you're keeping me waiting!
I can't believe you were waiting too!
I can't believe, I can't believe I'm waiting!
You gotta stop awaiting!
I got to stop waiting. You got to stop waiting. You got to go in.
I got to go in. I got to repay.
Oh, he has to go in.
He has to go in and repay.
While they distract him, I die.
We're distracting each other.
Why did you have lunch today?
Oh, what did you have for lunch today?
Yeah, yeah. I would say you guys are able to get in through the side door pretty easily.
The guard does eventually come out.
the
Did they come with us or are they still out front?
We're still out front. Or at least I am.
Yeah, I don't know if you guys...
Did you guys... Are you guys still out front?
Are you guys still way out front? I'm still guarding, because now I
now I fully believe this is my job.
Very cool.
In that case... No, okay, no. You know what I'm gonna try to do?
Mm-hmm.
I would like to purposely
have my disguise, like,
fail. Like, maybe my mustache falls off a little bit.
Mm-hmm. And then I go like,
"Oh no! I've been found out!"
found out and I like run I start to run away but really slowly like I'm trying
to lure the guards away so they don't notice what's going on
the other guard comes out and says yeah we have no RK repair what is this little
green man doing?
He's getting away!
We have to go get him!
I'm running slow motion.
If you see him, he's running away!
I'm running away!
He's running away!
I said he was running away!
The other guard looks at the guard who came back and is like, "I don't really know what
to make of this."
We got the guy!
And he's like, "Alright, I guess, yeah."
Roll persuasion, Pat.
19, nice.
Yeah.
the
is
I can't come in.
- You will be in the main lobby after that.
So it will be, you'll have to just like figure out what to do
but yeah, you can absolutely do that and figure it out.
- Okay, I'm just gonna, I'm, well, actually no,
that might make them run to the side door though.
So maybe I shouldn't do that.
Okay, I'm just gonna run just slightly faster than them
and go, "Oh, I hope they don't catch me.
"I hope they don't catch me.
"I'm gonna get you.
"Don't catch me, don't catch me."
- While I'm in a big guard suit,
the
further down the hallway, it looks like it's pretty clear
from what you can see down here.
No sign of anybody there.
I mean you could do obviously you can do perception checks
or investigation checks or insight checks into certain
things that you're observing.
Feel free to ask questions.
Can I to clear this section of the hallway?
I'm looking into my backpack and notice that I have a huge
worm and I actually have two huge worms.
is a number two.
You really should start paying attention.
I mean, you already you left the huge worms in there and I did.
You do it now.
So you have to reckon with that.
I don't know how there's two, but go on.
I don't know either, but I'm going to drop one, just one.
And OK, I'm going to slap it on the ass like a donkey
and watch as it wiggles through and I love that if it falls
into the mouth of any kind of creature.
OK, cool.
So you slap the ass of the worm or what you think is the ass you slap.
- He has a big ass.
- Okay, cool.
You slap the juicy ass of that worm
and it slithers forward
and you see it start disappearing in the darkness.
And then you hear a pop sound
and you see the worm running back
and it looks pretty injured.
And you hear like a, it sounds like an alarm clock.
And then you hear the alarm clock stop.
- Call me your baby.
I put him back into my backpack.
Yeah, the worm's like whimpering in pain.
Um...
Okay, uh...
This bit of darkness is like, straightforward in this direction, by the way.
Okay, Sullivan,
now you, your turn.
No, no, no, I don't want to do that.
Fine, we'll all, we'll all go.
But,
slowly.
And Sullivan goes first.
And Sullivan takes point.
Hey, Sullivan, it's because you're the leader.
I
that
Mr. Sullivan. Uh oh, I killed him again. I've killed him every episode of this fucking D&D
thing. Oh, poor Sullivan. Yep. Alright. I killed him again. Sullivan is moving forward,
he's dashing forward because of that great charisma. And a pop sound is heard. And let's
to Mr. The Frog.
Okay.
Yup.
And then let's see what happens to Mr. The Frog.
Uh...
God.
Oh, well.
How much HP did I give him?
A million.
Not enough.
Million.
Did I kill him?
Uh...
outright kill it today is he unconscious or dead? Obviously. He just dies off screen.
Literally off screen. A little popping sound. Not even a whimper. Okay. Alright, alright.
The worm came back with a bruise. He's not dead but he is, if he got hit like two more
he would have been dead. So he is just knocked out. You just hear him go "AHH!" and just
flop to the ground. He can't tell you what he saw or anything.
Sullivan! Quit farting around down there!
I guess I'll start doing death saves for Sullivan. If you guys don't act.
Is there a way to take the flashlight and examine exactly what happened to the worm?
Yeah, if you can uh, yeah, I would say you can do like a medicine check to see what happens.
Alright.
I'll do a medicine check then.
Hold on, sorry, I'm not great at this.
No, it's all wonderful.
A lot of fucking characters here.
Thank you.
Alright.
You say medicine.
I say ROI.
I say, I look at.
Mm hmm.
Oh, 15. Very good.
And with only a plus one.
So when you're looking at the worm, what you can tell is that it's covered
in some kind of like snot.
Like it looks like a snot bubble blew up on it.
And that's that's what the natural mucus of the worm.
Yes. Like a separate kind of mucus.
That'd be funny if he described that news, like, but that's just normal for them.
That's the natural mucus.
It's a good thing you asked that, because otherwise you could be completely led astray.
Yeah, I realize that now, yeah.
You're a fucking nerd.
I didn't have to put an eye on her to know that the worms are slimy!
You're so smart.
Hmm, looks like there's some kind of...
I would say, Travis Ocelot, you've been in the field long enough,
that let's have you roll in a history check to see if you can
like kind of recall what kinds of enemies do this.
Okay.
Very good history.
Yeah, I do 20 nice.
So you would recall that something that has that kind of like
amount of mucus that can cause that kind of like forceful of
the
So you would know that about them, so you would probably assume that there are a number of them littered throughout this facility.
Right.
Travis, I noticed you staring at this worm.
I just remembered that these are DQIQ DaddyBots!
Oh, oh no!
Oh, and they snot when you get close to them?
*snoring*
I
I could walk up and maybe use the bottom of the iPad stand to like shuffleboard him into the next one.
[laughter]
Across the cold, snowy grass.
I would say, I mean you have like, with your computer, the computer like, hacking ability involves you having some sort of like detachable wiring that allows you to hook into other things.
He'll die if he goes into another one though.
You could, yeah, he might die.
All right. You know what?
You just gave me a better idea.
I would like.
So they're bots, right?
So they are electronic.
Yeah. So I would like to I would like to hack these electronics
instead of kill the instead of kill the thing
that we put in this to kill them every time.
OK, so yeah, I mean, you could you could try to like seek it out.
You'll have disadvantage just because you can't see it.
But how much how much like can I see ahead of me with this flashlight?
It looks like I got like it's like a like a good amount.
So you can move a bit further and you'll see if you can see it.
Okay, let's do that.
Okay, cool. So just move your character how much further you want to go.
As you tiptoe through these sort of sterile hallways.
Okay, and let's reveal a little bit more of what's happening here.
And I have this guy with me.
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
Travis, would you like to join me?
Yes.
So you can see one of the Doatwake daddies.
What does that say?
the
open sort of door, looks like it's in what would be somebody's office.
So you can probably try to, uh, saying that I'm gay.
So you can probably, uh, try to, uh, you can definitely try to hack it now.
Um, and you're going to be able to hack it automatically.
Oh my god, whoa.
Because it's not really, like, able to resist. It is sleeping.
It is asleep, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, so I, I, I'm going to hack it.
Nice, cool.
So, let's review the hackability, the hacker mode ability.
So, the computer can go hacker mode and on a failed intelligence saving throw, which we
won't talk about, you lodge yourself, your computer tower, into the Don't Wake Daddy
and they can do whatever you want as the robot.
So the bot is able to move, so yeah, you do that, and now what do you want to do with
it?
is
the
more than one close by, it's like, you know, one goes off and then another goes off.
Yeah, could I, I would like to communicate to all the ones in the, in the area and let
them know that we have, that it's, it is a pizza party and we have to all meet in the
center of the room and run into each other really fast.
Okay, let's make that... So I was thinking about what to give you for hacker checks.
I was thinking we should just do Arcana for you. So roll Arcana.
And I'll say that DC for this... Yeah, you have a very good one.
I'll say that DC is going to be a 16 for that.
You should give him a... To make him... For hacking, you should give him a puzzle that's basically just playing
connect the dots but it's on a black background and it's green so it looks
like computers. That's a really good idea. Yeah I got a 26. Yeah so what do you say
to the other don't wake daddy bots? Hey don't wake daddy bots like me there is a
serious pizza type party in the middle of this room and I'm gonna need every
the
pop pop pop pop sounds as they all wake up and you hear them like all sort of
walk towards the center of the room. Okay. And so like I'll reveal a little bit
more because you could hear that too.
And then I have an awesome plan also. Yeah nice so they're all in the center
of the room except the yours. Okay so because it's some it's a bot I mean I
I would assume it has a self-destruct button with a timer, yeah?
[laughter]
I'll allow it!
What are you thinking?
Oh, I'm thinking I set the self-destruct button with a timer
and then I inject my fucking computer ass out of the back
probably land on Sullivan's dead body
and shoot my bot right into the middle of the room
and watch, I mean, sit back and watch the fireworks, baby.
Hey, I like that!
Let's do another Arcana check to see if you can hack into the self-destruct function.
25.
Yeah, you're the king of this.
And then what we'll do is we'll do a...
Let's do a Dexterity saving throw for you with advantage, because that was a very solid...
You could perfectly time when you want this thing to explode.
So what are you doing?
16?
All right, cool.
What are you doing?
Describe it to me because you succeeded.
Okay, so I already described it, but I guess I'll describe it again.
All right, man.
Set the timer for I mean, I'm pretty fast.
It'll probably only take me like one second.
So I'll set it for one second.
Well, that's too much that it can't go 30 feet in one second.
So I'll set it for five seconds and then I'll shoot it.
I'll shoot my computer body back out into my demon body and I'll
also put a cartoon bomb on the screen on the Don't Wake Daddy bot.
Just as kind of a like, kind of a fuck you, you know?
And also, and...
No, no, I don't have any pizza, do I?
No.
Okay, I just scrapped the pizza, it was all a ruse.
No, what were you gonna do?
I was gonna maybe like put like some pizza in the room.
(laughing)
- Yeah, this is pizza, no.
- Okay, so it's pizza, so they're like,
they're in the right moments, they're like,
oh, this is awesome, and then they explode.
- Yeah. - All right, cool.
- Then when they explode,
standing where one of the bots was, is me.
And I say, I bet you weren't expecting to see me here.
And then some awesome plot twist music plays,
and it's like a montage of I was running in circles outside.
You see me switching clothes--
- How'd you do it?
Switching clothes with with Patrick Yoda
so he becomes the arcade repairman and I become the guard and then he's gonna be
Like climbing up the side of the building and going into like the gutter on it
And then I'm going through the pipes and then I'm like crawling through the pipes between the floors and then I crawl through the plumbing
up inside one of the
We're gonna have you roll a couple stealth checks
He just said
I just walked in the
Continuity
All right, they come roll his shit if you want to be such a
Okay, what do I have to roll I'm gonna beast it let's do a stealth check to I guess get into events without anybody noticing
Okay, well first of all I'm wearing a perfect guard disguise and the guards are chasing Patrick Yoda because I switched with him and second
Of all the ability to turn invisible. So you're wearing a girl. I'm gonna use that instead. You're wearing a guard disguise
Why did you go through the vent I switched?
Because I because I did if I had gone into the side door then I would have come up behind those guys and the plot twist
Wouldn't have made any sense
I'm gonna make you roll for that then. All right, you just it's like perfect sense. Yeah. Thank you
Alright, so I'll say that we can review
Let's reveal more of the room at this point. Yeah, I revealed all this I already saw it all
Everything yeah, I pretty much saw everything already
Patrick you know, are you distracting the the team the trip distracting the guard?
I took off the arcade repairman suit and I walked in the front door
All right, the guards are going to attack you at the me
Why how are you?
Arcade repairman suit off. They're looking for an arcade repairman. They know you were the guard the entire time
Green and you're two feet tall. I'm three feet tall
All right, Patrick, just use a plot twist. You won't make your roll for it.
Oh, yeah, okay.
The plot twist was I was an arcade repairman.
Oh, wait, and I take out the thing that we're looking for.
[Laughter]
Pat, why don't you-- you could try to explain to them what's going on.
Oh, I take off the--
I take off the arcade repairman hat and I look at them and go,
the
All right, we're gonna roll initiative.
This is one of those just for laughs pranks from 2008.
Oh, okay, you're trying to persuade them.
Okay, let's do a persuasion check then.
13.
One of them thinks maybe you're the just for laughs guy.
The other one is definitely sure you're not.
And you both get $15.
Do you have $15 on you?
I have $100. He needs 30, right?
I have $100.
You have $100.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, hold on, hold on.
Okay, I say and you both win an Xbox game because in my inventory I have every Xbox game ever
Okay, roll persuasion again. You get another chance
another 13
One of the guards are the other guys like he's giving us an Xbox game. Let's just go just a little freak
You know the guards like fine, but if we see you around here, you're fucked. You got it. Hey
Hello
ODST
So they go back to their post so you try to go to the side door they would probably see you
So you might have to just chill outside unless you want to like start something with them
I I'm in it. I walk back and I'm in a don't wake daddy repairman
costume. How would you know to get that?
You wouldn't know. So we'll come back to it.
Dress up as a blueprint repairman. That's what we should have done from the beginning.
Okay, that I dress up as a blueprint repairman. So you guys can go to the computer here and
start searching the files. There's no issue getting the information from there.
got the there's no issue because I already hacked it 20 minutes ago.
Okay. Yeah, you get the blueprint for the facility.
Now the dope week daddy bots are gone.
You could pretty easily get out through the side door that said,
you know getting out all at once and getting by the guards back
to the car.
I would say you'd have to either move stealthily or kind of come
up with a way around that unless you want to you know again incur
trouble down the line.
Do we have what we need from this facility?
Yes.
Can we get the blueprint?
Mm-hmm.
You can just get it from the computer though.
You're already there and the Doki Parry bots are gone.
Oh yeah, alright.
Cool, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Alright, so let's get it from the computer.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, so let's start by logging onto the computer.
Yeah, the computer says, "Here you go."
Oh, no, no, no.
Okay, you go.
Yeah.
Okay, let's click log in.
Okay, it's loading.
This is taking too long.
I destroyed the computer.
And then the Plot Twist music plays in the background.
Oh, no.
And then the plot twist music plays again and I hold up the blueprint that I already printed out when I'm sitting here earlier
It doesn't matter. God you saved me from my own rage. Yeah
Now there's a destroyed computer, which is you know, in addition to the don't wake daddy bots Leo. Let's see. All right, cool
So you got it now? Yeah again, you guys can go back out the side door rip up the blueprint
All right, you don't have to do copy now
*laughter*
Oh my god
You're a fucking asshole
I'm getting confused between
Heists and
Magicians
*laughter*
You're pulling an infinite
string of tied together blueprints
out of your ass
sleeve
Okay so I think we should get out of here
You can just leave
You wanna leave him there?
up
All right, how do you guys want to get out of here?
Keep in mind you have to cross by the guards at the front of the building to get out
All right, I pull the hammers back on my golden deagles
Yeah, I'm gonna kill them. We haven't fought anything yet. I'm down to kill. Okay, let's go kill
Does Travis us let have one golden deagle or two
I guess I thought I had two but maybe I only have one I
I mean you said you had two. Let's give you, I think you have both. The golden bullets are what you're gonna need.
Oh, right. But I have regular 50 action express. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Yeah, that's tight. Yeah, you're gonna kill the guards?
Yeah, whatever if we have to sure fine.
Okay, you guys want to see me do a trick shot?
Yeah
Yes
Okay, cool, so you can go up and try to kill them
if you want to sort of get the jump on them, you could try to move stealthily to see if you can get like a
Sneak attack round. Yeah, let's
Okay
A lot of honor in that I kind of want to line up a shot to kill both of them in one
With one bullet
It's gonna be hard but yeah go for it
So yeah, you guys walk you just guys just walk out and face the guards I'm sneaking I'm sneaking ahead of them
I want to get a surprise round. I don't care what they do. All right, how are you? Where are you gonna hide?
Well, I'm also wearing a guard outfit question mark. So maybe I can get a moment of like confusion
- out of that I would say if you roll your stealth high enough like yeah, I'm just gonna I'm like
So, I don't know what the layout is, but I'm kind of like I assume they're like out
They're kind of like outside the door. They're like, yeah, so I'm trying I'm trying to kind of like sidle in like I've been standing
Behind the desk at the lobby or something. Mm-hmm. Okay, cool
And then sorry, what are you gonna say Ray?
I just follow Travis and I'm just like I kind of just want to see him kill these guys
Mm-hmm. I'm not really planning on helping though. Okay, cool
And Patrick Yoda, you're just where are you right?
I'm your outside. We know I'm I'm looking through the disguise box and I'm just like no ah
No, I wouldn't work. Ah
crap
Okay cool
Shit you just you sort of square up on these guys and you're like hey, where the fuck did you just come from?
Yeah
I, um...
I'm filming with the
Barry Gey iPad. I'm like, "Come on, Travis, do it!"
"Come on!" I'm recording the call on my phone.
This is such a bad idea for
criminals. Okay, so...
My gym arm is not
gripping the Desert Eagle correctly. It's upside down. I'm looking down at it now and realizing that I'm not
poised to do a trick shot because my chimp arm is not as dexterous as I
thought it was. But I do just aim my other regular test vehicle at one of their heads.
Alright, cool. Let's roll initiative for you and the guards. Can I get a
surprise round if I roll a stealth right now? Do they notice me? Let's roll stealth
of
the
I'm gonna lay down good. I'm gonna bury back out. Mm-hmm. I pipe
And you're gonna have advantage on
Okay, your assassin ability. That's a 23 second one. Definitely hits roll for damage
Is it a sneak attack from assassinate if it's on a surprise round?
I'm critical. Yes. It's a guaranteed critical. Oh, yeah shit. It is. All right, so that's 16 damage and then I get a second attack
Okay, that's 22 damage. Yeah, you just one of them you just like you just pop up out of nowhere and just
Beat one of them to death and you hear all the people it's like oh
Like screaming as you're like beating this guy as I'm piping him down. Yeah, say that
Yeah, Travis Osler that wasn't one you were aiming at so maybe you just move your gun
That was the one I was aiming in so now I'm aiming it at the other guy. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
the
(laughter)
Did something like intimidating?
No, it's blurry now.
Oh.
(laughter)
He's got self-conscious suddenly about his like, how messy his room is.
It just changes his background to blurry.
Alright, and now you're up.
Uh, um, uh, Travis, sorry.
Okay, so I got really nervous and forgot how to do trick shots.
So I have my Desert Eagle pointed at his head and I look at Ray William Johnson and ask,
"Okay, what would be cool?"
You could like, so you just have the gun at his head?
Yeah.
So like maybe you do like a battle, a flip first and then you shoot him.
Okay, I'll try that.
Try doing a flip.
Okay, so I crouch to get into flipping position.
(laughing)
- Okay, so I mean, it's looking good so far.
Here, let me put on the slow motion mode on the camera.
(laughing)
Okay, now, now go.
- Okay, cool.
Do an acrobatics check and then do an attack.
Nice, 20.
Yeah, you execute that for me.
(laughing)
Roll attack, roll attack with the deagle.
- Oh, didn't I?
- You click on the golden deagle roll.
- For the damage.
the
this
Yep, you got two attacks.
Alright, so I have to put down my other gun so that I can flip the Travis gun around.
This time, could you do like a spin?
Yeah, I'll give that a shot. This spin, I'm not going to leave the ground, I'm just going to walk in a very tight circle.
That's cool.
Alright, so another acrobatics check.
No, if you're gonna walk in a tight circle, I think you got that.
Well, 22, it looks really good!
Best spin I've ever seen.
Alright.
And, yeah, I tried to put a little English on it with my Krav Maga.
How's that?
Yeah, leave that there, that's fine.
Sorry, some guy's knocking on my window.
Try to slip that there, that's fine.
Okay.
[laughter]
Alright, so I also
I also did a grab on him.
Yeah, I did a grab on him.
Okay, the Krav Maga 2000,
that move, uh, you try to karate chop him, I guess,
or with like, I guess the sharp end of a pen.
Um, and, uh...
No, it's with the gun. I'm holding two guns.
I've got no other...
Okay, not Michael, sorry.
Yeah, you miss with the 12.
So you spin in place and then sort of
try to whack him with the gun,
and he just sort of gets out of the way.
He's like, he's like,
retching back and forth with the ball.
Okay, wait, then I want to see if I can
can
You almost did it really cool.
You sort of do the thing when you're trying to learn how to...
You just watch the circle of Enzkwagas armor.
[Laughter]
You do the thing when you're trying to learn how to
spit pencils between your fingers
and you're just gonna like...
I do the rubber pencil trick
with the Golden Beagle.
It's not rubber. It doesn't look like rubber at all.
[Laughter]
Alright, cool. Ray, it is your turn.
Let's wait. Sorry, Patrick Yoda, did you roll?
You didn't roll initiative. Roll initiative.
Okay, I'm still looking through the the disguise bin you don't have to fight then. All right, cool. We could just have you just
I'm just I'm like pulling my hair out and just like
All right, you're up Ray
I feel like I feel like Travis has got this kind of like I I really just I mean, okay, whatever
I I don't think I rolled initiative though. Did I you did you guys six?
the
The guard did really bad, so you're still up.
I'm gonna throw my sexual grenade between them.
I got a 6, he got a 5. This is so fucked up.
Oh, I'm sorry, you're right. You should go.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, I mean...
I dive in front of the grenade, I cover my body.
Okay, alright.
As a reaction, do you want to take that damage?
As a reaction, I would like to dive toward the grenade and use the guard to cover it.
You dive into the guard and put his body on it.
And it's technically not a reaction because my turn is before Caleb's.
Alright. So yeah, your action. We'll say you did a joint action.
Where you held the guard.
It's like when we were co-parenting.
We did a lot of this.
You guys smile at each other sweetly as this guard swallows a grenade.
Yeah, a cum grenade.
the
and I'm like, I got two maracas and I'm like, yo, hello.
Yeah.
We're like, we're like, yeah, we're, we're, we're burning rubber and a
giant Flintstones car.
We're all running.
It's all of it's just passed out, um, in the backseat, I guess.
Um, wherever you want them.
the
I'm not sure what I'm saying here.
to do that on the same day. The only issue being that there's definitely a little bit
more suspicion around you now that you sort of needlessly murdered two guys. When you
get back and you're sort of, you know, starting to crack open drinks to celebrate, you get
a knock at the door. Somebody got past your guards, Barry Gee, in your absence. Does anybody
get the door? I'll get it! No. I got a smart door. I got a smart door that opens up by itself.
It's very unsafe. You accidentally bought a fart door and then it farts right in Travis's
face. Oh that smells horrible! Oh my god! Why would they even make a fart door? Oh, it's
disgusting. I like the smell of it. I like it. It reminds me of home. I'm running, I
run up I'm in the sombrero I have the maracas oh fuck okay what the hell was
that it smells it smells bad here oh I think Jesus it solvent gets up it's
like a foot nearly still want a lot of a lot of paid and he gets this door he
opens it. And who's behind the door? None other than your old friend slash femme fatale,
Mommy Goodlegs. And we'll end it there. Did she make that spell? Holy shit. I need to
update my fan theories.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[ Music ]