Ho ho ho!
A merry Gun City Christmas to one and all!
It's me, Santa Patches!
I'm here to bring you some holiday cheer.
I hope you have your favorite Christmas cybernetic enhancement and hot cocoa at the ready, because
Because today is a very special episode of Gun City.
Because not only is it Christmas, but we're on TV!
Hi Mom!
Hi Mrs. Claus!
I'll see you later tonight.
Gonna fuck you for first it's Christmas Eve!
Wait, did you say you were gonna fuck your mom?
You said you were gonna fuck your mom.
Your mom is also technically Mrs. Claus.
Your mom's name, Mrs. Claus.
I guess that's right.
Your Santa Claus, Mrs. Claus is also your mom's name.
Oh my god is Mrs. Claus Santa's mom the whole time?
But first, it's Christmas Eve!
Shhh!
All the good little boys and girls, and worse, are asleep.
Except for three very, very special ones.
Patrick Yoda, Blotas Piss, and Ray William Johnson.
Wide-eyed and breathless with excitement.
Their...
[GASP]
Their friendship has taken them across the planet E-Bomb, all the way to jungle-infested
Earth, into the virtual world, and even into each other's penises.
Oh yeah.
And now, they're in space!
That's right, on Leo the Collector's, I mean King Leo of New England's, space station.
King Leo's Pleasure Palace, the finest space station of its kind, a city in and of itself,
and a perfect holiday getaway.
We'll get more on that though later.
But now it's time for something a little less interesting.
It's time to read some Christmas story classics.
Gun City Christmas story classics.
Blotas, Ray, and Patrick each have
come prepared with their own Gun City Christmas tale to read.
And there are so many great ones to choose from.
Another list joke here.
OK.
Frisky the Ho-Man, A Christmas Carol Baskins--
That's right, because Santa never forgets.
And Rodolfo, the red-nosed Latin king.
And to whom will they be reading these stories?
Well, they're reading them to the greatest gift of all,
a son created in a lab who is a penguin
with a water bottle jutting out of his head
that holds his brain.
And he's wearing a leather jacket, I think.
That's right.
- We should get figurines.
- It's New Sullivan.
- Oh yeah.
- Woo!
- Yeah!
- New Sullivan!
- Woo!
- Yeah!
- Oh yeah! - Oh yeah!
- Created in-- - Aw yeah!
- Created in the remote village of Hootown by our humble three
while on an adventure searching for the fabled N-word pass,
just so you know, he quickly became beloved by all.
(laughing)
Guess I almost wrote that right.
A college student who is also eternally four,
and forever silly, there's no one more fun
and more awesome than New Sullivan.
forever silly.
Oh, would you look at the time.
I better get going.
I have to fly all over earth except for Syria to hand out toys to good little boys and girls.
Why don't you spend some time with our heroes on a relaxing, low-key holiday adventure in
a cozy Christmas hotel room.
Probably just what you need during your stressful, anxious, and very lonely holiday.
Ho ho ho, ho ho ho.
yeah so you guys are in a hotel room you're chillin with chillaxin new
Sullivan is going like
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
Go Sullivan! Go Sullivan! Go Sullivan!
He's doing like a little side to side, he's trying to work it into a headspin.
And then that crack hits and what does he do?
He headspins even better.
Holy crap.
So it's true. It makes you better at headspinning.
You guys are just sort of cheering on New Sullivan while he's doing his little dances.
That's all, let's do the wavering.
What presents, do you guys get presents for New Sullivan?
He doesn't have to know yet. You shouldn't tell him, obviously.
It's Christmas Eve. Yeah, I got a present for him.
What'd you get him? I got him a gift card.
Yeah, he's gonna last to where I got him a gift card to Target, okay
That sounds fine, I mean can't go wrong with a gift card to Target no I got him a sous vide a sous vide yeah
It's three hundred fifty dollars above and beyond this fucking. Yep. I got you a sous vide
I don't know if you know how to cook or anything, but uh I fucking hope you know
I really I really fucking hope you know how to cook I get a little I spent I went a little bit
out of my budget this Christmas and I'm really fucking hurting right now.
He's picking up on nothing. I get a little bit self-conscious about my gift card gifts.
I'm like, "So the gift card, that's part of your gift, but the rest of it's actually in the mail right now. It'll be here soon."
I got him a sweater that you guys have seen me wear like a hundred times before and you're thinking like,
Oh my he's giving him a sweater that he already owns that's a lame gift, and then I'm like look Sullivan
I got us matching sweaters, and I actually got him a brand new one of the one that I always wear my god
That's so fucking awesome. I take out the one I always wear and I put it on
I was really fucking hoping one of you got a I don't know like a vacuum sealer, so I got that too
Yeah, I also got him a vacuum sealer. Thank Christ because you can't really use it without that vacuum sealer
So yeah, he's fuck. He's uh he goes over to his little play area
He has his three favorite toys with him which are all action figures of you guys
Guys he's singing our song
- He's having so much fun.
- Yeah, he's having a good time.
(imitating a dog)
He turns around, he starts smiling,
he's like so happy to see you guys doing it back.
What are you guys, do you guys have any food around?
- I just cherish him.
- What are you guys eating?
- I'm eating his little button nose.
(imitating a dog)
- I'm snacking on some doubled eggs.
- What the hell's a doubled egg?
- It's from the future.
- It's a deviled egg that has a deviled--
- No, I don't want to break my brain if I hear what it is.
- Alright, it has a deviled egg filling.
- It's a egg from the future.
- What about you, do you have an egg?
- No, I'm just smoking crack.
- Okay, so yeah, Dusala goes there,
he kinda like tugs at your, like,
(grunting)
asking for the deviled egg or one deviled egg.
- He's saying up!
- Okay, I throw him up in the air.
(screaming)
And I catch him, and then I throw an egg up in the air
and I hold him out.
Does he catch the egg?
- I'm gonna roll actually to see if he does.
- I'm staring at Sullivan like the straight drop video.
Something about double-degs is they have a special type of gravity where they can be caught by anybody
Yeah, he rolled we rolled well. He rolled fine, and then we should be clear when we should be saying new Sullivan
Yeah, we don't want to confuse yeah, I I gave old Sullivan a hit of the crack pipe, and he is terrified
He's not here. Yeah. He's not here. No. No you guys you guys parted ways. Yeah, we haven't seen him in forever
Right yeah, I should have read up on the Lord. That's I should honestly make the lore available
I feel like to you guys.
But anyway, so yeah.
Somebody should make a wiki.
Yeah.
It was made.
It was made and then it was updated a little bit.
Then I think it got deleted.
Somebody should not have deleted it so that I would have a resource.
Yeah, because I'm not good at providing information.
I ate one double dig.
Okay, well, New Solvent ate 15.
So New Solvent goes over and he starts like, "Nom, nom, nom, nom, nom, nom, nom."
He starts eating them.
He takes another hit at the crack pipe.
He's like going, "Whoa, whoa, whoa!"
It makes him able to eat more food.
Yeah, oh yeah, he has more of it, and then he sort of like lays back like
I look at him. I just what's wrong little buddy. I look at him. I'm paranoid as shit. He's got my hand on the wall
Stop it
And he goes he takes he takes a he takes his
His three favorite toys he puts them away in this little basket
He said good night, and he goes over to the bathroom
Say good night. That's cute. He goes. He made me not scared of crap anymore
I'm gonna smoke some more and when he goes he goes over to the bathroom and
when he does you just
You feel a chill in the air
And the lights flicker just slightly at first and then
total darkness
So it goes, it's Kirk Vonnegut.
The arity bomb, drained of all its color and verve, saved the opalescent eyesore that is
a one-gun city. From up here on King Leo Space Station. It's a smoky mess of
nauseous light, artificial to its silicone bones and ugliness in its hot plastic
guts. But up here things are new too. Shiny, still derelict, still made from the
recycled parts of ancient attempts at similar space stations, but new. You'd
You'd think the trouble wouldn't follow any of us up here, but I'm telling you this tale
from beyond the grave.
There's a killer on this space station, and they go by playtime.
They usually look for childless couples.
They usually wait for one of the freak outages that occur on the space station.
They usually slit their throats, and when the lights come back, they've usually left
at the top, each victim's corpse, their favorite toy.
Could be a new video game, an action figure, a sex toy,
hell, it could be a book.
They somehow know.
Playtime always knows what your favorite toy is.
What was my favorite toy?
Well, I wasn't killed by Playtime.
There was a bit of popcorn kernel stuck between my teeth,
and I was really digging in there, trying to get it out.
And so my elbow hit the airlock, and I took about 100
people with me into the cold inky blackness of space.
I really liked Crazybones though if you want to know.
Now playtime he always kills his victims but he didn't this time.
Well we don't think he did.
But New Sullivan is gone.
Snatched from his hotel room during an idyllic Christmas Eve with his adoptive parents and
uncle.
They thought they were out of the game, Blotas, Ray, and Patrick.
They haven't solved a case in years.
Actually, they've done several B&Es since then.
But up here, things are new, shiny, still degenerate, still made from the recycled parts
of ancient attempts at being funny, but still new.
And the trouble followed them up here, too.
So maybe it's time to don the hats, the silly voices, and the D20s.
time for gun city a broad city playtime continue fun that's good that is really
good Wow listen play time continue fun yeah no you have to go there so badass
yeah it's gonna just be a like Bill Hicks right now yeah I feel like bill I
feel like the white Bill Hicks. You do look exactly like that! The leather jacket? Yeah. Where'd you get that?
Bill Hicks store. Wow. Yeah, so you guys have been in your hotel room on Leo's Pleasure Palace for days,
months actually, completely despondent. You gotta get a little closer. Yeah, I have to get closer. Yeah, sorry.
So you guys have been in your hotel room for months, completely despondent after New Sullivan's
disappearance.
Oh, we did a flash forward.
Oh yeah, we're flash forward.
Oh my god.
Okay.
Did I miss my birthday?
When is Ray William Johnson's birthday?
It's my birthday.
Okay, you didn't miss your birthday.
When is my birthday?
Your birthday's in April sometime, I don't remember what day.
What's the date though?
I just told, I don't remember the date, I'm sorry.
Alright.
I know the date.
I guess you can continue.
12th?
10th?
What are you gonna do, every single number?
It's the 17th, right?
Real friend.
I knew that too.
I knew that because I used to have a Paul Blart Mall Cop 2 poster.
You should know that because I didn't memorize it.
I'm a very close friend of yours.
No, that's why.
Because in my head, when I think of you, I think of Paul Blart.
April 17th, 2007.
I wish.
I wish I was 15.
Wish I wish I was
Well anyway, so
Christmas went by without a thought in your head New Year's even Martin Luther King Day didn't register
Probably because he's been dead for many years
probably thousands of years
300 roughly 300
Okay, but awaking yeah
Yeah, you could have remembered.
But awaking from your comatose state in this decidedly not holiday-themed campaign, you
have found a resolve to find playtime, stop his grisly murders, and most importantly,
recover your beloved son, New Sullivan, and nephew.
Heard that.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
My nephew?
Your nephew, yeah.
They're the parents.
You're the uncle.
Yes.
Okay.
Oh, I remember this now.
I remember this now.
I repaid off all my debts.
Mom, dad, yeah.
Or does this take place before?
So, this falls canonically after...
This is after the heist, so you paid off your debts.
You guys were just here to celebrate Christmas.
You did your one last job, you solved your one last case.
You did your one last adventure.
So we're technically...
You thought you were done with all of this.
We're hiding.
No, no, no, no.
I thought we were in hiding.
No, wait, I'll explain.
At the end of the campaign.
Okay, tell me more of the lore. I need to know.
The space station of Pleasure Palace was erected a few months
after you'd helped Leo the Collector locate the temple of Topenguin of Doom
and complete his epic toy collection with the N-Gage.
You guys were supposed to give him the N-word pass, but then it didn't...
I forgot that's what it was.
And then you guys were gonna give him a fake one.
Times have changed.
Yeah, they sure have.
Yeah, we don't do that kind of thing anymore.
It was so funny back then.
Yeah.
Rude.
He first invaded Sky Ireland and turned the leprechauns into his slaves,
then used them along with his royal guard to continue invading the numerous sky
islands that exist above Gunn City and Planet E-Bomb. He had declared himself
king of the skies and struck a treaty with Gunn City including both the
government and the oligarchical board controlled primarily by Papi Chuko's
Technoslime Corporation. The relationship between King Leo and the city is
contentious but if they were ever go to war there'd be destruction you know all
this you know they don't want to do it so they they have proxy battles and they
We have a sort of healthy, unhealthy relationship, kind of.
Okay.
Yeah.
Cheers.
I don't have a drink.
Do you want one?
Yeah, I'll have a drink.
Yeah, thank you, man.
Alright.
Continue?
Oh yeah.
Crossing battles?
Yes, absolutely.
Wait, now we gotta do a cheers again.
Oh yeah, hold on.
Cheers.
Wait, can we get the toy cam?
Can you get the toy cam?
Cheers.
Lower.
Where do I should go?
Cheers.
To Dungeons and Dragons.
Oh.
What the hell's happening?
What the hell's happening to your mouth?
Stop drinking like that!
That's not right.
That fucking freaked me out.
That's not befitting and it's not right.
I'm sorry.
Alright. Anyway, um...
Oh yeah, so, uh, all this is to say that after Leo had carved a significant enough portion of the land above for himself,
he took to space, where he could finally create his pleasure palace and include all the toys Leo the Collector,
before he was King Leo, has ever collected and wishes to be enjoyed by all for an astronomical
fee, political favor, or blackmail. Or in the rare case of you three, a combination of a
sizable chunk of change you got from your heist, but overall at a discount because Leo
actually kind of likes you guys. Though, since he's become king, you can't really get in
touch with him. He's sort of doing his own thing.
Ghoster. A little bit.
Still around in the future. Ghosting. Thought they'd have abolished it by then.
I thought it would have been criminally punished by death or worse
Yeah, we'll talk through what's in the pleasure palace as we explore it right now
You guys are in your hotel room in the resort the ten seasons
There's ten seasons on guys on planet. Okay list them winter spring summer fall salt pepper paprika
And then cumin and monsoon season
I thought about this.
God, he's good.
Wow.
Yeah, um, so yeah, you guys are in your hotel room.
Let's see where you guys are, actually.
Okay.
Sorry for anyone who's listening.
Go to patreon.com and check out a video from us.
Because I made my own character.
That's right, start over here.
I did.
Check that out, if you can even see it.
It's so small.
Put that up to the camera.
That's right, it looks beautiful.
Beautiful, holy crap Patrick Yoda. I made him out of my old Mike windscreen and a grogu that I bought did you?
Wait you dressed like him today. Yeah, I did purpose. I'm a purpose Wow
I'm whoa look. Oh my god. I didn't even process that
Incredible high effort yep, this is unreal. I put so much. I have so much super glue
He got an outfit to my finger wow I'm proud of you, man
I built all this yeah
and I wore a costume.
[laughter]
Yeah, okay, cool.
So we got Patrick Yoda.
But where is he?
Yeah, so this is, right now,
for you guys to know, this whole area is just your room.
This is just your room.
Oh, okay.
Sick room. It's huge.
It's fucking badass.
It's basically like the holodeck, so we have to just say whatever.
Come on, do something on it.
I'll add some shit here.
okay
after
well done
yeah
let's do some sense
well this is sick
i never thought that this would happen
well see guys want
uh... it's your picture for the way it would have been okay so this is my
career
this is my corner here in the barracks like order that's yours and that's
cameras is what we're doing now this is the
i'm gonna tell you room
unless you do some really weird this is going to be your home base
for the campaign so if you wanna if you wanna
we're going to have this sort of monolith
in your room that's my pillar
you can't put stuff in my room i don't want anything though i don't want anything
yeah you guys have a suite yeah that's what your computer you're like odo from deep space
ninety you're like a demon with a computer in your back
this is my stuff do you have to do stuff for your demon though?
i don't know let me see him
i haven't even seen my character where is your character
i mean i was i thought we were going in order to get a good look at what's going
on in your send the uh... okay blowtoss
okay all your guys your guys so this is actually what i want to the store today
i get my guy and actually was able to find i didn't know i think that i'll be
able to find this but actually found officially licensed u_s_ army
grinch hunter
figurine wallacy he has a little he has a who knows and who whiskers and his
his gun says he says grinch gone on it which i thought was crazy 'cause that's
the name of my character's gun. It's really cool too. I mean I'm really happy with this
toy that I was able to find at the store. It was a dollar tree. And as you can see,
look at that holographic sticker that says "official licensee". You got that for a dollar?
And this was a dollar. So how are you going to fit that motherfucker in that little ass
room? My guy's big. If that's the size of a Yoda, this is the size of a guy. Come on
I'll take that.
Come on now.
But I went out while I was at the store too.
We're going to play fast and loose a bit with the sizes as we'll soon learn.
You were at the...
So you just got everything at Dollar Tree.
What else did you get there?
Yeah, well I just got two things.
I got one toy for myself, but I knew Caleb was busy building all this stuff, so I decided
to get him a toy for his.
That's so kind of you.
Yeah, and I was like, "Oh, I really, really need it."
I just want to say one thing before you go any further.
I was in Manhattan for three hours looking for that.
I was in Dollar Tree for four hours deciding what DVDs to buy and I actually didn't buy any.
Ah, that's a buffer.
Damn, because they had some good ones there.
They do have some really good ones.
But I did get Kayla.
I couldn't find...
I had to get cold.
You know what my character is?
That's Peppa the ballet dancer.
But my character is supposed to be a demon.
I brought a whole set of like...
We already showed this one so this one is kind of permanent.
I showed you all the ones that I brought earlier.
I was stressed out.
I was thinking about all the...
I can't even hold it.
I was thinking about all the different shit.
I was thinking about how to make him look super cool.
Come on, I had other shit on my mind.
I was showing you all of the things I brought.
No, you know what?
Hey, Cameron...
Mine also comes with a motorcycle.
Mine maybe because I haven't getting to talk about this at all mine actually has a music system
Wheels it's got a music boom box, okay, so Peppa Pig
Maybe is actually kind of cool and also I have guns you can have that I just recently got can I have some you can?
Have this one
But basically
Ray William Johnson will be like around here. Yeah, I would say that's kind of his sweet
We
important so I hope I hope it isn't the arrangement of this but uh... okay cool
but the front door is going to be to your suite is going to be over here okay which
does matter if you have to go in and out of this room
uh... allegedly
uh...
and uh... cool yours doing a little unboxing video
this is cute this is very cute
okay my room's all set up
I really like your room thank you this is my computer my secondary computer and
this and this is my monitor
and so i go over here and i do technological hacking against my
enemies
so my guys in his michael motorcycle hanger
uh...
yes i think i think i'm going to have to
here can you zoom in on that camera just a little bit
this will be a is the super glue over there also
whereas i'm not giving superglue
while we have a live recording
okay
I could have just superglued all of our guns into the hands, but...
No, you wouldn't be able to do that.
Yeah, we'll do that later.
You'll have to be too close with it, Kim.
Alright, the gun, I will use that one day.
Continue.
Okay.
Thank you so much, Cameron.
Thank you so much for my character.
So what have you guys been?
You guys have been kind of like, just comatose, basically.
You've been so depressed that New Sullivan was taken, stolen away from you.
I can barely even get up.
Yeah, and so and so finally we're all we're all so sad
We're all
Voices in a while we have a little conversation
Fuck yeah, I'm so fucking depressed I hate my life
And then your voice sounds like
My face is in the ground
Knock knock knock at the front door
Who is it who's there?
fuck off
Hello, sirs
Here are the towels you requested
What's up, butler inside of which no? I'm just I'm just a person who works at the hotel
it's
the role of the role of the packer or
uh... that's not what we're going to go
school
ships which is why i was just a little bit
shes
fucking nightmare
alright
we won't
you're going to do it though you know you should look at the man should play
with the toys are you sorry it's okay
yeah i i don't attack this guy
what do you want
And why do you stand so fruity?
Look at that.
[Laughter]
I can't help the way God made me, sir.
God didn't make that.
He's got scoliosis.
True.
You don't remember that about him?
No.
I don't either.
I don't even remember who this is.
I don't remember the last couple of fucking months.
I'm just one of the attendants at the hotel, not an important character.
That's Mr. Attendant.
Mr. Attendant is my name. How did you know?
Because I have a good relationship with you.
That's right.
we do have a good relationship rub how far back to okay just rub it you'll bet i
paid you to rub my my back in my thighs it's not good
you know i do that for free you don't have to pay him and i pay him because
he's good at it
here you'll tells you requested along with the various candy treats you wanted
inside of them
also have a message from a one but in the croaks
she works for the king's so i'll take a look if i were you
and uh...
He presents a small UMD cartridge, which projects the image of a royal guard, a member of Leo's
Royal Guard.
(laughter)
Okay, what does he look like?
He looks sort of like this.
Okay.
But he's also decked out.
He looks like a pop star.
He's got a space marine armor.
Is this a Roblox guy?
Yeah, it is.
Oh, wow.
of all of her uh... leo's royal guardia roblox guys
while some of them will be other kinds of guys but that's the main kind of guard
on a new type of guy roblox type
and i know that
sunday greetings belit belinda croaks head attendant of the king of leo
the magnificent has requested an audience with patrick you know the
blowtoss piece in ray william johnson
she says it is urgent and she'd have you come to the world district immediately
he uh... the u_n_ deep slots out like she said
three tickets and uh... like like uh... they're made of like let me grab that
man you know
these should allow you to do
these should allow you to have a little my friends
to the royal
to the royal district on the city loop
uh... the city loop trains so
just come straight away and all that
I didn't decide if he was British or not.
This will now self-destruct and it explodes.
The guy explodes?
Well, the UMD cartridge he was coming out of.
Oh!
Oops, I shot it!
That's why it exploded.
So you guys have been summoned by Belinda Crokes, who's the head attendant to the king,
about an urgent matter.
So if you guys want to start going there, because that's kind of a wrap.
Even if Belinda Crokes tells me to do it.
Oh!
I don't fucking care.
I should put this gun to my head.
And pull the trigger and kill me.
You should line it up so it shoots me in the fucking head too.
Okay, let's line it up and kill all three of us with a single bullet guys.
So who, so you have the Grinch gun so if you want to roll the tackle.
Oh and I fell down.
Oh.
Stand up straight you fucking hammerhead.
I'm so drunk because of my painful depression.
depression another knock at the door oh I'm saved hello hi I'm the god from
before oh could you please wait if you were here why did you use the UMD thing
I thought it would look cool I really did I thought it would be sort of like
who's that what do you want I really do need you to come well okay we'll go I'll
I'll explain, hold on.
It's concerning playtime.
The killer who stole away your boy.
Why are you saying that so-
How do you already know that he did that?
The king knows many things.
So he knows who playtime is.
No he don't.
I feel like I've posed a whole-
For the rest of this episode, subscribe to patreon.com/contestdepartments
(audience laughing)