[MUSIC]
Last time on Gun City and the Temple of Tepenguin of Doom.
Our heroes awoke from a horrendous crash into the soy wastes
after narrowly escaping the Kinbone officers in Gadsven.
Greeting them were their adventurer pals Rex and Marie Stain
who nursed them back to health using the warm and voluminous yeti skin.
Leading them to the Wendig Station, the gang performed their tried and true method
of pretending to be arcade game repairmen to sneak on to the first class cabin.
Sullivan, stocking coach, befriended Leroy Peanutbutter and his 299 mice wives
and the one human one, and his larger hobo community of rejected Ken Bones and Robins.
Sullivan was asked to sneak up front and bring back real food for these less fortunate, and he accepted the task more or less.
Meanwhile, the party ran into their old friend Gary C. Enterprise, who introduced them to the newfound wealth they received from the cold dogs and hot soda business.
Also, they finally met Snoochie Boochies, who it turns out is the last of the Tamagotchis, and wishes to restore his people, using the N-word pass.
boys agreed to help him and trick their benefactor, Leo the Collector, into receiving a phony
pass after they get the real one for Snoochy Boochies.
Finally, after the Ken Bone officers tried and tried to kidnap the boys, Sullivan the
Frog's terrible stealth abilities led to their undoing and an ambush that may end their lives
once and for all.
So yeah, let's roll for initiative.
Oh, I have not rolled, huh?
Alright, I will roll right now.
Can I roll again?
Hell no!
No.
Damn.
Fuck you.
That's yours.
I got a 7.
That is Sullivan's initiative.
Oh my god, Sullivan also got a 1.
Sullivan and Patrick both got 1s.
Not our finest rolls.
That's because I'm impersonating him. I'm doing everything he's doing.
Let's see how... Alright, well, Snoochy Boochies did well.
Alright, so let me just crank out this order here, and then we'll get started.
Well, okay, yeah, and then the Ken Bones. Okay, yeah. Alright, cool.
Regardless, Snoochy Boochies is gonna go first.
So you see the Ken bones dive in and Stoogey Boogey sort of like looks around and surveys the situation
And he like looks to you guys. He says are they after you?
No
They're after
They're after you. Hold on. Oh, hold on. I could have all right there after
shit
Yeah, they're after shit
That's why they're running towards the bathroom. Mm-hmm
Okay, they seem like they're after you
That's up for I don't know why they would be I
Can't remember anything we did wrong me neither didn't we?
Wait Sullivan there after you cuz you came to first class
Yeah, what do you do hey, I'm gonna run as soon as it's my turn stop
Okay
Why are you sounded like me now? I don't remember
Okay, well in that case, I guess all we need to do is sit tight and he just doesn't take his turn he just chills
Okay, I think I'm gonna stop being Sullivan real quick he's got a wait until Sullivan's turn and he'll run away
okay, and
now it is
Who got a you got a 17 right? Yeah, but toss it's your turn
Why are the Ken, but what I don't remember what's going on.
Yeah.
I have no clue.
What's that?
What are the Ken bones actually after us?
I don't.
Yes.
Yeah, they're so so they they came to the like train station like
outside their jurisdiction to chase you because of like what you
guys did.
Oh, the shake up because of the chase sequence.
Yeah, okay.
You guys murdered several bones and defiled one of them that was
shaped like a ramp.
We just used him.
It's not defilement.
Yeah, you don't defile your micro.
That's not what his therapist called it, okay?
He's dealing with this in his own time.
He's fine.
Alright, well, I guess...
How many are there? There's two or three.
So, there's three that you can see, but roll a perception check.
Okay. There's a guy right here.
So there's more than three, is what I'm getting from this.
this
That's what he's doing.
You got a 23.
Okay.
Yeah.
So blowtoss you kind of survey the situation and you're looking
sort of like up towards the further cars and back towards
the water cars and you're realizing that like they're not
going to stop coming like there's a lot of them on this
train.
All right, and the three you're seeing here are the three who
could fit in the car into violence.
How far are we to getting to our destination?
Yeah, that's a good question.
So you're probably about half an hour away from Wutown station.
By foot? By train.
How long by foot?
Probably about like three hours,
but then also you have to deal with the cold of the soy wastes.
so you take damage over time.
What are you going to do jump off the train?
Well, I mean, yeah, what are there are infinite Ken bones
that are going to come and kill are they infinite not
infinite.
How would you know that there were countless or something?
There's just a lot.
They're not going to stop coming is what I said.
You said they're not going to stop coming.
That means infinite.
Well, you know, at a certain point what that means.
Yeah, wait to run out of how how how far are we?
or three hours away by foot
we need to which frankly is is a crazy that there's only a half an hour by
traded three hours by foot is a crazy said there's only
uh... it's a very slow train
he said that this is a three can fit in it right now right
yes i would like a show a little for
with and we have we need to shrink the train
that's a good idea
all i have got i agree it's barricade the doors
so nobody else none of the others can get in
i'm sure they'll they'll play of people waiting for us we get a guy i i a
was on my turn
but i have a lot of you tell me what
tom i'm gonna do i'm gonna nail sullivan to the
opening of the door
uh...
are there any like loose planks are the benches on the investigation check to
see what you can see
for this will be mostly return though by the way uh...
yet so you can see that their that the windows you could
break the windows
for sure and in can climb up that way
well i thought i would i think i'm there's this place also over to the
right side over here as well do you mean floorboards cameron
i'd know i want to build something
i don't wanna if i want to get out of the train and his camera cameras got
fortnight of the funding break
if i want to get out of the train i could teleport out i don't need to
i'm here in the world out and get i mean reals outside of the train
but take some boards and i i did i teleport to the top of the trip
yeah and then within thirty feet
and then
you you can easily
stay up there for thirty minutes you wouldn't take you would take damage
yeah okay way i i i grab
i
i get i can't i can't get out to do it you have to do it like i like one at a
a
Okay, you guys teleport on the roof of the train and immediately it's like
*fwoosh*
Just like you're blowing by as this like icy cold soy just like
Starts hitting your face the second you appear on it.
Um, both of you roll uh, athletics check.
*laughter*
I had- by the way, I did not consent to this teleportation.
He did not ask me at all.
17.
*laughter*
I got a 9.
Okay, Cam, you uh, so, Cam, you like,
do most of the teleporting and uh you know uh or blow toss i should say right
William Johnson you have a moment to like get your footing
um but but blow toss you like just kind of like
and like kind of slip bang your head and like fly back a car but
with a uh with a roll dexterity saving throw
16 and you managed to grab on to the edge of another car uh you teleport
the
Is it yeah, you take three damage from that by the way you blow toss
Yeah, you're fine. Ray William Johnson. It's just cold as shit cuz you're a demon
But you're okay
Yeah, you could teleport back down and that's your turn. I'll say
Basically, you just like did a couple checks. We'll consider the teleport your movement
You should lower your techno slime points as well -
Why or do we have every time? Oh, no, we don't you just tell I just get to do it as much as I want you really
I fucked up probably the biggest balance fuck up. You've ever one of the biggest
Yeah, I just sometimes you just get distracted I forgot about this in the gun city campaign the first one I
Became allergic to the Sun. Oh, yeah, I just completely forgot. Okay. Do you should I start being allergic to the
I want that thing.
That was it was a different guy who was allergic to the sun. Right, right. It's your twin. Uh, I know I think
Maybe it's something carry around maybe it's like a
Psychosomatic thing where I didn't re until I remember that i'm allergic to the sun. I don't actually feel the effects
Okay, but I did I have now remembered
Okay. Yeah, so we'll deal with that too. Okay, I do take damage from that. Um, just try it back
Yeah
uh... and now it is the can bones turn so they're gonna run up
uh... thereby passing solvent now i mean they
they're gonna
they'll deal with him later
uh... but you're not here anymore
uh...
uh... so they're gonna go after you patrick you know that i can bones
there uh... to get their their little can bone but times
uh...
and they just get it he gets a crit one he literally falls prone
he tries to hit you any just like
with so hard he spins around and falls on his ass.
He's on the ground.
So he didn't do it.
So me just saying he didn't do that.
It worked this time, yeah.
And now this other one's gonna try to do the same thing.
He's like, "I'll help you, brother! We're all brothers!"
And he's gonna try also.
And that time he did hit.
Oh, how much?
Let's see, he's not that strong.
What's the damage?
Oh, boy.
Yeah, he does four damage.
So he just, like, conks you on the head.
with like a nightstick.
Fuck!
Which I think Ken Bone has in real life.
He does. He puts it up pregnant women's butts.
And now this guy's coming,
and he's gonna go after Snoochie Boochies,
and Snoochie Boochies is like,
"I think they are after you."
"Now, I think that these what's happening."
And as he attacks Snoochie Boochies,
which that just misses, Snoochie Boochies very easily,
like, deftly dodges out of the way.
And now that they're all sort of like crowding you guys,
we see a couple more
show up
uh...
uh... but only three could fit in at a time
well no three can come into the entrance at a time
i told you to shrink the train
don't worry patrick i'm coming for you on this for you on top of the train
uh...
as last month okay
i don't think i want that
i think it's gonna happen with the lights out
now
it is and well you know the problem is the problem is they're all in the train
right
yeah this is the latest that this is the new trolley problem if you can't
you know it's your turn though patrick you know so you have you have the the
floor uh...
i have every xbox game in my inventory i'd just remembered
uh... and in our neighborhood repairman outfit
i can i just say no sometimes
do you have to stare at xbox on the trip
and then what would you do what would you even do with that
tell me
i don't know if you have to tell you
is there an xbox on the road he twenty if it's more of a ten days of xbox on the
train
there is only a p_s_ five of the trade are the book okay
uh... and that's a mold tech
the
you could just break a window pretty easily. Climbing to the top, yeah, you should roll
athletics though. Okay, I'm gonna, well, what if I hoverboard to the top?
Uh, you could do it with advantage then, because you are kind of like, have like a little bit of
like a magnetism mechanism there. All right, then I'm doing that. Do it. 16. Nice, yeah,
you managed to like sort of ride the sides of the train and like skate yourself up to the top.
And now roll another athletics check to stay like steady on top of it. 21. Yeah, nice, yeah,
Yeah, you just managed to like chill up there very easily
Can I break waiting? It's like hitting your face
Bring snitchy bootches with me
Or am I - am I too far into it?
I would say you're too far into at this point because also also stitchy booties will be able to get there probably
Okay, wait, then I throw I throw like a rope down
Do you have a rope?
Have every click to you just do you have that?
Every Xbox game. Can I Daisy chain them together with a piece? I have my well
I can I have a rope I can teleport I can tell right. All right, never mind then. Okay
Now it is Sullivan the Frog's third
Can I yell something to Sullivan on on?
His chair you're nearby. Yeah, I want it Sullivan get on my back like a backpack
Okay, and he like you watch him hops for the first time like a frog like he's freaking out
Your back immediately
Okay, I hear Cameron say his first leap and I poke my head through the glass and I go oh my god
Oh my god, my PSP and I'm Jake trying to take
Solvent is just like cooing
Imagine just like a ps4 share image
of a small flurry in the middle of a hop.
Just getting auto posted to your like 18+ twitter.
[Laughter]
Okay yeah, okay cool. So yeah, now it's back
to the top of the order. It was good thinking scrambling
to get ahead of that. I didn't have a turn.
Yeah well you're on top of the train. You don't need to. You're right. Oh yeah!
You didn't, I'm sorry, you should go.
Okay, I build an igloo.
Oh, that one looks like he likes building.
[Laughter]
Okay, I'll let you try to build a soy igloo.
I build a beautiful igloo.
What should I roll?
I really want, I was so sad that I didn't get to do my turn.
I feel very bad, I'm sorry about that.
I was like, I'm going to do the best, and by the way, I get advantage on this because you forgot me.
because you forgot me. Yeah, I feel like you should do.
Let's consider it. You'll do it. I guess it's a is it a nature check?
Like yeah, we get precedent on that every time patches forget something we get advantage on doing it.
I'm basically we said that as a rule that is okay. All right. I'm rolling nature.
I think that's fair that holds me accountable. Okay advantage a nice.
Yeah, you build a pretty solid igloo for a train that's going like,
you know as fast as it's going and like as you're you have to like build it
Rebuild it as it's like blowing away, but eventually you solidify it you have like the base of a new glue
I'll say nice and I'm getting there pretty cool. You could do in six seconds. Pretty cool
Yeah, it looks good
Um, it's a good glue you got there. Thank you. You got you got room for one more
You know what? I'll add a second wing. Oh
Next turn coming up. Don't forget it patches. I won't forget it. You'll add a second wig to the igloo
So the the Ken bones are getting quite befuddled by this and then it down in the in the bottom of the train blow toss and
Blow toss you hear some commotion coming from the further back of the train cars, but it doesn't sound like
The Ken bones and then you see burst through
the door
Leroy peanut butter with his his
299 mice in a bag
uh... in his way his wife abigail by a sign she's got a rolling pin like women
do
and uh...
uh... we were peanut butter
uh... looks at sullivan
he says now you know you you did a good job yes i will do not tell you what
you distracted them guards you know i i i i i i i i i you know
you we second part of of taking up fifteen of the seventeen train cars on
this your training
now they got cops in the end of the one aside this year train all
scottie archery now
bizarre trade now does belong to the whole bowl was easy although like
can bone pobo's like screaming
from the back
and uh...
he's like
and we don't know we'll make a new society in this train one
one of a my name a leroy peanut butter
and these are not
two hundred wives he said swinging his bag of my surrounded just like knocks
this can go and clear out on the ground
uh... so he enters a turn order now as well
uh... you just see that there's a way
as one of those fights
partially yeah and so you see
you see that there's just like now a full out brawl
uh... there's just like
can bone cops versus can bone hobos
uh... total class war just like happening on this train
in snowpiercer fashion his uh... with the picture for this kevin smith
yes
his last time i can describe them in the i'd and and and can was like that sounds
like Kevin Smith and I was like, yeah, I guess I made a Kevin
Smith who talks like a jive turkey. And so now at the top
of the order, Tsuchibuchi sort of like like takes a cue and
definitely like hops on top of the train.
Plotos, it's your turn. You're with Sullivan. You can tell
we're up there. There's a there's a there's a Ken Bone
right next to me, right? Yeah. Okay. I look him in the eyes
and i say
have you seen the who that hides from guys who are gay and then i teleport to
the top of the tree
i should i'm gay and uh... then uh...
but can't go to i've my it's just a little bit all the other
it
i don't know
well for a little bit boats in the cockpit and boats stop fighting for a
little bit all just stop it is just a test to go
I mean, it's fine.
I just got to deal with it now.
It's sort of a new thing.
Yeah, there are no pregnant guys.
So yeah, I poke my head down from the roof and I'm looking through the window and I have a one tear rolling to my face.
That's so it's so beautiful when someone finds themselves.
And yes, you guys end up on top of the train pretty easily.
and here are the commotion going on for the so you knew we're going to the top
and you know you do you do
and uh...
you're all able to sort of hold your ground for a little bit
and then uh... uh... you see some of the combat strike climb out
to the top to get you guys but they just quickly just get like fucking
and i think it is like an old on
which is not athletic enough
uh... but then uh...
from the distance you see a speck
uh...
the and you hear like a a jet engine it gets louder and louder and louder
and as you look over you realize it's some sort of like giant mac
uh...
and
use notice that it's shaped a lot like
josh gap
uh... and
policy
it's the king dad inside of the mac
and
he looks at all of you
And he screams at you through like a megaphone.
[clears throat]
I threatened my son with an unfriendly spanking,
and he told me everything.
The tournament?
Robbing the gadfly?
Arcade repairmen?
And now,
you've blown up our caves and murdered my Ken Bones.
Do you have any idea what you've done?
You've brought naughtiness and shame and
icky yucky gun city perversions into my settlement.
There should only be musical theater and improv.
is that so much to ask for?
you're a donzo, all of you
you're all a donzo
and uh, he uh
takes out like his gattling
I have an idea
guns, he's gattling guns
I have a feeling we're just gonna have to fight him
well if you can try it, I wanna hear the rest of the description
I'm interested in ideas
I know, I'm just letting you guys know I have an idea
thank you for letting us know
he takes out his gattling, I mean that was mostly it
what's the idea?
I
Agandum, Agandum.
Or like, even Gadleon?
Even Gad--Neon Gaddesis?
Gaddesis.
It's somewhere.
Yeah.
What about like, Pat Labor, like Gad Labor?
What a--uh, Neon--
That's another mech thing.
Neon--
Mechad--Mechagadzilla.
Oh!
Mechagadzilla?
That's it.
Mechagadzilla.
I was thinking Neon Gad--Neon Gaddesis, Olaf Galeon.
No, no, no.
Jet Gaddwar.
Yeah, he's like writing all of these down.
He's like...
In the cockpit, you see him like this.
That's good. That's good.
Yeah, so now that we gave you all these awesome names, you should probably just like...
Hold on, I got an idea.
Let us go...
Wait, Mr. Gadd.
Um...
What do you want?
Okay, you guys, I've got...
Guys, huddle up. Huddle up in the igloo.
We seize is huddling hold on we're huddling but you can see you
Just so cold. We got to get close to each other. Yeah, just give us a second, you know, you know penguins
Yes, I know penguins that we're doing that what they do
Yep, okay, there's a penguin shit over here don't lie to your belly
I like when they I'm sorry. I like when they slide on their bells and you be quiet for a second. Just shut up
I mean, okay, let me fucking talk. I'm sorry
Okay, you guys
What if we did a song and dance number for him? Oh
Oh, no
It's what he likes he does like that if we can prove that we have the music in our hearts
Maybe we might
We might reach the little man inside that nasty robot. What what song and dance did you have in mind?
I was thinking we could vote on it. What about Kiki? Do you love me?
We could do the tootsie slide
We could we could do that we could we could do a Kiki challenge for him it could do a barbershop quartet
That's also good of us in Sullivan. That's a great idea. Do you need me to sing?
Yes, he sounds like Christopher Lambert. I'm warning you now good.
Are you done? You're all familiar with the lyrics to in my feelings, right?
Yeah, what role history check, you know, in your feelings, the ancient bard song.
I got a 17. I got a 24.
Okay, that's pretty good. Let's see if Sullivan knows your feelings.
I hope it's a good...
We all have PSPs that have Rap Genius on them too.
That's true.
Okay, yeah. Here's... Actually, you know what you could do?
Ray William Johnson, since you're a computer, you could...
I'll let you try to...
Can I print it out?
Yeah, figure out a way to get the lyrics here beam it from your head something that you like. Do I have a printer?
No, yes, you're like, yeah, okay
Copies of in my feelings by Drake
Hey, yeah, we're by unknown. It's been so long. We don't
Wait, what are you? Why is he printing? What's your trust me? You're gonna like this. You're gonna be blown away
Okay, okay trap trap money money money
I'm trying to keep you till you love me but I'm far from loving you
I know where my summer's been staying
And I'm down for you always, KB
Are you in this room?
Are you riding?
I'm down for you always, KB.
Marvin's room, are you riding?
So you'll definitely--
I mean, you get the idea, right?
Yeah.
That's pretty--
Marvin's room.
All right, everyone roll.
[LAUGHTER]
Performance check.
Three.
Saw the 19.
19.
I got a 17.
OK, and Sullivan.
Let's see how Sullivan does.
Sullivan just got a nat 20.
Yes!
the
no we've got a net twenty-one dot what do you got a quick
dad sort of like uh... the king gets a look so overall view
after this insane performance of i guess a drake medley it became sort of the
middle
uh... schizophrenic drake medley
and uh...
he sees mech arm the kind point towards all of them
and he's like
kid
you have something
i can't believe it
was for all
that brought him
haven't seen that
in years since
any sort of looks
down and looks up he says
it's my great great great great great great great great great great great
great grandfather
josh
you have what he had
you really think so yes
Yes, please you you must come back to Gadsfield
We can have you sing and dance with all of us
And Sullivan sort of turns to you guys as guys. I think this might be my big break
I mean, I never wanted to do this before shut up, dude
No, ask him ask him if we can work out a deal
Do you want okay?
To tell him you'll go back to Gad's oh with him after we finish our adventure
I know but I didn't trust Sullivan to come up with the terms of it. I was gonna say I was gonna offer him some buttons
I was getting
Kind of glad you interrupted
Okay, okay, that's the deal that's totally the deal we can after our adventure
We're gonna I'm your manager now Sullivan after your adventure. We're gonna have a three record deal
We're gonna go we got the money
Yeah, look
Look after the event look all charges dropped on us. Yeah, and
Okay, okay hold on
We can have a farm with rabbits that too you can take care of the rabbits
Basically, we're trying to get the best deal that we can out of this
Okay, mr. Mr. King, sorry, dr. King
Thanks for remembering my doctorate in musicology, what is it my manager my managers?
They have a deal for you, I would very much like to intern in your kingdom, which is what I think you're offering
But but but we have to we have to do an adventure first
Hmm and
Do you guys want to try to talk to you because then otherwise this is this is the persuasion check
Persuasion I - one let me say zero
Okay, yeah
Okay, um
And you can fuck him
you
reminds you of your dad, 21.
(laughing)
- No, that was perception, fuck.
- That's the same as the same bonus.
- You're right, it's the same bonus.
- Oh my God.
(laughing)
- You see him pause, and he's just like
a solid minute long pause.
- Okay.
and uh...
and then um...
we see some
uh...
okay
and uh...
he had to do is john
uh... in the air
says her
looking to kill you guys but i can't ignore our talent like that
weekend also part of the deal was all the charges are dropped and you're no
longer met us
well-treated dot
and i'll be mad at you for the rest of my life
now we're going to have a rock code three inches deep and subsolvent dude
it
and
salomon
this is a
it's always like
got into
yet he uh... he flies away i mean
got
to put the song in. I'm singing over it. Are you writing? Hey Sullivan, listen man, that
was all a big joke. That's not going to happen after the adventure. I just don't want to get
fucked by a gad. Well, wait, wait, hold on. Sullivan, are you a virgin? I personally hate
figuring out whether or not that's canon. We could have totally fucking gotten you some
pussy on the way here man. Didn't we? Didn't we already do it? He fucked a penguin. Oh yeah
that was savage. No that was not, I did not want to do that. You didn't really fuck her,
you kind of just ate her out if I remember. I tripped and fell. And then you see Stoogey
Boogey goes, you ate out the sacred penguin? Is that bad? Yeah you should have, he's a total
the
Okay, I'll keep that in mind that the frog eats out the penguin
They didn't I didn't I didn't want to I was just trying to talk to her I mean, I don't know
Whatever that fucking Drake dick dog dancer
And the fight below the commotion below you here it's sort of settled down and when you hear like a yeah
like a cheer
And then you hear
the classical hobo music playing
Like below which is just in mirror songs
Just blasting below
Yeah, you guys end up back on the you guys want to stay on top of the train. You'll take some damage
Let's get back in the train are the Ken bones still angry at us now that no they're they're like retreating back. Okay. Yeah
Yeah, I teleport us back into the train
and
But yeah, you guys are back on the train
You see Kersey Enterprises is a I tell you here is the Enterprise to the top of the train and then come
He was no
Of giving everyone hot soda cold dogs
Yeah, we do need it. Yeah, he needs to yes the money
Top of the train for like half a second and then back
He just vomits
enough time to give Caleb
Or ray william johnson hot a hot soda and a hot and a cold dog. Mm-hmm
Here you go. I use my cold dog as an igloo piece
It's the door handle
Yeah
Very advanced igloo that I'm building. Yeah. So yeah, you take you to while you're up there wait, but I drink my hot soda
So it's a balance. Oh, yeah, I'll let it be half damage. Can you take the drink the hot soda?
How much did I say the soy?
Damages you guys how easy a negative damages use zero. I think I said I have double day
I think it's three for me right normal. It was three for you. Oh, yeah, I know what I rolled. Okay, let me just roll it again
Okay
But you take regular damage now because you're guzzling a hot sauce. You only take three damage. Okay, I see you guys
Once I build my igloo, am I safe?
Yeah.
The rest of you guys are partying on board with the hobos who've taken over the train.
You see Leroy Peanutbutter is teaching Sullivan how to do a little hobo dance.
And you see the Ken Bones and the robots are hanging out, eating hot soda and drinking cold dogs, I guess,
is the rest of what was happening in my mouth just now.
And yeah, and the train sort of slows to a stop and you arrive in
You arrive at who town and you see Leroy peanut butter go up to you guys before you leave. He says thank you for all your help
Yeah, yeah, you don't done. Don't you clean these trains out now? It's gonna be the hobo strains now
There's no way nobody can take these trains from us
Let me tell you we're gonna be gonna be eating something other than synthetic spaghetti
Oh for the rest of our lives will have some more of these hot saunas and cold dogs
any any vanishes you guys still here like through the roof just a muffled like
and yeah you guys you guys file off the train see a pretty impressive igloo on
top of one of the cars it just like the second we pull into the station just
is
that
the
you guys are you guys I got off the train and it's like a little you know it's
like a train station so it's a little walkaways - but not too far because this
is again like the furthest out in the soy wastes the soy wastes are like you know
really new territory as you can remember from here like you know the frozen waste
of soy the soy wastes it's just like very new not a lot of this touch it so
So you're pretty nearby this town, which as you sort of start to approach it, you see
like sort of soy farmers who are all Hoos.
They're all like Hoovian soy farmers.
And they harvest the stuff and they sell it back to Wendig Express Tycoons and suppliers
for that.
They sort of give you, they look at you with a little quizzical curiosity.
And as you get a little bit closer, you see "Welcome to Who Town, not Whoville" in big
bright letters that stands over a small archway, sort of, like a little gate.
And you see "Who Adults" and "Who Children".
You see a few normals wandering around, maybe a frog or two, but generally mostly Who's.
You see the standard bread lines for the legally required poor population any township needs
trade with gun city as well as some like modest homes and shops the style of the place unlike
the cube like sort of like neo amazon you know modern cadsville this is like kind of more primitive
and angular but it has like sort of like a techno mystical kind of vibe like like like they clearly
tried to like cobble this together did their best to like recreate a who a who ville kind of place
right? So there's iron, metal outcroppings that jut out, and those are kind of shaped like a Dr. Seuss house, but they're apartment complexes.
And then you have some more neon bulbs that create kind of a Christmassy flair, despite all the harsher angles from all the buildings.
You have some more classical like pliable material that makes the like who houses maybe like just trying to recreate that feeling
And you even see like, you know way in the back of the of the you know, there's homes or shops and there's even a Dematrix 2 pod
So it's like very recent very new for them
But it's like a very exciting attraction that was added next to the soy processing facility and community housing area
And so yeah, you see this you're in this sort of small town that's that's a that's like
very new and yeah you walk through you're here so yeah you have to go find the
the Oracle which snitchy-boochie says we must find the Oracle he lives towards
the other side of the town we can start walking there now unless you need to
rest or something we should probably rest right I think at 10 HP wait is has our
maximum health gone back up now since we're not in the sideways no you're
your
the
I'm glad I have a long rest.
Don't do a long rest.
If you do a long rest, that's a different amount of time.
Oh.
So if you do a long rest, that's like...
So wait, how many dice do I have now?
Is that what you said?
Let's see.
I'm at 16. I'll roll one more and then I'll have no hit dice left.
Yeah.
I'm at 27.
You have 5 hit dice left, so you can spend all that.
You can spend as much of that as you need.
Actually, I'll spend one hit dice just to get back up to 4.
the
Okay, seven.
Nice.
And then Sullivan will get his health back as well.
But yeah, you guys just sort of rest in the town square area
taking some of the who sites some of the news sort of like it
down in the middle of the street.
Yeah, they sort of look at you quizzically especially blow
toss because you're a who and you're like a new who and people
and
I think that was because I was a cool guy.
No, you're just not.
The who thing.
This is the first time I've ever seen another who.
Yeah, is it?
I think it is actually.
Yeah.
So yeah, I'm just going like.
Oh, I'm just freaking out.
Mommy, what's wrong with that one?
I don't know, honey.
Let's just keep going.
Yeah.
disease to keep it he comes over and says
you are meeting your people for the first time
you should be glad
how did you know that alone
i could help i think that the exact way that you are well it
it's also screaming unseen by people
well yeah that too
that was also helpful
yeah so yeah you guys are you guys can continue making your way to the oracle
uh...
Walking through the town, yada yada yada.
You come across sort of like the oracles place who towns or who
villages all those places.
They all have like an Oracle that tries to tap into the mystical
Lorax sort of powers and and use it and they sort of help guide
the village or guide the town, you know, wherever they are.
And so this one has an Oracle just as any of them would but
this one is an Oracle that is in the soy wastes, which is pretty
rare so at least what Tsuchibuji explains to you he says I have been looking for
the temple for a long time however I until now thanks to your smart
investigative and archaeological work now I finally know that if we talk to
this Oracle he should be able to locate it this is this is going to be this is
going to be good. I have a good feeling about this. Please, let's go.
And you guys walk into this sort of modest home and you immediately realize that it's
sort of different from the other ones. It's not as like, you know, gun city light kind
of vibe. It's much more earthy, much more mystical. And you walk in and you see the...
i love this guy
here at the front of the used in so many cases of the kids that zombie right
it's not pretty to back with you know he's so he's so good and he was in
something else what else was he in
ideas and we're going to rethink
i think you know the guards and we're down
so he's one of the same guys one of the best i got their own
but i was like i'm it's related
to the other character
uh... yes so he's this is guy there this just giant invalid just steering
blankly
ahead
uh... homes
and uh... uh...
he served by as you all
and you're coming in the says
what you see
it's a good giant
like blank minded to
he says again what you hear see
christmas
but that christmas
and holidays
are you are you mock me
i'm trying to speak your language
are you here see oracle
christmas yes no we're here to see joe
uh...
there's no joke
only a lot of
he says what he can't even let the company i know that would work on this
is it
i'm here to see d_c_'s
all that now
it was all
who was these
these knots
or should i uh... it were here to see the
the
the who
yellow
the whole world is the oracle and the other
before the role in this guy any
he knocks twice on like a back panel
and uh...
it slides open
revealing uh... the oracle
uh... over here
any easy c_n_n_'s like this all
all told old old old who
and you see any sort of like wanders towards you all he says uh...
My name is suck-ass shit.
*laughter*
Alright, uh, is you-
Suck-ass shit who?
*laughter*
Suck-ass shit yo mama!
I like this guy.
I like this beautiful woman.
How do you all do?
Ah, Snoochie Boochies.
Doodoo.
Yeah, Doodoo, yes.
How do you... how do you know my name?
The stars foretold it.
And... and... I don't know.
I... I kinda just guessed. I feel really... I'm pretty glad that I got that in one go.
But you are a Tamagotchi.
You must be the only one left.
How fucking sad.
the
just nodding vigorously.
The second he says, "Is he?"
Yes, Christmas.
Ah.
And a hacked demon.
Completely ignore Sullivan.
What up?
You like Dominican women.
She.
You could say that this frog eats pussy anyway.
Come with me.
Please, we have we want to know where the temple of the penguin of doom is.
Of course, it is nearby, you see.
We found this village because it was near a Christmas jungle.
There are only. Yes.
Yep, that's right, buddy. Yeah, sound it out. I
Thought that's what you guys liked. I'm trying to fucking talk to you, dude
You're sitting here all fucking talking you're talking to these guys. I'm trying to get your attention. I grabbed Patrick. I teleport
Into a snowbank, yeah, he's just completely inside it
"CHRISBURN! CHRISBURN!"
like the idea of like the who is just like talking about like long ago and
then did you just hear like pitter patter like what's coming up as you're slowly
coming back into the scene. I teleport him back out again every time he comes back in.
I go get fucked at a restaurant.
[laughter]
Before performing a ritual to find the temple,
what are your intentions?
To save the Tamagotchi race and also get out of jail forever.
No more jail ever again. Free from jail.
You want to get out of jail forever?
That's, I mean, that's the second thing I said.
I feel like you ignored the first part.
the
on
to
the giant guy just slowly backs out of frame.
(laughing)
He's, I mean, there's just not,
they don't make them like they used to.
Let's just put it that way.
Okay, everyone, we're going to do a chat together
so that we can see where the temple is.
Kiki, do you love Bums?
Are you riding?
Say you'll never, never leave from beside me.
While I find the lyrics in my notes.
Perfect.
Do you love me?
(Random gibberish)
In the middle?
(More gibberish)
Teach me how to dougie.
Teach me how to dougie from Jaipur City.
Your mouth's all...
Once you say Jaipur City,
your mouth's all...
open a gape and just like
this like rainbow dust just like flies slowly out of your mouths and uh like you don't know
where it came from or what it could be and it's happening to everybody um and uh uh
um and it's like this it's like an ugly glitter almost and it starts swirling around
and in the center of all of you and then it just sprays out to the side and uh lorax bless us it
has worked and um as you look around you realize you're sort of like inside like a panorama of like
the tamagotchi empire and it's like the five of you are like looking around you and you could see
like the rise and fall of the civilization these quick shots of history like uh the age of tamagotchi
when they were no more than like scattered warring tribes of
matechi and you know other tamagotchi types
living and dying within 24 hours of birth
desperately craving a bowl of rice or a slice of bread in the international
versions. The rise of the empire as they began to
sweep across the region now known as gun city
ruling over the frogs and worms of yore moving from a brutal
controlling sort of like needy like they always want a meal or
or they always want to have like play or whatever rule.
There's something resembling a Republic.
You see the Crayola rebellion that happened and with sort of
the and you see the battle like you're zooming through it now,
like you're like a camera zooming through this battle like
flying through it.
Tamagotchi is covered in marks of Crayola suffering from all
this fear and pain and the Crayolas themselves which are
turning and disintegrating into pixels.
It's like horrible battle between these two toy civilizations.
And then you know, you see the Empire fall internal strife
warring egos corruption and then the rise of Tamagotchi
immortality which changed everything an endless death that
chases their hearts.
Finally, you see the birth of a young Tamagotchi hatched
from an egg.
It's cooing for food becomes a teenager now needs cared attention.
You see this all happening kind of in like a stop motion sort of like you like a age, you know, like a see this man smile like for a whole every day for a year.
Yeah, time lapse.
Fuck my ass.
Yeah.
Pictures in a row and they have sound.
What is that?
Video 24, 24 pictures per second.
Per second.
Yeah, and
And you see it now, but it's an adult and it's it's you could see it's snitchy boochies and you see he's alone and
Then you sort of see him in gun city and he's completely confused and it's so different from what he understood and
the alienation older
yeah, I don't want to see this anymore and
And the old man goes you must see this you must you must like like just like and then we move past
Snoochie Boochies now, the only Tamagotchi left alive. And we fly north past what would become
Gadsville into the soy wastes and the panorama settles now at last through a dense Christmas
jungle. And you hear like Christmas monkeys and Christmas light snakes hissing and blinking.
And then you just come across like a white, pure light, and you can't see anything, but
you know with perfect clarity that you're looking at the temple even though you can't
see it.
It has infected your hearts.
You know exactly where it is.
And then, just like that, the panorama just sort of vanishes.
And the oracle turns to Tsuchibuchi and says, "Your connection to this temple has revealed
its location.
You and your friends shall be able to find it.
Please do before our small village is disrupted further by the greedy tycoons Gun City sends
our way.
If they know that the N-word pass is here."
"Well."
"It's in front of us?"
"Well, it's near...
No.
the
here
what don't
it's in that corner of the room
don't try to guess where the n-word pass is
it's under this jar
i think it's in d's
d's what?
d's not
i was like which character will fall for this bill
yes oliven it's in d's
is
the
- Joe Mama.
- Yes.
- Oh my God.
- Jody's nuts.
- I in real life fell for that one just now.
(laughing)
- Somehow forgot what we were doing.
- The Christmas jungle is past the battered women's shelter
over yonder.
Is that gonna read or is that gonna just be too mean?
Should I change it?
We're definitely not going there.
That's all I'm going to say.
Good.
We're steering clear of that one.
Okay.
Well just walk that way to the jungle.
Make your way through it.
You will know which way to go.
Which way?
It's north of town.
That's pretty good.
That's pretty good because there was nothing about it.
Yeah, Joe Lama.
That would suggest that that was going to come next.
yeah next to Joe mama okay I need you guys to get out while we're leaving
while we're leaving there's like one of those like you know an ocarina of time
those like brown pots there's one of those next to the stairs and I pick it up
and I throw it on the ground to see if the n-word passes in it. It's just his food.
not do that. I was looking for the... Oh my god. I'm spinning around the room doing my
spin attack at every... The pipes, the pipes! Just like swinging metal pipes around. Hey,
sing it, Danny boy! Yeah, you guys managed to leave, I guess, the place at some point.
And yeah, so you can walk a bit north to go to the Christmas Jungle. You can take a long
rest too before you do that yeah let's take a long rest yeah I take a long rest
in his house without asking me too I get really yeah from spinning around I would
I lay down in the space under the sink yeah that's fine I don't have anything
else I have nothing I'm doing all day these nights
the
Yeah, we should all start a band.
That'd be great.
No, just me and you.
Shut up.
Just me and you.
I'm not getting fucked.
I'm doing it.
Sullivan and I are going to do an Ike and Tina thing.
What?
Oh, no.
Nothing.
Did they do something?
Maybe I should have picked a better joke.
How about Sonny and Cher?
I tried my other joke earlier and then also fell on Debbie or so.
Okay, well, hold on. We're gonna do a clean take.
Okay, yeah.
We're gonna do a Sonny and Cher thing.
That sounds fun.
I close my newspaper.
What the fuck are you two talking about?
What are you talking about takes?
And you guys walk outside of the Oracle and walk towards the Christmas jungle.
So the Christmas jungles are jungles that exist in cold areas of planet Ebaum.
they're just jungles that are made of like sort of like
christmas trees only but they also have like
like ornament creatures that sort of scurry around and like uh
uh is there a predator yeah it's you can there please can there be can there be a
ginger predator can you put that in really quick yeah
it's done that's pretty good thank you um yeah and there's a ginger
your predator in every single one.
So...
Oh, that sucks.
You should not have said anything.
That's so scary.
It's so cool.
I'm so happy.
But you guys can navigate through this jungle pretty easily.
You know, you see like all the little critters and creatures going through and it takes about
an hour before you guys start to sense that you're getting somewhere.
the
thing just happened to me guys.
And as you walk a little bit further Patrick Yoda, you feel
the same thing that blowtoss piss felt but you wouldn't I
guess know that I'm on the same exact thing.
And yeah, and you roll your perception check to see if you
know where it came from.
18.
Okay, you look up in the trees and you see
for a brief second.
What you think is a penguin and then it just pops its head
back behind the tree.
the
There are ornaments that are edible up there.
They're edible ornaments.
Oh, so it's like edible crossing?
I open my mouth wide to let them drop onto my mouth.
Alright, so I got a real strength?
Yeah.
Oh no.
Alright.
I'm also shaking the tree.
Sixteen.
I'm walking around catching the ornaments.
And you're shaking the tree and the duck didn't do so hot on its roll.
So it's like, "Quack!" and it falls out of the tree and lands on its back.
And it's a penguin, a little penguin with a VR headset on its head.
And it starts like freaking out and it starts to scream.
I grab it by the feet.
Yeah, you grab it pretty easily.
And I swing it.
I swing it back and forth.
"Guys, look what I found!"
Put that thing down
No, you just want to touch it
I don't just trust me. No, I found it, please. No
Grab it I just I just walk
Yeah, I
Just pick it up out of his hands. I take off the VR headset
From it no eyes. Okay. I put the VR headset
I put it on Patrick. I
Could see just like what does he see? Everybody's a penguin?
Yes
penguin but it's also in predator colors it's like yeah the being john
malkovich thing yeah yeah everyone yeah caleb's trying to talk to me at all
here's penguin penguin penguin penguin the penguin without its headset is like
insert my sock in its mouth it starts vomiting and then i start vomiting because
i don't i can't do penguin vision for some reason
Wait, wait, wait, wait, hold on.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, put the VR headset back on this creature.
Oh, God. Yeah.
And Christ,
Snitchy Boochies goes up to it.
He says, Are you OK, little fella?
And he's like, Oh,
I don't know.
And it's just like doing like frantic dancing.
It's do you just like smacks in the face?
Is it? Well,
it's just like it calms down.
OK.
Where is the temple?
And you see the penguin go like, "Aaah!"
And you see like four other penguins come out and go, "Raaah!"
And they all like, show up.
And they go in a single file line.
And they start walking towards the temple.
What could be the temple.
Can I put a leash on one of them?
Yes.
Okay, I daisy-chain a bunch of Xbox games together.
And I throw it around one of their necks.
Can I kick one like a field goal?
Yes, yeah, yeah, raise one hand all the way up here.
And I run and I kick it.
Just like it just like disappears. It's the sky.
It's like Team Rocket star.
I hope we don't need four penguins later to like stand in a circle or something.
Well, you'll you'll fill in a four-sided circle.
and uh... you guys march with your three penguins one of them in slaves i guess
and uh...
you notice i was just making sure they don't go away
the jungle starts to get like
hotter
but it's a warm up you see that there's less snow
it's kinda slush now
and inexplicably it's like now really warm
and uh... and you see snitchy-boochies and his eyes sort of like light up he says
we are nearing it
I know these temperatures.
Is it near a desert or something?
It is near.
Is it a desert?
Is it near a Christmas jungle?
Is it a desert inside of a Christmas jungle?
It's a temple.
Let's just test what kind of hot things it's near.
Is it near a fire or a volcano maybe?
I feel like I'm just asking because I feel like we didn't need the penguins.
All we needed was a thermometer.
Yeah, I mean, is it a temple?
I think the penguins are just sort of here for flavor, but yeah, I mean,
okay, then I kick another one.
Okay.
I'm starting to really like this.
Me and Ray William Johnson are doing like soccer footsies.
Hey, Pat, when you're done with your slave, could I kick him into the sky?
Well, we'll do that later.
It's starting to understand you.
Oh, good. He's intelligent.
That's better.
Wait, I, I, I, can I put one of the penguins, can I just put one of the penguins in my inventory?
Yes.
Yeah, wait, hold on. Yeah, I take all the, I do that too.
Because I just, I just, I have, I have a lizard skin and I have bones and I think penguin might
be the last ingredient to build a guy. Okay, yeah, sounds good. I agree.
Yeah, just, just holding on to that.
Yeah, and you guys walk a bit further and you come up against the edge of the Christmas jungle.
And which is at this point, it's like hot now.
You can take off the Yeti skin that you were using to keep warm and you don't need it anymore.
And you come across like the edge of a beach and a small stream like about 10 feet wide
wrapped around a small wrapped around a massive I should say actually sandbar.
I'll tell you that can coke on top of it and even more massive.
And golden penguin that resembles the one that you had and that you
still have with you that's all the need out.
And it's beautiful and gleaming and sushi booties.
You see like little pixel tears start to form up in his eyes.
And he's like, it's just as I've seen it just as I dreamed it would
be. The temple of the penguin of doom.
And you look upon this like massive structure and feel a sense of awe and a
sense of dread as the final stage of your adventure is here.
Kiki, do you love me? Are you riding?
Yeah, that's it.
Say you never ever leave.
I'm a 10th wheel of a Porsche, the aerodynamics of the engine
It's gonna be a medium, very low
I'm not gonna lie, I'm not gonna lie
I'm not gonna lie
(upbeat music)
(outro music)