Last Time in Gun City presents Batman the Villains are Incredible
We left off with the evil demon man giving Mr.
Wonderful some instructions on what to do ahead of the parenting parade and now here is the thrilling conclusion of our campaign
Enjoy
My god that was almost so fucking bad it wasn't at all
It's a completely empty can but if it was a full can it was a full can when I tipped over Batman voice
It would have fried
Got it, okay
The parade is supposed to celebrate Gotham's Living Parents' Day.
Celebrate all the parents who are alive, in honor of famous Gotham citizen Bruce Wade
whose parents are dead.
All parents, good or bad, ugly or hot, ride on top of floats that celebrate, coaching little
league games and helping you with your homework, installing a latch key or having the talk,
anything that still living parents do. The raid takes place at night, because that was
when Bruce Wayne's parents were murdered. And Gotham wants to show all the parents murderers
out there that the night does not fear them. Or wait, hold on. I wrote that completely wrong.
That the parents don't fear the night. That's crazy how wrong that is. And that parent murderers
should instead fear the night wow okay cool dude okay, because that is when
parents who are still alive or at their most powerful
night yeah night. Oh, because that's when they watch flight of the concords
and they close the attic door.
I've not had a single thought about that
(laughing)
in like a long enough time that's making me aware of my age.
Commissioner Gordon, who if you remember is Filipino,
watches over the proceedings intently.
His ever vigilant Gotham City Police Squad
patrolling for any dubious villains.
- Yeah, and you see people as you're walking by,
they're saying happy parenting to you,
and a wonderful parents day celebration to you.
and yeah, it's a whole parade and all those floats I described or Batman
described are going on and the scary guy voice.
A squall. Well, that's going to be pretty confusing because I already carry
around a lot of scrolls, so I don't know that I...
The blue one?
No, it can't be the blue one.
is it the right one?
No, this can't base can't be it. No, I just remembered I got this another time,
which one what color was it
oh, I have like ten green ones
forest. Oh, you should have said that from the beginning yeah, yeah, wait, no,
no, I got I got it. I got it. I got it. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
So what I need you to do is go on top of the tallest float, which should be the latchkey one.
Because they turn the latchkey vertical.
And then I need you to read the scroll out loud and then you will have control of the crowd.
And then you will lead them to the manor.
And when Gotham...
When Batman arrives at the manor, Gotham will be ours.
worse. Okay, all right, okay, okay, okay. So yeah, there's a number of
different ways you can try to climb up this float. I mean, is there a ladder
on it? No.
You should climb up the... It's a first. Well, I can levitate 99 feet. You
have to have your claws, right? Yeah, but I also established in the first
one that I can levitate really high. Yeah. Did we establish that? Oh, we
So I guess I'll just do that, but no, I'll use the disc.
No, you don't have to use that. You can use your levitation.
No, that was kind of like nothing.
Keep in mind though that Gotham's cops are around,
and they will be beatboxing and also looking for you.
Stop. Come on. People got to hear this.
Okay, I use the disc.
I do the disc.
very cool.
Describe to everybody at home tensors floating disc. Well, first of all,
it makes a disc that I can fly up to five hundred pounds or I can be up to
five hundred pounds. What I'm on it. What do you mean? You can fly up to five
hundred. What do you mean? You can be five hundred pounds. It holds five
hundred pounds. Okay, so why do you say I can be five of your summarizing? I
because there's a whole paragraph. I'm trying to read. I skip to the number.
Well, okay, three feet. It's one inch thick as well. You should cast the spell
of unending fatness and then get on it.
I didn't give you that spell. I'm sorry. Maybe I could. I didn't give that
spell. I'll cast minor illusion then to become honey boo boo. So I think it's
very fat. Cast the spell to become honey boo boo's mom. I appear 501 pounds.
That's too much now. But that's what I appear. Oh, I see. People are like,
I was doing that yeah yeah, they said that disc only holds five hundred.
This can only fly five hundred, but he looks about five hundred and one or oh,
I can't
I don't know. I don't know if this can go up. It can't it can't go up. I don't
think so. Oh, well, why do you tell me to use it? It can't go up more than ten
feet. I want people
what the hell are you doing? I just saw he pointed it at his head and then it
fell over. So how tall is this thing? I mean, I can just climb it.
Yeah, it's a couple. I'll roll to just climb a hundred feet. Okay, you got
well, so keep in mind, though, there are again, there are cops around. So
if you right, so can I
there's an illusion make me look like a key repair man.
Or what if you do an illusion to make yourself look like, I mean, you can
also go up buildings and then jump out of a window. You can try to talk
to somebody. There's lots of things you can do. Just be Batman.
Okay, well, I guess I'll go talk go first first things first. I'm going to go to
the float okay and
I'm still disguised as Mark Cuban, too. I never took that off. No, you never took
off your mark. So
I'm Mark Cuban from TV and I need to get up on your float at the highest point.
We're filming a show and I need to bring this camera
and I look around
and then I go like this
to the top of your float roll moral talking.
No,
can nobody see that
I can't do my glasses.
Three
that's a three guys like you're acting extremely strange. I'm not
going to let you near the float. Okay, does this change your mind and
I pull up to be Pluto TV on my phone and I pull up Shark Tank episodes
and I'm pointing and showing
it's just I'm sure right now. Okay, I can't fast for you can't fast forward on
Pluto TV. It's like live cable and then an ad break starts for the ice all yeah
yeah. Oh what hold on let me one second. Sd Johnson, I'm looking at it. I'm
screenshotting all of the the ads and check that out later
BAM and I
Batman villain style
all right roll roll your melee attack. Okay,
with my oh that's a dirty twenty yeah. You cold cock this guy roll damage
nine damage nice. Yeah, he's not out cold. Okay, then I start climbing and I
put on an illusion to look like him.
hold on or that's how my illusion works. It's not how it works. I quite let me
read this actually a couple of the cops are starting to stir though nearby. They
might have heard that a little bit. Okay, then I'd
so you just knocked out a guy who right okay. I was going to take a different
approach for the illusion. I'm going to use an illusion on the float to make it
look like a ladder, so it's normal that I'm climbing it.
now the minor illusion has about how much how much how big is your can your
illusion be again doesn't say of an oh you create
a bit of five you just create a sound or image of an object it doesn't say it
thirty feet doesn't say a size at all that's definitely it's not thirty feet
distance but it doesn't say any size that's thirty one feet big there's no
way you can make a fucking ladder with minor illusion maybe read it there's no
restrictions on it at all anything under under a hundred dollars should be yeah
you should be able to make.
It's a cheap letter. It's a rope letter to shitty lighter. It's a shitty ladder,
but it's a ladder. It's the ropes course from Jim
God damn it.
I hate this fuck. Oh and I'm also going to cast protection from evil on myself
and if the cops can shoot me, you're saying something
I'm saying bullets. I'm saying cops kill the guns, kill people, no cop cops. You
know what I'm saying? You said gobs
so you said
I'm a fake ladder. You're climbing a fake like Gotham. How long does that
last again? One minute damn it there's no way I got to
somebody call me. I'm not going to I could do something so crazy. Somebody
somebody call me. I there's not that what I just want to know how wrong I am
right now. What am I doing wrong, but can you seriously tell me that a ladder
is that crazy? That's not breaking nothing crazy about it. That's not even
going to work. That's what's driving me. I'm going to be mad at me. All right,
tell me of a ladder, no and a sign and a game thing be on side that says it's
okay
I just want to get I'm ready. The cop is trying to stir your going to start
climbing and we're going to cut to
the cook. So he forgot my name, the could know I didn't know. I didn't want to
wait for the sound to know he was going to say the chef. No, it was not Curtis
or something. I was going to say Curtis. You didn't even know Curtis, the cook
Get that gun out of my face. Stop.
Stop with the gun.
The butt is even scarier if you've seen action movies.
That's true, but you could go by Curtis the Cook.
No, I'm just the cook.
I'm not trying to blame you. You and Sullivan are singing Paralyzer by Finger 11.
Can we sing a different song?
No, no.
Okay, sorry.
Yeah.
I'm trying to make you go to bed.
There's a lullaby.
I'm not paralyzed, but I seem to be struck by you.
When roll dexterity, sorry,
roll a balance bing ball saving balance bing ball.
Just roll the blue one.
It's like you need some real life.
Roll the big ball.
Caleb, there's already one in there.
Just roll that one.
Caleb, there's already shut up, bro.
Shut the fuck up.
And that was a fucking with my balance bing ball.
that is still just a eight. Okay, cool.
Blue one would have rolled higher.
The blue one rolled me a twenty on my first roll. I don't want your stinky blue dice.
A chef's knife flies by you and slices you across the cheek.
You take four damage. Or what?
Four heart? Sorry, you take four heart. I lose four heart?
You lose four heart from the heart number. Okay, I'm at
one heart.
Whoa, mine is half down.
Oh yeah, because you took damage at when we left Arkham.
Don't even remember.
I remember that.
Didn't you get, you got hit by like a bug?
I guess.
What?
He got hit by something.
I don't think it was a bug.
What happens?
And also, wait, a chef's knife, what is this, my twin?
Oh my god.
It is I.
Oh, it's my twin.
Sous Chef.
God fucking damn it.
He's done.
You thought you were done with me, did you not?
Yeah.
Yeah, honestly.
Yeah, I thought that I was done with you.
You thought, oh, I don't not need him anymore.
I do not need my sous chef.
Well, that's exactly why you can barely speak.
And now you talk to frogs instead of cooking and eating them.
Talk to frogs?
This is a, I'm trying to, this baby.
I'm trying to, I'm trying to go to sleep.
Yeah, you need to chill, Su.
You gotta keep it down, Frenchie.
Oi.
he gets mad about that. Oh yeah, so mad that he called him French. He could have
called him a frog.
Yeah, it's all been solving in the end of the suit. You have to have the same
realization about
it's like you're like kind of like oh yeah, there was a
could have done a thing here like a moment. He's like no, it is my time for
revenge and revenge is a dish best served with you dead.
That's another reason why I didn't like you being my sidekick.
Shut up. Roll the initiative.
Your lines are bad.
Roll initiative.
Exclamation point?
Sorry, roll exclamation point.
I got a three.
Roll bang.
Okay.
Alright.
Sorry.
Alright, what'd you say? You got a three?
Yeah.
Okay.
Sous Chef is going to go first, unfortunately.
I don't care.
Sullivan's kind of sleepy, though.
Shouldn't a sous chef wait and listen to the head chef?
Well this is the proving grounds.
This is topsy turvy world.
This is chef vs sous chef.
Chefs or sous chefs can do whatever they want in Gotham.
Now that Batman has taken the law into his own hands.
Patrick is fully out of frame.
Disgusting.
I don't know why that keeps happening.
Patrick is slipping out.
He's addicted to leaving frame.
I've taken which.
He learned.
There he is.
You have taught me.
I think he hit the frame.
I have the master the gumball better than you ever could. Oh yeah, fuck you.
Bro, you don't have to cook gumballs at all, you just chew them.
I don't know what kind of master chef bullshit you're doing now,
what kind of Michelin star gumball you're making.
That would be so good. A Michelin star gumball?
He takes out... Because you know it would have flavor the whole time, all day.
We're thinking of Willy Wonka. And it would be rosemary flavored.
No, I'm thinking of a Michelin star gumball.
And it would have a rosemary flavor to it.
Somebody should do a...
They should have done a Chef's Table episode.
Oh my God, yes.
They should have done a Chef's Table episode about Willy Wonka.
Yeah.
Oh.
We should do a Willy Wonka campaign.
Stop it.
He turns invisible.
Oh, he's gone.
Thank God.
All right.
Back to burping.
Ha, I am not gone.
My conscience?
No, no.
final my calm. My God, your come is that my come talking my come is talking
your come. Let me guess you want to get out. No, I'm I'm now know where he is by
the way. Yeah, because he's talking
he's like a little bit off to the left. It's your turn. Okay, I'm going to use
my gumbo to teach him a little lesson about gumballs. Okay, you have some
gumbos stored up to? I have fortifying broth. You have speedy, spedy. So sorry,
yeah. So you can do that or you can cook up a new gumbo and then use it. Are the
gumbos, do they, are any of them like instantly damaging type gumbos? Some of
them will, some of them will like be like, can be like poison that you can
apply with a knife or something and then it's random. I'm going to take my
chances. Any gumbo you're going to roll the dice will be instantly damaging.
(claps)
- That's a 10. - Cheese.
- Cheese. - Cheese.
- Cheese.
- Nice, okay.
Insatiable hunger.
The cook prepares a dish that induces intense hunger
in all creatures within a 30 foot radius.
Each affected creature must make a DC 14 wisdom saving throw
or spend its next turn consuming any available food--
- I use it. - Or rations within reach,
taking no other action.
- That includes Sullivan.
- I use that. - Does consume.
- Does include Sullivan. - That's fine.
There's plenty of burp on my--
plenty of bird that he can eat. Okay. Sullivan passes.
The chef does not. The sous chef does not.
I'm so hungry. Well, how about you eat your fucking gumball bitch? No,
I do not want to eat my gumball. Well, if you know,
here I'll make, I'll make you something. If you just start,
stop being invisible. No, no, no, no, no. You have to eat it.
It's the rules of my dice. It's the rules of your dice.
Can't he just make himself his own food? He's a sous chef. He's only a sous chef.
He has to follow orders. He panics. He doesn't know recipes. Yeah, exactly.
And he eats his knife and he takes six damage. Oh, shit. Oh, God.
You are a moron. No, you do this to me. Okay. And it's back to you. Okay.
Okay, so you've been terrorizing the people there and it's time.
Oh, I've just been voice.
Should I point it out of a window or?
Yeah, you're doing well.
It's it's a side Batman.
Hey, man.
How you doing man?
If I can bring you in a bit man fucking shit.
What have you done man?
I don't even know man.
I just picked up this shit from the girls room.
You first of all you then I went downstairs.
I don't know. I just I forgot your power. This is gonna. I've been just showing it
off to everybody that wants to look at it, man. I've been showing all the
dexterity saving throw. I mean a balance ball. Roll it in the wall. Not 20,
though, but I got a net 20.
Fine. He should roll it in the box next time.
Yeah. Okay, show everybody. Okay, Batman throws a batarang and you just how do
Why do you sidestep this? You tell me.
I am talking and I chomp on it.
It flies by my mouth and I just go,
"Damn it!"
"Man, what the hell you put-
Man, now I'm pissed off, man.
Now you're going to make me fucking get like all mad and shit
and trying to kill you, man."
Roll exclamation point.
Seventeen?
Yeah.
17 plus 2. It's a dirty 19.
OK, just beat Batman barely.
OK.
Sorry.
Alright, your turn your turn. You're up man. I don't even know
what the fuck I'm gonna do.
The evil guy voice.
I need you to kidnap Batman. So do him like you did the mayor. I got a
kidnap Batman man. I killed the mayor. What the hell you talking about man?
I don't but after you got the hey Batman, I killed the mayor. Oh,
why? Okay, don't do that.
That's what your response to that is man. Man says I just don't kill the
the mayor. I thought you guys had like a report.
He would lose his mind.
Why did you kill the mayor?
No! The mayor! He's my friend!
And then I say, "Follow me, come look at the mayor."
No!
The mayor's dead body, man. You wouldn't want to see this, man. I fuckin' melted his all shit up.
You're wearing his skin! Oh my God!
Surprise!
(laughter)
Wait, hold on.
He laughed.
I'm scaring my voice. Okay, okay, stop.
I'm showing Batman my tongue, my sober tongue.
you need to give up. I remember do not. I have a plan and I'm trying to make him
go back to the other room right now. Okay, so I'll let you do your thing go
for it. So I just run to the other side of the building. Okay, cool. Yeah, use
your dash. You just run sixty feet. You go back around and you go back into the
room and that's actually a good cue because we're back to you. You're
climbing the ladder. That was his dash sound, so we'll need another one.
okay, you're like sixty feet up now at this point, and so some of the cops are
trying to notice you.
Hey, get down here. I point to the sign. Wait, is that Mr. Wonderful?
No,
roll talking
mark Cuban.
That's a net twenty wow. That's why I didn't roll of disadvantage, because
he's dressed like Mark Cuban. No, I think that's Mark Cuban. He's the
the mission according to yeah, it's mark Cuban for sure.
Yeah, okay, cool. You just keep climbing uninterrupted. He gets to the very top of
the float
and now you can use a scroll. If you wish to open the scroll, what does it say?
It's an ABBA ABBA
do
and
you say do and it's just a light
you just sprout wings out of your front. It's all fucked up. No you
yeah, everybody in the parade just there's something under command. Oh,
there's no command. No, yeah, they're not scared. They all go. They'll go
Mr. Wonderful. Tell us what to do for roughly one half hour. That's a long
I how many people okay what I want you to do is like open up your everybody
take out your phones and the other guy
finishes bit, but yeah get him open up your phones everybody and take out your
uber app. I want you to request a ride. Stop stop stop,
request it and make sure you pay and then wait and just don't cancel it, but
it will say that I'm here and wait for five minutes and don't cancel. Make sure
you don't cancel it.
you believe it to be a leader of this whole city, you'll get whatever you
want. Why rate five stars? Thank you, my God, okay,
now add me now give me the thing on it. That's a picture of a gem and says
friendly conversation. Can you get like a half of them? Give me that now make
it say that I have my snacks in my car, make them at you make them at you on
now follow me on instagram a thousand followers.
Oh my God, add me on Instagram, sensual food pics,
I never watch shark tank again with my brother.
They all asked who's your brother? Who do you think
mister wonderful?
Now they think that everyone on shark tank is brother and sister.
now take off your clothes.
Some of us are kids.
It's not going there. What the hell is that about? It's not like that. It's
funny for yeah, it's not an army of people to be naked. Yeah, it's not like
it's not a sexual, not a sexual command at all. It doesn't matter if it's not
why do you make me give you that voice? If you're just going to be a crowd,
no what because he was he was saying stop and he's going to tell you the
commands and then you anyway, the point was just that it would be funny for
and they tell you what they're making. You turned it into some you had a
fire, dark place, disgusting. It's a okay fine. Everybody switch clothes
yeah, because that's yeah the girls were the guys close. The guys were the
girls clothes and then do the cupid shuffle. They all do the cupid shuffle
down, do it down, do it yeah and then I guess I do whatever he wanted you to
storm the manor. Oh, then storm the manor.
Okay, yeah, they start doing that. They start marching. They're all how they
the jumbled. How are they going to get there to the right to the right?
Everybody
their parade, their bar that's no they all get they like World War Z on top of
the car and I just yeah cool.
So yeah, they're marked marching towards that back to the chef fight.
it's his turn. So he's now no longer invisible after he tried to swallow his
own knife. Okay, and he's going to try again to attack you. Instead of doing
the gumbo, he's going to
he's going to try to throw his knives at you.
They're all doing it. Oh, he does hit you, though.
He only does he only has four damage.
I'm just fucking kidding you bitch. I have twenty eight, twenty seven more
where that came from. No, twenty seven. Yeah. You have so much more hearts
since I last saw you. Yeah, that's what jail did to me. Damn. Or asylum did to
me.
Cool, it's your turn.
Now,
I think I'd like to use speddy.
All right, yeah. So speddy. I swear it's gotta be spaghetti related. It's
it's yeah, it's a spaghetti gumbo. Okay, which does I mean it all does is it
gives you movement speed is doubled from movement in it. You mean sorry, it's
bad foot, your move, your rabbit,
oh,
doubled.
All right, well, that never I don't want to use that. Then I thought it'd
give me some kind of sped power. I will use my cleaver
I will use my cleaver. All right,
cool yeah, you run up to him
and you
just all I do. I'm the worst
all the time all right
to that's so to ask away eight, though not I shit yeah you whiff
all right, let's pretend I didn't do that his turn and he's going to you're
gonna need to roll another dexterity saving through. Oh
all sorry, sorry balance ball.
Wow. Oh, you're fucked. Yeah. Fuck you, bitch. It's not my character's name. Oh, you take
11 damage. That one didn't hurt at all. That actually does actually have a bunch of knives.
You see him as he dodges the cleaver. He lifts his hands up and there's like string attached
to it and these knives come up from behind. He yanks his hands back and he's nicer to
stab into you and your back.
But now it's your turn.
Oh yeah, that's so cool that you have like the knives on a string and I just ran at
you with a knife. Yeah, you're so cool.
Yes. Bitch ass.
Fuck you.
You want to go? Oh wait, we're
Oh, that's OK.
Mind tearing my guns?
OK.
Sullivan is asleep now.
I'm not going to miss with my cleaver.
Twice!
The two again.
Really? Yeah.
Yeah, you miss.
Damn.
Okay, he's gonna attack you again this time with his his own
nine up front.
Yeah, that hits you for sure. Damn it.
Damn, he just ate damage to you. Oh, dude.
I've ate health.
You have grown weak. You have never. Yeah.
Behind you. Okay. What are you gonna do?
love. That's just what you say. Yeah, roll behind you roll roll a mouth roll
talking
five. I will not look behind me plus minus one. So for that is not going to
work on me. I've been in many a key. All right, well, we're always supposed to
watch by you in a kitchen. Oh, they say come coming up behind you or whatever
they say. I have a language behind you behind behind. Is that what they say?
Well, I'm going to try to use Pimentos. I'm going to try to use my oh wait. I
I'm a healing. I have a healing potion or healing gumbo. You do I'm gonna use my
healing gumbo. He's really gumbo. How much does it heal?
Heals a lot 3d 8 plus 3. Oh shit 3d 8.
My life is amazing. What is that?
A six
plus an eight. Come on man.
Plus a two. Fucking childish. Healed 16. Healed 16. There's a poop on the dice
roll camera for everyone listening. Cameron put a poop.
All right. I have 24 health. Do your worst.
He's going to try to do his worst. I don't give a shit. Do chef.
Do chef. He has another 12 damage to you.
Whatever. All right.
You're up to, this is like the, I haven't hit him for anything. Yeah.
This is a real, okay. I'm gonna use my cleaver again. Go for it.
There's no way I get another two.
- You're gonna get something good.
- Yes!
- What'd you get?
- A 23.
- That absolutely hits.
- Okay, 2D6 plus four.
- Yes.
- 13.
- Describe your kill.
- Oh!
- Wait, wait, wait, before you describe your kill,
check this out.
- Like Batman.
- Oh, that's me hurting him.
- When they beat them up, when they beat,
ooh, ah!
Well, well, well.
No, please! I underestimated you.
You just missed so many times.
Those were distractions.
So that I could hit you with the final blow.
I would have thought that you'd learned from me.
And you would know that this was my signature move.
But I guess you're just too fucking stupid.
I guess I am. I'm stupid.
So I'm gonna ask you one thing.
Okay.
Hand over your apron and your knife.
You're chopped.
Oh, that wasn't...
God damn the question that was sick. He didn't ask me anything. He asked you to
hand over. I asked you to and don't be a bit. Okay, here's my command. You say
like I'm gonna ask you to hand this over. That's not nice. Something the
same. He's something hand over your knife in your apron. You're chopped.
It's that simple. Be pedantic. You're 86. Get the fuck out and you kill him. No,
I don't kill him. Oh, you just taste 86. Oh, that's so much worse. Yeah, he's
not a chef anymore.
He like shrivels up to the left
what happened. Oh man, you de chef to don't worry little one. I won't thanks
for saving us. I throw him like a football
cool. We're back to you. You're fighting a batman into this into the room.
She's on fire with the girl. Is she dead?
She's not dead.
Okay. So I have an opportunity to hide.
Actually, sorry, I just realized the thing you didn't notice.
Roll dexterity saving throw.
What symbol is that?
Sorry, roll balance ball.
God, I'm so bad at this. I'm sorry.
You can move this. This can move around.
It's clipped onto this.
It's not like moving it will change.
Well, I can't move like my chair.
Yeah, that is a 20.
OK, no.
What is it? I was I almost 17 plus whatever you
oh wait, 17 plus balance ball was balance ball.
That actually is a dirty 19 again.
OK, you see at the corner, I
what looks like the mayor's daughter inside of hamster ball.
And she's rolling towards you and you get out of the way just in time.
She had a hamster ball. Wait, is she the hungry hamster?
She's hungry to
hamsterina. That's right. Wow. Damn. Yeah.
Oh my goodness.
She's Greta the Hamsterita and she says, "Ah, damn it! I almost got you!"
And see Batman...
Hungry... Hey, Hungrita!
Batman.
Wait, is she good or bad?
She's against you. She's trying to kill you.
But is she against me in the same way that the sous-chef was against him, where they
used to be partners? Or is she...
No, she's partners with Batman.
Fuck! Okay.
She's like a catwoman, but she's Hungrita the Hungra.
But catwoman also has bad moments.
where she's a bad a bad kitty. Yes
you're just disgusting. You're honestly repulsing at every turn. You guys don't
let me do anything fun
at
but yeah,
so
did we have a history?
My boss won't let me be. Does she stank?
but she's thinking I don't know man. Yeah, she's pretty gross. Do we have an
old history of like us being like yes, you do a compatriots yes and
and what man hungry to man I fucking knew that was you fucking big ass bitch.
My ass is not big. I said big ass bitch. I did say that yeah. I thought you
batman batman. Well,
well, you know you know this. You know this. You know this guy. You know the
Rambler and she's like yeah. Well, we sort of and then I turn around and then
I take off the skin on my face and I turned a batman with the gun and now I
reveal my true identity.
I've been the Rambler the whole time. Wait, I knew
*laughter*
This is fucking with my head in real life.
I've been the- I've been the rambler this entire time, Batman, and you were none the wiser.
Now, me and Hungry- oh, and let- no, we're not, 'cause she is on your side right now,
because I've done- gone and killed her father.
*laughter*
That's right, you did!
How could you?
By accident,
I put a flashlight on his face.
It was not by accident, I know it wasn't, 'cause I'm a girl now!
What?
Sorry, I was just noticing my voice.
No, she knows it wasn't an accident.
There's no way.
Well, I was in disguise as a French diplomat.
[laughter]
So I had to do what he would do.
Role talking.
Role talking with advantage.
Oh wait, no, a Mong- Mongolian?
Man of Mark and however you say it Monica Monica Monica gay skin a
diplomat.
But now I've been I'm in my true form the Rambler.
What do you get on the and I got to
don't look at it.
14 cells can see 14 plus my talking.
So that's an 18.
You roll again by way of advantage.
Okay,
because you confused me in real life.
That's a two wow, okay, so I keep that eighteen yeah and you're in so
you got it.
It's a Batman says
no, it can't be true. It's all true baby. Yeah,
I can't believe this.
What are we going to do hungry to hungry to
have to defeat him for my father. Oh, don't know you don't. I'll just go. What? No, we
know we need to stop you. We're gonna stop you right now. I'm just gonna go roll initiative.
You bitch.
Dang it. Just put it in the account or no, no, no, put it in the box. Just roll it. 17
plus your bang. Dirty 19. Oh, that's what he had last time. I should have had him keep
that anyway. She really is the only one who has to roll initiative.
When in Rome, what you get?
Seven.
Dumb bitch. All right.
So, okay.
God damn it.
All right. You're up.
Okay. First thing I'm going to do.
So all three of you are kind of like upstairs by where her room is in the
manor.
So do my attacks like Babble Blast, is that a, that's like a, is it like a cone
of damage?
It's an area of effect.
I am just...
Not an area of effect, but it's a cone. Yes.
with my babble blast. I am going to look at them with the gun. I'm going to point it and
then I'm just going to start reciting the entirety of the great Gatsby for memory.
Oh man, how much does the Rambo remember of it?
Roll brain.
That looks like a three. That's a three minus one, so that's a two. So I'm just going.
Full score and seven years ago I was the great Gatsby, baby.
Yeah.
What does it say for what I have to roll?
What I have to roll?
What you have to roll?
3d6?
No, no, the middle one.
It'll be the middle number.
3d6?
You mean 36?
Wisdom 14.
So DC wisdom 14.
Okay, they're going to roll against that.
Okay, the bat does well.
And Greta does not.
What happens to her?
3d6 damage? Yeah. Oh, she fucked.
Well, she's already damaged cause I lit her on fire. Yeah.
All right. She's not looking too good. So she hears it.
She's like, Oh God, it's like our arguments again. Oh,
all our fights when we were, were we dating? Were we an item? You're,
you're sort of in charge of this.
I don't really remember most of my life.
Ah, you're so fucking thoughtless.
He's like aloof.
He is. It is.
It is.
Aloof is my middle name.
That wasn't your voice though when we were dating.
What was my name again?
Manor.
Manor Aloof Dilfroy.
So you think your name.
My name is Manor Aloof Dilfroy.
So I'm revealing my identity.
And I work at Kinko's.
All right. Yeah. So, yeah, no, you did a lot of damage to her.
but now it's the Batman's turn. Whoa.
This is why he can't wear the glasses.
He keeps missing it.
I know I want it to be seen by the world.
All right. So Batman, Batman has to go to attack you.
He misses. He goes, he tried to like, just do his like a Arkham,
Arkham city kind of combo. I'm doing this.
You're doing what? What was the first one?
That's me touching him.
Yeah. Pink Panther dodges.
- Panther dodges. - You're like, "Whoa!"
- Yeah, right, yeah. Okay.
He's gonna try again. He misses again.
Just like whiffing completely.
- He did the same exact moves twice in a row!
- Your dodging abilities have only improved since I put you in that asylum.
- And that's why they called me the Rambler, because I ramble around.
[laughter]
Like a dust buddy.
- Or a tumbleweed. - It's her turn now.
So she's going to try to roll up at you again.
She's going to try and roll.
She's trying to charge.
That is
she's charging.
What has gotten into you?
She's changed my whole identity.
Like a jiggly puff and smash.
And she's got which so and she's going to try to attack you and she misses.
But she's going to do a good.
But she comes back around.
You rolled all saving throw or second attack.
I started bouncing ball.
Is that you can't see that, Caleb?
You got to look at that.
Well, no, wait, you show me the dice.
show the dice cam.
You kind of like really look, I think it's a problem when it just goes in
this corner, so you just stop rolling into that corner.
All right, so I screwed.
I screwed.
So I screwed.
You take seven damage.
Seven, yeah, it's not bad, it's only 25.
Cool.
So I screwed.
Story of my college life.
Let's get back to you.
All the way back, all the way, literally before I was even in school.
what's what's happening.
What's happening to you right? I told school literally when I was being
babysat as a baby, my in my middle school teacher, middle store, middle
school, whenever I went into any store in my childhood, I was eating pussy me
with my dentist
me with my dentist, me with my doctor,
me with everyone who lived on my street, I'm up at a zigzag across the street
and I was boning them and doing them and I was boning them and doing them hard
boning. So
literally five bonings a day. Pause here on this. Let's just pause. You never
said anything gay. Yeah. No. He was just talking about how much he would jizz
inside of women and bone them. I was boning women. From jizz. How long?
Jizzing in them.
Okay. Now, the first thing I actually want to address
is that where address now
not is that i i just joke when i told you
that it was uh... hungry to the hamster arena
uh...
i have strong he was mistaken it was not as no it was a very few were very you
were still very close it was hungry to
uh... it was hamsteria was what i had hams terry hamster hamsteria is what i
had not hung on to the house is hamster yeah that's kind of i don't have any
inside a ball. I have a million hamsters but I, I ate them all.
Cause they eat the fucking children.
So he still did a really good job.
Hamsters eat their kids.
We should have stopped at I don't practice hamsteria.
Hamsters eat their children.
I don't run inside a ball.
He said live, they don't live in a ball.
But I was trying to think of I don't have no, and I was trying to think of what that
water bottle.
I don't have no water bottle.
I don't have no running ball.
So, Mr. Wonderful, you are up on the parade.
I'm a cage.
You're completely, you lost it.
It's too tall.
You are at the parade right now.
The parade has now at this point become a full mob of people rating you highly on Uber,
marching towards the Peaches Manor.
You could see the manor in the distance now.
It's like not, it's like, you know, it's pretty close by.
I heard that if you get like a high enough rating on Uber, they could send you a golden
car.
I heard that too.
as a driver. So really how most over drivers, how high is that rating?
That's too heavy. My rating. I'm checking my phone. What's my rating?
Can I roll
to see my rating? You have to roll. Can I roll five stars first ever six
star? Well, I want to try and get more than five. Max is five. Yeah. So
what are you gonna try to do? I just want to know if there's a good
rules. This must be this must be this. There can't be any other Uber driver
in the world. Who is having the experience I'm having right now? You
can't look me in the eye and
calls your phone
just want to say congratulations.
Thank you ask about the golden car and the golden car is on its way. I presume
by any hangs up like a
but roll perception check sorry roll an owl. I was going to ride in the back
I'm also writing in a car made of all the people
what you're not writing up. You're on top of a parade float right now. It's
made of a latch.
One you got a one. Oh my God, who gives a fuck about it? Yeah, let's just
skip it. Number I got number one. I got the number one roll. We'll come back
to you. So I rolled so bad. It ended my scene. Yeah, pretty much. You'll see
So, Chef, sorry, fuck! Cook.
There we go.
You're chilling with Sullivan right now. What are you guys doing?
You guys killed Sous Chef.
You're just standing by the button that releases the animals, which I think...
Smoking weed.
Is everything in here was, would we say it was dogs and humans?
It's dogs and bugs.
And bugs.
And humans.
Dogs and bugs and humans are in here.
Screaming humans.
Yeah.
So, yeah, I mean, you're just chilling in here and you're smoking weed, you said?
I mean, I actually don't think Sullivan could probably smoke weed. I think he might get...
I don't know. What's Sullivan... What is he like doing? We're just killing time, right?
Yeah, for sure. Yeah.
Yeah. So...
You guys are probably playing...
And I don't know that I hate him yet, so...
Yeah, you're probably playing war.
I'm down to play war. I'll play war with Sullivan.
What about Rummy?
Rummy's too complicated for Sullivan.
Yeah, definitely. Also, not as good of a two-player game.
Would be good, yeah, but then you can just tell him... You can make up your rules as
you go along and can confuse him.
- Do you start to realize he's a bit of a mark?
Like when you start playing cards together?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- He's a W-A-R.
- Sullivan, I have a really fun game we could play.
- Oh, what?
- Do you have three cups?
- I can go get them, hold on.
- And he goes to the back room.
- Say the game is called Fuck the Frog.
- He comes back with three cups.
- One of them's a different size than the other one.
Is that okay?
- That works, and do you have a ball?
- Hold on.
- And he goes back to the room.
- I crumbled up a piece of paper.
- That works too.
- Oh, awesome, okay.
- Do you, wait, actually, do you have one more ball?
Okay, I crumbled up a different just in case. I need an extra yeah. I crumbled up
two pieces. Okay, amazing. This game is called fuck the frog. Okay, so I'm going
to put one, so I'm going to put one. How much money do you have? I got like
three hundred dollars. Okay, let's bet three hundred bucks to start. I love
telling my friends how much money I have. Yeah, amazing. Okay, so
could you put it on the table? Yeah. Okay, amazing. Now just follow the ball.
Okay, I'm going to put it under this cup. Okay, right, so follow the ball and I
have it right on the edge of the table that I'm doing this on you're
definitely you're just a roll roll balance ball. By the way, balance
beside it doesn't have to be very high for him. It's a nineteen. All right,
whatever you do, you're going to trick him. Keep going like yeah. I mean I go
ahead, pick one left, middle, right at least roll inside to see if he crits.
No, okay, you got you got a three
subtract five from that base. Okay, okay, so what you said to go ahead, pick one
middle left right
left is the best that doesn't really round, but okay, okay, sock him in the
face and I take his money and I'm just running away. Okay,
damn it, where are you running to? I think I'm going to run to the parade.
Okay, cool, wait, wait,
and I fart to you know there's a there's a faster way to get to the parade.
I fart there's a faster way than running to get okay. Well, you know what
I've run to the exit of the zoo and I'll call a fucking uber. Yeah, and on my
phone I get like and I go, oh shit, hold on everybody and we
tied like a hard right. I go down the stride going towards the zoo. The zoo's
got to be close to the parade. While you're doing that,
you make this hard right.
The float starts to fall over
as you're making this hard right.
There's a number of things you can do to try to prevent this. Okay. You should
start to come up with them. Okay, well, and I'll give you, I'll give you help if
you're having a hard time coming up with ideas. Are the people still under his
control? They absolutely are. Oh, so you can have them push it back? So I was
thinking about it, yeah. I guess, well, before they push it back, I'll have them
get under it.
They're all under where it's gonna fall, so they can catch it if it does fall all
the way over. They're gonna catch it. Yeah. All right. I guess it's a float.
It's a lot of people too. And it is. How much does the how much force is the
float exerting? How much weight is it falling over? Just a float. Let me ask
Chad GPT. I can give me one second. Just give me an over under 500 pounds.
Oh, like okay, like per person, right? Like that kind of thing? No,
just the whole thing. Oh, I mean it's
Is my disc that can lift 500 pounds? Can it lift? Can it push it back?
No, it's a car, basically. No, it's also unwieldly, yeah. Right.
Maybe it's not like the whole force of it yet, because it's only leaning a
little bit if I act fast. You could negate 500 pounds of the force and we
can, I can adjust the DC for that, if you're, for whatever you're gonna do, but
I'm not gonna give you like advantage or anything. Okay, then maybe I'll have everyone go to
the other side and pull it. Okay. All at the same time. Okay. And then maybe also do
the disc to do 500 pounds. Okay. To try and do both. So spend your, spend your
spell for that. I'm going to roll for their strength. Their strength check for
this. Not great. Solid six.
You said solid. That sounds okay to me.
Yeah, I guess that's a good point. So yeah, what do you say to command them,
by the way?
Go and pull on it.
Yes, master. And they all like run around, children first, because they can
just it's like a yeah, you know it's like in a video it's just whatever the
smallest thing goes through the closest units are craft yeah exactly there's a
little zerglings and they're going over there to and just like a good like
thirty percent of them are just crushed by the flow. They're pulling there on
the other side. Oh the on this I'm sorry about that. I hate it on to them. So
they're so strong. No yeah, you start to fall over this float is like I mean
it's pretty high up by the way, so like I'm going to give you I'm going to give
give you a chance. Am I driving or I'm not driving riding on top of the flow?
That's what I thought I was driving. No, no, no, because how'd I turn then
what you commanded them? Nice try. I thought you were doing
interest. I'm gonna tell you what that one on perception. There's some other
reason. Yeah, so I assume
yeah,
so it's gonna fall is the sense I'm getting it's gonna fall and you're gonna
okay. Well, I'll levitate
you're gonna levitate with what I could levitate before,
but I can I'll stand on my disc that I made to push it. Your disc is all the
way down there.
What I was- It doesn't move at lightning speed. What do you mean? No, it's
pushing it back.
It's not like under it. You were on the disc pushing it back. No, the disc was-
okay, if I can imagine here. Well, it still fell. So, let's imagine, let's say,
is this what the- can we say the float looks like this, maybe? Eudropean. And
these are the wheels?
Yeah, no, I don't even know if you have to show the camera, right?
it.
That's what the flow looks like from the side. What is that? Yes, yes, that's
already covered that and okay, okay, and then this is and
this is me clinging on to it. Yeah,
right, the beauty mark. Wait, hold on.
That's me clinging on to the floor near the top of it right. We can is that
true? We parts the top yeah. I don't know why you're a lawyer. It be, but
yeah, we could agree on that. Okay, the top would be roughly this area, so let
me draw an arrow to point out where the top is yeah, the folks at home just
listening he's he's drawing the rest of what you imagine you would draw for a
penis. If you're so that's an arrow pointing to where the top is and I drew
a little line to divide off the top for sure. I might have to put this in the
discord and it needs to be what you said. Can you do me a favor when you're
done? Send that to him? What's up? Is that just yeah, just keep going, but
Okay, okay and then let's say that
there's a bunch of people here, but
from the hair below the balls right after people, we mean hair, okay, I mean
those are wheels. We'll just put a hole at the top of that, so that's a
common. This can come out of stuff, but anyway, the point of the point of this
is that I would love to know what that was. So let's say it's Lee. It was Lee.
It's leaning over this way right. It's going like this, then my disc is was here
like pushing against it right. So can I not just get onto my disc?
Yeah, you can. Okay, that's what I would like to do. Alright, can you show that
to the camera?
What's this character sheet I think? That's my toad I drew.
You drew a toad? It's eight tons by the way.
What is it? That's how much it weighs. Eight tons? Eight tons. This thing
weighs eight tons? Yeah. Thank you, Julio. But yeah, so... Julio.
I
and
I've just get off onto my disc.
Yeah, you're fine. There's going to be some collateral damage for okay. Well,
that's fine yeah, not too much
because I don't weigh more than five hundred pounds. No, certainly not okay,
yeah, okay,
and then I need you to roll dexterity. Oh wait, no, you know what I just
realized this whole thing didn't matter because it can only go three feet off
the ground. Well, it's three feet. I'm saying three feet from off from where
you were on the float. If you let me do that, but I don't
what does it say? It was three feet for you are it's three feet above the
ground, but you would think about the ground you're on. If you're in
Colorado and you're going three feet above the ground, just because you're a
mile up, I'm three feet off the ground right now. Oh, are you floating to the
on the side of it? That's what I was thinking I was doing. Oh no yeah, yeah,
so I maybe I'm just going to have to jump off
or try and climb down really fast.
Okay, which one do you want? I'll climb down really fast and I'll command them
to catch me if I fall down.
Here's the thing, I mean this is all happening so fast. Yeah, let's have you
roll
acrobatics or athletics first, just to see how you do it climbing. Sure, and
those are both balance ball? No, one is one is one is our arm and the other is
balance ball. So, pick which one you want. I'll do balance ball. Okay,
that's a ten. Okay, all right. And then,
God, all right. I am gonna need you to roll talking 'cause you're basically
kinda communicating with them really fast, and I feel like this has been
happening really fast, so I wanna make it a little bit more difficult.
Talking is another ten. All right.
So, what do you say to get them over there to catch you? Get over
here. Get over here! You do it twice. Exactly.
yeah, you're going to take some damage. Okay, so we can't be that much damage.
Can it do me to distract him? Oh, my glasses fell off. Oh, look at that this
time.
Oh, you drew. Oh, cool. Hold it up.
Get out,
you take
nine damage. I'm at one. My distraction didn't work at all. He just showed him
a nine nine nine. Okay, you're not
You're at one health right now. Yeah. And you also see on the ground. We can't lose
another campaign.
Your worst nemesis. Oh no. Is it Batman? The floater. No, not the floater. Damn,
that's a good idea though. No, Professor Magical. Oh fuck. Oh my god. No.
I've taken shit. I've destroyed your float. Now I will destroy you. I cast
detect magic, the one to stop it.
Is he magical? He's not
I'm show I'm showing him the result of the detect magic. I'm somehow I'm like
it's like making a like a hood come up. It's like no magic detected. I'm like
witch thing. Yeah, I'm showing him like you're not magic.
Oh, I hate you for that. Okay, Mr. Normal. I'm not Mr. Normal. I
professor magical and I hate you professor scientifically normal. Not
even a professor. I am a professor. You should make him show you. Okay,
the guy who said make him show you his show me a thing. No,
not you got it. Mr. He's crazy. He's a villain. They'll show you this
thing for no reason. Oh my God, that's really roll for initiative.
What does this thing look like?
It looks awesome. Can you describe it to the vein? What is an awesome thing?
Blue. Blue? He is magic after all. That is a 14.
That's gonna be besides that. Yeah, it's a 16. So he is. I'm gonna die y'all.
Damn. I'm dead y'all. Yeah, okay and I'm waiting for my Uber. Yeah, but this is
all your fault. I saw the little cartoon float that was coming. It fell over on
on the map, so I'm going to walk over to the parade. Okay, that's true. Yeah,
wait, can I press the button? Can I press the distress signal that all uber
drivers have that sends a distress signal to their to their rider? Yeah, so
you can go
you press it. He's not going to go faster, but he is, but he knows that you
know, you're in trouble. You still have people you can control to okay, cool. So
the first thing I'm going to die before that, though, probably he's going to run
up to you and just try to like wacky with his staff, because again he's not
magical. Okay, that's pretty okay, pretty cool that you clock that, but
okay, he's definitely missed. Okay, sick, he's got one more. It's his wiener
swing around when he swings the thing does that probably hits you
fifteen AC, fifteen. Oh, is it really yeah? You wrote the fourteen and I saw
it and he has no strength. He's all owned damn. Did you guys see that he
this almost killed me unfairly. I wanted to I he wanted to kill and kill
didn't even ask
I thought your a you to you pulled out that d six any number on that any
number on that d six would kill me and you know it and you don't get to see
my drawing.
Where's where is it? Oh, nowhere
we erased it, but you can look at my toe. You don't get to see it. Oh,
now I realized what you meant when you said that I can see it now. Yeah,
you can see it in the thing.
you know anybody who looks like this
man,
I mean probably the folks listening Caleb drew a pussy and a butthole. Yeah,
yeah, where's the arms? She has no or
or maybe they're taking the picture. I'll give her arms. Hand jobs are
useless. So let's talk about it. Yeah,
your turn, my turn. You have an army. Yeah, do it.
can I control the army and also cast? I can't believe you fuck. I feel like I'm
sorry I almost did that, but also I'm pissed off that I didn't get to kill
you.
I did not mean to do that. Do I what's that? What's that? Do I get to command
the army and cast a spell or is it either or I think that the command
armies in action? It's okay, it's too am I do I get the sense that well so yeah
what can what can they do? I mean you can tell them to go. I mean the whole
point was that they would go tear tear Batman apart. Yeah, turn them into a
But can I imagine, can I gauge by looking, like, is it like spaghetti arm
adventure time type guys? Is it, you know, is it Terminators? Because I just
want to know if I should use them or if I should cast a fire spell.
For sure. So, I mean, immediately around you, the people you got to pick you
up again were just kind of random folks. So you have some strong people,
some are like...
But there's a lot of them.
there's like there are like you could reasonably get like
twenty five, twenty six people to just mall this guy right now, okay, I guess
fucked that's I think I'll do that. I think that makes more sense than a
fireball. Yes, he tried to like stab you with his staff and you just like
backed away and he just hit the ground yeah and I go and I say eat him
well, they go gobble gobble gobble gobble and they just run up and start
eating him. How many people is it just just twenty five twenty seven, but you
see other only twenty five, but other people now are that I eat that much
eat. They're all trying to get in on it. Now the whole they like the idea of it.
Yeah, I kind of unlock the twisted true nature that a good villain
isn't just fighting. The hero is also revealing something about society.
Most people are hungrier than they believe possible. That's what my that's
but my whole revealing is about yeah. People love to eat. I'm a cook. People
love to eat. That's what he's revealing. That's crazy, Patches. I know, I've
gotten that wrong like
eight times. That's crazy.
It's like the scene in Day of the Dead. Exactly like that, but if you can
imagine,
it takes a tenth of the time, because there's so many more people.
He doesn't even have time to say a joke on him. It's like the nematode
SpongeBob.
Sorry, but anyway, so you guys, you guys, I mean you did that now. I
think, keep in mind, you don't have, you have a limited amount of time
you can have these people under your control. So once you've done eating
them, you should probably start marching back. You probably arrive at
this point, like, "Oh yeah, I don't wanna waste any time." I'd
dap him up. Yeah, you'd dap him up. Let me hear one second.
That's a 15 on performance. I assume it's balance ball. And we're gonna
back to you. So you were just dodging Batman. So we're gonna go back to, oh my God, my brain,
the Rambler. So you were dodging Batman and Hamsterina.
Ha! What a futile attempt at trying to hit me, Batman, you bitch. Give me that Batman
voice. Oh yeah, sorry. Oh, I hope it's all set up. Hello? There's your classic voice,
Batman yes, it's my classic voice that I've heard but I hate you and I hate your voice
But I love your suit Batman
What I love the way you're dressed
Like a bit really you look like a fucking bet
but also a man
And if I wore it I'd look different
and because I'm I think I'm shorter than you, I think I think it's I would look
like I was in my daddy's suit. It's your because it's bigger. What are you still
doing the ram? What do you want to kill? You want to sorry attack that man or
hamster? You know what do you want? What was I doing before? Because I had like
I had some thing that I was, I had this big plan in my head.
I hit Hamsterina's on the desk door.
She's not doing well.
Yeah.
No.
She's not doing too well right now.
I guess me saying, me talking about how if I wore Batman's suit, it would be as big as my daddy's suit, is a Babble Blast.
Oh, I like that. Yeah.
So I'm going to roll for Babble Blast.
Roll it.
that is a six plus.
Or is it a DC? Is it a DC for Babble Blast?
Yeah, I think so.
Because it's 3D6, right?
What did I put for your own thing?
It is! It's a wisdom save.
So he's going to make a wisdom save.
So you don't have to worry about that.
Oh, alright.
Here comes Batman. Unfortunately, he is pretty wise.
Oh my God, it was a 19.
And he got a 19, so he's able to withstand it.
What about Henrietta the hamster?
Yes, it is a cone. That's a good point.
That's a good point. Henrietta's a hamster.
Ham-ri-etta.
Henrietta the hamster.
Hamster-ietta.
Oh my god!
Damn, they both resisted your battle blast.
Um, yeah, they know that.
I gotta say.
From dating you, I learned how to avoid your crap voice and your shit stuff, you see?
Now you just know I'd be tall enough to wear Batman's suit and it wouldn't look like my daddy's.
It's not gonna work.
'Cause I'm the same height as Bruce Wayne, Batman.
Now you're just annoying me in real life.
Just kidding.
Just a little joke.
Bruce Wayne is your identity Batman.
What?
No.
No, it's no, it's not.
Wait, hold on.
Maybe Batman.
What?
How did you shut up?
No, it's not.
My name is my name is Batman.
Obviously.
Bruce Wayne.
No.
Batman.
Bruce Batman.
Nope.
Not.
Bruce when Goose man, man, your name is on Bruce Gooseman. It's not Bruce
Gooseman. It's Gooseman. Fuck you. I'm not. It's my turn. That one's good
try to attack
whoa trick shot. Eleven plus LEM or what you're saying my AC is a
fucker.
Yeah,
How much stop?
Stop. That's enough.
Roll. Yeah, roll one more.
One more, one more.
The seven damage.
OK, it's not that bad.
Yeah, and he's going to do it again.
I have 11 health.
Stop. It's an eight.
And yeah, that's not going to do this.
OK, and then hamstring is going to roll on through.
So all age a charity saving throw.
What we say she was five fifty thousand twenty twenty four.
Fifty thousand.
I have a net. Oh, the measure. One fifty thousand, like thirty thousand one
thirty thousand. Yeah. Yeah.
What do I get to do? One fifty thousand one. Yeah. You dodge that. Okay, but now
she's going to. It's just a dodge. I don't even get like an attack of
opportunity because it was such a good roll. No, the whole, her ability allows
her to negate attack of opportunity. You said her, by the way. Rolling by, but
now she's going to roll back around and this time it becomes a hit and that
does hit you
for
here
for damage,
so
looks like you're looks like you're out of juice. Rambler looks like I'm out of
juice. Batman what no what no
stop stop stop copying me
the
old man with his head turned on his children to I said arms. I said a
different thing. I win I'm the bad yep. That's because I've run out of juice.
That's what I was saying earlier. Let's cut back to you guys. So you're
marching on to this scene
and you finally get to the to the door. So you can enter door the ramble. Yeah,
The Rambler, you hear this crowd outside and you guys have made it
and this is what they sound like.
Can we have a toast, please?
Okay, so I was like you did a while to probably go.
That's how is that them banging on the door at something?
It's a glass door.
They're very delicate banging with a girl. They're running.
It's the back door. It's the back door like near the patio.
yeah his peach lido's a little peaches drug wife is just in the pool. Just
hanging out
this is them knocking on the door.
No, no, it's not. No, that's some playing that's actually this so
Batman.
What what is that? Oh, it seems I've run out of juice, but the whole
there's there's a there's a lot more juice outside.
Yeah, that's some bullshit.
I don't know.
People crash through the door while you're like trying to find the quip.
There's a bunch of fuckers.
And Batman, Batman like...
And they're bitches too.
Batman says, Hamsterine, here give me that.
Sorry, I keep doing this.
No, Batman.
Hamsterine, we gotta go.
This is getting too fucked up.
And then she says, "You're right, Batman.
Let's get out of here."
And they start to try to run out of here.
And then you hear crush, crush, crush, crush.
And then you hear the dogs barking.
And you hear the bad guy, the main bad, the amazing.
(evil laughing)
I've got you now, Batman.
And we've all got you.
In crashes through the manor,
what looks like Optimus Prime,
yo, the robot who saved you.
and if you take Maisie up up town, which ends in an E, you reverse that
anagram. No make
optimus Wayne. No
we should have known I should have done that earlier. Yes,
to this way, your cousin Bruce,
and I'm here to finally kill you
and one more thing and he pulls out a scroll that looks a lot like the
declaration of independence.
my God,
I can't believe you've done it.
We've been trying to do that for years. You've successfully stone of
independence.
He's like how you do it. He's familiar with the movies, he does an appreciation
and he says
it's not the question of independence, then fuck that. I don't care
(laughter)
- It's a counter spell.
- And he casts it.
And all--
- Oh wait, wait, wait, hold on, hold on, wait, wait.
(laughter)
- Wow.
- Damn it.
- He casts a spell and all the people there
are now under his control.
- Oh fuck.
- Who gives a shit, he's on our side.
He's on our side, right?
- I'm not on your side.
- That's what!
- It's 'cause I said F that when he pulled out the scrolls.
Hey, it's not because you said
I don't care. I just want
he's got five stars on Uber and I'm his friend. So and we get free rides and
there's going to be a golden car.
I really don't care at all.
We're kind of all kind of middling villains anyway.
We're not, didn't really aspire to do that at any point.
I changed my voice too.
In my whole thing.
Oh.
I was all like,
I was all like shit, I better like make sure
I betray them.
I got the frog.
The frog was going to release the animals just in case.
Magic missile!
And I shoot.
I shoot a magic missile.
It's a magic missile automatically hits. You should use your automatic hit.
Thanks more. I guess I should have. Yeah, you 1D4 plus one. Okay, so that's
two plus
two is four plus
four is eight. Nice. Oh my solid damage to Optimus Wayne.
You see Batman hamster in by the way are gone. They already look they yeah,
they are pussies and they know
but roll for initiative. Okay, you got a free hit. Can I just can I can he get an
instant reaction and hit me in the face? Of course I got seen I got to oh shit.
I caught it. Whoa.
I got it. Finally you got here. You finally got it to that's happened like
five times. Fuck.
All right. Can I use you can take I want to go basically we got the you take that
one. If you want we got the bit. What's wrong with these aren't going to work
either. You don't need to wear glasses. I basically what I want to happen is I
want to walk. I want to say magic missile. I want to walk right up to him
and basically be toe to toe and cast magic missile into his face, and I want
him to backhand slap me and I fly across the room and I die yeah.
I'm the cook. I have barely you can cook me. I always you can cook him into the
yeah my powers. Oh like a lich like what's a like a cook like a no eating
is a
no it already is how it a sandwich. I was trying to figure out a sandwich like
if you like you don't get a sandwich as powers when we need a sandwich. No,
but you're cooking a sandwich. No, you do you do you do. Thank you guys. When
you eat a tuna sandwich, I think this is backing me up. I don't want to cook my
friend. You just
live for you just came five stars on uber the golden car and the only and I
know that I will never first of all the car is not on the way. You don't know
that you I know that I know that there I will never have. I will never feel
greater than I do in this moment. It's all downhill as my rating at five. He
said it himself. You can't go above five point. Oh, what if you what if you
roll? The only one place for me to go is my rating four point nine nine. What if
you that's the only place I what if you roll to see if you get the the coveted
six star on Uber in the golden car. Do we want to do that? Yeah. Okay, we convinced
him he wants to live. I want only if there's a golden car. What is he? I'm
trying to think because I mean think about also just not to get into my
character's psyche too much, but think about his brother. Mr. Wonderful is
famous as a TV show. You could have a cash cab show.
Taxi cab confessions meets cash cab where you ask trivia questions about
fingering fake uber foober foober foober. If you roll, you can make food to
higher than a fifteen or four over by a d twenty. Yes, okay, you get the gold
higher than what than a I get the gold car right now. If you get higher than a
fifteen, you get it right now.
What do you get? I got an there's a card in the way. No, no dice, no dice. Why
we okay, okay, wait, so many years, I say no, just kidding. I don't need to kill
myself. I just wanted to trick the DM into maybe giving me a golden car. Damn,
I thought that I was going to say we should go by Cilo rules for a second.
And if you get three, four,
four, five, six, four, five, six, four, five, six, we got my dad. I don't like
taking things away, but we got it. We got to we got to add a little bit of
flavor there. So it's do you guys roll initiative, by the way? Yeah, I got a
I got a two.
Should I roll initiative?
Am I dead or alive?
I mean it's up to you. Did you want to die just now?
I wanted to die but I basically got convinced by my friends.
We need your wizardry.
I'll stay alive and I got a 19 on initiative.
Oh man, only if you got that roll for the golden car.
And then let me roll for our friend.
Friend? He's our foe!
Our foe.
Okay, plus...
Oh, minus.
Okay.
first. Okay, thank God. All right, so first is going to be you, Mr.
Wonderful with that 19. All right. Oh yeah, you don't want it. You don't want
to die. You want to you want to take the freebie I gave you. I basically okay. I
have completely had resolve my resolve strengthened. I don't want to ever die
okay in my entire life. It's you're so scared of die. Yeah, I have a new fire in
my heart, but I still also have one hb
yeah. When you rolled that that eight, it's like
the ceo of uber text you and saying, but maybe one day I had no, I think
actually what happened is he texted me. He's no, he's he texted me a picture of
himself riding in a golden car and said you will never have this and it made me
like lit a fire in my heart where I was like I'm going to become the greatest
going. I'm going to kill that guy and I'm going to take that golden car super
Super Saiyan, because I deserve it because no one else has ever done
like I did uber in Gotham City. Yep,
you send back to you, I never get this. You'll never get this. You send and
then one day he gets I get this. Yep, you send back a picture of your
face, photoshopped on his face in the car. Yeah, and you say we'll see
yeah,
yeah, I know I've been seeing I killed it. You killed it. You got it.
I want to cast a gun as ours scorcher. I'm gonna have their scorcher. Yeah, and I
need a red dragon scale.
You have one. Yeah, don't pay attention to material. Okay, you dragon tail
motherfucker.
I can as our scorcher about a cadaver. I've ran one campaign where I cared
about material components and that was
that was annoying because I'm not smart. It has to make he has to make a
Dexterity 14 saving throw. Okay.
He does succeed, but he gets half. He gets half.
Half damage. What does he get? Let's see. He gets half of 3d8.
Damn you. You still have spells. I haven't cast any of my spells.
Really? You just gave me way too many spells.
Yeah, I wanted you to have all the funny names.
So I went a little crazy there. What the fuck?
Oh, that's nine damage. All right. He's not he's doing okay,
but as a level to spell take up two slots. No, I also didn't say that, so I
can't let you do that.
I should have said that, though we're gonna kill this robot. I should have said
that up top. That's really it. You know what can I tell you something cam? Yeah,
it's a really good idea.
I just assumed that that's why I never casted this. Yeah, save the best for
last. Well, you always give him the best shit in these games, man. That's not
safe. No, I just I'm the only person that's gonna read crazy. Yoda's gave him
the
That one's good.
But it doesn't work on like anything like the...
Like a monster?
It worked on the first campaign.
Yeah, it doesn't work on the monsters.
I mean, the last campaign we did...
That's because you're always picking like a paladin.
You're always picking like the strong guy.
You guys just don't have the brain like me where I figure out how to make shit broken.
I want something so overpowered that it's...
Like when I gave Leo the gun.
Yeah, it ruins everything.
Yeah, that was fun.
I like that.
Yeah.
Okay, all right.
I'll give you something.
And I never get...
I have a knife and I can make a soup.
I have speddy broth.
I think next. What the fuck is speddy broth man? You never even explained what
speddy broth is. You wrote it down wrong. At the end of this thing you'd never
explained what speddy broth is. This is what he was just saying, you can't read,
so that's the whole thing. I can read completely fine, watch this. Max HP,
current HP. What if next campaign... Balance ball. What if next campaign,
regardless of what it is, you are the Kool Aid man and you get to
break down the wall?
That's crap. Yeah, I thought of it on the spot, okay? It didn't work out
Well, whatever it's you got a right yeah, yeah, your turn. I am you blast him
with agonizing scorcher and it's just like like a fire blasting into him.
Those it's actually a line of fire line of fire. Oh yeah, right. A line of a
line of roaring flame. He holds up his arms, try to block it and it just it
still goes through him and he doesn't melt him a little is like an anime. I
I think he I think since he's a robot and he's metal, maybe and maybe some parts
of plastic since the transformer you have fairy fire. You can do that. Whoa,
but I just want him to be ugly is all I was going to say. Maybe he gets a little
ugly from here. It's a little droopy. Well, I can I can I can do something
maybe he sounds like this. Maybe he's
guys. Is it doesn't really come across? Okay,
What I'm going to do is roll and I'm starting to understand speddy broth
here. Why? Because it looks like it's going to be a character in something.
No choice. I'm going to roll verbal distrabident.
What? Is that what I wrote? Verbal distrabident.
Give me that. Give me that.
This is distraction. I have the handwriting. Let me see. Oh, you do
I think it's maybe possible that you put speddy broth. I didn't write that.
You wrote that. Prove that. Prove that right now. This is verbal distra...
That is your handwriting. What the fuck? You also drew a fucking giant pussy
on the back of this piece of paper. What the hell? Can you show that one
time to the camera? You already showed this to everyone. Did I show this
to the camera? You show your drawings too many times. Okay. Well, that was...
And I'm gonna rip this in half if you show it again. No, don't.
That's nice. I just wanted to show off the king of pop.
See, he just showed it again. He literally just got it showed and he showed it a second time immediately.
Okay, so I'm rolling verbal distratadim.
I wrote the word down.
Okay.
I just, there are certain times where the lowercase letters become kind of their own cuneiform.
You turned a T into a T.
Cuneiform, my friend.
Is it cuneiform?
Okay.
Oh, really?
No, you have to roll a wisdom saving throw.
I'm trying to sound smart, but I sound like a loser.
You have to roll a wisdom saving throw.
Yeah, for sure.
And it has to be higher
than a 14.
Well, let's see what his wisdom is.
Yeah, he gets a plus
on that.
Sorry. It was literally a 13.
I would. He gets a plus two on that.
So, damn it, dude.
I love doing this with you guys.
Really? Yeah, I never want to stop,
man.
Man, me too.
So.
What is out from his Wayne's turn?
He is going to
shoot out his missiles out of his fucking hand.
Bitch.
So all of you guys roll DC.
Well, what if I take my speddy Brother right now and I sped up
and down. Roll a balance ball.
Balance ball.
That's a six. Thirteen. Ten.
Speddy.
your bed, a broth, you all take ten damage. Okay, can I have a moment to
dead?
So basically I just I just shot my my fireball and I'm like I'm having I'm the
and I'm completely anime and my teeth are gridded and I have the sharp tooth
and I have and my eyes are shining and sparkling and I'm having like my
internal monologue and I'm going like let this fire symbolize the fire in my
start that I will never give up that I will pick up and drop off as many
passengers as I can to get that six star to get that golden car away from that
piece of shit ceo, because ceos have everything nowadays and there's nothing
left for guys like us little scrappy villains like us just trying to do
what's right for ourselves in our own sense of twisted morality, where we
believe evil is good and good is evil and this is the last straw. I'm going to
take this robot down and then I get exploded by the missile and it's tf
two vibes. Oh fuck, how do you know when it does all the chicken nuggets fly
everywhere? What they're both down? Yeah, yeah, I have to HP. You have
healing potions. How much damage did I take? You took ten and how low can you
get before you outright die? Oh, it has to be negative your own HP, negative
your own HP, not a negative hat. Okay, no, no, I gave your max. I'm at negative
He has healing so can I go get him off his body? I'm chunks. Well you you make
I
Mean, of course I make well if you get healing potions
Fortifying broth and I've speddy can you
Bake the healing potions into a loaf of healing bread
That would take I'd have to wait
Okay
least, so I'm the only one alive. I mean yeah, I'm going to go try to I'm going to
go try to get the health potions off of his body.
Okay, what health potions you do? I gave you potions. Oh my God, look at the
bottom of your wizard. Those are those are spell potions. Oh, there's only for
spell. Let's say potions for replenish two slots. That's my best go along with
it. You've after you're the one who had healing potions. I have a spiny,
steady and okay. I do have three. What are your potions advantage on persuasion
and deception? I can, I can cook three things. I'm not a potion. Can I cook
three things right now?
What I'm going to cook three things. I have three ingredients
three. It costs like it'll cost a bonus action to cook right now. I don't give a
fuck. Okay, that's just you better be careful. It's the only chance using a
bonus action.
so I just rolled the twenties right
yes. I walk into a restaurant, say let me use the kitchen. I'm a cook three
things
yeah
yeah, let me cook.
Okay, yeah, I'll have you
things. I'll you do it. Let's do it twelve, please be a thirteen or a ten
and a fucking nine. Okay, eleven is
bewitching aroma. That's going to be an aroma, not even a food. No, just a
scroll. He just cooked a smell. The cook creates a dish, the captivating aroma
seven twelve and nine
so when we finish saying what it does, though yeah, I can all creatures within
a thirty foot radius centered on the cook must succeed on a DC fourteen
wisdom saving throw or become charmed for one minute.
Regarding the cook as a trusted friend number twelve disorienting spice
he
still
popped up a bunch of chicken and put it in a pot and made a spice
and turned it into powder.
You like boiled a leek.
The cook adds a potent spice to a dish.
Okay, I take back what I was saying about Caleb not being able to read.
You did not give him anything cool.
No.
You're trying to make him smell the spice.
I just looked at a bunch of random-
No, no, no. I'll be honest.
I looked up a bunch of shit and copied and pasted it.
all right. This one will work this one because you can make you can make you
can add you can make a spicy petty.
I'm so excited to hear what the third one is. Cretan cloud, you are cloud of
disorienting particles. That's that's to each creature with a fifteen foot
radius, said third on the cook must make a DC constitution saving throw or be
blinded for one minute. Okay, I'm a number nine
it out right now. I wish I read these
acidic surprise.
I knew there was I made sure there were a couple because I knew there was
going to be an arc, at least a moment. We're going to deal with the mayor,
but I didn't read all of them. The cook prepared a dish
he mother fucker actually he he the cook prepares a dish
that release
an aroma, a spice and a surprise
I'm making a surprise
okay, okay, what is
a corrosive acid? The cook makes a range attack against target within thirty
feet, dealing three D six acid damage on a hit. Okay, can I use I'd like to
use disorient
to blind is blind. I want to blind. It's a fourteen. Do you see fourteen
constitution saving throw? All right,
Roll to see if you can get the lid open on the spice.
Dude, 19.
So you release the spice.
I have to dodge one attack.
You have sensors.
You're dead. You're in chunks.
You're in chunks.
Yeah, yeah, go ahead. He does try to attack you this time. He's trying to
just smash down. You think I fucking lie about these roles. I've been watching
him like Patrick has been watching keeping 18 dude. How much how much I
have to HP dog. We're done. Yeah, you guys are done. You thought you had to
two H. P. I had to oh my God, HP
yeah you die.
We're all dead. I don't I'm so afraid of fucking dying.
I don't want to die. I just I don't want to die him do okay, wait, wait, wait,
all right, what's up? Can he can he get a hail Mary? Can he can he cook as he
slips slips out of consciousness? Can I takes out you take out your materials
on your ingredients and your tools, you take out a mandolin. Yeah, I'll let him
let all of the of shallots. Let me look with my chunks and nobody's going to
want that dog cook with he cooks. I think that is the save here is you are
allowed to do one more turn. If you cook with his chunk, I cook with his chunks.
I cook with his fucking what electable dish. So he's really dead. Can I get the
rambler up? If I win this? No, you just have to get another turn. Why you could
You can hide, you can run, or you can hide.
Well, what do I need to roll to use as chunks?
You just need to roll a d20 to see what happens to his chunks.
Hopefully it's not something...
17.
What am I going to be?
17 plus your...
Oh, you know this one. You use this one.
This is speddy.
Confusion concoction.
Okay, I want to use the confusion concoction.
What do you have to be, a d14 again?
Yep.
I thought that was reasonable. It says wisdom.
Oh my God, just killing the role. Yep. Okay. He just that's a loaded dice dude.
Give me a wire. If anyone was watching the video, yeah, see that's more like
these two
and that's a nine hundred. He already hit the eighteen. Whatever. Yeah. Wow.
Tell us what happens. Wrap this piece. I didn't expect you guys to get that
hurt. Why did stop it? What? Stop? Stop? What? Stop it. What? Stop you change.
I'm not touching anything.
Damn it that
I think you, but deba deba deba deba you went to deba deba change my voice back.
All right,
please stop stopped stopped it. Okay, this is yeah. He just won't do the
engineering work, whatever it'll just sound like shit. No, don't you don't
don't touch anything not just chain
make sure that when you hear me, make sure my voice sounds like me.
No, this is...
You're good.
Okay.
I don't sound like this!
This is so fucked, dude.
We're done.
I'm done.
All right.
Let's hear this.
Can we hear?
Fine.
I'll read it.
No, this is fair.
Maybe I made him too overpowered or maybe you were.
I don't know.
you were just goofing around like usual. Or maybe you gave me twenty pieces of
food to make that all suck shit. No, they were all actually pretty good.
Why are you like talking different when the filter's on? Pretty good, because I
don't, no, pretty good. I was just talking a little bit higher than usual,
because now I'm adjusting to the voice now. Okay, do it again, but talk lower.
Alright, let me try that. I'm gonna try to sound more... I'm not even like
thinking about it. I like this
Batman. Oh man, all right, Batman kind of cringe
I was like that, but if I had the squeaky voice of
stop man, no, if I had the squeaky voice on, we've been fine. Okay, what's it?
What happens? What's the this is the worst ending we could have got? Yeah, so
Optimus Wayne now
takes has all the people and he has them all. The spell he casts cast them in his
as long as he lives,
they will be under his control. Wow, so he boards up. This is them. He turns the
mansion into his fort
and
rules over Gotham and spends the rest of his days trying to find his cousin.
Bruce. It's actually a manor instead of mansion. Manor, yeah. Yeah. Okay. But yeah, his insatiable
need for revenge has never... So this is like a Dark Knight, or this is a Dark Knight Returns
style thing where it's like Bruce Wayne and Hamsteretta or whatever. They're training
in secret. They're going to do like an uprising. Yeah, but here's the thing. Alfred is still
still alive. Oh my God, I forgot he was at the dinner. I too is still alive.
Wait, wait, wait, Dylan ending. I need to hear it again. Say don't is still
alive. Dylan is still alive.
That's
doing the
the Dylan
and he gets a little self conscious. So he just starts bobbing his head and
yeah, he goes like
he's pointing down yeah he's off beat yeah when you're a star, check my star
yeah
so there is
because because
Dylan is a
myself. It is blue and my favorite shirt,
and my own shirt, so maybe maybe Dylan will find a way to win to to conquer.
You have a Dylan monologue. I do have a monologue. You have a deal in monologue,
Dylan one. Okay, can you improvise a Dylan monologue after your monologue?
Sure, yeah, I can or start with a Dylan one. Yeah, I do Dylan. Yeah,
sure.
That makes a lot more sense. Yeah.
Okay.
Well, it's been tough. I gotta really figure out a way to stop this guy.
He's super strong. Why does he need to stop the guy? I don't know. He's not
a superhero. He's driving his car. He levitated through the building. He
he thinks he's got to stop the guy
Dylan has powers, but he only one of the powers still and thinks he's the only
guy who gets
doesn't know about
so stressed out. It is room he's on a computer right now he's writing for his
blog yeah and he's just like well, it looks like I got to stop the guy and
he's like has like and it's his blog is words of an insomniac blog spot dot com
good.
Oh man, like even I'm going to need my sleep and he is a little winky emoticon
yeah and he goes and he goes into his closet. He opens it up and he sees,
first of all, all the same blue shirt, but only one with the gold star
and he puts it on and when he goes to he says Mom, I'm taking the table cloth
and he goes to get the table cloth and ties it around his neck. Yeah, and he
is like, oh, I almost forgot and he goes and he puts on his favorite pair of
jeans and he goes, yeah, wranglers, they're wranglers, they're a little bit
distressed and he thinks that's the coolest shit in the world. And his shoe,
what's his cool superhero shoes? New Balance. Those are the cool dude. No,
what is it? I know, I know what Dylan's shoes are. He wears New Balance maybe
normally. No, he wears those, what are they called? Starburys. No, wait, that's
a good idea. He's wearing a pair of all birds, but then his super hero shoes are
starbreeze
because of the star, yes, and he puts he puts
you see that he he drew like with per like permanent marker gold star on the
starboard yeah
and yeah and he goes out and you see and it's his
super hero name is the star is yeah and he the super star, the super the
super star one hundred percent and he you see and it's like a you see him. He
walks outside of his house and he turns like down the road and for some reason,
like the manners all the way in the distance and he's got his hands up on
his hip really yeah, like he's trying to do like a heroic pose, but he just
here and he's and like it's like silhouetted from behind him. You see the
manner you see that's like now this tower and yeah, you see like a side by
had a cut now with Optimus Wayne.
- And you see him from the...
♪ I feel love in my bones ♪
- You see him for stays from behind,
standing at the, looking at the manor.
And you can see that one of his,
one of his shoes, he didn't put it on right.
And like the back part of the heel of the shoe
was like collapsed and he's like standing on it.
(laughing)
- You also see him, you see also him,
you see him like while it's from behind him,
like the camera's looking a little too long.
So he just like from behind.
♪ To let my system blow ♪
- Like he just like puts his hand on his nose.
he's a little bit yeah yeah yeah and he
and then somebody else just walks by and he's like trying to show him a shirt
and then we cut to the real ending. Is it we're not the real ending? Sorry,
the other ending, that's the dylan ending. I'm sad, they're both real.
You got the good news. Now we get the bad news. Okay, the bad news,
the good, the bat and the ugly. Has anyone done that in a batman movie?
Joker says that. Really? In one of the comics. Oh. The Joker's a fucking loser. Joker's a
bitch. Yeah. I'm trying to find it. He wears makeup. Girl. Girl. Girl. I know he does not
wear makeup. It's actually scars. What the fuck? Where is this from? And makeup. Well,
it's actually a combination. Yeah. I think it's his skin that's turned white from all
the chemicals. Chemical. He falls in a bowl. I fell in a bowl now I'm the Joker. A big bowl.
Yeah for my song. What's it called? A Vat. Yes. He throws him in himself. He
falls. Yeah. He throws himself into a vat of acid. That's for my son. Back to
his wife and he goes, I'm fucking weird. Um, something happened at work.
Something weird happened. I fell, I fell wearing, I was wearing my classic red
hood. Yeah. And now I've gone completely white with a red. Also, ha ha ha ha ha.
he it's all a big joke to me, isn't it
so funny
all just here by me. It's a big joke to me that I fell it's Batman. Okay,
you got got like a damn
okay.
Who knew my own cousin would betray me and round up my strongest foes and then
pray them also.
Sometimes it seems all people crave is chaos.
It's a pain.
It's the next great thing.
The next distraction, a respite from the slow death of life in Gotham just shows you what
a place, what kind of place this is.
I wonder if it's even worth saving.
Maybe I should hang up the cape, the cow, the costume, put away the mask, go back to
to telling people to jump when they get close to the platform edge at the train station.
Or maybe Gotham needs more of an enlightening rod for the most sadistic people in the city
to organize violent campaigns around. Maybe it needs something more substantial, something
that can last. Maybe a why. Maybe I'll make a why a really big one like, like five like
like five stories, but you pay for membership with crypto, but it's built on a sustainable
all block chains like environmentally sustainable. It's powered by solar wind
and not stupid. No one. I don't like that stupid. Maybe I'll stress up like a
fucking bad. I don't know. He already did that. How does anyone like themselves,
man?
God, it's hard.
I feel like we're all having a hard time, you know, in the city.
The pandemic. In politics, yeah. Like, is voting enough? I don't know. Like, I
I consider myself a leftist but it's like damn
I should open a Y
and that's it
Wow
Something in the way
Yeah
Don't have any feelings
Blue shirt with gold star
Something in the way
(outro)