So, uh, this way.
Uh,
see it like you were before.
This sucks.
Yeah.
No way.
What?
I want to give up.
I'm going to get there.
You're going to get it.
I think I'm going to do it.
Give it to a given your all.
Yeah.
Something in the way.
You look so fucking cool doing that right now. Hold your chain out.
You look like you're on, man, that's a thin chain.
That's gonna get snatched. You better tuck that. Be careful. I will snatch
that. We are all snatching chains now. So let's just, you know what, last
time,
You guys were broken out of Arkham by some kind of giant robot and then you were brought
to some kind of lair that kind of existed out of nowhere and were told by this villain
guy that he wants you guys to kill the Batman and to take over Gotham for him. His name
is Maisie Uptown. And he said the plan for you to do it was to first enter into the mayor's
manor and basically kill or dispose of somehow all of these very influential people, except
for the mayor, who you would then, the rambler would then torture by rambling. We're at that
point in the plan right now. Now, the plan, the rest of the plan then was to go eventually
go to the zoo and then go to the parade and then storm the thing. And now what the rambler
is going to do by torturing the mayor, at least what the plan was, was to get the mayor
to give you, Mayor Lionel Peach, to give you the emergency bat signal. The reason why was
to summon the Batman when Maisie Uptown tells you to so that you can trap him inside the
Mayor's mansion. Not sure how just yet. But, um...
That didn't happen though.
No, right now we're at the point where we had the gumbo, I believe it was Confusa gumbo
was what was used. I think it was confusing gumbo, right? Okay. And by
used by the chef and or the cook rather who is a chef,
everybody ate it except for the general, the
general who's visiting and Dylan, who is wearing a blue shirt and a gold star.
Right, we remember Dylan. Made of felt. Otherwise, Alfred ate it,
everybody else ate it. So now,
you also
So Mr. Wonderful, you took out all the security guards by making them soil
their own pants. No. Oh yeah. Or making them think they did. I soiled their
pants for them. You soiled them. Oh, and they all left one by one. Call me the
Soila. Yeah. I think your name is... Call me Soilin' Brown. What's his name?
Mr. Wonderful. It's Mark Cuban right now, though. He's been wonderful. I'm
disguised as Mark Cuban. You're disguised as Mark Cuban on the roof. No,
just as Mark Cuban, but I happen to be on the roof. Okay, got it. I'm not
the fastest mark Cuban on
yeah sorry. I've got the you got on the different kind of character yeah
and then meanwhile the rambler you and you the sorry the chef. I make sure I
round out
the cook who is a chef. Oh there it is yeah. The cook is my name fucking right
you yeah. You cook the meal. You cook the gumbo. You have some gumbo stored. I
believe to oh I cook at a meal. Say that hey come on. I don't think I'll say that
I have a good one
FF broth, any clue what that could mean? I fart face broth. I have speddy and
heel.
So FF broth was probably,
and I have no ingredients right now. I used only- It was probably fortifying
breath. Oh, fortifying broth, that's what it is, fortifying breath. If I remember
that.
Any guesses for speddy? That was probably speedy preparation. Speedy or spaghetti.
It's not very like me to omit an E.
- So, well, you did this time.
It was speedy preparation.
- So what, heel was heddle?
- I mean, what did you write down?
- Heel.
- Okay, yeah, it was heel.
Do you think it should add another letter
because you didn't?
- I'm just saying, if I wrote down speddy, I meant it.
- I mean, there's nothing on here that says speddy.
My glasses are gonna fall.
- Okay, so he can't even read it.
I can't read it. So there could be a speddy and you're just kind of glossing over it.
Stop it. I'm reading it all the way through now.
And you don't see S as in Samuel.
I'm familiar.
Okay.
How does Patches have his mic all the way up and you guys have it all the way down?
Because he's in a taller chair.
Any other mysteries you'd like for me to solve while I'm at it?
That's not our job. That's Batman's job.
Yeah.
What is the reason for the blueness of the sky?
Condensation.
from the blue water.
All right,
and could the rain how much of a grain of rice or if you doubled on a chess
board, a grain of rice, would you take that or
if I doubled on a chess
would you take would you take that or me?
You if you don't I would take you
if you double your Nintendo switch
Me or a PS5? Me or a Nintendo Switch 3. Definitely a Nintendo Switch 3, it hasn't come out yet.
They made a Switch 2? Yeah. Your turn. Imagine that. The mayor is terrified of you right
now. Terrified of what's going on. He doesn't know what happened. He's like, "What's..."
He's saying this, "What's happened?" And he's sort of cowering in his chair. You see the
general goes over and says, "Mayor Peach, I'll make sure I'll protect you from whatever
whatever is happening and Dylan, meanwhile, is sort of still enjoying his
quail eggs, kind of eating, his hands are on his hips up here, you know,
yeah,
shirting, he's Rodney, sure danger fielding, sure, sure thing, yeah, he's
doing a little bit of this,
he's doing
and when he stands and I, and I unleash ultimate locks his knees every time he
stands, yeah, second he's
bowed, locks his knees, hands in the front,
leans forward like this, yeah,
yeah
nodding. He nods when he's not talking. Yeah, yeah, no and also when he talks
goes like this, like he uses one hand yeah, yeah, and he puts his finger up
when he's entering a conversation. Yes,
it would be like a be like yeah, that's a good point and like a kind of like
solely he won't. He doesn't like fully owned and at times he farts and blames
it on others or never admits an animal in the room. Yeah, the dogs farting
just parted just now. I was like I couldn't hear it. He's like I heard it.
The dog is far right now, but before I say it, I'm the only one who heard it.
You guys, Oh my God, just right now the dog just farted. That just happened.
Did you hear the dog just for here's a dog?
So yeah, what do you want to do
right now? You are not suspected of colluding with whoever
these quail this quail egg broth into a uh uh confuse it what it was so it's the general
confuser yeah everybody that's what speddy means yeah everybody is right now like this i think it
means speedy they're going like this right now they're all confused except for the mayor
um the mayor isn't confused yeah and you have like i'm gonna here's what we're also gonna say
is that like let me see how long is this yeah you got about a minute of action right all right
So let's say like right now we're what's what's actually you roll initiative just so we have like a turn order established
What'd you get?
Our new camera box our new friendly, but I don't know what it says
Your feet it's a feat or what is what is initiative is I'm gonna build a box as your BAM where it is a
eleven. Okay, eleven. So you got eleven. Okay, and I'm just going to roll
initiative for the other characters in the room. It won't really dictate too
much. Probably mayor.
And then that was general and then Dylan. Dylan will be going last.
Good as usual. As usual. Well, I got picked last. I'm used to it. Save the
best for last. That's what he says. Yeah, the best for last. He says it as
if it's a reflex, it's before he's even processed what's happening. Yep,
all right, well best for last, I guess cool. So
yeah, I mean they kind of already did their turn, so it's really you're up.
This is like you're like six seconds of like kind of like figure out what you
want to do. How do you want to take advantage of this moment? Everybody's
confused. You have a chance to torment the mayor, but the general is also
there comforting him right now. So I should get the general away. You can get
general way, you can take out the general. What's the general's weakness? Peace.
Shack. Peace? Well there's technically peace right now. There's a lot of chaos actually.
Okay. Everybody's being poised. Are you crazy? There can be a chaotic peace. Yeah. There's
peace and chaos. Like Vietnam. Duh. Do I have a gun? It was chaotic. Did you guys listen
blowback? Do I have a gun? Your character? Yeah. Look at your sheet. Why are you asking
me? I have a ranged attack. Oh yeah, right. I forgot. I gave you sort of whatever you
wanted to put there. It could be a gun. Okay. I have a gun. Oh yeah, you chose fireball
to steal from mine. I remember now. Thanks for reminding me. Do you whip out the gun?
Yeah. I'd pull out a gun and I'd try to shoot the general. No, I think that was from some
some of the thing else. Okay, some of the thing else. Yeah. Do you say anything or
you just pull it out? You can. I have it. I'm just like, man, hold on. Let me go
get that my fucking gun. Once I just gotta get that thing over there. Dylan
sort of like, huh? Dylan, you're gonna wanna close your eyes, man, 'cause fuckin'
some bullshit's about to happen. I don't even remember even what I think I was
gonna do. I can see. There is some, you just, why don't you, so. That's perfect
Dylan body language right elbows away away right right yeah man, you better
just get the
maybe you should go on the roof or something, maybe get like
I don't see why it would be. Oh, you know it'd be fun. If you go up there and
you get a parachute and try and jump off with a little bit of his fingerless
gloves on for protection. Dylan, what you're going to want to do is put on
your cardigan, your fingerless gloves.
you're going to want to go all the way over to the bass. Do not do not come
back until your pocket watch says an hour has passed. He has a booger, but
he's trying really, really hard to pick his nose right now. Just go do that.
Roll persuasion with advantage. Dylan's like a lot cooler than Dylan. Nat 20.
Holy shit. Really? Yeah. Dylan. I should have rolled that into the dice thing,
but yeah, you've got to. Dylan's star starts to glow
and he floats up to the roof, just phases through the ceiling and like the
figure fully in his nose.
He appears on the roof. He doesn't see you yet. I just say I knew it yeah,
but Mr. Wonderful, but Dylan is on the roof with you right now and he's
looking to
stop
stop. All right, what does that accomplish? Why are you saying that
dress like that? What kind of joke do you think that is? What do you think
I don't even really remember which guy that is.
Me neither.
But Buddy, I know he was not one of the presidential candidates.
Yeah, he was a shooter, but I don't remember which one.
Well, don't.
I remember, I can remember for all of us.
Let's keep going.
What would he do?
He'd shut up the black church.
Ah, rats.
Rats?
You call them rats?
What did you say?
I shouldn't have said that.
So here we go.
Yeah, so that's just like a free action. You can still pull out your gun.
Alright, so Dylan's gone. Obviously he's the ultimate powerer.
I'm just not going to be able to see.
I wish you got that.
That was crazy.
I'm going to need to get them repaired.
Oh lord.
I can see perfect.
Can you?
No.
Oh, okay.
Obviously, he's the most powerful person who could have stopped me or anything.
I think I have a very clear and open shot at the general.
Can I just walk over to the general and shoot him?
Why do you need to walk over to him?
You don't even need to walk over.
He's like the gun.
Yeah, but I have terrible aim, but like walking up to him in his boondock style,
the back of the head
boondock
docks, a style
or
we're having a race
walking up to it. The
there's only in my mind there's only
and it's the same know where he's from. That's not fair. He knows when he says
boondocks. We know what he there's a one boondocks and it's two Irish guys.
That's true. You want that other show out of out of existence. I like one
character.
So you do you walk up to him boondock style? I walk up to him boondock saint
style.
He starts speaking in Latin. And instead of saying shepherds we shall be, I just
say,
"Well,
shit." Okay, yeah, the general... And when I have to kill people, I don't
that much. Yeah, roll intimidation. That's kind of bad. I've never killed. My character's never killed.
My character. Roll intimidation. Well, no, I'm like, oh, sorry, roll mouth or talking,
talking. Well, I'm shooting him in the head. Just roll talking. He's telling you to roll.
Well, here's you can either. OK, we get 16. That is a dirty 20. OK, yeah, he's really he's like,
the
of
the rest of the year. You're gonna get there. They're all they're all
confused. There are other don't shoot into the room. You can phase
through bullets. No, we don't know that. We don't know that. Well,
might have just been for the bit. Okay, then I'm shooting a painting.
Okay, don't one of the most expained, expanse of things. I mean, all right,
you use up all your ammo.
I can get more. No, I guess so. You're just at a jail. Yeah, but I can get
more ammo from anywhere, anywhere shopkeeper. Is there a shopkeeper around?
There is a, I mean, there's, there is a, like a, there's like a Duke style
boy. And it's not like a, it's not like the kind of, why not?
You know what? I don't let them do it. I'm not going to let them do it.
And we're in the middle of the city. Okay. There might be a place to get
to the next turn soon. Yeah. So anyway, moving on, the mayor's like,
What do you want? What do you want?
Can you hog tie yourself up and then put like,
just get in this bag or wait? No, you're not. I need,
hold on.
Cook was area would have told him about an apple in his mouth and get into a big
pot robot voice guy. What am I supposed to be doing? Hold on.
I gotta give me one second. Yes. I switched things around.
Is that it?
I have to F him?
You started with an F?
I don't know you were getting real close to that.
F word.
Get him to tell you where the emergency bath signal is.
Where is the emergency bath signal?
you're still talking in the voice. I know I you what well you're going like
being a mayor, because because I can't I when you hear yourself, you feel crazy,
okay, stop and a cheerful and a playful boy. I'll do that. I'll go okay, so
so funny, but my my
vocal.
I don't know where it is
okay,
all right, and then I call the gun out. I put the gun in his lip in his lip in
his lip, like
like right in front of his teeth right here, that's cold as fuck
no talk like there's a gun in your lip, put your finger in your lip like this
wait, wait, wait, why teeth because he's trying to block it from going in his
mouth, teeth closed because he doesn't want in his mouth. Oh he's going to yeah
he'll show he's going to show you right now clean that
fuck
close to
yeah and now into the microphone.
You know where the damn bat signal is, motherfucker.
You know that there's a goddamn bat signal somewhere around here, man.
You get the fucking...
There's one on the roof.
There's probably one on the building.
(whimpering)
All right, roll intimidation.
Christ, that was scary.
(laughing)
I can't read that.
Nine, plus whatever you're talking.
I mean, roll advantage.
Nine, oh yeah.
You have a gun in his mouth.
I now know, but that's scary.
And then, plus talking, so that is a 15.
Yeah, sorry, plus talking.
Okay, yeah, he says he says
you
you man. I'm going to get in there. I'm walking there. I'm going to get
fucking cooties and shit man. You got to come with me to do this. I don't
want to get fucking no, because your daughter is I don't know. I'm going to
get fucking cooties man. I'm fucking gross man.
All right, he's going to come with you. I put the gun in the back of his head.
All right, you two now. Yeah. So let's start with the hell you doing adjusting
the chair. You're just in the table boy.
You got to tell me that
why what's wrong? Can't say that dressed up like a wizard. What's wrong with that?
Mr. Wonderful.
Mr. Wonderful. Yeah, you're on the roof. You're part of the plan is basically
done. Yeah, here give me the voice. So he just gets to chill now. Lucky. Now you and the cook go to the stew. Go to the stew?
Wait, what was my voice again for this? The stew. You did. You did this voice. What? Go where? Go to the stew. The stew? You said the stew?
I would like to go to a stew. He wants you to record a song. Yeah, kind of under, super
underdeveloped. Go on Zoom! Go be my associate in the zoo. Meat. Meat? Stew?
meet from the zoo? I mean you can do what you want when you get there but first I need you
to get there and you know come to your place. Are you gonna call us a car or? No you have
to take a train I don't want any of this to be traceable. The train? The train! Or you
can walk out of the front. Wait, wait. I'll never take the train. Pardon criminals are
terrified of the train. Never taking the train. Why do they have to go to the zoo? Because
It's a backup plan.
In case the parade doesn't work, I want somebody to release the animals from the zoo.
Hey, uh, uh, Mr. Wonderful.
Yeah. Can you hold my hand?
Yeah. As we go to the train. Yeah.
OK, we start walking to it.
What's the nearest train stop?
Gotham Train Stop.
What? Why are you laughing?
What's so funny?
Wait, are we all on this call?
I don't know. Why is it always a call?
It's not, no you're not.
Then how are you talking to them?
I'm talking to them on the call.
Yes, I guess.
That's a call!
God damn it.
What do you want to say?
I don't know. I just wish I could be part of the conversation.
This is okay.
This is okay, yeah.
No, the nearest train station would be
Peach Station, named after the Peach family.
Of Lionel Peach Fang.
so why'd you say Gotham station or
okay,
kind of a weird time to make a
twisted sense of humor, hang up on this. I'm hanging on
okay. You hung up on him. Damn, that's cool. You can actually hang up. Yeah,
okay, we start walking over to peach station. Okay, we go.
You guys are at the train station.
Okay, yeah, you see some people hanging around. Hey, okay, here, let me play the
ambient sound of the train station. Hold on.
It's true.
It's pandemonium at the train station.
Okay,
the guy,
the guy making all this noise, I put a dollar in his cup.
It's pretty good for a one man band. It's not too bad.
Okay, but first I mean I don't even I've never even ridden the train, but I
don't even know what to how to do this. We jump the turn stock because we're
criminals. Yeah. Do you guys jump to turn so blow up the
I duck under the turn style? I say okay, I go like yeah, I'm right behind you,
but I pay you pay. Yeah, the person does not look up for their where their
station is. No matter I cast a minor illusion of me paying for it.
That's bad ass. It works. It works. It looks like tokens, though. It looks like
for some reason, though, it's card now. Oh, it's all card now in Gotham. Damn.
Damn. They kind of fucked up. Gotham. That's how they trace you. Is it QR code
menus in Gotham now, too? Yep. Oh, yeah. And it's a you have to show your Vax to
get in. No. The bars. Wait, is that all still? Wow. They blame the pandemic on
Batman. Yeah. Oh, my word. He's going around getting everyone sick. He was
seat in bats. Oh true. Yeah, I guess everywhere they got selfie spots for
everyone to take selfies with on the walls. They've got painted weirdly in
design to stand in front of wings. Yep, they got wings painted on the brim.
Bro, an influencer in Gotham is probably the most dystopian thing I could ever
fucking think of.
Okay, so where do we go to the train? Are we going? Is there only one train or do
we have to figure out which train to take? No, no, no. Which direction? Do we
know which direction to go. There's only one train you said. Well, there's not
only one train, but you're out here at this station. What line are we on? You're
on the- oh man, I didn't map out Gotham this much. Well, you don't- I just even a
little bit, just what- just name a line. I got you this. Yeah, okay, you're on the
blue line. Okay, so that doesn't make much sense based on what I know about
Gotham.
I don't think we'd be near there at all. I think the blue line is like south to- I
think that goes to- no, this is going north. This is I- no, I'm- that goes from-
so we're on the Batman line. I'm doing the mind pal goes from blue village
north. Okay, I'm seeing it. Cut city cuts north. So I'm like spur it's
getting cold.
It is getting cold every as it goes as we go further, like like the window
start to freeze over. You go down to gothic becomes a desert. You go east to
becomes Asia.
Okay, how many stops are you ready? Five stops
and how long or too many for me. Yeah, how long does it take
excuse me like 30 minutes? Okay, we get on the train to express. Okay, we are on
the train on the train riding. Yeah, and
I get in the middle and I say, excuse me, excuse me, ladies and gentlemen of
the of got the of the blue line. We are going to do a little performance for you
today. If you'd like to support a youth basketball league, go ahead and give
whatever you can and then being him for doing like watch everyone get like a
little stiff. We start doing a lot of weird back flips. Yeah, and you maybe
you could beat box a little bit and take care of the beat box thing. I gave you
what play the beat box when I gave you you didn't give me a beat box one.
There's a beat box sound in there. Press it.
There we go, so I'm new doing back flip with the railing, your parking, but the
railing I'm sure I'm actually you're doing that and I'm trying to ignore you.
so I sit down. I take off my backpack that I'm wearing and I unzip it and I
take out
I take out Moby Dick and I sit down. I go
and I cross my legs and I open it to page one.
I put on my glasses and I flick my finger and turn past the title page.
I'm spinning on my head in the middle of the thing and then I and then I take
out my phone and I just scroll through. It's the you hide your phone in the
there. Yeah, you cut out a part of the book to put your phone in
roll talking, roll talking, a performance
for
you just
you can't everyone can see that you're a cook. Yeah, I'm also I'm also like I'm
waiting off the chef's hat and roll again. I'm incredibly overweight. Yeah,
so I'm take off, take off the hat and roll again. No, not in real life. I mean
in the game in the game. I wrote I wrote okay. I'm trying to spin on your chef's
hat. Oh, it's a problem.
thirteen. There you go all right. You get a lot more you got a lot more yaw
there.
Okay, thank you guys so much
have an amazing rest of your day. Suddenly from another car
kick in two guys dressed in fucked up makeup come in with guns. We're the
goofers gambit and we're here to grab all of you. I said I just give him a
dollar. You give him a dollar.
God bless
and then you had a row. Everybody's like kind of cowering and they're like
giving them the money and they do that and they go to the next car and they do
the same exact thing. They just keep going from car to car robbing people.
You guys don't have to stop them.
Bill and you're watching tick tock on my phone because I'm a villain, max
volume cool and my tick tock sounds are they're coming out of my phone. So like
this
and I scrolled another one and everyone sounds exactly like that because I only
follow one account, your follow, you're you're clicking the sound and watching
all the videos
yeah
every video posted with that sound, but it's only two it's only two videos. So
you're scrolling back.
Yeah, you're scrolling up and down. So once you're done with the air drop them
elbowing the person next to me, you make a make a side by side on air drop you
reacting to it. Just
damn what the hell is this video?
I'm watching it on the train. I shouldn't watch it on the train.
Yeah, and I do that you plan paying the camera over to me and I just
go
yeah, you get to the you know the fucking vibe. So the cook
the zoo, the zoo doors open, the train doors open. How does it drop you right
in front of the zoo. No, no, you're like a couple blocks away.
What time is it?
It's midnight right? Yeah, it's pretty late. I'm calling an uber on midnight.
Okay, call it. I'd like to get in the uber with you. This is a dangerous
neighborhood. I hear there's animals
you wake
the voice for the way. What are you doing calling an uber? Stop your true
away. Don't call it. Can I use your card? No, I'm fucking tired. It's a business expense.
Yes, you can write it off. Disexpense it. No, just go to the zoo. We're going right
now. That cook saves the zoo. That cook saves the zoo. What do you see? That cook saves
the zoo. Pup putt saves the zoo. Never played that? No, I don't. Pup putt saves the zoo.
I've played pup putt, but not that one. Oh, okay. Was that one good? It's basically the
the main one.
No, there's like Papa goes to Mars, right? Or something, or the moon.
Shut the fuck up.
No, that's different. Stop, you tricked me. Let him walk his line.
What's up, y'all? How you doing?
Zach XA is the zoo.
Okay, bye.
Hang up on him.
Just don't.
All right, yeah.
We're in the Uber.
The Uber pulls up.
Be the Uber driver right now, Patches.
Okay.
How you guys doing?
Tweet Sullivan in an accent is what happened.
land.
How do you guys doing? I'm the driver. Okay, I'm going to leave you a tip
tomorrow. Just we just try and bus you get I'm hitting the no conversation
button as hard as I can on the I'm. Do you have the trivia we have? Do we have
trivia? Oh yes, you of course you do. I love trivia. Can you go on the block?
Let me find some bad nature. I see the trivia and I go on my phone and I
change the route to be like I add a stop that's across the city and then the
second stop is this who okay? What super villain once broke Batman's back,
leaving him crippled and wheelchair bound? Oh, who is Mr. Wonderful? You
all hear the rule Raza ghoul Joker Bane or Mr. Wonderful is Mr. Wonderful.
We turn my headphones down a little bit. They're so loud. You're correct.
It's Mr. Wonderful. What those Bane who is credited with creating Batman?
who is
wrong? It's Bob Kane. That must be as disputed, though
is it disputed? It is disputed. It's either Bob Kane or Bill Finger. Yeah,
is it true? Bill Finger,
they took it from Bill Finger. No, they fucked over
in Detective Comics number two sixty seven, a magical cobalt from another
to mention decides to help Batman fight crime. What is his name?
Is it Mr. Mitzelplitz or something?
Yeah, what the fuck? How do you know all this shit?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Do you know all this shit about Batman?
Yeah.
The original Batgirl was related to what familiar Batman character?
Fucking Commissioner Gordon.
Yeah.
Which of these Batvillains were introduced first?
What?
The Penguin, the Riddler, Catwoman, or Mr. Freeze?
Say it again.
which of these bat millins was introduced first the penguin, the riddler, cat
woman or penguin was first
whoa wrong was wrong is scared me scared me to I thought I was getting
electrically. We made her first. Oh man number one, okay, so that arrives at
the zoo. Yeah, that's what happens. You get a question wrong. He's like sorry,
I got to drop you off. All right, I was that I reached to the front seat. I
pull his eyeballs out.
No,
I
I'm a villain. Oh Shit me to
sitting behind him and I'm also I'm doing that and I'm also shoving my knees
into the back.
I'm still kicking
I start I start punching him in the chest.
he's dead. He's in terrible shape. At least okay, do the car we're back. Oh
my God, we are car. We have a car. We have a car
way before you go into the zoo. You should you should pick up some uber
mission. Oh, no wait. Here's what we do. We drop. We'll definitely get some
movers later, but we do we get some writers. We throw the body in the back
seat or in the trunk. I put the body in the trunk. Yeah, I take the car. Okay, I
drive through the gate to the zoo.
Oh, then we can go through all the exhibits.
Busted open.
Uh-huh.
We'll cut to that in a second.
Okay.
Manor.
You are brought to --
My name is Manor.
Manor?
What's up?
My real -- the Rambler's real name is Manor.
Excuse me.
I should have talked, but I have to --
Manor Dilfrey.
The mayor, you're pointing the gun in the back of his head.
Lionel Peach brings you to his daughter's room.
you there's fucking Barbies in here. She's an adult. There's a bar. She's an
adult. There's a Barbie from the back in the day. What's a measurements? I don't
know. Thirty you have. What do you mean? You don't know you're the dungeon
master. You have to have something. Thirty thousand one and thirty thousand
really? Did she feel like this?
All right, yeah, so his improbable daughter hair color blue,
like though not for me, but she's an SJW. Yeah, that makes it worse.
I don't want to be in this room. She vote probably. I bet she has a
freaking probably the penguin, probably her dad, Penguin Obama.
No, yeah, she's the worst one of the worst. You show me the signal.
Okay, okay, okay, fine.
And he goes under the bed, and he taps it, and out drops a like a, um, this like super,
super, this hyper power flashlight.
And it's got like a Batman symbol on it.
It's like, you just point this at the sky and that's how you get the Batman to show
up.
How bright is this damn flashlight, man?
Is this fucking...
He's tricking you, man.
He's scamming you.
How bright is this man's fucking flashlight and shit, man?
It's fucking...
It's not just an ordinary flashlight.
How many lumens is this? Because one time I had got, went to the store for the
light bulb that had a billion lumens. I saw a light bulb with one billion lumens
and it was so bright, it lit up the whole store.
It would light up more of it a fucking store.
And I just flash it right in his eyes.
Oh man, a billion lumens? He's gonna go blind.
He's dead.
[laughter]
You're not supposed to kill him, bro.
That's the one guy you're not supposed to kill.
I don't know. You got the kind of got the thing you're supposed to get.
Raider lost Arctum.
That doesn't really matter again. Oh, wait, can I now?
That was 10 days. No, I don't. I don't just guys, right?
What? I can't disguise. Can I? You were already in a disguise.
I have a disguising ability is what I need to ask.
You're French. You don't have a disguising ability. You are in a disguise, though.
Can I change into the mayor? You can try to dress up like him. You're going to need some other.
I mean, like, are you, are you, uh, how are you rotund? No, man, are you round? I'm pretty
normal. I'm round. I basically look exactly when I take my mask off. It's string bean.
When I take my mask off, I don't have to become a string bean. When I take my mask off. Okay.
I look exactly like Lionel Peach, except I have a big mole.
That's what, that's what the rambler looks like under his, his mask. That's convenient.
Because we're twins and he doesn't know because we were separated at birth.
Is that true?
What?
No.
I just made that up.
Well at least you whispered it so I wouldn't find out.
Hey, you can stuff your suit, you can try to put on a fucking little hattie hat if you
want to.
Okay, I'm going to take out my pen knife and cut the mayor's skin off of his head.
Crazy crazy crazy crazy.
From his neck.
Okay.
So you're going to do a fucked up like skin over your face.
We're going to do a skin over.
All right. We're going to roll a couple of things.
We're going to roll balance ball first to see how well can you put it in the
face? That doesn't count. Doesn't count. Doesn't count.
It has to be inside the camera zone. Six. Damn, dude.
Add balance ball. What's your balance ball? Plus my balance ball would be eight.
It's eight total. Yeah. Yeah. You don't do the best job.
you're going to look like Leatherface a bit for sure.
Okay.
But now you want to do the rest of your disguise.
That's talking.
Okay, Halloween.
It's not Halloween.
No, not this episode.
No.
What is it?
Can't see it.
I can't read it.
This has been a huge oversight by us.
It's been a normal sight by all.
It's a two.
What I see right here, it says it's a 20.
I'm just looking at the thing in physical space.
You don't need to look at the screen.
I just can't see this because it's so close to the...
You look the least like the mayor, maybe.
one of the least what I'm looking at the mirror and I'm just going like yeah.
The daughter comes into the room.
Because I'm actually shaped, but she's that a W is stack.
She sees her father triangle dead on the ground and she sees you got that
literal hourglass figure.
See if she notices.
Can I
I'll see if she noticed how you have you going to see me over her gigantic boobs.
That's a good point.
She has won 3000 size boobs.
30,000 30,000
one door and destroys Gotham
giant.
She can't see anything.
She's all boobs.
No, no, no.
Here's what we'll do to do.
It will give you a chance to try to convince her.
Okay, you're her dad.
she's coming in. She's normally a law school student. I can just turn the
flashlight on again.
Let me ask you a question. How come you felt the need to tell us her
measurements, but not that she was a law school student? I said the law school
student last episode and I didn't mention the measurements. Do not pound
it for that. I'm pounding it. Stop it and hold on.
You just wait.
You are a misogynist.
you are. No. Masogyny red alert. Maybe I am.
Yeah, maybe I fucking am. Okay, so why can't I just shine the flashlight at her
again? You definitely could do that. Yeah, I'm going to do it. Yeah, roll.
I'll roll for damage. That's going to hurt her. I got it. I got it. That
doesn't even do good because I mean, I think it was a good score. All right.
She is very injured.
Like she's just like, just like, just like it just like lights or fucking
shit on fire. She's in trouble. Wait, so I can light stuff on fire with
this. She's not literally, but she might as well be. Okay, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. So then I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna...
So she's out of the doorway now? She's out of the doorway? She's...
Yeah, I mean she's in trouble. Okay, so I'm gonna turn and then just...
Whatever in this room is like a really like thin papery fabric material.
Okay.
Like if there's like a rayon curtain or something.
I'm just gonna shine it at that so it just burns up the house.
Okay.
Yeah, you start doing that.
Well, I got a roll.
Stop sucking off.
Stop saying anything right now.
Okay.
I mean again, probably won't light anything on fire, but like
But what if I got a 19?
I don't know what we're rolling for, but I guess I did let you do that.
You let him have the most insanely powerful weapon of all time.
Also roll a lightsaber.
Luckily it's never going to run out of battery. Roll owl.
Roll my owl? Okay.
Oh. What did you get? Two.
Is that a three or that's a three? Okay, then it was a two. Okay.
All right, you don't notice anything.
Great. Yeah, and yeah, no, you that's the worst feeling in DND. Yeah, when he
says, roll up, roll an owl and you do and you don't know. It's not nothing.
Yeah, yeah, pretend. I never said that. It's a fun, fun little trick.
Okay, cool.
You're having fun over there. Batman is in here, isn't he? So, meanwhile,
go to the transition. You guys are blasting through the zoo. Do we have
music hold on
I love
your plastic through the zoo you're tearing up the place. It's like
night time, so it's like basically the only people there are stand. Here's
all the dogs in the zoo.
There's no did they do this? The worst do ever
that's
the exhibit right next to it.
What are you doing? Which one's the people yelling?
That's the other
dogs and people who are scared of dogs, people who are scared of a way and the
other exhibit
one of the worst suits
where the fuck of the lion
where,
but the kangaroos are also freaking out.
What else you got? Who else is in the zoo?
The guns
yeah we walk by
you drive by the
we
I want the hula hoop.
Hurry car, please stand away.
Please Christmas don't be late.
Wow.
Wait.
That was amazing.
What?
These guys should not be in a zoo.
They could speak English and be on stage.
They're singing that and then we drive by.
[Gunshots]
Three.
yeah, tell it
that's right. That's the guy in the scared people exhibit seeing that
I
so yeah, you guys drive by the worst zoo in the world. Well, it's got I mean, I
will say if it did have Alvin and Jim is probably the best zoo in the world. I
under it.
Money, the worst in terms of ethics, they
had all their money on yeah, there's people protesting this every day.
Release the chip. They wear clothes. There are zoo guards there who are
they're going to try to they're trying to stop your car. They're jumping in front
of it. We're flooring it you for okay yeah. You just you just start killing
zoo guards
and now the guy calls in
you guys. We're
I need you to we at the zoo mother fucker.
I can hear the dogs and the people. I just want to know where it's not. Oh,
Look back and watch me smack that, all on the floor, smack that,
banging his toes, smack that.
I just want to know where the animal release button is.
Can you guys find my contact?
Find your contact? Is he a fucking chipmunk?
Because if he is, he's six feet under.
You killed all the chipmunks.
All three.
Lonely, so lonely.
There should be a fourth one.
You kill him or no?
There's no fourth one.
There was only three that we heard.
Go back to the chipmunk cave and see if you can find a fourth one.
Chipmunk cave?
Cave.
I meant cage, but I said cave.
Well, we're launching here.
It says only three chipmunks can be famous.
It's not a famous one, it's the one who is...
Oh, we need to go to the non-famous chipmunks.
Wait, your friend's with a chipmunk?
I don't think he's a chipmunk.
Alex the chipmunk.
Oh wait, I just found the fourth chipmunk.
No, don't.
Fatality.
that that was Sullivan
tell you where for damage. We don't know if he's actually he's dead.
We didn't even get to
kill them before we even heard him. He was going to tell you where the animal
release. Okay, wait, I do want you really quick to do Sullivan right now to
Sullivan's voice and just what he would have said
right,
because he's a chipmunk yeah.
Oh, hi, you guys.
Yes,
it's what it would sound like as a chipmunk. Yeah, I guess so.
This is how he should have sounded the whole time. Oh my God.
Okay, but then we take Sullivan's consciousness and we upload. Okay,
Can we not kill Sullivan? I do, I want to hear, I want him.
I want to hear.
Okay, can we go back and undo that?
Yeah, yeah, why don't you go back and undo.
Just this one time.
Okay, so we're at the chipmunk exhibit.
Where the fuck is this fourth chipmunk, man?
You guys, oh damn.
No, no, no.
No, he's a chipmunk.
He's not a chipmunk.
No, no, he said he thinks he's in the chipmunk exhibit, but he's not a chipmunk.
Oh, so he thinks he's a chipmunk, but he's not.
he the zoo put him in the chipmunk yeah. What happened? Yeah, I mean he'll
explain okay, wait, who are you?
You guys here with
Mr. Uptown,
driver.
Oh, I see. Oh,
very funny. The guy you better watch out.
Please don't
you guys. You guys here with Mr. Uptown right? What's up to or who's uptown or
nothing much down with
yeah, we're with Mr uptown. He's like dressing like a little chipmunk outfit.
Can I real quickly while I'm while he's talking? Can I be scooping the chip
monks into my ingredients bag? Yeah, of course you can. So that's three
ingredients. There's no frog exhibit here, so I had to be a trip monk. I was
starting to get to know those. Wait, what do you mean there's frogs right
over there? Look,
they're happily jumping. Oh, come on
I'm mad. I've been eating nuts. I don't even like nuts. I'll make you eat nut.
No, I didn't say that you're going to make this frog eat nut. You might not
you really are villainous. You guys want to know where the button is. It
releases all the animals. I know your buddy.
I have one question, though. Yeah, wait, don't tell me it's on the bottom of
your body.
you want me to tell you yeah, but does it release you also
the button yeah yeah it would okay. Well, I'd really like for you to stay
here
yeah. Is there a partial button? Can we press it? I just thought I was going to
go once I did this for him. I've been I've been staking this out for about
two years now, so I would really like to go if I can you undercover yeah, I was
on the cover as a chipmunk for the last two years
just for this. We just killed the chip box. No, I know I saw that okay all
right well yeah. I usually come out and not it's saying, but I don't join them.
They said they said I think well, a little yeah. Well, we need to hear it.
I think they're right.
Christmas
okay, we'll tee you up okay.
Is here
time for
time for cheer time for my
plan.
Loop me. I want
okay, yeah, now I see you should not be okay. Okay, now that's fine. Yeah, they
already dress me down pretty bad. So maybe he should say me. I want a lily
pad.
I don't think it's about the toe. No, you're not here. Who's that? Nothing? Oh
yeah. Where is this? Where
Oh, man. Where's this button? Maybe you should say I want a lily pad.
It's underneath the people exhibit.
Okay. Like what? They're fucking dicks and pussies.
No, it's just, it's just underground. There's no wonder what part of the
ground, the part they poop on. Oh fuck. No. So there's like, Oh,
the part they pee pee. Well, so they, I mean the zoo keepers store,
a lot of the goods, there are the food that they serve the people biting my
lip by the way.
Beneath in certain compartments beneath the zoo and underneath that exhibit there's a lot
of food stuff there.
Does this frog look kind of fine to you right now?
Yes he's fine.
Of course he's fucking fine.
Frog.
Damn.
Yeah.
Can you take us to the button?
Yeah you got to let me out or you got to at least pull me out a little.
Alright all I undo is shackles.
jackals
oh boy.
Thanks.
All right. I'll take you guys there and then I handcuff them to mr.
Wonderful.
I don't know about him
actually.
I'm going to I'm going to put a diaper on him and I will carry him around.
Okay, not sure why this is a diaper, but okay.
All right. I can't I put you on my hip and I start I'm chillin. Okay, lead the
way. Okay, point in the direction to the carrying.
okay, let's go and then
he leads you there to the
break the gun. You're making all sorts of noises right into your mic. You're
a gun. A S M R my bad,
so yeah, you get to the to the hatch.
Sullivan's able to open it for you. You go down there,
hatch and you got me thinking about eggs and then
here, the lady, the voice. Oh, okay,
Okay, now, cook, you remain here with Solven.
Commandeer the button, you, Mr. Wonderful,
head to the parade.
You can, I guess, take the card you have now.
- Oh yeah, all right, all right, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Got it.
I take the card.
- The card.
- Come on, man.
You know what I'm saying?
I know now that you guys know what I'm saying.
What I'm saying.
I want to play with this voice, okay? I can't.
I was.
I'm not a smoker.
How dare you.
It's a little rude, no?
Can you say that again?
(Hawntek sounds)
Oh my god!
That was actually beautiful. That was Hawntek like beautiful.
That sounds like a whale.
(Hawntek sounds)
Can you put that voice on all of us?
Nope.
I would love to do a chorus of that.
You can't do that. All of us do that.
It's not doable. I can't do it.
It's over for you Patrick. It's not your scene right now.
So why don't you go back to playing with your little gun.
I put the gun back together. Thanks. So do you leave you leave the hatch? You
have the car? I'm going to start burping. So I see now it's his scene. Now
real quickly to solve and spit up when I burp him
roll
roll,
talking
strength. Yeah, how hard you can
that is a ten. That's a perfect. The man you hit me my
you. Oh, he made himself burp so that so that it would stop
sounds like a lot more, but
that's like I need to burp you some more. It sounds like you're struggling to get
that out. Please don't okay
man. I got to be a lightsaber now. Okay, the fucking I got to do with the thing
man. Fuck it. Hey, what you doing bitch? What the fuck's up with you man? I had
Wait, I took a, I think I ate the food that the cook made or something.
I need you to just...
Man, there's so much bunches stuff in this fucking home.
So first of all, everybody who is downstairs is now, what, not confused anymore.
So you need to be on the lookout for that.
Alright, I'ma call an Uber.
Well hold on, don't. Wait. That's... Please.
I'ma call an Uber and I'ma get out of here.
Do not call an Uber.
Ring
I see a request pop up from T Rambler
window. What I want you to do is
yeah, I can do that for maneuver pretty comfortably.
Holy shit, no the whole point is that the bat goes to the manor.
So if you do it from an Uber, do you understand?
Unless the Uber's gonna be parked there.
Wait, no, you don't go to the manor.
Go to the parade.
Well, I can't, man, man, I can't cancel it right now.
I can't cancel it.
I, I, I just canceled Uber.
I don't cover the $5 cancellation fee.
Man, I don't even have a penny to my name.
I don't even know why I called an Uber.
Cause you're the worst person who's ever lived.
That's why.
Will you please use the bat signal?
Oh, that's...
[Laughter]
Okay, yes.
All right, cool. So yeah, you're shooting on the bat signal towards the sky.
I'm just pointed at stuff in the mansion. I'm trying to be I'm like being like
what we see some of the guests. They go, Hey, that is him. Get him. They're
French. Some of them you're shooting at them. Okay. They are normal people, so
they will just shooting light shooting light them.
I wonder if in our lifetime, we'll have laser guns in the military. I hope
everybody. And do you energy weapons? We already have them.
They just don't tell us. I don't tell you. Yeah, they're
developing dues. We've had them for years. That's what they
call them. Two of them died.
How many? How many were there? There's 11 people. You killed
two. How many of us there's already dead. The rest the rest
are semi injured. One of them is badly injured. Who's that one
Senator is badly injured. What's his name?
I have to make sure I'm getting that right. Hold on. I'm just standing there
very nonchalant with the flashlight. The Senator is badly injured. Here's the
thing.
Dylan is still on the roof, so he doesn't know what's going on, but
security is no has now been like, hey,
we never pissed ourselves. Well, maybe we did. I don't know. Can I add lore to
Dylan? Dylan is Dylan Wayne and he's Bruce Wayne's brother.
can I add lower as well, but he doesn't know anything about the bat. No
Dylan is one of those really flexible fat guys who can put their head in front
of their leg. No, he's got to be like a no, he's like a pace. He's he's pasty,
skinny, skinny, skinny, skinny, skinny, skinny, skinny, skinny, skinny, skinny,
He can like bring his fingers back and touch his arm.
He does double jointed, he says I'm double jointed and he does the thing where he does it.
Right, yeah.
He does the least interesting double. He can't, he can almost put his foot behind his head.
He like does the same magic trick whenever he's, I know magic because he's like
He has one wallet, he has one wallet in his left back pocket and that's his regular wallet.
Right.
Then his right back pocket, he has one that when you open it up it shoots a paper dove.
super dove. That's his dummy wallet because he gets robbed.
Yeah. Dylan Wayne. Blonde?
Dirty blonde. Blonde, bowl cut. Dirty blonde, bowl cut. Is it bowl cut or is
it like... It's not full bowl cut though. But it's accidentally a bowl cut.
You got a great clips cut and then you grew it out. Right, it's like it
could be side swept but then it like... Yeah, he has bangs and he
does this. Yeah.
He gets them out of his face. It's perfectly kind of swooped in the
the front right. It's like it's only bangs under the same line, but there is
a
and he got braces last month.
He just got his braces off yeah and his teeth hurt so bad. He can only use
really soft so big though.
When he smiles every time he's worth every time he smiles. He does this. I
got my money's worth right yeah,
he laughs like this
and he keeps his keys on a lanyard.
I don't show that he swings when he walks around around his neck. He puts it
around his neck when he's sitting down.
Anyway, I can't touch this
yeah and he goes like this.
Oh my God, but he's the life of the party at weddings. Really is
I want to be real so bad. He is basically real. No, you don't know if
you are built like Dylan. If you look exactly like contact with us,
Dylan Wayne. I know that there's probably fifty Dillons listen.
You look like Dylan, please, please, please, you get us of any time. Yeah,
please dress up like him and send us photos and villains always get. They
always follow the trail of villains, always follow the trail of clues to try
and find out who Batman is. They always mix it up and think it's Dylan and
they're always like corner him and he's like whoa buddy. I don't know what
you're talking about his name. His name is Dylan Wayne. They're following it
from behind. I think it's Batman. They turn him around. It's Dylan with a
I'm sure in the face. What's up
his name's Dylan Wayne, but it's
it's Dylan Wayne by like adoption or something adopted. He was adopted. No
Batman was adopted. Dylan was their actual child. Yeah,
we need another kid yeah and we obviously can't. We obviously can't use
the same d
anyway
back to
you going to the parade, a bare thigh is on the chair,
but he's getting an uber ride right now, and I have I'm looking at all my uber
my
try to complete all the right, so I could go to the parade, but I'm like
going all around every time about to finish. What I got like I see like
another one
stop the guys like saying stop at you who the the mother of the voice. I can't
Oh, no, tell stop stop picking up people. I have somebody in my car. What I
supposed to do
oh
I grab side of his head. I
well, actually for I really slowly roll up the back when I try to do it and
then there's no back window to slam his head against and I roll the back window
up. It takes a long time.
I'm turned around and I'm blessed and scary music, a day to remember type shit
only the break down you put your you put your phone on you put a
you put a on to go to a day to remember, but then it accidentally it plays
you're playing a punk by a punk a punk a bro. I don't know what you are talking
about a punk and he's saying it. We went to he went to click a day to remember,
but then he has a punk by...
He clicked on songs.
And then hit the first one and now
A-Punk by Dinosaur Weekend.
That would be a badass montage song.
That would be killing motherfuckers too.
I was gonna say, sort of like a singing in the rain.
Like Steve McPubrick.
Well me and Sullivan are listening to music too.
We fly high.
I'm not paralyzed but
I seem to be struck by you.
I wanna make you move.
Because you're standing still.
Okay, I burp him. Okay, now I stopped accepting the Uber request. I'm going to
the parade and I'm also listening to music and I'm listening to that song
that goes like, "When you see yourself in a crowded room..."
I don't know how the rest of it goes. Cool, yeah. So you're at the...
And they're playing the... They're playing the song from Titanic at the
manner right now. So the parade is supposed to celebrate Gotham's uh...
Medley mix with moves like Jagger. Yeah.
Okay, then I turn the social network soundtrack.
(laughter)
(singing)
Here, put on Batman voice, not scary guy voice.
(screams)
Oh my god, that was almost so fucking bad.
It wasn't at all. It's a completely empty can.
But if it was a full can, it would have...
If it was a full can, it wouldn't have tipped over.
It would have fried.
What did that last one do?
You got it!
Okay.
The parade is supposed to celebrate Gotham's living parents' day.
Celebrate all the parents who are alive in honor of famous Gotham citizen Bruce Wade,
whose parents are dead.
All parents, good or bad, ugly or hot, ride on top of floats that celebrate,
coaching little league games and helping you with your homework,
Installing a latch key or having the talk anything that still living parents do
The braid takes place at night
Because that was when Bruce Wayne's parents were murdered and Gotham wants to show all the parents murderers
Out there that the night does not fear them or wait, hold on I
Wrote that completely wrong that the parents don't fear the night
That's crazy how wrong that is and that parent murderers should instead fear
the night wow okay cool dude okay, because that is when parents who are
still alive are at their most powerful
at night yeah night. Oh, because that's when they watch flight of the concords
and they close the attic door day
Commissioner,
I've not had a single thought about that
into in like a long enough time. That's making me aware of my age
Commissioner Gordon, who, if you remember, is Filipino watches over the
proceedings intently. His ever visually Gotham City Police squad patrolling for
many dubious villains.
Yeah, and you see people as you're walking by, they're saying happy
parenting to you and a wonderful Parents Day celebration to you. And yeah, it's
a whole parade and all those floats I described or Batman described are going
on. And the scary guy voice, amazing.
The uptown, oh that's me.
Now, it's too wonderful you should have a squirrel. A squa? I gave you a squirrel.
Well that's going to be pretty confusing because I carry around a lot of scrolls so I don't
know that I...
This story will continue in two weeks with our third and final installment of Gun City
Presents.
Batman, the villains are incredible.
Thank you for watching and for your continued support.
You are not going to want to miss this thrilling conclusion.