[MUSIC]
Last time on Gun City, the Temple of TehPenguin of Doom.
The boys finally reach the last room of the Land Caves where they met with the handsome winged gamer.
After defeating him in tic-tac-toe, they were rewarded with a dark Eldritch Boppet that they drove the DM insane with.
So I assume they eventually solved it, leading to the Boppet transforming into an egg,
then hatching into a golden penguin with a realistic-looking vagina,
with strange, tinny blizzard noises coming from it.
Pennsylvania Jim, lurking nearby, saw the whole affair,
and sicced his ninja crayons on our heroes,
with new colors pink, yellow, and green.
After Patrick Yoda's new dark side powers quickly dispatched of them,
along with Ray William Johnson's patented sexual grenades and Blowtorch's deadly... pipes,
Jim destroyed the land caves with deadly explosives.
That's why I didn't want to save that game twice.
And our heroes had to narrowly escape before it all came crashing down around them.
Finally arriving from the mouth of the now-destroyed land cave,
the gang was faced with a row of Ken Bone police officers, along with the Gadd King himself,
who noted the group's tardiness (they were only allotted an hour's time in the cave)
as well as the cave's destruction.
Thinking quickly, the three archaeologists, along with Sullivan the Frog,
hopped onto three Walmart scooters sitting outside of the cave.
It sped off beginning the chase of a lifetime
Oh my god, yeah you guys hopped onto these fucking scooters
um
And you sped off behind you. Um, uh, you hear uh, uh,
The ken bones coming nearby with the the siren, which is sort of just a let it go
But as a siren in the gadsville, um, police, uh, police, uh department, that's what they do
and you guys get a call on your PSPs and it's it's Leo as you guys are speeding
away and he he patches in he says what's going on how's the investigation going
oh I forgot about this guy mm-hmm what who's that who's there it's me Leo
there's a lot of noise around you a lot of a lot of what's going on we're fine
I
well cameron you said the truth
i got a 19 so i win
i didnt say the truth i said we got the pass
the n word pass
oh i thought you meant the pass to go to the cave
ok
he says well i
i'm glad
i'm glad you're watching a movie
i love this movie
and then you see
you see sullivan
go we're running from the cops
i'm so scared
or it's all of it in this movie will
well all my god he looks so it's a bit this movie
i don't know what's gonna happen to me he's been there
you hear uh... is he on one of our bikes or is he uh... this is the thing that i
was on
now he was on one of your bikes that which ones by keepers on i think he's on
blowtoss yeah
uh...
uh... his mom but i know i was not but i think that uh...
you hear we are going to calm down calm down calm down i'd look i i i
I figured as much just based on the general sort of atmosphere and the tone of your voices
as you're, there's sort of a Doppler effect going on.
Look, if you make it out of there, it'll be fine.
Just make sure you get to the galleon on time.
I'll have the Jollibee start everything up for you.
So you can just ride in there and depart to your next location.
You got, you got something there with the caves, right?
You guys are like weaving through like things.
He's trying to talk with you.
I got this for you.
I can't see it.
Look, look, never mind.
We can talk we can talk later.
Just get to the galleon.
Okay.
All right.
Okay in it.
Okay, and he hangs up.
So yeah, you guys are sort of racing down the track here.
So I call him back.
Okay.
He says, well, I looked at can is your refrigerator running
blowtoss.
I know it's you.
Who all right, just just don't die.
I threw my PSP off the bike.
All right, he totally bought it.
All right.
So here's what's happening.
First of all, I'm taking a picture of this for posterity
in case I need to use this in court later.
Okay, great.
just knowing that I did not see you. I you've not sucked my
wiener. I have. I saw patches as wiener and I sucked it moving
on. so what what this is is essentially I have we have like
a little chase sequence here and I have a little like a way
that we're going to handle it. so you have. Cops behind you
right now and basically what's going to happen is it's going
to be a series of things happening as you race down this
track race down this mountain and we'll see how you handle them and they're
going to try to take you out you might be able to get down there in time or you
might have to destroy them you know and fight them as well off on in the cars
while you're doing it so everyone offered I'm ramming into the police car
in a role for initiative to this you you'll have an opportunity to do that I
promise. Okay. 19. Okay. 13. It's a spoiler. Um,
you say spoiler initiative. I mean, where is,
he said that we will ram into that. Well, I got one on my initiative.
Contrived. I tried with my one. Okay. All right.
Okay. Yeah. You're one. Okay. Um,
so the police cars we have, those initiatives are got them. Okay, cool.
So the way that this works is that your cars move at a max of 30 miles an hour, because
that's sort of the regulation for the Gadsville zone.
They don't want anyone getting stomach aches.
And their cars, though, because their cop cars go at 40 miles an hour, so they go slightly
faster.
Is there any way to soup it up?
You can definitely try on your turn.
Who has the best mechanics skill?
Who is the best at souping?
Who has the highest soup speed?
I would say it's you Ray William Johnson since you are a robot and it would probably just
be a straight intelligence check.
Now this first turn it's a Ken Bones turn so one of the Ken Bones is going to try to
drive up alongside you guys so he's sort of like speeding up a little bit getting alongside
and he's saying pull over pull over and then another ken bone
bosses head through the window like in fortnite and uh
starts trying to spray bullets at you uh the three of you so
uh three of you all of you roll uh uh in this case what we're gonna do for
this because uh there's no like vehicle handling i mean there's vehicle
handling stuff in 5e but i don't there's animal handling yeah right so
about well that's actually what i'm gonna do is have
You're going to do animal handling, Patrick.
We want that.
Patrick, you're going to roll for animal handling.
Because that's wisdom-based.
You two, Blotas and Ray William Johnson,
you guys can roll for either athletics or dexterity
to see if you can avoid the bullets.
I will roll...
I'm rolling athletics.
Athletics as well.
15.
14.
I got a 10. Okay, cool. So the bullets spray and Ray William Johnson, you managed to sort
of move around them pretty easily. But a blow toss and Patrick Yoda, you guys get clipped
a little bit by the bullets. Your cars are looking a little a little hurt, but they're
not too bad. So but I'll give you I'll let you know and you'll be able to tell when your
cars are like not looking good. So but for now you guys are doing okay, but you did get
hit by the bullets a bit and now it is your turn. Who got the 19 you did can blow toss
it's your turn. So you have one that's on your side and three that are behind you.
Hmm. Let me look at my abilities. Yeah, get get creative do whatever you can keep in mind
you're in a moving vehicle though. So your movement is really just restricted to
like you moving in the vehicle and then if you want to make lateral movements
as a person you can try but yeah yeah.
Is it sunny out? Yes. Okay, can I try and I want to try and reflect the sun into
the Ken Bowen's eyes that's next to us using my very my very shiny pipe which
is made out of chrome. Yes, of course. Which has been made out of chrome the
whole time. Yes. I agree it has been so okay. What I'll have
you do then is I guess that's really like a a slight a hand
check right like you're trying to sort of a I guess that's
slight or is that just general dexterity? Yeah. I don't know.
Let's say dexterity check. Let's do that. Alright for that
nineteen. Oh yeah. Okay. so you yeah describe how you how you
sort of hold the pipe up. What do you do like exactly to make
that
but it also goes into my eye, but only one of my eyes because he only
has a telescope with one eye. That's right, you do.
Shit, wait. But both of his eyes. Oh, there it is. Okay, cool. Yeah, so it
goes into his eye and the car sort of like spins out a
little bit and he's like, "Ah, jeez, I can't see. This is
oh my goodness gracious." And he sort of spins out back a bit.
And so he backs up a bit so he can't, he's not as close up to you
And he takes you see his car sort of like knocks into a couple of a couple the size of the road as he tries to gain
Traction back and he's a little bit further back now
Um, so that's that's pretty helpful for you. Um, yeah, you have uh, uh, that's basically your action though. So
You're good there next
will be
um
The two other ken bones are now going to go so they're they're going to try to shoot at you guys
From the back rather than try to go up
Um what they're going to use are they're going to use their they're going to use a little these like little um
bombs that they have
um, so you see one of them just break through the windshield in the front and uh,
He's throwing uh, these like tiny little bombs at you
So guys roll the decks the decks throw the athletics checks in the animal handling again
These ken bones back shots are bomb
Oh
20 baby you got a yeah, we got 20. We got a nat 20 and we got a uh, uh,
Athletics 14 on the athletics. So yeah, okay Patrick Yoda and
Both Patrick Yoda and blowtoss piss you guys very easily weave out of these bombs. It's it's it's fucking easy for you guys
I think you mean Ray William Johnson. Oh, no, you do too though. I'm Johnson to something different because I say true Ray William Johnson
How do you how do you knock the bomb back at at the guy?
I secretly is entire through all three campaigns
I have a tennis racket with me.
Yes, right.
I forgot.
I, much like Bowser in Mario Tennis, I hit the bomb back towards him.
Yeah, you say "four" as you hit it back.
Yeah, I'm also, it's a golf sport too.
Yeah, exactly.
It's just a rock sport.
You say "Bowser."
I say "Bowser" and I hit it super hard.
And everybody dies except me.
Yeah, and the Ken Bone here, he goes "Bowser!"
And then the bomb just like, goes into his face.
But it also doesn't explode, it just gives him a concussion.
[laughter]
He can't take a concussion, he's fine.
It's like a cartoon Bowser bomb, it's not a fucking real bomb.
Yeah.
He's like, "Ah, jeez!"
And you see the other Ken Bone in the driver's seat kick him out and like take the wheel
in his stead.
And that car is knocked further back now too.
Now the next Ken Bone is going to try to drive up and try to target you specifically.
This red one is...
Cameron that should be that should be Cameron. Yeah, so got a target target you specifically know the red ones not me. Oh, yeah
I'm the way it's not you. Yes, you're the black one. Yeah, they get Sullivan
Yeah, that's okay
So, yeah, he's gonna try to target you specifically blow toss after the Lotus Ray William Johnson after you did that so roll roll again
Athletics saving throw to see if you avoid his bullets. Bye. Yeah, he clips you
He clips you it's knocks you a little bit back, but not too far back
And now it is it's your turn Patrick Yoda
No, I will say Patrick your dark side abilities have subsided because it's been like enough time since you used it, but um, no
How fast is my hoverboard go?
Your hoverboard can go like what like probably 20 right probably right now faster than uh, I thought it went
I thought it went faster than the scooter. I thought it went...
You thought that?
Yeah.
No, I thought it went... I thought it was like 60. I thought it could go 60.
It would go 60 feet. 60 feet maybe is what we said. Yeah.
Yeah.
It's different than 20 miles an hour.
Like 30 miles an hour is like 480 feet a second or something.
Or 260 feet a second.
Okay.
Yeah.
Or every 6 seconds. Whatever. I'm done.
Okay.
Um...
How close am I to the car?
Okay, let's take a look.
So there's the one that's near Caleb, right?
Yeah, the one near Caleb, I'd say you're about 25 feet from it.
Like, you're pretty, you're getting near it.
Okay.
Yeah, ignore the measurements in the 20.
Got it.
Yeah.
Oh, my athletics is pretty low.
Mm-hmm.
What?
Nothing.
Give yourself 250 HP.
I saw that now.
Nothing.
You gave yourself 250 HP, I saw that now.
I'm gonna change it.
It was 25.
Okay, you just added a zero.
I don't know if I wanna...
I'm checking my inventory. I still have that Xbox from the...
You did take an Xbox.
Yeah.
So I'm 25 feet away.
away I would have to do an athletics to throw the Xbox into the windshield.
It's pretty cool.
Yeah, I think I'm gonna do that.
Alright, I'm gonna throw the Xbox into the windshield.
Okay, yeah, you're swinging it around by the wire.
Yeah.
And...
Oh!
You got a crit!
I got a crit!
I got a 20!
Oh!
Okay, yeah, nasty.
Describe how you do this, because that's pretty fucking...
So I'm swinging it around, and then the disc tray opens up somehow, and...
Yeah.
Every Xbox game ever...
...enters my inventory.
And I go...
Every Xbox game ever comes out of the disc tray, and I go, "Oh, what the hell?!"
And I throw it.
I try to catch all of the Xbox games.
[laughter]
What a critical hit that is.
Wow.
Yeah, the Ken bone in the driver's seat is just like...
is just like...
it's like it came from nowhere. It's like directly in his blind spot.
And then like an entire Xbox takes up his field of vision.
And just like obliterates his skull.
And he just like rolls out of the car.
And another Ken bone has to move into the driver's seat.
is not way back now i have now have two copies of the opinion of the and i have
strength john was stranglehold yeah i've heard really good things about the
opinion of at least uh...
and uh... yeah you you you you crushes you crushes that one's had you did some
damage to the car by virtue of that
now uh...
now it is uh...
really johnson's turn
okay i'm gonna see my ride
Okay, cool. Make an intelligence check. Let's see what you get on this.
16.
Nice.
Yeah.
Okay, you sort of go into the the you hack into this Walmart
scooter, you know, everything is technologically based, right?
It's a it's a future and has like a hacker puzzle from like
video games where it's just like you have to like connect the
dots at the right time and then you can break in and you just
solve that easily and you're now your vehicle goes like 20
miles an hour faster.
And I put a playing card in the spokes of the bike.
Okay.
Yeah.
What, what, what, you guys hear this shit?
It's like going so fast.
Yeah.
The card like disintegrates.
But yeah, so you, you are not going to be easily like overtaken.
Cause that's what they're going to try to do is keep trying to get in front of you.
Okay.
I, it's going to be a lot harder for them now.
Pull as far ahead in front of blow toss and Patrick as possible.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're like up here. You're at the very edge of the map.
Yeah, be my dust.
But because of that, you're going to have to deal with what's coming up next.
So a few things that that happen on your journey down.
And so this time...
OK, I wish you'd told me that.
Yeah. No, no, no, no, no.
This is good. This is really good.
So let me...
I mean, my character has eyes.
He can fucking see what's in front of him, right?
Yeah. Yeah.
So you you like speed up and you're doing like the looking back
And then you turn forward like what and it's just like a whole like line of police cars
Sort of just like barricading the next juncture. You see one of the Ken bones on like a megaphone go like hey
Yeah, if you could slow down there, that'd be real great pal
We got yeah, I guess this ain't surrounded but you know, we're all right in front of you
And I guess I do know what we got guys behind you
We got you surrounded, but I thought about it a little bit more and I think we got you surrounded
So and so about the left and the right sides
Well, the left is to Iraq. Well, wait, why am I answering you? No, like I in the right is off the cliff
Look, I don't have to I don't have to I so yeah, you don't have a surrounded then
Stupid I have you as far as I spread this point. You're like passing as far as you're concerned. I do have you surrounded
What if we went up?
What we win
I guess you could you could you could try that I guess you could I use his body like a ramp
You say Patrick Yoda, well, what if we went up and he's like well, I guess you
(laughter)
Just roll over his face
As you coast
above him
and uh, and you see
Sullivan point to that all and go
"DO THAT! DO THAT!"
To you, Blotas.
But now it's easier for them because now he's kinda
shaped like a little
He gets a run. There's tread.
His feet are stuck in the ground
and he's like curved at like a 45 degree angle.
There's grooves for you guys to hit now.
Yeah.
[LAUGHTER]
Yeah, roll an athletics check, both of you.
I'm going to pull that off.
Do I roll animal handling still?
Oh, yeah.
You can roll animal handling.
Oh, a nine.
Oh, shit.
OK.
What if I try athletics?
So--
[LAUGHTER]
So you guys try to use the grooves.
And you manage to get some air.
But you end up on the edge of the cars behind the blockade.
And you kind of spin out a bit.
So your vehicles suffer some damage because of that,
and you end up a little bit back.
- Damn it.
- But you do make it through.
Like that's, I mean, Ray William Johnson
did enough of a number that you guys like made it through,
but you just have to deal,
you just take a little bit of boo-boo.
- I need it.
I want an update on that Ken Bone later
to see if he's like become a ramp full time.
(laughing)
- I'm literally gonna make a note
so that I remembered an update on Ken Bone ramp.
So yeah, okay, so you make it through this blockade.
Now we're back to the top of the order
and it's that Ken Bone,
that first Ken Bone is gonna try again.
So he's gonna speed up.
He's gonna be able to take advantage of you guys
sort of like messing up the blockade a bit
and able to get in front of you.
And you see the back window,
another Ken Bone smashes his head through the back window
and drops and shoots, it takes out like a big bazooka,
shoots it and it's a really, looks like a,
- Yeah. - a really slow moving rocket
is coming towards you.
So both of you roll your saving throws,
athletics and, or you roll your checks
of athletics and animal handling.
- Meanwhile, I'm gonna-- - Before anything,
can I flip the rocket off?
- Yes, absolutely. - Will that do anything?
- No, but you can definitely do that.
me go to the night don't do it
a whole my god all i get a great
i got a good and a role you can see it and then your rules are
yeah
so as it approaches closer you start to realize that it looks like a
pregnant woman made to look like a sub
it's moving very slowly
and uh...
Patrick Yoda, you sort of do like a sick ass
like spinning out on your motorcycle
and then whipping around and going faster.
- Can I touch it?
Can I touch the rocket?
- Yeah, you can.
- Can I touch it?
Can I feel the belly to see if the baby's kicking?
- You feel a kick.
- Oh, yeah, I spin into like, I have my hand out
and I feel the kick and I go, "Oh."
(laughing)
And then I continue to spin out.
- Blowtoss, you sort of misjudged the timing on it
because it's moving so slow.
and but but with with that eleven you're able to sort of like
block it a bit with your pipe
and explode
works through the fire like to do the day to come out
uh... yeah quickly and it's it's a lot bigger than the ball it's a careful
custody touch them
the stuff that you need to fix the pick the
the
yet
camp campbell's i don't know what i try to i try to bat the the missile when i
I accidentally hit it right on the belly and yeah, you see the
baby fly in the air and it like goes to becomes like a teenager
of an adult than an old man and he dies.
It's a flying in the air.
And you take some damage cam your your bikes looking a little
messed up because you've taken some damage so far, but you're
doing okay, but it's not it's not looking ideal.
But now it is can camera hop onto my bike.
If push comes to shove if he wants to do that he can that might have to happen if his bike gets destroyed though
Yeah, so that's also why staying near each other is good, too. Um
uh, but now it is
Oh good god
Is your turn blow toss
Okay, um
How how far is it from where because we're behind the car?
How far is it from where I am right now to the front of the car?
to the uh...
of the car and a second wait a second
how far is it from where i am to the driver's seat of the car
i'd say it's about
could you get hit by that bomb it's it's about
thirty-ish feet but let me i tell you what into the driver's seat
on our way
okay i a m
all right so you teleport
and you should you bring sullivan with you and i grab sullivan
yeah you teleported making sure you are on the can bones lap
bro there's a strength contest here as soon as it happens
uh... but you're ready and he's not so he's gonna get disadvantage on it
nineteen
yeah he's not gonna do it
and he beat ken bone in a strength contest
uh... yeah you just like
slant on his lap
and then just elbow him in the nose
and kick him out of the vehicle
uh... yes dude
so you and you just plop sullivan on the uh...
on the
one is the passenger seat.
I saw him like, I threw him into the back.
Yeah, you throw him like through the little hole that like,
yeah, police car stuck him through.
He's like, ah, it's like feet are dangling.
You're just like trying to knock him through.
Just for my turn.
I want to know how close I am to the car.
Okay.
Yeah, you're also about you're actually closer to like 20 feet
because you didn't get hit by the bomb.
You sort of like found a way to get through it.
Okay, but am I near the car?
Yeah, it's pretty near. It's up to you. What do you think of 20 feet?
Yeah.
All right.
So yeah, and so yeah, Sullivan's in the back seat.
So yeah, you'd manage to take the car.
That was a smart move.
But yeah, and so the bike meanwhile just sort of like spins out and just
like falls away.
I'm going to just keep it here though because it does have your stats
on it.
And yeah, it is now your turn.
Oh, no, it's the Ken Bones turn now the other two.
So the other two are going to try to ride up
on uh... patrick you know that was the first behind a try to uh...
she with their guns against a role that animal handling check
and for twice so we can just you too
okay i got a twenty three ended crippled yes so uh... the first one you dislike
continue to spin it's been do sick
moves deflect with your lightsaber
uh... sandwich is very easy for you
uh... you get a little cocky
one of the bullets just flies directly into like one of the
bikes engines and flies up and then just like nixie when the
nose and then you just like you just like spin out and you're
like now in between the two of these cars are sandwiched
between them.
That dad and he booped
was a crit one.
And yeah, your your cars now your bikes now sort of in the
shape that that that blow tosses was and you're sort of like
sandwiched between them.
But I'm gonna Ken bones. So it's one Ken bone in each car,
right?
There was there was two you guys sort of like took care of the Ken bones and all the cars by
killing them
Um, but now there's like one in each. Yeah at this point. Okay. All right. I'm just making sure yeah, okay
Um, how much damage did that hit do to me?
Um, oh, we're just doing like car damage for now. So don't worry about that. I'm tracking your car damage. Um,
Okay, cool. So now, um as you guys are kind of coming up on the next uh,
So another thing comes up and it's it's it's you get a call you hear your phone ringing again
Patrick Yoda and this time it's it's a it's your mom your mom's calling you.
Oh hell yeah yeah okay good she's beautiful. Oh god okay do you want to pick up not right now
Pick up the phone. Hi, sweetie. Hi, Patty. How you doing?
My what do you fucking do? I can't fucking pick up the farm in the middle of the biggest car chase of my fucking life
Oh, I understand honey. It can be very difficult
You do
Your friends are so wonderful. You want to come over for dinner?
Roll a wisdom saving throw as you're trying to fend off
Your friends if I were 700 years older and green
25 okay. Yeah, you're used to your mom getting nosy dealing with her nonsense, and she's sort of like
I'm getting confused by my phone again. I I I need to go, but you make sure you're getting enough rest
and you're drinking enough water
Yeah mom, I'm drinking so much fucking water
Can you just get off the phone
We're taking good care of him
You got your father's mouth on you I swear
Hey, bat, stop sucking my dick
Hey, come on
Come on, that's my fucking mom on the phone
Get that poop out of your mouth
What are you fucking doing?
Stop smoking poop like weed
I'm not smoking poop, how do I even do that?
She hugged up like 4 minutes ago
minutes. Okay. Yeah. And yeah now it's it's it's it's oh **** I
guess that that you took care of that Ken Bone. So now it's
your turn. Blowtoss piss. Um well, you're in the car now.
Yeah. Ken Bone was in. Um can I slow down some so Patrick can
try and jump onto the car? Yeah, absolutely. Alright. Uh
yeah, I slow down to try and get Patrick into the car. Okay,
cool. All right. So yeah, you end up back there. And so on
Patrick's turn, he's gonna be able to have advantage jumping
into the car. That's what he chooses. I guess. Can I take an
action to? Yeah, okay. Yeah, I'll just try and I guess shoot
the windshield of one of the Ken bones that sandwiching.
Patrick, okay, wait, did they leave any whip? Was there a
bazooka left in this car? Oh, was there? Oh, yeah, there would
be. All right. Yeah, blow one of them up. Okay. Yeah, you can get
Sullivan to do that because you're driving. Yeah, Sullivan. Yeah, so he does exactly what I want perfectly
You sure you need me to shoot this? I don't I've never I'm driving Sullivan. Oh my god
Fucking focus. Okay, okay
And he he sort of like
bangs through the windshield glass with the
Rocket and he like he gets a little scared and he um, he's like just sort of wagging around
out
a
how he does. He face plants against the plexiglass. I'm hoping. Yeah.
I hate that. Yeah, no, he absolutely just hits his head on the back of the car.
He's like, "Ah, shit!" He's just like, he's like concussed almost.
And he just sort of like sits back down into the back seat. And that'd killed him.
As he sits back down, the gun just goes off again, because he just drops the bazooka,
and it just goes straight up into the air.
and we see this submarine exploding and you're like "WAAA!"
like as it does.
Um, uh yeah, so that's your turn.
Now these two Ken Bones are gonna try to do a little bit of a crunching maneuver on you, Patrick Yoda.
I bet they don't do it.
Um, uh, well let's, hey, let's find out as a family, alright?
So, they're going to, what is it, oh yeah yeah yeah, roll a DC check to see.
With this you're gonna do a decent disadvantage on animal handling
Mm-hmm
Okay that eight. Yeah, they like go they like just go
And like just shake and bake you just like trying to squish you a little bit. You're you see your bike is sort of like
Taking some serious damage
Yeah, I will tell you now
As far as my how I keep track of this goes your bikes at like one
So it's not looking good. One million. That's no. So one, right? Yeah, one what? It could be one million.
Could be one million. I mean if you think about it the way that we invented math, it just it's like it could be anything.
So it's your turn Patrick.
So this is a concept.
Math is like a concept. It's like invented by society to try and like combine us all into like one one person.
So you guys gonna have been on Chappel already? So we'll just read.
as smart or will it be before Chapo and it'll sound like bullshit. Gear up.
How far away is Cameron? Cameron's pretty close. Cameron's like a good like 10 feet from you.
If I tell Cameron to do something will that count? I'll allow it this time.
Okay. What are you trying to do though? Because I could have Cameron
because they're like trying to squish me with the cars right now.
That's right. What I could do is Sullivan has broken the window out so if Cameron
just rams in the in between I could just run up I could like hover or maybe
hoverboard I don't know. Okay so here's what you can do because like in the turn
order Cameron does go next yeah or goes before everyone else so if you could
ready your hoverboard and then Cam does it because he already sort of set you up
for a jump you'll have an automatic success if you do that. And I'll have advantage with that?
Yeah. Okay. Yeah basically automatic success so I would say you could ready
your hoverboard this turn and that's sort of your action.
Okay, so I'm going to do that. I'll ready my hoverboard.
Okay, cool. So you sort of get it out. You're sort of like balancing on it
while you're on the bike. I'm saying you're pro.
I have not had good luck with the hoverboard.
Yeah, I don't think you've ever succeeded using the hoverboard.
Hey, the times they are, it's Ray William Johnson's turn.
So what do you want to do? Oh shit. I'm way far ahead, right?
You're way far ahead.
OK, so I have it in my head after that
ramp stunt that I'm like, like an evil,
Knievel level like stunt man.
So I just start doing like a like a headstand on the bike.
OK, yeah. Roll an athletics check.
OK, that 14.
Yeah, you do a handstand, but you kind of do the kind of handstand
where you're like, oh, headstand like a like a breakdancer.
Oh, OK. And being on my head.
Yeah. 14 is not going to cut it with a headstand.
I have a flat head, I'm a computer.
No, you're a demon with a computer in your back.
Okay, well actually my horns dig into the material on the motorcycle.
Okay.
And...
Got yo ass.
And, uh, you just like, left to slow down a little bit to pull it off, is what I'll say.
I speed it up.
No, do you speed it up?
It's gonna be a very different result.
I don't care.
Okay.
Yo, I'm evil Knievel right now.
Roll a dexterity saving throw.
that 10 okay your bike just like fucking you spit out like your bikes like like sliding all over
the place and um actually as you're doing that you're coming up uh um you're coming up on a uh
a uh a gap friendship over so uh there's a gap now coming up okay and and you can you might spin
now and just fall off the gap. Okay. Don't do something quick. I speed up even more to
clear the gap. Okay, roll roll that fun. I'm not gonna die, dude. I'm gonna I'm like, this
is crazy. Go for it. All right. 19. I said it was crazy. You just like fucking use try
to speed up and you just like like almost like crash into the wall fall down this gap into
oh my god you fall right into nickelodeon slime yeah oh it was on purpose that was the stunt
yeah and you're uh yeah your your your bike is totaled um you can do you guys are sort of like
spiraling down but he got a 19 how did that because he did so much dumb shit before that
Yeah, and so the difficulty classes kept going up and up and up.
So you're now stuck in this Nickelodeon Gak.
You take three damage from the Gak, the Nickelodeon Slime.
So what happened, what it is now is you're like in this pit of
slime that was in this gap and you can see that the next like
round of like racing that they're on, like, you know, you're
going to, you could jump potentially onto your friend's
cars or Ken bones car if you time it right if you wait after your next turn
okay I will time it right yeah okay so the rest of you though you all have to
clear this gap - you just saw Ray William Johnson just like try to do a headstand
and then just eat shit so you gotta do you can obviously just do a straight
check or you can try to be more creative if you think that'll help hmm we could
rocket jump over it with the bazooka that's true that's not a bad idea okay
right it's not a bad idea okay so very good idea if you can do that Patrick
you have to get into the car yeah I'm gonna say Pat you gotta roll your
athletics check now let's resolve that that's more fun yeah yeah you just like
fucking like like do us a kickflip and just like fucking and then nose manual
right into the car and just just slap Sullivan the head with the board and just like
and you're now sitting next to him in the backseat of the car and he's just like rubbing his little
frog snout and he's like oh good to see you okay and yeah so you made it in so now
you want to grab the rocket launcher and do it yourself or do you want Sullivan to do it
I mean, it's up to you.
I'll do it myself.
Yeah, it's definitely a better move.
Yeah.
Because Solven's a really bad shot.
So yeah, just roll an attack roll with Dex as the modifier.
Just roll...
I'd say you're proficient with this.
So just roll...
Let me see your fucking character sheet.
It should be something you could do that'll make it easier to roll.
Yeah, just roll the hoverboard...
hoverboard... what does that say? Hoverboard Boomerang.
That's going to be an indicator of how well you do at this.
Okay, nice. You didn't have advantage on it, but
14 is still fine. Yeah, you use that and you guys rocket launch over this gap.
You see the slime below you, you see Ray William Johnson doing
backstrokes in the slime. It doesn't blow up the gas tank, too.
No, it does not and you guys make it over the uh, the gap. Um,
so
uh now
Uh as you guys are sort of cruising down to the next part of the hill, uh next part of the gap is your turn blowtoss piss
Um, you're up. Um, I keep driving
Yeah
You're not gonna try to attack the I tell solvent to shoot more to shoot more rockets at the car. Okay?
Yeah, solvent's gonna try again. He's just gonna continue to probably
Miss unless he somehow does really well right now. Holy shit. He got it. He got a crit 20
He takes out
Let's go
I'll screenshot it. So you now i'm gaming dude. I tapped the brakes again and that's what makes him do it
I'm screenshotting it just so you know, but that happened. Okay. Um
yet so you use tap the brakes and so it'd like
something in him just like clicks
for the first moment in his life
he's always been just like the part of the joke that the we've the
happy-go-lucky loser and something in him just fucking
clicks and he just like
so it gets like a it's a little bit snap
you know
i think it's just like i'm not going to look over patrick you know you could
swear he has like a chad job
for like half a second.
He looks like the like
the like uh
handsome uh like
Joe Biden Pepe
that like 4chan people post.
He just looks perfect and he just shoots
his rocket and it just blows up
one of these cars straight up. It just blows
it up and he's like
"What have I done?"
Just staring at him like
like, oh, wow.
And the the other car is now starting to pull back and he's
gonna take out the gun and try to shoot you guys roll roll
athletics.
Blow toss 20.
Yeah, you easily just sort of like maneuver out of the way
these bullets Patrick Yoda.
It's now your turn.
You're in the backseat of this car.
Keep in mind, you know that Ray William Johnson's probably
to want to try to jump through.
You don't know that for sure though.
He might just chill there.
So should I make room for him?
I don't know, just like the stuff you can do, or you can try to attack this car too behind
you.
Oh, okay.
So is there two bazookas in the car or is it just one?
Just the one.
Okay, should I take the...
Yeah, should I just try to blow it up?
you're deciding to do this, you Patrick Yoda in particular, see a really weird bird just
sort of off in the distance. Do you see that on your screen?
No. I have to fix that. I rolled 20.
Is that the uncle's falcon?
Here, let me, there we go. You see a really weird bird. Do you see it now?
Oh yeah.
Oh fuck! No!
the
For the fans, it's a shoebill stork.
That's one of my most hated birds.
You're like, "Oh, maybe he's kind of friendly. Maybe he's a little silly."
You're not sure anymore. He could be silly.
Oh, I don't trust those eyes on that bird.
Yeah, roll a wisdom saving throw.
Ten.
Okay. Yeah, your mind is a little confused by this bird.
And whatever you were trying to do, you're just way too focused on this weird bird.
You're just like getting upset looking at it to do anything. Why the fuck does it look like that? Yeah
Come on, look at the fucking thing
You've like passed by it and Sullivan's like what are you talking about? Where?
It is now that
that
Cars turn or that Ken bones turn. Oh, you already went here to try to shoot you
so it's now your turn Ray William Johnson and
Are they here in the slime that I jump or no? Yeah, they're coming down but before that happens
Ring ring ring ring. Hello. Ray William Johnson. It's me your mother
Fuck my
Hello, I have others the demon I'm your mother. I haven't talked I haven't spoken to you in in years. I just
You guys you're too far away
the
since you did that thing
so
I try to hang up
but I fat finger it and I
hit the finger instead
yeah so anyway you know I was talking
with the girls and how they reconnected with
some other kids after since it's like really
much louder now and like
I'm like looking at bloatoss
and ray and I'm like making
I'm doing like a muppet
action with my hand
I'm doing the eat pussy hand symbol back at him
I know god was never your thing you know
try to maybe force that on you a little bit but you know I I really
care.
It's a picture of Steven Tyler.
Wow, he does look like a mom.
Roll a wisdom saving throw as you're trying to fend off your
brother interrupted you again. I hate my mom. I get a 14. Yeah, you're able to sort of like,
what do you say to her to just shut her down trying to like connect with you after all this?
Well, I'm getting a call. I just got a call. Dad died. All right, bye.
What? What's going on? My dad died. Bye.
Yeah. You just, you figure out how to unfat finger it and you hang up.
Okay, now you can make that jump.
Okay, I jump on to whichever whoever will have me.
Okay, roll an athletics check nine.
Okay, you're you like try to you try to like run out and you
kind of like are like running through the slime.
So it's kind of slow moving and you kind of like don't get as
much air as you think you're going to get and you kind of
miss time and as the car is speeding by so you're not going
to land on the Patrick Yoda blowtoss Sullivan car.
But roll a Dexterity saving throw to see if you can position yourself to land on the Ken Bone one instead.
17.
Yeah, nice. So you just like fall through the front and you're in the passenger seat next to the Ken Bone.
Oh, this is awkward.
Okay, yeah. What do you want to do? You have a chance to attack him for sure.
I get really nervous and I put my hand on his leg.
*laughter*
He's like, "Oh, ah, God!
I- not since college I-"
and, uh, he starts like to
swerve a little bit.
While he's off guard, like, he fuckin' caves
his face in. Yeah, roll with attack,
roll with advantage, roll with the, uh,
USB, uh, blade.
Oh my God.
Yeah, you gotta
crit, so you just like, hit him with
the butt of the blade and it just crushes his skull in
like Mortal Kombat, and he's just like,
the completely you had a moment of like maybe like a
my old sexual awakening maybe you might learn a little bit about himself
yeah i wanted to hurt more yeah yeah right and so he's just completely dead
you kick him out of the driver's seat you're in the car now
uh... you guys you guys are now sort of approaching you see a
as your uh... as you're driving past and since you've
defeated everybody uh... you drive past what looks like at first a uh...
A giant donut and then you realize that it's a 10 Ken Bones in a donut costume
And you guys just drive past that event you're not distracted by it it doesn't affect you you guys make it through this fine
and
Hey, can we turn around and go find that bird
You look up at the sky and you see the bird flying but its head is come turn towards you the entire time
It is flying away up in the air and it's just looking down
Is this fucking bird never mind, I'm sorry for interruptions
Yeah, all of the DM lines happen in Patrick Yoda's head.
Yeah.
[LAUGHTER]
He hears every last one of them.
He's used none of that to his advantage.
No.
No, I did.
I did try to persuade you once.
That's true.
And you were successful at it.
So you are using it to your advantage.
Yeah.
All right, so you guys reached the bottom of the hill.
You guys bested all the traps and all the little silliness.
And you're approaching sort of now the open field
where the mountainous, you're probably past the mountainous outskirts of Gadsville and
towards the open field where your ship is located. All of you roll a perception check.
8.
I have a pretty high perception, I'm confident.
14.
21.
Nice, okay. So I need to use perception more.
I'll say you do. Cameron, your mic sounds weird.
Yeah, your mic sounds kind of weird, dude.
Okay.
It sounds better now.
Yeah, it sounds weird because you're talking, bitch. What's up?
Oh!
I was not... I thought it sounded weird for a different reason, but it was a pretty good burn.
I thought it was because he was talking.
Hmm. Are you gonna cry?
What?
Crying right now?
Yeah, I'm crying right now.
You fucking idiot!
I got him, guys!
Yeah, Pat, are you gonna cry?
I'm leaving the call. I'll do it again.
Please don't leave the call.
I did it once, I'll do it again.
So yeah, as you're approaching it,
Blotas, you're focusing a little too much on driving right now,
but Patrick Yoda and Ray William Johnson,
you guys notice because this is the open field where,
you know, a lot of the airships and sort of like sky vehicles are parked,
as well as, you know, where there's enough space for the Gateway GADCOW.
And you see the udders are like have this like red light
Like sort of pulsing through it
Um, and as you see that
You look down towards where your ship is and all three of you can see this
and you see just like along the horizon like a sea of
Uh of ken bones and more serious looking armed police officers who have vehicles and weaponry
all along that. So we take out the thing that's doing the red light?
Leo patches in to talk to you guys. He says,
I should have waited. No, it's fine. My Jollibee's have been compromised and
you guys look back and you see a couple of Jollibee's like with their
hands cuffed and they're just like their heads are
against the like hood of the car, the police cars.
And he said they're really taking this far. The guys probably want to make an
example of gun city through this.
I, I, you know, I, I, look, if you want, you could try to push through, but if you do,
it'll be a massacre and I don't know if I'll be able to help you, you know, look, if you
get the inward pass, and even if you do, if it doesn't prove to be as much use as the
legend say, well, it just might be back to being executed for you three.
You could definitely try to push through, but just, you know, there, I have other sky
galleons if you could find another way to wherever you need to go so we guys want
to do I looked to the the the corpse of the kin bone sitting next to me in the
police car and I say you think it what I'm thinking you see like a bit of its
skull like drop from the top of his head. Yeah, and then I using my computer vision computation,
I decide which of the Ken bones looks the most like a ramp and I am going to jump. I'm going
to jump on. Okay, you guys gonna follow his lead? There's a bunch of Ken bones on top of the
so we could all get murdered right now. This could go in a few different directions. You can either
the
risk
you
among
you haven't talked to patrick you know the effect
i have a good idea to go off his headphones he's not listening anymore
uh... he literally can't hear us right now
uh... i don't know i don't understand the situation
listen to it. So in front of you right now is I just have the
radio turned on and I'm just dancing here all day. It's
Fortnite. Yeah. All the in front of you is like a line of of
cops and it's just would be so it would be tough to break
through them and to get to your Sky Galleon and if you do, Leo
is essentially saying like you are out on parole basically to
get the n-word pass for him and if you do it you're free right technically you
were supposed to be executed but if you do enough shit to these Ken Bone people
like it's gonna get to a point where right you can't vouch for you anymore
right so I'm thinking we can't we can't jump it because that's gonna work we'll
get that we'll get the pass and then we'll just fucking it doesn't matter
we'll die at the end of the campaign I don't want to die at the end of the
campaign I want to reap I want to reap what I sow you want to get as many uses
out of that n-word pass as possible exactly so I'm I'm thinking we we get
the F out of here we can we can go to the okay so if we go around we can tell
him to put a sky Caleb put your headphones back on cuz you're gonna want
to hear this no you're gonna want to hear it you guys can do whatever you
want how is he Caleb Caleb we're gonna jump I don't know okay spooky I'm weird
so what I'm thinking of doing is we can do you can turn around and jump onto the
other can on you Kayla can you tell what I'm saying you want to turn around and
jump on to the other.
Alright he's doing some bad stuff.
You got your headphones unplugged.
No way.
No he can just hear them he just has it turned up loud.
Yeah that's obvious.
I didn't even think about that.
That's smart.
Yeah I'm thinking we could turn around to ramp Ken Bone.
And then.
Go back to ramp Ken Bone.
Yeah go back to ramp Ken Bone and have Leo put a Sky Galleon near it.
Because we could contact him.
has to pilot the sky galleon though and the jolly bees are out of it.
Well doesn't he have more? He's got he's a fucking billionaire he's got more shit.
He doesn't have more sky galleons. Oh like another sky galleon. Yeah.
Yeah. Hmm. But does he have a sky galleon nearby? That's the question because he kind of...
He said he did. He says he has more sky galleons not like one nearby. I jump onto the
galleon. Are you guys gonna try to jump on the galleon? I don't want to I don't
want to try to jump on the galleon. You can split this we can do this we can do
this where Patrick Yoda tries to find another way and the other two
characters try to get on the galleon. I plug my radio back in for one moment.
I say, "Hey Pat, you there?" "Yeah, what's up?" "Listen bud, it's been a fun ride, but I
I gotta do this.
(singing)
For me.
Yeah, I become CGI in the car.
(laughing)
Yeah.
Listen,
if I don't make it,
call my mom
and also tell her my father is dead.
(laughing)
It's been a wild ride, bud.
Let's do this.
I'll see you on the other side.
Okay.
Patrick Yoda, you're accepting this?
I'm in the car with Cameron.
I can't choose anyone.
I'm just trying to convince everybody.
Oh yeah, blow toss, what do you do?
Are you going for it too?
I'm like, guys, I don't want to fucking do this.
What if I teleport into the car with Caleb
and let Patrick take control?
So it's me and Sullivan?
You can do that.
I'm gonna do that.
[laughter]
Okay, so here we go.
- There you go, so you two.
- No, I take Sullivan with me and Caleb too.
- I don't take Sullivan with you.
- You know, I was kinda trying to do a lone wolf thing,
but you know what, this works too.
- Hey man, and I changed the radio channel to my music
to annoy Caleb.
- Well, this is, I'm having second thoughts about this jump.
(laughing)
- I put my, I'm sitting in the back seat
and I put my feet up on his headrest
and he can smell my feet.
I want to die as fast as possible now.
This is the pivotal moment in the story here.
Let's do this.
I'm going to, can I, on the way, okay.
Can I, I'm in a new vehicle now.
Can I spend one turn on my way to jump him, or jump on top of, or through the kin bone
ramp, man, can I soup up my cop car?
Wait, can I go into the cop car now that he's souping it up?
You're in your own cop car.
How are you going to get in there though? You can't teleport.
Cameron teleport back.
I teleport back.
I teleport back with Sullivan and then I teleport back and shake Patrick and leave Sullivan.
No, dude.
Bring him back too.
Okay, I teleport back to Sullivan.
Sullivan vomits from all the teleporting.
Just molecules being reanimated over and over again.
Yeah.
Okay.
I turn Freebird on the radio too.
That's right.
the the the part of the song is the solos playing when jenny looks like she's
gonna jump off the building in forrest gump that's the that part playing
uh... okay
intelligence check
ray william johnson
intelligence
just soup up the car
you've amply found a way to sort of soup this up you you go in there into the
you sort of hack in
this time it's uh...
it's uh... blocks it's a little bit blocks you just have to spell out hack
with the blocks and you do it
uh... and now the car is
a little bit faster
which means that difficulty
check is a difficulty class a little bit lower on this
but still
i'm gonna tell you now
it is
at an eighteen
to pull this off
can we, can me and cameron try to super this car too?
now that you've committed to this, i'm telling you now
me and cameron can also teleport back to the other car
I'm
If you want to take the wheel, I what's your athletics bonus rate - 7 so I'll turn wheel
Okay, switch up the wheels. Yeah, I'll let you switch
All right
But in the game, I'm a little like jealous that he was
Well, you know, I mean I I did that earlier so like
Before the jump happens, I know that it's like a 26 and I just go like, "Aww!"
And that's when Cameron floors it.
Do we find like a Ken Bone who is just perfectly shaped?
A couple of things happen.
So part of why the difficulty class was high was because the cow was charging up what were udders,
udder lasers, and it started shooting them out at you guys.
With that 26, you're weaving between the lasers.
You almost predict where they're going to be used.
It's insulting.
And as you approach this massive group of Ken Bones,
and also armored Ken Bones,
one of them says,
"Would you please step out of the vehicle?"
And then you start to realize that he says,
"I heard that my brother turned into a ramp, so I don't..."
I'm a little concerned.
Wait, he turns into-
He's wearing shoes that are just like a perfect like quarter pipe.
*laughter*
He's the Bob Bernquist loop.
Like the fucking-
The loops that they have in Tony Hawk, but he's also got like a kicker at the end.
Yeah.
He's just- His brother turned into a ramp, and he just is a ramp.
And he's the one with the radio.
He's like 30 feet tall and 30 feet wide.
*laughter*
And you just do a loop-de-loop with this guy's body.
Like, as he's trying to yell, he's like, "Oh, oh, jeez!"
And you're just like, "Oh, they're using me as a ramp again!"
*laughter*
And the police chief's mad at him, like, "I knew it! Shoulda never hired you!"
And you guys crash the SkyGallery.
Um, you're in there now.
Um, uh, everything's ready to go.
The Jollibee's had it all set up.
that
uh...
and uh... it's got out of the house
he just
you'll get by this case
athletics that
the cows shooting
while you're getting skyline
twenty six again
so
God.
You are like messing around with it and you figure out where the shields are, you press them,
like a blue light comes up in front of the galleon,
*pew pew pew*
like the lasers from the cow, just like bounce off of it.
You sort of start to scoot up and you just fucking shoot off into the sky.
And you look down and you see the gad king go
"NOOOOOO!"
And you see the baby gad, he puts his fedora back on,
and he tips his hat to you guys as you fly away into the sky.
it's
see
and there while we killed a lot of guys on the way so you guys are flying in the air now
uh... you guys can contact we owe uh... you also have the penguin
and he just sort of figure out where to go next you probably something to
investigate that artifact
uh... the golden penguin with the vagina
uh...
and uh... yeah i mean will sort of see how much trouble you're in because you
did basically like
you didn't like you didn't even hide away you just like in their face were like
were fugitives and we're fucking out of here
So we'll see you didn't you didn't then just like you didn't like it could have turned into like a
massacre against them, but you didn't let that happen. So that's you know, good.
Definitely good to use it take advantage of the dad holds on for yeah, we could have killed
Yeah, I'm in court like the narrator told me
uh... the insanity plea would work in that case i guess uh... but uh... yes
so uh... you guys don't really know where you have to go at this point
unless you investigate the artifact or contact we are talking solvent or
whatever
i'm i'm gonna say that you have some downtime in the in the the ship now that
you could take advantage of to
uh... if you want to investigate it if you wanna
hang out take a breather do whatever i go make some jolly spaghetti can i take a
a
Let's take a look.
It says I have 500.
Come on man.
You have 5.
You have 5, yes. You can spend 5, so that means you just roll D8 5 times.
If you want you can spend up to 5 for this period.
I'm going to roll some. There's 9.
Yeah, that's good.
I'll just take one more.
Alright, well.
I'm going to roll some too.
Yeah, you're full health now.
cool
Yeah, you recharge you recharge five techno slime points on a short rest cool
Yeah, you have some of that jolly spaghetti - does that count does that count as a healer?
Yeah, no, it's just yummy
Just yummy this time that only food only heal Sullivan
Okay, how much what is Sullivan it?
Sullivan needs some spaghetti
Sullivan and I are doing a lady in the tramp
Right now he's like I did not I don't want to do this. Why do you always insist on it being like this?
It's gotta be this way
Okay
All right. I'm gonna roll. Yeah
Yeah, I spent four hit dice to get back to 40 HP nice out of 50. All right. I just rolled three
nine four nine
Nice
Yeah, and you guys get your you guys get five take this on
Well, you he got five you get four back Patrick Yoda and
blowtoss you get three back when you should do a short rest
just because of how much techno slime you guys have.
Wait, what?
What you get for techno sign points back in a short.
Okay.
Yeah.
Can I can I cancel out that last roll because I'm at 38 out
of 41?
Yeah, that's fine.
Don't worry about that.
Okay.
Yeah.
Yes, so techno sign points.
Do I get again?
Sorry, you get four back.
Okay.
What was I at?
No, you was it too.
So I got to yeah, that's good.
I just wanted to make sure I wasn't putting too many.
Yeah.
No, you're fine.
Yeah, so yeah, you're in the lush Sky Galleon again, you know,
a beautiful wood paneling and all that you see the screen turn
on you see Leo the collector and his signature steampunk Victorian
gear with his white dreads white guy dreads and he says it's
good to see you're all safe.
I don't know how you made it through there.
but did you
didn't
you can kill the body to cool anybody else right
uh...
no pretty you know
i may have like stop by
the blood of my dong blade into a guy's head
that i did
well you know that they said we were allowed to go and we were in trouble to
and we're leaving
i'm not even a
mc as the he has eyes roll into the back of his hand he says i'm not even gonna
make you grow for that i know that that's a lot of heat
and some
his eyes return to normal and he says uh...
okay just be careful i can
i could try to talk to the gates of battle this you know
especially if you didn't blow up the cave
uh... you know
then and you know we just have to
sort that out just
try to for good if we end up doing somewhere else just don't uh...
did we do that
just try to answer
no to cause too much trouble
if if uh... that's alright
uh... what
i love my game boy
now let's let's take a look at that artifact you got back and uh... yet
because of the uh... golden penguin
with the uh... realistic look on and we left it behind we have to do that
uh... yeah it's is going to penguin with this like realistic vagina in a new
here like a teeny blizzard sound coming out of it
how large is it
uh... it's about like uh... it's really good business all of in size
now it's short of insolvence but like two feet
tall i'll go so then
well what what
i guess i guess i just look at it is i'd dislike tilt my head toward him
i don't know i just kind of point my finger a little bit now that's not
that's
come on could it could be the solution
and home and i don't know how to talk to you know i just know i think that's a
little bit more
and the same height as him
i spit on patrick you know
uh...
hot had many
promises a statue right back here
there's no way she'll likely
do it and she's giving you the eyes
he looks at his the dead eyes of the statue of the at the same color as the
skin yet i don't know all the way to get it
he's like
uh...
uh... so
matt hi
on the frog
uh... god
not
you're a part of the sub-zero
and you've got a game what are you doing there
and all the guys for all our perception checks as uh... as a sampling
twenty one
in my six
okay he yeah
twenty-two the uh... blow tosses to focused on berating solvin
uh... you to you notice that the uh...
the realistic looking vagina is is getting a little
almost
uh...
all of it he did go ahead
you got this but
uh...
i'm sorry i just heard something
It's her, the god in my brain, tell me something bad.
Um...
uh...
I'm an archaeologist assistant.
Um...
Ask her if she's wearing space pants.
Call her a bitch.
Hi bitch, um...
Oh Jesus, I'm sorry.
i could hear my mother now
well i've got a good
colorado
and
the world
say she looks like your mom
you look like my mom's answer
it
and i think that's a good
and uh... you see the vagina get a little bit more moist
uh...
uh... guys we have to keep doing this
- Show her your tongue. Show her your frog tongue.
- Meanwhile, you see Leo. He's like, "Yes, keep going. Yes."
- Show her the frog tongue.
- Hop around. Do a flip.
- Say, "Ahh."
- And he tries to do that while he's trying to do a flip.
And he just sort of like falls, but he falls headfirst.
at first
into the policy
and
you hear the penguin go
all
it's not
and it's uh...
eyes uh... glow
and uh...
all of you like go
blind briefly for some huge flash of light yet
as a blood it's all of the new to their nasty for you
And then as you start to regain sight, you see that a beam of light is shooting out from this penguin's face.
Almost like no matter where it's facing, it is somehow beaming in one direction in particular.
Oh, it's pointing to Mecca!
And Leo said, "Not quite, but I think it's something like it." And he starts typing on his side.
Is Sullivan's entire head inside the vagina?
No, it's just the mouth and neck.
And he's getting he's he's he's like can I move can I move your look your tongue and
Yeah, fucking get it boy. He starts writing the alphabet with his hands
And yeah, you see
Leo says okay the coordinates of where there's light a beam of light is
It's pointing towards north towards towards the soy wastes
towards oh goodness, okay, there's a rumor that there is a
a small temple that is outside of a...
well, this might be a bit personal for you, Blotoss, but uh...
outside of a, uh,
Hoov...Hoo Town, a Hoovian village filled with Hoo people
who live in...among the Soi Wastes. Hoo?
Right, that's correct, Patrick Cure. What? Hoovians.
in the middle east on who town
my ship can't go that far to the soy wastes it will get destroyed
by the blizzard of soy
will need to
pocket down somewhere in
take take the wendy express
no who are you talking about
the wendy express is a notary of the town
are you still on
the who's on first bit right
yeah sitting back and get you know i i just showed it yesterday he's been doing
it kind of yeah head it's it's when you first i'm crazy
when you first see it it's kind of like while what guys were crazy
the like that's a class i get it right now no i'm i'm british
we love
comedy here
uh...
and uh... he says he says
the wendy expressed which is a
famous
uh... winter so i train that
goes across the so it's it's the only method of transportation in the
untamed waste
if you take you head down to the station that park the ship outside of its
it should be a days journey there
to take that rain up to the who town and then we'll get to
i think we're gonna get to the temple itself
at last
okay i do that
you too
yeah now that's not come on
right will do all that right now and then we'll go to will be at the temple
when you don't think that's not how it not you know this temple crazy please
sell doing this well my favorite temple i've ever been to a lot of notes on the
outside and solvent is now like married to the penguin that i think that the
future he's like me
uh...
yes so
uh... he says
this is great work for you've done an amazing job by me besides
the people you've had to kill
amazing work
those were all accidents and we also also we didn't kill anybody
and he's saying that
uh...
you see a red light martin brown
brown brown pop up on the ship
and you see a lake lake warning symbol
and then you see the warning symbol
like in this hologram on the ship
and it's trapped in jello
and
and uh...
uh... you see him say uh...
I have a great summer see you next fall Dwight's and the ship
is falling now through the sky.
And it's going fast and it's falling towards the soy wastes
but far outside of the Wendig station.
What okay?
I got a question.
Yeah, so it's an air galleon.
So it's shaped like a ship.
That's right and the soy wastes.
So I'm assuming that the soy wastes are made out of soylent.
Soylent and Frigid Blizzard Soylent.
So it's snow?
Maybe. There's no river?
No. Hold on. Is there a trampoline maybe?
Exactly where the ship is going to fall? Yeah, maybe a giant pile of pillows?
I thought we were going to be able to use the galleon in manual mode. There are multiple
stations you guys can go to right now to try to fix this, or try to make sure that this doesn't get
too bad. So we head to the stations. Okay. Yeah station one
blow toss. You can take the ship driving the ship.
Hey guys blow toss is sus.
I eject Patrick.
Patrick Yoda and Ray William Johnson.
You guys can take the different different sort of emergency
like power stations and emergency shield stations try to
prevent the crash which one wants to take the shield which
one wants to take the power.
I would take the shields.
yet what uh... you're a you are you're doing the power
mister you should do the power i should do the why
is your the computer
what is a a both of them are good computer-based never over the computer
basin but i mean that we're you're gonna need the power to power up the shields
uh... you're in some star trek is really smart
you know i'm not so right
okay so you're you you guys go to the station to get what you switch
What do you mean I should switch? You guys have to switch back and forth and you switch positions.
Ray William Johnson, the power station requires you to hit the Jollibee's Whack-A-Mole style that are in there.
I would love to do that.
And so roll an athletics check to try to hit them to turn on the power station.
22.
Nice, yeah. You managed to whack them pretty efficiently.
And the shields, Patrick Yoda, you have to... you're playing against a computer in Hangman right now.
and it's like the award try to get to try to guess what the word is
so that i need to pass to guess this word yeah
uh... yeah uh... so uh... yeah let's let's start playing hangman okay you
ready
i'm gonna set up a better once again
and one
who
Drawing a circle.
Okay.
No, that doesn't count! You drew a big one!
Okay, it's not a one, it's the hangman thing.
I just screwed it up a little bit, so it looks like a one.
Do I get letters?
Um, if you guess letters, you do.
Do you know how to play hangman?
Hangman, don't you get letters for free? Don't you get, like, free letters?
No.
No, that's Wheel of Fortune.
That is Wheel of Fortune.
That's what I'm thinking of.
But I get it. Yeah, okay. Is it four letters long? Yeah, it's only four letters. Try poop. Try poop
Try pee
Do I have to ask you what I haven't you just guess a letter?
I haven't played hangman in so long guess the letter just guess letters. Is it a noun?
You just guess letters. Yes. It's a noun
Okay, is it how many letters is the rule of hangman? I got four
Four letter
Just say a letter, dude.
There's 26 letters, it could be fucking any of them.
Say P.
P.
It's 26 letters, it could be any of them.
P?
P.
Say P.
No, no P.
He said B.
He said B? No B.
He said D.
I did not- no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
He said T.
Stop! Stop!
I don't know why you're screwing this up so bad.
So many letters that are in this word.
Stop!
Do you have one more guess?
Put those- no, put those back!
Put those back that was not that was he said he he said he no
No, that was all cameron. No, the word was fish
No
No, no, none of this counts. Yeah
The shields are not up you guys are
This doesn't count. I didn't even get to do I didn't even get to play
I was just on the intercut the ship and you're not just saying letters not realizing he was playing
I was like, now I will list my favorite letters to motivate
you on whatever tasks you might be doing with the power on
though.
Like it you you are able to sort of like steer the ship pretty
well, but without the shields as you guys go falling through
the sky and the the you start to fall through and you're going
towards a soy waste right over the desert the like sort of
dusty desert of where the Gadsville is.
This is an immediate shift in you know in a meteorology, right?
It's a completely different environment completely
different biome and is the soy wastes where nobody's been able to settle.
Really, the only thing that has been a couple of who villages and a couple
other scattered settlements that have been able to live in the harsh climate
there. And the second you hit it, it's like a, it shifts completely. Now
there's just like this flakes of soy and, and, um, snow just like ripping
through and the ship is starting to like lose control because of whatever
tampering that Pennsylvania gym did to it. And with the power supply, you are
able to get a little bit of extra different distance. So it's no longer
going to be probably a days out from the Wendig Station. However, without the shields, you
guys fall, you fall hard. You like go like thousands of feet down. You manage to pull
up as best as you can, Blowtoss, but it's sort of like in Spongebob, "We're good, we're good,
we're good," and all the ships like fucking like bits and bits of wood and like metal
and I'll fly off and everything goes black.
(dramatic music)
And that's where we'll end it.
- Oh wow, what an episode.
(dramatic music)
- All right, good work.
- Yeah, that was really fun.
(dramatic music)
[Music]