[MUSIC]
Last time on Gun City, the Temple of The Penguin of Doom.
Three brilliant archaeologists, Patrick Yoder, Lotos Piss and Ray William Johnson,
were hired out of prison by a one Leo the Collector, one of the richest people in Gun City,
who is an avid collector of rare artifacts from Planet E-Bomb's ancient past.
He brought our heroes via his Sky Galleon to his island in the sky, New England,
to ask them to help him find the long-fabled N-Word Pass of the lost Tomogachi Empire,
located in the undiscovered Temple of Tepegwin of Doom.
To do so, they will need to need a key into discovering its location,
which Leo has arranged the obtainment of by a holding an auction on his island.
That's a cool sentence.
Auction on his island in which one of the items is up for grabs.
Where one of the items up for grabs, the floppy disk, is in his own little deep hangar
and is said to contain clues as to where to find the temple.
Sullivan the Frog, assistant to Leo, will be representing the collector at the auction
and the gang will have to protect him from many dangerous folks who also desire the item.
Whether they are Gerard Depoupou, rival collector to Leo, or Pennsylvania Jim, rival adventurer to the gang.
After fucking a couch for the second time, spending a day stealing techno slime percocets from a
hospital in New England, and stealing the time of a sales rep at a Brookstone at Leo's shopping mall,
our heroes made their way to the events center, where they met the aforementioned troublesome
duo of Depupu and Pennsylvania Jim, along with Blowtoss' and Ray's ex-lover Marie Stane
and her bodyguard Rex.
After getting right plastered and all that, the fellas settled down for the auction, but
not before taking note of a strange figure in a hood sitting quietly among the crowd.
About halfway through the auction, Patrick Yoda, with his super hearing, heard what he
thought was Jafar sneaking around the center.
He and Blowtoss Piss went out to investigate while Ray William Johnson held down the fort
to the auction house.
Blotoss sent Patrick the Monkey up the air vents where he confirmed the worst.
There were party crashes about.
Blotoss strategically used- strategically- oh no wait, here it is.
Blotoss- I know all that!
Blotoss helped the strategically tiny Patrick Yoda up through the vent to learn more, and
Patrick Yoda assessed where in the ventilation system the intruders had gone.
Earlier, Blotoss had managed to sneak a set of Volkswagen Jetta keys into the auction room,
Buying Patrick Yoda just enough time to use Yoda's mind,
reading the thoughts of the intruders with such incredible clarity that he breached the language barrier
to understand with certainty the intent of these foreign invaders,
to steal the floppy disk that lays under the penguin.
Thinking fast, Patrick Yoda
busted down the gate, the grate of the vent,
whipped out his hoverboard, and brutalized these intruders,
beginning a brawl in the auction house.
And so,
that's where we are.
So,
basically what happened was is what all the shit i just said and patrick you
know just burst open the gate
not to those two guys uh... to ninjas red and blue dot yes yeah i dotted them on
the map so you could so it's easier to see
in the head and so
the any time
and so uh... the hoverboard
it's both of them
they uh... crashed through the doors of the room
out into on the balcony
and his general gasp from the audience is ever answer to looks up rex a bodyguard
are
who a little bit more closely
murray stains are digging
like growing wary and uh... the rest of the audience a lot of posh
come or answer sort of figuring out
what's happening
uh... really johnson blowtusk as you both see
guys pop out
of the balcony
uh... the auctioneer looks up and go
loans
and uh... yeah role for initiative
i got twenty one
and eight
it's twelve
and i will roll for the other people involved in this
oh yeah
all you
all right
yet yet
yet yet yet yet yet yet
what do you guys to it
uh... sorry
i mean
just cut this out of me rolling initiative for everybody yes you know i
always a year sweet time around the house
fruitcake about first-world why do you have to go to a
it i think i would have
over a year scald me a fruit and you know i
all through the
uh... alright
i know what that means i've heard that
not times in my life for no
had no reason that i can think of
but
and that i know it has guys a few sperms
uh...
a
You're empty, dude. I hate when I forget that.
And let's do this shit.
So, first is Blow Toss Piss.
So you see these guys fly out of there, they're on top of the balcony, you're sort of on the ground floor,
you came out to warn everybody that there were some guys sneaking in the vents that you thought was Jafar.
And they're now up there. So they're pretty far away from you, all things considered.
So also for the people at home, I guess to like help give you a sense of this.
There are two balconies.
There are a bunch of balconies around the event center on the top left
floor level two balconies are over the stage where the auction is happening
and the floppy disk is being presented right now.
And they are they were in the room behind that balcony.
And now they're out in that balcony.
So presumably they were going to try to steal it.
You can see Sullivan the frog is still trying to participate in the
auction. While this is going on, he's like a hundred dollars.
Just like trying to yell over the commotion that's going on.
But yeah, so how far can my character move?
I don't have a speed listed on my sheet.
Oh, I fucked that up again.
All right.
Yeah, so you have 30 feet of movement like everybody else.
So you're 30 feet and then an action or you can use your action
for a move action and just get into or you can move 30 feet and
prepare an action to move 30 feet.
to hear. Nice. And I'm going to shoot at the red ninja with my Grinch gun. Hell yeah. Okay.
Roll for that shit. 21. Oh, that that's a hit. That's a hit mama. Five damage. Now we're
talking. Okay, cool. So yeah, you get to jump and just like on this like you were ready
for them to you were somehow knew Patrick Yoda was gonna do that. And so you just you
just ran up and just me and patrick yoda have a friend link it's true hey do i have we'll get to
that we'll we'll figure it out we'll figure it out like another episode or another campaign okay yeah
no it's fine yeah but no okay so um anyway yeah so the you shot the gun and uh uh and uh it just
sort of uh this guy just got knocked in the head by the hoverboard fell out of the fucking room
and then like just gets clipped by uh... the grinch gun
uh... which it's like little uh...
like twenty cc and looking bullets like brian like images like fucking
cuts along the side
andy's and grab a side and and uh... make those sound that you can hear
uh... but you have another attack to support you to get off for god i have
to attack them and i said
he's double dipping
and right
he's the only he's the only one for this time that hits god damn son
six damage
yeah and you just like
pop out and just like
like i get him like
left right shoulder like going back like a guy get shot up
yeah uh...
so yeah he's uh... at between patrick you know that doing nine damage earlier
you doing eleven like a he's getting uh...
he's getting pretty pretty beat down
and those are just warning shots if i was actually angry he would be like
completely dead
yeah detail on that
yeah i think that the
Yeah, those are war. I'm saying it like, you know, I'm like all the way across the room.
Nobody can hear what I'm saying. There's a bunch of people like talking and screaming.
Uh, yeah, so you shoot it at him. You do that to him and uh, it is now the their turn though. So,
the the red still in the vents, you're you're busted down. You're in the room behind them.
Okay, you're sort of like for right, right. That's what it was. Yeah, for initiative sake,
you're sort of just like getting yourself up now i remember i remember there was
thing that happened like yeah you did something cool it was cool
uh...
so now it's gonna happen is the the red
the red guy is going to uh... uh... after being shot by you is gonna return fire
uh...
uh... he whips out a gun
and it looks like it's look it's like
it's really really like red and looks almost like it's made of like clay it
looks really weird
uh... and uh...
when he pointed at you like a hole opens up it where the barrel is and like a
bullets come out of it
like there was no whole and it looks sort of like
like claymation like opens up
and then uh... a bullet
comes out of it so
and
c_p_ hits
and uh... yet he he missed
little why do you still like kind of a little rattled
uh... it
and uh... he's going to uh...
jump down at this point
And, uh, what's his range?
And he was able to jump down without any, like, sort of issue, it seemed like.
And he's just going to try to shoot at you again.
He got two attacks too?
Yeah.
Oh my God.
What's the big leagues now?
You guys are in the big leagues now.
Yeah, that's not fair that they can do stuff too.
And, uh, that's a hit.
What?
And he does, yeah, we're in the big leagues now.
You guys have played enough.
I can start bringing out the sexy stuff.
That's fine.
I'm going to start lying.
This is bad news for me.
Yeah.
I like that you think that us having played several hours of D&D means that we're good
at it now.
Yeah.
We've learned anything.
I'm going to start rolling the dice myself.
We've gotten nothing but worse.
Like just strictly worse.
It means to me that maybe there's some sort of subconscious level you're picking up on
something.
Nope.
are getting a no
parade no one who will ever have to attack that this is the
and i would have been to attacks the
uh... how to attacks for us and then uh... one or zero every other tax for
them
okay
also i'll talk with my people
and i'll get it
uh... so he had he shoots at you this time
dot on the ground
sort of like got his bearings shot at you
and you take three damage. He shoots you right in the left shoulder, and when you look there,
you see a red mark on your shoulder, like that seems to be imprinted in your clothes.
Oh, blood!
And now the other one is gonna go, and he runs along the wall over here.
Whoa.
That was awesome.
That was sick.
and he hangs on to the wall and takes out a couple kunai, which are short throwing knives.
Sorry. You're acting like we don't know what kunai are. I was embarrassed that I knew.
So I was, oh god. All right, so he throws the two of the knives at you, Ray William Johnson.
I dodge.
Hold on, alright? You gotta wait.
[laughter]
You do that every time. You gotta wait now.
New rules.
He SOCKS!
Fuck!
Well, he does...
You know what?
You dodge. How do you dodge?
Uh, backwards.
Okay, you go backwards.
Yeah.
You know your famous moves where you go backwards.
I just walk backwards.
[laughter]
Until it doesn't hit me.
Yeah.
the
of range. Yeah and then he pulled out the 31 foot kunai. Oh he's so smart dude. You see it has like
you see it's like like weights have like the weight numbers on it this one has just 31.
Yeah and it's just like and he throws like two of them and they just like right in your your chest
and you look down if I remember you're either naked or still in your prison clothes but you
you see
and
we like talked about it in the last episode no no no no no we didn't we
didn't man I got a feeling these guys are gonna pull out the pancake minds I've
got a feeling tonight's gonna be a good night oh I fucking wish that I the plan
that now but yeah so now it is your turn Ray William Johnson and actually before
Before you go though, you take 2 damage. You feel the marks on your chest start to freeze you.
They feel really fucking icy to the point of it's almost like a burning.
I think I figured out who they work for.
Fuck dude, I'm at 19 HP already.
Goddamn.
Okay, is it my turn?
Yes.
I'm gonna matrix beam, wait which one did you hurt, Cam?
The red one.
I'm gonna matrix beam the red one.
Okay, I will let you know, there's a lot of people in your range.
I think of that.
Don't care.
Okay.
Alright.
Wait, will we get in trouble if he hits any civilians?
We'll deal with that later, okay?
We can explain it to the police.
I'm very interested in you trying to explain it.
So yeah, do Matrix Beam. I think it's a D, I think yeah, I think it might be a D.
I got an 11.
Oh, is it an attack roll? It's an attack roll, it's too bad.
Yeah, an 11. So you shoot out this like, you like put your hands together,
Kamehameha, this like beam of like stupid code, and you, I think is it, let me see if I got this right.
But I'm naked, right?
And you're naked the whole time.
I kind of, I kind of a little bit, just a little make it look like it's my wiener.
Yeah, so what do you do you like to use just sort of point it down?
I just kind of like just you know, you know, you know my hands are I don't know where your hands are
My hands are on my wiener and I'm okay. Yeah, I'm kind of I'm going like
I'm kind of like looking at blowtoss, but in a row, but it'll good but in a robot voice. So what does that? Yeah
Yeah, right like a blender coming and you exactly yeah and
There's squid words on the map now. It's a really good squid word. Thank you. Yeah anytime
Yeah, so you shoot that out. It does not
hit the
The the ninja he sort of is able to juke it, but it does incinerate that Jollibee. So roll for damage
Swag one of the Jollibee guards who was here. Oh my god. Yeah, I guess describe how you kill that Jollibee
Well, he looks he looks before even feels what's happening to him
he looks at me and sees what I'm doing like kind of making it look like it's coming out of my dick and so as
he's
Incinerated he's like smiling and laughing like his last like getting the joke and kind of laughing and then he's gone
Yeah, so he's dead
Three to go a couple people in the crowd are kind of like clipped by it, but they look okay
There's not as much crowd area within the range
But yeah, that's your turn
And how many techno slime points does that cost for you to let's keep me. Let me check a look
Holly zero looks like it's about five now it is
actually
I might be the worst turn I've ever done.
[laughter]
Well, you're actually, you should be weirdly proud.
So, suddenly, this Jollibee who's next to you,
who seems to be pointing at the ninjas,
next to you, Blotas, I should say,
turns around and tries to hit you with his baton.
Me?
Yeah, and he's like, "For glory!"
And turns around and tries to whip you with the baton.
on
just started is looking at you like oh and the other one from the back here
runs up and tries to shoot at you ray William Johnson and suddenly you see you
hear a warning warning warning and you hear Leo's the collectors voice over
like the inner the the loudspeaker well seems we've got some I know I changed my
voice from last time to sound a little bit more like someone in particular
It seems that the Jollibee's are turncoats. I don't like that, innit? Oh God.
Caleb predicted them being traitors.
Yeah, that was weird.
Dude, I'm a genius.
The doors shudder all around and you hear over the loudspeaker, "Intruder alert, intruder alert, intruder alert" and all that.
and all that, intruder alert, just keeps doing that.
And the Jollibee, this other Jollibee
is gonna run up and try to shoot you now, Caleb,
with his chicken stick gun.
- Fucking slap him in his shit.
- I mean, that might happen.
Oh, he hits you, I'm sorry.
- Oh my God.
- Yeah, this one gets you by surprise,
doing a solid two damage to you.
- Oh, dude.
- Meanwhile, this one is running
and tries to hit the auctioneer to steal the floppy disk.
- Oh my God.
- And he does not beat the auctioneer's insanely low AC.
So he just tries to whip it,
and the auctioneer's like, "Oh, dear!"
And like sort of just, "Oh!"
Like holds his hands to his chest, like Britishly,
and barely dodges out of the way.
But now it's your turn, Patrick Yoda.
- So the auctioneer just took the floppy disk?
yeah i guess you say he has the floppy disk is protecting the
protecting it from the jolly
was committed
i had a whole thing planned where i was going to bust through the back wall
you're gonna bust in the back wall
must into the back walls and grab the floppy did
is there any way i could still do that?
you could bust floppy into the auctioneers back wall
yeah exactly can i bust my floppy into the floppy
I'm
Go I'm telling him to throw it. I'm like
What what
Listen you British bitch. Okay. It's not the first time I've been called that
You're gonna get called it a lot more trust me. Okay, you throw I sort of just a fancy ax you telling him to throw back
Throw back throw it back for a real one right now one time you see him just sort of like fluff his like
like
the bucket uh... is being used in the office hops back to that movie word ends
with that happening
some billionaire
uh... of ways examples when they're doing the big the gay dance about it
yeah
he's just doing that that dance now
that i didn't mean like that but you know what i'm kinda like in this
okay i could keep doing it i'm just trying to adjust it actually know what i
I shouldn't get distracted by this.
Can you throw it up to me and then I'll use the force to grab it.
Okay, cool. So, what we'll do is on...
Should I use Arcana?
No, because you know what I was thinking?
Yeah, so here's what we'll do.
The auctioneer's turn will be right after yours.
So, yeah, we can have the auctioneer throw it up now
it up now and just like sort of resolve that now I'd like to do that so what you
should just do Patrick Yoda is roll athletics okay yeah roll athletics to
see if you can like make sure you have it okay now the auctioneer is gonna roll
athletics yes it does have a minus on athletics
Damn it.
He got a...
He got a zero.
So he just like does the thing where, you know, that kid and they try to throw the ball
and they throw it at the ground.
Yeah.
Yeah, he just does that where he just like tries to toss a floppy disk and it just like
this is like sticking out of the ground.
And he's like, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'll get that.
And he sort of bends down to get it.
That's what you could try to do in his turn.
You could still like move.
tonight
moved to a jump down to a yeah yeah yeah i can see you know what role acrobatics
to do that though okay so you don't damage yourself
twelve you're fine
you know i pretty easily i'd jump down on the floppy disk and i grab it
okay yeah
you're about your better
so that's all you can do this that's all you can do this turned again if i could
tack
uh...
okay cool
do you have the floppy disks that's now happening
it's a now it's gonna be a a rex's turn
it's a rex after uh... seeing the jolly be uh...
is basically just like targeting anybody closest to marie
so he just like runs at this jolly b
he's like
on the record
what he just like grabs it by its throat
and uh...
you just pops it's head off
thank you
squeezes it
just pops its head off his body had just like flies clean off its dead
uh...
uh... he said it gives you a good night blowtoss but his eyes are like putting
it is a it's easy to do in like a
we're both fighting together but he looks like he's like
gonna die
you know i think time
uh...
and uh...
now it's back to being your term book
all right
i'm gonna
i'm gonna move
uh... towards the stage a little bit
and then i'm just gonna shoot at the
the red ninja again
okay go for it
this is not it
are so she did not suit again alway also by the way i forgot
yet you take four damage that red mark on your shoulders that's burning all
you take for damage
it's nothing to me
and i'm just gonna shoot again
and twenty one
okay that it's for sure
six damage
nice yes you should have again this time you get him like in the five
and he's he's
uh... he's like smarting and uh...
does he have thick thighs
he has really thick thighs. they look like
almost cylindrical like they're like just like pillars
yeah and uh...
like tomato soup cans
roll a perception check blow toss
ten
k yeah
uh... you see his ninja mask sort of go down for a second but you don't get a good look at his face
uh... and he comes and he sort of puts it back up quickly
and um um now it is their turn and this guy's gonna sort of like with his die injured but
he's still gonna try to run at you and he draws his uh uh he draws like what looks like a sword
but he's just pulling his arm out his arm is like clay and it turns into this sharp clay and he goes
in to stab you um with it and he makes that sound that patrick yoda had heard earlier but it's like
And uh, and uh, he whiffs though completely you just like fucking
Knew exactly saw exactly what was happening there
And uh, but he's gonna try again the snap to do it to you. And uh, yeah, he misses again
So he's just like and just sort of misses you. Yeah, i'm countering with my pipes. I'm blocking. Yeah. Yeah, he's like
yeah, and uh, uh
The blue guy now is going to continue to run along the walls and he's gonna hang on this one here
uh... at the way this guy's running on ledges they should call him yours ledge
yes sir
this is the answer is no right did and he's got broke tonight at uh...
patrick you know
uh... terrible ninja can you just be mirrors let's run on
yeah i think i think he's going to be i think it's going to be revealed that he
somebody
pretty cool
i don't know
okay let's not let's not assume
because i already have an idea of who he is in my head says it's a sandman from
spider-man three she don't ruin this
and the i have idea too
and uh...
he does
i will say i think the other ninja is his brother he does ten damage to you
uh... patrick you know he doesn't do you know how but he doesn't do that
so you're just like grab the floppy disk you know i got it and then just like
Don't don't like to kunai clay kunai just like bump into your head
Bump and
now
he's gonna drop down so he drops down from the wall that he was hanging on and
he starts to like move his shoulders up and
like convulse almost and then
These like sharp tendrils come out of his back and
and go flying towards you Patrick Yoda
who the ninja?
yeah
oh then this ruins who I thought he was
yeah who did you think he was?
I thought he was going to turn you to snow in his clutch
I...me? yes!
yeah!
I thought it was going to be Snowmizer
I thought it was going to be Snowmizer and Heatmizer
me too!
oh my god
me and Cameron
look at our friend link
on the same wavelength
look at our link
yeah this link is true
yeah I thought that
[laughter]
I thought that too
and yeah the hopefully he comes in later
I just like frantically texting Joey like can you change the poster I know it's last second
they really want to see snow mice
so he's flying at me now with wings?
no he's like he has these like tendrils coming out of his back
like you know fucking like tentacles kind of shit
and they just are flying towards you and roll a dexterity saving throw
tentacles?
he's a squid
I know how to figure out who they are.
Patches, if you had to compare them to any character...
They're not, they're not any...
Okay.
They're not, they're not obvious at all.
Have you seen...
It's Red vs. Blue.
Patches, have you seen Year Without a Santa Claus?
What?
Have you seen Year Without a Santa Claus?
No.
Oh, really?
First of all, that sounds awful.
It's a horror movie.
Yeah, that's what I'm telling you.
I got really scared just hearing that phrase I've never heard those words put
yeah it's it's one of the scariest movies it's got two of the scariest
brothers has these two scary ninjas they're made out of clay they have people
talk about the remake but the jab the original Japanese version is so much
better and you are gripped by these like squiggly things they wrap around you I
didn't I didn't dodge it no fuck they wrap around you and roll and this roll
d20 okay they got to be bent and aliens was it 10 roll again okay 12 okay you
you get a mark on you that wraps around your body like this whole like blue tattoo is kind
of around you now.
And I'm a Navi now?
You take 10 damage as like this searing cold gets into your body and you are also now suddenly
seized with fright
like you don't even want to come near this guy so you have the condition is
called
literally called frightened um
and it just means that you have disadvantage on ability checks and
attack rolls
while the source of your fears in your line of sight
and you can't willingly move closer to him. I close my eyes
I'm gonna let you try that. Okay. That's hilarious
that's literally a good way to like you will still have disadvantage on attack
rolls and saving throws on like ability checks and attack rolls but like you can move closer
to him and there might be some ability checks and saving throws that you don't have disadvantage
on because you're not scared.
Now you're not scared as long as you have your eyes closed you're not scared.
Okay.
Yeah.
So yeah, you just like you got gripped by these things they leave a mark on you and
they fly back into this guy's back and now it is your turn Caleb.
Okay, I'm going to use my dong
Dongle blade my dong blade and I will attack the red twin from the matrix
Yeah, go for it. Go attack that albino. I hit him for fire. I got a rule to five
Is it a twin from the matrix is not the twin from the me?
I think is it is this is it chase and Marshall from Paw Patrol? I don't even know
It's not anybody that you guys will probably guess because it's to row grass
tell you it's you know it because it's crazy frog and mario otherwise this is gonna be the episode so
here's what i'll say is and they take off their masks right now first of all no
second of all um you they are part of a larger set oh okay so they're not brothers or twins or
anything doesn't do anything for me it's charmander and squirtle so i just that's a spoiler for
everyone I had to give make sure the show kept going so it's not Charbander and
Squirtle that's right members of the Miami Heat you make it too easy dude
they're they are they are a solid 510 now I'm just more interested in you
Yeah, it's okay. We'll keep going
You guys have used your character voices once so far
Completely and now like enamored and enraptured with
Think I hit my my shot really well, though you missed yeah
Okay, yeah
Yeah, where is that guy anyway? He's right in front of blow toss
Are you went on top of him? Okay, I couldn't say I was like, where'd he go? Yeah, so you do that
and it misses
and
That's that's you know what I think everybody I should probably give your characters all two attacks at this point
Because I feel like it's it's
Now everybody you should have you should you should be able to attack again at this point cuz these guys are kind of oh my god
I'm can I get three attacks then? Like no
I already had new so
You keep two attacks. I go for the dong lady. You're already like the best one. That's right
At fighting you all have different strengths and you all different fighting also
Well just from like a pure I don't know
No, that's not what I said this happened another time. I'm not gonna play
Take it back. I take it back and camera gets one attack. I
Can't do that. Oh fine. I attack him again. I hit all right. I do not hit. Yeah, I do not hit again
Yeah, you miss again. He's always a ghost brother. Yeah
Now it's the Jolly Bear the Ghost Brothers
My notebook this one is gonna try to
This one is gonna try to grab
Attack you Patrick Yoda because he wants that
floppy disk
You see Sullivan meanwhile is like a thousand dollars
Calling from the crowd still what if I say sold and I give it to Sullivan
Tell you what if this misses, uh-huh, and you say sold and give it to Sullivan
I'll let you roll an athletics check to try to toss it to him. Okay, okay
It missed okay. Yes. Okay. Oh my god. This is some real Indiana Jones shit
Mm-hmm, they would do have done this in one of the movies. So so yeah, so so solve it says a thousand
ten thousand dollars and
Sold and you toss it roll an athletics check
Nice. Yeah, Sullivan grabs it as you toss it to him as a reaction and
Now you owe me
$1,000. No, no, I don't that's not yeah. No. No, I sold it to you
I thought we were doing a thing this seemed cool. Now. You know it'd be for money. You owe me
$1,000 I will not I don't I just hang up. Hey, I don't have it on hand
Man break your kneecaps. No, please don't do that. Well, I pay up now as interest
You hold on to it for now, but later you're gonna give me $1,000. Can we do installments?
That's even better
No, you wanted to do installments man, that's not my friend
That's not you all those people just like shouting and like it's like a fight if you just try to extort your friend
Great that happens it's now your turn patch again, by the way
What voice was I doing for this you weren't doing a voice this okay?
All right, so I
Don't think I'm gonna go towards that guy, but the Jollibee's are bad. Yeah
I'm gonna fuck this guy up. I am going to hoverboard or hoagie surprise. Mm-hmm this
Jollibee right next to me. Yes, Jollibee on the stage with you. Yeah, I just noticed him I turned around it went oh shit
You bastard give me the floppy disk, how did you not I just threw it like halfway across the road
I was just I had like a line I had a line ready and I I saw it happen I threw it
25 feet you just mentioned that Gary proud you proud you can bet like why
did you just hit me with your fucking sandwich oh shit you gotta oh my god
yeah he's saying why'd you just hit me with that fucking thing and then like
yes
fuckin' knock his head clean off
*laughter*
he's... no more
you just fuckin' obliterated that guy
yeah what did i get? 18 bludgeoning?
yeah you just fuckin' like
28 hoagie surprised was 18 bludgeoned
you just like fuckin' destroyed this guy while he was
badmouthing
i turned him into dust
his head just flies up into the fence
it's a bad smell forever
here like the uh... there are no there are no bad
that uh...
uh... don't come to that uh... this had flying indiana jones he was playing
uh... if you still have another attack to another action you can do
uh... attacked it's a
uh... p_r_ no
i think
is there any other psychic damage to that jolly bees ghost p_p_s_ is there is
is
You have the I can I can't no I don't have the needler. No, he's afraid of that ninja
Yeah, I can't attack that ninja and I don't want to gang up on that one with you guys
So I think what i'm gonna do
is uh
I'm, exactly 30 feet away from sullivan. So i'm gonna walk over to sullivan
And uh start talking to him about the money he owes
Okay, okay look look I I I may I just called some friends I could probably get something together
I'm gonna take a little bit of time. Okay. All right. It's not something that could happen right away
I can we can do this like Klarna it can be like
It's a it's a thing on websites now where you can pay for shirts and installments now in the year
2025 hundred yes
Finally perfected it
Perfected extorting. Yeah, okay, okay
Okay, sure, so should we can either do you have to give me a link or we can either do
250 for four months, okay
I
Don't know the math
Any interest in?
You just turn around from 40 feet away fighting the other night. You're not new you have to put some kind of interest
Otherwise, it's not alone. You know what let's
So let's put a cork in this let's put a cork in this right now and later
Ray is gonna teach me about finance
No, no, we're finishing this right now
No, no, we're gonna tell you, you're gonna tell me about finance later
Just repossess his fedora and his jacket
No!
And for now and then we can
A six month term, 2.5% on the principal every single month
The principal?
The principal loan, the principal loan is $1000
I thought you were talking about the principal.
No, not the- no, there's no- what- where do you think we are, man?
We all- we have a flashback to school.
*laughter*
Yeah.
This looked like the-
Yeah, I just- I just- I was like, "Ugh."
I was in your stairs thinking about the principal.
Well, looks like you three have really ruffled my feathers again.
I'm Principal Bird. You're all in detention.
And, uh, we flash back to a completely different game.
I thought this looked like the multi-purpose room from high school.
This just becomes a breakfast club version of Gun City.
Yeah, I flashback to me smoking so much weed in the library that I scream and I break a pane of glass like a helioestivist.
Okay, I give up. Fuck this.
Yeah, I told you we'll do this later.
Okay, fine. Ten months.
- Yeah, yeah, and yeah, so you go over there and berate him,
and now it's Rex's turn,
and he's gonna run up and try to attack this guy
with his knife.
Let's see how he does.
Check this red ninja.
So Rex is running up to him.
Rex does, does that hit?
How long is this guy's AC?
Does not hit.
He's gonna try again with the knife.
and this time he's like
war
which is a screaming now he does it
and he did he just like fucking like
grabs a guy by the head
crushes his skull on his knees asserts stabbing him in the neck with the
night
like or like looking like a psycho
uh... he still alive though but
but barely he uh... uh... and now it is your turn again blowtoss
so this the red and is still alive barely a yeah
and you guys haven't surrounded
i guess all of this attack and with my super pipe
cuz i'm right here
might as well try to finish him off
as a twenty
that's baby girl
don't call me that's
sorry thirteen damage
yeah uh... describing hit him
connected young children's yet scurry uh... okay
uh...
i'd
i swing my pipe and it
i kinda mess but then it it
it ricochets off of uh...
will bring william johnson's forehead and
it's it's the red ninja in the face
so red ninja's things you you like dodging the call for a little and then
like it is about his back and
it's in just like sort of the jolly be just in his life
and just crashes into the wall
uh... right next to destroying a squidward
uh... the ending of squidward hanging up in the action and he's a strong
And he's just knocked out right now.
And you have another attack you can do this turn.
And a movement, right?
Yeah, yes, indeed.
Okay, I'm going to walk, yeah, I'm going to walk down, like over to the center of the
aisle and then I'm going to shoot at this last Jolly B with my Grinch gun.
16.
Yeah, that hits.
10 damage.
You guys keep getting their exact hit points.
you
and he falls over
yeah
I don't know
yeah you shoot him in the head with a gun
and after that his, so the gun goes into his
prefrontal cortex right
and it just sort of obliterates all of his life functions
and he uh, the force of the bullet
he's still alive, he's just a vegetable
yeah
and the force of the bullet hitting his head causes blood to squirt
work
and he falls to his knees any types
that's right
uh...
and uh... yeah
now it is the uh... ninjas turn
in this uh... balloon ninja
over over here
see what's the distance of this year
okay cool
this blue ninja over here
dashes
over to his friend
and he uh...
you see him uh...
slap his friend awake and shake him
and you see him jump on his friend's shoulders
and they uh...
all their hands together like they're praying
and then you just see
they just start like phasing out and then
and they're gone
so i lost the fear stuff now
yeah they're gone
i'm afraid now
yeah i'm more afraid than ever
i still think that's snow miser and heat miser and others
and uh... i think he's over the over the loudspeaker over loudspeaker you're
still hearing uh... uh...
through the world intruder alert and then like suddenly
sorry
and suddenly uh...
you uh... here uh...
boys is going to be in it
and then the uh... the alert turns off
uh... the doors the metal doors go back up around the uh...
event center
but they were blocking the doors
and yet you're out of combat now
so you see uh... commotion is died down
uh... the doors are thrown open
to the event center you see uh... leo coming in
uh... dressed in his uh...
jonathan davis meets team punk uh... outfit
and he uh...
sees you all he says i came as soon as it was safe
what happened here
i just kidding i saw it all on the video screen
this is this has been a complete disaster
but also a looks like we got
looks like we got the uh... the floppy discs so fair and square right now and
only cost a thousand dollars from sullivan
uh... to me so thank you so much for buying it
does not have a lot of it would be ours no please
i don't i don't
uh... also you know you're saying we shouldn't have the floppy disks so i'll
go i'll go throw it out now let's go to the other side of the world to give it
back to the blue and red ninjas so i don't know what you want to know i don't
Red Ninjas, where are you?
Calling them right now on my phone.
Pressing random buttons on my phone.
I know their number.
I'm calling them.
Patrick hides outside the door and knocks really loud.
There they are.
Okay, I'll pay.
I'll pay.
He see Leo.
He's like, oh Sullivan.
Don't you would kept you know, you were buying it with my money,
right?
Like it's not.
Part of the deal.
it
the
of
you get one dollar i'll pay you later
so no i have one dollar so that's all the paid me
no no no one's paid you
uh... for the floppy disk
and i told him it was a thousand dollars
and uh... you see everyone's are starting to file out uh... you see a uh... rex
uh... and marie start to leave
c_-rex come up to you guys and
was pretty good back there
you guys know it's right
i'd punch him in the stomach
it's just like
rock
yet and then you you too
he's certainly looks at you he's trying to figure out
what i want to use the robin and broken
yeah okay cool
i'm gonna go
and then uh... you see marie
he says
ideas i do say i'm sorry about that he always gets all riled up whenever this
any chance to make blood spill out of somebody's body
but i'm gonna have to go to philip said it was nice seeing you all play next time
is an auction i'll be in town as well and she uh...
uh...
blows you boys kiss
she blows us
okay i will
no character will ever do that i have a good and
and heading out the words that you have to do
and she has she starts to walk off and uh...
you see a
uh... pennsylvania jim just sort of
jim facing at the camera and like a lot of people
i threw a chair at him
the
here
it's not a big dot in the chair is that i think the face directly at the camera
don't you ever make that they see me bro
spread it might have pretty quite a few guys
uh...
you see it right now
said hall do i can be this was the last auction i've ever seen the leo but uh...
i'll go off to run you
i don't know what that is
i'm fran
he just uh... exits with uh... pennsylvania jim
and uh... everybody else are so far allowed as well and uh...
the a_c_l_o_ says
or we need to take this back tomorrow
to most of the role away
you know this head over there
are all you guys will
i'm walking over there now in a little starts uh... walk out
uh... of the center and solve in sort of truck trotting behind him
uh...
because what do you that you want to
chill here or do you like see if you could find out where they broke in or
something like that
that's also you do
and followed and yeah i'm going on going out
or and i don't wanna get left behind
uh... yeah
So yeah, you guys leave the center you go back to Leo's place.
You go back inside upstairs to his study and he has the floppy
disc now and he puts it inside of a he will he bangs on his
desk like bang like you would bang on like a jukebox almost
and it opens up and a like 1997 Dell comes out and he powers
it up and it has like Windows 98 in it and he puts in the floppy
disk. And it plays, what it does is it opens up a link. The floppy disk opens up a link.
I should have thought this through. This is very good.
It opens up a link to a QR code.
Yeah, it opens up a link to a QR code. Yeah. Link to a QR code.
It just takes you to EdwardPass.com.
And Leo's like, "Oh, hold on, hold on one second." He goes to a desk drawer and he finds like
like an old iPhone and he takes it out.
He scans the QR code.
He's like they want me to hold on one.
They want me to enter in they texted me.
Hold on.
He gets the code he puts it in and then the computer lights up
and it shows Club Penguin Island, which loads up and you just
sort of see the the penguin hanging out on the island.
You see Leo sort of studying it and all of you roll a
Roll a straight investigation check.
See if you guys can assess this.
27 dude.
Woo!
Crit 1.
14.
Okay, with the crit 1, you're not sure if this is a computer anymore.
Yeah, this is a window.
We have to get in there and we have to make friends with the penguins
and not start trying to open the computer screen like a window.
Yeah, yeah, and Leo Leo's like no it's not Zoolander very funny get out and he starts
Batting you away, but you ray William Johnson
Since you are of course a computer, you know just attached to a demon you
immediately recognize
What it is a computer?
Yeah, that was no problem for you. I'm a genius
And you also are able to sort of see what it's trying to say use like zoom enhance and your demon
suddenly like is able to like
Like zoom in and you you notice in the bottom left corner and very small black text
it says a longitude and latitude of the location of this quote-unquote penguin island and
So you notice that what do you want to do with that information?
He thinks it's a Linux penguin I
Know that they wouldn't give us the straight-up coordinates and
Leo says Leo says what what coordinates are you seeing? Well, you sorry. I'm talking to myself. Can you just let me finish?
Oh, sorry. Yeah
Cheers. Yeah. No, I think that was kind of mean I think what you did, but all right
Take it back man. Yeah
Back down so fast. Yeah, sure. Whatever. I don't just
I
Get up everything in my life recently I've been pushing people away
Yeah, I'm British so we do that all the time, okay, so come here come here, okay, all right
Get real close to the screen. Okay, like really really close. All right, his face is his nose is pressed up against
He falls over it falls on the computer
Alright, are you done fucking talking?
What's this guy got?
Investigate something, you fucking British piece of shit?
He pops his head up from behind the desk and he says, "I know those coordinates."
Oh my god, fine, okay, fine, you do it, fuck you.
"Thank you for pushing my head directly into the screen so I could see them."
And he says, "That's the longitude and latitude for the scope."
now
we'll we'll uh...
bangs on his wall
and a giant map comes down
uh... like all the secrets you got here that lower what the fuck is a bit
uh...
uh... no
but i don't feel like that man
and uh...
here is a
for viewers at home showing them right now a a sort of
early stages of a gun city region map
so
here is uh...
what gun city is on planet ebom
there is and and leo is explaining this now
and you guys would know this actually i should say
you guys would know that gun city is sort of a landmass
that was like a bunch of toxic ooze that they built a city upon that toxic ooze
ended up being techno slime
that techno slimy that being very very valuable and in enrich the city
uh... it was like the first settlement on plenty of our the first major
settlements of plenty bomb
density also has
these things called outer zones
these are sort of like a burrows
in uh... in the big at the big as speaking my language yeah yeah yeah
gotta fill in new york in here uh...
and uh...
one of the burrows is
as as scope
which is uh... literally like a scope on top of the pistol
uh...
because gun city shaped like a pistol
and then they have has a scope a landmass it is a scope on top of the kind of
pistol
uh...
uh... i was i was so i mean this is this is world building in real time i was
envisioning
a uh... you know a magnum
like three fifty eight or whatever
a thirty eight special with the scope on it
yeah
Yeah, maybe.
Okay.
Yeah.
Making sure.
And so it has the scope on it, this 38 looking special that is Gun City.
And the scope is like scope outer zone sponsored by scope mouthwash.
And it is sort of like a landmass that is a desert.
But right north of it is this massive mountain and then behind that, beyond that is the frozen
wastes of soy, which is sort of this like frozen expanse that people don't really go to.
All around the Gun City landmass is the uninhabitable sea balm sponsored by Stamps.com.
And it's this sort of like oozy, but it's also smoky, like sort of like unfinished planet
material, sort of like a gaseous kind of thing that nobody can live in for longer than like
half a second.
There's also, there's a couple other places but we'll get to them throughout the adventure.
But yeah, so you see Leo pulls down this map and he says, "Those coordinates are there,
Gadsville."
You guys would know of Gadsville as a a one of the small
Cities that one of the major cities, but it's a small city within the scope region. There's Gadsville and there's Tuppy Town
and
You'll you'll learn more about Gadsville
As we continue to play and he says what I'm guessing is
That there's something there in that area. There's probably I don't think that the
the actual pet temple this day, but there might be something that we need there and
You guys all you guys roll a history check
I love history. Mm-hmm
Fifteen more history. I got a six. I got a nat one Caleb. It's a six though
Yeah, Caleb doesn't remember what he had for breakfast
Pat
Yeah, Patrick Yoda and Caleb look at each other. Don't know
and uh, and uh, uh, blow toss piss.
You, you have a recollection from your studies as an archaeologist of, uh, of a, a, a like
set of caves that are embedded in that mountainside, um, uh, called the land caves.
Um, I'm having a recollection from one of my studies right now.
all
touching it.
No!
Fuck you!
You can talk now, I guess.
I'd like to, an officer, I'd like to report a murder.
Yeah, a list of burn centers in the United States.
Wikipedia.
Wikipedia, do you do you mind if I I'm gonna steal that means
Me acquisition
Acquisition at this me Mac silence brand and you know all that. So yeah, you remember those those caves
And and Leo says what I'm guessing is that those caves?
Yes, and he sort of pours over one of his books and he says that those caves of where the last vestiges of the Tomogotchi
civilization when they were finally
Dying out and all that this is where they ended. So maybe a key to get to the temple is in there
My only fear is that well, I don't know if any of you have been to Gadsfield. Have any of you been the Gadsfield?
Yeah, like a million times. I
Go there every weekend
I've been there once
Okay, okay. I lied. I've never been there
okay, so
This is very funny. I go there every weekend and I just got a three of five
So I'm very I
Like the idea of
One of you lying about going a million times
When are you going exactly once I want to use like a treats it like you're a fire island gay and that's like you're your hotspot
So, Gadsville, you would know, especially Patrick Yoda, is a city that is run by the Gads family.
And the Gad family.
So they have sort of control over that region, I'll get into a little bit more about what that means.
But you would also know that they are very protective over their territory.
And so you see Leo and he says, "This is a bit annoying, I'd say."
"Hmm, we can't really just drop you in there. Stykems does not have jurisdiction over that region."
Oh, yeah, they know me there though, so I can just go.
Oh, let me tell you something.
They remember the time I was there.
Look,
well,
I already lied.
Never mind.
Here's what I'll do.
I'll go to Expedia.com.
All right.
I'll book you guys a room at the that's what she said in
one room.
Do you did you all want separate rooms?
Fuck?
Yes, dude.
I saw Island you fucking big pussy.
You're giving vibes.
I just wasn't what is that?
Who do you think I am you all slept in the same room earlier, I'm pretty sure I don't remember that
All right, fine
I'll just hold on and he goes back on Expedia calm from Windows from his Dell computer
It's the last time the one time I was in Gadsville. I just want to say I was arrested for drunk driving
Okay, but I fled
The vehicle the only vehicles that are permissible in Gadsville are like the scooters that people ride in Walmart. So
Image flashback to that chase you're going like I am two miles an hour
This I keep like getting in giant crashes, but somehow just still going after the crashes and just causing another one
You're in a deathproof Walmart scooter
I'm in the killdozer of Walmart scooters, and I'm drunk as hell
and
Leo says all right
what let's I will lend you all my sky galleon and my frog here and
You you can take both of them to Gadsfield and in and seek the favor of the GAD family
They might let you in if you you know sort of got a sort of you know
Kiss their feet a little bit
but then they might give you clearance to go and visit the caves.
Otherwise you're shit out of luck.
I wish I could say I could help you there, but even all my money in the world can't move
the people of Gadsville.
They're a bunch of, you know, stubborn nonces.
A nonce, by the way, is a pedophile, I'm pretty sure.
I'm realizing as I'm saying.
You can't- you can't just hold down from a pedophile?
Nope.
I just-
After he goes there every weekend?
I just realized it as it was coming out of my mouth.
So I'm sorry about that, Josh Gad.
And yeah, so you guys can hop on the SkyGalleon or you could go tomorrow too if you want to
like sleep in Leo's New England Island and chill.
Yeah, no, let's sleep now because I have 14 HP.
Yeah, so you guys take a long rest in your chambers again.
Patrick, do you get freaky with the couch again?
the
so good
uh... and you just get down to it uh... me fuck couch and it's the morning
and uh...
yes
you guys are fully healed uh... you know this line is back as well uh... yes sir
that's right
yes lag
don't worry about that
uh...
yet you had done to the hanger
area
of leo's place and you see uh... leo
is already there with solvin
and they're sort of a they have a accrue
ready for you all jolly bees
uh... uh...
leo said don't worry i'll check that these ones on my children or turncoats
to another did that
yes yet totally
okay from fond of a model now i want to know
we were being sincere
he sort of looks around his eyes go back and forth and use
uh... ask them
And he's like saying it's a really good idea, like nodding.
I asked them this time, because last time I didn't ask any of them if they'd betray me.
But this time I made sure to check if they would.
So you don't gotta worry about that no more.
That was pretty smart actually.
Yeah, I wouldn't have thought of that.
Yeah, well both of you roll deception.
Two.
21.
He could tell that you're lying low toss and he's sort of like like frowns a bit but then he like winks at you a pretty William Johnson.
My man, he's sort of he says, all right Sullivan, you know, help these guys sort of go to the land caves and discover what's in there.
But you know, hope everybody I have a safe trip. If you guys need me, you can always call me on your PSPs.
you
Thank you for doing this. I promise once we find the inward pass, you guys will be free.
No more, you know being in jail and all that and be free to live your lives as a famous archaeologists who discovered the inward pass.
So yeah, run along now get in the boat and all that and yeah, you guys file onto the sky galleon as you come in and you hear yard matey.
I'm just kidding.
You know that.
Yeah,
welcome to me ship and I just hear that over the loudspeakers
that like you see Jollibee's like hoisting the sails and like
it's like they're like hoisting the sails and doing all the
ship stuff and then just like a jetpack like engine is just
like actually powers the whole thing and you guys fly out in
this airship and you're flying on the sky and you start to
approach you start to fly over you guys are like sort of right over gun cities you're flying over
you see the toxic waste of gun city in the dark lights and the neon weirdness and you fly over
these mountains that are between uh gun city and uh the scope you pass through the great invisible
wall so uh no a little known fact is that uh uh stakeham's promised to build a wall around gun
city a long time ago. And it was going to be an invisible wall.
They didn't finish building it. So they just have some parts of
it that are unfinished, and that people just know, don't have a
wall around it. And so they're just hoping that people don't
know. So they have a whole propaganda campaign to stop
people from learning about the fact that the wall is unfinished
and some of it is not invisible. So you guys fly through that.
And you go into now it's completely desert area like
completely arid and the ship sorts of the sorts of go down you go over the the
city of Tuppy Town which is just a massive derelict building filled with
like little furry guys called Tuppies and you go a little bit further north and
now you can almost see the frozen expanse and it's vast a frozen waste of
soy and it's vast like sort of a just like ice soy ice that just like covers
the whole thing and you settle down though before there to Gadsville and it's this colorful
blocky town.
You settle right outside of it and you sort of hop off the ship right outside the gates
of Gadsville and it says, "Welcome to Gadsville where all your dreams come true."
And there's like an asterisk there.
And so Gadsville, Gadsville is like a mid-tier industrial city in this zone ruled by the Gadd
family.
It is, there's sort of an old world charm to it, quote unquote.
You would know this, especially Patrick Yoda, obviously, because it appears like a late
21st century earth, which had all these like muted blues and brown colors and these perfectly
square parks and roads and boxy shaped buildings that looked almost like Legos, which is part
of Amazon's planned communities that first cropped up in Duluth after China annexed the Midwest.
However, there are also tons of electrical wires everywhere, running along the ground,
running along the sides of the buildings. They're clearly trying to say that we don't do wireless.
We stick with wired shit because they're very anti-gun city, being everything wireless.
They want to like keep their own thing. People ride on trams that are affixed to these electrical rails
that like just have like a big giant bed in the middle of the trams and there's just people just
lounging around eating snacks as they fall from like these little compartments and then everybody
else is riding the scooters from Walmart, the Walmart scooters. The Scope Valley itself produces
the only edible vegetation on planet Nebo. So that's how the Gadd family has been able to keep
control of the area because they control that. That's probably where Leo buys his food. Everybody
else eats carbon-based new plastic, but they get to eat real food, which is regulated edible
artificial lentils, which is probably what you ate, Patrick Yoda, when you ate the Jollibee
food. That's why it tasted so good. It tasted like actual real food.
Look, I go to Gadsville all the time. Yeah, and they have really good food there.
And the one other thing you would notice about Gadsville, you would definitely know, anybody
Who's been there or even you ray william johnson who's never been there is that what looms over?
I've been there. All right. Look this I'm the DM now, so it's can't
been there
Doesn't remember the name
Much like the world's biggest computer looms over gun city
the Gadsville cow looms over Gadsville, so
Gadsville has been independent from most financial influence unlike almost anywhere else in the gun city area
Except of course, they have to have at least one person. That is one benefactor in this case
It's the gateway computer company. And so they have a giant cow
That is the Gadsville's biggest computer
And it's the relationship though like culturally Gadsville is Gadsville
you know gateway just takes a cut of the money and runs to helps run the place with the computer and
Their Gadsville had one concession
Which was to have a gad like face on the cow and so there's this giant
Gad like face on top of this cow's body that stands 55 stories and like the next tallest buildings like 22 in this sort of like
Short short town like kind of like not that not that tall the buildings are tall but not that tall
And this cow just fucking towers over all of them. You could see it way in the distance
And yeah, you guys arrive in the town
and yeah, you you can
Kind of if you want to go to the inn you can rent some of the rent a scooter or you can take the tram
First thing I do when I step off the boat
I reached down to one of the wires on the ground and I just cut it just to see what happened
Yeah, roll an attack roll on the wire.
Okay, alright I'm gonna use my pipe to cut it.
24.
Yeah, you dent it in pretty hard.
Do you do that stealthily or do you...
Yeah.
Yeah, okay, roll stealth roll.
20.
Pretty fucking good.
You just roll up in the middle of town, fucking like put a cloak over yourself and just bang
I got the structure with a pipe.
And it was I'm just trying to learn how the system works
and which wires go where and this is the only way to do
that. Yeah, it busts in and you see the you see the wire
no longer light up the inside of your cloak.
You're under I've decided and when you lift up your cloak
in this town, you see that it goes to like a little center
node and it has other wires shooting out from it.
But that wire is dead.
So you don't know somewhere.
something something later in the campaign is gonna fail in a crucial moment
yet maybe that might happen
i'm not not taking a note of the fact that you just went to this town and
sabotaged its electrical
like infrastructure in the second
you showed up
i'm just
looking around
it's tourist stuff
it's good luck everyone does that
so you arrive in the town and you look for some tram operators who are
who are like trying to get people to go they all for the most part are worms
are anthropomorphic worms you've seen worms in gun city
and they're all like trying to solicit you guys to go I mean you see there's a
rent a scooter and it's run by a Ken Bone type who's running the rent a scooter
the
Killed like three Ken bones. Yeah, but those were those were Ken bones not Ken bone. He said Ken bone type
Yeah, look. All right
Let's move past this
Yeah, so what do you guys want to do or you can walk you can also walk
to the end
Let's walk to the let's get a taste of the local flavor. I don't think they're gonna let me back on any vehicle here
Yeah, yeah, and I keep stopping at random like like bus stops and like
telephone poles like the end of saving private ryan like where he goes to the to the uh...
the cemetery and i'm just i'm just remembering i'm just
well this is
is a group of the
yes you guys walk walk uh... along and you see a
uh... as is the custom in in gatsby l
there's lots of performers and shows being put on you know it's a very
musical place
there's lots of uh... uh... people putting online
live reenactments of famous Josh Gad movies and Josh Gad's progenitors.
So they trace their origin their their their bloodline to Josh Gad
whose children and their children's children started an acting dynasty in
the 21st century that performed in all kinds of movies.
But so you see reenactments live reenactments of pixels
and that one that one episode of Party Down he's in he's pretty good in
and uh uh episode it's a fucking great club yeah yeah it's a great episode yeah you see people
reenacting it and you see uh uh um and uh uh there's also olaf in this bitch yeah oh yeah
well the frozen ones are usually like reserved for like the biggest shows when they reenact frozen
of course yeah they're not doing that in the street yeah the streets are doing all the bees
the b sites please some book of mormon in this bitch uh book of mormon's like an underground
flavor kind of thing. Okay. Yeah, and you guys arrive at the
inn. You also notice as you're walking along by
the way, it's like it's a it's like the desert
has mostly escaped this area, but like it's still pretty like dusty and sandy
kind of around. It's still kind of an arid place and
you get to the the the inn and a worm
a worm behind the counter some worm woman behind the counter who's
filing her tail
Sees you all and she's like, yeah, can I help you?
You look like a worm I
Am a worm
You look no seriously. No, you know, really? No, it's like a worm. No, you don't get it
You look like a look exactly like a worm to us Mike. They're doing the worm thing again
they sent more kids in here to do the worm thing and
and uh... you see and i will not let you look like the most beautiful worm in the
world's hope is a subject
uh...
three
the three as you say that you expect a little bit
and she's like making the face or it's like
he's a little face but the as you say that you didn't like the face where
girls got there
when girls look like they're about to be
there but see ya
babydoll come on you remember me
uh... okay
role deception with disadvantage to make what the hell
uh...
she's like i'd don't remember you
i've been here before do you have a room or like what he is doing here
yeah we are you got a room
So we're just gonna go upstairs. We already got it. Can we have the spare key to our room? Whose name is it under?
yours
Yeah, yeah, you're it's under your okay, and she you see her like start to type it in with her tail your
Last name your is mama. Ma
Mike they're doing it again
It's under
And that you see the first name the first name is no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
And then the last name is
You see the bigger worm in the bag bigger older woman the bags like all right
I'm gonna have to ask you guys to leave you can know we
Seriously have a room we have a room wait, but listen, I don't know whose name it's under
We don't have any money. Shut up. We but we do have a room
I think it might be under Lee Leo's name
Wait, hold on we can read your room. Hold on. Let me just call up my friend and I pull out my phone and I call Sullivan
What's it gonna be like a thousand dollars give or take see us all that who's with you guys
You got a front this for us
the
Yeah, okay, we see Leo the Collector here. Is that actually...
Yeah. Oh, okay, hold on. Okay, hold on.
Yeah, so it's gonna be $1,000 for a room.
If you could just give me that $1,000, that would be great.
No way! No way!
Wait a minute, I'm right here!
And he answers the phone.
He crosses his arms, he's like...
Oh, somebody's grumpy.
One dumb frog.
You guys can't stop you guys gotta try to stop extorting me.
Listen, Sullivan, I'm gonna be honest with you.
The other two, they fucking can't stand you, dude.
I'm like the only guys on your side here.
So, if you wanna give me the thousand dollars, like,
I'll put it to good use.
I'll get, I'll like buy you like Chipotle or something.
Ten seconds later, I say that exact same thing to him.
[Laughter]
Okay, here are your keys.
You see, the girl worm hands you guys the keys.
Alright, well, go to your room.
What are you, our mom?
We don't have to go anywhere.
What? Fuck you, I'm staying right here.
We're sleeping in the lobby tonight.
I'm sleeping on this floor right here.
And there's nothing you can do about it.
And you see Mike,
she turns to Mike the worm,
and he's like,
"Yeah, there's nothing they can leave.
It's all paid for, so yeah,
I guess they can't really kick him out."
That's right.
Yeah, you guys go to the lounge,
So you guys go to the lounge, the lobby lounge, and you start making beds out of the couches and stuff.
So yeah,
you guys are setting up the lobby, you're like moving the couch cushions around to make a bed even though there's like a couch you
could sleep on. We're making a fort.
All right, I'm gonna have to ask you guys to not make it into a fort if you could have...
Oh, I thought we paid for it!
Wouldn't you love that?
I just, yes I would. I would honestly.
I bet you would.
No, you got a sexy pillow fight get your underwear on no, I'm not
First of all, I'm not wearing underwear
Come on
You sit with us in the lobby. There's all these windows all around. We'll have a sexy
Okay, can I get again? Can I have the key to the room? He's a guess sure and Sullivan's like I'm just gonna I'm gonna go
To the room you guys want no fair. He gets a room
We all have a room.
Come on.
Okay, I'll stay here and everyone's right.
You see Sullivan trying to like, like a dog is like making a bed with his front paw.
Sullivan, hold on.
Can I see that key for one second?
Okay, sure.
Okay.
All right.
Cool.
I just go to the room.
If he's going to be there too, I follow.
follow. Yeah, I follow but I bring all of the couch cushions
and blankets that we were using. Come on man. Just alright.
Just bring it back later. Please. No, you keep walking off.
He's like god damn it. You guys walk upstairs. You go to the
room. You see that it's just like every room looks like a
Josh Gad fan room. It's just like posters everywhere. There's
of like Josh Gad action figures of him action figures of his
Kids and his kids kids who continue the acting dynasty like the Barrymores
And uh, you guys hang out in there for a little bit and then you hear um a buzz
From your buzzer, which is shaped like olaf and uh, you hear uh, the girl worm darlene on the phone and she's like
You guys have like a visitor you want to come down here what?
I sort of changed her voice a little bit. I was I made her like a girl
I mean I was like she's not that I wanted to be like this. So
Just like a regular girl now. Okay. Oh, you want to come down here with the accent work I go
Okay
So you go downstairs and uh, you see before you this like beautiful
uh
v folk, um
They have like this wispy
Danny phantom casper ghost tale and they're floating in the air and this beautiful jojo's bizarre adventure upper body like
super buff
um, super stylish in in like the way that um
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure is stylish.
And this person, or this V-Folk says to you all,
"You're cordially invited to visit the GAD family!"
*SCREAMS*
*laughter*
Yeah, that's where we'll start next time.
Yeah, that's the perfect ending.
I'll be doing whatever snow does in summer.
The drink in my hand, my snow up against the burning sand.
It's all fine and dandy, you know, as Patrick Yoda screams with excitement at meeting the
Gads.
We cut back to Leo's Sky, England.
New England in the sky, Neo-England.
And Leo the collector sits in his mansion in his study, he spins his cube globe around
in frustration as he reviews the security hologram footage from the break-in at the
auction.
How did they get in there?
You know, he goes over each moment in the security hologram, you know, over and over
again circling the image that's being projected, trying to understand what could have went
wrong.
It's like he's reviewing the Zapruder film.
And he spins the cube load around even more in frustration.
"What do you miss?"
He spins it so hard, "Gosh bloody dang!"
That it spins off the axis and thumps onto the ground, shaking the security projector.
And now this hologram projector starts skipping.
And Leo, flustered as he is British, bangs on it to no avail.
but then he looks over at the hologram and sees what's skipping.
The hooded figure, the one who came in and gave their name as...
Snoochie Boochies.
Repeated over and over on this malfunctioning security hologram footage is the hooded figure,
this one Snoochie Boochies,
getting up and leaving.
Right when the attack started.
Oh, my bloody queen.
Oh my queen got, oh bloody.
Shit bloody queens.
Oh my god.
Bloody shit.
Hell queen bloody.
Oh man.
Shit.
[Dramatic music]
[SCREAMING]