Interior, detective's office at the Top Ten's Tattletail Agency in Gun City.
The year is 2245.
Or 2245.
A grizzled old detective hits his jewel and kicks his size 4 men's vans up on his desk.
He's wearing a cheap felt fedora over a thrasher hoodie and dickies.
His haggard face has seen better days, but better days are just around the corner.
Exhaling his favorite techno-slime vape flavor, come, the detective chews pensively on the
string of his hoodie.
His monologue slips into the scene, a silky saxophone precedes it.
An air of mystery and intrigue blossoms.
He speaks.
She's just a V-Girl.
That's what I said to myself the moment I first laid eyes on that anemic mouse of a woman.
And V-Girls aren't even real, like all V-folks, and that's with an X of course.
If you could remove your calculus rift, the virtual reality chip shoved into everyone's
penis when they turned 13 in Gun City, you'd see the truth that she's nothing but a bunch
of ones and zeros, the two lowest numbers.
If you tried to kiss her or give her an old-fashioned spanking, you'd get nothing.
Worst of all, like all V-Girls, she doesn't have nothing, neither.
No chest, no ass.
She sounds like a baby and she dresses like a hot topic meth head.
Me thinks, no thanks.
But god damn it, I couldn't help myself.
Those games, like two pale twigs sticking out of a schoolgirl's outfit.
And those cat ears.
Adorable.
I wanted to make that kitty purr.
Whoa, I'm getting a bit ahead of myself, aren't I?
Let me back up for a second.
My name is Detective Lenny Krapschitz and I'm about 10 minutes away from retirement.
See I was planning on running out the clock on my last day by drinking absinthe and playing
helly attack on miniclips.com when all 85 and a half pounds of that v-girl walked in.
Hasekitsune.
Soon as she got situated she started crying about her husbando who went missing last week.
Apparently he might be mixed up with some totemawariito or very bad men that may have wanted him dead.
She tried to talk around it but I pressed a hard real hard.
And eventually she admitted that her husbando is an unfaithful lout.
Jacking into Da Matrix 2 sponsored by Teen Vogue to get V-Paid by other V-Girls who look
like V-Children and say they're 18 before stomping on your V-Junk.
Not that I would know anything about that.
She thinks he might have owed some tokens to the Totemo Waruito for these excursions into
Da Matrix 2 and didn't pay up.
And everybody knows that in Gun City it's all about the tokens.
make the planet E-Bomb go round and round and round like an awesome famous video of a dick
spinning around.
So even though some of her story didn't add up, the tokens sure did.
So even though I wanted to tell her to fuck off mom I'm trying the game I took the damn
job.
But by the time she was ready to leave I was more or less off the force.
So it goes.
It's Kurt Vonnegut.
Now I can't promise this will be an easy case boys.
Something tells me there's a lot more going on than I know especially since this involves
and the greatest liars of all time.
So as my last act as private investigator for the Top 10's Tattletail Agency, I pass this
on to you three hotshots.
Report in, detectives.
He walked into my office in a pair of the biggest platform Adidas Kobe 2's I've ever seen.
It's like he was 3 foot 7 and the shoes were doing all the work for him.
He looked 5'7" until I saw the shoes.
How he learned how to walk in those, I can never figure out.
I mean seriously, how do you get platforms on a pair of Adidas Kobe 2s?
They already look like the cloud cars from Bespin, which exist in this universe by the
way.
But I digress.
He said his name was Larry Crapshits, being a case he just straight up didn't want to
work on anymore.
Because he had just retired.
Shit.
More paperwork for us.
When I read through the dossier he handed us, I immediately spilled hot coffee all over
my cock and balls. It was unrelated to the shock I had felt reading the case. I burned
my cock and balls so bad I had to go to the bathroom and splash some cold water on them.
I later realized this was a mistake, as I was still holding the dossier in my hand and I
got water all over it, making the page completely unreadable. I had to look over Ray William
Johnson's shoulder and read his. I've seen over a million cases in my time at the agency,
but none that were like this. My name is Patrick Yoda. I've been a detective for the Top 10's
Tattletail Agency for two weeks. I may not be much of a hero, but heroes don't solve
mysteries. Not in Gun City.
That was awesome. Yeah, you got me.
I liked it you just there's you just invented a new scenario
For some reason we're in your office
He's wearing different shoes
We all have the same office yeah as Larry, okay, I just you know
The names piss
Blowtoss to my friends, but those seem to be few and far between these days
You can't trust anyone in gun City
Especially not in my line of work
the city bristles with a thousand laser knives eager to plant themselves in the backs of anyone with the nerve to ask questions and
I happen to be in the business of asking questions
difficult questions
questions nobody else seems to ask
questions about grinches
That's right. I'm a Grinch detective.
I've solved every Christmas crime this city's ever seen.
The case of the missing present, the case of the lost gift, the case of the stolen stocking.
Of course, when I say solve, I mean it in the loosest, most violent sense of the word.
I'm not so much one for thinking.
I got my own special way of closing cases, and it involves my colt Santa Claus special snub-nosed revolver,
Two lengths of very disagreeable lead pipe and a dash of vigilante justice
I may not be much of a hero, but heroes don't solve mysteries not in gun city
Yours was scary
Scared
You're the scary one
You're a sit. Yeah, I've got I've got I'm chewing on a jewel like it's a cigar
Whoa.
Dan, I got sharp teeth.
I have like in comic books when they draw someone with sharp teeth.
Yeah, and it busts open in your mouth, the pod.
And I drink it.
And then for ten minutes you're just like, "Ew."
And spitting.
That's disgusting.
Okay.
No, you're chewing on it from the electric end because you like to lick that part.
Yeah, you're chewing on a poop like a cigar.
A hard poop.
Now, just go ahead and read your thing.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to be completely honest here.
For most of Larry's meal, I was pretty clocked out.
It's been about 4 hours since I last ate, and I actually have a friend who is going through
some stuff, so I kind of have been dealing with that.
I was also just imagining that movie Jumper with Aiden Christensen and thinking about
how fucked up it would be if he got stuck in a wall.
Would he clip through it like in Gmod, or would he get cut in half?
I don't know, there's just a lot on my hard drive right now.
I've been trying to paint recently, and it's not going super well.
Maybe I just don't have an eye for it.
I also kind of feel like I'm coming down with a cold.
My name is Ray William Johnson, and I am a computer that has been duct taped to the back
of a demon.
I may not be much of a hero, but heroes don't solve mysteries.
Not in Gun City.
Thanks boys, I just needed your names but I'm glad you...
I mean that's good you know, I see a lot of color character too.
Alright.
So uh...
So yeah I know at least one of your dossiers are covered in piss so let's just open one
of yours and I'll tell you what's going on with this case.
What you're dealing with here is a classic, what I think is a classic missing persons
case or perhaps just a husband gone wrong situation.
So if you're going to want to solve this I'm just going to need you guys to go first probably
just talk to Hussie see what she knows see if she can point you in any directions
you know she only gave me so many details but after that it's up to you look I'm
out all right I'm retired I don't I know I'm trying not to deal with this I'm
trying to go to space Cancun I thought you had 10 minutes left you know I have
about you know those intros were long so you know I got about like three and a
half minutes left to oh my god yeah so no but I know here's the thing here's the
thing look if you start with her I'm sure she's got some stuff going on look
She is a pretty big streamer, she is a big e-girl, v-girl I mean obviously.
And so you know she is pretty popular so she might have a lot of enemies herself.
Her husband Sean McKelvey, he's got a lot of enemies too.
Like who?
A lot of real jerks who like to call out people who pretend to have integrity.
Just real, real jerk-wads.
Stuff like that, you know, or maybe cuckservatives.
Some normal world types.
That was fire.
Oh, damn.
Oh, okay.
That's right.
Thank you.
I see what you did there with the words.
He chews harder on the string of his hoodie.
In excitement at your approval.
Patrick, are you Australian now?
No, I'm doing a mid-Atlantic action.
Alright, I'm Australian to take.
That's on a screen.
I think we were just doing Cockney.
Oh boy.
So, oh.
Alright, that's good, there's a cat.
So, look.
If you guys want to ask me any other questions, though, I'm here.
Let me see if I can answer anything.
thing. Go ahead. What's up? I'm retiring, you know. In a minute and 30 seconds you are retiring.
What will be your first move as a new retiree? Honestly, it's something I've been thinking
about because the pension is pretty nice but, you know, oh you mean like the first thing
I'm gonna do it like like do you do you walk out of the room or what? Oh, yeah
No, I get 30 seconds. Yeah, I can't stay at here
You sure you don't want any of the more valuable information because do any time off the clock
You know
Do you have any orders for the vending machine do any I do have some quarters? Here you go
I'm a couple quarters short. You see and I also have some quarters. Yeah, hold on. He gives you guys some quarters
Each 10 quarters add them to your inventory 10 quarters each
Score oh wait hold on one more thing before I retire
seconds
My all the duties that you guys need from normally for me are gonna be handed over to him my assistant who is now gonna be
promoted to head detective and he and
And his assistant walks in and it's none other than a dapper little frog with a bowler hat and vest
Oh my god, dude. With the Winnie the Pooh style cartoon no pants situation.
Mm-hmm.
Oh. I don't think I've seen this frog before.
Uh, how you doing? My name's Sullivan and I guess I'm the new head detective here.
But I guess I'm-
When do-
Sullivan, when do you retire?
[Laughter]
Well, I've had a lot of college debt, so I don't think I could ever really retire anytime soon.
I spent 10 million dollars on the Vrije University.
Is that the one on the computer?
I'm a full-sale graduate myself.
I've got a-
We have separation issues because we lost our old captain.
No, I understand.
That's very frightening and stressful.
I've gone through that myself with my captain just leaving also, the same one you guys have.
How do I know if I'm gonna trust you?
Uh...
You could roll an insight check to see if you...
...consensate a nefarious intent or...
...or something.
No, I just have trust issues 'cause I missed my old captain.
Oh, okay. I understand then.
But look, I can drive you guys.
Was she our captain?
I guess so, like a police captain.
I guess.
Sort of like the head detective.
Okay.
Okay, so we need to ask him some questions.
No, you don't have to have to you know, well, but so Sullivan Sullivan, where's this V girl stomping ground?
So to speak
Well, she lives at the spaz or the sucker fucker auto erotica zone
Which has been annexed by gun city for over ten years now
So it's seen a slow but steady increase in crime since the introduction of a Dunkin Donuts that gives free donuts to officers who have
approvable negative IQ score
uh...
to get the at the head past the lockheed martin prop plaza and make a right on
mister hans boulevard
uh... but i'll get you guys there i've got i've got out of the official
detective vehicle outside
the frog mobile yet if you get
no idea i i i i i see the news for us
you know it's like a big and i i i got a booster seat so i could see over the
steering wheel
it's a two thousand seven rocky hughes
it's a two thousand seven ryan dunn two thousand seven portion on eleven g_t_
three ryan's done addition
doesn't say random here on the spoiler
you know it
all right well that is the right about four
all right well i think he's a crikey for me one time in the right
uh...
i thought i was doing a mid-atlantic no i think you're doing better than caleb suggesting
but no i think yeah i think i just never realized how close those two accents were
yeah because it's mid-atlantic it's in the middle of the atlantic ocean just like australia
exactly damn dude that's such a good point yeah all right um i say we get down there and we we
head over to the Saz. That's a good idea. All right. So yeah, Sullivan leads you
guys outside the Tattletail agency and leads you to the 2007 Ryan Dunn, 2007
Porsche 911 GT3 Ryan Dunn edition. Let me put the detective voice back on. It's the
Havokah of dreams. It cruises smoothly and easily and has working brakes and a
breathalyzer installed that won't let you drive if your BAC is anywhere near where
Ryan's was at the time of his tragic death. As he swerved on the roads of
Eastern Pennsylvania, endangering countless innocents and killing a
thirty-year-old production assistant who was riding with him in the passenger
seat. People seem to forget that he just killed another person, you know. Very cool,
no, it's awesome, he's a hero. He's my hero. Yeah, and so uh yeah, Sullivan leads you
guys
This car from yeah, I have I have about 300 television screens inside
So that's how you kind of know incredible for that makes sense makes sense to me
Yes, any videos you guys want to watch while we're in here. Can we watch Numa Numa?
original
Hold on now, I'm hold it on
Fingers hovering over the Numa Numa button, but go on have you seen Napoleon dynamite dance the Numa Numa?
Wait, hold on, wait, this is your car?
Right?
Alright, well it's a detective...
Okay, just wait.
Shocks...
Pegs...
*laughter*
Lucky...
Continue.
*laughter*
Okay.
Can we watch the video where the spy from TF2 says "surprise buttsex please"?
these
uh... i can have half the screens played the surprise but sex video in the other
half the newman
by uh...
the following day
uh...
is that what we want to take a look at it
relation
that makes everybody
okay and caleb you can
ryan william johnson
you can play
uh oh
you can play one of the max pain games
i'm green but you know
i guess i get mistaken for white sometimes
can i quote you on that
yes i've heard green is white for frogs
well yes it is that's a good point
great frogs always complain green people used to be slaves to but you're white
now
yet the interesting you try to walk around tracy green lives matter also
never once i go
what do you say you're a system like a man to say that i've met a two-year
song exactly
that's right
and that's what i believe
this character
anyway so uh... you guys drive in the car you have
like three thousand stimulating
uh... screens going off
you know
you drive through the lockheed martin plaza
uh... with the voice back on
passing by bars and techno slime cafes and department stores and
things that look for green all the sun
the last bit of grass in all of gun city besides
that kind of grass
starts to come into view
What kind of grass?
What the hell are you talking about?
It's weed. I'm trying to say weed.
Wait, stop. I can't. I'm supposed to be...
Nice. Sorry.
Hold on.
You reach Mr. Hands Boulevard and make a right on it.
Suddenly there is a front lawn, expanse like you've never seen.
And there's not just a gate, but an entire fence in front of you made entirely of photon lasers.
On the center of the gate portion of this laser palisades are the initials SM.
In a white hot laser booth sits the absolutely still security thwomp, protected by a thin
layer of iron around him.
Your car cruises up to the window.
I think he's trying to say state your business.
Um, uh.
We're detectives.
And we're here to see a bitch.
That's right.
He seems to nod approvingly.
How does he nod?
He moves his entire body just back and forth.
So he wiggles?
But you can tell it's a good wiggle is what I'm trying to say.
He's not falling over onto us, flattening us into a pancake.
No, well actually you know what, I should roll, let me roll an athletics check to see
see
the
You got it. You got it already. You actually got a crit on your first one. So you both got crits
I don't get back to the chat and where's the there's the button. Yeah. Yeah, you got yeah, you did it. Yeah, so Caleb
Ray William Johnson perp and and blow toss piss you guys have a you guys completely get out of the way just in time
Patrick Yoda you do okay - that was sort of the check that was about the the amount you needed to get through it
So now the flop is crushing the car and Sullivan is still inside. Hey, I'm trying to get him off, please
I
Look, no
I look into the camera and I say I
Can't stand when people hurt frogs and then I run and I grab Sullivan and I try to pull him out of the car
Okay, and that case do a do a strength just do a strength check. So strength saving throw again
No, I guess just a straight straight strength check. Okay, so just hit you strength button on top of your thing. Yeah. Yeah, it's enough
That's perfect. So you pull him out of there and uh the thwomp is going to crush the car though if
you guys don't pull him off so I'm going to give you guys one chance to do so.
Um the thwomp meanwhile is just like
I perfect form I deadlift the thwomp back up to his resting position.
You have I think the lowest strength. I have I am I am so strong.
actually if you all of you guys roll a strength just strength check and we'll
see we'll see yeah okay all right that's that's look at that 19 dude yeah that's
yeah you guys are all fuck you man look at that 19 dude yeah yeah that's good
the 19 is what does it so you guys all sort of get together and lift as hard as
you can you lift the thwomp up you see a giant anime sweat drop and he's like
embarrassed yeah and he waddles back to his booth and just presses a button with
his like stubby and 64 a circle hand and you watch as the photon laser palisade
sort of slowly disassembles you see the long like football field length road up
to what looks like princess princess princess pieces castle is what I almost
said so I'm just gonna keep that yeah all right guys let's get back in let's get
God, that was close.
"You should learn how to nod!" he chastises the Thwomp.
The Thwomp sort of looks downcast.
So, anyway, let's all pile in.
So you guys all pile in, and when the laser gates go up, you see countless other traps beyond it disable.
EMP charges and turrets retreat into the ground.
Electric netting dissipates.
The road to the mansion itself is about a football field in length.
You see wealthy folk parading around the gardens and fields on either side, treating the estate
as if it were a public park of some sort.
Once you all reach the mansion itself, the Princess Peach Castle, you're greeted by a
massive fountain, spraying what looks like gamma fuel, and it refracts against the artificial
argon-charged lighting radiating from below the base of the fountain.
It's quite the sight to behold.
Sullivan is directed by one of the staff to a parking spot near the fountain, and you're
escorted out by the same staff and led to a massive gothic front door of the mansion.
The front door is covered in logos for off-brand sodas and other crude cultural detritus that
suggest a civilization in decline.
This is that old gun city money you've heard so much about.
So you're at the front door, what do you guys want to do?
Ding dong ditch.
Mm-hmm.
I agree.
Let's do it.
Yeah, so there is a doorbell.
See if we ding dong ditch.
Sorry.
No, keep going.
I'd rather you guys do that.
I just wanted to explain our tactic.
Explain what a ding dong ditch is.
Well, no, if we ding dong ditch, then we can get in there.
Yeah, I'm going to go ahead and do that.
I'm going to go ahead and do that.
ding dong ditch, then we can get in there.
We can sneak behind them.
Once they're out the door.
- It's also very funny.
- It's also too funny.
- I need a laugh right now.
- Do you guys want to ding dong ditch this bitch or what?
- Okay, I already did it.
- Okay, yeah.
- I'll do it right now.
- Okay, yeah, you hit the taco-shaped doorbell.
I sense an offensive accent coming on Patches of Smart.
No, no.
And uh, yeah, and the doors open.
And do you guys try to run away then before the doors open?
Yeah.
I hide in the bush.
You guys actually try and-
I hide in the same bush really, really close.
Everyone makes a stealth check.
So go to your skills area, yeah, and just hit stealth.
22.
I'm so good.
damn.
Alright, so yeah.
So yeah, and you guys all, you guys, uh, so you guys all ding dong ditch and you all, you
all beat this, this guy's perception check, so uh, uh, uh, the guy who answers the door
is a robot of some sort.
Um, and he opens the door.
He is a robot butler, he has a little robot bow tie.
And he goes, "Who is it?
Those damn teens again.
I hate this."
And he, uh, shuts the door.
shut the door no we can't
wow
wait can i try to step my foot into the door
can we try and ding dong ditch again
i used my yowdy ding dong ditch again
let's do it again
but this time we stay close enough
that we can just we can we can bum rush him
we can poke it we can poke it with the
from the bush that we're hiding in
ok yeah so you guys go back
fucking ok
wait so so hold on
can i strategize for a second
I apologize for a second.
Yes, please, please.
Now, Ray, once the robot gets out here, I need you to throw your computer at his head.
You want me to hack him?
If that's what you call it.
Let's see.
I still have my hacking ability, right?
Yeah, you should still have that.
Alright, you know what? Fuck it. Yeah. Do it again.
Yeah, sure.
Run it back. Let's ding-dong-ditch him again.
Alright, cool.
so yeah so you all have to make a stealth check again if you want to hide this
time again so go for it doesn't really matter because as soon as he popped I'm
not gonna hide because I'm just gonna throw my my as soon as you I'm gonna I'm
gonna pray. Oh no. Patrick made a religion roll and got three. He actually got a crit
one so he got literally... You try to pray to God and you just... Honestly I'm gonna need you to
roll a I think I guess a constitution saving throw just to see if you're able
to like withstand the like earth-shattering feeling of emptiness
that just overcame you yeah you just found out God wasn't real yeah that's
not just it's not gonna be enough man
you are sitting in the bush for the remainder of the campaign yeah for the
remainder of the campaign Pat is in an existential malaise just completely
unreachable he's right now realized that he will never see his grandparents again
they're dead forever. You take two psychic damage.
What do I do? I take that out of anything? Yeah, your hit points.
Oh, my hit points? Okay. Yeah. And then I come up and I pat him on the back and I say,
"You should dry headspace." So what you're telling me is there's no techno Christ?
have you ever heard of the flying spaghetti monster now that's not funny
that's not funny have you ever heard of pinned Gillette he's a magician I don't
support his dark actions you will now okay so you guys think you guys think
dung ditch or is it just you're just gonna ring the bell okay cool okay this
is just a ding-dong. Yeah, okay, so you guys ring the the taco shaped bell and the
the robot answers. Yeah, me too. Somehow I didn't understand that. Somehow I didn't understand that the first time. Yeah, no, you just thought I was being racist.
Yeah, well I was like, "Oh, he's setting up sort of Speedy Gonzales voice later." Yeah.
Okay, a taco bell. Now I get it. Yeah. Yeah, so that's more, it's one of those puns
It's more for me than it is for anybody. So I looked into my camera. I look into the camera and I say
Talk about a crazy pun
guys
Need you to roll for that. Yeah roll performance check. Come on, you know the rules 13. That's good
Yeah, so everyone kind of was like, oh there's enough there was enough irony in there, but it's okay like
Spirits a little bit. Yeah
So the robot answers the door and he's like, and then like while he's answering the door
he's like in mid sentence like, I swear I'm gonna kill these teenage and he sees you guys
there.
Okay, now immediately I hack him.
Whoa, it just switched to a different part of my character sheet.
Oh, sorry, I did that.
I was switching to your spells area.
That was gangster.
Thanks, dog.
Yeah, okay, cool.
So, it is a, what is it, a fucking, I wrote this all.
I forget I have child porn upload.
Yeah, feel free to use that, you know.
I will.
I'm gonna use it on you in real life.
No.
Yeah, I'm going to.
No, I don't think so.
you can't do that. So I made the spell. So, it's like I know that it doesn't work on cool
guys. Frankenstein's monster kills Frankenstein. No. There's no way. You can't read, so you
wouldn't even know that that's what happens. I've read the book twice. So I'm pretty much
an expert on books. I've never seen you read before. You've only read one book and it's
Lolita and I'm going to upload Child Born to you. I actually wrote my dissertation on
lolita and why that's bad. So yeah. Yeah. Well, you're canceled for going to college. No.
Yeah. No, actually, I got a I got a I've got a only have a GED. So I'm one of those cool.
I'm cool. Actually, guys, this is a GED. This argument is is is Caleb's computer data attacking
the robots data and the robots.
I thought it was fighting back.
I thought it was a roll.
It's a D-DOS attack.
Or a D-DOS?
A D-DOS?
I don't think the pronunciation on that one matters all that much.
It's THE DOS.
Yeah, it's D-DOS.
Yeah, so anyway, roll a...
Roll, I guess...
Oh, what do I have here for this?
Oh, hell yeah. Oh, I just got a roll.
I rolled intelligence saving throw against your spellcasting modifier, which I think I'll
do pretty well on because I am a fucking robot.
So my stats are pretty decent for intelligence.
Let's see though.
You're not even that smart.
No he's not, you hacked him it turns out actually.
Yes!
Yeah so you hacked this robot.
So your computer tower, I guess, that's on your back or whatever, unhooks.
Yeah, you describe the process actually, because I want you to take ownership of this, man.
Okay, yeah, so my demon, he turns around and Blotoss gets behind me like a quarterback,
and I squat down and I basically hike my computer directly into his skull.
And then now I've taken over his body and I coyly say, "Come on in, ladies."
What?
So, yeah, you hack the robot, you tell him, "Come on, ladies."
What do you want to do?
You're now inside this mansion as the robot.
I believe you hacked him for 10 minutes.
Oh my God.
So you basically have full control of this guy for 10 minutes.
Well, I guess I need to see...
I mean, I haven't seen inside the mansion yet.
I don't know what I'm working with.
banks and find where they keep the snacks and treats affirmative the pantry
okay cool yeah so he you go into his files and you see he has a snacktivist
selection they could choose yeah the the treats are pigs dead in the blanket an
an LGBLT, a Me Tootsie Roll,
or if you're feeling frisky,
the Lovely Bones Caesar Salad.
- Do they have any Magic Spoon Protein Cereal?
- Why don't you roll a, I want you to hack in deeper.
So I'm gonna have this guy roll
an Intelligence Saving Throw against that idea.
Like, does he have that?
Let's see if he can pull that up.
- Okay, 'cause it might be like how parents hide treats.
- Yeah, yeah, he has that.
- He has it? - He has that, yeah.
You have to go into the pantry behind,
yeah, go for it, yeah.
- Yeah, I pull like a secret bookcase,
I pull one box of Lucky Charms,
and it opens up a second pantry.
- Yeah, so you go into this kitchen,
it's pretty clean and pristine, pretty gorgeous.
You do the Lucky Charms book turning thing,
and it opens up a deeper pantry
where it's got more secret snacks in there.
you take those out
you make it all this ruckus in the kitchen so i'm not trying to try to do
it quietly or what
i don't know how to possible and you know you i'm yelling at the top of my lungs
snacks
yes i would like to know how to get a separate from low blood sugar
yeah so we we need something right now as we're going to try and get
solvin sort of like trying to run interference is gonna freaking out
and uh... yeah uh... you guys here over a loudspeaker
uh... hello
Who's here?
Robo, did you let somebody in?
- Wait, no, wait.
Well, she won't recognize my voice though, huh?
- You'll be Robo.
You'll have his voice. - It's me, your robot butler.
I just said nobody was here.
I'm here, I'm your robot butler.
- Yeah, so she's coming downstairs.
So-- - Go back upstairs.
- Go back upstairs.
- There is an actual shooter downstairs.
(laughing)
Go back upstairs.
Do you guys wanna- wait so the robot's now saying that.
Alright, I'm gonna need you to roll a deception check with disadvantage because there's all
this other insane noise going on.
What's my disadvantage?
Yeah, she's like, "Okay, that is- this is not okay."
And she starts walking downstairs and you do see, out of the corner of your eye, all
eighty-five and a half pounds of that hussy kitsune.
Uh, v-girl.
And she looks at you all and she's like, "Oh, are you guys the detectives?"
"Fuck."
"I don't know this for nothing, dude."
I say, "What's a detective?"
"Okay, I, there, so like I reach out to the Tattletail Agency to get a detective to come
here to look for my missing husband."
"Wait, I forgot that she sent us here.
Why did we do all that?"
"Yeah, I was kind of wondering, but I didn't want to stop you.
I was having a good time."
"No, it's okay.
Now we're full."
"Yeah."
now we get now we got now we're ready to solve the mystery yes a whole bit solvent
like goes up to her and takes off his bowler hangs I apologize it there they
have a lot of blood sugar issues we were just testing you to see in you past that
you would you bail hey you roll roll deception roll deception Cameron that's
a nine mm-hmm yeah I mean she's let's see me see her insight though into this
cuz she might be dumb as shit yeah she got a - so she's like oh yeah for sure
sure okay I can see that she's like not like yeah I could see like why you would
do that um yeah like come in then and I guess make
yourselves at home and yeah she sits on a a Game of Thrones style chair the yeah
the Arthur Chu chair can I attach from the from the the yeah you could attach
you could yeah absolutely I go back to my guy as soon as she says on the couch as
soon as she says make yourselves at home I start taking everything from the
pantry and putting it into my backpack make us make us slide a handshake on
that I'm not doing it secretly she said okay she's like speed this is I say this
is what I do at home she's like yeah for sure okay like you know she's rich
Make a strength check, because that's a lot of cereal.
Yeah.
Yeah, make a strength check to see if you can carry it all later.
While this is going on, I need to use your bathroom.
Uh, yeah, sure.
Or wait, that was a strength save.
One second, that was the wrong thing.
There, ten.
I mean, we can just subtract from that.
Alright, cool.
Yeah, that's enough.
I mean, you can carry it, okay.
Ten is fine.
I think anything lower than that.
Like, you know how much you can carry.
Um, uh, yeah, sure.
If you want to go to the bathroom, it's just go around the corner there and up the stairs
and you'll find it.
Okay, I'm going to go there.
Okay, good.
Yeah, so now the robot.
She can't see me winking.
No, Patrick does a large wink and it actually makes a cartoonish wink sound in real life
when he winks at her.
Yeah, she is just sort of skeeved more than anything.
I'm gonna use my time in the bathroom to investigate some clues.
For sure.
You can roll an investigation check.
Okay, let's see.
Oh no, I have a negative one.
You're sort of like the resident detective here, really.
Oh, I got a seven.
Except for that terrible roll, I guess.
Yeah, so you see some toilet paper and some good housekeeping magazines, but nothing really
that intriguing about the bathroom.
You notice that the decor is like kind of chintzy, like it's not that, it's kind of a little
bit tacky.
That's mostly what you notice.
I'd like to investigate the toilet paper roll.
Yeah, do it, do it.
How many ply?
You notice that the toilet paper roll is made of like double, like double layered, like rich
cotton toilet paper.
Like it's probably like three dollars a square.
like this is rich.
Yeah, this is insane.
It's insane money.
- You mean she didn't tip me off?
- Yeah, no, but this is good.
- The toilet paper does.
- Yeah, and you also, you look a little closer
and you notice that it says,
yeah, it says #abolishice on all the squares.
- Whoa.
(laughing)
This really is Sean McElwee's house.
- All right, am I downstairs with her still?
- Yeah, you are.
- Okay, I feel like we should ask her some questions.
- Yeah.
You know?
Yeah, she's...
Yeah, she's uh...
Yeah, she says, "Yeah, please, uh, I guess ask away."
Tell me about your husband.
How... how tall was he?
Uh, he was like 5'3".
Am I more or less attractive than him?
He is 5'3", I should say.
I... I think he's still alive.
Um...
Well...
I mean, he was pretty ugly, but like...
Agree to disagree.
You...
[laughs]
Well, why...
Why do you think he's dead?
Like, have you learned anything?
Um, it's called a hunch. It's huge in detective work.
Yeah, she sort of looks downcast at that. She's like, you know, like, honestly, like, he was just like so wrapped up in his activism all the time, you know, it was hard to sometimes to talk with him, you know, he always had cheeto dust on his fingers wherever he went.
we
check I guess. Okay. Uh. Terrible. This sucks. Fuckin' hate this game. Do it, do it. Tell
me about the zex now, bitch! Uh, it was like, like when it was good it was good, but most
of the time he would just sort of lay there and just be on his phone. You know, he ran
data for pogress so it was like a big deal. That's P-A-W-G-R-E-S-S. Pogress. Thank you.
Uh, cut thank god oh my god have you seen those ones that aren't? They look crazy.
Not a fan of uncut, hmm? I mean, you know, whatever. I take out a notepad and I write that down.
in a in a blue's clues notepad. I take out an L.A. Noire legal patent and I start drawing
a picture of an uncut penis. Yeah. Does it, ma'am, does it look anything like this? I
grab his notepad and show it to her. Nope, I said it was cut, so. Sheesh. While this
is going on I I have gone to other parts of the house I'm I'm in I'm in the I'm
in the bedroom now okay cool yeah you're in the bedroom um yeah it's uh it's it
smells awful this is clearly Sean's room there's just underwear covered in shit
everywhere huge tubs of cheese balls
wait hold on are you alleging Sean McElwee shits his pants?
no Sean McElwee the gun city character does all kinds of things
it's a gun city character it's a gun city character
yeah i don't know anybody named Sean McElwee and i wouldn't pretend to
there's no guy no i mean maybe probably but like not anyone i know
I thought it was just a good name.
[Laughter]
Yes!
Ahooga!
Cam's got the heater on him tonight.
So yeah, there's huge
huge tubs of cheese balls scattered on the floor.
The computer has, uh,
the computer looks like one of those keyboards
that, like, Joyce Carol Oates had.
You know, when they get all the fucked up shit in them.
Um, and he has a huge board
on his wall with red string
running along, connecting it to pictures of AOC
and Ilan Omar, people like that. And it says in big writing over it says I will
pretend to have ideals until it is inconvenient. So yeah you can sort of
do whatever you want now when you're in the room. So I'm just gonna do some
general investigating and then I'll get into the hard stuff. Okay cool. So I
rolled a six on investigation. So yeah with that six I mean you know you get
it the poopy smell is happening you know you sort of notice that there's just a
lot of shit in the way of anything out like you can't there's like just too
much stuff in the way for you to really get a sense of what the layout of this
room is or what is even in it basically do I have a yeah wait can we eating
ability do you know what would you ever I was just checking I wanted to see if I
I had an ability to eat poop.
Can we cut back?
I want to ask her a question.
Yeah, sure.
We can cut back while Patrick's still navigating the room, figuring out what to do about it.
Navigating bodies in space.
Of course, absolutely.
So I say, "You said you think he's still alive.
Any idea where he could have gone?"
And then immediately before she answers, I say, "I have to go help Patrick in the bathroom."
And I go upstairs to the bathroom.
we like to call that metagaming folks but yeah let me let me get let me get my
bearings I'm in Sean's room with her and they're in the bathroom no no you're
downstairs Sean's room okay you two are in Sean's room now yeah you guys are in
like yeah Caleb and and Haseeky Tsunay are in like I left you alone together
yeah okay you guys are in like the like you know parlor right like where you like
greet guests there's like bear rugs and shit in the mud room yeah right yes yeah
yeah so Kate Cameron asked that question or I just blow toss asked that question
and she and she she sort of says like I mean I don't know like he would always
I always go into the Matrix 2 for a little while.
We go to clubs a lot of the time.
Like he just stopped paying attention, I feel like, at home.
You know, I was doing a lot of sex work,
like really important sex work,
and like, he just like stopped caring, it felt like, you know?
- You said sex work.
Can you speak on that for a little bit?
- Yeah, sure, I just sort of like show a little bit of skin
and then--
- Can you give an example?
Can you show an example?
Alright, so while that's going on, Cameron and I are investigating.
Trying so hard to figure out how to respond.
Alright, so...
Yeah, we'll give you time to figure that out.
I have something already.
Alright, I say, Patrick, Patrick Yoda, you grab one side of that mattress and I'll grab the other.
Let's flip it over and see if there's anything underneath it.
Okay.
Okay, let's do that!
Yeah, you guys don't need to roll for that. You guys just flip over the mattress.
And which is a good instinct. It's a Casper mattress, it's very light.
It's a purple mattress. It's a purple Casper mattress collaboration.
Oh, well, most companies have sort of combined at this point. So yes, it is a purple Casper.
So purple and Casper are together. So yeah, you flip it over, which was a good instinct,
Because you see a some sort of like looks like a cyber diary
um underneath the mattress
If we find this under the mattress, let's flip over the dresser and the rest of the furniture too
before I can open the diary
Yeah, okay. You guys flip over all the other furniture in the room and just make a fucking mess
Um, and uh, yeah you find you find like more shit covered underwear
Well, I guess my hunch was wrong that time around.
Well, we still need to look through the closet.
Yeah, yeah, go into the closet.
Can we cut back to the mudroom?
Yeah, sure, we'll cut back.
The foyer?
Cut back to the mudroom.
Yeah, yeah, the foyer.
I just asked how, for an example.
Yeah, you just sort of asked this woman to show her ass.
So she, this V-girl.
Or anything else, do.
She's not really real, though.
Anyway, she's just ones and zeros.
She says, "Well, I guess you can check out my OnlyFans if you want to. It's like 3,000 tokens."
"Do you have a code? Do you have a promotional code I can use?"
"Yeah, for sure. I have the AbolishICE promotional code you can use."
"Well, good thing I'm a computer."
"I say this from upstairs."
stairs. How many times do you have to spell out abolish ice? You have to, and she yells
back up, you have to spell it out like 120 times. Okay, so since I'm a computer I do that.
Is that a hashtag? Uh, no, you don't need the hashtag, just slur it and like clump the words
together. She says that louder I guess than I do.
I do that in my computer self immediately and then I just do this. Oh, oh nice. Oh yeah,
super cool. Yeah I guess remove 50 dollars from your inventory.
Okay, wait, alright.
Okay, so now I'm at 50 and now I go, uh, here wait, no, cut to them, I'll save this.
I'm just trying to distract her.
Cut back upstairs, me and Patrick are ripping the wallpaper off the walls and tearing up
all the carpets.
Okay, it's just the diary.
I haven't touched the diary.
The diary is just sitting there.
I am, the diary is sitting there, you're destroying this room.
Now it's the darnest thing!
I just don't understand!
Why can't we find any more clues?
He found pictures of Carmen Electra behind there, but he was hiding.
Nice.
Yeah, dude.
Okay, I say, maybe there are clues written on the walls in invisible ink that we need fire to reveal.
Wait, wait, here.
(laughter)
- Ah well, that's a good idea.
- Okay, okay wait I run downstairs to ask
(laughter)
Hussie, what is her name, Hussie Kitsune for a match.
- Okay yeah, what, yeah one second let me go get one.
What are you doing up there?
And she goes, oh it's a bit close.
- Okay, okay, okay, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, to distract her, to distract her,
I eject a CD from my CD slot and I say, "What do you think of this?
Want to do anything with this?"
What's the CD?
Uh, James Blake's CD.
Oh, I love him!
He's dating that annoying woman!
Wow.
How about you touch it?
Uh, I guess roll a persuasion check?
That's right.
This is rough, man.
21.
I'm gonna I'm gonna all right yeah she goes up and she sort of like like sort
of gently like poke the hole in the middle and just go sort of embarrassed
all right and then I look to I look to blowtoss and I say I bought you some
time go. Okay so I look at I have the match do I have I did I take get the
match? Yeah you got the match man you got it you got it from her. I ask her before I
look at her and I ask her we don't really know where to begin with this
where should we even go to look for him what were some of his favorite haunts and
also what was his favorite color and then before she answers any of those
questions I run back upstairs with the match. Oh he liked to go to the Mommy
Good Legs Club a lot um that's one of the places he liked to go and I guess he's
gone but his favorite color was teal? Is, is teal. I'm trying to say is. I promise you I'm
writing all this down now focus on the hole in the middle of the ZD. Okay he's
focusing on the hole what are you guys doing upstairs? I hand the match to Patrick.
I have already just like ripped the bed in half.
Okay, let me just see if like the robot notices this is happening at this point.
Because this is just too much activity for me to not just check to see if the robot notices.
I mean we are going absolutely thing one thing two.
He absolutely does not notice.
He is the worst robot ever.
You know.
Nice.
God damn.
The rolls I'm getting.
Yeah, so keep going I guess.
What do you guys keep doing?
Alright, so we have the match.
Yeah, I hand it to Patrick and I say, "Do your Yoda magic."
Okay.
So, I've, uh...
Are you gonna light the match or are you gonna do some Yoda magic?
Um...
Huh.
Well, would lighting the match be Yoda magic, is the question.
It was just a figure of speech, okay?
I just meant light the match.
well that you used if you used a force you will be able to cast lightning at
will
lightning striking in the house then I'm going to use the force okay yeah that's
five technic line points but when you use the force Patrick Yodic used to force
for one minute giving him an extreme boost in combat ability and skills. Based on a wisdom
DC check as determined by the DM, Patrick Yoda can move objects, people, and more. As a passive
ability, Patrick gets advantage on all saving throws, can levitate at will, and is able
to shoot lightning out of his hands, dealing 2d8 lightning damage as a bonus action.
So basically what this means is you are now levitating in her room with a match in your
hand do you shoot lightning at the match to light it on fire or do you just shoot
lightning at the wall? I'm shooting lightning all over the house.
If it hits the match it's coincidental but it does hit.
Okay yeah you're shooting lightning everywhere the sound is reverberating
through the house. It's like going absolutely crazy. At this point Hasek
Kitsune is like oh my god what's going on and she runs upstairs to see what's
going on and she sees a floating... she sees... do you have a grappling hook?
Do I have one? No, nevermind, continue.
She runs upstairs to see what's going on, you're just shooting up the fucking room with
lightning and she's like "uh okay is there anything I could do to help you
guys in here? What are you doing to a A'Shaun's room?"
We're looking for clues!
Uh, no, we are, um...
Huh.
Meanwhile, I'm downstairs ejecting and then putting back in a CD over and over again.
He's going, "Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah."
Yeah, you destroy...
We are just kind of... I'm sneezing.
Yeah, I guess roll a deception check.
That's okay.
On that.
That's gotta be disadvantage that lightning is...
Yeah, it's, I mean, I wasn't even gonna, but yeah, it should be.
No.
Okay.
I got a 10.
No, but it was gonna be a crit.
Here let me see.
Let me see how she does on, on believing you.
I mean...
It was gonna be a 22 until Cam mentioned...
Yeah, Cam, this is all your fault.
She believes you.
She's like, "Oh, yeah, I guess I've heard that you guys sneeze like this."
"You? What do you mean, 'you guys'?"
*laughter*
"Excuse me?"
"I'm so sorry, oh my god, that was so..."
"You better leave right now and let us investigate!"
"So unwoke of me, I'm so sorry."
And she walks out, she's like so fucking embarrassed.
She's like blushing, anime blushing, all over.
like she's a v-girl so like her fucking like body is like like shifting in and
out it's like almost fading out because she's so fucking flustered by it and she
walks away sort of totally embarrassed she comes back down and I'm smoking a
cigarette I say thank God I was I was it for you
uh... and before she has a chance to answer
that uh...
you hear uh... the taco doorbell
ring once again, bong
and the rob, the robot goes up to the door
and opens it
and out walks
a man
that looks like some kind of
fat cricket
or something and he's got uh... slicked his antenna or slicked back he's wearing a
pinstripe suit and you would recognize this man anywhere he is none other than
poppy chuko of poppy chuko's techno slime oh shit whoa and hussy hussy says uncle
poppy and and she runs up and gives him a hug and he says this way little girl is
me uncle papi I'm here who are these fellas they're the detectives who are
investigating well this is one of them at least he's smoking a cigarette inside
her house what's up bro oh it's nice to meet you you know it's good it's good
that you guys are here where the others I heard that there was more than this time
both of them are in the bathroom yeah cut cut to upstairs the room is just
completely destroyed there's it's you can see like the underneath the paint on
the wall it's all been stripped down the bed is ripped in half all the furniture
splinters and there's just in the middle the diary is is lying in the middle
like yes absolutely I guess that was the only clue after all and I pick it up
put it in my way way way before you before you open it I run upstairs I
don't open it I put it in my backpack all right before you pick it up I run
upstairs and I look at you guys and I say have you checked the floorboards and
And then I run back downstairs.
(laughter)
Oh, great idea!
I guess we have to now.
You guys start ripping up the floorboards.
(laughter)
Papi Chuko looks to you,
Ray William Johnson,
as you come back downstairs.
And he says...
At this point, Haseki Tsune has gone away.
She's been dismissed by Papi Chuko.
And he says,
"Look, I'm very thankful you guys are here.
I wanted to make sure that Hussie had somebody who was looking into this case.
We're all very upset about Sean.
He was a good guy.
I didn't always agree with him, but he took care of her.
She's my niece. What can I say?
When you say you didn't always agree with him, what do you mean?
You know, he just abolished this, abolished that.
I'm not in the business of abolishing anything. Let's put it that way, okay?
What, what kind of business are you in?
Oh my buddy, you know, I can see you got the glow behind your eyes.
I'm in the techno slime business, you know?
We try not to abolish or regulate anything in techno slime.
It's just not, uh, it's just not ideal. Let's put it that way, okay?
Okay, Chachi?
Okay, is there any way that I can get him to charge me like seventy dollars for a gram?
Of techno slime?
Yeah, you can try.
You can, uh, you can...
When I, when I hear the word "technoslime" from upstairs really faintly, I run down, I
start prepping up the floorboards and I run downstairs.
Okay.
I'm committed to my detective work though.
I know, I know that it would be a fun 20 minutes, but I'm committed to my detective work.
*laughs*
Okay, so you run downstairs, he's like "whoa, whoa, who's this guy over here?"
He's cool, he's cool.
I was in the bathroom.
Oh, I guess who is right?
He parties.
Oh, okay, that's cool.
No, I mean, hey, that's good to know.
But look, I'm, look, fellas, you know, I'm not into the small time dealing, okay?
I let other people do that.
Let's put it that way, okay?
Are you holding?
No, not on me.
Come on, I'm a CEO.
Oh my god, you suck.
Oh my god you suck bro.
I go back upstairs.
Stop it.
I don't suck. Come on.
Hey I think you suck.
Ok look fellas.
I'm being very generous with you right now.
I'm not gonna ask who I am.
I'm not gonna shout who are you.
When you're all the way up there.
Oh ok. I was worried you would think he was just very small.
But yeah he's upstairs.
I'm not that small!
Okay, I mean, yeah, I haven't seen you yet, so I believe you.
He's definitely small, don't listen.
I'm not, hey, I'm not Yoda, but I'm not that small.
He's like three feet tall.
That's fine. Normal height.
That's not fine. Not normal.
It's a pretty good height to be if you're a Yoda.
What, did you think like a tall Yoda would look normal?
I'm saying it's all downstairs.
I mean now that I'm thinking about it, I thought Yoda would be pretty weird looking.
I gotta say.
Yeah, you would hate it.
I wouldn't hate it, you know, I don't hate anybody, okay?
Let's put it that way.
When, okay, we're getting off topic.
When was the last time you saw Sean?
Sean?
Ugh.
Well, I mean, last time I saw him he was in here, he was ranting and raving about abolished
cocks, you know?
I didn't even know what the hell he was talking about at that point.
Abolished what?
Patrick Cullum.
Abolish Cox!
Say it again!
Cox?
Cox!
C-O-K-C
S
I think you spelled it wrong!
Hold on!
He pulls out a tiny dictionary
Ok yeah, no I see now
what I did wrong, ok, I got it
I got it.
But you know what I said though right?
I said Cox?
I think I get it.
Ok good.
Who is this guy?
What the hell is his deal?
I'm Patrick Yoda!
How did you hear that?
I got huge ears!
Like a Yoda!
Hey you know what?
Let's do this.
Roll perception check to see if you can hear.
Hear shit like that.
Ok.
Um where?
I'm Patrick Yoda.
Oh wait I still have disadvantage on hold on.
Just take, yeah you can just take the 15 but um.
Oh yeah I'll take the 15.
Oh whoops.
Okay wait wait wait.
Try again.
Oh there we go.
Fuck alright.
Yeah I guess you could just hear shit with your big ass Yoda ears.
Let's put it that way.
Okay well while this whole conversation is going on I'm ripping up floorboards in the
the bedroom and I rip up a floorboard that causes the floor to collapse and we fall down
next to Papi Chuko.
So we're all downstairs now.
Well, I heard you, now I can see you.
Alright, let me just roll some damage for you guys.
What?
On that, because you just fell.
I can hover though.
Oh yeah, you don't take any damage.
Cameron, you take one damage, you're fine.
Okay.
Either way, I'm going to roll damage.
I'm going to roll damage.
and you take you take one damage you're fine okay easy fall for you yes you guys
land in the hallway probably whoa whoa whoa okay all right fellas now I want
you guys to try to find Sean for my girl here okay she's a good she's a good lady
she doesn't know much but she's she's good so I don't know try to look around
around
the name of the bar or whatever that she...
Mommy Goodlegs.
Okay.
Mommy Goodlegs?
Yeah, he'd go there every once in a while.
He was...
Look, he was cheating on her.
Let's put it that way, alright?
Whoa!
Oh!
I would never do that.
Hold on.
You're telling me the woman with the OnlyFans was cheating on her boyfriend?
No, that's not...
no it's not what I said it's the other way around yeah wait you're telling me
the man with the girlfriend with the only man what was cheating on her yeah that
was what was I mean what's a look with me that's I don't know with or I mean
with any friggin girl was around in a club like that okay not any girl I mean
You know, he was the anaconda.
What was he into?
Sure.
Tell me, he loved big bitches.
Yeah, he fucking loved them, you know.
Let's put it that way, okay?
That's what I thought. My man.
Hey, he's no man of mine. Just make sure he's safe, okay?
safe okay. Alright, I grab Papi Chuko by his collar and I kick him, I literally kick him
off the property. Okay, I guess I'll just. I need you to roll the DJ Jazzy Jeff check.
He's like, "Oh, whoa, okay, all right, all right, all right, okay, I know what I'm not
wanting."
He sort of starts to waddle away, the giant grasshopper he is.
So yeah, what do you guys want to do now?
I kind of got some of the intel.
You have the diary too.
I say we go to Mommy Legs, the Mommy Legs place.
You want to try that again, big shot?
I say we go to the Mommy Legs place.
Good enough.
Yeah.
All right, I agree.
So you guys head outside I guess and you see Sullivan's waiting in the car.
He sort of already gave up on...
Oh that's where you went Sullivan.
I was worried about you.
Yeah I saw that you guys had sort of a DIY style so I just didn't want to interrupt.
Did you see the lightning Sullivan?
It was awesome.
Yeah that was really cool.
I got a little scared I'm not going to lie.
But I thought it was pretty cool.
Why'd you get scared you bitch?
Oh, oh, oh, okay, I mean just 'cause lightnings.
I'm sorry.
No, I gotta toughen up, you're right.
I gotta toughen up.
I'm gonna flick your belly with my fingers so you toughen up.
Oh, please, please don't flick my belly.
Sullivan, we need you to-- Don't touch him.
He has a poisonous coating on his entire body.
I'm immune to it.
It's like a child.
Yeah, I'm immune to that.
Sullivan, we need you, we need you to drive us to the Momleg store.
for
like
book you'd probably like something lame like that Sullivan and I throw the diary
to him okay yeah he says huh that's interesting he huh hmm and he puts it
inside a like like a it's like a cyber diary right so he is observing it and
he's like hmm it's interesting all the logs seem to be deleted after hmm hold
And he puts it in. This is the last entry.
And you guys hear this play over the car speakers as you start to drive out of the fucking place you're at.
"Dear Diary, Another day in early retirement after selling data for progress to Stakem's Federation of Bodies and Spaces.
I'm glad I spent all those years posting, making people think I had convictions when really I just had ambitions.
like a tumorous slug sucking shit through a straw. I don't think that analogy applies,
but it's the only thing that comes to mind when I think of myself, me, Sean McElwee,
resident of Gunn City in the year 2245. However, I've been bored lately. There's only so much
child porn- I mean, Karl Marx books, I can masturbate to. And my dutiful wife, as sweet
in
This is almost two months ago.
He just stopped
Just stop recording his own thoughts. It's probably good for the world, but hmm
The sulvin ejects it and hands it back to you blow toss
All right. Okay. I put it back in my backpack
I take it out of the backpack
Sullivan drives the three of you down the long driveway out from the mansion back into mr
the hands of boulevard. As you cruise down into the Lockheed Martin Plaza, you veer down
a narrower, seedier alley where it perpetually rains. At the end of the alley, you see a
giant pair of legs spread open with a door in between them. Mommy Good Legs Club. I would
like to take a moment to apologize to all the women in my life, I know my irony will
not be enough for many of you. You walk into the club and you're flushed with intense red
lights. In some corners the lights are bluer and in another corner it's more black and white.
You can sort of pick your noir vibe. To your right you see a long bar and a stage where
performers, all Goyles with gams, with the backing band from Mos Eisley performing with
the ass cheeks on their foreheads. A few regulars crowd the stage and a stag group of some kind
occupies a corner hooting and hollering at the Goyles saying things like "D" in crumpets
or whatever British people say.
Some V folks, and that's with an X of course, wait staff are flying around serving people
drinks, giving people sly winks and cooing.
You know, how they do that to get tips, because that's what they have to do.
At the last song comes to a close, a cool cat takes the stage.
Thank you Mos Eisley Band and Girl.
Weren't they great folks, and that's with an X of course.
In case you don't remember, I'm your host for the evening, the Fucker.
And I'm pleased to announce, and is that a cool cat?
That it's finally time for the star of the show, the head babe in charge, the foxiest
gal in gun city.
She turns boys into men, men into women, women into non-binary people, and non-binary people
back into boys due to a curse put on her long ago.
It's Mommy Good Legs!
Rawr!
Cause I'm a cat.
And out comes the most beautiful woman you've ever seen.
In fact she looks exactly like whatever you find to be most beautiful.
Which is... what exactly?
Oh my god, Lisa Ann, Nalen Palin.
Oh my god.
Each of you.
I'm trying to think.
Hell yeah.
Oh wow, oh my god, she looks exactly like my beautiful wife.
Wow, this is truly the coincidence for the ages.
That's incredible.
But to blowtoss she looks like the sexy hoo-hoo bitch from the Grinch.
You're thinking of Cindy Lou Who because you're also thinking of her.
No, no, no.
The one that marries the girl.
Cameron, you're thinking of the child.
Oh no, the one with the big tits who shoots the lightbulb gun?
Yeah, you know who I'm talking about.
The scene in the Grinch where she shoots a gun that only exists to make her tits shake.
That's cool that you have that on hand as a memory.
Yeah, I've an entire movie memory banked. Why I'm googling lightbulb gun big tit Grinch
Christine Baranski, okay
Sexy who the Grinch there's a photo of the Grinch drinking milk holding a rose with a Santa hat on his penis. I
See that I see that picture I
I see, I see, um, I see yaddle.
Yeah.
But, yaddle is, um, just like a full, like a...
Like, six foot tall.
Amazonian yaddle.
And a dominatrix apple.
Yeah.
So, Mommy Good Legs, who looks like a combination of a six-foot yaddle,
a, uh,
uh, that who, uh,
that who girl who's shit with the big titties you shouldn't like old gun i
think is what i heard
and uh... lisa and in the old hill and
uh... to whatever you whatever you want to see it's a mommy good legs looks like
uh... she starts singing a uh... jazzy
uh... rendition of break stuff by lindt biscuit
uh...
it's uh...
it's a it's it's it's a stirring number
uh... everyone's holding in trance by her
um... so
you guys want to look around the bar
now would be the time
uh... i pull out my binoculars and i just keep looking at her
i go up to the bartender and i ask
you know a guy named sean
yeah the bartender who is a uh... i go to the bathroom
no so he's going to... patrick you're going to the bathroom the bathroom
actually has this like blue like glowing light coming out of it as you're going
towards it and when you walk in you notice that there is a a bunch of like
fucking weird. There's a touch tunes in the bathroom.
There's a touch tunes. But there's also...
Wait, there really is a touch tunes? No, it wasn't what I was gonna put in there.
No, there is a touch tunes and I walk up to it and I pay
three of my quarters and I play
Toby Keith beer for my horses
So I have the I have the app I have the app and I keep
Skipping all of Caleb's plays
And I keep playing closing. I keep playing closing time to get people out of the bar so we can investigate
Yeah, this only plays in the bathroom. So you're just trying to get
So I'm playing it but it's only playing in the bathroom. So everyone leaves the bathroom
Yeah, the only person who stays in the bathroom as you're playing it.
So these blue lights that were flashing were techno-slime light drugs.
So it's like you shoot this light into your eye, using a Men in Black light,
and it makes you see those spots that everybody loves, and you get fuckin' high off that.
And the only guy left in there is a anthropomorphic Tommy gun named Gavin Shit.
And he's just, he looks sort of like Clippy, but he's a Tommy gun.
And he's like, "What are you doing?
Why are you driving out my customers?
I was trying to sell them the techno slime stuff!"
"Well, Gavin, I'm an investigator, you see."
"Well, I don't want to deal with any coppers around here, okay?
I have no interest in that!"
Well, I gotta go to the bathroom.
Okay, fine. Just go to the bathroom then.
But don't stop scaring my customers out with your closing time.
People hate that song.
I like that song.
I like it more than you, I feel, because you're the one who wants to tell me to shut it off.
I don't, I, no, no, no.
I don't dislike that song.
I dislike seeing my customers leave.
They hear closing time, they go, "Oh, I guess I gotta go home."
And that's the problem, because they need to sell them stuff.
Well, that's their fault. I don't care
That's a bad fault, but it's my problem
That's the worst part about playing music in a bar is you play dance with the devil in a bar and everybody thinks they have to
Have sex with their mom
People just follow the orders of the song
God well I
Didn't do anything wrong, so I don't know why you're yelling at me
Okay, so cut cut back. Can we cut back to the bartender?
Me and Ray William Johnson walk up to the bartender and we simultaneously say, "You got no guy
named Sean."
"You got no guy named Sean."
"Look, I don't know anybody named Sean, okay?
I mean, well, Sean McAleese, who you mean?"
"That's his name is Sean."
"Yeah, I mean, he's a big deal.
What can I say?
Nothing to say about that except that he's a huge deal.
I haven't seen him around here in a while if that's what you want to know.
I heard he used to come here to cheat on his V-girlfriend.
Well, look, I'm not trying to say I know what he did or didn't do, okay?
But yeah, I mean, let's put it that way.
You are so confusing.
Can you please just say it's true or not true?
I just don't look, alright?
I'm a worm, alright?
There's enough I gotta deal with being a worm.
Quit bragging.
No, that's...
Well, thank you, but no.
When people see a worm they think, "Oh, he's a worm."
You know, I'm trying not to throw my patrons under the bus, okay?
Let's put it that way.
So you threw Sean under a bus?
No.
And you killed him?
No, I did not do that.
We have the confession.
Well, well, we heard the news.
No, no.
Book him, boys.
All right, we attempt to arrest Jamal the worm.
Okay, yeah, roll a strength check then.
I got a 23.
Yeah, you guys killed him.
I got a 19.
Wow.
Okay, cool.
Yeah, that's...
I'm arresting Jamal Da Worm.
Are we allowed to do that as detectives?
Can detect...
No, not really.
So we'll try to...
Just sit and try to rest.
We'll try to resolve that.
You can detain, as a private detective, you can technically detain somebody until officers arrive onto the scene.
We don't call the cops.
You're just arresting this bartender.
Yeah.
We just arrest him, we just kinda, we just like sit on him.
Yeah?
Yeah, so he can't go anywhere.
Yeah, so you sit on Jamal the worm and he's like, "Yo guys, fellas, please stop!
Stop!
I didn't do nothing wrong!"
Um, and I- You're comfortable.
Yeah, you're squishy.
I guess thank you, I don't know.
uh... and then uh... i want to go i want to go talk to uh...
mommy legs
here i'll just a year sitting on jim all
yes so she's finishing up the uh...
she's a she's finishing up a break so break stuff
the jazz standard version
and uh... the crowd is a roughing
over it
uh... yeah she sort of as she has a moment between between tracks so if you
want to
to get up but get up in their talk three bird
uh...
so yeah i uh... i pushed it out for a while
so i'm rolling pipe like one eighty two
i think that this case
right at adams on
play sorry do you take requests
in the uh... felt
we say go ahead
she was just gonna say fellas fellas please please calm down
yeah i a m i get up on stage with her if this is just in between songs right this
is not the end of her set
now it's not the end of the idea i get up on stage and i'd
tried a i'd try to uh... whisper into her ear
uh... but i'm also i'm standing right next to the microphone so everybody
I'm going to get the entire venue, you can hear it.
And I say, "Um, this guy named Sean McElwee just disappeared.
And do you know anything about that?
Also do you want to go on a date with me?
You're so hot and you look like the Who woman from that movie.
Do you've seen the movie with the Who woman?"
She puts her hand over your mouth and says, "Okay everyone, we're going to take five.
One second."
And she turns to you and she says, "Okay, can we just talk about this after the set?
I'm happy to tell you anything you need to know about Sean, okay?"
"Well, how long is the set?"
"It's like a few more songs."
"That's so long.
Can we- can you just end it early?"
"How long are the songs?"
"What?
What did he say?"
"What was that?"
"How long are the songs?"
"It's like three and a half minutes, you know?"
"Each?"
"Yeah, each one.
And it's like three or four more songs."
three or four more songs. I thought you were saying it was three and a half minutes for all the songs.
Yeah that would be fine if it was a three and a half minute set that would be fine. How about
you do one more song and then we'll talk. Roller persuasion check. Okay um that's an eight.
Yeah um yeah she's like she's she's like no I'm gonna I'm gonna do like three more songs. Okay
but what if I gave you this entire backpack full of snacks?
I guess role persuasion with disadvantage because you already tried but but that's that's worthy of a check. Okay
um
It's a one
She's like I don't I don't eat
what is that one of those is just
It looks like the the the cosmic brownies, but it looks like they're made of poop. I don't want any of this
Just just just please just three more songs they'll all be i'll make them two minute songs
I want to help you guys. One minute.
[laughter]
He's telling friends. Is he sitting on the bartender?
You have, uh... Get off of Jamal!
You have one minute for three songs. Please get off of Jamal.
20 seconds each on average.
Go. Please get off Jamal.
I want to hear the songs before he gets off of him!
Do you see him? Do you see how he
handcuffed his worm?
We handcuffed his head to his tail?
You're next. [laughter]
Unless you play one
minute of songs. I guess roll an intimidation
check on that. I'm about to fuck this bitch up. Let's go. I think you have very good intimidation.
20. You're a demon. Alright, let me see if she can, let me see if she can uh... Yeah,
no, she's not. She's intimidated. She lost. She's very intimidated. Uh, she's like, "Okay,
okay, okay, okay, okay. I'm gonna play one more song, okay? It's gonna be Blood Vision
by Jay Retard and it'll be done in a second, okay?
Jay what?
Can you say that again?
Can you do a clean take on that second word?
I don't think so.
Oh okay, just play it then.
Okay yeah, she does a jazz standard of blood visions.
I don't leave the stage, I'm standing right next to her the whole time.
Okay.
Cameron's on the stage and he's just hitting one note on a synth.
Okay, awesome. That's awesome, dude. What note are you hitting?
C1. Very low. Very low note.
C1? Yeah, it's insanely low.
Yeah, so there's just like, you're playing...
She's playing a...
[Laughter]
So yeah, she's playing her song and uh, and uh, she's playing her one last song and there's
just a brownout playing.
Everybody, uh, uh, Patrick and uh, Caleb, roll a constitution saving throw to see if
you shit your pants.
Yeah, I got nine.
Yeah, Patrick Yoda, you destroy your fucking Yoda ride.
I'm not, I'm not shitting, I'm in the bathroom so I'm on the toilet already.
Oh, yeah, you're on the toilet?
Yeah.
Okay, alright, so yeah, it all goes into the toilet actually, and uh, but it fills up the
toilet.
a little bit of it on your butt as you waddle out.
Yeah, alright?
How do you like that?
I give you some poopy.
I don't like it.
Alright, you don't like it?
I'm sorry then.
Yeah, Caleb, you're fine, man.
You're just so- Thank God for Jamal, because you're sitting right on top of him.
Yes!
So that would've- Yeah, that would've been brutal.
Okay, I voluntarily shit my pants.
Just to fuck him up.
Yeah, so you- You're just like, "I don't know, man.
It must have been the brown note.
Yeah, roll deception check to see if he believes it's the brown note that did that.
Uh...
Twelve.
Okay, let me see if he believes that.
He's pretty good at telling when people are deceiving him.
No, he is a worm.
No, he's a bartender.
No, he's a worm.
He's like, "Dude, I know that you just shit on my head.
I am not fucking stupid.
I know you just shit on me on purpose."
It was the music.
Bro, that is only a brown note.
That is a brown note for Yodas.
Uh, sorry.
Music make me lose control.
[Laughter]
He's like, "Okay, yeah, I mean, it's a good song and everything, but you just shit on my fucking head. Oh my god, dude."
"Stay here, I have to-"
"It smells like, it smells like fucking, like asbestos. I'm so confused."
"I'm gonna pass out."
asbestos no i wasn't i no i eat normal stuff he can eat asbestos because he's got a demon
belly that's full of flames no bean burrito that makes a lot of sense to me patrick's poop smells
like poop because he was eating poop not true why are you always so far away yeah yeah she's
great hearing we've established this yes she's just she's just singing um uh live in la vida loca
while you guys are just arguing about but the version from the end of shrek 2
that's the one
uh yeah so she finishes she finishes the song and uh she uh uh uh turns to you blowtox and she says
okay fine just meet me in the back okay and we'll we'll talk about sean okay i'm gonna go
Go to your door and you're gonna get laid.
She heads to the back, there's like a door to the back and everybody's going crazy, they
love Mommy Good Legs, they love her club.
She goes to the back, she goes away.
So yeah.
Okay, I talk into the microphone and I say, "Hey, Ray William Johnson and Patrick Yoda,
come to the back, we're meeting up with Mommy Good Legs.
Wink, wink."
And I say, "Wink, wink" into the microphone too.
Okay, I'm a little busy in here still.
I had, I pooped so much from the brown note,
I had to go to a different stall just to wipe.
So, it's gonna be about,
gonna have to give me like two minutes maybe.
But again, I just wanted to make clear,
I was in the bathroom when it happened.
And none of it happened in my pants.
And, uh, have a good day.
You see everyone in the bar kind of go, "Oh, thank you, thank you.
Yeah, no, thanks man."
Yeah, so two minutes go by and he cleans himself up and you guys get out of there.
And you guys start going towards the door.
And that stag party that was hanging out by the stage, sort of gets in front of you guys.
"Oh, where are you guys going?"
"I'm not going to the bathroom!"
"You guys trying to go to talk to mommy good legs, huh?"
"Yeah, you try to talk to mommy good legs, you can't talk to mommy good legs, she's all,
yeah, she's all girl!"
"She asked me to talk to her, she wants me to talk to her in the back."
You know, talk to this in the back and one of them takes out brass knuckles.
You know, talking to mommy good legs.
Yeah, you know, talking to mommy good legs.
One of them's a boy.
I'm an orphan.
Um, I grabbed the kid.
Okay.
Yeah.
Roll an intimidation check for whatever you're about to do.
Because I know you're going to try to intimidate him.
Ten.
Okay.
Yeah, you don't scare me!
I'm gonna kick your frickin' arse!
I sit on him and I shit again.
Okay, uh, roll initiative then.
That's where we'll end it here.
That's real initiative.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[Music]