[Music]
Okay, so I'll give you guys a bit of a recap on last time on Gun City, the noir spectacular,
case of the missing activist. You guys are three detectives for the Top 10's
Tattletail Agency. You were hired sort of last minute because Lenny Krapschitz, the
head of the agency, retired basically 10 seconds before you guys got there. You
guys are now looking for the husband of a one Hasekitsune, a wealthy V girl.
So that's sort of like an E girl, but it's like a virtual girl. So they're sort
like they're static either not really don't really like they both exist in
this world and also in the virtual world which is called the matrix - and so
you're looking for her missing husband and she you guys went to her place up and
up on the spaz which is the sucka fucka auto erotica zone and you went to her
mansion which looks like princess peach's castle and you investigated and
looked around for to find some clues you chatted with her you also chatted with
her uncle a one techno slime tycoon Papi Chuko and from them you sort of gathered
that probably mommy good legs is like a good place to start to look for Sean
because he was a bit of a he's a bit of a sleazy guy despite being such a good
activist. And you also found Sean's cyber diary, which had like a, a, the last log was, was
recorded two months ago about thinking of maybe getting back into posting, which he loved
to do so much. After that, you guys arrived at the Mommy Good Legs club. You watched Mommy
perform a few numbers and Patrick went to the bathroom and talked to uh oh shoot I
gave him a name the gun the Tommy gun with eyes sort of looks like Clippy I
forgot what I called him I God let me find a note oh yeah his name like was
like Gavin shit and he yeah he was a Tommy gun with I with with like Clippy
looking eyes and he uh he was just talking about a kind of techno slime where you
sort of like shoot into your eye it wasn't it was just like a weird
conversation Caleb aka Ray William Johnson I should say beat the shit out
of a bartender and sat on him and and shat on him too pooped on him and
blow-toss piss using his like negative like charisma just went on the stage and
demanded that Mommy Goodlakes talk to him.
- I seduced her.
- Yeah, you seduced her by yelling at her
in front of everyone.
And then she said, "Okay, yes, after this last song, fine."
She did the last song, she went back into her,
like dressing room or whatever and said,
"Come meet me there."
And when you guys went to go try to meet with her,
you ran into, there was a stag party.
so much a gross brent's
who were just screaming and yelling and they said you can talk to his art girl
and uh...
people for mission
only a time uh... i'm so
so glad that you recapped all that design didn't remember any of the and now i was
a i i i i took diligent notes
we're ready to go
i'm sorry rumble
i'm ready to
ready to beat the shit out of some brits
Yeah, I'll set the stage. So, so yeah, so, so yeah, Caleb tried to intimidate them and one of them who's the the fiance and he's, he's like, yeah, I'm the fiance, you know, gonna intimidate me. And he said he wants to fight you. And so the fiance is there. He's got his stag mates, and he's got a little orphan boy also in his stag party. And they're sort of sizing up to fight you guys. And Caleb, you actually rolled the highest initiative. So you go first, I should say Ray William Johnson.
It looks like I rolled a two.
Hmm.
Not what I have in my notes.
Look at the feed.
Yeah, Cameron rolled a two.
Cameron rolled a two.
Oh, I get to go first?
Cameron rolled a 20.
No, that's not, no.
Cameron rolled a 20, I rolled a two.
No, I rolled a 16.
Yeah, wait.
Was it Cameron, not Caleb?
Oh yeah, that makes so much more sense.
I fucked this up. Let's re-roll.
Okay, no, you wanna re-roll?
No, I want my two.
you want to do you want to go last
i need my to
he has a special plans and going well i made my bed nice i'm sitting in it
okay i mean i got it right hey i got a wrong makes way more sense of the
camera we go first to see is how it works and i was go for a resume where
she is the entire decks
disease these tire initiatives for that's all i'm better
by i am
i'm more lucky than you at rolling eyes
uh... so there is this map here that we have a friend of us this is the
situation
Yeah, so for the viewers at home, I provided them a little, I think a fairly useful, just
battle map, just to try this out, see if this works to help give them a sense of space.
So each of those squares, and anybody who's familiar with Roll20 is going to love this
kind of audio, but each of those squares is considered 5 feet of space.
So if you need to sort of figure out where you are, or who you are in range of, you can
do that.
Does that mean that my body is 5 feet by 5 feet wide?
You're all basically just Roblox Minecraft Steves.
I wanna...
You guys actually aren't, but all the stag brits in front of you are cubes.
They are perfect cubes.
They look like soccer fans.
You know, the type.
Yeah.
Okay.
Can I get going?
Can I start my turn?
Absolutely.
Alright, so I want to run up to one of them here.
I'm just going to drag my little marker.
I want to run over here and I want to just hit him in the face with my lead pipe.
Absolutely.
Yeah, let me roll an attack here.
That's an eight.
Yeah, that's not going to do it.
In fact, it's a crit one, but plus your seven attack.
So you swing at the fiancé, but because of the love of his woman as he's trying to cheat
on her, it empowers him and allows him to sort of swiftly dodge away, and you actually stumble
and you end up in between all of them.
Oh no, oh no, I'm surrounded.
Yeah, you stumble in and you're surrounded by all the stag mates and the child, the British
orphan and so they're like yeah yeah we're gonna poke you in the dick with our British sticks and
they are uh you you do have an extra attack as your character so you can try that out.
I can try uh what out? Just an extra attack you have an extra attack. Yeah I'm gonna attack the
fiancee again because I do not give up. Yeah. I got a 26. Yeah that's a that's absolutely a hit
So just hit, hit, so what you do now, hit dual pipes inside the chat.
That's 17 damage.
Yeah, you, you bash the shit out of him.
So you fall on your ass in, in, in, in the middle of all of them,
and they're all laughing, they're all throwing their, their heads back,
you see their awful teeth.
No matter how many thousands of years in the future we go,
the British just never figure out dentistry.
And you just bash him right in the fucking teeth.
And he's just like, they're falling out,
they're making little piano key noises as they do.
uh... it's a great uh... you just like bashing him
uh...
and uh... you he's looking pretty fucked up he's looking like
way messed up
nice yesterday messed up to the ice yeah you be stood on him yeah
you would be small i want this is a good work brother
thanks you guys have to rest i'd you guys have to rescue me now because i'm
in the world uh... i don't know next or disc
caleb
no actually the stag party goes next on the
uh... no
yeah can we just get their turn
yeah
i don't know what they do
yeah i don't even to you just just put the damage on the i don't even want to
know
now you're gonna you're not here you're gonna have to find out so here's a
thing that the way the same for
what i think that the only me you can you make you can you be in the dungeon
i can't can you hear you right now
You can't hear me? Okay, well Caleb's a pedophile and he loves to have sex with boys.
Him and Bryan Singer love hanging out.
He's talking about his favorite movies directed by Bryan Singer.
Yeah, my favorite movie is called Caleb's a Pedophile and he's my best friend by Bryan Singer.
No, it's not a movie.
It's confirmed that Caleb can hear me and he's a liar and he's lying about not being friends with Bryan Singer.
No, I can't hear you. Okay. What are the stag party? So the stag party, so the
fiance takes out his brass wedding rings from all the marriages he's had and he
after getting bashed really hard by you, Blotas, he's gonna try to go in on
you so he's gonna he's gonna do a little attack roll. Let's see how he does.
Okay yeah so he does not hit so he barely misses though he just fucking starts
swinging he's swinging at you but you you manage to get out of the way.
I just under attack like the Matrix. Yeah no and everyone takes note of it in the club but
they're all just like damn that was a very that was a lot like the Matrix.
That was just like the Matrix. Yeah yeah and now the one guy one of
the stag mate number one is gonna come after you.
uh... he's gonna use uh... his his uh... laser knife to attack you
uh... let's see
yeah it's really bad.
yeah let's see how he does
he fucking just whiffs it
he uh... he tries to swing at you and he misses
yeah your your expert combat training as a grinch as a grinch detective is
coming into play here. I never I never stood up from my matrix duck I was still
just standing there completely still in the limbo and he didn't aim he aimed
where I would have been but I still done right it's like Dark Souls he couldn't
animation cancel so yeah yeah someone hey someone somewhere is a love in that
joke um okay and now the the stag guy number three and the boy are all gonna
attack you they're all just like all over your oh my god they're all just
that Cameron they're all over yeah because he's yeah cuz he's in the middle
to
number three guy who has he can only punch and so he started going like this
for the viewers at home I'm punching and he does six damage to you. No! All right
yeah type that in. What's your health at? 26. Oh you're good dude. Yeah don't forget
don't forget you have you also have your monkey too I forgot to mention. Oh yeah
your deputy detective. I forgot about my monkey. I always forget about my monkey.
Yeah he knows too. So the boy is gonna try to get you now. The boy has has just
his like stubby little orphan hands and so he's gonna try to whack you with
those. Yeah he fucks up. So he's just pathetic and nobody loves him so he tries
to slap at you and it doesn't work. So you get out of the way. That's what's up.
Now the last guy, he's gonna sort of peel away from that crowd and he's gonna go
after Patrick Yoda, who he sees as the smallest and therefore, so they're
all trying to feel big and strong. So he's gonna try to try to do some
kicks on your ass. Let's see how he does. So do I get to attack him now? Once
it's your turn, yeah. Oh my god. Yeah I know, it's pretty wild. Yeah. Yeah, but
What's your AC, man? Let's see.
- 13.
- Yeah, so he tries to swing at you.
He has a posh cane, and he tries to swing at you with it,
but he just totally overestimates 'cause you're a little dude
and he just goes right over you.
- Okay.
- Yeah, that's their turn.
I mean, that's all they can do.
So it is actually your turn, Patrick Yoda.
- Okay, cool.
So what I'm gonna do-
- Hell yeah.
- Is I'm gonna take...
So Cameron's surrounded by guys right now, which he loves.
He likes this.
- No.
- He loves to fight. - Absolutely not.
- He loves to fight.
- I like he does. - That's right.
- I do like to fight. - Yeah, that's what I was saying.
You love being surrounded by guys 'cause you love to fight.
- No, I like to fight one-on-one on or against guys.
- No.
- You like to be one-on-one with a guy.
- Yeah. - You like to fight.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- So what I'm gonna do, I'm going to use my hoverboard,
my hoverboard swing.
- Hell yeah.
and I'm gonna try and take out the three people
around Cameron up top.
- Okay, so the way you would do that then,
because, so your hoverboard can really only,
all right, so you just roll.
- My hoverboard boomerang?
- Yes, that's how you would do it, precisely.
- Yeah, I just got 18.
- Hell yeah, okay, cool.
So if you're trying to swing at the three guys in front,
that actually beats all their armor class.
So hit the hoverboard boomerang inside the chat.
- I got two.
- Wow, okay.
- God damn it.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
Oh yeah, so you swing the hoverboard
and it just like clocks all three of those guys
in the front for two damage.
But what is it, how does it work?
How do you throw it?
Describe it to me.
- So I kind of kick the back of my heels forward.
shit like this and then it goes around in a circle okay yeah so you do like a
little actually you know what you did you did you did so I want you to describe
your kill on the fiance because I just realized that Cameron beat the shit out
of fiance so bad that you did kill him just now okay so it kind of so it goes
around the three guys and then it just continues to spin on the fiance's head
until he gets CTE so bad that he dies. Okay yeah so he's like holding his head
and he's he's he's screaming "my mom warned me about this" and he just crumbles to the
floor, X's go over his eyes, Jollibee police come and take his body away and
throw it in the incinerator. But don't stop us from from fighting at all. No this
is population control. Gotcha. Yeah so yeah so he's gone so that was a sick move.
It is now your turn, Caleb.
Um, okay. So they're all grouped somewhat together, so I'm gonna use my grenade.
Oh, you're gonna use the sexual grenade.
I'm gonna use the sexual grenade. I don't think I've got the chance to use that yet.
Will that hit? Will that hit me?
I- God, I hope so.
Yeah, it will hit you.
No. Sorry, buddy.
No, you don't-
Sacrifice doesn't have to be made.
You don't use the sexual grenade.
I'm already using it as we speak, and there it goes.
Oh yeah that's definitely that definitely beats your armor class. That's a 20-foot
radius from point of explosion that's gonna hit everybody. No, I'm immune.
Depends, what's the point? What's the point of explosion? Oh, hit it in the
square in the back. Yeah, I throw it in the furthest square on the map. Can I mark that?
Okay, cool. Yeah, yeah, just like here basically? Yeah. Yeah, perfect.
Okay, so that hits. So basically you hit you throw it in the back it uh and 20 feet is four squares
so you get everybody in there uh yeah hit the sexual grenade damage now uh yeah so you throw
your your sexual grenade which is like a pulsing like like nut sack it looks like and when it lands
it explodes and like semen piping hot semen comes out of it and just splashes all over these guys
And actually describe your kill on the orphan boy.
You just killed an orphan boy with semen, dude.
With cum?
No, okay, I can't have that.
I jump in front- I say, "No, not like this."
And I jump in front of my own- No, say it in your voice.
"Not like this."
And then I jump in front of the- I cover him like a man jumping on a grenade.
You cover him, but not me?
But it's kind of the opposite.
No, dude, I don't give- You're not- No, we'll just wait, okay?
I got a plan here.
I cover him, I protect him from my my own cum. Okay. Okay, the all familiar, but then I
experience the all familiar feeling of cum, my own cum hitting my face in my
ass. Okay, so. Do I need to take damage now? Yeah, you do need to also take damage. So,
yeah, well first, well actually, you know what, first we'll hold an athletics check to see if
you can succeed in um, oracarabatics. I can do that easily with my minus one. Yeah, you
You somersaulted onto the child and protected him from your own semen.
Um, yeah, Cameron, you take 14 damage.
Um...
[Laughter]
And make a- make a, uh, a deck saving throw, also.
Me?
Yeah.
24.
You're fine, okay, cool.
So, you're able to- to wipe the- the explosive fiery cum off of you after it initially scalds you.
Now let me see how they all do in terms of their deck saving throws.
They do fine.
They're all able to shake it off, but they're all looking really fucked up.
That was a really bad hit by them.
Except for the orphan.
Yeah, except for the orphan who you saved.
You take 14 damage.
I also take 14 damage?
Yeah.
No, you don't take 14.
You actually just roll a deck saving throw.
Oh, he takes 14.
No, you're not the boss.
He takes 14 damage.
Roll a deck saving throw.
Roll a deck saving throw, actually, Caleb, first.
uh... really job
only got a ticket
when i was a little shy so i was a little bit myself
i sacrifice myself to avoid being a pedophile he's like any good american
you take nine days which uh...
from from the the residue the comrades to do this on you
So how much total damage do I take?
You just take nine, you don't take the fourteen also.
What?
Because that was your throw.
He threw that and then, oh well I guess you know what, he was doing that to protect the
boy.
So you...
What if I pray to keep Caleb alive?
How does, would that work?
Can I do a reverse on not letting this kid get covered and come?
i feel like you're a felt kinda guilted into it because i'll tell you what you
read so you're so now you're so now you know i don't think you know what i'm
not you know i have not been a little
reverse again
i i am so i am
absolutely plaster
with my own com and i'm sitting on top of a spot of a boy okay you also take
time covering a boy and i'm covered in com
And you're- and you're-
There's no good way to say this.
You're also de- you're also knocked out.
No, I have 1 HP. I have 1 HP now.
If I take 14 more-
You take 14, you also take the- the 9 from your failure.
Yes, that puts me at- that puts me at 1.
No, so if you're at 15 HP-
No, I already added the 9 to that.
That's what-
Oh, okay, I didn't realize that.
Okay, okay.
Dude, that'll teach you to throw a cum grenade at your friends.
It was absolutely worth it.
The boy is looking up at you, he's like, "Thank you, sir!"
I feel like he...
We neutralize...
There's no way he keeps fighting us, right?
Yeah.
No, we turned him to our side.
We could probably convince him to be an ally.
He crawls out from under your limp demon body and scurries away, rethinking the crowd he
runs with and what it means when you grow up.
We just saved a child.
We saved a child's soul.
does he break the seal of cum that marries my body to the ground around him?
I've kind of created a dome. No comment on how he did that. Okay. I can't possibly
imagine how he did that. Pure ingenuity. Yeah. Pure childish ingenuity. Yeah. So, it is now
It's now, uh, uh, Blowtoss, it is your turn again.
Alright.
Um, so, I, there are two...
Yeah, they're looking pretty bad.
They're not looking good.
Yeah.
Please kill us!
I don't have any area of effect, right?
Yeah, I don't.
Okay.
I'm just gonna, I'm gonna, uh, hit, first I'm gonna hit the, one of the, there's two
guys right next to me, I'm just gonna hit one of them with my, my pipes.
Mm-hmm.
um that's a 16. yeah describe your kill. um okay so i i started i swing it like a baseball bat
and his head comes off and it go yeah flies across the bar and they have a um they actually have a
basketball hoop in the bar and it goes into the basketball hoop and it says you just scored
1000 points. Yeah, it says you scored 1000 points and also all the V-girls who are
waitstaff, they stop what they're doing and they pick up a, they write down on
note cards and they hold up all tens. Okay. Ten, ten, ten, ten. Okay, yeah, that's right.
Yeah, so that one's dead and so now you have another attack too. Yeah. And there's
one one other guy I'm gonna I'm gonna pull out my Grinch gun and I'm gonna
please only British spare me I'm gonna shoot him with my Grinch gun point-blank
that's a 14 okay yeah that's yeah that's that's it describe your kill okay
sort of didn't go on and he dies yeah um nice yeah he's uh yeah he fucking just
collapses slumped over dead on the ground.
The one guy who's left is sort of panicking now.
And he's gonna try one more--
- Oh, he's right in front of me.
- Yeah, he's gonna try one more time
to try to swing at Patrick Yoda.
I don't think it's gonna go too hot for him.
Actually, actually it did go very hot for him.
- No!
- Yeah, inspired by his fear, he got a critical hit.
- Damn, no!
Yeah. How bad?
Uh, we'll see.
Critical.
It's probably...
It's nine damage.
He's not that strong.
So he just...
He just tries to kick...
He kicks you basically right in the gut.
Alright, so I have seventeen hit points now?
Yeah.
Fuck.
Alright.
Uhhhh...
Now it's your turn.
And he's like scared.
Alright, so what...
What I'm gonna do...
Hmm.
This is interesting to think...
About.
I think maybe I might do a yo- no wait that's different from last time okay um
I'm gonna hit him with the hoagie surprise whoa do it okay well this all
just switched around what's the hoagie surprise sorry sorry yeah describe your
Describe your hoagie.
Ok, hold up. Let me find hoagie surprise in here.
Ok, so my hoagie, it is just a classic.
It's not in your spells.
It's not in my spells.
So it's just a classic, it's probably just like an Italian job from 7-11.
It's got the hot peppers on it, it's got the garlic mayo.
It's called 7,000 11,000. Yeah, it's an Italian job from 7,000 11,000 and so I
hit him with the hoagie surprise. Oh you fucking yeah roll for damage let's see
you do. Yeah describe your kill you bludgeon this guy. So I pull out the
hoagie it's a very old hoagie it's I mean I've been carrying this thing on all my
missions the bread is stale the meat is disgusting it's like it's just like it
is so gross and the bell peppers there's like mold coming off of it so the bread
is so hard the bread is like just like the strongest wood on earth right and I
think that's cannon yeah bread the bread is as hard as the strongest wood on
earth which is is it teak wood I don't know so let's let's find out strongest
wood on so lignum vitae yeah so it is a lignum vitae well this is this says an
Australian blokey. So... A blokey? Yeah. That's just any old guy in Australia. There is a landmass on planet E-Bomb
that has almost the same ecology as Australia except all the people are also
marsupials so they all have pouches too. Yeah. But yeah it has that kind of wood. So
I it is just as hard as that and I hit him over the head with it so hard that
the top of his head slides off. It looks like I'm opening up a Wonderball to get
the Mario stickers out of it. Yeah. Yeah, so he has stickers on his brain. Yeah, so
I'm basically, I knew that he had some stickers in his head. Mm-hmm. And I just
wanted the stickers. Yeah, add Mario stickers to your inventory. I will. Okay.
yeah he gets how many how many Mario stickers did I get how many are
typically in a water ball like - I don't know should we roll for it yeah let's
roll roll roll d4 okay there's one Mario sticker in there there's one but yeah
but it's it's the mark it's it's Mario sunshine sticker which is the best okay
all right controversial Mario sunshine sticker yeah and so he the guy he gets
hit in the head with the hoagie and he's like it's still better than British food
and he dies and yeah so so everyone knows self-effacing I love them for that yeah
dry British wit we all know exactly dude Ricky Gervais is so funny man he rocks
man yeah he's awesome so yeah he doesn't believe in God sorry no what do you mean
You know God? Yeah sure. Yeah you know what you know I love him yeah it's all just
rubbish to this guy. You gotta be kidding me. Yeah he doesn't give a flog about it dude.
Oh my god. He seriously doesn't. He looks like a fucking pig. So yeah you guys win. You guys
beat the shit out of the British, the British stag party, the rowdy boys. Yeah I
don't know that I won. I'm covered in my own cum and I have 1 HP. I look
around I look around at the dead bodies of the stag party and they're all covered
and come from the sexual grenade and I look into the camera and I say this
thing started as a stag party but now it looks more like a and then there's a
censored bar that goes over my mouth and stays up for a full minute.
It's a really long time.
Yeah that's yeah yeah the audience loves that it's very funny.
(laughing)
- Yeah, so the whole bar--
- Blowtoss, you crazy for that one, bro.
- Well, I couldn't hear what he said.
All I heard was a string of beeps.
(laughing)
- A string of beeps?
So they used the beeps?
They stop and start?
- String of beeps from--
- They keep stopping and starting.
- They stop and--
Yeah, they Morse code the actual word.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
But luckily I knew Morse code
and I knew what he was saying.
Because of my time as a Morse code captain.
Yeah, so everyone in the bar who knew Morse code is like, kind of looks a little disgusted, but everyone else is just, was sort of turned to that, sort of does a polite golf clap, they're all kind of happy to see that SAG party dead.
Nobody likes a group of British guys together.
Of course.
Yeah, it's really horrible.
And the orphan boy, you see a single tear. He sheds a single tear and he leaves the bar in a hurry.
But yeah, you guys have a clear way now to Mommy's dressing room.
You see the security guard outside, sort of his steps aside. He's like, "Whoa, yeah, of course."
So yeah, you guys can do whatever you want. What's going on? What are you thinking?
I say we head there. I say we head there.
dressing room. I'm gonna go in there and I'm gonna look around. I turn to Ray
William Duss and I say, "Hey, why don't you consider healing up? You look pretty rough.
You're covered in cum." No, I'm alright. I don't think you are. I think I'm fine. I think you should probably wipe that cum off your face before you go back in.
No. You know what? No. I think you gotta heal up a little bit. No, it's called fashion. You
Just a little bit.
Just a little bit of one hardship.
Probably would help us out.
No, it would make us worse.
Just heal.
Because now I look scarier.
Well, I don't think that will help anything.
Don't wipe the come off and just heal up your power.
Your hit.
Okay.
How do I heal?
So yeah, you have the ability to heal.
I forgot what the spell is called.
You also see people, you say
say like I you I seem scarier and you do see people actively avoiding you which I
guess you interpret as. Yeah because I'm covered in stinky, stinky cum but like yeah like I
haven't had it's not like I've been eating just like meat and like salt for
like months so that's like all I like my cum is really fucked up. It's one of the
worst things I've ever heard so I think it's called going viral is your healing
ability okay so it costs three techno slime points by me to heal how many
techno slime points you have so far yes so you can spend three oh yeah so that's
up to you so if you cast if you spend three you will heal ten points to each
member of your squad but if you by dispersing faves and RTs but if you for
every extra point you spend above three you heal three more points okay so level
one would be spending three mm-hmm okay so I am gonna spend I'm gonna do level
three so that'll be five points total right okay yeah so you spend five points
Yeah, and everybody heals
Everybody heals 16 HP. No, I'm not 16. Yeah, everyone heals 16 HP. So nice, dude
You're welcome
Yeah, and so now you have one techno slime point left
Obviously you still have those refills
But yeah, when you run low on techno slime.
- Oh damn, I got extra health points from that.
- Yeah, so-- - Can you go above your cap?
- So you would go above, so in D&D,
you would go, quote unquote, go above your cap
when you like, and it would be called,
like it would have to be specifically called
temporary hit points.
- Okay, so I would just put-- - Which we don't have,
but we can, yeah, well so yeah, exactly.
So otherwise this would just max out,
But what we can do is we can make the excess go into your temporary hit points.
I think that's a fine ability to do.
How long do they last?
So they last until you take a short rest or a long rest.
Which we can go over what short rests versus long rests are.
But basically a short rest is just like a 30 minute rest and you spend hit die to gain
hit points back.
Which we can talk about whenever that's relevant.
So if you guys ever want to like, be like, before we go in here, let's take a 30 minute,
you know, nap.
Yeah, before this fight, let's nap.
Yeah.
No, no, I get it.
And then a long rest, you gain all of your hit points back.
You gain your, I'm going to say you gain your techno slime abilities back also.
And because that would be like a spell slots.
And then you also, you would gain half your hit die back used, I forgot what that rule
is, I don't ever go by it, it's stupid.
Yeah, so what do you do to heal them up?
What's your, I called it going viral, but I mostly wanted you to describe how you heal
your friends and your son.
What's my viral post?
I hit command C on the keyboard in my brain
and it fills in, not wearing my glasses anymore,
I've seen enough.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- And then I become the president because it gets so big.
- Yeah, yeah, and that always,
that will always, you can always use that one if you want to.
- That's the thing about that one,
And you can use it about once a day.
For about, yeah, you can use that for the rest of your fucking life and everyone will always
think it's novel and like they haven't seen it before.
Yeah, somewhere deep in the heart of cyber Texas, a young goblin named Thomas is seething
at a monitor.
Because I, I, when I made the first campaign, um, I had Thomas as a character, um, a potential
character and I had him as a bugbear, because they're like just big hairy dudes, um, and
I had him just killing, uh, being the shit out of Michael Rapaport, but I like him as
a goblin, as a Texas goblin.
Yeah, no, yeah, he, he's a, he pretends to be, he's a cave goblin.
Exactly, he's a cave goblin.
Yeah, and he's crying at a on it to it to an Android phone that he's holding
and
Yeah, and he's like I should have made t-shirts
Yeah, yeah, so you guys are yeah, you're all healed up
so yeah, you know at your hip points here, whatever your character sheets and
yeah, you guys walk into mommy's dressing room or into I should say the the backstage of the
You know place of the mommy's good the mommy good legs. And yeah, it's sort of a typical
You know backstage of a theater so it's just decrepit
The wallpaper is peeling
There's some like affects of you know cyberpunk decor in like neon lights, but they're like flickering
It looks a little bit cheaper than it does
outside in gun city proper and
And you get to a door that says mommy on it.
What do you guys do?
I knock on the door.
I jump on the door.
I go two feet. I try to drop kick the door open.
Okay, yeah. Roll an athletics check to see how you do.
Should I roll? Okay.
Athletics or acrobatics.
back
It's a suicide door from a car.
Yeah.
It's a front door that it detaches out and then opens sideways.
Yeah, you hear like all these locks unlocking and like
like like *clicking noises*
and then it opens towards you
and just like takes up the whole hallway as it does.
And you walk into
Uh, uh, and you see it's, it's, it's Mommy's, Mommy's room.
And, uh, uh, it's a, it's a very, it's a very nice looking room.
Let me, let me, uh, *clears throat*
*inhales*
You hear a mechanical sound go on from behind the door,
and you watch as the mechanical door unfurls,
security locks unwinding in a clockwork, get-smart fashion.
When the door finally opens, you're hit with a scent not unlike Chanel No. 5.
Mommy Goodleg's dressing room is velvety and lush with curtains and beads and draperies
and other girl shit hanging around.
You see her finishing removing her makeup as she's looking in the mirror.
So what do you boys want?
I look around the room for coins.
Okay.
Do I have to roll an investigation?
Yeah, I guess yeah. Roll investigation. Also, do you care if you're-
Seven.
*laughs*
Before you do that, do you care if you're noticed looking for coins in her room?
No.
Okay, yeah, so you just start like turning over stuff, looking for coins.
*laughs*
She's like, she's like looking like, she's like looking like a real femme fatale.
She looks like Yaddle, I think to you, is what you said.
*laughs*
So her legs are kicked up on her dressing and you just are like unfazed, just walk past
her and just start turning shit over.
Looking for coins.
She's like, "What are you doing?"
Well, I'm looking for coins, obviously.
I don't understand how you didn't get that from what I'm doing.
He wants to buy some candy.
I'm trying to play at the arcade.
is doing like the thing from located at the back of the bar I'm trying to find
I'm trying to play the we have joust and we have dig dug - he's doing the the
Benedict Cumberbatch Sherlock thing where like words are flying up in front of his
face but it's just pennies and just pictures of coins yeah yeah it's uh yeah yeah she's
He's like, "Yeah, we got Dig Dug. That was a big get for us."
"It draws a big crowd of perverts who love Dig Dug."
"Um..."
"I'm not a pervert, but..."
"No, no, no, I wouldn't dream of saying that."
"I do love to inflate a dragon."
"Alright."
"There's nothing sexual about it."
"Inflating a dragon."
"Roll a persuasion check, 'cause you're trying to persuade her that that's not sexual."
"And I think that's hard to accept."
Yeah, she's pretty certain that what you said with that seven, she's pretty certain that
what you're saying is like probably sexual, but she's trying not to show it, that she's
noted that on her face.
Again, let me reiterate it, it's not sexual at all.
I just want to play some Dig Dug.
Yeah, at this point you have to roll deception.
I have it on my Xbox arcade at home.
It's gonna be very hard to deceive her.
- So I have to roll a deception?
- If you're gonna insist, if your goal is to deceive her.
- Okay, I got a 15.
- Yeah, it's just not, you just,
you kind of dug yourself in a hole.
It's a good roll, but it's not enough
at this point kind of thing.
(laughing)
Yeah, she's like, "No, for sure, definitely."
So did you guys, besides coins,
you guys were, seemed pretty insistent to talk to me
and I think I know what you're here about, so.
- Nope, just coins.
- Hey buddy, why don't you go look
for coins back in the bathroom?
- Yeah, I put my arm on him and I interrupt
and I say, "Sorry about my friend.
We were wondering, do you have any recommendations
for lunch in the neighborhood?"
- Oh, well, as far as places to eat, there's--
- Yes, places to eat, you stupid bitch.
I said it was night time it seems more like dinner time I guess roll straight
time is what it is they call her stupid bitch try charisma check to see if you
can come across as cool so just hit the charisma button on your abilities on the
the far left. You just seem like a regular misogynist. She's like, "Well, I don't have
to help you all, so if you don't get right to the point right now, I might as well just
get my security in here and get you all out." Sean McElwee. What do you know about him?
Sean, so you're looking for Sean. Shut the fuck up Patrick. I don't have any of his coins.
He never, he never let anybody have his coins but him. I heard he has a shit ton of
buffalo nickels. You heard right and he loves those nickels. Which are very offensive because they
feature a photo of a Native American on the front. He was trying to collect them
all to stop them from being in circulation. He was such a good activist.
Yeah that's why I have all this red skin gear in my apartment. I'm trying to keep
other people from having that. Yeah so I started hanging the Confederate flags in
my room. I was just trying to stop. Nobody has a Confederate flag. Exactly. Oh why do I have to
hang them? It's just so I know. I can keep track of it that way. Exactly. Yeah I know
I know how many I have to, how many are left.
- Yeah, right, in the world.
- Yeah.
- So yeah, she says,
"Well, ah, Sean."
She sort of sighs.
She crosses her legs.
Whap!
Her thighs slap against the other thigh.
- Nice.
- "Well, I found his persistence charming,
"but ultimately he was,
"well, I have eyes, ears, and a working olfactory system,
So I wasn't enamored with the fella.
I don't know what happened to him, if I'm being honest,
but I want to help.
He was a, he was a beloved man.
I found his disappearance strange.
- How, how so?
- Wait, we should ask how she knows him.
- Oh yeah.
Well, he came to the club all the time.
- Yeah, but, but why?
Tell us straight up.
Was he two-timing his old girl?
Uh, ooh, roll a persuasion check on that then.
Yeah, such a...
It's a classic...
...pervasive sentence, that is.
Classic noir question.
Yeah, yeah, she's...
She's, no, that's enough. I mean, she's okay with talking about it.
She's fine with... that's fine.
Thirteen, she says, uh...
I...
Look, I didn't see him two time, but he was grabbing at every v-girl who was in here.
How'd he do that?
They're all computers.
Playershit.
Yes, he had the Playershit mod installed as part of it.
But frankly, while Sean had his vices and his demons, I do believe he wanted to make
gun city a better place just I don't think he always had the best methods how
so what word what what was he doing what's the deal what are you doing how
about you just tell us the solution in the mystery look I don't know anything
about any solutions no spoilers how about you just tell us the ending
I'll roll persuasion for that. Yeah, roll a persuasion check to see if she can tell you the ending.
Yeah, with a solid six she lets you know the ending of the story.
No, she says, "Look, I, I, I, Sean was always trying to..." Are you all familiar with, I
imagine the matrix 2 correct oh yeah I've seen the first one hmm however I've
never seen most of the matrix movies which we're curious which where did you
stop I've only seen the animatrix you know saying I saw half of the first one
at cyber community college I actually only played enter the matrix so I get
what you're saying. I've never watched any of them because they're basically my life.
She says, "Well, The Matrix 2 is... well I'm not a fan of it if I must be honest. It's
where all the all the clubs seem to be moving there now. People don't like flesh
and blood. They want to... they like bits. They like ones and zeros. They like to
enter the virtual world. And Sean thought that would be the best place to do what
he wanted to do and get done what he wanted to get done.
And so he started to post there a long time ago, posting every day, countless, countless
posts about all kinds of issues that plagued him.
But he got far, but he never really made a dent, and he sort of seemed like he gave up
hope towards the end.
But he started coming here more often, and I started asking him, "What's going on, Sean?
You're not tipping as much, what's wrong with you?"
And he said he had more important work to deal with and I haven't seen him since.
How important?
I didn't follow up.
Yeah, like what was he doing?
Exactly, what was he doing?
What's his favorite movie?
Oh, it's The Help, of course.
(laughter)
- Well, obviously.
- Isn't it everyone's?
- Yes, we all love the help in Gun City.
- You're of course talking about
the remake that was made this century.
- The all white remake?
- Yes, of course.
the white help
you know we all know the white help
it came out right after white hamilton
i remember
the white help starring sean king
it's too good
what an amazing performance
Yeah, he's incredible.
Him and Sean were great friends.
They used to post together all the time.
Yes, similar kinds of people.
What exactly, what was the kind of changes that Sean was trying to make in Gun City?
What was he posting about?
Well, he started talking about penises more and more.
He started talking, he seemed obsessed almost with their shape, with what they're made of.
of
guys can you guys roll insight yeah I got a 19 yeah blowtoss pisses it knows an
innate yeah blowtoss piss knows that you that you are very interested in in the
anatomy of dicks Ray William Johnson what do you think it's just your fascination
there's nothing wrong with that I must have had you confused you yeah no you
You hate penises.
I do.
Once again I'm the only one burdened with the dark truth.
Can I say that into the camera?
*laughter*
And well, yeah, so he just...
He started getting obsessed with them and...
He started to talk about abolishing penises.
I... I...
Couldn't make heads or tails of it to be honest.
Look, I...
Well, it's probably tails, because that's the lower half of the body.
That's a good point, Patrick Yoda.
Look, I can't have you all in here for so long. People are going to start...
People will talk.
Let them talk.
Right, that's usually what people say after that, but...
But if you could all just...
Just leave, and you can come back here in the morning, and we can talk more about...
about Sean. I think I know what we can do next to find out.
What time?
10am.
You want to get brunch with us?
Sure, yeah, we can have some of these.
Wait, so that was a friendly toast.
We have Subway Jared here, he can whip us some breakfast sandwiches for a while.
Oh, no!
Finally, you answer my original question, you bitch.
No, he's been lobotomized, it's different.
Okay, the misogyny again. Okay.
It's not misogyny. I am not male nor female. I am computer.
Right, I forgot misogyny is dependent on...
It is.
Just the tin. Yeah.
Also, remember, you said tin. I might be a bit late because of computer people time.
Well, keep that in mind. It will probably be closer to 10, 20...
I almost spit on my white cloth.
Damn. Damn, dude. Okay.
Uh, yeah, so...
She started shushing you guys...
I heard Hillary Clinton ran on that back in June.
Fuck up.
I heard that was the time she used to run on.
until back in 2016 that was the time.
Can we not bring up that election?
It's triggering my anxiety.
Yeah, roll a constitution saving throw, Caleb.
19.
Yeah, you remember sitting in your parents' brownstone and just watching the numbers come
in on CNN. Yeah. And your mother just clutching her Rolodex of pedophiles that your father
knows and works with every fucking day. Yep. As the numbers came in and that memory sort
of flashes back into you and you remember watching Wolf Blitzer just shit his pants.
But you push that memory out of your head. You're like, "It's okay." I successfully un-remember.
Yeah, you unremember the orange... well you know.
Okay, well I wasn't...
So, yeah you guys, do you guys occupy mommy's dressing room or do you skedaddle?
We do an Occupy style protest.
I just start sleeping right there.
Can we at least finish looking for coins?
*laughter*
Yeah, you guys wanna all-
We got machines open right now!
Yeah, all of you guys roll investigation checks, see if you can find as many coins as you can.
Yes, dude, finally the real game.
Mm-hmm.
I got a nine.
No, I got a nine.
I got a nine, too.
Oh, wait.
I got a sixteen.
I got a sixteen as well.
Pretty awesome.
Yeah, see, you guys find a few, uh, uh, um-
*burps*
Oh, how many quarters did we find before?
Oh, yeah, we each have ten quarters.
Okay.
of
it
I just punched Caleb in the head for 15 points.
Okay, you rolled a, you rolled a, uh, what's it, a strength save?
Um, okay, uh, do you want to roll initiative?
Do you want to fight Caleb?
No, I just punched him in the head and I took all of his quarters.
No, you didn't.
Yeah, I did.
No, I block.
Okay, I didn't.
You know what?
Fuck it, I roll initiative.
I'm gonna kill Patrick.
No, no.
You wanna do that?
Let's do it.
Let's do I want to do that we can do I roll then wait I want to talk them down
I want to do persuasion and talk. Okay. Yeah, try to talk them down. All right, I
Get a 16
Okay, okay
So we did
If we're doing persuasion talk you down guys down from a fight
I
Guess you would guys roll with
Whatever your charisma
I mean like if you want to play that way or you guys can also just...
You can also just fight if you want.
I'm willing to be tucked down.
I rolled a 5.
You rolled an initiative.
If you rolled initiative 5 I'm ready to fight.
Okay yeah we're just gonna roll initiative.
Okay.
Alright.
Roll initiative Caleb.
For 27 quarters.
For like...
For 5 dollars.
for five dollars
we're not even i said seventeen it's three dollars and like fifty cents
uh... three thirty
and i have a home now because that's what i what he sees from the steel my
quarters
ouch you've got five who has hired acts of the two u
dexterity i have a one
let me see and i have minus one
Okay, so Patrick Yoda's gonna go first.
Okay.
Um...
I mean, you guys are like right next to each other in the hallway, so...
Yeah.
Um...
Well...
I'm gonna go with hoverboard boomerang for nine.
And I get five plunging damage.
You use a boomerang from five people away- five feet away?
Well, it's gonna spin around your head like I did with the guy before.
Well, it's-
You seriously suck at fighting.
It didn't beat his armor class, so...
so you you through the boomerang in a missed
uh...
kill it it's a a really a chance that your turn
okay
how much i have like no techno so i have six ten percent points were good
now you don't know it not on i have one
so you want
do all i think i can't do anything right
you have your dongle blackjack
okay use my dongle blade
not for
that's a
it's not a blade
but you did it
in chat
bitch
uh...
well i i i i'm giving him an opportunity to give up before i knock him out
alright uh... i'd give up
the
and what will it be used for that
you can use just giving up and then he had a chance to give up
Yeah, there's not a button to give up.
Play this out, play this out, play this out.
Alright, so I give up.
So you miss me and then I hit you with my dong blade.
And I'm like, you gum at the
get me,
you best not miss.
Okay, so then, um,
so I stop.
And then I attempt to pickpocket Caleb.
I karate chop his hand.
Hold on, I got a 16 for slaying Caleb.
I think that was his disadvantage, I fucked him up.
Yeah, okay, okay, okay.
Alright, then I'll roll again, sleight of hand.
Yeah, roll again.
Okay, and Caleb, roll a, um, I guess perception to see if you notice it.
Perception.
*laughter*
You absolutely notice him, just like, his grubby little hands, just like reaching for
it.
Okay.
karate chop his hand as it tries to enter my pocket.
Alright, then I'm all done.
As it tries to enter the pocket of my JNCO jeans.
Then I'm all done.
Okay, cool.
Yeah, so the hall, yeah, there's just a shit ton of commotion in the hallways and you guys
walk out.
Wait, Patrick, did you take that damage?
Wait, how much damage do I take?
You take 12 damage.
Really?
Yeah, because I hit you with my dong blade.
Right.
Yeah, also make sure you guys add the help.
I have 21 hit points now.
You gained 16 back.
You all gained 16 after healing, so make sure you add that too.
I only have 21 hit points now.
Oh no!
Yeah, some people don't have...
Some people in Africa don't have any hit points.
So why don't you think about that?
Some people in Africa are starving for hit points.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Are we all going home?
wait so yeah you guys walk out of the bar and uh uh Jamal the worm calls you all over as
you guys uh leave. Is he still handcuffed? Yeah he's still handcuffed he's still handcuffed
you're gonna shit on him um sorry and he says uh he says um uh some guy wanted to talk to
to you. He's outside. He looks a little weird.
You're a worm.
Okay, well, all right, you shat on my head. So I don't
like, I barely
With all due respect, Jamal, you are a worm with shit on your head.
Yeah, I'm not sure you have any standing to call people weird
looking.
Okay, no, I mean, okay, well, good. I mean, look, I'm just
glad that you said that with with all due respect. So now I
Yeah, I'm just like taking that in and, "Oh, I feel good.
Ooh, ooh."
All right, well, let's go see what this guy's all about, right?
Yeah.
We don't clean up Jamal at all.
We just leave him there.
Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah, you guys walk outside of Mommy Good Legs and you walk through the doorway and you're
You're flanked by those two giant legs that crowd the entrance.
And you see, skulking in the corner of this little alleyway where Mommy Goodleg's bar
club exists, is a little man with the flattest head.
He has like just the flattest head you've ever seen.
And he, he, he has like two beady eyes
shifting back and forth.
He looks like a weird fucked up penny.
And he says, he says, "K, come here.
"Come here, I got something to tell you guys."
- What?
What do you gotta tell me?
- You gotta come closer.
Don't, don't do that.
- I put one of my coins right on his head.
I pick the coin up off of his head and put it in my pocket.
Damn.
My name's...
Let me subtract a quarter.
Yeah, and I get to add one.
Nice.
I'm going to get them one at a time, dude.
My name is Michael.
He starts licking his lips.
Sorry, did we ask?
Oh, no.
No, I guess.
What is your name?
What's your name?
My name's Michael.
My name's Michael the Clown.
Thank you.
Thank you Michael the crawler?
Yeah, that's my name.
That's you? That's what you look like?
I don't know, I never listened to the episode where you guys mentioned that name. I just sort of thought.
Um...
So uh...
Look.
He's just licking his lips a little bit more. He's like,
"Look,
uh, my uh, my employer
needs to talk to you all if you're gonna
I'm just uh, keeping uh, insisting on investigating this uh, disappearing Sean fella.
Where do you work?
Like Staples or what, who, what's the deal?
You work for Office Depot?
Yeah, can you get us a good deal on printer paper?
We like to draw.
I don't work for Staples or for Office Depot, okay?
I don't work for any of your places.
Look, meet me at the abandoned porno factory.
Tonight.
In an hour, we can talk then.
Why not just now?
Can we just follow you there?
It's too many prying eyes, too many jolly big cops lurking around.
That's all right.
They work for us.
Yeah, we know that they actually work for us.
That's not how private detective agencies work.
Nah, it works.
It works that way.
That's actually how it works.
That's how it works, I rolled a 9.
Okay, I don't believe you.
Yeah, he's familiar with
just like how that works. I turn to
RayWilliamJohnson and say, "You try deceiving him. See if he'll believe you."
Alright, let me try.
15. Yeah, that's actually how it works.
Okay, maybe that is how it works, but...
[laughter]
Look, look, look, I'm just trying to follow orders over here, okay?
Yeah, so we're-
Well, how about you don't follow the orders?
Well, maybe you just sweeten the-
That's just a stupid question.
Why don't you just sweeten the deal in that case?
Look I got-
Here's another quarter.
He starts crawling in a circle.
Okay, as he passes by me-
Look, alright, okay, alright.
Alright, we're on his head. I take it out of my pocket
Fuck have I have one Super Mario sunshine sticker. I could give you
Wait, what are we trying to get?
If you tell us what we were asking for in the beginning
Guys are just sort of the most aimless detectives
Just like there's information that could be gleaned.
We just want to know, I guess, who you're working for?
We just want to know what we want to know from you.
Yeah, I pick him up by his lapel and I say, "Tell us the Konami code."
Up, up, down, down, Ike.
Is it left, right, left, right, then A, B, A, B?
Why do you sound so nervous? I've seen lie to me. I know it's somebody.
I'm not trying to lie, I'm just trying to remember.
Ray, we can look that up on E-Bombs World. They got a t-shirt of it.
We live on E-Bombs World.
There's a t-shirt we can buy of it.
True.
We don't need to know that. We just want to know what we were asking about.
All right, sorry, okay, let's hey buddy listen, and I put him down listen. Let's just start over okay
We're reasonable people. I'm open. I'm open to it. You have a flat head. How about yeah, I do it's really
Why do you know about?
Sean McElwee and
I could give you a sticker
If you tell me what I want to know
Okay, so one at a time this far Sean Tom McKelvey no goes
Now there's a sticker I really don't want to let go of this sticker
It's my son McKelvey goes that's what I want to talk to you about the abandoned porno factory
Because I can't why can't we just like can we just talk here?
It's like cuz I told you it's probably nice that's all
I do not see anybody. Yeah, how about you here?
Here wait, oh yeah, I take it I'll take it I take out a piece of paper and I write
Do you like me circle? Yes or no?
I know I also I go over to the dumpster behind
Momma's bar. Yeah, that's there. There's a dumpster.
I go behind the dumpster and I find two cups and a piece of string.
You can also, you guys can also do an insight check to see if you...
Yeah, I pretty much do an insight check.
Believe him when he's saying that, um...
I got a 7 for the insight check. I'm gonna do an insight check too.
I got a 12.
Okay, let's see how he does.
Yeah, Caleb, it's all on you.
Oh, oh boy. Basically I suck.
Yeah, so you can tell that Michael the Crawler is not being totally truthful with you guys.
He's uh, he seems to be, he's saying like, oh, like, there's too many cops around here,
but there seems to be another reason why he doesn't want to talk about it here.
I bet he's setting up a trap.
Yeah.
Okay, I look...
Wait, would you have to roll a perception to see if he was setting up a trap?
I wanna look Michael Kraler in the eye and say, uh...
Yeah, we'll definitely meet you there. You should go back to your house right now.
- And just get ready. - Wait, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Can I use Yoda's mind right now?
To read his mind and find out?
- Whoa... - Yeah.
- Okay, I don't say what I just said. - You definitely can.
Okay, Cameron doesn't say what he says, and I use a Yoda's mind.
Yeah, so Yoda's mind...
So it should cost...
Oh shit, actually I don't know if you have enough Techno Slime points for it.
I have uh, I have five.
Yeah but it costs five thousand dude.
It costs ten so I made it cost more because I figured that in a detective game you would
be using that more.
You should inject Techno Slime right now in front of Michael Kraler.
You can, you can do that.
Okay I just injected, I have ten Techno Slime refills.
So I'm gonna use one of them.
So each of them, yeah, add five techno slime up to your total?
If he's techno sliming, I mean I do it sort of socially, if anything.
So I also start.
You all shoot up in front of this guy.
I put on Lil' Winn, I feel like dying, and I shoot up techno slime.
Okay, everybody, everyone who's shooting up techno slime in front of this weird flat-headed
man, roll a constitution saving throw.
because we're gonna start addressing the techno slime addiction system now okay
I'm gonna shoot up techno I know I have a way I still have this I still have
disadvantage on hold on let me redo that again no you don't yeah I do I had it on
I see so wait that's fine though no just keep the 16 yeah I'll keep the 16 so I
got a 16 I got yeah so you yeah yeah so you withstand the the techno slime our
camera you injecting techno so I'm also injecting techno slime even though I
haven't used a single point of I'm peer pressured very easily yeah so you and
you and Patrick Yoda are able to withstand the effects of using techno
slime and but but um Ray William Johnson you're only gonna get three points of
techno slime back for that okay and you just and you have disadvantage on dex
rolls for the next in-game 10 minutes. So all that's really happening is, you know,
you're feeling a little bit woozy, your vision's a little bit blurry. Describe
the feeling of that sort of like that initial wooziness of using
TechnoSlime when you go too hard. Yeah, so basically I start... at first I'm like,
"Okay, this rocks, you know, this is the all-familiar high." But then I get
pretty paranoid, you know, and then I start getting so paranoid
that I'm wondering if I even took techno slime
and then I'm thinking about like the dealer I bought it from
and then I'm looking around and I say to
Blowtoss and Patrick, I say,
"Hey man, do you guys feel a little weird right now?"
- I say, "No!"
- No?
- I feel completely normal.
If you feel weird, there's probably something wrong with you.
- Cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool.
Do you guys wanna just like watch a movie or something?
I don't know.
I'm thinking of going to bed right now.
(laughing)
- Well, all right, well.
- You know what, actually, I'll just see you guys later.
I have to go home, and then I leave.
- You leave?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- I go to a Korean gaming cafe,
and I drop myself off in one of the ports.
- Yeah, you go to the Korean gaming cafe next door,
called Kim Jong-un's sister Korean Gaming Cafe.
(laughing)
- Yeah, I just called that. - I don't remember her
fucking name.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, so, yeah, you go there.
There is only, the only game there is,
is Cooking Mama.
But she's wearing, she's wearing a do-rag
and she's cooking up meth and crack.
Yeah, she's in the kitchen.
Yeah, so, yeah, you're doing that
while they're continuing to talk to Michael.
So yeah, Patrick, you have refilled your techno slime.
So you've done, yeah, Michael LaCroix
was just watching you like do drugs.
And it's just like--
- Like you would a detective.
- Yeah.
And so do you wanna now do Yoda's mind?
- Can I use, okay.
- Yeah, use Yoda's mind.
- 30 feet again?
- No, I mean like, so it has an ability.
So, the way Yoda's mind works is, it has a 30-foot range.
But what it allows you to do is,
you can basically probe the thoughts of a person.
And you can get those initial thoughts,
so you can see their surface thoughts,
and then you can also get a deeper
sort of look into their mind if necessary.
- Okay.
So, but first you're gonna get those initial thoughts.
If they fail, the wisdom saving throw,
which your spell DC I believe is pretty good.
Yeah, it's a solid 16.
So let's see how he does.
I don't think Michael the Crawler is that wise.
Yeah, the stats here, he's not.
- Damn. - Nice.
- All right, so now I--
- Yeah, you got it, yeah.
- I find out all of his info
and I found out all of his, his account,
his banking password, his bank passwords,
and the passwords to his,
I found out the password to his FARC account
and his Gaia Online and his Habbo Hotel.
- Okay.
- You also, you also figure out his surface level thoughts.
So he's thinking, and what he's thinking is,
why won't these guys just come with me to the damn factory
with taking them so long.
Do I find out why he wants us to go to the factory?
uh...
uh... if you probe deeper
well i have probed deeper
yeah okay so we'll probe deeper so he has to resist again
uh...
so let's see if he can do it
while you probe deeper
into his mind
uh... let me uh...
Double check how I wrote the fucking spell.
I think I did it the right way.
Yeah.
I find it out.
Let's find out.
I'm sorry, I have to roll.
Yeah.
So what you find out is...
You basically gain insight into their emotional state.
emotional state and it's something that they worry over love or hate.
And you realize that their emotional state at this point is fear and agitation.
And what they're worried about, Michael the Crawler, what he's worried about is that you
guys are going to figure out that he wants you to go to the abandoned porno factory for
nefarious reasons.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
So I immediately beat the shit out of him. I immediately hit him with a hoagie.
Fuck I forgot I'm already gone. Yeah you're gone Caleb you're out. Yeah you're
just in the Korean bar right now chilling out. Just having an absolute freakout.
I'm trying to distract myself but then I'm just thinking like what happens to
them when they turn into dust? Like are they conscious still somewhere? Yeah the
other two of you guys roll initiative in that case.
Alright.
Okay.
And four.
Okay, cool.
I got a fourteen.
Alright, cool.
Patrick Yoda, yeah, you do the hoagie attack in that case, because you definitely go first.
I got a ten with a ten bludgeoning.
Okay, yeah, no, he's not that strong.
So yeah, you beat his uh, you beat his uh, uh, uh, AC and uh, you whack him in the fucking head with the hoagie
um
Uh, and he's like, okay. Okay. I'm, sorry. What do you want? What do you want from me?
What do you want from me? He's trying to like give up he's like he's like he's like on his knees
He's begging I want to know why you don't want us to know what you want it what you know
What we are trying to find out
You heard me.
He's like really trying, he's really scared, he's trying to figure out what you said.
Otaz, you tell him what we're all about.
I'm gonna make it real simple for you, okay?
Either you tell us what we asked you and what we want to know from what you didn't want us to know
from what Patrick was trying to figure out what you didn't want to know.
Before I read your mind.
Before he read your mind.
Bitch.
Or else you're gonna be in a world of hurt.
Okay.
Alright, roll an intimidation check with advantage.
Who, me?
Both of you.
Okay.
I got a 12 now, but I did roll a 14, so we're gonna keep the 14.
Yeah, the 14's the highest.
Um, let's see how he does.
Yeah, he's pretty fucking scared.
He starts crawling really fast in a circle, basically burrowing a hole in the ground as
he's so friggin' scared.
I'll tell you what you wanna know.
Okay, what do you wanna know?
Well, what we asked.
You heard us.
You know.
Okay, I think I got it.
Look, I just...
Why did you need us to go to the abandoned porno's factory?
And where is Sean?
We just wanted to scare you and to stop investigating, that's all.
That's all.
I got nothing else for you.
Who do you work for?
Where's Rachel?
No, I can't say that.
Who's Rachel?
I don't know who Rachel is.
I don't know where she is.
Like, like, like.
Dola Jo?
Rachel Dola's all.
God, she's.
You know Rachel Dola's all.
Rachel Dola's all.
Rachel Dolezal is E's Planet E-Bomb's foremost pinup model.
She is like in-
You see her billboards everywhere.
She's like in the Blade Runner 2049.
She's the giant holographic girl is Rachel Dolezal.
She's the biggest v-girl of them all.
Yeah, yeah.
She is.
She is the biggest v-girl of them all.
Who do you work for, Michael?
I can't tell you, I can't tell you if I tell you...
We just beat the shit out of you! Why don't you tell us?
I won't, I, I, if I could I would, but, but my, but, but, but...
This is gonna be some Zam Wessel shit!
I think you can tell us.
You're not gonna get, you're not gonna get hit by a poison dart like Zam Wessel.
I won't get hit by a poison dart like Zam Wessel, it's true, but, but my, but first, first my cock will explode and then, and then the rest of me...
You got a ring around your cock that explodes when you tell us the truth?
Well if you don't tell us, we're gonna make your cock explode also.
We all have rooms around our cocks.
We're gonna do it in a safer way.
We all have the cockulous rift inside of us. We can't escape it.
Well, I just remembered that.
Please, please, I can't tell you. Just, just, just, look, if you just don't go, just don't go to the abandoned porno factory within the next hour and you'll be okay.
be
going to the abandoned porno factory I just kind of headed in that direction
hold up I'm gonna roll persuasion and try and figure out should I roll persuasion
with advantage what are you trying to do us I'm gonna see if he can tell us who
he works for are you trying to intimidate him or persuade him persuade
him into telling us okay yeah go for persuasion work okay and we definitely
with
He goes real close to your ear as much as his waddly flat head
Can sort of like wiggle its its way towards your ear and he purses his lips and he goes
I work for and then like all of a sudden roll dexterity saving throw. Okay. Oh my god
This is getting scary
Okay
You at the last second you avoid this
First you watch his lower half his pants start to explode
From the cock down and then his body starts to explode him in his head shoots up into the sky
damn
And he's done Michael the crawler is no more. Holy shit Wow
Rest in peace Michael the crawler. I'm still just kind of walking
Down the yeah, Sullivan the frog is driving next to you. It's like hey, do you want to ride?
I call I call Sullivan on the phone after the explosion and I'm like
Sullivan
There's some shit going on
Yeah, yes, I saw that explosion. That's pretty scary. I yelled in the car
Doing Sudoku I yell into the phone I say yeah, he said he worked for explosion noise
Okay
Are you anywhere near Ray William Johnson? Yeah, I'm driving next to me ignoring me
All right, get get him in your car as fast as you can and get back here as soon as possible
You got it. Hey, hey, Ray
What's a
Can you can you look I think I'm under the speed limit. They're probably gonna arrest me
Can you you just hop in and we can go back to the rest of the gang?
I'm supposed to go to the highway
I'm not not on the highway. He's on the highway
Johnson is walking on the highway
Walking in the middle on I think the yellow line in the middle is where you're supposed
This hover car is just blasting by you
Can you please?
I think I I think I kind of want to see what this abandoned porno factory is all about
Okay, I can I can bring you there just
Yeah, I mean that's what the car
Okay, can I can I roll an insight check to see if I believe Sullivan yeah, you certainly can all right
it
I hop in.
Yeah.
Yeah, he takes you in the 2007 Ryan Dunn.
And you turn the air conditioner up.
Porsche 911, he presses the air conditioner up.
GT3 Ryan Dunn edition.
And he does a U-turn and goes back to the alleyway where the two of you guys are standing
there with the exploded corpse.
I get out of the car and I look at the scene and I'm just like, "What the fuck happened
here?"
"We don't know what happened.
His got kind of exploded.
The rest of him went."
"Yeah, that, yeah."
"Okay, okay, I'm up to speed now.
Thanks, dude."
"Hold on, throw your computer at my mind so you can figure out what the hell I'm talking
about."
No, I, it doesn't matter. I don't care what happens.
I don't even care if you throw it at my head. I'm giving you a free throw.
It's almost like you want me to throw it at your head.
I don't want you to throw it at my head because you can find out my other thoughts.
Can I roll an insight check?
Yeah.
Okay. I want to see if he...
This guy's obsessed with insight checks now.
I love it. I'm very insightful.
Yeah, I mean, so you can tell what his meaning is. What is it, Patrick Yoda?
I'm just admit you kind of want me to know what you're thinking I want you to
know you want you want the feeling of me in your head you got that you know what
it is you got to feel in the in the last step in the first in gun city I threw the
computer at your head and you can admit that you liked how it felt but I will
- I will not be hacking you.
- Why not?
- Do you guys wanna go home?
Or do you guys wanna go to the abandoned,
what do you guys, or somewhere else?
- I kinda wanna see what's happening
at that porno factory, if I'm being honest.
- Let me propose a tactical strategy.
- What if we scout it out?
- Let's, yeah, let's set up a stakeout around the factory.
- Yeah, that's definitely something you can do.
See, I can go there if we scout it out, but if we're going there just...
Just because, I don't think...
If there's one thing I can't stand, it's people who...
Blow up the cocks of crawlers.
And fake people!
So, and fake friends.
So I say we have to bring them to justice.
We have to bring all the fake friends to justice!
So we should set up a stakeout.
And figure out who's at the porno factory.
yeah i love that idea
uh... okay cool
uh... okay so uh...
y'all happy and let's get this thing going
it's funny how it keeps saying hop and he's a frog
okay alright
you little frog boy
we laugh for thirty minutes
i'm thirty five
so
We just point and laugh at Sullivan.
Yeah, he feels good about that.
He enjoys it.
He likes all of it.
You guys hop in the Ryan Dunn vehicle
and you head over to the abandoned porno factory
and you stake it out.
So we need you all
to describe what you're doing for the stakeout
and then we're going to roll stealth checks.
okay
i'm looking i'm i'm posted up i'm like hiding in the bushes read health check
i'm hiding in the bushes right uh... right
by the the porno factory
and a holding my two lead pipes up to my eyes like binoculars to look into it
look look
into the factory parking lot and see if anyone is
is falling in
showing up
okay cool
We would yeah I'm looking at a at a call of duty heartbeat sensor.
Okay, hold on.
Let me let me roll my stealth.
And it says it it says it says there's people on it.
But I don't know if it's people walking around.
Oh, wow, that's a that's a terrible role.
I'm just kind of I'm like, I have a U-Haul box.
And my head, I cut out a head hole.
I'm kind of just T-posed in the middle of the street across from the porno factory and I'm
going like "I'm just a box!
I'm the man in the box!"
I feel like you're underselling what 8 Stealth gives you.
I don't think that's so bad that you have to yell that you play pretend in the street.
I'm not playing pretend, I'm just standing in a box and I'm singing Man in the Box by
Alice in Chains.
That's not even...
You wouldn't even notice that if you had a keen eye.
I got a 19 and yeah, I'm basically...
I take the heartbeat monitor thing back.
I'm looking through a pair of binoculars but it's backwards like Steve Martin in the Pink
Panther remake.
Okay, good.
i got a twenty three by the way so i'm the best at stealth but that's great
i'm pretty much better
it's literally a twenty three so
it's way better than you could ever even dream to do in your life
you literally can't get to a twenty three with your stealth bonus so
just consider that
he's actually right about that i'm sorry i am actually right about that and everything so
just consider that next time
you gotta consider this what do we see
you guys look into the abandoned porno factory and uh...
uh... you're staking it out
And you see two, um, huge, like, not huge, huge, like 20 feet, like seven feet iron
men, like these like large iron men, one of them wielding what looks like some
sort of, you know, blue sort of saber with like two or two spokes, um, coming
out of it and sort of, uh, I'm, I'm telling them, um, what you're telling,
what your narration right now. I'm saying all of your narration to them in a Bluetooth headset.
Yeah. What does it sound like? What are you saying?
Saying, "Hey! There's a guy and he's got some kind of lightsaber! And he looks like Iron
Man! And they look the same! It's two men! Two guys!"
I'm muting my Bluetooth earpiece the second that he starts talking.
I'm saying it loud enough that you hear it from far enough away, but you can hear it
in the distance like...
[Muffled]
Like that.
[Laughter]
You can hear it that way.
So the uh the and you see another another one another iron iron guy looks nearly identical to the other one
but instead holding a a a sort of pistol of some sort that uh, uh seems to be uh,
has a bunch of sort of like I guess spokes or spikes coming out of it and they're standing
standing in the abandoned porno factory, which which you guys would know has not been in use for
for decades now. Porno was banned from Gun City many years ago. It was considered ableist by
the Stakehams Federation of Bodies and Spaces. So there's been no porno here ever since the Himbo
debacle of 2300. And you guys are seeing them standing there and they're just standing still,
looking out it looks like. Not doing anything in particular. I give them the
finger. Noticeably? Yes. Okay yeah so one of them notices you giving the finger
then and starts to walk over to you. I give them both fingers. You give them both
fingers yeah and it's the one with the the the sort of energy sword looking
thing and he he starts to say what you do here citizen show your business I'm kind
of I'm kind of looking at Caleb in my box in the middle of the street and I'm
like
straight
uh...
he's he's he's with me
he's my best friend
and
denied
the just at our covers the we're here we're here
I didn't say that!
He was like "That's too much rage against the machine!"
You have one more warning before you get off the premises of the abandoned Bortle Factory.
yeah well you have one if you wave your way to one more finger don't you don't
don't do that to give them the middle the middle toe there's no way you can even
there's no way you could do that roll I'm roll for that roll I guess athletics
nothing it's nothing to me never seen anyone do a middle toe that's fine you
You kind of do a middle toe.
It's just not a thing.
I give you the middle toe.
Which is like even worse than a fuck you.
Because it's like I don't even, I can't even give you a hand right now.
Right.
You get my foot.
Which I guess I don't have any shoes on.
It's stinkier than a finger.
Not mine.
It's the stinky middle.
Yeah, I give him the stinky middle.
Don't you dare give me the stinky middle.
I already gave it to you, buddy.
No, no, no.
Give him the stinky middle?
What is that?
I gave him the stinky middle.
Here, here.
Damn!
You give him one too.
I'm flipping him off regular.
No, give him the, come on, give him the stinky middle or else it's like.
Alright, I'm going to sit down on my hoverboard and give him two stinky middles.
Now I feel like I have to give him another one.
Okay, you all, both of you, roll, roll, sorry, roll the legs check.
I
each of you describe how you fail and how you succeed. I want to hear what you guys have
to say about that.
So I try to sit on my hoverboard and then I end up, um, so because it's got like a, a
cyber grip tape, my butt kind of clings to it. And then on my hoverboard, I'm just kind
of like spinning indefinitely. I've got my two, I've got my middle fingers up and I'm
spinning like fucking a million degrees on my hoverboard too fast and I'm just
kind of going like this is a successful stealth mission yeah basically I do I do
a full lotus position okay my demons he jumps from the one leg that he was on
on
real
Can I sneak past the guy and get into the factory?
Yeah, uh, uh, let's keep your stealth check actually, and I will instead roll there in sight.
I feel like he's very distracted by these stinky middles.
He's insanely distracted by this. Let's see how he does on this perception.
Yeah, of course he doesn't notice you. So if that guy doesn't notice you, you approach closer into the factory while they're giving the stinky middles.
and you see the other guy there as well, he also doesn't notice you.
And you start to see, you go in there, you see the conveyor belts
that used to print out the pornos, and then the scanner that used to upload the pornos
into the Dumb Matrix 2.
And you see a few rats scurrying around.
This is truly an abandoned place.
But you can certainly investigate and look around and you you have free reign of this place at this point. Okay, I'll investigate
I'm gonna roll an investigation check. Yeah, go for it, homie. I got a 16
Yeah, okay. So so you you scour around you find some old max and mags and you find some
pictures of you find some JPEGs of Sarah J lying around and
You also find a door that looks a little less decrepit than the rest of the
factory
But it's also locked
so
You might have to try to either bust it down or pick the lock or something to get in there
Hmm. I'm gonna I'm gonna try and
Beat up the lock with my lead pipes
Okay
Do you want to do that?
stealthily or not?
Question for you.
Hmmmm.
No.
While this has been happening.
Yes, cutting back to you guys.
While this has been happening with Cameron, I somehow hit the Spotify button on my hoverboard.
And now as I'm spinning around, it's playing Ride and Solo by Jason Derulo.
I'm spinning in an indefinite circle and it's going "I'm riding solo, I'm riding solo"
and I'm kind of like George Jetson right now and I'm like "HOW DO I GET OFF THIS THING?"
"I'm riding solo, I'm riding solo, I'm riding solo"
Uh, Caleb are you doing anything also while this is going on or are you just still flipping this thing off?
Uh, yeah, I'm laughing.
Okay, good. So...
Uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh.
Okay yeah, so uh, uh, yeah Cameron you start, or I should say Blotoss, you start bashing
this door, uh, and you start to bash it open when the other Iron Guard, uh, comes up to
you and says, "Stop, you are violating the law, you are trespassing."
I'm a repairman, I'm fixing the lock.
Yeah, roll deception with disadvantage on that.
disadvantage that's very believable
you just snuck in
eighteen with disadvantage
wow damn ok
yeah
yeah he's like
next time please let me know
yeah i can't promise that but
we'll see
ok
it's not a big deal just
you know
let me know
and i actually i have to apprentices that were supposed to uh... watch me
repair this lock and still learn how
i think they're outside somewhere if uh...
you could grab them for me he and bring them in here
yeah i wrote a letter that i believe us be for a few hours
and properly with advantage
uh... fourteen
nevermind
yeah uh... that five would not have done it before teens find out
uh... is like
okay shorty one second
and so uh... he starts a walk outside
and uh... meanwhile the other guys drawing his energy sword
and he's like he's like if you keep playing a jason derulo song i'm gonna
fuck you up your you're a bitch and uh...
please press the stop button on the hoverboard
and uh...
the other one comes up to him and is like "yo dude these guys are chill they're with the
repair who inside the factory"
and he's like "oh ok for real they're kinda rude"
"yeah i think it's
i think it's just like a cultural thing
oh ok i don't wanna
i don't wanna get cancelled so" and they both just sort of like
let you guys in
so if you wanna wanna go into the factory
uh... you can now
uh...
Caleb's zoned out. Caleb's head is empty right now.
I'm still staring into space.
No, I've been meditating this whole time.
Remember? I've been meditating. I've been distracted.
This one guard is completely transfixed by me.
Just looming with four middle fingers.
He's trying to do the math to see how that adds up.
And it's not making any sense to him.
Yeah, I'm gonna roll a calculus check for him to see how he does on that.
Yeah, it's just intelligence. He doesn't do too hot, so he's having a really hard time adding it up.
Yeah, I got one of the guys. I bet you relaxed, Cam.
No, I already got you guys inside. Were you seriously not listening to that?
No, but I'm just hanging out with him.
You weren't listening to any of that?
No, I listened to it.
Yeah, and as they were as as you guys walk by them, you notice that they they they sort of seem like static like they're made of static like they're
They they like they're they're kind of fuzzing like you're kind of fuzzy around the edges
And as you walk by them and into the into the abandoned porno factory with this mysterious door
That seems to be less decrepit than the rest of the abandoned porno factory
And I think that's a good place as any to cap it off.
With you three standing outside the mysterious door, waiting to see what's on the other side
of it.
If you guys are good.
I'm so excited for the next one.
Yeah.
Ended on a good note.
And I didn't even have my recording.
have my recording turned on.
[Music]