Last time on Gun City Abroad City, Space Time Continue Fun.
The party split continued down their respective paths, with Patrick Yoda pursuing his hot lead into the undercity,
and Blotas and Ray pursuing an even hotter lead with the snake Blotas had sex with twice.
Patrick and Baby Gadd made their way to a huge-ass fax's HQ, the Lair of Fax,
the
I have to keep going.
That's what Jubio does.
Or Gun City for that matter.
Such are the benefits of a sovereign outside the draconian bounds of E-Bomb.
I'm sure that sentence made perfect.
Let me start from the beginning of that sentence.
Uh, here we go.
Patrick and Baby Gadd made their way to Huge-Ass Facts' HQ, the Larifax,
where brokers of secrets gather and share information that can't be tracked by any system in the New England Empire.
Or Gun City for that matter.
Such are the benefits of a sovereign outside the draconian bounds of E-Bomb.
I'm sure that sentence made perfect.
Let me start from the beginning of that sentence.
Uh, here we go.
or Gun City for that matter, such are the benefits of a sovereign outside the draconian bounds
of E-Bow.
There, they met Kenan Thompson, flamboyant assistant to Ms. I like the word draconian.
I don't need the bull-head.
No.
I'm saying the word draconian.
No, no, no.
No.
You're hallucinating him making a face about that.
It's not my word choices.
No, no, no.
It's totally fair.
You're going crazy.
I am going crazy tonight.
No, no, no.
Kenan Thompson, flamboyant assistant to Ms. Janet Blowjob, high-ranking member of Huge-Ass
Fax's gang.
Kenan led Patrick and Baby Gadd straight to Ms. Janet Blowjob, since they had some intel
to share about Gumby Superior, captain of the Pleasure Palace Space Station.
After giving her the intel, where he more or less admitted to wanting to destroy Huge-Ass
Fax's gang and potentially the Undercity.
Janet Blowjob let Patrick know that he's welcome to stay in the guest room in his suite, where
he can play video games and rest up before tomorrow, where he'll meet Huge-Ass Fax himself.
Meanwhile, Blowtoss and Ray met with the scientist Ebenezer Keech in the GUTS station, in the
command station of the GUTS, who was somewhat underwhelming.
He didn't see anything too unusual about the snake that was uh, had all the sexy holes in it and sent our boys away
However, his assistant, the red-headed Reddy
Offered to give them more insight into what the scientists might be hiding by moving further into the guts
However, it seems that this may have been a trap. As soon as the boys slid down, went into the fucking thing
They slid down a chute deep into the guts of the ship.
Shit, wait.
What did you write, fucking thing?
No, I was just remembering, I was trying to remember.
I realized that I missed a part, so.
(laughing)
Where they sat upon a pile of discarded toys
and scattered flesh and corpse matter.
And worst of all, a terrifying sexual tentacle monster
was here to take down these fearless parents
of an erstwhile penguin.
What does erstwhile mean?
Oh shit.
You tell us, you wrote it.
You better know off the top of your head what that means,
otherwise this is the most embarrassing moment in your life.
- It's like, um, like a--
- It's like while you were--
- What was.
It's like what was, like a,
like a, what was a penguin.
If I'm, oh shit, maybe I don't know what it means.
- As I just now realized I don't know what it means.
I've probably read that word a trillion times.
- Yeah, you read a lot.
- I've read basically everything.
- Yeah, like former, yeah.
- I've probably read that word two times.
- I looked it up, made sure, yeah, it's like former.
Like what was.
- Okay, I would've read that.
- See, there's a difference that 30 makes.
- I don't know why I wrote erstwhile though.
He is a penguin.
I guess I was just feeling myself.
- He's a hybrid.
- I guess he was a penguin at one point.
- Combatant.
- He's barely anything.
- That's why I wrote it, 'cause he was a penguin.
- No, you used it correctly.
- Yeah, I think it's--
- I was a penguin.
- I wasn't trying to undermine you.
- And then you guys put a water bottle on his head
and put his brain in there.
- Oh yeah, he has a water bottle.
- He was a--
- Hey wait, what does he sound like?
- Oh yeah, that's good.
- Yeah, let's get the tentacle monster out on the field
You're gonna you guys are gonna roll for initiative. Holy fuck tentacle monster
Yeah, you Jinx. I'm a you're a 10 tackle monster cuz I'll tackle you 10 times
I'll tickle you on your 10 toes get up 11. I do
Wanna play 5 to 10 of your toes in my mouth
You need to stop stacking blocks man. Okay, who made the blocks fall so you're not in this scene. It's you -
- Whoa, that is cool.
- You're amazing.
- You're a G.
- Fuck.
(laughing)
- You guys are probably about, let's get the,
yeah, so each of these squares, as you guys usually know,
are about five feet each.
You have your move set.
Let's get the D20s out, let's roll initiative.
I will roll, yeah, let's--
- Stop being same timing as me.
- Me.
- Fuck.
- All right.
- Not a very good initiative by the tentacle.
- Okay, well I'm going to be--
- Okay, if Caleb and me roll the same initiative--
- Roll the same initiative at the same time.
- I'm going to kill myself!
(laughing)
- 15.
- 10.
- Oh my god, I saw the one, I got worried.
- Plus, add your decks.
- Oh shit, wait.
- Your initiative.
- 12 total.
- Oh, and I have a negative three decks.
- Fuck you.
- I actually do have negative one, so.
- That's too bad.
- 14.
- The bugs that could have been.
- You still go first, though.
- Let's try it.
- You still got first, Ray.
- Well good, I'm the only fucking person
on the board right now, so.
- Where is me?
- Let's do this thing!
- Oh, my guy's laying in a stain.
- Come on, bros, let's do this.
- So, as you see a tentacle monster come into frame,
you also now notice that there are like, human guys.
(laughing)
- Okay.
- Wait, let me take a look at this end.
- I think I do notice that.
Human guys, you note section.
- Attached to the tentacle monster.
- Human guys.
- And they are attached, like they're gripping it,
and their pants are down.
- Oh.
- And their heads are kind of exorcist
all the way turned around,
and they're looking at you,
and their eyes are rolled to the back of their head.
- Do not be about to make me say
not me fighting a tentacle monster with the gripper.
Do not.
- I don't actually got a list track of what you wanted me to
- Don't make me say not me fighting the monster
with the gripper.
- Okay. - Yeah.
Don't make me say not me fighting the grip reaper monster
with the tentacles.
- The grip reaper should be the name.
- The gorilla grip reaper.
Not me, don't say, don't I say not me saying that.
Or not me doing that.
- Ray, what do you wanna do?
- I want to join in.
- You wanna join?
- Well this is for human guys, clearly.
And you're not really a computer guy.
You think I don't like pussy?
- It's not pussy.
- You saying I don't like pussy?
- You think that's pussy?
- Definitely.
- It's tentacles.
- You sexually harassed me in the very first episode.
- I love, I love pussy.
- You don't like pussy.
- I fucking.
- You fucking hate it.
- I love pussy.
- Okay, maybe you do, but your character wouldn't.
- No, I hate pussy.
My character loves pussy.
- And plus this isn't pussy.
- Well then I'm going.
- Maybe you have some twisted idea.
- All right, then I guess I'll kill it.
- It's, you know, there's a few kinds of orifices.
- I'm gonna use a sexual grenade.
- Wait, describe the orifices.
- So there are a number of tentacles, as we know,
on tentacle monsters, upwards of eight.
Each, four of them have--
- Don't tell me they all have their own fucking health bar.
- Okay. - No, no, no, nothing like that.
- But they have special abilities, each different?
- I'm not gonna say that they don't.
- And they all have individual personalities?
- That they don't have.
They all have the same personalities.
- They do. - And it's,
don't tell me that it's a beholder.
- No, that-- - Damn.
and a whole, like, whole--
- I'm a little mad that it's not a Beholder.
- Don't tell me that I--
- I could have called it that,
but I probably should have called it that.
- Or a Behold Her.
- Yeah.
- I didn't come up with it.
- Okay, well, I just rolled a nat 20,
so are you going to acknowledge this?
- Are you throwing a sexual grenade?
- Yeah.
- Damn, that's gonna, yeah, I mean, that's gonna crit,
so roll crit for that.
- What does that mean?
- So look up the damage. - I don't have any
of my info on here.
- Oh.
- Because it just says--
- What does it just say?
It says plus 9 to the attack and 0 plus fire.
0 plus fire.
Man, I mean, it says this.
I think it's 2d8, if I'm correct, for a regular hit.
Can we take a look at it?
You want me to take a look at it?
All right, so I forgot that I left the sheet at home again,
so I got to use the roll 21.
So I know it's being targeted.
It's all my fault.
Yep, and I don't even get to write.
Oh, this looks a lot better now than they used to have this.
Cool.
So free advertising is also something that you're doing.
- Well I didn't say what the app was we're looking at.
- No, while we're at it.
- Can you open up Caleb's messages
while you have that in front of the camera?
- I will not do that.
I'm way too respectful.
- Okay.
- Joke's on you.
- Why does it just say zero?
- My phone's too little to read anything on it.
- It is too little.
This should say 2D8.
I mean, I just know off the top of my head.
I'm just not going with that.
- Okay, well I'm glad that you wasted all of our time.
- All right, I was gonna double check.
But okay, so you're gonna roll 4D8.
- 4D8?
- 48.
- No, don't. - No, come on.
All right. - Yeah, no you come on.
- Seven.
- Okay.
- A three.
- All right.
Keep it up.
- A four.
And a 519.
- That's beautiful. - Nice.
- That's gonna be a pretty hefty hit.
- That is a very hefty hit.
So yeah, you throw your sexual grenade, and you just--
- So that's gotta go, so this thing has a head?
- No, it's kind of indistinct.
- It's like tentacles and then like--
- Yeah, wait, did you describe the orifices
and I spaced out?
- Yeah, a little bit.
So I just didn't get to finish really.
No, it's fine.
So it has like phallic ends on some of the tentacles.
- We didn't have to go there.
- And more orifices.
- Also, I don't know what that means.
- Me neither.
- Like ends on the ends of the other tentacles.
And then it has like a couple of other slit zones
- On its body. - Slits.
- Slit zone, slits. - Yeah, slits.
- And you see some like,
sort of like, what's the word I'm looking for here?
- Sniz spots.
- Sniz. - Dribblers.
- No, just like, kind of like malformed
or like unformed eyes. - Weeping wounds.
- Inchoate, maybe, eyes.
- Vestigial.
- Yeah, vestigial's a good way of putting it, right?
- Percy does erstwhile, now inchoate.
- Like, they're just like, they're just not fully--
- What does inchoate mean?
- It means not fully formed.
- Again, I just don't know.
- I always thought it was in show it.
- Oh, 'cause it has CH in it.
I guess I say, I don't know,
I've never listened to the lady saying on Google.
- I've never listened to many words.
- Can you guys just think of the fucking,
the truckers and the electricians who listen to this show
and how they don't know what this bullshit means.
- Stop reading out bruh loudly.
- Listen, it doesn't matter what this thing look like,
because I'm turning around to you
and the sports fans will appreciate this.
I'm drawing a play on my chest, right?
- Yeah.
- So I'm like, you go this way.
- I have a plan already.
And I'm writing on my chest, I have a plan already.
- Okay, so you're completely--
- But I'll take whatever you say
and maybe I'll add it to my plan,
but my plan is pretty well formed.
- I basically just draw like a--
- And I'm still writing that whole sentence.
- I draw like a completely,
like just nonsense sort of Madden 2006 play
on my, that just has a bunch of lines on my chest,
but I pretend it's a football play.
- It's never nonsense.
- And then I crack the grenade, I pull the pin,
and toss a perfect fucking Brady bomb.
- Nice.
- Right directly into this bitch's hole.
- Yeah, I love it, yeah.
And she, 'cause it, yeah,
that's always a she if you throw it there.
- And I make it not.
- That's right.
And yeah, no, it just screams in pain.
- That's the same shit.
- Yeah, it's pretty bad.
And she is gonna also have to roll a,
you know, with a crit 20, do I just let that happen?
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Right, I kinda do.
I think it makes sense.
- What are you gonna do against a crit 20?
- 'Cause the only thing was like,
there's usually extra sticky damage
so, or to stop the movement.
So yeah, I'll say that there is.
- Stinky damage?
- No, sticky.
So yeah, her movement's also,
or their movement is also just sort of like,
hampered right now.
So now let's go to blow toss.
When we hit the end of this round, by the way,
we'll cut to you.
We'll do kind of a little editing.
- Yeah, that'll be great.
- Yeah.
- We'll do the (imitates blowing)
- Yeah, we'll do a little bit of (imitates blowing)
- Okay, so my plan.
- Yeah, go ahead and show us, genius.
- Okay, so here, I'll do a diagram.
Oh, there's already something on here.
- Yeah, you should put a diaphragm.
- Mini mouse fetter.
- That's right.
(laughing)
- I'm a feet of feather, yeah.
- Here's my plan here.
I'm gonna draw it right here on the table.
- Yeah.
- So this is the tentacle monster.
Okay, and this is its gash.
- Okay, and this is me.
Hi, I'm waving. - Okay, hi.
- I run here all the way up.
- Those listening at home, he's drawing himself,
and he's drawing a little line.
- Running into the gash.
- Not into it, running up to it.
And then this is my pipe, my lead pipe,
not my pipe, but so basically it will go like this,
and it's gonna go like uh, uh, like uh, uh, uh, uh.
- So he's drawing sort of like action lines now.
Like here, I'll do it like here.
Like that's the gash.
And then I'm like, uh, uh.
Wait, sorry, let me do this.
- He's sort of drawing like a separate plane.
- Type it up.
- Yeah, 'cause I get two attacks,
so I can at least do uh, uh.
So that's my plan.
So I'll roll for that.
- Starting to think that this is the best night of my life.
- Okay, that's an eight plus seven.
- And he ate it?
- 15.
- Oh shit.
- As you run up to, you're gonna need to roll
a dexterity saving throw.
Come on, tentacle monster, you know what's up.
You know what's happening here.
- Yeah, I guess I should've known
about the dexterity throw.
That's 18.
- Yeah, you're fine.
I mean, yeah, you duck, you weave,
but the 15, you don't really quite connect.
- I missed the hole.
Yeah, we've all been there.
- Yeah, right.
- Yeah.
- Into the thigh.
- Sometimes it happens, man.
- I mean, you've got--
- It happens to the best.
(laughing)
- I hear the inside of the thigh.
- I hear some of the best fuckers in the world.
- Just get it right into the bed frame.
- Oh wait, no, I have advantage
'cause that hasn't taken a turn yet.
Or right, 'cause I'm an assassin.
- You're taking advantage of this first attack?
- Or is it when you don't have a turn?
- It's when it hasn't had a turn yet, I think.
- Oh, heavens, yeah.
- Okay, then roll.
- Right, I don't know where that is,
but I'm almost certain.
- It should be on the right there, on the.
- Oh yeah, advantage on attack rolls
against any creature that hasn't taken a turn.
- I apologize, thank you for remembering.
- I'm glad I remembered.
Okay, that is an 18.
- Yeah, and that hits.
- Okay, and then any hit is a critical hit.
- I gotta nerf that a little bit.
All right, go.
- Okay, so that's five plus, whoa.
- Christ almighty. - Damn.
- Okay, 17 plus four, that's 21.
For my first attack.
- Blackjack. - So that's in out.
- Yeah. - That's in out.
super painful uh-huh wow no you're beating this thing up
this is pleasure damage so this tacks up separately
wait he just said you're beating it up
I'm actually beating it up?
yes you are actually
does the thing's fucking hymen burst?
I just rolled a 20
just fucking spills hymen blood
so I get a double crit
this is pretty rough for the tentacle monster
ok 7 plus
10 is 17
that's another 21 damage
so that's 42 damage
So can I go in and out 42 times? Can that be the representation of that?
Uh, uh, uh, uh.
Yeah, so you just take your double pipes and just go...
Yeah. Oh my god. That was an amazing sound. Thank you.
That's lots of women who have machines that do that to themselves.
Which is strange. I don't really get that, man.
Yeah, I'd rather have a like kind of a small unassuming one I could take
wherever, if they look through my luggage it's not immediately obvious, it's like
penis-shaped.
- I want a sex toy so small someone might assume
that I'm just trying to like cheat at chess.
- I want, you know what I want?
I want a sex toy that I can, it's a vibrator,
and I put it in the palm of my hand,
and it's, the vibrations kind of conduct
through my bone and body, and it can vibrate
me down below, but it doesn't even have to be in my hands.
- It vibrates so fast on your hands.
- It just travels down my arm.
(laughing)
- And in your chest.
- And it might cause a heart murmur.
- And in your chest like Tony Stark.
- I want something that resets my defibrillator.
Like, yeah, right.
So that's a very, very good first turn from you two.
- This thing's dead.
- This thing is not looking good.
I mean, she has a healthy amount of HP,
but after you went in with the fucking
double pipes like that. - Oh, I went in.
- Yeah, you see the guy that is like attached to it
just going (gurgling)
like he is-- - Oh.
- Like he just wanted-- - 'Cause he had
a gay experience.
- He's having a gay experience.
- They are having mutual orgasm.
- That is fucking romantic. - That is also painful.
- Yeah, it is, it's beautiful.
And now it is the tentacles' turn.
- Bitch.
- Yep, that's right. - Bitch.
- And almost like in like retaliation and like a fear,
they're going to just like,
you're gonna watch 'em congeal,
like sort of like squish in,
and then just launch out,
and all this gas just flies everywhere.
Both of you guys-- - Oh, pussy gas?
- Both of you-- - There's gas flying everywhere?
the famous pussy
- Yeah, snowflake. - Not me catching it
like that booth you get in the money's all sticks to you.
(laughing)
- Reaching around.
- If you just land it on my tongue.
- Nope. - You could do that
or you could roll a-- - I got my butterfly net.
(laughing)
- Or you could roll a constitution saving throw.
- No, I fucking, I cheat. - Jesus, Jesus.
- I cheat the whole fucking thing.
- Yeah, take it to the face. - One hit.
(laughing)
- I face the entire room. - Just take it to the face.
Okay, cool.
(laughing)
- I love it.
- If he faces the entire room, am I safe?
- Yeah, he's safe.
I literally, one pull.
- I'm gonna space the entire fucking room
of gas, juice, and smoke.
- What'd you roll, by the way?
- Oh, I didn't roll anything.
I thought he was saving me.
- Are you both gonna chief it?
- No, I'm chiefing it.
I'm literally pulling the entire thing.
- All right, all right.
- I'll still roll.
- I want you to, I'm very open to you trying.
That's gonna be, let's think about this.
Is that strength?
Like with longs?
- I'll wait to take a breath in
to see if he can clear the entire room.
- I guess it is constitution.
- That's gotta be constitution.
- It's gotta be just con, right?
I'm gonna take also the strength of pulling it all in.
It has to take some fucking ab strength, but.
- Seven.
- It's not quite enough.
(laughing)
- No.
- Even with your con, no.
- So I just take a deep breath though.
- Yeah, yeah, you do get, you will have to deal with it.
You're up though.
- 19.
- You're safe.
So you--
- Yeah, I'm like, my eyes, my eyes.
- You think he saves you though too, right?
- I have the high eye, I've got red eyes,
so I'm just like.
- Damn.
- You just feel butterflies in your stomach
and then you feel your eyelids kinda get heavy
and you kinda go, you kinda like swoon and fall over.
- That doesn't sound like something that I would--
- Pussy put him to sleep.
- And you're, yep. - Pussy put me in a coma.
- Yeah, and yeah. - Okay, that's fine.
- Your computer, like your demon is still awake.
- Yeah. - But your computer awakes.
- Well, he never sleeps, you know.
- Pussy and your demon awakes.
- Your demon's awake.
- He never sleeps, he always just sits there and does that.
- That is what happens to me, I inhale,
I inhale the pussy smell,
and the robot part of my brain goes to sleep.
- And the demon wakes up.
(laughing)
- The analytical part of my brain, it turns off.
- Right brain?
- That brain.
- The creative side.
- The alphabetical side.
- Tell me, motherfucker, how much damage I take.
- You don't take anything.
- Good.
- Instead, a tentacle reaches out and grabs you.
Don't care.
- Okay, now you're gonna take some damage.
- So, can I have a D10?
- You have everything right here.
- No, if I can't see it, then you hide it.
- No, don't roll it for me.
- That's not even the right dice.
- That was close though.
- Dice?
Why'd you say it cool?
- I have an X and I traveled.
- Oh damn, I forgot.
- Wait, oh I forgot to do that.
Wait, give me these.
- You take, those are my Warby's.
Hands off my Warby's.
- Hey guys, who am I?
(laughing)
- Stop, come on, I don't sound like that.
- I don't do that.
- The Riddler.
- No, I'm him.
- Oh!
- You take, you take, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh.
- Shut up.
- Yeah, you take 11 damage.
- Yeah, whatever, good.
All right, I'm at 24 damage, or health.
And also you are now grabbed by this thing you're grappled and you're knocked out is my head backwards
And I'm fucking coming into her shit like that not yet, but it seems like you might be happening
Yeah, the good thing of that body next to you like while you're passing like hey
He's saying hi to you
Mo bro the thief from the Bible. What's his name?
Which thief the thief that Jesus was crucified with Oh?
What do they call Barbara? Yeah, Barbara? What do they call him? They say there's something thief
Is the Bible stuff with Bible shit like me?
What does a Bible men do not despise a thief if he steal to satisfy his soul when he is hungry
You have to pick up your microphone if you're gonna talk. I don't know if I agree with that. I'm actually fine with this
But speaking of not being in the scene now you are in the scene, so we're cutting away my mic
Wait can we do sort of a mr.. Show transition?
Yeah, and I'll keep and can we do sort of a mr.. Show transition, and I'll pick up what Caleb was saying well
He does the instruction is the mr.. Is the mr.. Show
Transition I don't remember what it was I mean like I think is it just similar
I have only seen a couple episodes of mr.. Show, and it's been a long time is it similar the Monty Python
I asked if movie transition just kind of move into the next sketch
I let's just go to Pat base on the last sketch so Pat you are in
The guest room running around in the lair of facts. Yeah, he's doing a task. He's doing a task
I was a lap of the laptops laptops dying. Yeah, you're you're in though
So you are you said last time you and you were playing video games in the guest room?
Patrick you're the one who has to be on we talk about the guest room. I thought you were trying to plug it in
What what game are you playing is baby playing with I'm playing it's it's
charades for the Atari 2600.
- Charades for the Atari.
There's only like three options.
- Yeah.
- Like, yeah.
- It's the worst game in the world.
- Yeah, it's like you and baby Gat are playing charades.
- It just shows you what you're supposed to act out
on the screen.
- It's just a slide show, basically.
Costs like $150 when it came out.
- It shows you what you're supposed to act out,
but like everyone else in the room can see it.
(laughing)
- It's cool.
- You're,
yeah, you're Geena Davis again.
- Yep.
- How do they want you to--
- There's only three options in the game.
- You know what, how would you act that out?
That's what I wanna know.
Okay, so to just make your lips different,
and your eyes.
Okay, so to, okay, Geena Davis.
- Yep, got that one again.
- Roll a perception check.
- This sounds really fun, I wish I was in this scene
instead of the fighting scene.
- I'm pretty much sick of face fucking the squid.
- I got a dirt, I got 12 and then my perception is eight.
- Yeah, dirty 20.
With that dirty 20, you hear something,
so you're in the room--
- I hear a dirty thing.
- You hear a dirty thing.
You're in a room, the room adjacent to
Janet Blowjob's room.
This is like the guest room off of Her.
- And you know it's gonna be dirty if it's Her.
- That's right, 'cause of the name.
So you hear something move of,
you hear something move,
and then you hear kind of a metal scraping against metal
in that other room, and if you remember,
that's usually the sign that the killer is near Frederick,
just so you know.
- Oh, what if it is a Freddy Krueger type?
That's good.
- Wait, wait, hold on.
- That's a Christmas sweater.
- We have to guess every time.
- It could be gloved.
I like everything every we already guessed that it was Santa Claus we guess maybe a hundred things
Yeah, but now I'd like to amend my guest and say that it now that we're further away from Christmas
I'm gonna guess it's Mike burbiglia. Oh
My god the sleepwalking he's sleepwalking and it's a dream. I look at his face. It's my
It's fucking Mike for I he cannot believe that I just did this to him. I figured this out now. Yeah, that's what I thought
It's my per big lady. Yeah walker
Okay, yeah, my guess it's a guy with metal okay, so I run out of the room, and I'm wearing a shirt
This is Joey bag of doughnuts. Yeah
That's what they used to call his brother patches
Okay, whatever
You run into the room and you don't okay, what do you I don't actually do that okay?
So I hear the metal on metal, right? That's right. And I'm in... Yeah, what's Slayer playing over another band? Megadeth.
Metal expert Cameron.
Like Slayer twice?
Okay. I don't feel like thinking of another band. Why would you?
I couldn't read his mind, could I? I couldn't use Yoda's mind to see.
That's a little bit of a leading question. On whomst?
On whoever is up there. What is wrong with you tonight?
The middle on the middle. It is Meme Wednesday.
Oh shit. I forgot to send him.
We'll send him after. We will flood the group chat. Open the floodgates. Release the Kraken.
Oh, that would be a good one to use.
Maybe, okay, I don't have like a...
- Brain?
(laughing)
- Damn.
- What are you trying to do?
- I'm on, I'm trying to see, I'm trying to see,
like, okay, so it's past my room, right?
- Past your bedtime.
- Okay, so I'm gonna poke my head out of the door.
- Yeah, for sure.
- You do that, and you don't see anything
too unusual in the room right now.
It looks similar to what you saw before,
you just see the nanobots kinda cleaning and tidying up.
- You said I heard metal on metal in the hallway,
not her room, right?
- No, in her room.
- In her room, okay, okay. - 'Cause you gotta get
adjacent to her room.
But what you will notice, she's not there anymore.
And she was there when you last were there.
But that's it.
- So she's not in her room?
- No.
There are the bots in there.
- But there's metal on metal sounds.
- You heard that.
You can investigate, you can try to do it.
- Yeah, I'll roll investigation.
- Yeah, roll investigation.
Let's see what you got, brother.
- That's a six.
- That is a six plus. - It's a six.
It's a knife.
It is eight.
- Okay.
- You don't notice anything too curious.
- I'm gonna roll persuasion and say,
if there's anybody in here, get your ass out right now!
- Go for it.
- That will work.
(laughing)
- If there was somebody here, they will never come back.
- I feel like you need more dire consequences.
- Isn't that what you want?
It's a killer.
You don't want 'em to come back.
- Yeah, all I'm saying is if you say a one--
Yeah, he should die.
Well, I didn't say there was a killer in the room or not.
Who says?
Well, now we know there isn't.
You said there's metal on metal.
Are you trying to create--
Wait, OK, now that I'm thinking logically,
there can't be a killer in the room.
Because if you rolled a one, he would
die if there was a killer in the room.
Yeah, definitely.
And also, we live on a fucking-- or we're
staying on a fucking fully metal ship.
Meta gaming.
I'm not metal gaming.
Metal gaming.
You're the one metal-- trying to game metal on us.
You're trying to change our--
Scraping metal on metal.
I'm going to roll--
You're trying to make me afraid of metal.
I'm gonna roll deception and say I was just kidding about that last thing.
Okay.
And that is a 17.
I mean so you've been yelling this in a room, the nanobots when they first-
And I'm gonna roll religion and pray to God that there's nobody in here.
Okay, whatever's going on here is a clusterfuck but it's still a better love story than Twilight.
I couldn't agree more.
That's a 15.
What did you get?
What?
I have a 15 for the religion.
you like your God cough a little bit.
I mean like, I don't know, like there's just,
you're just kind of like pleading to,
from what you can tell, just the nanobots
who are pissing themselves clean.
- Why don't you go find, she got killed.
And so solve that.
- She didn't get killed.
- She was there and then she got gone.
What do you mean?
- She didn't get killed?
- What do you mean?
- She's around.
- She clearly got killed.
Why don't you go get that her?
- You're both talking strange.
- What?
- Get that her.
- I didn't say get that, Herb.
- You did.
- No, and if I did, that's within the margin of error.
(laughing)
That you're allowed to say stuff like that,
'cause you knew what I meant.
- This is what happens when you kick back a couple of pints.
(laughing)
- Whilst, whilst to steal a throw.
- Dude, I have had a third of this white claw
and I'm feeling a little plastered.
- Yeah, look at his cup too, that's filled with vodka.
- No, don't look at that.
- That's beer vodka.
- Don't look at what's in there.
- One of the nanobots comes up to you and says,
"Can I help you, sir?"
(screaming)
It's nano, it's small.
It's head pops up in the air, it spins around and lands back on his head and you're like,
"Whoa!"
Holy shit!
This guy's cool.
Okay.
Can I help you sir?
I can tell you're a silly kind of guy.
Can you tell him he recruited this guy?
Bring this guy onto the team.
You're on my team, what is your name?
You're on my team.
That's what I say when I meet cool people.
You are on my team, my friend, what is your name?
You're joining my party.
Scooter.
Scooter?
- Scooter. - Scooter.
- We need this guy. - Dude, come on.
- Wait, what can you do to turn into a scooter?
- I just clean, mostly.
- Okay, you're the cleaner.
- Scooter to the cleaner. - Scooter to the cleaner.
- Okay.
- And do you have any kind of assassination stuff you do?
- I could probably crawl into somebody and beat 'em up.
- Into somebody?
- Yeah, I'm real little.
- Oh yeah, okay, you're on my team.
What do you need me to do?
- I haven't thought about anything past this.
- Okay.
- Oh, I was looking for Janet.
- Oh, I'm not allowed to tell you where she went.
I'm sorry.
- Okay, but now that you're my teammate, you can tell me.
- He's thinking about it.
Roll persuasion.
- That's a good, that's gotta be advantage.
- He made you part of his team.
- He made me part of his team.
- Oh, wait, with advantage I can roll again.
- It's gotta be advantage.
Oh my god a 21. Wow.
Yeah sure just yeah.
You didn't even know that was going to happen when you said you were on my team.
So that wasn't meta gaming.
That is how it is done.
And also I just screwed her the cleaner.
Oh my god.
Juvio can you just put the camera on me for a second just so I can get it.
It's a living.
You do kind of remind me of one of those Flintstone birds.
Yeah?
What is it about me?
Just your attitude and your body.
(laughing)
- Your purpose.
- Yeah.
- That's true.
The purpose part feels real.
Yeah, so with that 21 that you bullied me into,
but I'm allowing, so that's on me, really.
I'm blaming the victim here.
- Yeah.
- Scooter, he, he's a guy.
Scooter says--
- What's up with you, this whole episode
you've been saying he, they, she, just, you know.
- Well, the--
- These are all--
- Do you have something you wanna tell us?
- The sex beast doesn't really have a gender,
but I can understand.
- But then it's a beast, it's an it, it's a bear.
- Oh, they still have like a sense of self, right?
- Maybe they don't. - I don't think so.
It's a tentacle monster. - I guess that's true.
Probably isn't an it. - Everybody just takes
it turn face fucking.
You think that that has a sense of self?
- I think anything that gets fucked that much is an it.
- You think Anna Nicole Smith has a sense of self?
That's what I'm trying to understand here.
- Anna Nicole Smith. (laughing)
- Showing my age. - That is amazing, yeah.
- Yeah, well I guess, who could I, Riley Reid?
She's even kinda old.
- Marilyn Monroe.
- Yeah, I would've gone Marilyn Monroe.
- Lillian Gish.
- You take that, hussy Marilyn Monroe.
- Yeah, Lillian Gish.
- I don't wanna, that's a third rail topic these days
'cause of the movie that came out like three years ago
in our time.
So yeah, with that 21, Scooter says,
well, since we're on the same team, man.
- Yeah, high five.
Yeah, he pulls his little hand out for a high five and I smack it. Oh, it's so hard that he flops
You're trying to get him to tell you man
She she she sometimes goes behind the bed
What?
That is sexual
Okay, I'm gonna pull the bed back. Okay. You pull the bed back. Oh wait. No. There's a button somewhere isn't there
No, when you pull the bed back, okay, it just glides and makes him like no sound
Wait show the
Give me toy camera. He definitely the cleaner Wow he's a spider with hands
He's a nano, but you know what I'm gonna call him from now on because you're drawing clank
Looks like head that's head
You drew clanks head
- Give him a nose. - Give him another antenna.
- So I go-- - Now he's a bug.
- Nose will make him different.
- There we go. - There we go.
- Now you drew a bug.
(laughing)
- That's not a bug.
- A bug with hands. - So I go behind the bed.
- You don't see anything like that.
I would say you could probably look at it more closely.
Let's-- - Wait, I pull it back
and it glides?
- The bed just kinda glides over, it makes no sound.
- I'm gonna ask Scooter, I'm like,
how does she go behind the bed?
- Well, she'll go behind it and then--
- Press a button.
- Not a button.
- Pull a lever.
- Something like that.
- Do a code thing.
Pressure plate, book.
- It's sort of like a pressure plate.
- Metal scraping on metal.
A secret door opening.
Yes, she, yeah, opened one.
She opened the door.
- My guess is she is it.
- You know, I've been playing the new Harry Potter game
so I know this one.
You should use the spell.
Reveleo.
Use Reveleo.
I use Reveleo.
OK, yeah.
Roll a d20.
Two.
It doesn't work.
OK, I'm going to use Reveleo again.
All right.
14.
What do I do?
It works.
Oh.
OK, you can cut to the end.
No, what do you want to do?
So you see the panel there.
Well, I used Reveleo.
No, you don't use-- stop that.
You don't use Reve--
There we go.
He's standing up for himself.
I like this.
OK.
Thanks, man.
So I'm gonna investigate the room for like a
button or a lever or a shelf
that has a book that makes a lever book.
Yeah. Look for a lever book. And it's always a title with delicious irony.
The Hidden Key. Yes. That was a 10.
You do find a book called The Hidden Key, but there's just like weed in it.
Yeah. Just a pipe in it.
- It's carved out. - And it's a one hitter.
(laughing)
- All right, that's a good idea.
- We could make millions. - Yeah, she's 13.
Try to hide it from her parents.
- Okay, so that didn't work.
- Yeah.
- What else, should I roll insight?
- There might not be much else you can do right now.
- I'm gonna roll another investigation.
- What are you gonna investigate?
- You should be a private detective.
- Yeah, I am in the--
- What are you gonna investigate before you roll?
Talk to me. - Again for another lever.
- No, you can't do that.
- Okay, then I'm investigating.
- It's like you failed a check.
Hey, Pat, try this.
Open Sesame.
- I'm gonna investigate if there's a voice-activated
Open Sesame code.
- Or you could just say Open Sesame.
- Yeah.
- Which one of those are you doing?
- He's got the worst rolls ever, he just rolled a four.
- Okay.
- You say you, you go Open,
you don't like, you just fuck it up, yeah.
- Open Semily.
All right, I'm just gonna start
Shooting my gun around. That's a good idea somewhere the light bleeds. Don't have a gun okay knock on the wall, and yeah
I'm gonna start eating things with my hoagie, okay
I'm just running around the road just hitting shit
Nanobots are panicking now. You just they just cleaned everything and you're knocking shit around. Oh, yeah, that's they can clean it up
He's on my team now. He can clean it up. They don't have anything else better to do there
I mean, that's what yeah, that's what they're trying to do baby
Maybe Gadd opens the door and he's just like, "What are you doing?"
"Shut up!"
"Stop."
"Shut your mouth!"
"You're gonna fuck it up!"
"You're...
Fuck you!
I'm gonna do nothing!"
"You're gonna fuck it up!
We're about to get rich!"
"What?"
"We're giving them vital information.
Don't fuck up her room!"
"There's a lady in the...
Behind the bed!
In a wall!"
"I don't give a shit!"
"Or the floor!
Is it the wall of the...
Is it the wall or the floor?
You're on my team now.
You have to tell me."
"Um...
I mean, it's just behind the bed.
I don't give a shit!"
tell me I mean it's just behind the bed I
don't we don't really just stop just
just just can you look into this later
just wait till I'm out of the you got
to help me look for it now okay what do
you want me to do look for a lever or a
button or an entrance there's a door the
door we came into shit okay yeah we'll
cut back from this to you guys now
- Another turn.
- There we go.
- You're at the top of the order.
- 40 minutes in and we're starting
our second round of combat.
- Yeah, that's right.
- Let's go.
I'm going to use, wait, I've been taken though, right?
- Taken.
- Like, yeah, I was gonna say like the--
- I'm stuck in that guy, right?
- Oh, yeah. - In the tentacle guy?
- Yeah, you wake up this round.
- Okay, so I can do something.
- Yeah.
- Okay, since I'm close--
- But what you have to do basically is,
you're restrained right now.
So you could roll a strength check to break out
and that's about it right now.
- That's all I can do?
- 'Cause everything you do requires--
- Yeah, all right.
I'll roll a strength check.
- These puppies' hands, you know.
- Okay, but plus zero on strength.
I think that these stats are outdated.
- They actually might be a little bit.
- Yeah, I got a three.
- Even if we add it, 'cause they are outdated
'Cause your strength is actually, I think, a plus three now, by the way.
But, regardless.
So I'm still stuck.
You're stuck.
Can I, like, bite?
Um, you know what? Why not go for it?
Let's do an unarmed attack.
Okay.
Just roll a d20 again?
Roll a d20 and we'll add your new strength.
Wow!
Okay, 19 plus 3, 22.
Okay, roll a d4.
Oops.
I will roll...
A one!
Okay.
And I will roll...
He's able to still like hold you.
Um...
Let that do one thing.
But you do do...
Four damage.
And they're not...
It's not looking good. I'm gonna just start saying it.
I'm sorry guys.
It's not looking good. It's looking pretty
fucked up.
I think it looks good.
I'm feeling...
Mmmhmmm.
- Oh. - Botas, what are you doing?
- Pipe, crit one. - You got a crit one.
- Two. - You swing your pipe at it
and you kinda like-- - Swing.
- You trip over one of the tentacles and you're knock prone.
But you can still get up and try to attack again.
- Okay, I'm gonna get up. - Does he get up,
you know how some people get up butt first, does he do that?
He like slides his butt up to look like an inchworm first
and then you get up. - And I go.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- And as you're doing that, roll dexterity saving throw.
- And then when I stand up,
I take one hand off the ground first,
and I'm like three down on the ground.
And as I stand up, I like drag my hand across the ground
towards my legs, and I go up my leg.
- Fuck dexterity, you got some sex there for me.
- And then I go up like this.
- Well let's first see if you dodge.
- And I go like this.
(singing)
- You are a fucking amazing diva.
You are a fucking amazing singer.
- Which is a song I wrote last night,
which I shouldn't be premiering on this episode.
But I'm hoping nobody catches that.
And I can try to attack again?
- First you're gonna roll a dexterity saving throw.
- Okay.
That is a 20.
- You didn't roll that, you plopped that.
- I can roll it again.
- You're a plopper.
- That was a roll, I rolled it in my hand.
- I don't give a fuck.
- As you're getting up, the tentacle was swiping to get you
and you managed to dodge out of the way.
- I really can't sing that again.
- Yeah, right, sorry.
- I'm sorry for making you do that.
- And now I'm gonna try to attack again.
It plopped again, that's the same number,
but I rolled it in my hand.
What do you think? - You have bad technique.
- What do you think? - You have bad technique.
- Can I, if it's-- - You can take it,
but you need to be rolling out.
You're rolling, you're plopping.
- I tried, I even thought, I even tried that time.
- Yeah, don't plop.
- He's a plopper.
- He's a plopper. - Do you want me to re-roll it?
- No, don't re-roll it, it's fine.
- Why are you being a drama queen?
- I'm not.
(Ian imitates dramatic music)
(laughing)
- That's a 22 though.
- I mean it definitely hits, so roll for damage.
- Okay now watch this, now watch this.
- If these plop, if these plop.
- There we go.
- That is 11 damage.
- Okay, ooh, not looking good, very close.
I almost wrote on my computer.
(laughing)
- That was real close.
- He had one white claw and he just tried
to write on a computer.
- Bro.
- That's not what that was.
I'm not friggin' drunk.
- You're just, it supports my hypothesis about you.
- About that I'm--
- You're just the biggest lightweight
- That's the word of all time.
- You're sloppy, bro.
- I'm a sloppy drunk.
Can I get another one of those, by the way?
- After you tried to draw on your computer?
Yes, dude, we're trying to make a competition.
(laughing)
- Okay, so now it is its turn.
So it is going to do another bit of damage to you, Caleb.
- Great.
- It's gonna be Ray William Johnson.
- Thanks.
- Okay, plus another.
- I already saw the six, so I'll start counting down.
- Yep, does another 12 damage to you.
- Oh fuck. - Jesus Christ.
- Oh, fug.
- And it is now going to--
- I got motherfucking 12 HP.
- Damn, I have 14.
- It is now going to-- - I'm glad you said
it's looking bad.
- It is, lurches back and reveals
its mega hole on the bottom.
- I don't want no big ass hole.
- And you can see that it's--
(laughing)
- Sorry, I just noticed Pat's holding a gun.
- Yeah.
- I'm so unhappy that we found that.
- Me too.
- Somebody dropped it and then I found
where you put the CO2 cartridge.
- That's great.
- Yeah, so we could get a CO2 cartridge
and use that thing as a real fun toy.
- Blow toss, roll a charisma saving throw.
- Charisma saving throw?
Bro, am I literally rolling for Riz today?
- Damn, dude.
- That's a 16.
- Wow. - That's pretty high Riz.
- That's very fortunate. - I'm like this.
Um, yeah, you, yeah, you're giving a troll face.
Troll face.
You're giving the troll face into, as you see, it's, it's the, the whispering eye as the, uh, this, like, it's,
it's real eye is revealed here and you hear like,
[whispering]
And like,
What was that?
I say, I say, pardon?
Yeah.
Come again? Oh, did I say come again?
But it doesn't, it doesn't, uh, it doesn't, uh, uh, envelop you.
And so you're only going to take half damage here.
Okay, I'm still going to die.
Mm-hmm
You'll be fine
Yeah, and then you're fine. Yeah, you got seven you took seven. Okay. I'm only at seven HP
Yes, the way I do half damage folks is I will sometimes slice the number of dice in half and so now it's also
Some you do half damage we're doing I find that no
Interesting half damn no because people do divide a game. Yes, if you know, you know
- Thank you, and some people do know who it was.
- Is it my turn to attack?
- Not yet, 'cause it still gets one more move.
- Great.
- 'Cause it gets two attacks.
- Cool.
- The squeeze on you is just a sort of a passive effect.
And so that not working.
- Bro, this thing fucking you was just completely passive.
It didn't even care.
- Good.
- I'm just a thing to be used, I guess.
- That not working frustrated it,
and it sort of like uses two of its tentacles
from like a back and just kind of like tries to lurch around and like kind of
clap you. Whoa that's actually kind of cool. You're telling me I rizzed on this
thing and it's trying to clap me. Damn. Wow and it got a one and so when it claps it
like like it kind of like there's like a dick one and a pussy one. It did the
wrong one. Does it let me go because of the vibration through its entire body?
I'll let you roll another strength does it does it doesn't get out Tom and Jerry hit with the frying pan
Yeah, very much. That's another three not quite letting you go, but all you knock down is blocks
But now we're back
So sorry you should maybe try being just an adult
Instead of a little kid who plays with blocks. I did bring the blocks onto the
Hey, you put it on why they all in front of him
that I didn't do he's getting angry you should just start your turn okay I'm
good I guess I stop I guess I'm gonna try anything just a strength check again
yeah you should try that okay okay that's a 17 nice yeah you're able to
break out all right but I can't do anything else right no you can you can do
you can do a melee attack okay I was an unarmed melee attack or use your dong
blade all right I'm gonna use my dong boy how apropos yeah super I was just
thinking that's apropos totally it is it's it's ironic isn't it and that's an
eight it is ironic I threw an eight to use a penis blade on a pussy monster it's
very ironic it's a bit ironic a little sarcastic - um yeah it doesn't hit okay
well but blow toss it's your turn okay please kill this thing man I want to get
to the next stage. Okay we're gonna kill it. Okay. I love it this is just a video game.
Eleven. Eleven. You're up. You gotta go again though. Okay twenty. That hits. Okay ten.
Describe your kill. Damage. Yes! Okay so he's still, he's like still, you're
not tangled up in it. Well can you be tangled up in it just for this? And also
I'll give you one extra thing. Okay. One of the holes it's stuck to my mouth like
sucker I don't want that well I do so whatever tangled up right and I'm like
and I go like like who are you Ray William Johnson watch out and I'm like
kind of throw my pole like a javelin and you say watch out but I can't do
anything well you kind of do like you're I don't have a pole here this is my pole
and this and it goes and you kind of like dodge your tummy out of the way a
little bit you suck in your tummy and it goes right by you like it would have
fucking killed you if you didn't suck in your tummy.
And then it goes, also the pipe has balls at the end of it,
and it goes, balls, dang.
(laughing)
And then the monster goes, and the monster goes,
and then it explodes like Mega Man
with all the circles that go out.
- Right.
- Yeah.
Like, doo doo.
- Yeah, and the--
- And then the balls are gone,
'cause I don't want that on my weapon normally.
- That would seem gay.
- Yeah, it just looks like they were on there for a second,
it was a trick of the way but there's not actually ball of soft fluorescence yeah
the guy when this thing like gets stabbed and like slumps over and then it doesn't
and explodes like Mega Man 2 also that also happens it can be Mega Man 1 it
doesn't have to be Mega Man 2. Pretty good. What is up with your cleverness
tonight? It's Riz. Somebody pound him. Cameron better Riz. I'm scared.
said pound him. I'm scared of him. So you, the guy, lands like this thing, this like guy is
spazzing out. Yeah he's doing a cool dance move that I just did. And then his
eyes roll forward and then they kind of just glaze over and he's dead. The guy
that was attached? Hmm. Shame. Wait, but the technical monster. Technical monster is dead as well, very dead. And as that happens you two
hear footsteps coming your way oh my god I'm so scared I'm so scared I'm so
scared and we'll go back to you uh-huh so what are you what are you doing in the
room right now? My heart's gonna be beating this whole time. I've picked up baby Gadd.
and I'm just ramming him into the wall behind the bed.
Show me. Where's the... The you. Yeah. So I have him picked up and I'm just going like
that on the wall. Okay. Stop ramming me! Just like every time you hit him against the
wall. And you do... Does it open the door? No, but you do hear a bit of a hollowness
on certain parts of the wall, towards the bottom of the wall. Towards the bottom, so
it's the floor. Maybe. So now that I hear the hollowness, I start jumping up and
down on the floor. Okay, you still hear the hollowness. Is it getting louder or...?
it's getting it's less loud as you jump up and down the floor so it's on the
wall you gotta these are the things you gotta figure out so it's maybe on the
wall so perhaps it may be behind the wall
or the floor or the floor I don't see him figuring this out I'm gonna be real he
doesn't have to figure it all right you don't have to figure this out it'll keep
going the game then why'd you cut to him because I wanted to resolve whatever
this is for you should kind of you should cut to a cutscene now where he has no
control. That's fair. I think he's giving you no choice. I am going to roll a
suicide threat. I'm gonna say if this door doesn't open right now I'm gonna
fucking kill myself. I can't tell which is real. What'd you get? I got a nine. It's
not very convincing I don't think you're gonna do it uh-huh I don't have a gun
anymore okay
yeah I'm like my breath until something happens in this room baby cat who's just
He's completely beat up.
He's just trying to take the hoagie from you.
Stop it!
You're going fucking crazy!
He's drunk like an accordion.
Yeah, yeah he is.
He's smushed.
He's walking around, he's waddling back and forth.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, he's like, just- Can I roll investigation again?
No, you did it already.
You just didn't get a very high roll.
Can I roll perception?
No, it's not how that works.
Why are you so obsessed with this secret room, man?
Get the fuck out of there!
No, I need to find out where this room goes to.
(sighing)
- All right, well you gotta come up
with some other way to find out.
You need to use your brain here.
Your real brain. - Perception is a brain thing.
- No, no, no, no, don't think in terms of stats.
Think about what you wanna do to try to figure it out.
I'll tell you if there are stats involved.
Think about that. - So there's a hollow part
of the wall.
- We know that, right?
- Can I shoot my, okay, I'm gonna overclock
(laughing)
I'm gonna overclock my hoverboard's engine
and shoot it at the wall.
- That's insane.
- Until it makes a hole. - So insane it--
- Just might work. - That's a long pause,
can I shoot my--
(laughing)
- Well what about here, here, here.
- Can I shoot?
(laughing)
Can I shoot my--
- You can try this out.
- Okay.
- I like that he said overclock, that's kinda fun.
- He did say overclock.
- Yeah.
The price is you have to describe to me what it means to overclock your hoverboard.
There is like a normal skateboard. There's like I have a tool and then there's like a little like
there's like a 3/8 nut on it and I'm just I'm loosening it.
Loosening your nut.
I'm not sure that that is an overclock. You're just loosening the trucks.
To make the trucks wobble so much or to make the hoverboard trucks wobble so much
that when they go really fast it'll kill me.
- But how does it--
(laughing)
- Wait, I thought you were trying to put it into the wall.
- Because if we're going back to the suicide thing,
what's happening?
- Okay, then I tighten them up so that the battery--
- No, no, no, wait, snap it.
- No, no, no, so the battery on the inside
gets overcharged.
- Okay.
- Yeah, there's like a--
- I like you unlocking new things about your hoverboard
that I didn't know.
I'm very into that.
So let's have you try, so roll a ranged attack.
So just roll a hoverboard attack.
I think it's trickier attacks on top.
- Yeah, it's just a one D8 plus one.
- So the plus in the middle, in the middle,
that's gonna be what your attack roll is.
- Okay.
- So look at those numbers in the middle.
What does it say next to the hover board?
- Plus four.
- All right, roll it and add that four.
- Okay.
So I roll.
- Roll a D20. - Roll a D20.
- D20, D20, D20.
- D20 plus four.
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay. - That is an 18 plus four.
- Wow, okay.
So you sling the hoverboard, and it gets jammed
into the wall, and almost enough that you could
wrench out a piece.
- Okay.
So I wrench out a piece.
- Okay, roll a strength check.
(laughing)
Your hoverboard is stuck inside the wall.
- Oh my god.
- Your hoverboard is like stuck inside the wall.
- Okay, then I'm gonna go on SkyMall and buy a new one.
- That's fine.
Okay, you're gonna go on SkyMall.
- We are in a spaceship.
It would have gone.
- I just like that he's not gonna,
like if she could come back
and your hoverboard's in the wall.
- I don't care if she comes back.
I know she's in a secret room behind the bed.
- I care, I like her.
- You like her a little too much
based on the game you gave her.
- You're in love with her.
- You are like a creator who falls in love
with his characters.
- I know. - Yeah.
- No, don't. - Like, fuck him.
- They could make a movie like Stranger Than Fiction.
- Yes. - Where he is God.
- Oh, shit.
- And instead of Will Ferrell, it is a woman.
- There's more to the idea, I thought it was just him as God.
- Yeah, wait, what happens in that movie?
- I don't remember. - She basically writes him
into a walker. - That was a movie
that I think me and my family had the same experience
as millions of families around the world.
- You think it's a funny Will Ferrell comedy?
thought it was a an elf movie and then we rented it and we all went huh yeah yeah
it's kind of like a boring Truman show yeah yeah pretty amazing I had the same
yeah I said everybody a lot of families yeah that experience that was his movie
immediately because I'm the cause of the cover of the DVD five going like this
fiction yeah and you're like what I remember I'm very much a he's going like
"STOP FOLLOWING ME!" and you're like "that's a funny willfowl"
but it's... and we all were trying to laugh
we were all watching going "uh"
we were all trying to calibrate
I remember I watched half of it and then decided I wanted to go play Tony Hawk upstairs
then came back down and asked my mom "how was the movie?" and she said "eh"
yeah it's not very good
it's that kind of movie
ok so his rollerblades are stuck in the fucking floor
and what's up with you?
What's up with me? Yeah, how are you? What's your life? Okay, wait, I just say, "All right, I give up," and I walk out of the room.
Yeah, finally. You see Baby Gat is now just like, his feet are on the wall. He's trying to pull it out.
Like, he's so... Oh, Baby Gat. Yeah, he's such a goofball. Yeah, ah, it sucks.
He's such a fucking idiot. Wait, can I say something to him right now? Yeah, of course you can. If anyone
comes in here and asks what happened, just say that I got bored.
He like looks at you, and he's like wants to kill you
More than anything and he just goes back to pulling up the skateboard out of the wall
We'll cut back to you two now
so
Footsteps who's this cute little pitter-patter walk. It is cute little putter-patter. It's
It's a Seamus
He's a leprechaun you rescued
who do you think it was?
fucking Sullivan!
the good one!
the one that I'd be excited to hear the pitter patter of his little fucking feet
and the other one is not even named Sullivan
he's crud
dirt or nothing
he has a lot of different names
Adam
like an atom
the molecule
the wimp
so a Seamus comes up to you guys
and says
name? Ashamis. Like Ashanti? Ashamis? I didn't know it was Ashamis.
Ashamis, like he's a shame. Was he the guy playing on Osama?
Play on Irish names? No, it's a play on Ashamed, not Ashanti.
Wait, why are you, what are you doing here?
What, a better question would be what are you two doing here? Was this the guy who got
killed, who got killed and then we rescued him?
Yes. He didn't get killed. But he got almost got, he got, that was a different guy, right?
That's a different guy. That's what I was saying. Wait, who's this guy? So who's this guy?
So you guys very first episode you guys run the zippy loop and a royal guard. Oh, yes
You guys helped him out I remember now a Seamus
We fully have remembered you it took us a minute. Where are we we got thrown down here by a fucking
scientist assistant
curious
Amazing
*laughter*
Oh!
You guys are deep in the guts!
I don't know where, uh...
I don't know what you think about the assistant scientist, but are you guys doing alright?
Oh, shit!
He looks at the, the, the, the tentacle monster mass and the guy on the ground, he's like...
You guys killed a greech!
And a...
A greech?
A greech and it's fuck toy!
A grinch?
A greech!
That's a greech to disagreech.
What the fuck are we doing here?
here? I don't know. How did you guys get down here? I just told
you we got pushed by a little man, a little man, the scientist
**** brother or something. It's so cool. Um well and we just
realized he's the killer or oh yeah. We think that well he
laughed like the killer laughs and like play time. Yeah. We
think it's play time. Wait. Don't hey, I have a strategy
Playtime, you're a killer!
Wait, who's playtime? Wait, what's that guy's identity?
*laughter*
Yeah, wait.
Wait, like, whatever reason we're all blanking.
I don't know, everybody's trying to figure out.
I can't remember.
Everybody's trying to figure out what his identity is.
And it is?
I don't know.
Oh, it's you, right?
I'm not playtime.
Well, then who is it if it's not you?
Okay, then laugh for us.
laughs mother fucker
okay tell me a really funny joke girls is not going to laugh for him
to try to make a black man
okay
a
white guy
uh... walks into a bar he's like now he's a really excited to hear this joke
andy and uh...
a white guy walks into a bar right the bartender says get the fuck outta here cracker
okay
yeah that was good
and i would just like to say that's pretty much how it is these days
that's true he's irish remember
uh... yeah he agrees
uh...
i should get you guys out of here you guys shouldn't have to be here
fuck yeah you should can we go back the way we came
Uh, well, where'd you come from?
From there, I point to where we came from.
Yeah, the chute, all the way up there.
Well, not that way, but I could take you to the Boglins and I can get you out through there.
The what?
Oh, you guys don't even know.
I guess, why would you know?
The Boglins.
A lot of us leprechauns, we don't really prefer the slave quarters, so we kind of made a little home for ourselves here in the gods.
Why wouldn't you want to live there? It's nice.
Um...
They feed you, there's beds.
Well they do feed us in the slave quarters, but that's about it for benefits I would say.
That's about it, sounds ungrateful to me.
Here, here, here, I can help you guys navigate here, I'll bring you to-
Oh, and you guys should meet Bear McGinnis, he'll love you guys.
He saved me.
Okay.
He's our leader, here, I'll lead you through.
Oh great, another fucking community we have to meet.
Cool.
I hate communities.
Me too.
- Yeah, I'll always find my notes for this, I'm sorry.
- I'll find your notes for this.
(humming)
- Oh, you're the one tapping, Patrick.
- Made this song for you.
- Patrick was making a rhythm.
- So, leading you through the guts,
the slick, winding passageways of--
- Are they slick and wet, guts?
- They're winding.
- Oh. - And winding?
Drab paneling are almost nauseating in their contortions.
It's hard to get a sense of where you are
and where you were.
A Seamus moves through them though
with a somewhat practiced confidence,
but an altogether ease.
The drone of the space station begins to fade
as you move through, giving way to a more localized
hissings and moanings of the machinery around you.
This is like, a lot of things are very cyber-y
and like, (mumbles)
but this is like real fucking machines.
Like this is what actually makes a ship work, you know.
But even those begin to fade, replaced by a stillness
and then drip, drop, drip, drop.
And he says, "Watch your step now."
And you hear the gentle plod of his small boot
in a shallow puddle.
And as Seamus gestures ahead, you see a pathetic stream
of murky green liquid just kind of like winding through.
And he says, "It's waste, but it gets better."
And as you move down the corridor,
this sickly little waste begins to shimmer and reflect
with like a little additive luster, just like a little bit more like oomph to it.
It takes a second look to realize that in the dark of the guts this can't be
reflection, right? Like it's too dark down here so it's genuinely glowing.
There's something sparkly and glowing about it. You can see the flickers of
green light dance at your ankles as you push through the waste and when you
reach the end of the corridor there's a wall in front of you made of the same
plain paneling you saw before but the stream goes on, not pulling up by this
wall but clearly originating from behind it. He says we're here and a Seamus cups
his hands around his mouth and presses his face against the door and he says
he laughs and then he says something "hearty-tarty-farty-hearty-tarty-tarty-farty"
muffled reply and then the door opens but only about three feet high that's my
people you're talking about yeah well we apologies precautionary the pass
precautionary measures you have to crawl through a bit but then you'll get to
extend up and yeah he sort of walks on through you guys want to crawl through
- I'm crawling in. - Yeah.
- You guys crawl through the muck a little bit.
You get a little bit, as you crawl through,
you guys feel a little bit of like a,
it's kinda like a--
- We're getting high.
- A little bit, but it's kinda like
you're just a little bit more aware, suddenly.
- Okay, all right.
- Hyper reality.
- There's a pool that sits in the center.
(laughing)
- Come on, man. - Whoa.
- Hyper reality.
- I'm just trying to analyze whatever passes through.
- In the center where the muck trickles,
in that is a glowing, fully, vibrantly green.
So there's a real, like, actual pool
kind of settling in in the middle.
Can you show everybody what that is?
- Here, let me hold it up to the toy camera.
- So Patrick put the beheaded Barbie on top of Cam's figure.
If I read anything that's longer than three sentences,
this is basically, which is my fault, really.
- I put my hands on the, listen, I mean, look at me.
I'm ready.
Thank you, yeah.
(laughing)
I'm a teacher's pet, I'll admit it.
And yeah, you see this pool of the muck,
and around it is a protective glass dome.
And around that dome are terminals
with nozzles and respirator masks.
And there are a number of tunnels extending out
from this little atrium where you can see
a little bit more clearly that there's a whole other
kind of little village there.
You see a few leprechauns sitting at these terminals,
interacting with the modules,
and then intermittently huffing from the respirator,
which seems to be drawing from this domed gas
where the sparkly green liquid is--
- Dome and gash?
Keep reading.
- And if you look closely,
you can see the corners of their eyes
filling with faded spots of that murky green
that matches the muck below,
and then, excuse me, slide towards the corners of their eyes.
It kind of like fills up like like kind of like you're taking in a breath and then
falls away
Until all that's left is the whites again that little bit of pink
and
Yeah, so that's what you guys see and you see a shame as he says this is where some of us will draw our strength
Sometimes when you have to go out to fight with some of the sex toys and the the greaches
The greaches are madmen
They're people who have been exposed to way too much of the bad quality air and water from
Living in the guts and working in the guts and now they're crazy. I think that thing was people that tentacle thing
Well, not that but the guy you touched I thought it wasn't it me too. The guy attached to him was a people. Oh
Okay, true. They'll ride them that way
The ride the fuck toys that live dance between the guts you sound a lot like Jordan Peterson right now. Oh
That's a problem with
Yeah, right, that's kind of I felt listen that one muck
I'd like to take a big bite out of that I kind of knew you would say that
Fuck you, man. I don't take a bite. I do I can't help myself
Oh, yeah, you take a big huff out of this shit
Yeah, and you feel kind of like this like that similar to that rush or it's kind of like in your head
but it's kind of more um and
Ambiguous now it like kind of goes in your head
But they kind of like filters throughout your body and for the next 10 minutes you'll add plus one to all of your rolls
Whoa, okay, I want to do it luckily we're not in any combat situation, so this is pretty useless. I'll take it, okay
You do the same yeah, you also for the next 10 minutes
Fuck I just feel like fucking killing something well. Maybe wait a little bit on that
Okay
And as you walk through a little bit further in the tunnels, and you start to see
This murky green bog completely still
You see shacks and like little pockets of shamrock fields,
sort of like lawn, amongst these shacks
that are made of like kind of bits of metal
kind of yanked from the, not the siding,
'cause we're not on the side of the ship,
but kind of inside the guts.
- It could still be siding.
- Is that what, yeah, right, 'cause it's just a material.
This is where it is, right, yeah, so.
And you see leprechauns dancing,
their little stumpy feet bouncing along to the--
Let me guess, they're doing Irish jigs.
They certainly are.
Come on.
Yeah, the Macarena.
Yep, they're doing-- I like that so much better.
They're all doing the Macarena to a fiddle played
by a one-eyed leprechaun.
The room itself is covered in like a little thin piping
that kind of weaves to and fro, along with paneling,
and some more of those terminals where
you see leprechauns sit while drinking Guinness
while they're working on the terminals.
Clothes hang on some of the thinner piping
and makeshift rafts of fallen debris
sit on the bog.
- Just debris though.
- With little leprechaun children playing atop them.
Further back there's an iron building
that's about the size of all the shacks put together
and then some, it's like much bigger
than everything else you've been seeing.
And taking up the remaining space
in this kind of large chamber.
And it looks like a submarine almost.
And within the small circular windows,
you can glimpse some leprechauns moving around
and the faint blue glow of other terminal screens.
Hopping along those rafts, by the way,
inside the bog where the children are playing,
kinda like jumping around,
you also see somebody else there,
and you see the children have taken this somebody else's hat
and are now saying, "Froggy in the middle,
"Froggy in the middle,"
and are just passing it around between them.
Who is it? - Oh, I hear that,
and I'm like walking the other way instantly.
It's like complete reflex reaction.
- Come on, this isn't fun anymore.
Ha ha ha.
- And he's trying to grab his hat
and they just took his hat from him.
And he sees you guys walking in, your friend nothing.
He says, "Oh, how did you guys get here?"
- I'm going long.
- I start just going for a Hail Mary, a froggy hat.
- The kid immediately tosses it to you,
bully recognizing, yeah, bully, yeah.
- I grab it and then I throw it on the ground
Step on it sir doing in zone
Yeah
But not before I take a shit in it you take this I do it before the fire you are so fucking stupid
And then you have to wear it
Roll persuasion with advantage
It's five everything's plopping is plopping. It's a plop and a ten
Have you guys been a plop night? I think your charisma is pretty high
It has been a bit of a even just the rest know you guys open the battle you guys both did great
You guys talk about the quality of the rolls even though just like the plopping plus three
I have been there 13 campaign 13 13. It's enough for Sullivan
He puts the hat on puts his poopy fire hat flaming poop. It smells like shit. It's like that
Oh God, what the fuck smells like shit Sullivan. Do you have a shower? God? I do all the time. Oh, I meant to tell you
It's bad for your hair I text the both of them on my PSP and say guys I Sullivan smells like hey
I
Haha react and then I switched my haha to an emphasize and I say we clowning I put yeah
We clown and the gift that I said is so funny. Oh
I forgot to tell you guys I went to the check called clowning
Into the gym you told me to get stronger. Yeah, I can't
I bet I can lift this you guys have the snake. No, but we have this and I'd what's the heavier close your eyes
I got a snake
Close your eyes. Come on
Okay, put my fucking cock in his mouth
(laughter)
- Oh, come on, man.
- That's not how it would sound.
- That is how it would sound.
- It would be so full.
- That's exactly how it would sound.
- You wouldn't be able to say anything.
It would not be perfectly enough saying everything.
- You have the worst tasting Tic Tac I've ever had.
(laughter)
- Sullivan could not own me.
Okay, I cut his head off.
(laughter)
No, I don't put my cock in his mouth.
That's all just funny.
- Yeah, that's right.
- Yeah, that's true.
- Yeah, that's not.
- But I do put,
- What are you gonna try to see what he can lift?
- My gun in his mouth.
(laughing)
- I say, "Lift this," and I shoot a bullet.
- Do you shoot him?
- I shoot at his feet.
- Okay, cool.
- Like I'm saying dance, but I say, "Lift this."
- You should have to roll to see
whether or not he shoots him.
- I might miss, I guess if I miss where I'm shooting at,
it's gonna hit his foot.
I mean, his foot.
- We have to do this?
All right, yeah, do it, roll.
- It's mechanics, right?
- Yeah, I think I can't help that.
- You're the one who's like, you know,
trying to keep all the rules in check.
This is obvious.
- So if I hit, I hit the ground,
'cause I'm not aiming for his foot.
- No, you're not aiming for his foot.
- But if I miss badly enough, it's gonna hit his foot,
and there's really not much I can do about that.
So that's a 14.
- Okay.
I mean, that's, so here's a question.
What was the goal?
- The goal is just to shoot at his feet and have him--
- 14, you don't hit him.
- Yeah, yeah, that's what I'm saying, yeah.
- 14, yeah, yeah, yeah.
you back
okay uh... adult
uh... i don't think it'll be fair
he's so we can get a little bit darker
shrewdly
do you eat
you eat
units yes you can make it
uh...
I'm just, I'm not even, I'm completely spaced out and that voice is talking in my head and I'm not sure I'm supposed to...
You want to kill them!
We'll cut from that back to you.
I'm back in the room playing charades.
You're playing charades again.
Charades by myself.
And I would say eventually like you, I mean like you're gonna go to sleep right?
No, I'm playing charades with scooter.
Playing charades with scooter? Okay.
Gina Davis.
[Laughter]
This game is so good!
Okay, who am I now?
Apollo 13. Dang.
No, it was Gina Davis.
I was thinking about astronauts.
Okay. Do you like astronauts?
Sometimes I wish I could be an astronaut.
Okay, I'm gonna go to bed now.
Me too.
Goodnight.
He just starts spinning in place.
I try to sleep like that and then realize it's making me more energetic so then I lay down.
You have like 35 minutes.
Like this is not working.
Oh, new sleeping style.
- No, I've been sleeping late.
- Sleeping style unlocked.
(laughing)
- No cap.
- So yeah, as you start to,
sorry, here, let me find this, I apologize.
I thought I had this up, I don't have it up.
I have it up now.
So yeah, you start to feel your eyelids get to heavy.
And the images of the screen, the Shrades game is still up.
They start to get kind of more smeared and indistinct,
but as you try to stay focused, you hear a familiar song.
- No.
- And when you eventually relent and fall asleep.
- ♪ When you see Tupac ♪
♪ Call the cops when you see Tupac ♪
- You have to put your microphone on.
- No, I'm doing it's faint.
- Yeah, you first hear nothing but
the sort of like gentle whirring of Scooter, your new friend.
As you, and then also Baby Gadd kind of struggling
in the other room trying to yank the skateboard out.
But then that familiar tune starts to get louder
and it starts to really eke its way into your head again.
Roll Perception.
- That is an 11.
- Even with that 11, you can almost swear
that you see the Shrades game starting to play itself.
Shifting between different options.
But then the lullaby you had heard earlier does,
(burps)
- Oh man.
Does that, it burps in me, it burps in your face.
- It turns it, it's Hit 'Em Up by Tupac,
but it's all burps now.
- And it lulls you into a slumber.
You're dreaming now.
And you find yourself at a carnival or amusement park
or maybe a mall, some kind of dream-like hybrid
of the three.
You see faces you know, friends, lovers from your past,
all partaking in the festivities.
Who do you see there?
Who does Patrick Yoda, when he dreams and he sees
like the kind of faces you end up seeing in dreams,
who does he see?
- Every single person is a Yoda.
- Yeah, every single person.
- Every single person's green and small.
- Okay, do you see your parents
or do you see like cousins, friends?
- I see Tupac Shakur.
- You see Tupac, you see Yoda Tupac?
- Yeah, Tupac Yoda.
- And he sounds like this.
What's going on, Patrick Yoda?
How are you doing, man?
- You had such a layup there.
- I know, but did I have a layup?
Is that what that's called?
- You could have done Yoda voice.
- Oh.
It's too late now.
- All right, all right.
- But now I'm trying to think of,
what would Tupac Yoda, you should do that,
you run with that.
I'm passing the buck, you're right, it's not fair.
- Yep, it's done.
- So you see these guys though,
also Patrick Yoda.
What's your favorite toy?
(laughs)
- Probably the hoverboard.
- Patrick Gerdes' favorite toy is a hoverboard.
You see it rotate in front of you.
Like that old joke of,
I'm rotating a cube in my mind.
You see the hoverboard.
- Not really a joke.
- It's like an idea.
People use for humor.
It's like eternally within and out of reach.
It's like you can grab it.
my arms and I look away from it. As you look away from it, it's tracking you
obviously. I'm doing this. You're doing that. You're doing that, yeah. It's following you.
And you follow it, darting through the nowhere of this nowhere fun land, and as
you do it, it begins to fade away. The toy starts to fade away until there's nothing
left, but an indistinct corridor and you hear the
faint sound of an, "Oh yeah!" from far away down the
corridor.
And you hear it alongside a bizarre series of
squeals and pings and pangs and general, you know,
onomatopoetic clamor, you know, like, "Bing, bang,
ping, pong, bop."
But it's all like a hundred octaves up and like
getting stretched and compressed.
and it's like, maybe like, you know when it's like,
they try to show how bugs, what the hell, ass?
You know, they try to show how bugs talk, you know that?
Like that kind of thing, but like,
it sounds like it's going through a computer
and it has more character to it.
And you hear like, "Oye, oye, oye,"
like kind of in response to this.
"Oye, como va?"
(laughing)
- It's the origin of the voice discovered.
And as you move closer to the sounds,
the toy in your mind begins to spin faster and faster.
It's supposed to reappear.
And the lullaby gets louder and louder,
drowning out the seeming chatter.
And you feel yourself pulled out of the dream.
And as you do, an ancient, otherworldly character
bears down on you.
The pulsing yellow pus pockets of flesh glow in time.
- Told you I got Pennywise vibes.
- SpongeBob.
- The ones, you would recognize them as the ones
that you saw outside of the lair
that were overhanging over the lair.
They were part of a giant cascading
like a mountain of flesh and shit.
And they glow in time to a heartbeat
that doesn't make sense.
It's like arrhythmic.
But you can tell it's something that is living.
And you can also feel that it's from deep,
deep within the space station.
And you wake up this next morning
and you have the foggiest sense of the truth
as to where New Sullivan is.
And we'll see exactly what you know,
'cause it's not quite what you know now,
but what you kinda know.
- Okay.
- Next time, we'll see that next time.
- And right now, I'm throwing up.
I throw up 'cause of the smell of the puss.
- Okay, bye.
- Bye. - I have to pee.
- No, I have to pee first.
Bye everybody.
Ready?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
What?
I don't see it.
Oh.
You got funny ears.
[Music]
(upbeat music)