Interior, The Matrix 2, The Groundhog Concert Hall.
The artificial air is thick with anticipation at the Papi Chuku Concert Hall.
Today is the most celebrated day in The Matrix 2, Groundhog's Day.
A familiar voice creeps into the scene, aching for attention, for validation, for respect.
The ever-present ghost of your long-dead mentor,
head detective Lenny Krapschitz.
- Holy crap.
- So it goes.
- I forgot about him.
- It's Kurt Vonnegut.
Yeah, he died in the very beginning, so.
I'm sure many of you thought that with their passing,
the adventures of my protégés, Blotas Piss,
Ray William Johnson, and Patrick Yoda would cease.
This is not the case.
- We fucking died?
- Yeah, remember?
- Yeah, you remember you died?
- We've died so many goddamn times.
- This was the real death.
- The real death happened.
You've died in other campaigns.
This is what happened to us. You got killed by some disgusting monster was a
giant tentacle. Yeah, we were in like a hole or you in the core ship. We got
killed by a fuck this shit. Oh yeah, that pissed me off so much. Yeah, I was so
mad about that mission. I was genuinely for like he gave us some good couple. I
think for an hour after I think I was like, I think you can hear it in the
episode. I sit there and I'm about to yell at you. Yeah, that's true. Yeah,
it seemed pretty upset. Yeah,
this is not the case though.
For a detective never dies.
As long as there is a case to be solved, the detective will rise from the dead, wipe the
dirt off their trousers, rub the maggots out of their eyes, grab a magnifying glass, and
look at a clue.
But we're not dealing with the undead detective.
This is a mystery solved before the gang's untimely demise.
They solved many crimes between my passing and theirs.
And this is, this one.
- Wait a minute, are you saying that we're gonna be revived?
Our characters are gonna be revived,
Mass Effect 2 style?
- I didn't say that. - We're three ghosts.
- No, I said this is, but--
- You said that rub the maggots out of their eyes.
- No, so I--
- Are we, is there gonna be a new Gun City campaign
where we get revived like Commander Shepard?
- You just thought of this?
- I cannot, I cannot confirm nor deny
that there will be a new Gun City campaign
with these characters.
but this is in the past. Okay, this is not just like you said that we like
commented on the line. There was a kind of a pile and then he started his next
life in the middle of you at way to
come back to life. I was drawing an eye. Yeah,
yeah, the letter I know it was an eye full minute.
They solve many crimes between my passing in theirs and this one is not
this one is one of my personal favorites
who killed Mr. Groundhog
see
As the narrator said up top, Groundhog's Day is a big deal in The Matrix 2.
Many a celebration is thrown across the virtual world, celebrating our wonderful furry friend, Mr. Groundhog.
Mr. Groundhog is a very popular creature. You see, a celebrity in his own right, an artist, a businessman, a member of Mensa, you name it, he's done it.
He throws the biggest party in the Matrix 2 on the day of his namesake, Hogfest,
which takes place at the Papi Chuco Concert Hall.
That day, he drank, partied, laughed, cried, and put on a show with the talented VTuber artist Haseki Tsune.
Unfortunately, it would be his last.
But our intrepid investigators don't know that yet.
They stand amongst a crowd, out on a large, welcoming garden and patio outside Papi Chuco Concert Hall,
where unmolested techno-slime fountains roar.
far. Just wait till Patrick gets in the room
damn my slime hasn't been molested.
Here comes that way. What's that sound?
They see all matter of famous guests that they may recognize
celebrities, businessmen, financiers, scientists, academics, social media,
marketers,
The gang are honored guests as well, invited because of their numerous exploits and adventures
at this point.
It's turned all three of them, and even yes, little Sullivan, into celebrities in their
own right in Gun City.
Though where they go, trouble is sure to follow.
So it goes.
And so you guys are.
You're at this sort of gathering.
bit on the reveal, the hairline reveal
didn't know
and we get a punch in and a dramatic music sting.
I don't know how you immediately got hat hair from a hat sitting not even
really on your head on top of head for it's it's
had not on your head, but I'm so like precarious right now. Yeah, that's okay.
The amount that's here, right? You gotta give it volume when I'm doing to it.
You do look a little wind swept. Yeah, I think you could rock this for 25 years
and it's gonna be that's the plan. Yeah.
So you guys are standing right now outside of the this
concert hall, the poppy chucos concert hall. Obviously, poppy chucos been long
dead. You guys killed him, punched his head off. You specifically killed him
at William Johnson, actually. And so, but he has a concert hall still in the
virtual world of the Matrix two who gets the money from this hall if he's
passed away. So he has a family. I'd like to kill them too. Well we can make that something.
Are they there? Does he have little kids? Real young ones? He does not have little kids.
I'd like to kill his mom. You want to kill his mother? Yeah, but we'll get to that later.
His mother is alive, his father is dead. Explains a lot about his personality. His father died
very recently, though, so it doesn't explain to explains recently. His
body was still that's why he's dead recently. That's right. So yeah, you
guys are hanging out outside. You'll see some people you recognize. Leo, the
collector is there.
What's his fucking name? John Carlo is there. What point? Wait, when is this?
So this takes Yeah, this takes place in between two. This takes place in
between right after the heist campaign. Yeah. And right before we die on time
only space time play time continue. Okay, cool pain. So like because between the
other one and the heist one, what happened at the end of the heist, the
end of the heist, when you guys ran off with your millions, we won, you won, you
got the heist and so we're rich now. Yeah, this is in the this is in the
lowest to be as characters name again for that one. It was Gary V. It was Gary
G okay yeah or Barry V Barry G Barry G all right just keep that in mind
everybody yeah because he can he can pipe up and maybe pipe up and be in
yeah. We can do things and find his care that before he
I said he was gay.
So yeah, he's about to be when Cameron gets to him. So yeah, you got to be
there. Hang that is a we said that you were a molester and you came with that
he's gonna be gay on. He's gonna be gay when Cameron gets to him?
He's gonna be gay long before I get to him? No, no, no, 'cause Cameron...
That's your roast? Is that Cameron's so good looking that he... No, it's not a
roast. It's not a roast. It's... Turns him gay? It's terms on... It's about their
relationship. We do have something special. You've seen their texts.
We have kind of a... We have a bestial relationship where one licks the other.
Yeah. So, yeah... Sorry, we haven't seen each other in a couple of days.
We're all hyped up. No, I understand. Yeah, you're hyper. Yeah. Leo, the
collector, comes up to you guys and goes, "Well, it's good to see you three all
still all well and together. How are you? I don't remember what my character is
supposed to sound like or what his personality is like. So his personal
nailed it on both
we're good man. How are you?
I'm well wait. What was that? What was that little bird? I heard
what the wait are you being controlled by Sullivan? Oh, fuck me. Oh, no, wait,
why you're changing characters.
Hey guys, yeah, I mean, you guys told me to...
Can I break the fourth wall like Deadpool now?
Yeah, you guys left me in the car with the windows up again.
Yeah.
And you made it out.
So what are you complaining about?
It's getting harder.
It's called a test.
Because the glass is really sharp.
Oh, you're still in there.
We get by bigger and bigger cars that have a higher handle.
This is a Hummer H50.
This one had a maze inside of it I had to get through before I found out.
Yeah, yeah.
far. Well, you solve the maze on you. Aren't you proud of that? Yeah, we're
testing you, Sullivan. How would you be fucking proud of yourself for once?
You solve the fucking maze roll deception
three that sets a bad tone, but I've noticed the first role sets the tone for
every role. We have the whole episode. Really? Yeah. So don't ask me to do any
I don't think it would be too worth my time to be proud of myself to be honest.
I'm going to punch you in the head.
Well, if no one else is going to be so you better be.
I'll punch you in that fucking head if you don't do that.
Where does your head even fucking start?
You look like all head to me by the way.
You look like one leg.
We have a picture of him right here.
You're basically one leg.
You're basically a leg to me.
You're like the leg lamp from Christmas Carol.
You're worse than the light lamp because you can't even make light.
I can't even rub ya.
We've been over this.
I have arms and legs, you guys.
But the rest of you is neck right into head.
So where is the point where it becomes the other one?
You see Leo the collector's like, "Well, I'll just leave you."
No, Leo, Leo, Leo, Leo, Leo, Leo, come here.
We uh...
Do you know stuff about frogs?
Oh yes, I collect frogs.
Oh, you collect frogs.
Well, we have a frog for you to collect.
Oh yes, I know Sullivan.
You didn't want this one?
Sullivan worked for you.
Just for a brief period of time.
Sullivan was his assistant at one point.
Sullivan was both your boss at one point,
the head of the detective agency,
after Leo Kravchits died.
Immediately became an assistant for
Leo the Collector.
Downward mobility.
Yeah, I just felt that Sullivan was not going to...
No offense by the way, Mr. the Frog.
He just wasn't very good at anything.
You're kidding.
wasn't very good at anything. You're kidding me. Yeah, he wasn't good at
anything. No, I've been told this before, too. He's a little too good at getting
out of a fucking hot car.
Also, I just remembered we're
guys we've been we're called. I don't know why you guys are calling this thing
Sullivan. I think his name is shirt. His name is so sorry.
Wait, where is Sullivan?
you left your your son's at home. He's sleeping. It's too late for all that's
so cute.
Are we actually maybe his name isn't sure yet? I don't know the timeline. It
is well, he is shirt by now. I came shirt in the heist. I think he became
sure the highest or in Indiana. I thought his name was you know, you know,
sometimes nothing. I think in India, nothing
you know, like you know when they do like they do like he was like nothing
again or he's crap.
crap right now. You know how they'll do the thing in like a prequel or like a
spin off that set in the middle of something where, like you know some new
detail about a character will get like revealed that they just never, ever go
back to and yeah because it's obviously because it's to with Jess. So he needs
to have he needs to have a completely new name. It just doesn't make any sense
for the future. Yeah,
plug
probably we all call him a different thing and we're like no it's not
stick. Yeah, he has no name
so Leo Cup. I just keep looking at him and holding out my hand and just keep
going the cop. I just keep looking at looking at him and trying different. I'm
just going to like Cup. No, no, try and try plug glasses. No, like but plug
grass. No
Adam, so what what about ourselves at home
listen David the frog.
so what about oops? Are you all good? Yes, because I don't know his parents,
but I know he was very accidental, not did not mean to be living.
It is very good. We're going to go with accident for this episode
or this mystery. You're all excited for the concert tonight. Yeah, I was
playing Ja Rule. I wish it's Lily Katsumi, Hase Katsune and Mr. The Frog.
I hope there's no whoa wait, wait, wait, Mr. Groundhog. Oh, okay. Are
you going to Mr. The hog? I hope there's no bad blood between you and
Hussey. So you guys remember you guys kind of incidentally put Hussey behind
bars.
Why? Why would there be bad blood between us? No, it's a problem. Yeah.
What did we? Well, never mind. We put her behind bars. Yeah.
So
All right, yeah, it's good. She's out now. Yeah, no, she's out now and it
did actually do wonders for her. Korea gave a lot of credit street cred
great for Korea too.
And then you
you see
the
big like sort of like projected like there's like a big projected wall over
the arena and like a shadow shows up like a groundhog shadow.
And
oh, it's time. It's time for us to get to the concert and so time for the
concert. You guys walk inside into the concert. You see Gary C. Enterprises there also. He
comes up to you guys. "Hey guys, how's it going?"
"Shut up!"
"Hey man!"
"What are you doing? You should be at work."
"I'm at a concert, I'm hammered."
"I've got lots of people making us plenty of money for hot dogs and hot soda and cold
dogs."
"Oh that's what you do. Wait a minute, don't you have..."
"Yeah, I run your business. We're partners."
"I forgot."
"We missed your last 100 Zoom meetings with me, but that's okay."
"I don't have a phone anymore."
I don't have a phone anymore because I sat down on it.
Hey, it happens all the time I'm sure
to people who are like you.
In between the two, the heist and the...
Aren't I addicted to cocaine? I think for you, yeah.
I blow all of my... You blow all of your money on cocaine eventually.
So I take $100 out of my pocket and I put it in the lapel of his shirt and it keeps
keeps falling out. I forget that the pocket is where you put the money.
Oh, that's...
Yeah, hold on, keep that.
You heard the number 100 and you're now giving me a $100 bill.
Yeah, well, here's that. That's for you to hold on. Oops. Sorry about that. Let me just
grab that for you.
You hear an announcer. Ladies and gentlemen, boys and girls.
I'm a boy.
Mr. Groundhog and Hasegi Tsune. And you see come out a furry, cute,
friendly little groundhog named Mr. Groundhog. Does he look like the Chinese
dickhut one? Yes, Caleb. Maybe. Where are we? Okay, a couple of things.
What's the cap at this venue? How many people are here?
Like probably 300, 15. 300? It's like a very intimate sort of like...
Okay, where are we sitting? Private party. Are we VIP? Standing... Oh,
it's standing room. So we're... We have bottle service 'cause I spent way
too much on tickets. You can get... There's a bar and stuff. 'Cause I lose
all my money at the beginning of the campaign, right? I would like to
force myself to the front with me and my friends. So yeah,
so I'm just giving money to security guards and I'm like... I got us
bottle service and VIP and everything, but I'm still like... I basically
bought one of each ticket for each of us
to the whole venue. You guys were invited to this, this is like an
exclusive. We're VIP. But you still bought a wine to buy tickets, yeah.
Yeah. Okay. So roll, roll strength check just to like push your way through. I
mean, you'll be fine, but I want to just do this. Let's get a roll out of the
way for even with that. You're fine. Like these are you guys are strong.
Oh, you guys are fighters. These are normal people. I say that with a four
though. It's like you, you kind of go. I want to be right at the front. You
can't do that a little bit. I want to be right at the front. I hang back
cross my arms, nod my head. Every few down beats nice and I'm going to every
single seat that I purchased. Also, when I say not my head to see which one I
like the best when I say not when I say not my head, I'm not like nodding to the
rhythm. It just means everyone's from here and note that I like and I'm like
I brought a bunch of ziplocks full of Indian food that I started eating like
maybe four minutes into this whole thing, like really, really pungent Indian food
and I start I start crowd killing anyone who has a cell phone up. So Mr.
Groundhog and Husky today put on like this kind of like it's like a hyper
pop.
So all right sing it
it's it's really just sung by the ground hogs sing it
okay,
okay, I'd like to the best musical artist ever. I'd like for you to make
this song. Now this is something I would listen to. Oh, I I really wanted to
I'll take it after this, but it's a mind blowing song. It's like the best song
you can imagine. And Mr. Groundhog is clearly carrying it entirely.
Like Haseki Tsune, it's hard to imagine her having any creative input in
this and it's a little bit evident in her body language. It's like when
they bring...
It's like when a rapper brings their... They're like a feature on stage,
but the song doesn't change. Yes, exactly. And they're just both dancing
to it and just occasionally just going, "Yeah!" Yeah, yeah. They suddenly
become demoted to a hype man, they don't... They're out of their element.
so and the crowds eating it up and it's not so much a series of tracks as it's
like a fifteen minute long just kind of odyssey where they're all playing.
It's a cover of Edmund Fitz the Reckoning.
The legend. How would that go down?
People are like going crazy, they're crying, it's so beautiful,
but concerts are also usually about fifteen minutes in gun city due to the
decrease attention span. So concert ends and you're all directed to the dining
area now and you have a sign table for just a three of you. Wait, the concert is
one fucking song? I mean it's like it's technically like four or five songs. I
spill my butter chicken all over the stage.
And then I like I would I get on all fours and I crawl under everybody back to
the back of the room. Perfect.
and yeah you guys sit at your assigned table.
It's just the three of you for safety precautions. You guys are sort of like
considered the most dangerous people in gun city. Maybe we're selling bad ass
solve. Oh sorry, I chair high chair also they put a chair. You see the and one
for your baby cup and I would like to tip it completely. No, I
they put they put him at the end of the table on the high chair and I'm like oh
guys, one second I'm just I need a little more room. Can I I'm just going
screwed the table this way and I start pushing it towards them. He's under the
table. Yeah, we buckled him in
why did you do this? I don't table his head pressed up against the other side
of the table. Please, please, I didn't want to. I start kicking the legs of the
high chair. Oh come on. I can't even fix this. I kick out one of the legs of the
table.
He becomes the
he comes to stay
the table go or
food's going to spill. It's going to get every if you find this is not right and
I get up and I take a folded napkin and I put it under the high chair because it
was wobbling a little bit
that
that's much better. Okay,
just like move the napkin slide it and I put a booger in his mouth on down
there.
you like that I'm going to call you bugger
and
you hear the once again the MC for the evening goes like you know
dinner is served and it's time to celebrate with the groundhog banquet.
It's dinner with every sweet meat treat pastry and sauce. You can imagine I
slip the waiter two hundred dollars and I say, can you give me like for other
plates?
I want like I know I know I know it's like a five course meal, but I want I
want to make it a twenty course meal just for myself. Oh, you want you want
four extra of everything yeah, so four so so three more plates and so yeah
these things are all brought out. You're giving you're getting extra dinners
and then finally yeah, I look I'd glance down at Sullivan and I say and and for
me and for me I'd like I'd like the normal amount of food, but can you
somehow make it so that it's ten times heavier.
Yeah, could you put like some way
eye contact with Sullivan as you say this? Like could you put like a forty
five pound rogue plate? Could that be the plate that I get served?
Oh yes, we have several of those. I'm perfect. Thank you
Sullivan's
and
then it's the final, the main course, the most delicious scrumptious treat. Mr
the butter burger surprise.
Ooh, from Culver's.
It's from Gun City.
Oh. Shut up. But it's also from Culver's.
Is Gun City in the Midwest of
Ybom? Of Ybom?
Sort of. I mean, geographically.
Yeah. So it's the
Chicago kind of. It's kind of the Chicago
of Ybom. Yeah. I mean, it's the
main, it's also the only city.
It's not the only city, but it's the main
city. It's a future hell where Chicago
is the best city in the country.
in the country. And when the Butter Burger platter is brought out with the
silver cap on top. And it's lifted up by the chef. You're making me starving with salad.
Something about those platters make me so hungry. I know, god damn. Me too. That reveal.
Oh yeah. I experience it three times a day, but it just has never gotten old.
The reveal. My god, it never gets old. It really just every time. Well this reveal
still has Mr. Groundhog on it. What dad with an apple in his mouth apple and the
chef looks I start digging in what
what is wrong with this is the groundhog right and everyone starts going is
horrified. I'll take three more. It's like we just found it also solve the
mystery and it was the chef. Yeah, the chef must have done it seemed like it
was the chef and everyone is okay. Immediately they rush and to tear apart
chef and as the bloodshed rises, you feel yourself get a little lightheaded,
not because you guys aren't scared of blood, but you just your vision starts to
fray glitch almost whoa and then you're back exactly where you were when you
first arrived on the patio. Time loop a time. We are caught around on a time
glue. Fuck dude. We're playing twelve minutes and then you hear from your PSP
in one of your pockets. I guess Pat you sat on your phone. So who else has a
PSP? I got one. Okay, I'll have it here. Hello, hello,
Blotus, Blotus, it's Dr. Touladeralis. Wrong number.
We go through the time when we can.
We just do the same shit. Don't solve it.
Blotus, please, please pick up, please. Oh,
I was supposed to pick this up.
Hi hello, how many times how many phone calls has it been
by
on your on your five times already and then I
and I
if we die, I say does this is your fault
does the time loop reset if we done yes, okay, yeah, it loops back around to go.
That's how I get away with you guys don't have to worry about dying in this
campaign right because you your characters are because they're so
talented. It goes what I did die, though, and it was revealed that all along in
the play time campaign. They were an imposter. Wouldn't that be cool? That
would be cool, but now we have to cut that basically invalidate everything. It
goes back around again,
like one of the time solvent is three eyes for some reason. I think it's just
like it's like completely fucked up and then it's like okay, a cause calling you
this time. Hello ray, you got red. Oh my God,
Hi ray, I managed to get your number from blow toss during one of the do you
realize there's multiple time loops going on?
The fuck are you talking about? You guys are stuck inside of some kind of time
loop right now. No, we're not time loop a time. What is a time loop? What the
hell's a tie loop?
I
what's
No wait wait wait guys. I think he's saying we're caught in it. I
it's time.
Wait, wait, wait.
Yeah, so what's that time a loop? It's a time a loop. Now. Well,
you're caught in a time loop. Oh my
cocks in my cocks in a tie loop a double winter.
Okay, well,
it's been the entire loop in the bathroom. It doesn't really look like
well, I guess I'll keep messing with it.
Okay, roll perception.
No, just just just just Ray, would you
sorry? That's owl owl
six. Okay, can I roll it too? Because I got a sixteen what now
I go that's the curse. I don't have a phone.
Okay,
please. Okay, time loop. Yes. Oh, okay. I was just trolling you, Mr.
Ladder.
I know what a time loop is. I'm getting trolled. It doesn't matter. We
could do it a hundred times. My friends are trolling me. Yep, you got
trolled.
So it's time to solve the mystery of... Okay, I figured we could. It's time.
Wait, it's time...
No, I'm kidding. Who's Miss Terry?
I know Miss Terry, she's the bus driver.
It seems that
if you don't figure out what happened to Mr. Groundhog, you might be stuck in
this forever. How do we know it's that and not that we need to like do...
We need to... Well, let's try kissing. Yeah, we need to do something.
Okay, we'll try kissing. Okay, well, let's rule out kissing. Guys,
go for it.
You guys solved it. How was that kiss? How was that kiss?
that's the fastest you guys have ever solved on my
okay. We ruled out kissing. We ruled out a hand.
Under the bad stuff, I pulled his hair for a little bit. We did all this. We
did all this stuff and it we did all this stuff and it took like five
minutes. So then the rest of the time that loop was just as waiting.
I bet this is going to work. I bet it. I bet we're going to
yeah having the like time loop you kill yourself thing, but you just
the other people who are also stuck.
So you all remember what I forgot you guys are also in it. Neither of us will
remember this. If we just go for it,
okay, all right, so we need to wait. It's time. Okay, hi, nice to meet you.
I don't remember
I've never been here before in my life.
He has no idea.
We both think we're taking the other one okay, so I'm at beginning of the next
loop. I immediately I'm just going to go into the kitchen and I'm just going to
be in the kitchen the whole time. So
jubio if you can bring up the map, please whoa
okay there we have no screen. Yeah, we don't have a screen today. Jubio do not
bring up the map. Why didn't we connect the laptop to the because it's playing
this? We didn't know we needed visual. So did you guys see on this aesthetic
kind of back drop we have here? This is the most exciting part. First of all,
it's a beautiful noir backdrop, which fits the noir theme. But what you guys,
I'd noticed while I was looking at this when I wasn't paying attention before,
ribs are only 23 cents. Whoa, that's quite cheap. Oh my God, I want to jump
into the TV like Super Mario. Milk is more expensive than ribs. These hams,
fresh hams. Oh, I love ribs and I love ham. Yeah, milk is more expensive than
ribs. That's so and it's all next to the Deluxe Club. I went there. I will give
you guys this to just look at for a second. Then just know this. There is the
outdoor patio. That where we start. Yes, this is where you start the concert
venue, the stage, the green room.
There are some dressing rooms, one for the Mr. Groundhog, one for Husky
Kitsune.
There's the dining room, the bathrooms
and the kitchen. I would say you should draw this. I can, yeah, just draw
this. I drew a guy. And I'll keep describing this while we're doing this
so also the folks at home. So the way this works is I've always wanted to do
this with you guys actually. It's very exciting for me. Is this detailed
enough or do I need to add more? I'm being serious. I know, I know you are.
Just add the bathroom area. Where's the bathroom area? The squares? Yeah,
yeah. And then I would just divide up the green room top into three separate
areas, like the right behind the stage. And then I think you're pretty much
good. Okay, there are some doors there, but I will just tell you about those and
we'll just play it like that. So the way this is going to work is that each of
the time loops, there's 15 minutes. What did you do? He dispensed his in by just
opening his pouch and one perfectly just flew out. That's pretty cool. That's
crazy. That was amazing. Wait, can you just say that? So I'm sorry, say the
rooms from right to left really quick again. Yes, yes. It's patio on the right,
outdoor patio, patio, and there's patio one. You're right. It's really like four
sections right where it's like patio concert area dining area kitchen.
I'm trying to listen Patrick, it's not the time. Kitchen right and so there's
the outdoor patio, then there's the concert area where there's a concert
venue on the bottom. So it's like the audience area over here. I don't have,
I have the free license so they don't let me make the fonts better. Okay.
The stage
and then there's like the green room in the back. What is a groundhog DR?
That's a dressing room. Oh okay. Yeah, not groundhog Dominican Republic.
Okay.
Can the groundhog be Dominican?
If you guys are really that
interested in that, yeah.
Then what's the next one on the
left?
Next is just the dining area.
Dining area.
And then in those are the
bathrooms off of that.
OK.
I mean, all the way left is the
kitchen.
Sick. All right.
And officially the groundhog
is Dominican.
So.
Yeah. Sorry.
Wait. No. If you have something.
Yeah. No.
The way this works is
there are 15 minutes sort of
increments and I will just signal each one as it happens and say like what do
you guys want to do during that time and then we'll play that out and then when
those end we'll move on to the next 15-minute increments. Okay. That's how
we're gonna try to figure out what happened, what went down. Yeah, that's
that's kind of the beginning end of it. So right now you want to go you want to
beeline for the bathroom. The kitchen. I would like to do I remember I've done the
loop now probably 10 or 15 times. Yeah, okay. We can do something with
that. Can I...
I would recognize the waiter who serves the hog. Yeah, okay. Let's... So I'd
like to just try to find him and tail him for a bit. Perfect,
that's totally fine to do that. And I am gonna go backstage.
Perfect.
Nope, those are good moves. Your first opportunity to go backstage. So let's
start with you going to the kitchen. Okay. So
you guys, you guys arrive, it's back to beginning
Sullivan goes. What do you guys want me to do by the way? Oh, actually, also I
wish you guys we didn't have. Why'd you guys make me do hand something I
noticed in the last loop that I didn't haven't mentioned anybody yet is I
noticed that the
killer, the waiter that brought out the dead groundhog actually looked like on
his wrists and and up to his elbows. He had kind of encrusted shit. Okay, yeah,
so I need you to go into the toilet okay and go down as far into the pipe as you
can go because it's think that if he had killed the guy, the weapons probably
down there, that's probably
yeah, you need to dive into it ahead first, like all the way like do you want
me to do that every single loop like you? Yes, I think actually I have a better
idea. I think my fist, I think I was just like a baby. I think I will just
kill you right now so that you're not in the loops and I'll do that every single
time.
I'd like to shoot him in the head yeah, okay, yeah, you do the crowd around you
goes crazy,
going nuts. You guys are getting arrested. The loop restart arrested for
fucking what killing a
fucking animal okay, okay, wait, maybe just kill me in a quieter area or a
quieter.
You know what's a living that might be the best thing you've ever little
clip.
No, it's not worth it. Go eat the poop out of the toilet. You got it because it
runs to the toilet. Okay, cool. So you go into the kitchen,
you see Leo goes up to try to talk to you guys. I guess you just
beeline past him. Yeah. Okay. Hi, bye. You go past him. I'm sure I
know where everybody is right now. Cool. You go past him, you go past
the crowd venue,
you get to the security area to enter into the concert. He's like,
"Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey, hey, concert hasn't started yet. You're not allowed
in here."
Yeah, we are.
what we're all allowed in here because I bought the most tickets.
You bought a lot of tickets, but the concert I bought the most tickets. I
didn't buy a lot of tickets. I bought the most old speaking with disadvantage.
Well, it's true, though. Well, it was a natural. What he's saying is true.
All right, can I can I have a can I also have a can I ever have so we
can have a retcon memory from a past time loop was the waiter wearing a
the waiter wearing a name tag before if not that's okay. Now it was okay, but I
wouldn't reasonably know his name. Can I pitch a name? Okay,
well, maybe you maybe one time, but you don't have to give it to me. That's I
won't go to yeah. You can try again, though. Try it. I have to. I just have
to go to the bathroom. I think I mean I think I saw my friend. I don't have
that. Why don't you let that frog go to the bathroom? Now I can't go in. You
have invisibility and disguises you guys. I want to go. You want to yell at
the guy, though, okay, I saw you literally let you stop. Okay, first of
all, a frog who was an accident, one of the most pathetic forms of life on the
earth. You let him in. I'm important. I'm a celebrity. I borrow somebody's phone
and I start filming and I go, we got a we got a Karen y'all. All right. All right.
All right. All right. Enough with. Okay, fine, fine, fine. Just get just just I
don't want to be Karen. Okay, so just like keep. No, I was saying don't say
anything. Don't say anything. Okay. Did I misunderstand that? No, you didn't shut
the fuck up. Karen, go home. You're fired. Okay, I'm fired for being a Karen. And
so yeah, you guys are allowed in. I can't believe that were
happen this time, and so yeah you're going to go to the kitchen right and
you're going to backstage the backstage and where did you want? I'm trying to
find the waiter, the waiter. Okay, so let's finish you out. So you go towards
the kitchen and
as you're walking past, you see
you're walking past the kitchen, the doors to the kitchen. Oh, this is
perfect. Actually, you see Gary see enterprise sitting at a table on the
phone with somebody
Oh, you can keep going. I'll kind of cock an ear as I go maybe catch a snippet.
What do you mean? No, I... Well, tell him that... This wouldn't happen if... Roll, roll. If
you want to listen further, you're going to have to try to like... Roll stealth. To get
closer. Okay, what stealth is that? That's balance ball. Okay, that's a 14. Okay. You're
able to sort of like perk over a little bit more you hear him say I don't care
how popular he is it's not right he stole our IP and now his product is gonna do
better than us I'm in his own freaking event right now okay cool so he stole our
R P.
Can I help you? Botas? Yes.
I guess you go into the cool. We'll go back to that. You Pat,
you're backstage, right? I'm sorry. Wait. No, you weren't. You were third.
You're next up. You wanted to go to... I wanna find the waiter.
To find the waiter. Okay, so you walk into the
venue as well. You see Gary C. You see the same conversation that he saw,
but he was listening into it. You flag down the waiter. Yeah, you see him
there. And he says, "Is there anything I can help you with, sir?"
Yeah, I am
training to be the new waiter at this venue, and they told me that I need
to come and tail you for a little bit, just for the service.
old. I'm not going to I could do it just regular
damn well, of course, I'll tail the way to program. Well, let's just I don't
know why you're being so condescending. It's pretty common. No, no, no, I'm not
condescending at all. It's not calling. It doesn't have a name. The tail the
waiter, no, it's very you would do it any kind of you guys really rich.
There was somebody's following when somebody's following somebody to learn
to do a job, you're tailing them or you're shadowing them. Fucking Sonic the Hedgehog
vibes man. Real as fuck. That's crazy. So I would like to start shadowing this waiter.
Okay cool. So you're going to follow the waiter around and we'll go back to you as he goes
about his shit. Shift. Nice. You're up. So you're going backstage. So you get through
this first bouncer but now you're going backstage. And I have a lanyard that has every ticket
that I bought. So I could have bought... Is there a VIP backstage pass?
You did establish this up top. I'm gonna let you just go in there. So you go in
there, you're in the green room right now.
So the green room on your right... You're nut? I nut. I nut. I nut. I nut.
I nut because I've never seen something so lavish like this. You're on the...
When you walk in, on your right, you see a door, it says the Hase Kitsune's
dressing room on the left is to Mr. Groundhog's dressing room. Okay, while
I'm in the green room, though, I nudge one of the roadies and I say green room.
This room is barely green. I didn't even call it a green room. This room is
barely green.
Yeah, man, it's true.
He is one hundred dollars.
Nice man.
Your laugh is super scary,
but I kind of like
I did too much some kind of tech.
Yeah, so I'm freaking out a little bit, so I run to
I run out of the room because I realized that maybe I run out of the
green room where I was and I made that joke out of embarrassment because I
realized that the joke was bad and I fall. I liked it too. I fall back and I
lean my back on the door near Hudson's room. Okay. And what do I hear?
Who's Hudson? Very nice. It's fine. You could say that. Roll. No, no, no. You
just hear this. You just hear this. You just hear this. Should I roll
perception because I'm freaking out. Why do you want to not hear it? You don't
have to roll. You're hearing this. I was trying to be fair. No, no, because
because it's a it's it's I would say roll. Actually, what I would say is
because you just slammed yourself against the door
roll.
It's kind of more like a
okay, you're fine then all right. So, then you hear you hear her say
take this
stand. Okay,
do it
say it doesn't sound like you heard that. Can you say that exactly again?
say it louder and so that you hear the door start to open, but a fly buzz by my
ear. So I didn't hear it, so it's not fair. You hear a door start. I was a
real life intervention. You want to react to this. Where am I in relation to
the door? Your back is against the door, which is what you described to me. Okay,
so I stand up and I lean with the door. I try to make myself as flat as possible.
I like that I try to follow the door to the wall. I love that
roll
that's kind of athletics. That's kind of I guess I guess I still Panther,
I guess still so it's been we have. Can you make a new stack very nice
calling a way about just all pink and I teen right yeah, that's a great idea.
We need a new for big head. That's only a pink Panther, a kind of things,
pink pants are good. We would use a we would basically only roll. I would only
how would be an incredible. Can we make a system where it's like the different
things are like a pink panther, Mr. Mago,
think of all the things that we do yeah right yeah, Mr. Bean's, a great one,
Tom and Jerry, Tom, Tom and Jerry Frank's driving yeah bugs bunny, the
squad. This is such a good idea yeah. I love this, but so this opens up and
yet you do it perfectly and you see walk. I make a creaking sound with my
mouth
Okay, that's what you do you do a motor a Ducati
the roadies like that's the beginning of a playboy car. He's on a cool sound man
that door is awesome.
These doors he's a wait wait wait a second let me make that door.
You have to do the sound of
he's like what put you mess it up you like,
but yeah, so you see walk out not husky tsune, though, but one of her V tuber
like girls who are part of her posse, remember V tuber kind of hose.
I wish I had a phone to text the other guys what I just saw and you see her
go
dash P
and you you see her walk right into the ground hogs room.
So
look at the time for this. Yeah, I would say fifteen minutes go by.
Okay,
and you see how we'll go back to you in a second. Okay, fifteen minutes go
by. So you make sure I know where everybody is right now.
Cool. You're in the kitchen, right? Yeah. Okay, so you're in the kitchen.
You've been just, I guess, like
I'm eating all of the ingredients, the wrong
ingredients.
Bla bla bla.
Please stop, stop.
I do not do this.
That's how we treat French around here.
And you see, what?
This is how they treat me.
Bla bla bla.
That's not what I sound like.
No, it's not what I sound like.
Bla bla bla.
Stop it.
And how can you understand me?
Because I don't know.
I did not think about that before.
Do I sound like Zitong?
No, it's not true.
And so, like you see, so far from what you can notice, nothing unusual.
I mean, I'm not saying that I'm a bad singer.
I'm just saying that I'm a bad singer.
no, it's not true
yeah, and so like you see so far from what you can notice nothing unusual
people just doing. What was the dish that was supposed to be the ground?
How to be the butter burger butter burger? Okay, I basically I'm like can
you show I just really want to see the making of the butter burger surprise
nailed it.
I suppose I can show you this yes, and yeah he goes well. No, when it's like I
I heard about your Tale the Waiter program.
Yes, of course.
I wanted to participate in it.
Very famous, very important, not condescending program.
Maybe then you've also heard of Shadow the Chef.
Shadow the Chef.
Oh.
So I was hoping that when you do make the Butter Burger I could...
He sounds cool.
Roll persuasion.
We're speaking with advantage.
My God.
You know me.
I could be a DM so easily.
You could.
It's really not very hard.
It's not.
It's a joke.
Oh, that's a 17.
That's very nice.
Yeah.
He's like, "Yes, of course.
shout to me when I make zip about the burger surprise,
Bertie Burger,
Pink Panther
in my head. I'm going to go home and re watch that. I watch it. I watch it a
couple of months ago. Honestly, funny
things. So I keep myself. This is a Steve Martin. One of the stuff with his
secretary is so which one is it when the giant globe rolls down the that's the
first one. That's the first that one I saw in the it is fine. I remember
specifically that scene. I almost peed myself. I think so. That movie is still
fun. I've never seen the Peter Sellers one is that one. I think it's good. No,
I mean it's it's good. It's not the same kind of no yeah, it was there. All
they're very dated, but the the the new pink panthers came out after Austin
power, where they realized this should be Austin power. Yeah, right yeah, he's
a foreign guy like right yeah, yeah, let's have an American play a foreign
guy. Okay, cool, so yeah, you've got that on lock like you're going to be
the shadows guy throughout. Oh, it is that the one to where he where he farts
in front of Beyonce. Yes, Beyonce is so fine in that that movie is funny. When
you
also even think about this, she was she is my God, she was just doing that.
Why does she have the greatest taste of all time and literally a large, but
that's you probably would heard the fart and she was like that's nothing yeah.
You should smell
You can see my farts. My farts are loud. So you, meanwhile, Ray William Johnson,
you've been shadowing your waiter friend here. I wanna say this, he goes to
the bathroom, I go to the bathroom.
I'm glued to his hip. Yeah, yeah, he's like, "Of course, that's what I expect
you to do. You must pee when I pee." I will. Good. I will. Poop when I
poop. I won't. That's a little too much. Well...
I will. I will. That's right. And so yeah, you keep doing these things and you
walk back into the kitchen and you see,
again, this is before the concert, so this is an area that's not supposed to
be open yet, really. But you see Leo the Collector walk in and you also see him
with one of his leprechaun slaves as well walk in too.
What up, slave? High five.
Yeah. Hearty, hearty, hearty, hearty. Yeah.
Oh yes, I live right what you oh shadowing a waiter. I see terrific
program he's tailing yeah it's
the chef actually think of it because shadow chef and to ale a ter a I brilliant
lovely stuff. Thank you, though, toss wherever you well he's also in the
kitchen because he's shadowing the ship. Oh yeah, well the waiter doesn't go in
the kitchen. They have a waiter's room, a waiter's pantry yeah
because they don't really bother with the food.
Oh bother!
I hope it's going well though the program, then you're enjoying it.
It's amazing.
I'm learning how to carry a bunch of stuff.
That's incredible.
And how to pee and poo mostly.
That's wonderful.
It's good to hear.
I will leave you to it.
And yeah, he goes and he turns to his slave at this point.
Now,
you slave at this point, he'll be free. So well, this is in the past, so you
never know he will be free. Yeah, he may be free. So you you see
husky tsune come out the door and she sees you. She goes
Patrick,
I say nothing because I'm pretending to be part of the door.
She rolled her eyes and she goes and she sort of like starts to linger,
I used to linger around. That's my creek sound and then I jump off the door.
Yeah, and I say, aha, I bet you thought I was part of the door. No, I said your
name, so I knew exactly who you were. Well, I couldn't hear because I was a
door and doors can't hear right
smart as ever
bitch.
deserve
like what do you want anything or what
I just take out one hundred. I just just I'm just folding hundreds. I'm like
look whatever you're going to do.
Let me do it and I'll pay you and I'll double whatever they're paying you.
what wait if we this is such a good strategy. If we have if we have
infinite time loops, all we have to do is go to every single and try to pay
them off and just pay them off here. That's why can we let's just skip
through it. We'll go through every single time when we choose a different
person, go up to them and say I'll pay you five hundred million dollars.
Don't what he said was whatever you're doing, I'll do it and I'll pay you and
I'll double whatever, whatever they're paying you way created so many for you.
she wants to perform yeah. I was like she's like I'm you want to go on stage.
If that's what you're doing, that's what I'm going to do my God yeah sure roll
insight
what that be bird owl
would be okay, then I got eighteen okay, it's time to simplify you have plus
three bird have plus three bird owl
apple more to bird
bird of an animal.
This is too complicated.
So
this is literally a
sheet for people who have mental this
literally for dyslexia.
the thing that still cracks me up. Maybe people haven't seen this because I
know we introduced these a while ago. I know I think the one that still gets me
so fucking good balance speed.
Speed is a picture of an outline of a rabbit
a big as rabbit
yeah balance ball. I was really I was funny because it's on my I haven't
transferred my hard drive to my new computer, so I couldn't find this, and so
had to re Google it and they added like now they added like dexterity and like
strength, like we need to add labels just because people are dyslexic. It
would be they can't read. There's a new one that's a Facebook like with a
metal. Yes, I that was never there before. They added proficiency bonus down
there and then like where you can list your skills, which I thought was a nice
idea. I like that it also skills I add bonus to
Oh, I add the bones for like simplistic folk like like
my God, it's both a simple character sheet and also one that's for this like
it's honestly still quite hard. It should be one number yeah. Yeah, it
should be yeah, then yeah that number against just average this out yeah. We
just do that and then we just roll again. I would be down for that. It's
basically what we do anyway. Yeah,
I'm still dead. I'm still I'm still fucking with the Pink Panther sheet.
Yeah, so you
So, with the 18, that's not all she's doing. You know that for sure. And when you said
to her, like, "Your insane thing about paying her," or whatever, but when you said to her,
like, "Whatever you're doing, I'll do it," it was not just a, like, "What's this weird
guy saying?" There was, like, a, "Does he know something?"
He knows.
So but then she brushed past it because then you said a bunch of random weird crap. But
like you noticed that she was trying to like hide something for sure. Like no doubt in
your mind. Can I roll perception? Because now I want to now I want to. You have the
ability Yoda's mind. I drew I drew Cameron. You can read people's minds. Oh my God. I'm
going to read her mind right now then. OK. So she has to roll to resist that. This is
- So you don't roll for that.
- Oh, she does. - No, no, no, no, no, no.
Nothing happened.
- This is goofy's, this is a goofy.
- What is your max? - An extremely goofy.
- I think the DC's 13 for you, yeah.
She does not pass it.
So you hear, when Yoda's mind,
it's you hear kind of at first surface level thoughts.
- Yeah. - Which for her right now.
- Then deeper, then question, yeah.
- Yeah, which are right, like so yeah.
So it's surface level thoughts and I sort of augmented it
where it's like, you get surface level thoughts,
then you can get a bit deeper in terms of motivations
and things that are really troubling them.
And then question, I sort of made this
into your divination piece of this,
where you get, if you keep, if you keep,
she keeps failing the DC and you keep wanting to dive deeper,
you can literally ask her thought a question,
like remind a question and get an answer.
So this first level though,
you do hear her basically think,
just 'cause it's right on her mind,
which is like, what does he know?
Okay, I'm doing I know that you're up to something. Do you say that to her? I say that in the mind
Yeah, I'll let you do that. Wait
No, I'm just gonna delve deeper. I'm gonna tell you okay
Okay, she fails again, oh fuck yeah, okay
She's really really concerned about how much people like mr. Groundhog more than her
and
case to stop it like murder him to I'm delving deeper I'm delving deeper.
She got a 20.
Oh, I'm son of a crap.
Redo the blue kicks you out.
But you know these things.
But now I look at her and I just say I know I know that you're starved for
attention and you're going to do something crazy tonight and I wanted and
whatever. Hey, you know what? I'm actually on your side.
I'm on your side, so I'll pay double what they're paying you to do.
Well, that didn't sound so on the side.
Role deception.
A crit 10.
It's a 10 plus...
Role speaking, yeah.
Okay, so that's a 13.
She's like, "Why would you want to help me?"
'Cause I'm on drugs and I'm bored.
that's actually I'm not a good role for that.
Basically, the best reason I've ever heard of you ever.
She says
I'm just trying to screw up his performance,
so there's no other motivations or anything like that. I want to go back
to jail.
Yeah, I guess you have a kind of you wait. I don't want to screw up his
performance. How you gonna screw up the performance? The performance was
unbelievable every loop. She clearly fails to screw it up right now. My
girl's in there.
He's a well, guess what? I know that she screws it up.
What do you mean? But let's get the details, though. Yeah, yeah, well, yeah,
tell me what's up, but I know that she's gonna fuck it up because that groundhog
is too charismatic and he probably he's probably bone in her right now. Patrick
completely fucks us up, but we go through the
here again.
he starts talking. He says I already know
yeah,
no, no, no yeah, we're good here yeah.
She says right now
she's trying to do him.
He's going to do her anyway. He's a complete pig, but he's a hog. He's a
hog. He's a ground hog. Correct. A hog is not a pig. I mean, a ground hog is
not a is going to give him a bad batch of technos line. I think he's going to
completely blow it tonight.
Well, he doesn't.
What are you talking about?
Just explain.
So I'm in a time loop
and I have to...
Well, he dies.
And you get framed.
What?
And if you don't want to get...
If you don't want to go back to jail, you're going to help me out
and
if you're involved in a murder
or something, or if there's somebody that you know...
What do you mean he dies?
I'm stuck in a time loop. Look, you're gonna fail at the, he's gonna do good on the performance
and I know that he's in there boning her.
He's not boning her. Why don't you go in there and check?
Okay, and the doors are next to each other?
He is boning her.
Yeah, he's... Look!
God damn it! But like, you see him also slugging down the drink that she gave him.
Don't do that!
(mumbling)
- Yeah, she poisoned it or some shit.
Yeah, I know exactly what you're talking about.
(mumbling)
Yeah, I don't know, I don't know.
Well, let me tell you, I'm stuck in a time loop
and you die.
(mumbling)
- Someone barging in on you having sex,
it's like, I'm stuck in a time loop.
- Listen, I know you're in the middle of something
right now, but you're gonna die.
And if we don't figure out--
- Hussie's like--
- How about you just--
but you're fucking traitor. You fuck me again. You asshole. Well, no, I didn't
he fucked her
and I think you see you see the ground hog. Go you see security go in and grab
Hussey to I'm going to get you for this Patrick Yoda. All right, off and now I
got to perform on the stage. I guess you see the ground. He puts his hand on
your shoulder.
so we'll go back to that in a second.
You are in the kitchen right. Let's have they when are they going to start
preparing the butter burger. Do I have time to do something else before? Yes,
you definitely do. Okay,
well, I guess
what else is there that I can do? I guess I want to go find and I want to
make sure that whatever I'm doing, I could be back in time for them to
completely start making the butter burger. Yes, you will be able to have
Okay, I want to go find your action this time. You can do one thing. I want to
find out Mr. Enterprise. Okay, cool. So we are now in the yeah, we're gonna
move forward anyway too. So the concert's about to start. So we'll go to you
too. I'm backstage. I'm throwing up.
You're gonna find Mr. Groundhog, Gary C. Enterprise
in the crowd and roll perception.
natural eight natural eight plus owl is ten. Okay,
it's probably that's actually probably sufficient. You notice that he has a
camera he did not have before. Okay,
I want to try like a big old fashioned camera with like a light bulb that
would like explode if you took the picture. It's okay. I would like to
first, I just wanna try and steal it from him without him noticing. Sure,
several side of hand. That is balance ball right, it's correct.
That's a 14. Okay,
let me see if he notices.
Yeah, no yeah, you're able to sort of like take this off of him and what do
you do? You walk away. Is there a way for me to view the photos on it or is
it so old that I can't see
because we're in the future? So I figured old camera could still be. You
you can see the photos on it. What's what's on there anything it's just it's
him vacationing with his girlfriend. Okay, well I take pictures of those
with my phone
as the chef and then I and then I tap and then I tap him on the shoulder and
as he turns around, I take a picture of him with the camera.
why I'm holding it up. He's small right. Yes, he is
give it to me. Why do you want it so bad just because it's yours? I need it for
what it. What do you need it for
promise? You won't tell he's yeah of course, right to gather partners and
speaking of partners damn
wait, wait, wait,
what's it out of play?
This is perfect. Our TV stopped auto playing, stopped playing the noir
background and now we're in a cafe. A beautiful cafe. It's a relaxing jazz
piano. So there's the through line. Wait, turn the volume up.
I wanna hear what this is. Let's hear this shit.
Okay.
It's a bad remote. It's not jazz at all so far.
I think this is jazz.
Completely jazz.
Oh yeah.
It's pretty relaxing.
It actually is putting you to sleep.
It is very relaxing.
Turn it down.
I'm going to save this video though.
Okay, cool.
So, roll intimidation, so speaking with advantage.
He was about to say that it was okay.
Yeah, he said he wouldn't tell, but he's almost there.
With advantage.
Okay, that's a 19, 17.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He goes for it.
He's got it.
seventeen. Yeah, he goes
trying to take a picture.
That's it
promise. I won't tell anybody
fucking more.
You go through the time with again
realize, oh wait, probably had something else. He's trying to do
it. Yeah, try to take a picture
Mr. Crown.
After concerts, he likes to go out with his horse
and I'm trying to take a picture so I can let people know about this.
Why?
What's wrong with... Why do you want people to know? He's ruining my
business. How? First of all, when you say my business, you mean our business.
I assume, unless you have something on the side, I don't know. He's not
touching hot soda, cold dog. So what's he touching? He's touching my... Your
thing?
I have a lot of...
Okay, this does kind of involve you guys, so you--
- I need to know about it. - Promise you can't get mad?
- I won't get mad unless it's--
- I have been selling action figures
based off you guys for a little while now.
- Slap him.
- Oh, my God.
- Are you serious? - Pretty badass, honestly.
- I want three of each sent to my house today.
- Socially maladjusted kids love it.
They've been using it to--
- So what's this Groundhog, idiot?
but he's basically been profit. He's been investing in knockoffs and then
selling them as his own. These are my statues, you guys are my guys. We
should kill that guy. No, I don't want I'm looking for I'm waiting for his
reaction when I say that
I just don't want him to be fighting, but just getting in the way of what I'm
trying to do, but it's actually a good idea. Kill him. We should kill him. If
someone did kill him, you wouldn't care.
Who you think would kill him?
I don't know. Okay, it seems all right, whatever.
Okay, okay, so when at what time are you planning to take the picture
after the concert?
We had question, are you planning to take the
making the butter burger or right
well, the butter burgers part of the I mean he usually bows out before dinner,
so I'm going to try to go right before they serve the meal and go out. You
mind if I take if I take the picture with you,
if you want to be involved with me, yeah, I could probably you
roll the
septum. He loves him. No, it's a nat twenty. I love you man.
Okay, okay, okay, I'm going to go out to the to the to the patio again
right right before we go into dinner and then meet me out there and then
we'll go out to the back. Okay, all right cool and I also want to text.
Am I going to miss the butter burger for this? Probably. Okay, I'm going to take
Sullivan. I'm going to text Sullivan and I'm going to tell Sullivan.
He's just way too down.
Can we do another time?
No, no, what do you I'm in the kitchen?
I just wanted to tell Sullivan to go to watch over the butter burger.
Can we do another time?
We were still Sullivan's phone.
His mind's broken.
I am and we go back to exactly where we are.
I'm going to roll athletics to see if Sullivan can climb out of the pipe.
This cycle.
He has not been able to.
he's been dying in the poop every time. So
okay, pretty good. Yeah, he'll get out of the pipe this time. Yeah,
I where am I with this waiter? So
right now you are
going back to the bathroom again with the waiter. This guy really has a
problem.
He might be diabetic. Yeah, his prostate. It's looking actually quite foamy
waiter.
Yes,
And as you see now walking there also is Leo's leprechaun.
He's going, "Heart to tart, heart to tart."
And he goes into the, like, a, you know, fucking stalls that have the doors.
A bathroom stall.
This is cool.
This is great.
The stalls with the doors.
This is exciting to know that this can happen.
So he goes in there, and you're watching him pee.
and when you see him come out, he is dressed like a sous chef.
The leprechaun. And he sees you, you see him, and he's like,
"Hart-t-tart-t." Oh, waiter, so please introduce me to your chef here.
He turns around, fully foamed, coming in and dacing on the leprechaun's head.
Yeah, yeah. "Hart-t-tart-t-tart-t." I've never seen this man in my life.
He's eating on him. I've never seen this man in my life.
Oh, well, if you've never seen it before,
oh, now I recognize
I don't know. I've seen this guy before, but never covered in P.
He wasn't so wet when I met the leprechaun sort of tries to dash
out the door. I don't know if you want to do anything. I'd like
to grab him. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah roll.
Let's say which one is that? I mean, that's basically that's strength.
Yeah, it's kind of strength. It's kind of dexterity. It's a pick one
because it's really athletics, right?
That's kind of how I see this.
- Strength is my plus three.
- It's either athletics or an attack roll.
Let's go with athletics.
- Okay, I got 19.
- Nice, yeah. - Oh, good strength.
- You absolutely grab him by the like scruff
of his hairy red neck.
- Okay.
- And he's like running in place.
(yells)
- Wait, taste the chef's pee to see if he has diabetes
'cause you're a computer and you can analyze his pee.
- Okay, I do that.
- You're a demon computer, so you taste it.
I grab grabbing him and I turn around kind of so smoothly. He has type four
diabetes.
Three. Well, that's actually not which doesn't exist. Yeah, that's the best
one probably right. It's the one where you live forever. Okay, but you also
need to pee foam all the time. All right, that's not so bad. No, he's gonna
die in like a day or so. Okay, well, do you wanna tell him?
No, I'll keep that to myself. Okay, that's cool. So yeah, the leprechaun is
now like sort of like he's sort of like you're holding him up. He's sort of
Oh, our to tar. He's like looking at you kind of sad like you look like a sad
dog. What are you doing and speak perfect English that I can understand
keep
to
sure, so I for God, you're a computer. Yeah, why you roll? Well, Google
translating your body. Is it still brain? Yeah, yeah, brain roll brain.
if you understand him. Sixteen nice. He goes I'm trying to
help out Leo.
It's Leo. Pretty good. What does Leo need from you?
He wants, I can't see, I can't tell you. Okay, so he wants a groundhog dead.
No, I don't think so. Wait, okay.
Is anything happening in the kitchen right now?
I don't know you're in the like is oh you're you're right. Is there anything
in the bathroom that groundhog day style I could bring up later and say like this
is about to happen and then it happens to prove that I'm in a time loop.
Oh
he's about to pee on you
he's like that already happened ten minutes ago
like in twelve dates of Christmas, the Hallmark movie that we've all seen where
she says that guy is about to...
Right, we know the trick.
Yeah, we know 12 dates of Christmas.
Everybody knows 12 dates of Christmas.
Yeah.
We're all very familiar with it.
I'm trying to think of what the thing would be.
Okay.
God.
Roll brain.
It's like basically a history roll to see if you remember
what's about to happen.
God damn it.
Well, I'll just observe and I'll do this again.
You have to do it again later.
Yeah. You don't remember anything, so you can't tell him that.
And he's like, no, I don't think so.
he just wants to, he wants to collect him for the zoo.
He's Scottish.
Wait, collect him for a zoo? He's not going to kill him for that.
But he could to stuff him.
A zoo doesn't have stuffed animals.
Think about that.
There's no stuffed animals at the zoo.
The animals are alive.
Maybe in the gift shop.
Taxidermy.
I mean, I suppose it could be a failed capture.
But I do not think it's this leprechaun.
So I'm going to take his coat, his chef's coat off,
and I'm gonna pat him on the butt cheeks, his little butt cheeks.
I'd like to touch them a little too long, and then I push him back into the dining room.
Okay, cool. Alright, we'll resolve that in a second.
I'm backstage, throwing up.
Time for the concert.
[gagging]
Mr. Beaver, I don't know how you fucking do any of this shit.
You need to stay with this hog.
I know.
He like grabs you by the shoulders, he slaps you across the face.
You hear, he's going, "Fluh, fluh, fluh, fluh."
You hear, "You can do this."
I can do this.
You guys go on stage and roll performance.
You and Hussie.
No, Hussie's gone in this thing. I've taken a deal.
You and Hog.
Performance, so that is speaking?
Yeah.
So that is an 18.
Wow.
you people are like Patrick Yoda. I thought he just skateboarded and stuff
and you tear it up.
Do you take the spotlight? You take the spotlight away from Mr.
Graff?
No, it's in perfect tandem.
I better find your heart.
And you guys are just like, everybody's loving it. They're like, is this a new
duo? Is this something we could do? I think it is. We haven't heard music this
biscuits and solvent had the perfect blue incident. This is amazing.
The plot of perfect blue happens to so yeah, it happened to solve it. We
can't pay
this is a deep lord thing. I like I remember that I just saw that like two
weeks
exactly to solve and so what's that?
You got to watch that about a frog. Yeah,
it's a frog movie, but he got it should be called perfect green. Actually,
think about it.
yeah
yeah, I can pose nude.
Can we talk about a movie? I know yeah sure okay, Harry Potter and yeah, a
little fire
what I compose nude
it now. Oh Jeez,
so you do this. The ground hog comes up to you, he's like he's like hugging you.
He's like all right, let's he's like like let's blow this joint. The shit
rocks. I hate that I throw this ground hog. Me and you are the new Tyler, the
created ASAP Rocky
going to do something incredible to get a real the ground hog. You think says
the N word, but you're not sure and you guys I'm pretty sure you can say that
and you go look I'm from I'm from space Boston. I say it all the time
from space
from space.
You guys go back into the dressing room. You see the like V girls of eeho's
Groundhog's kind of like he's with me and you see the girls are hanging on you
now
and I didn't see the performance and
want him off of that. Well, they just like it's like a yeah, I guess he saw
the performance and also thought it was dope and so then yeah,
listening at the timeline here too for this, making sure
so I'm gonna get a pic of, I'm gonna get a pic of Groundhog and Patrick Yoda.
of them tearing it up. Cool. Okay. Yeah.
Concert ends, you...
Can I say one thing first? Yeah, of course.
I make
all of... You make whoopee. I make whoopee, but not before,
not before backstage, I,
me, the groundhog, and all these hoes are doing in the classroom from Wild
and Out.
just tight we're doing we're doing that we're doing that as a party game. Okay,
Brandon is there
you walk in you're like
by doing that man, the time loop does fail and you start back to the beginning
again because you spent fifteen minutes doing that, but that means the ground
dog didn't die. No, he didn't, but you need to find out who did it in the
original time. We're back to the top. Okay, then I don't do that. No, you do
that. We're back to the top.
Back to the top. Leo, the collector, is coming up to talk with you guys. I do
exactly everything that I've done. Leo,
your zoo has enough. Leave him out of this.
What are you talking about? We're in a time loop, Leo. Dumbass, you think I
don't know? I know everything you do. Should I go to the toilet again? No,
Give me your phone. It's a time loop, Leo. I can prove it. I'm about to hump
Sullivan's mouth. Watch this. And then I do that for a little bit.
Say we're in a time loop. I knew that was gonna happen. And I need his phone.
I need Sullivan's phone so I can text them when I go backstage. Did that
happen before the time loop? Leo. I broke my phone 'cause I sat on it.
Yeah. Enough.
It ends today.
everything from every animal in your zoo will be freed.
I will never allow you to do that. That's fine. Then can you at least give
me one then?
If I can't do all of them, let me choose one. Let us have the groundhog.
The groundhog. Don't do the groundhog. Well, I don't have a groundhog. Yeah,
I know, but you're gonna collect him. You're planning to have a groundhog
tonight. You're acting all dumb.
Or maybe you just are dumb. And you killed the groundhog. Yes.
And your slave is mighty short.
Martin Short is his name.
Okay, can I try and see if he's playing dumb or if he really has no idea
what we're talking about? Of course, yeah, roll and say.
Okay, that is a 10.
I mean, you see him... Maybe if anyone else wants to roll too. I'll roll as
well. I'm gonna roll Patrick's mind. We're all hearing it. Roll Yoda's mind.
Is it intelligence? 'Cause you don't roll... Oh, wait, no, I don't roll
Patrick's mind. It should be called Patrick's mind.
All right, he fails. First thing you hear is that first level of thought,
where he's like, "Why are they asking me so many questions?"
He doesn't know. "Why are they asking me about..." Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait. So then the leprechaun... I'd like to talk to the
leprechaun now. Okay, but I'm gonna delve deeper. Okay,
let's do you, the leprechaun, then we'll do you, you delve deeper. Leprechaun.
Tarty, tarty. You can speak to him now. You, like, I'll say that you
exceeding that so you can stop doing what you want. I know that you want the
gopher.
I don't want to go for ground the groundhog. I know you want the groundhog.
How did you know that because they're both small because they're both small
which I just came up with
you want to have it because you want another small friend and your crew.
That's not why I don't know. So you do want to know shit. You do want to be
you fucking little bastard.
Artie Tartie Tartie tell me why I slap him to Adam to the zoo.
Why does Leo not know about this?
No heat, he's he's ordering me to do it. He knows about it. He's our what is
Leo saying right now? Oh yeah, yeah, don't deep yeah, yeah,
yeah, he feels he says
I hope they don't catch on to my plan to capture the ground.
Okay, but we already know that he wants to capture the ground hog, so I want to
feel a little deeper. Please be a good role.
What is that a fail? What do you wanna ask?
Are you gonna... Well, no, you're not. You're just trying to collect the
groundhog. Don't ask a yes or no question. Yeah. So... Ask something vague
where you force him to talk for a minute.
What are your plans for the night? What are your plans for the groundhog?
Just what are you planning to do tonight? What are you planning?
What are your plans?
What I'm planning to do is to tell my leprechaun that he's going to dress as a sous chef to
go backstage, to go back to the kitchen, to leave through the back door there, and when
the groundhog comes out to do his usual stroll after the concert where he walks around with
his horse, he's going to beat him up, take him back to my place, then we're going to
have him in the zoo.
Wait, what goes where?
Wait, wait, wait, ask him where the- well, they don't know that.
I don't know.
Ask him where that happened.
Ask him where-
Where does that happen?
Oh, behind the kitchen, of course.
Okay, I would like to go to the kitchen.
I would like to go to the kitchen.
kitchen, of course. Okay, I would like to go in this time loop to nothing
really matters time wise until that moment. I'd like to go sit behind the
kitchen. Yeah, I wanna go there too. And I still wanna have the... I wanna
get the camera again. I wanna repeat all of this. I want to repeat going
on stage with... Yeah, you'll be with Gary? Yeah, Gary. I am repeating going
on stage also. I would like to stay... You crushed the concert, Hussie's still
arrested. Okay, cool. I would like to stay fully stealthed. I don't want
them to see me. Oh, and I'll turn invisible. Okay, you don't have to...
you should roll a stealth roll.
Okay, I've got a lot of time to set up, so it doesn't really seem like I need to.
Oh, okay, I see what you mean. Like you're saying all the time.
Still roll it, just in case it's a one. I'm sorry.
But then let's go to the next loop, man.
It's going to be, yeah, you're right.
That wasn't great.
That's fine. It's fine. Like you said, you have tons of time to set up.
You go around, you wait backstage, you go around the security.
Maybe they have a business-style dumpster with a big flap.
slap or what they have a P O S. I actually don't want to be with Gary.
I want to not talk to him at all, but I know he's going there, so I want to
also stealth and hide and I can maybe even turn invisible right before it
happens, but I want to just like keep my eye on him without him knowing I'm
with them. We can have you outside and you, I'm still doing the concert.
I'm not changing. We're fast forwarding, we're back to the concert, the
concert's over, you're with the groundhog now, right?
And you guys go out,
the groundhog looks at you and he's like, "Do you want to do that dance we
did in the previous time loop. Now he doesn't you guys go out. Look, we're
not playing in the classroom. We're going to go walk around with your horse.
Brandon leaves
Brandon
runs away
in the class. You the whores all leave outside you yeah, waiting out. You see
the leprechaun come out the back of the kitchen dress as a chef. You see Gary
see enterprise walk around, take off to techno sign points for use or whatever
it is for using invisibility. Okay,
We have so many take off. I think it's five maybe for Yoda's mind for this round.
Ah shit.
This is going to be, this is going to probably matter. No, no, no, that's your refills.
On the left side. See the left, the right side, sorry stupid.
Oh right, right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, fill those in or just whatever you want to do to make it so that you know.
So, here's what happens.
You go backstage, you start to see Gary C. Enterprise come out.
you're out with the horse. Let their laughing. You're like
conga line
and this leprechaun jumps up, goes her to her to fight the ground hog. The
ground hog scared. Gary C takes a picture. The light bulb explodes. Flash
goes off.
The bad techno slime and the fear inside the ground hog. We are. Oh my
God, his shadow emerges.
from the light. Damn in retaliation, a shadow immediately beats a shit out of
the leprechaun. The whores run away. He scared the hose. He scared the hose.
When my shadow comes out,
yo, whoa, whoa, and then I want to stay hidden. I think we should say I'm
staying. Why do you do it? I'm invisible. Groundhog now starts to run
and the shadow starts to follow. I'm skating damn. It was his shadow all
along. Holy crap. I'm skating towards him. I hit my back like Power Rangers Turbo.
Okay, now that they're running away, I'd like to trail them. I have full sneak attack guaranteed crit to shoot the shadow in the head with my sniper.
But I'm going to skate. What are you guys going to do? Yeah, let's follow him or are you going to sniper him?
Sniper. I think we should follow and attack him. Yeah, I'm following. You follow the shadow and the groundhog.
the shadow, the groundhog, some would say into a part of the matrix that
doesn't exist. You hear Dr. Tool out around
damn it man.
Game stupid. Hold on
part of the matrix that doesn't exist or the matrix. It doesn't exist. This
is but how can that happen? It's the two guys, the two the two tick tock
guys.
So I hear there's a part of the matrix that doesn't exist. But wait, how
can it exist if it doesn't exist? Well, basically the shadow followed the
Groundhog all the way across the parking lot at the ground hogs, a pop star
right yeah into a place in the matrix that doesn't exist.
So this is like the this is like that that portal I know okay. I know what you
want this to be visually, but it's from Kingdom Hearts.
You know, Mike interviewed those people yeah, I know I read it. Oh yeah, it's a
good interview. He said they were really stupid
Dr. Tool-- oh, that's crazy that they are stupid. Dr. Tool Lateralis.
This is that scene in Kingdom Hearts 2 where Axel meets Sora for the first
time. I know exactly what this is supposed to look like.
And it's-- and the reason why the glitch is happening, Dr. Tool Lateralis
realizes and he tells you, "Because the shadow was created! You have to
kill the shadow!"
Okay. I figured we had to do a fight.
Yeah. I snipe, surprise attack, snipe, sneak attack, headshot.
Oh, it's an auto crit, right?
Yeah, it's a guaranteed if I if I
oh, it's a three with advantage because he's a sneak with advantage.
He sneaked as a one. Oh, my God.
So that's why I surprise around. It doesn't matter.
Yeah, you miss the shadow, though, turns around and sees you guys.
Rolling.
Just silently.
Roll initiative 11.
Wait, don't tell me that the groundhog is going to take damage
when we hit the shadow.
I said don't 18 that I won't tell you a plus one on this. Oh, my initiative is a blank
You have zero then no you know
Your initiative should not be it should be plus three. I think okay. Well, it's blanks. All right. You have 16 decks, right?
What'd you get I got 21 21 21 what'd you get I got 19
21 can you do something for me? Okay, I'm gonna imagine my song like that with the
ground hug. I'm gonna attack with my Grinch gun. Okay.
Well, that's a good rule. That's an 18 because it's plus six hits for sure.
Okay, and that's a guarantee crit because I went before him because I
remember that part. Uh,
do I roll it twice or double it? Roll twice.
Okay, do I double what's added
Like the +3?
Oh no, no, no. The +3 is just once.
Okay, then it's 12 damage.
Okay, nice. Okay.
You shoot at the groundhog,
the shadow of the hog,
shadow of the groundhog.
Shadow of the groundhog.
And I have two attacks.
You do. You have an extra attack.
Okay, that is 14.
Okay, it does not hit.
Okay.
Oh, bloody hell.
Alright, cool.
DC 15, Balder's Gate.
I am going to do the
hoverboard boomerang.
So whatever I roll, +5, +1d8, +1 damage.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just said it. And that is a 19.
That hits for sure. Yeah.
And then the eight.
There's a D.
Yeah, it's like two D fours on top of each other.
Oh, my fucking God.
One to. OK, cool.
One to you throw the hoverboard boomerang
and knocks the shadow, the shadow, the groundhog in the head.
And now it is his turn.
Wait, can I like?
No. So he has nothing to do with the groundhog at all.
So I can't like convince him to like do like a dark evil type song,
like JPEG, mafia, Kanye style with me.
Maybe you've warned me down a bit. I mean, it's kind of getting late.
Maybe you can, let's give it some time.
So he's going to
okay. Roll you, Patrick, actually roll D20.
Oh, what'd you get? Great one.
Oh, you see emerge from you a perfect shadow clone of you.
No. Oh no. I fuck it.
I fuck it one time.
And meanwhile, the shadow of the groundhog shoots a shadow beam at you,
Blotas. And yeah, he hits.
Tealing. Yeah, I hit. I fucked my shadow.
Oh, sheesh.
Seven damage to you.
And now, you're up, Ray William Johnson.
I gotta go pee.
I would like to use, I think I will use my sexual grenade on this fool.
Nice. Do it.
Tooshteknoz.
That's right.
Alright.
Please, please, please, please.
What is that, six?
Yeah, it's not gonna hit.
second. 12. Not going to hit. Okay. All right. Back to the top of the order.
You're up.
All right. I want to close the distance and use a melee attack. Okay.
That's a crit 20. Wow. Shit. All right. Roll for damage. All right.
That's 4,
10,
11,
12,
14. Wow. Okay. Yeah. He's not looking good. You go in there. You just start
beating
you
saying a shadow creature
a witness. I have another attack yeah
okay. That is only a nine yeah. It does not hit
and roll a d twenty
six.
I do when you miss
the shadow pops up right behind you.
and I go like this. It's a free
reaction with advantage,
but he misses both the town.
Cool.
You are now up Pat.
Okay.
I am going to use my lightning on who
ooh,
give your shadow clone.
It doesn't have like a cone of
no, it's like a lightning bolt.
It's like,
oh, it's one bolt.
Okay.
I thought that it was like
all of my fingers spread out.
into no it's not quite a lightning, not this campaign. Okay,
what is my shadow doing? He's ready to hit you.
Yeah, but I feel like I should if I kill the ground, the big one,
the little one will die.
Speaking. Yeah. Okay, I'm gonna hit, but also I bet historically speaking
also that if anybody else hits your shadow, it will damage you.
Yeah, so I'm gonna I did that gimmick once. I don't know if I
can get away with no. I'm gonna hit the ground. Stole it from you.
They did steal it from I'm hitting the ground. I was a consultant on that
though.
What I'm hitting the ground on the
you look at these a lot
fucking son of a
bit. Yeah, you missed. Yeah, and I roll with advantage
say that. That was a good role. That's pretty funny. The faster you say it,
the more likely it is to be 17. Cool. Wait, wait, no, no, no, that was a
two plus five. So that would be a, well, it'd be a seven. So I
didn't even get anything. Yeah, that's fair. Yeah. Yeah. I thought you didn't
anything. Roll a d20.
Why are you rolling like this?
It goes off the table every time
you can roll a different d20.
Then that is a 15.
OK, cool. Yeah, nothing happens.
You. Nope. Sorry.
Your shadow is up.
Fuck you, shadow.
Great.
Yeah. Crit 20. He's going to beat the
shit out of you.
Damn it.
This ain't right, man.
He does 10 damage to you.
So it's not so bad.
And now he's going to try to attack you again.
He misses.
Misses because I did this.
Yeah, he does this back.
The finger works.
Finger work this time.
And now you're up.
OK, I'm going to use my sexual grenade again.
Please, this time, please.
I'd really like to get a hit.
Oh, wait, sorry. Don't.
Yeah, sorry. I forgot.
It's a shadow hog's turn actually.
Roll a d20 though anyway.
- Wait, shadow the hog?
- Shadow the hedgehog. - 19.
- Shadow the groundhog I mean.
- 19. - 19, okay cool.
Nothing happens.
He's gonna shoot some--
- Jizz. - Jizz at you now.
- Okay, not a problem for me.
I dealt with that before.
- Okay, he does hit you.
- Don't tell me you never had jizz on your belly.
- He does. - I've had it in my belly button.
- He does 12 damage to you.
- You've only had it in your belly button,
but not, okay, I'm at one HP.
You've only had it in your belly button, but never on your belly.
You're real glass cannon this campaign.
Yeah, it's just kind of, um, it's kind of violating cannon.
Yeah, I know you're just kind of a killer in the original one, but I mean, yeah,
just kind of you changed it.
And this is a red glass cannon would actually make you more balanced
because I made you too strong.
Ballot. We die every fucking campaign.
Do not. And I should have a teleport to.
Yeah, I should have a free teleport.
I should give you free teleport.
I'll do the missing counters more fun.
Can I roll if there's risk to the guy who does the most damage?
Because then you guys have you to have to figure out and I roll.
Yeah, you can roll.
But what are you doing? OK, it's fine.
Tecto slime. Twenty one.
Twenty one. OK, techno slime. Twenty one.
Write it down.
Sexual grenade. I need to use techno slime.
Roll the damage for that.
OK, to that absolutely hits to the tens.
That's hard to meet in.
Two and so seven.
Nice. Okay. Yeah, he's not looking good. Now he's got to roll DC to see if he
can even move next turn.
He cannot move. I rolled that. That's the hog's shadow. Yes. Yes. Okay, good.
Yeah. You did the thing where you like you draw the circle perfectly. So it
does. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I mean, yeah, yeah. I've never I hate that shit. I
mean, well, it is fun to do that, but not for this. It's fun to do that. But
you're up by the way, Blotus.
Okay, 22. Yeah, that hits.
Yeah, we're seven.
Describe your kill territory.
Really? Oh, we're already.
Yeah. OK, well, beat the shit out
of him. You got a crit earlier.
God, what's funny to do to a shadow
guys?
Oh, you give it bunny ears.
I give it.
You give it bunny ears and a bunny.
Yeah, that attack was not even a lead
pipe attack. I just kind of said
create a shadow.
and I just yeah, I just went like this
and it goes
all right now. We have Pat's shadow to deal with you, but I don't know yeah
yeah,
you know how that works. Thank thank good. You see the ground hog on the
ground scared likely place for him to be
he's a that likely place for him to be Pat and he's looking around me and Pat
that session some memes over here and you see the leprechaun now come over he's
beat up and he sees the ground hog and he's like are you guys done with him?
Can I have him? No
we're we're getting fuck you. I'm taking this ground hog to the studio. We're
going to put out an album that's going to make me lose even more money. I'm
going to I'm going to throw the rest of my money on this album. I can do a
perception check to see if there's maybe any other threat to his existence or if
we maybe reasonably could believe that we solved my
habit. We solved it. You solved it okay. Well, I'm going to tell the leprechaun
you know what you know what buddy I'm going to put you on game right now
just because you're a slave doesn't mean it's okay to enslave others.
Damn, that's our first singles. What that's going to be about
in the ground hog. It's going to be a first single. He like starts. He just
starts crying. He's so affected by it. So what happens if you guys don't do
anything is he finds the ground hogs corpse panics, gives it to the chef and
the chef serves it for dinner.
I see you guys did it. Happy ground hogs day. Happy ground hogs day. We did
it. Another amazing way to do a short scene of us eating the butter burger.
you guys are eating the butter burger. It has
butter oil, ground meat, pepper, garlic,
I thought we got the meek animal away from the kitchen. Why did you write
this down? 'Cause I thought you guys were gonna be like, "What's a
butter burger?" We know it's a butter burger. I always wonder,
I feel like you should publish all your notes because... They're kind of
crazy though. I know, but you can go back and fix them. There's definitely
stuff that we never touch that needs to be out there. Yeah, that's true,
and I keep making it too bespoke, that's the problem. What's one subplot?
What's a sub plot that we never touched? I mean in the space one,
like- Or no, in this one. In this one- I read, I got a, I read a
comment from somebody. We did a whole episode about the space one. Stuff we
didn't touch. I mean, in this one, in this one you saw a lot of it.
You didn't see,
I mean, you didn't see like Leo, you didn't see the full phone call that
Gary C. Enterprise has,
where he finds out about what was going on. You also didn't see what the
leprechaun does in the kitchen where he starts to like he messes things up, he
starts to fucks up, he hides the Butter Burger ingredients 'cause he panics and
like, like that's when he's like, "Okay, I just gotta go deal with this." What
else did you not see this one? This one you kinda saw most of the stuff. Yeah.
In the space one, you didn't see,
I mean the entire... The villain we didn't. Yeah. You never met the villain,
the entire, like you guys... Who was it?
Who was it? I told you guys who it was. It was, it was,
- Well, it was a bastard child.
- It was the bastard child of--
- See, I read a comment from somebody.
I got a notification from the Patreon thing
and it said somebody was like,
"God damn it, if they just realized
"what the characters' names are,
"they would have solved this."
- Oh, I guess I named, what did I do?
- You named somebody something
that we should have all picked up on.
- I'd have to look, my notes for that one are in Obsidian
and I'd have to, I'll re-download that.
- Why are you writing in that?
I engrave them into and you know it's a different program, but no that one I
had
I had a whole thing with them, the assistant like that you guys were
supposed to help the British woman like who's like Belinda, who's like the
version of Belinda, where she is and also oh my God, the entire John Carlo
subplot where he had multiple missions for you guys to do that would help you
both uncover what was going on and also like you would learn more about how he
was like planting, like
basically he's trying to like
understand
because Leo, the collector in that one, technically what the
what John Carlo had on him, I think was John Carlo had it on him was that he
like like to play with toys and there was photographs of him and it was a
whole thing. I'd have to find it, but there was a lot of plots in that. Well,
all of this will be revealed in the plot where we are John Commander John
Shepherd style revived. Oh, can I do an epilogue for this one? The commander
Zap Brannigan character was a vampire from Transylvania. What? Loud ass ring
tone. Yeah, it's my buddy Rick. Rick, he's gonna Rick call. Let me do an
epilogue really quick for this one. So basically it's days after the time loop.
I'm sitting at home, everything I'm like, for some reason days after I'm
just
well, I think I can finally confirm we're not in the time loop anymore and I'm
and like well, that's crazy. We live suit through so many loops and there was
there's
there was none of it even matt. It all got undone basically just only the
perfect scenario actually occurred. Well,
that's just a job well done. I guess and I kind of I take off my work clothes.
I'm like and I go to my hamper to put my work clothes in. I open up the top of
my hamper. I look in a thousand pairs of underwear filled with jizz from when we
fucked each other
- Wow.
(laughing)
- I smell the underwear.
That's my edition.
- Amazing.
- Cool.
- And I have a number one top selling platinum album
with the grand code.
- We can explore that maybe in the next.
- When I get, we get revived like Mass Effect.
- I think we need to.
- We'll see.
- 'Cause this is, I like doing this.
- I miss this character so much.
- Yeah, I love these characters.
- You do it in every campaign.
- I do the same character every time.
- It's a little, yeah.
- No, the only one that I've ever changed up
is the new one.
Yeah.
That one is nice though.
All right.
Bye everybody.
Bye bye.
I do love mustard.
Me too.
I like spicy mustard.
I like different types of mustard as well.
I like mustard.
Mustard.
Yellow, brown, pink.
Oh my god I love mustard.
I fucking love mustard.
I love mustard.
I
so
crazy.
I
different kinds of mustard. I'm imagining hearing this voice, hearing
this voice saying you getting this at a call. I was going to say I wouldn't
know when you pull up to the
getting
my scenarios. You imagine being a ketchup lover and yeah, getting that
mustard. My my scenario is you pull up to the McDonald's. You pull up to the
McDonald's drive through. You say, Hey, yeah, can I get a burger and I'll get
some ketchup on it and you know it all gets a mustard to
through the speaker on the
oh yeah, yeah, okay. You want a big you want a big Mac yeah, mustard and some
mustard mustard.
This is the this is the cashier who's talking to you through the speaker and
that's actually pretty funny. I guess I'm playing the guy in the restaurant.
Okay, cool you so just get ready for your big your big moment because it's
coming up. Okay, but it's very funny for that to happen for
or someone for you. Pull out, you pull up to the to the drive through and
you're saying like yeah, I want a burger and then say, oh yeah, I bet you
do want a burger on and then you pull it. They're like okay, next one. Don't
you pull up and it's just the guy, he's just there. He's looking very cheap
and you're like sorry about that.
The whip
and I forgot about this. I was trying to prank you. I forgot how this works.
forgot about this part of it. I'm new here. I forgot you were going to see me
is my first day on the job. Yeah, he's like
he ducks down really quick and then he throws the bag in the car like a
grenade. The restaurant is like
and then the guy in the restaurant is like
this is so much better than the McDonald's in the parry.
[LAUGHTER]
(upbeat music)