I'm so fucking little.
All right. Do your thing.
All right.
Last time on Gun City, a broad city playtime continue fun.
That's also the wrong one.
Hold on.
I don't everybody moaned.
Oh, what if I can I can I control these still?
Yeah. OK.
Last time on Gun City, a broad city
playtime continue fun.
You're wasting them. I said, you know, I listen,
I set up all these cool things for you so you could pull them out and surprise
everybody. Okay. You went through 25% of them.
And the first what is wrong with my fault. There's there's only eight.
And then that's 25 only eight. That's the only,
really appreciate that. You did this for me. I'm going to delete them right now.
Please don't continue. I'm not using them ever unless I need to.
You learned your lesson. I did. Thank you. Yelled at me.
I can't see my fucking computer screen.
I'm so little.
Last time on Gun City Abroad City, Playtime Continue Fun.
The gang moved further and further into the Greech's lair,
outsmarting Stretch Armstrongs and freeing the leprechauns
who were held captive by the Greech Queen.
They stumbled upon an odd photograph, an old photograph,
with young doctors Ebenezer, Lateralis, and Maud Reddy,
along with then-prominent investor
of the New England, in the New England Federation,
Huge A. Fax.
Are we doing swear? Are we swearing?
Yeah, we're swering. Go buck wild.
OK, huge ass facts.
Upon this discovery, they called lateralis, who explained that he and Ebenezer
are you doing bunny is he and Ebenezer form playtime industries together
where they were trying to take advantage of the incredible energy source
Stargoon found inside a derelict alien spaceship.
Soon, Ebenezer, Maud and Hugh J.
Wrote it for the swears.
Yeah, and huge ass facts were lost to the stuff.
Lateralis abandoned the project before seeing it come to fruition.
Though, he spoke of unknown mysteries about the Stargu and the ship in general.
Armed with this knowledge and not much else, the gang sprinted toward the room that held one of the energy cores that powers the Pleasure Palace.
Sitting in it, laying her filthy eggs, was the Greech Queen herself, who may indeed be Maud Ready.
When the gang entered, the lights went out, and blowtossed...
Maybe. Maybe. Well, maybe. It may well be.
May well be. Shut up.
And Blotas was attacked by Playtime.
It might be.
And after a failed attempt at getting Maud to relax,
My throat is gut-slit.
through a phone call by Dr. Tool Adoralis,
it is Maud's turn.
And she's probably distracted. Oh wait, are we about to die?
Yeah. It might be.
Oh! I...
I thought we had a 10-minute event.
I thought we had Tool on speakerphone.
Let's take out your character sheet.
Shit. This is gonna be a...
Mine says that I have 33 health.
there's no you that's I have six. It says that my didn't hurry. You didn't
track anything then yeah okay, then maybe this is it's clear that this has
never been erased.
I give you a spare sheet. I have three yeah you have three, but also my I
guess my throat's throat. I guess I'm the throat woe wow excused, so
I'm not hitting nothing okay. I'm pulling up the this is patches playground
today.
Okay, so yeah, so
so
yeah, this is pretty grim.
You guys have it doesn't mean it's light hearted like the brothers grim.
Yep, no, I would not say the brothers grim is light heart. Have you seen the
movie? The child turns into has no eyes. I didn't even know
oh, I didn't know they made the brothers grim into a movie. Yeah,
really scare me when I was a kid. I used to really, really scare me because
he got a bear and Cohen. Sorry, I know this is no, no, let's just I know this
it's a lane. I really want to start. I know this is a tangent, but there's a
part in that movie where a child loses their mouth and nose and can't breathe
and they fall asleep. Do you remember when when pans labyrinth came out my
parent remember when that came out? Yes, my parents got it on netflix on the DVD
mailing and I wanted to watch it because they were like it's like oh it's a
dark fairy tale. I was like oh fairy tale that's for kids right, but they
wouldn't let me. They would not let me watch it. I wasn't even even get to see
one second of it about span. I remember seeing the scene on HBO where he stabs
a guy in the head and I said brothers grim no in pans labyrinth, a labyrinth
of Delphi. I was a kid, oh yeah, the butt of the gun or whatever. Let me
watch. Oh boy, it's the same guy. Yeah, as a child, that's not comparable,
though. I don't know if it was comparable or not. When I was when I was
a child and my mom would take me to Macy's, I'd be in a damn pants labyrinth.
Wow, I'd be running around to be high. That was yeah and one time when we
went to the pan store, I was in a pan labyrinth. Yeah, I hid in the clothes
the great queen time and my mom got real upset because I was gone. No,
it's a normal episode. The great queen is going. There's no set. There's no
set. Now I'm being normal. Okay, I'm not being my character. Let's make this.
Let's die. Let's die. Yeah, I know you have some stupid afterlife plan. I have.
I don't. Well, I'm throwing the thing in my hand at you. Okay, don't.
what was that it was the inside of a dog, a black pasta
the inside of a black noodle bag, the great
not a black being new. I didn't just have a noodle. I didn't have a noodle in my
short row. We're not gonna have time to boil her vaginal interior in your shorts.
She rears a back interior and she screeches and you all need to roll
constitution saving throws. How about I roll that we were talking about other
stuff that's other. Well, imagine a black bean noodle this size that would be too
big to be noodle. Well, you know what I ever do cool that I'm dead then okay,
what are we rolling for by the way, constitution saving for their thorough
and I got a three. I also got a three way. If we get three threes
nineteen, wait, what's my what's my I was going to say, we got three threes.
That's an angel number and that means an angel will come down and save us. Yeah,
so I have a plus zero on constitution, but you're safe.
probably not. I got a three. Okay.
What do you have? Zero, I got, I have three. No, how much health do you have?
Six. Okay.
You are alive still. Woo! What? You have
three HP.
Oh yeah. You failed, right? It goes half. Can you hand me that? I also got a
three, but I just assumed that... You're dead. Yeah, you are... He has five.
Oh, you're five? Oh, no, you've got two HP. It's a halfing, it's a half.
It's a halfer. Oh, it's a halfer. I thought it was a vagina. No, the halfer
for you, actually.
Oh!
Which is a...
Well, it's just halving them.
I won down...
I round down for everything, so you only take one.
Okay.
But you...
Oh, actually, yeah, but you two have...
I went to middle school with a kid named...
With a last name Halffinger.
You two have minus five on all your rolls for the next two turns.
Minus five?
I took one damage?
Yeah, on any roll you do.
Cool.
Oh, that's cool.
Yeah.
Yep, and then she is going to...
I mean, she's gonna...
The thing is...
She's a...
She's going to attack again.
Why would you say what?
Again.
Yeah, she's a boss. She gets two
attacks.
She should...
Yeah.
So...
I don't condone violence against
women, except for in the campaign.
Really?
But I want to beat the crap out of
this lady.
I'm still kind of laughing a little
bit about black bean noodle over
here. I'm still thinking about it.
Still getting it, black bean noodle.
The black bean noodle.
It's not that crazy of an idea.
gave an idea.
Who tossed the phone? It's a vegetarian. You did your dad.
You're honestly like a you're a bitch. I'm I'm just I'm zero one of her
tentacle dicks
perks up for a second. We wears its eye towards you and shoots acid through
your gut. Okay, I don't see any of that because I look the other way. Okay,
you're looking at the way you're ignoring it. Yeah, I don't care. You
don't care about it. Yeah,
through my head, who cares? Whatever I'm knocked out. Okay, can I at least
describe what I'm dreaming about yes, I'm dreaming that I got cast on Saturday
night live.
That's right,
which in this universe is a different show. It's the show I invented the show
in my head and I and when I wake up, which eventually I will, I will be
starting Saturday night live. Oh yeah, Pat, it's your turn. You cook that's a
better idea.
So I commit suicide. I yeah, so here's the options I gave you last time, which
didn't involve that, which I don't condone. You don't condone it? No,
these people are wrong. I condone it.
That's condemn. Condone means... I don't even know what I can do, 'cause
I barely have any Techno Slime. I can't revive him. How much Techno Slime
do you have? I have like six. Weren't you about to tell him some
options? Yeah, so Pat, you have the ability that you can kinda go crazy
Jedi mode if you flip your sheet over. Oh, yeah. You never really use
that. I'm gonna use that then. Well, let's... Why wouldn't I use...
Dubio, your stuff is still making sounds.
It gets me every time.
The Cameron spice.
The Cameron spice, yeah.
That is pretty good.
So let's take a look at that.
And then, I mean, here's the other thing.
You can use that and then again, you can run.
Yoda's mind or Yoda which one?
It's like, it's basically battle.
I think it's battle meditation, I might have called it.
Oh, that's actually from the stuff.
From Kotor, yeah.
It's from the stuff.
Battle meditation.
Yoda's mind.
Here, wait.
No, no, no, no, no.
maybe it's on this page. Definitely on this one. Yoda's mega mind.
What's that one? Well, that's so when you use like your Jedi power, that's
supposed to be me. This is my fucking asshole. So when you use you maybe look
like Baron Harkonnen, I think I said last time, which is awesome nerd
reference. Can I look at your sheet for five seconds? It looks like
the guy from Men in Black. I think that was I was drawing the well.
enough to know for you.
Jonathan, I'll tell you.
Is he still alive or did he die?
I think he turned into a bug
monster. Full of bugs.
You can't live that long.
They killed him in the movie.
Fucking your back sheets.
There we are.
Cool. He's looking for my
best. It's called use.
Nope. It's called use the force.
You need you need a techno slide
points to use it. That's so
funny. You have you have a
refill which you could use as
an I'm going to use the refill
as an action.
Also, use that.
You could also start
to run. No, I'm going to use this. Okay. I'm going to use my techno slime refill.
Did you just say that he could abandon me? No, he could pick you up and stuff.
Wait, wait, wait. So that, you use the force, so then I can use...
Once you do it, you can like, you have like levitation, you have extra
lightning abilities, you have extra mind abilities. And then my health boosts?
know, then what's the point? I'm just gonna pick him up and run. You can do
that. You could do that. I'm gonna do that. All right, cool. So
cool. Yeah. So, I mean, you could just literally pick him up and run like
just and run. And guess what I'm gonna do? What? That. All right, cool.
So you turn around out the door, you start to run down the... Like away
from her, away from the core, away from the bridge,
now back into like the main sort of like lobbyish area of the like prior to
entering the bridge of the Greech lair.
Do I still have my phone?
And I go like, "Bye!"
Your phone...
Bye!
No, your phone is still by her.
Okay.
So, Lateralus is still going like, "Maud, listen to me!"
Like, you know, he's still trying to...
Cam, you have to pick up...
I have a plan.
No, I got a plan.
Don't worry about it.
Don't worry about a thing.
You're not out of the combat encounter just yet, but you are like, you're further out of range.
Yeah.
I was gonna call in a SWAT.
Mm-hmm.
Baby, don't worry about a thing.
All right. So yeah, we are at the top of the order. It is actually...
What did I write here?
Oh, it's Ray's turn. Ray, roll a death saving throw.
Thirteen. You're okay.
This is another success. All right, now you're up.
Okay, so what's every detail that I know about
the mod?
at some point pregnant with Ebenezer's Child.
Say every detail out loud.
But so okay just pretend I know all these things.
You do.
Yeah pretend though because we're playing D&D.
Yeah so it's all about pretend.
But what I'm going to do, what I would like to try to do is I want to use my I'm Who ability
which is teleport up to 30 feet to a location you can see.
If it is occupied by another person they must roll a strength or dex saving throw against
spell DC on failure inside their body and control them for six seconds until you
phase out of them. So I want to try and go into this thing's body and then be
like just start saying all of the details I know about the what it about
Maude and just be like I am and I and as a may be like I am Maude I was pregnant
I did all this stuff or whatever and try to remind her back out of and make it
listen to the phone and that's and just fucking chill out. Such a cool idea.
So I want to try and do that so it has to roll a strength or dexterity and this is the last
of my techno slime too and my spell DC is 14.
Okay.
Let's see what we got here for her stats on that.
Where is this?
This doesn't, if this doesn't work I'm going to nut.
Okay.
That'd be a weird reaction.
Yeah we got to try to avoid that I think.
That's okay you can't see it.
I'm going to nut out of scaredom.
Yeah.
All right.
yeah all right, yeah sorry yeah it by God, so you teleport into her and you
just kind of get knocked back and you're kind of just
standing in front of her. Now, let's move your character right in front of
all right, so the set up is also you guys right guys. Also, I know I did
that I had a plan or did anything, so you just saw me teleport right in
front
Oh man, it is her turn. Unfortunately, probably will focus on maybe there's a
fly flying around her head. She tries to swat yeah fly named your
dead. I'm dead all right.
No, I really thought that was going to be it, though you have to admit that's
a good plan. I love it pretty good. It was a great plan. It wasn't as good as
run, but it was pretty good. Yeah, oh yeah runs kind of boring. Well, we ran
we're a lot of fourteen minute and with his we'll have to figure out what I
think if this really is how these characters die, including solvent, by
the way, who wait, we're so wait, solve and save us solve it is knocked out on
your chest. Oh yeah, I have a bound to be getting right. I'm using him as a
bullet.
It was really good use of solvent. It really was probably the only useful
thing he's ever done. Okay, I'm stupid frog now. Sometimes he can't hear me
just sometimes I feel like you're so let's
whose turn is I don't like so long because he's a little learn all the
other. Yeah, I got it characters. He is smaller.
What is her health? Oh yeah, I guess she goes health bar. She's just gonna
move towards you guys towards the door. Okay, she and how do we say
your health bar? Okay, Pat, what is her health? You are the only person
alive. You have to health. You have to save both of us
or you have to run away as fast as what happens if he leaves us if he abandoned
what
run really fast was my suicide threat ability that we established. I don't
think it's going to register. I don't think that she speaks English. I think
you have to leave us by and I think you have to run as fast as you have to get
out because if you survive, then at least we don't have to do a hard reset.
If you survive, then I can come back and me and Caleb can play on our phones
while you do the rest of the
or
come back as girls.
I never played a girl character in the game.
Canada.
I still have my hover board. Yeah, you do I fucking throw that thing under my
feet, double like
agility check yeah yeah, I guess well, no, I mean you can just kind of like
I'm whipping I'm getting the hell out of here. I throw ray all die and then
just like out of like a big steamy room comes this girl for
just
still dead on your chest
Salvina yeah, no dead girls, the dead girl frog
let's you could just
we don't use your dash. I still make a I'm using my the only thing I will. I
still oh you guys did you guys you guys I'm trying to remember you guys killed
the stretch Armstrong right yeah yeah right you killed him okay cool so that
was the only other guy I think that's here so you can keep running okay then I
go all right you keep running she keeps moving towards you let's do death saving
throws for you what does it matter we can't get up any even if it's a saving
throw for you someone might be maybe might come find us if he goes and oh
Oh yeah, no, I mean you'll probably be eaten before then nine. You can't
you're not supposed to take a side. That's a fail right. That's true. Yeah,
you can't take
you are now pat you are a you are probably far enough away. Now there are
likes to like kind of like mindless creatures that are like looking for like
a monster body to like latch on to, but you're probably far enough away that if
you have any techno slime left to heal, you could heal ray. Okay, wait, how's
far enough away that I got it. Oh yeah, sorry. Do you see her get to the door
and she stops and starts to turn back and so go back further towards the
core. She won't leave that room with the core. Well, get me up, God damn
it, and let's go save Blotoss. All right, I'll do that. Don't run back in.
I have... Okay, I will take my... You're gonna get healed, get up, run
back in and die. No, I won't. I'm gonna use my techno slime refill. Okay.
so take it off your thing. Okay, you're already yeah. I think yeah, I should have
given you guys pencils. Oh, I did give you all pencils. I gave everyone pencils
actually, but
right. I forget. How much does the refill fill fills five technoslime points?
Okay, so you just use all all of them. You should probably use them all on.
Okay, I'm going to use them all. Yeah, wait. So then 11 is how many points 15.
I have one left. Okay. Sorry. Each one is one point of HP given to me.
No. All right. Then I'm gonna use the... I'm gonna use four skin on him.
Yeah, I think it's 1d10, right? And then... Oh, yeah, d10. I think it's
1d10 and plus four? I never can tell which one is the... Is the d10?
The d10 is... Yeah. Pretty much the same as the... Yeah, it's the roundest.
It's very close. It looks very similar to the d8. This one with the
10 on it. No, that's a 3d12. No, you had it. You had it. Okay.
The way to think of it, the D8 is like 2D4 stacked on it.
That sounds like it's not going to be helpful.
Two pointed one.
That's a three.
So yeah, that costs and then so I think you add four to that, right?
I never remember.
Yeah, 1D10 plus four.
So seven and you get the full one because you're not just grabbing his
foreskin and putting it over you.
So I have seven.
You get seven HP back.
So that's what you can do for your turn because we're just just because
we're still in the like turn order here.
Okay, I am running back in.
Is it my turn?
Yeah, I mean, here's the thing.
The only, yeah it is, oh actually wait let me check if it is.
Sorry I'm like goofing up the turn order here a little bit.
- It's his turn.
- And he's used a single phone.
- It is actually Blotas' turn, sorry yeah.
Blotas yeah roll a dead sign.
- Oh brother.
- And then it's, then it's.
- 18.
- Nice another save.
Okay and then it's Mama's turn.
'Cause I forgot to, I realized I skipped a turn here.
- Her name is not Mama.
- Oh yeah I called her.
- Let's try and keep the lore consistent
between the episodes.
- He called her Mama, the guy called her Mama earlier.
- His name is Maude.
(laughing)
- Asshole.
- And Maude is not short for Maude.
- You're gonna hear--
- It would just be Ma.
- Mud, mud.
- You wouldn't hear this,
but I guess you guys would kinda hear this.
- Get him!
Kill him now while he's down!
And so--
- Wait!
Motherfucker said what?
- So, they heard that.
Not lateralis, sorry.
- Oh.
- Yeah, that's very confusing.
- Really sounded just exactly like--
- I need to figure out, you said this last time,
I haven't figured out a better, different,
I guess I can do kill him now while he's down some or maybe
never mind.
Thought about it. Okay, cool. So yeah, she is gonna start digesting you.
Well, she didn't even eat me yet. I'm gonna walk in and I'm gonna grab my
nuts and I'm gonna say, digest these, mommy. So you are six, you are about
like 90 feet away, so... You can do that from 90 feet away. You don't have
you be close yeah. I'm just talking shit. You just hear like
when I
grab my nuts at so it is ninety feet away. It was like in it.
Those sounds like when you try to use a skill that yeah, just cool down
doesn't load in it.
You're dead blow to I'm dead dead capital D. You're dead, fully dead
you're. Can I rip my character sheet down the middle into the microphone? You
can
way.
Low toss piss.
Who's been with us for a long time,
like three years.
This is the first time one of the big
threes died, right?
Yeah.
I drew.
Didn't I die? Patrick Yodar.
Oh, yeah.
Three original gun city characters.
Yeah.
This is a reboot.
This year is really a reboot year.
Yeah. For the past six months.
Fuck it, bro. I'm killing.
I I'm like you're despondent.
Yeah, no, no, I'm not despondent. I am thrown into a
can you get a rage and I'm going to kill this squid
or whatever. Let's do it. You run in there seven HP. I think we need to do.
I think yeah. All right, roll. I'm doing this for you.
You understand me? That's I can't believe I got it. Yeah, I have to. Oh,
wait. Are you talking?
There we go. That's better. Thank you for muting. Yeah. Okay, so now you're
up so let's well actually so it's her turn and then it's really actually
Pat's turn. Yeah, I'm there's so much fear in me right now. You're not gonna
die for your friend. I'm in the corner. I'm jacking off. What? What? What is
that? How's he jack off? I'm nasty. We're all nasty dude, but you don't we're
trying. He just died. Can you show a little bit of fucking respect? That's
what he told me to do.
What the hell is that? That's what he told me to do when he died
in his... Back in the day.
Somebody's playing some instrument that only goes, "Ooo."
Yeah, the squid is a therapy. And then somebody just played a gorilla song.
Alright, I'm not jacking off. Okay, what are you doing? Come on,
help.
We have to kill this bitch. I'm looking at porn on my phone. That's not...
That's halfway to jacking off. You also don't have your phone. That's more
than halfway to jacking off.
lateralis
here's that's like that's like
what else here's you getting eaten
watching porn on their phone on the bus. I wouldn't I wouldn't be half as mad as
if I saw them jacking up, but what are their percent is matter they're doing
this yeah. I still wouldn't like hands up, but I feel like
I'd be half. I think it's halfway. I think it's maybe even forty percent,
yeah, because like sometimes somebody, you know, funny. I mean, I don't know
it's just
I'm giving benefit of the doubt in that case. Definitely, it's definitely not
half as bad, but
eighty percent, but it's a way there. What if it's like a hard core of the
movie situation and they're seeing their own daughter on that thing right if
they're crying,
that's a thing and they're watching porn and crying. I am not touching that
situation. I'm not feel bad for them. I'm not stepping in and saying knock it
off. I'm just I said I was I walk up. I'm saying tissue. I'm going to shoulder
to cry on you. What's wrong? Do you need to want to talk about what I wouldn't
expect you to need a tissue for, right?
Yeah.
All right. I guess I'm going to... Can I throw a techno of my foreskin at him
before he goes?
Excuse me. At me? At him or me?
At him.
At Ray.
You'll let him...
To heal him a little more.
I don't want... No, no, no, no, no.
You don't want it?
I want like the...
Okay. Then I'm using Yoda's dark slide.
I'm using the...
You're using the force?
Yeah.
Okay.
Can I use... Can I do like a rally thing?
like I send out a big burst of energy that helps him out?
Energy? You could do that. Force?
But, okay, here, if you want to give him like force powers, but there's got to be some
risk to you. Can we meld together?
You guys want to fusion dance and go and kill each other?
Can we at least Freaky Friday just for the last couple minutes of us being alive?
Yeah, if this is what you're committed to, we could do that. Well, how would we do it then?
Explain. So, well, you're a computer demon.
Yeah, maybe you upload yourself into him instead and then maybe my God and our health would combine
What if you guys?
So true and then maybe my health combines and you guys get like negative 50
Yeah, and maybe we combine with some of the other stuff that's in the room and we become really strong
So now he has all the powers of a computer, but also Yoda's force and also a demo and also a demon
do we do that character would have been way better can it what okay? What if
it's this simple? I take his asshole and I've put it on my head, so his entire
body is the head of the demon. If it's that simple,
I just put your computer on to him because you're the computer right fine
and you're just the demons like your but I try that first and I take a
and then I take them. Yeah, perfect yeah, and I don't you're going to get
cancer and I'm a computer easy computer. Okay,
no, I actually don't. I would just want to die all right. Okay, I want to run in
there. Everyone wants to copy me. What am I going to do
buddy? I'm going to shove you use the shelf shelf. Yeah, I'm so mad. It's like
when your buddy gets in a fight outside of the party. What the fuck is up? Yeah,
I'm going to do that, but my friends being eaten yeah, yeah, so I ran action.
What does it say that you should do for your show action athletics versus
athletics? So you're going to roll against her athletics. She's also is like
the kind of fat right yeah she's a bit of a size up, though, so it's going to be a
little bit. She can have some bonuses. There's a now that was a
fifteen. She also got a fifteen. Whoa, we I think you win. I win that right or is
it the yeah because if you match a see typically I've never heard of a me
stop this. I've never heard of a shove. I shove her. You do show
yeah, I show you why my what the fuck is a fucking bitch and then I do one of
the why by litigating this yeah, oh, they're kind of a soccer style. Fuck
that's make sure anybody who sees it gets it yeah, okay, and she what's your
AC
my AC is fifteen. Okay, mister,
so she gets the role again. No, she is to rose. She misses both of her attacks
on you just now. Well, she's like slapping her dick. You you shove her
back, she kind of lurches back and then she starts slapping her dicks around,
try to, like, whap you with it. Tell me, yeah,
stupid bitch, keep shoving her. I think I might be invincible. Keep shoving her.
All right, you're up. I tell him to keep shoving her. That's what you do. And
then I use, yeah, I use the force to okay, just push it, push it. All right,
you've you've you taken did you take techno slime? Let's say you took techno
slime last term because you didn't do any. I took time with my refills. Oh
yeah, you did take all of them. So yeah, you used to force techno slime is
complete. Read what used to force does use it. Let's read what let's read what
this move does. That is like the longest most involved move. You ever use
action. You can use the force for thirty seconds, giving him an extreme boost in
combat and ability skills. Ultra deflect AC increases by two and as a reaction
can automatically deflect all non supernatural miss with his hoagie
supernational Yoda fast movement speed is doubled and Patrick Yoda can fly up
to sixty feet vertically.
I gave you such a cool move.
Yoda strong, melee attacks do, well yeah, I'm saving it for big things like this.
This is it, you're right, you're right.
Yoda strong, melee attacks do plus two additional damage.
Yoda bonus lightning, Yoda can now cast lightning as a bonus action for no cost.
Dealing 2d6 plus wisdom can't be charged like Yoda lightning.
Yoda telekinesis, based on a wisdom DC, check against the size of an unbound object.
Automatic for tiny plus small.
DC 10 for medium, DC 15 for large, DC 20 for huge, DC...
You can move five for guard. It's Yoda in Clone Wars when he's lifting the
fucking. Oh my God. Yeah. Okay. So in the fifth movie, when he's like, turn,
I turned my eyes, turn blue and shit. Yeah. And then I run into the room and
I try to pick her up. Is there, we're near a cliff. You're on like a bridge,
like, yes, it's like the bridge in episode one, like when you're fighting
at least fighting. Okay. Then I'm going to pick her up and throw her off the
bridge like Palpatine. Oh, you're going to try it. Yeah, we'll give it a shot.
Wait, what were you about to say before we do that? That's a steal.
Well, I'm going to I'm going to shove. Well, we'll do his turn first. Yeah.
So yeah, that's going to be a gargantuan. So it's she's not gargantuan,
but she's large. She is large. That's DC 15. What does that mean?
Well, it's yeah, I have to roll. Well, she's also she's on an object.
I have to roll 15 DC 15. No, no, no, no. So really what it is,
this is just like you're going to contest her
in this regard. I can't have you just move because she's not like an object
technically, but he's an object. She's a woman. I knew this is going to happen,
right? So I was trying to preempt.
No, it's just fucking disappointing.
So I hope you do die. Yeah, let's no, no, no. So I take two
no, no, no, no, no, no, we're not doing that. You can't get out of this that
you
do
strong. What does it say there? I'll see if you always realize you have minus
five to all your roles to from the screech from earlier. Oh, no, it's been
more than two turns. Sorry. So what does it say? So you have plus two. So
fourteen and then two additional damage. Let's just make that also add to your
role. I think that's fair. I should have. Well, yeah, I should have made that.
What are you saying? Right? Doesn't matter. And then add your regular
strength. What is it? One is it minus one already? Oh, I'm sorry. It's OK. So
13. So she's going to roll. Yeah, okay. So you fly in and like like like Ray,
you just like her, I guess like like he just sort of like like goes around you
crashes into her. You like kind of push her back and you're like going back and
forth and she's able to with her like dick arms like just like shove you off
though. So I'm dead. I fell off the thing. Not yet. She just shoves you off of her
and you're still like flying. So you're kind of like hovering in midair like in
in front of her in front of you. Okay. So well, okay, then why don't I use Yoda
fast and move sixty feet vertically? That's your turn.
Yeah, so I can't do that. Not right now. No, you already did your turn.
Okay. I'm gonna be in on turn order. I think it's her turn probably, right?
I'm gonna check. I don't know why I keep forgetting.
It's Blotas's. He's, no it's not. It's your turn. Oh, for my turn? Really? For
my turn. Can I can I take a turn, though from you to turn? I just want to show my
drawing. Okay, show this you put it on the table, put out the table.
Wow,
dinner, that's dinner, hot dog burgers,
really true. Jubio honestly you work as a oh and you knocked the girl over. So we
went
one. I would like to walk up to this bitch and I don't use that word lightly
and I would like to shove the shits the shit out of her. This is okay. Do it
Yeah, rolls. Let's just do it. Yeah.
What's he get?
And I don't know. I told I rolled an eleven.
All right. You kind of just like your hands, like kind of like
do I shove her at all? No.
She kind of like moves a little bit.
Can I please just shove her?
No, it's OK.
Do I have like some kind of you're both your A.C.S.
My mind is double right.
Mine is fifteen. Mine is all my stuff is double yeah. My
increases.
Ghost block the attack. Okay,
really
that is so sweet. They see a ghost. So now really here's the question is is how
big of an asshole are you going to be about this? No, no, you guys want to
know
do we want to spend the rest of the session because you're both dead. So we
lost all three.
that's really how you you didn't have some big you didn't have something
written. I gave you the option to run away. I did run away and then I wanted
to show her. I will write something up and I'll even put it over a video and
you could just shove it in here as a in memoriam or maybe at the end of it. It
better be
better be. It'll be very hard for I love these characters so much. I can't
believe we all three died in the stoop optional. Now we gotta make new guys.
what that was the so that wasn't even the final boss. No, nowhere near the final
boss. It's nothing no. I got my I got attacked by the final boss. We didn't
even find a time.
Do you guys want to know can we take some guesses? Okay,
what do we get? We have a twenty twenty five the rest of the story or
I want we've it's always been. We try to guess and you've always given us, you
know, two good guesses per episode, I'd say okay, so I would like to do about a
twenty minute guest session to just see if we can guess okay, and you have to do
all your yeses and nos in the voices that you have programmed that we will
unfortunately not see like a podcast DJ. I know okay mixing it. Let's do it all
right so
guesses so I still know that have been the Grinch the now the Grinch. No, it's
not the Grinch. Okay, it's all yes or no stuff.
Was it the guy who pushed us down the well?
no shit was it his boss.
No was it huge as facts
no was huge as facts involved in the badness. Not really. I don't think so
no, not really okay. I still my words was was it was it was a low job. No
was it somebody that we've met was it somebody who was who was it was
somebody in that picture of all the people in the picture. No
well, then I don't have any guesses. Then okay, well, that wasn't a yes or no. I
guess
do you think I have any more guesses?
I think
I think you can. What would be the best ending? What would have been the best
and why don't we do? Why doesn't so wake up and go figure? I have another one
hold on hold on. I'm solving to go figure it out. Okay, is is new Sullivan
alive. Yes,
he's alive without any parents.
He's safe.
What do you mean he's safe? He's play time.
Don't do that because
that would be jumping the shark. I would fire you. That would be jumping. You
would be gone. No, he's not. We would fire you on the spot if he was play
time. Is there any way that we can zoom out and then zoom back in on wherever
little new Sullivan is and I just want to see I just want to make sure on my way
to hell. I want to make a yes, that's true. Can we all can we we could do a
hell can we go to well, can we right now go to hell and I do a hell campaign
somebody tell us everything when you're a demon so may or your demon part is
maybe just so then I'm just maybe I'm just a computer sitting on the ground
yeah, I have nothing to control yeah, you don't go to heaven or your computer.
You just get to lead it turned off. No afterlife yeah, you just power down, but
go to a day to recovery. I think it's arguable that that ray william johnson
had more heart than almost anybody that is arguable and you know, I'm just
thinking now. I think it's very it's very lucky to the continuation of this
story that we all
during in between this campaign in the last one each impregnated a woman.
Yeah true, that's very lucky that we did that. Oh yeah, I forgot that we I
completely forgot that we all impregnated women with yes, specials
terms that become identical when I come out. Did we have a name for that,
too? Yeah, it was called Identical Sons. Yeah. Oh, my God, we did have
literally
a
we literally had a plan. We had a we knew this
technical son. You a t p k. How could you possibly okay, but I do what I
ripped up his thing. Yeah, well, that's that's I got a blow toss. Yeah,
that's not what I was doing. I would really, really like to go see check on
Sullivan before we go any further, just so that we can piece it together from
there.
Yeah, I'll tell you where he is. So you guys remember Reddy, right?
Patrick has monkey pucks.
Reddy, Maud Reddy, right? And then there's Reddy.
That white bitch.
So there's Reddy, the assistant scientist, right?
The one who pushed us.
Yeah.
So how do you want me to tell this? Like a story or like with answers?
I literally wanted to zoom out.
Imagine that we won the game.
We zoom out.
We're in a small room.
We're on YouTube right now and we're looking up Final Fantasy VII best ending.
Okay, thank you. I got it now.
Maybe a little, maybe actually, yeah.
So you're in a, we're in a small room.
You see this hunched over young scientist with that messy red hair.
He has a microphone near his face and he's screaming,
"Kill them! Eat them! Kill them!"
And, uh, um, he's like getting frustrated and then he looks in his monitor and he sees as
um, Maude Reddy, his mother, eats all three of you, digests you.
And a smile creeps on his face and a sigh of relief.
He turns around and he exits this small room with these like monitors and this like speaker system
to a
uh off-white room with basically completely bare. R.I.P Virgil.
Which... Oh that Virgil? Yeah. Thanks. Um so. You said off-white. Oh.
You go into this room and you see New Sullivan and in this room there's nothing except just
just a bunch of little toys that New Sullivan's playing with. He's playing with the little action
figures of you guys. Yeah, he's like, "Oh yeah! Wow, wow!" He's playing around. He's
uh, he's uh, he's looking around. He's like, "Playtime! Playtime!" And in swoops, from
nowhere, this alien that doesn't really look... it's an alien. Okay, I'm done with this. Yeah,
yeah,
right this
alien. Okay,
okay, cool,
a cowboy comes in
and it's this
It has these gnarled sort of like fingers and this face that is kind of contorted
and twisted with eyes like they're like little slivers similar to what Maude,
the monster's eyes were. And he's covered in these like black and green kind of
like flesh that's kind of like warped together and he's like hunched over.
Looks similar to Reddy but he's not. It's a different person. And it's making these
we're clicking noises as it approaches New Sullivan, and the hand is going
for him, and then you see he picks up a toy, and they start playing together.
And Reddy is...
Says, "And I'll get you more playmates soon." So you're saying this is a
sloth from the Goonies style situation?
A little different. So... So Reddy stole New Sullivan from us, and that
that was his only plan.
So playtime...
Was to take New Sullivan and put him on his ship.
So Reddy is the illegitimate child of Maude and Ebenezer.
Yeah.
I see.
And he grew up in relative...
He basically grew up as Ebenezer's unwanted son.
Yeah.
Maude was a failure of an experiment that Ebenezer started to do to her.
And Ebenezer doesn't even acknowledge Reddy as his son.
Reddy...
Playtime, the thing, the noises that Tull Lateralis was hearing when they were working on the
ship and the noises that you have been hearing was this alien. That alien
derelict ship that was discovered held the child of a like alien race that
exists like one of their children. Oh my god and it was New Sullivan? No it was
Playtime and Reddy. I can't even follow this story anymore. Playtime was killing childless
couples because he was resentful of anyone who didn't have children. Because
he likes playing. He likes to play and he misses his parents. And then he found in New Sullivan
the perfect playmate. And so why is Reddy involved in this whole thing? Reddy discovered the alien.
The alien had escaped all the scientists' grasps except for Reddy the assistant. And
so Reddy said, "If I will..." Basically, Reddy is kind of cracked from resentment and basically
did the whole playtime, played it up, did the announcements on the loudspeaker, did
the whole media campaign for it and just said, "You go out and basically,
I'll target people for you to kill
and to cause this mayhem." And basically, it was like, "You just kill
people for me and I will give you
this perfect playmate here. I'll give you toys, I'll let you live in
the ship." So basically, the whole story is that
New Sullivan is too good of a kid, too perfect of a son
that we couldn't there's no way we could ever hold the most unwanted with the
most wanted son, huge ass facts wanted to you just facts part of his position is
that so he was an investor for Leo,
but he went he kind of turned you know, went went towards a criminal path, but
he has dirt on everybody in the federation, including Leo. He has
pictures of Leo specifically playing with toys, girl toys. No,
That was dirty. That's why I was able to operate his enterprise. That makes sense.
That makes a lot of sense. Janet Blowjob did was actually this was a whole...
Fuck! It was a whole other thing. Janet Blowjob was working for John Carlo.
Bloody hell. She was a double agent working on both on the case. Yeah, I figured that out.
I didn't know that. She was working on both the Leprechaun Rebellion, but she was also
people working with huge as facts to try to destabilize this the both of the
England Empire by playing up both sides on behalf of John Carlo. If you guys
went down that John Carlo path, a lot of his jobs, he wouldn't have given you
like details, but she would have been your contact and you would have done
stuff to help continue to destabilize. Yeah, so can I ask you a question is is
Is New Sullivan happy?
He is.
Okay.
Is he?
So this is kind of...
He misses you guys.
He misses us, but overall this is maybe kind of a story about three guys who created a
Frankenstein perfect child and...
If New Sullivan was in danger, it would have been one thing.
He's not...
Playtime would kill everyone in the world for New Sullivan.
Does he know what happened to us?
Does Playtime know New Sullivan fed New Sullivan?
he tells him? Will he ever know? And if we're going to come back to New
Sullivan at some point, I don't want you to answer that. Okay. Because one day,
and here's the only thing I hope. I hope that there is never a day
where he thinks that we abandoned him. Yeah, that we forgot about him. I don't
think he could ever believe that. I don't think he knows a lot of stuff
going on. And I hope
that new Sullivan pretty much knows. Oh yeah, and play time. I hope he never
learns any new words because I think with those words, he might wield them
against our spirits. Yeah. And he might say something really sort of a real
like you. He could say that he don't even that's not that's not that's not
funny man. God, that's really not a linguistic thing, right? It's like you
kind of know what? Oh my God, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Teenage New Sullivan next campaign.
Hopping out of the school bus, walking into high school.
What's up, Sully?
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Smoking.
What other things are going on?
What's his name?
Drink beer.
We do gummies.
He's not the type to drink beer.
And study hard.
He will be.
I sure hope he studies hard.
Study hard, but still have fun.
Work hard, play hard.
Hang ten.
Perfect balance.
Summer job.
Hang ten.
Perfect balance.
Summer job.
Restaurant.
Surfing time.
Meet a boy.
Internship.
Hang ten.
Meet a boy.
Meet a boy?
Oh yeah.
Being honest.
Okay, so that's okay.
Gumby Superior.
See, I want to experience all this shit.
was also like got turned into a vampire during the vampire wars, the
transylvanian war, nobody knew and so that was another thing that huge ass
facts had on him. That's why he was so afraid of him. Okay, everyone was afraid
of huge ass facts because he had all the information, but Leo was keeping him
around because he had to because he had information on him and he had guys
around. And was there a name for this alien guy that or does he speak english?
Does he say anything? I mean he was just play time, he didn't have a name at all.
Okay, another one other thing. He slices blow tosses throat,
but he had a child.
He knows his child very well. Yeah. He's his best friend. He doesn't know.
Who's that again? Who is it? Is it Matthew McConaughey, right? Yeah. I
don't know. You've been watching True Detective? No, I've been watching
YouTube videos about True Detective. Okay, cool. That's awesome. Yeah, they
loved their kid. They had a kid. And I was an uncle. The only one here
who should have died is me. So play time has been frustrated with Reddy on
more than one. The reason why you heard him screech in anguish when he sliced
what's his name's throat O'Neal's throat was because he was like that was not a
childless couple. That is who I want to kill.
That is the only people in like ready just directs him to who he should kill.
Yeah. So is there some kind of growing?
He would have been. Yes. There was this growing tension between the two of them.
Played it up. Playtime would have slowly is slowly learning that ready is
manipulating him. Because they basically like ready sees it as like like
playtime is the is my brother like we are brothers in this because they were both
born from the same like fucked up thing. I mean he wasn't born from the can we
can we ask questions about what we could have done? Yeah, absolutely. Was that
mod thing a good move? Well, no, we dying. No, no, no, no, no. I mean saying
her name. That was a good move. You just literally to where my did not roll
very if I could have gotten that role and I could have gone inside her body
being done, God knows what to her insides. Yeah, but I have one that
shut up. You could have found a way I would have if you if you nailed that
that was such a good. The way I reward you with you guys is like great
sweatpants. If it's a really creative because because you're not going to
always you're just not going to play the rules all the time. Yeah, or most of
the time, but if it's a really fun idea or really funny idea, like really
creative or really funny, like I usually was like that was a really creative,
cool idea. I was like if that worked out, I would have been down. I like that
this is turning a talking gun city. Now,
we should do a separate companion show. Yeah, the I think that should be the
next, the next thing, the next, the next episode is just talking. We should do
what they did. We really, we should do what they do for. We haven't really
talked. We don't talk always about it. We've been doing it. We should, we
should do what they do for the HBO shows and after everyone we do like a
like inside the episode. Yeah, okay. I might I have one. I have a couple more
questions. Actually, one is with play time is it would it have been possible
for us to
basically adopt him? Yep, yeah, of course. Wow,
oh my God, that's so beautiful for us to have the angel and the demon.
Well, no,
play time can't talk. Is there any understand he understands intention?
Could we have taught him, but he wouldn't they wouldn't have a conversation
between yeah. Oh my God,
play time and yes, what would play time saying? Oh, yes, I like
that's like how it sounds like okay, so
as we know is oh yeah, so it'd be kind of like this. It'd be kind of like
oh yeah, oh yeah, play time and the new song would like play with a toy and
then
oh yeah, now it's like most of their conversation. Can we hear can we hear
like the screw tape. What "Oh yeah" would sound like in Playtime's voice?
Oh yeah!
That's exactly what I wanted. Now can we hear it in Arnold Schwarzenegger's
voice?
Oh yeah, oh yeah. And now can we hear what Patches would sound like
normally?
Go ahead.
Damn it. Wait. Oh, it does sound normal. Stop your
blocking it. Stop, stop. You didn't even turn it off. Whoa. He put the deep
voice.
All right. Well, I mean, that's pretty much all I wanted to know. Okay. Wait,
because I had I felt like I was following a lot of the shark guy. Yeah.
The shark guy was also a double agent. I knew that. But he was working. He was
working with the fishes. He was working with Leo. He was working with
He was both there to spy on Belinda for Leo because he thought Belinda had
some sympathies for the Irish slaves, which she did, though she wasn't acting
on any of that. Okay, speaking of the Irish slaves, I almost...
The leprechaun slaves.
I was trying to... If we had gone down the path of liberating all of them...
Yeah, that was definitely a path.
And we were getting really close, I feel.
Yeah, I feel I I here's how I thought this was gonna go. I thought you guys would have run away
Uh-huh. I was I was trying to when this was happening. I was thinking like they might
Kamikaze and I would get why because it's like so hopeless and like it'd be kind of fun to like do a fresh start
So maybe they'll do that, but I was thinking like if you do this, I was thinking they would run away
Head back to the leprechauns
They'd be like you freed so many of our guys were so like we will go in and kill the green
That's what I was trying to do.
And then we'll help you guys find your kid because you guys have like fucking
like nearly died.
I had that whole, that's why I was trying to run away.
And then you were saying you want to go back.
You kind of put your lot in with them once you went for the Greech Queen quest.
Well, once he died, I was like, I don't,
I'm not so sure that I want to live in a world without me.
Yep. Don't make me say that. I'm serious. Don't make me say that.
If it's all three of us.
I did not want to live in a world where
glow toss was not there. Oh, also the sex toys that were being made were being
made by Ebenezer
for
huge ass facts. Was there a reason? To keep people addicted to shit, like
another... Was it a reason that... And using stuff from the Stargoo from their
old experiments back in the day, but reintroducing it on the Pleasure Palace.
Was it a connection that the spaceship was sex toy shaped to, or was that just
randomly both funny? That was kind of just like a... That was some space
- Bullshit. - Must be real.
- That was some space bullshit.
- That was just space bullshit.
- Yup.
- And the story came about as I realized
we were gonna be using toys to do it,
and then I was like, oh, this would be really fun
to play into how we're using toys.
- The medium is the message.
- Right.
- Marshall McLuhan.
- So what if, okay, so this whole campaign
was a test run for--
- It was not a test run.
- It was a test to see if we were brave
and all of us passed.
- Yup.
we get a sweet reward. Yeah, which is
you say
you have to sing one song right now. You have to sing one karaoke song to end
the episode of Our Choice.
That's not
you're making up all the... No, you have to sing a karaoke song to end the
episode. You're not in D&D anymore, buddy. D&D is over. Now, it's Bully Hour.
You're the singing master.
You have to sing Hero by Gabriel Inglésias.
Or not, Enrique Iglesias.
I don't know that song.
It'll be Pictures of Us.
I genuinely don't know that song.
Or Foo Fighters.
Foo Fighters.
That one.
You know that one.
And it has to be about us.
Because it's going to be about bravery.
Maybe.
Foo Fighters Hero.
Well, I don't know if I know the verses.
I'm about to verses you if you don't sing this song.
Oh, wait. I actually don't know this song.
there
you
know
- Dim as they go.
- Because it's us three.
- Yeah.
- Oh yeah.
- My heroes.
- And say extraordinary.
- Dim as they go.
- My heroes.
- Heroes.
- Watch him, he's ordinary.
- They're extraordinary.
- All right, sorry.
- Say that.
- Oh, 33 seconds.
- 33 seconds.
(laughing)
- And now at 33 seconds, musical interlude.
- Can you do what I've done by Linkin Park?
- Oh, that'd be good too.
- Because it's kind of you.
- I mean, we gotta feel it.
- Atoning for what you did.
Fill the hour a few more minutes
No, you're gonna see I'm not trying to avoid that oh, yeah, right, okay, you should try to avoid it this is
Okay, I don't remember I don't know the verses for this either
I I know the verse goes are you gonna sing it Cameron? I'll help him
Oh my God, when the drums come in, when the drums come in, I may get high
transformers.
Oh my word.
I feel like we all forget how good this song is. We are always forgetting.
Okay, you can skip to the chorus. Yeah, this is crazy.
Wow. There's no blood.
There's no alibi.
Cause I've drawn regret from the truth of a thousand lives.
So let mercy come.
Alright now just patches.
I don't know just cut away.
Ready? Okay.
What I've done.
I'll face myself.
To cross out.
cross out
sorry guys
I'm sorry,
wow,
wait,
all right now,
sorry,
I think that's enough.
No,
that's one more one more one more song that we all know,
sorry,
no put on fruit salad by the wiggles.
No,
we're not doing that was such a beautiful.
That was beautiful.
Wait,
do we are you going to sing?
No,
he I don't think you
day. But I'm I'll do it.
You've got to sing this one.
Anything that you'd like to say to
people before we end this this
campaign? Because this is this is
I know this is pretty crazy.
So this is the worst ending that's
ever happened in the whole show.
Is it up to this one?
Look to this. Do you have a final
monologue?
I don't I don't have I was I
was really not expecting to run
away. No, I wasn't really
expecting this. I was I thought
about it on the way here.
I was like, you know what? They
might.
Thank you guys for always
listening and enjoying the
show. It means a lot to me.
And I think it means a lot to them, too.
I don't know. But I would love to hear any thoughts or suggestions
or ideas you have for what we want to do next.
I always love it. You can always DM me your thoughts and ideas.
We could either do just clones of them, other holiday episode.
I'm really just looking forward to doing more.
I wish Batman episode we should do the Batman episode.
I think if I if I could do this all again, I probably will.
It's one of those where you're damned if you do, you're damned if you don't, right?
Like you could just, um, you could, you know, give them all,
hey, heads up, like this is going to actually start to take advantage of
all the kind of abilities I've given you and all the things we've done together
so far.
But, you know, instead, I was like, I'm just going to let them see
what they do with this, right?
They they've played with me now for three years.
She said I was going to be out of the rattle, but I thought
they were going to be going to go like this.
You can't you just can't always win.
We can't do that.
All right. That's going to do it.
We'll see you next time. All right.
Bye. Go see.
So this kid, I gave him that to me.
And don't think I'm going to give a lot.
I'm thinking, oh, I do what I do.
[Music]
Yeah, yeah, man, I'm a stand-alone
Normal, no, no me said he don't know me
Yes, I get the money
(upbeat music)
Bye!