Last time on gun City a
broad City play time continue fun
I don't have anything written recording right after but I just say what happened. Here's what happened last time
Here's what I just say I got a little fun game. Here's one. Let's just say housekeeping
Good housekeeping joke recap. We did housekeeping
So the Brotas and Ray William Johnson were brought to finally met Bear McGinnis the head of the Leprechaun Rebellion
and
He asked them to fight off to finally defeat the Greech Queen
the
Greeches who have been terrorizing leprechauns the Greeches being the
Creatures that are both the guys who attach to the monsters that have been coming up in the surface and attacking
so that's the the Greeches and
to convince him they did an amazing rap hip-hop style thing.
Patrick Yoda meanwhile was getting interrogated by Janet Blowjob
who thought he had nefarious intentions when really he was just kind of bored
and raided her room for no reason.
Then there was a very goofy surprise sort of joke part of the story
where everybody was showing their penis.
that lasted 40 minutes. We liked that. I liked that too. That wasn't really like a surprise.
There was no surprise there. I'm gonna go ahead and say, because now we're in the future,
that by the time this comes out, that is already a legendary, that is not about listdnd bit.
It's been picked, it's been animated. 100k, 500k, 10,000k, 70,000k. They're making numbers that
I can't... what?
Went down?
70,000k?
I thought it went down from 100 to 70k.
70,000,000?
Oh, 70,000k.
This guy's an idiot.
Oh, I'm sorry.
70,000k, K.
Not careful.
I didn't say anything further than that.
10 trillion million.
100,000,000.
Tons and tons and tons.
It says tons on it.
And also it was a lot of fun.
Patrick Yoda was recruited to join them in fighting off the Greeches, but first he had to go talk with
Huge-ass Fax himself and so Janet Blowjob brought him from her
Weird secret room back to her regular room in the
In the lair of facts and then they went to go see huge-ass facts who said he could find them
the nephew in 24 hours
if
Patrick Yoda
- Assassinates, in two days, assassinates,
which I realize now the timing of that is very confusing.
But he said he could find it in--
- So it's gonna happen in seven episodes.
- Maybe.
- Great.
- He says, well, you know, you could sleep.
You could sleep instead.
- Yeah.
- But he says if you assassinate Gumby Superior
when he gives a speech at the reopening of Thunderland,
which I forgot to mention in the last episode,
but I will mention now, is on St. Patrick's Day.
'Cause if you guys remember, you slept for,
or you were all upset for like three months
after you lost your nephew.
You were despondent in the hotel.
And then months went by to avoid
this being a Christmas episode.
But, so then, Caleb, are you okay?
- Yeah, it's just that I, never mind.
(laughing)
(laughter)
- He had a plastic bottle cap on his eye.
- I was gonna scare you and show you my plastic bottle cap
on my eye, but it fell off.
(laughter)
- Took his hand off of his eye.
- I thought it was gonna be really cool.
- He said, "Yeah, I just have"
- Oh, I was gonna say, "Yeah, I just"
(laughter)
- I literally just thought you had a migraine.
- No, I was gonna go, "Yeah, except I don't have my eye."
And I was gonna look at you.
- You were gonna say that?
- Yeah.
- You were sitting there that long?
- That's good.
- Yeah, I was gonna say, "Yeah"
- I don't have my eye?
Yeah, or I have a plastic--
[LAUGHTER]
I was going to come up with it in the moment,
but then the moment was stolen from me by gravity.
You're just sitting there like, I'm
going to say something so awesome.
No, I kind of forgot I was doing it for a second.
OK, wait, ask me again.
Caleb, are you doing OK?
Oh, I don't know.
You should ask my plastic eye.
It's not as good now.
It's not even a camera that's pointed in the direction
you're looking.
Hey, wait, look me in my plastic ass eye
when you ask me questions like that.
Bite my shiny plastic eye.
- I gotta guess.
- I shoulda said that.
- Ugh!
- Oh.
- You shook the table, you broke a guy.
- You shook the table and broke a guy.
- How 'bout I shake the table?
- So, yeah, I mean that's basically what happened last time.
And now--
- So the guy said I have to kill a politician,
I said let's do it.
- Yeah.
- And then we basically go after the Glinch.
- Yeah, and so you--
- Oh, and I gotta link up the Glinch up.
- Yup.
- So Janet Blowjob said she could bring you back there.
- Get the Glinch up.
- So Sheely's--
- Kill the Glinch up.
- The Lair.
- Kill my glint shop.
- With you, she leaves the layer of facts with you,
back to her room.
- You know what I thought that song was called
when I was a kid was paint my picture.
- You guys go into the panel,
her panel like behind the bed.
You still have a nano bot with you too.
- Scooter!
- Scooter.
- Yeah!
- What up, Scooty?
- How you doing?
- Not much.
- So you guys are going down the conveyor belt
into the pod again.
shot through space, makeup is done on her to make her--
- And on him.
- And I take Scooter and I put him in the thing.
- Yeah, he also gets the Annie treatment.
- Oh my God, triplets.
- Yeah, all of you guys have red hair and freckles.
And you guys arrive in--
- The sun will come out.
- Yeah.
And you guys arrive back in Janet Blowjob's room
and she says, "Okay, if you go out here,
You make a right, there's an elevator, you take it down,
and then ride one more conveyor belt,
and then take another elevator.
And then you're gonna have to crawl through a vent.
- Can you say, before anything, just say, "Twins vibes"?
'Cause I have my, triplets vibes.
- Triplets vibes, I'm gonna just lead you there.
You know, let's just go.
And so she takes you out of--
- Can we hold hands like triplets?
Me, you, and Scooter?
There's a--
- You don't have to mention it.
you can just talk and play the game
'cause you're the only person in the scene,
so you can't interrupt.
- All right, let's go to the bog and kill the greach.
- You should hold hands.
- Or whatever.
- So, and she turns to you also, she says,
and don't just,
I might change my voice,
people might call me a different name.
- Oh shit, the plot thickens.
- Say shit.
- Shit.
- I knew it, you walked right into that, buddy.
- You're so, you're fucking funny, I gotta say.
(laughing)
- Can I push my new curly wig up?
- Take off the fucking wig.
- I take the makeup off, but I leave the wig on.
- Okay, I guess that's fine.
I guess we could have some--
- No, I'm twirling it.
- All right, I'm taking the wig off.
Okay, and so you, her, and Scooter,
she leads you down through this sort of winding pathway
back into the Boglins.
I still, I'm still having one.
And she says, "Okay, now, just one second."
She knocks on the door and a slot opens up.
This is now in the guts of the station.
And you hear, "Hart-a-tar-tar-tar-tar-tar-tar-tar-tar."
- "Hart-a-tar-tar-tar-tar-tar-tar-tar-tar."
- "Stop it."
And she says to them, "Hara tatara, hara tatarata."
And it opens up.
And she says, "You go in, I'm going out of here, okay?"
- And Scooter can come with me.
- You have Scooter?
- Shh, I never told you that.
- Just fine, keep Scooter.
- Okay, I get to keep him.
- Yay!
(laughing)
- Scooter's happy.
- Scooter still has the wig and makeup on.
- Yeah, as the door opens, he says,
"Oh, Mini Shamrock, are you coming in?"
"Um..."
And you see Janet just changes her affect completely, and is like,
"Ah, no, I've got some business to take care of, but I'll talk to you later, okay? Okay, Shardy?"
And he says, "Okay, you got it."
And he says, "Who's this? This is a friend of mine, his name's Patrick, just..."
"Patrick Shardy."
"Just let him in."
[laughter]
I was like, I'm doing a disguise like you.
She wants to kill you.
(laughing)
And she leaves, and you walk in.
So yeah, Patrick Yoda walks in.
What's funny about this is I don't think
he'll ever be able to pull it together
to tell you guys that this is happening.
Can you tell them though?
Will you tell them?
- Tell them that--
- That the J.Pool job has a double identity.
- Oh, I don't know.
- Yeah, okay cool.
- It might come up.
- So yeah, you guys, he enters the Boglands
and he meets up with you guys.
So you guys are back together again
after like four sessions of--
- So that's one day. - Party being split.
Well, yeah, I mean you guys now,
so what it would have been is that
at this point you two would have rested.
I mean the timeline's a little wonky,
but you guys would have all rested at some point.
So now it's a new day, full health, full HP,
full Techno Slime points,
and it's time for you guys to enter the Griecious Lair.
So let's...
We're coming for your ass, Glanch.
The Green Glanch.
Let's get...
Let's get this going.
Wait, can I introduce them to Scooter?
Absolutely. You guys play that out while I draw.
What's up?
What's up, motherfucker?
(laughter)
What was that?
He spit the bottle cap out of his mouth.
(laughing)
- I wasn't even looking, I missed it.
- It was just for Patrick.
- Check this out.
- What the, wait, wait, wait.
- Wait, wait, check this out.
- Who's your beautiful friend?
- Now Scooter, brush my hair.
- Okay.
- 'Cause Scooter is also by the way like,
- He's my pet.
- He's like a nanobot.
- I would like to sit on him.
- No.
- You might kill him.
- Don't sit on him.
- I'm not, no.
- Buddy, you know where he's going, don't pretend.
- Don't sit on him.
- Around me, that's a two.
I mean, were you rolling to sit?
- That would be-- - You could just sit on him.
- That's not a swear word, that'd be an acrobatic,
so it's a crit one.
- Crit one doesn't work like that.
- Also, you could just sit on him.
- Then I'd like to sit on him and shove him up my butt.
- All right, you can try to stop this from happening.
- I'm stopping it.
- All right, so now it's a strength contest.
- Okay, well, now that I know that,
I'll roll at the same time. - Wait, we gotta roll
at the same time.
- All right, ready?
Three, two, one.
Oh yeah, he got a two and I got a straight 18.
- Okay, Scooter is in your butt now.
Whoa!
- He can get out at any time.
- Wow, this is red.
- Nuh-uh.
- Red, red, red, red, red, red.
- Scooter, activate electrosis.
- You want me to turn oxygen into,
you want me to turn oxygen into water?
- Electrosis and then electrosis.
- I think he means electrolysis.
- Electrolysis.
- I think I--
- It's an electronic exorcism.
- Oh, it's an electrolysis when you separate water.
- Yeah, is that when you separate water
and like, oxygen, I think, or something?
- It's an exorcism with electricity.
- Okay, I poop him out, it wasn't that fun.
- Whoa!
- And I wash Scooter.
- See his makeup and his hair are all askew
and he's trying to fix it now.
- What the hell, you came out with a bunch of brothers.
- What?
- There's a bunch of little poops that I also
brought out with him.
- Blow on that poop.
So, Bear McGinnis comes up to you guys.
He says, all right, if you're ready to go into the
creatures of there, I'm going to tell you a couple
of things about it that you should know.
Oh, really?
You're going to talk for a while.
Who are you?
Not that long.
Yeah, go ahead.
Oh, I'm Bear McGinnis.
You must be Patrick.
All right.
He's the Glouch.
What?
His, we're going to kill his sister.
He's Glitch and his sister is the super
glitch from Wreck-It Ralph.
Got it.
Kill the Glitch.
- I completely understand everything now.
- I've never seen Wreck-It Ralph, is that...
- Buddy, what are we even doing here
if you haven't seen Wreck-It Ralph?
- You have basically, and I thought this whole time
you've been copying Wreck-It Ralph
with this whole storyline.
- It's basically one for one.
- Yeah.
- Especially saying we have to kill a glitch.
- The greech.
- Speaking of, get on with it!
- All right, so he says,
- Pop it.
- So, I'll take you to the hole that leads into the lair.
Now in the lair, there are the pods that the monsters sleep in.
There are the greeches that wander,
and there's a few other locations.
There's a prison where they're holding
some of our leprechauns.
- Are they holding a little penguin boy?
- Not that I know of.
Is this your nephew you guys talk about?
- This might be our nephew that we talk about.
- Yeah, and he's basically legit AF,
so we may wanna see him again.
It's too legit to quit.
- Well, I promise you I will have my men.
If you do this for me, I'll have my men help you find him.
I can promise you that.
- Okay, there's also another guy who's gonna be helping me
if I kill the general.
- Um.
- I have to kill the general in two days.
- What?
- If I don't, oh yeah, while I was gone.
- What are you talking about?
- There was a lady who became another lady.
Through different types of hairs.
Wait, what's her name again?
Patty Strawberry? Who is that?
Millie Shamrock.
And then I have to kill the general in two days.
My betrothed.
He'll give me a bunch of credits.
You're betrayed.
What are you talking about?
And he ate a yellow stick off of the wall.
Stop, stop.
You're special, aren't you?
No, I'm completely normal.
I've been pretending to be this way so that I can get away with a lot more.
Wait, you're snapping out of it?
I think I've snapped out of it completely.
I remember everything.
I remember everything, but I could slip back if I needed to.
No, you can't.
The jig is up.
You are no longer playing a canonically mentally disabled cop.
It was all the ringer.
the ringer I so I have to kill the general in two days and you guys got to
help me you have to but after we kill this gleech and getting so many names
wrong who do you wait you have to kill wait I have to kill gum the great I have
to kill her obviously give the kill Gumby superior yeah isn't that what
you're also about to well potentially yeah okay then just join I'd like we'll
We'll just do this for you, then you have to join us and help me do that.
We're gonna like stage like a big coup.
Roll Persuasion.
Four.
Wait, wait.
No, you can roll a six with advantage.
Okay.
Now, what's your, what do you have?
Fourteen.
Or no, no, no, no, no, no, no, twelve.
You're gonna have to tell me a little bit more details about this.
Okay, so huge-ass fax took me into his lair.
- Huge-ass fax.
- Obviously, he wears the Sean John jacket.
(laughing)
- Waning on gold.
- And I can't even talk about that.
- Can we just go murder some snatch?
- Yeah.
- We have to murder, okay, we murder the glitch.
- I wanna beat the snatch up.
- The queen snatch, right?
- You, Yoda, you talk to me after this.
- Okay, we're gonna murder the glitch
and then you have to do this or else you're a loser.
- But I really don't want to be a loser.
- Okay, nose goes.
- Ah, fuck.
(laughing)
- He got me in real life.
- Okay, you actually have to do it now.
- You actually have to do it now.
- 'Cause you lost nose goes, so.
- It's an Irish tradition.
- Uh-huh.
So if we go and kill this Gleech and then do--
- It's a queef.
- Oh, the queef.
If we kill the queen queef, we're gonna be--
- No, a queef greech.
Okay, the Green Queen.
And we're gonna get all, and we're gonna stay,
we're gonna get all the lower--
- We've avoided wordplay for some time now.
- We're gonna get all the lower factions to kill the,
we're gonna start an uprising, obviously.
Okay, we'll go do that now.
No more!
(laughing)
(laughter)
- Hush!
- That was the best line read we've ever had
in our scripted series.
- Okay, we'll talk after this.
- No, we'll do after this.
- Star-billed snitch.
We're gonna kill the green. Okay, so let me tell you then a little bit more about the place.
Okay.
Just a little bit more.
This is important.
Number one, it has a blotch in it.
Yeah, we get it. We're killing the blimch.
Number two, the blotch is a quick clean.
If you move stealthily, you can avoid a lot of the monsters.
As soon as I get in there, I'm indiscriminately killing women and children and old people.
Yeah, that's why we're going oh yeah, cuz it's a society of women. You know what next leprechauns all men. Don't worry
All right, I trust you, and then we'll break all the prisoners out you're crazy as fucking hey
Here's a question when we see people and they're walking in the street in this new world
We're going to should we smack crap out of their hands and spit on them - if they have a cup you best believe that thing
Is getting yeeted to oblivion you guys?
(laughing)
- We're gonna yeet everything.
- Okay, yeah, can I yeet the fuck out of this fucking bitch?
- We're gonna yeet them on X Games.
- I'm gonna yeet them on X Games mode, bitch.
- Can you roll to see if you yeet?
- Well, we haven't done it yet.
God, you're old.
(laughing)
Let's go, come on.
- All right, so,
A Seamus leads you guys to a hole in the ground further into the chamber.
Oh wait, hey.
Yeah, what's up?
Get that other guy back here.
I played audio for them in the room and then also baby Gadd was there.
I thought you were going to talk about this when we get back.
Oh yeah, I'm talking about it when I get back.
Can I call him? Do I have his phone number now?
Who?
Bear.
- Bear McGinnis, no.
- We're going in the snatch hole to fight the snatch.
- Patrick is slipping back into character.
- It comes and goes.
I think I sneezed in the pebble that's in my--
- Yes, the sneeze!
We're fighting the sneeze, come on!
- Finally, you have a good idea.
- You can smell the stink of the greaches
emanating from the torn apart hole.
- The Grinch stench?
- The metal sheets from the hole curl upward
from this hole in the gut's layer.
- Crenches?
- Crenches.
- Crenches, stench.
- Passageways.
- Suggesting that something burrowed out from here,
so it's a second entrance, really.
But it's being used.
A layer of fresh slime can be seen at the hole's edge
before giving way to larger pools of the stuff
slathered across the passageway.
Upon descending into the hole, the darkness is immediate.
Ray, you are the only one who has proper
as proper dark vision, being part demon.
(imitates demon)
So meaning Patrick and Blotas will be--
- I'm just winging it.
- Somewhat of a disadvantage.
You'll feel some perception checks,
depending on the situation.
I don't like the just fail all,
or it's like depending on what you're trying to perceive,
you will fail them.
And you're gonna take a penalty on range attacks,
unless you find a way to produce light,
which is my own little addition.
Ray, you're able to make out the outline
of a broader passageway though.
- Okay. - So you guys,
let's get your characters in here.
So each of these squares is gonna be
roughly 10 feet right now.
- Holy shit, I'm huge.
- And then we'll zoom in here, over here.
- Okay.
- And then we'll zoom in sort of like
during certain conflicts and we'll change
sort of the size of each of the--
- Wait, these are, where are the squares are 10 feet?
- Yeah, but like this is just--
- I'm even bigger.
- No, this is just representing your characters.
- 20 feet wide.
- You're not-- - Where's Yoda?
- 20 feet wide, I don't know where Yoda is.
Didn't you eat him?
Did you yeet him, Rick?
I did not yeet him into oblivion on X Games mode.
You probably, when you punched all my shit away,
well, I see his hat.
I think I don't know what yeet is.
You don't know yeet?
No, that's not his hat.
Oh yeah, define it then.
Yeah, define yeet.
Define yeet.
Well, that's hard to do.
Trolololol.
(laughing)
I bet you don't even know that either.
Oh my God, we lost Badger Coder.
I only know the Drew Carey show.
Yeah, honey, Badger don't care.
- It's gotta be over there, 'cause I didn't touch him.
- You didn't touch him, nerd.
- Oh, check over with fucking Janet Blowjerb.
There he is. - There he is.
- You bastard, you in between her legs, oh!
- Nasty ass.
- He is nasty. - That nasty ass motherfucker.
- Baby cat is not here.
- Oh, bro, chill.
- I'm kinda mad that he was baby one.
- If you remember.
- I know, well, we'll use him again
for another character in another segment.
- Oh wait, wait, wait, Scooter, what'd you get?
- Scooter's a nanobot.
- Here's Scooter. - I barely know her.
- Oh wait, here's Scooter.
I'll just make a dot for Scooter.
- We'll just make a dot for wherever he is.
And if you remember, Sullivan is right now strapped to you.
- Well, Scooter's in my pocket anyway.
- Sullivan is a bulletproof vest for me.
And I'm not getting a good look at this Sullivan figurine
'til right now and I am pretty close to laughing.
(laughing)
- It is a loody coolo.
- Can you show the camera this?
- No, it's been shown.
- Okay, just another-- - But we'll have a reminder.
- Look at his face.
- I think I never noticed that was a mouth.
He's fucked up.
- I thought it was a good choice, thank you.
- All right, put him back on my chest to protect me.
- Thank you.
Excuse me.
Yeah, so Ray, you're able to make an outline
of a broader passageway with coiled wire
of a more sort of archaic alien sort of nature.
So similar to what you, you can't see it,
but similar to what you had seen in--
- Oh my God, Huge Ass Facts is a Grish.
- Huge Ass Facts Lair.
Well, not necessarily, but it's the same kind of alien
kind of architecture and
Giger-esque kind of layout.
- But they can't see it.
- So the Giger is what we're gonna get?
- You're trying to get the Giger.
- Oh, the Gleacher.
- Guys, I hate to interrupt,
but I'm seeing a broader passageway
with some kind of--
- Chlorus Leachman. - Foiling.
we have to kill Cloris Leachman.
- I think she might be in the broad passageway
with archaic coils.
- Okay, we should go get her.
- Fucking cunt.
You all can see a bit a ways away
the faintest yellow glow.
- This place is Leachman-esque.
- Suggesting that there may be some light to come.
So, from what Bear McGinnis attempted to tell you guys,
you know that there are monsters
similar to what you had seen come up on the surface,
like the snake monster, that purple monster,
that sex tentacle monster, kind of--
- Sonny D.
- Kind of Sonny D.
- That purple monster, Sonny D.
- I don't know.
- What are you talking about?
- I don't know what you're doing now.
Deadass, that's a reference that if you don't get,
you are not a true Kyle Cease fan.
- A what fan?
- Let's just get on with it.
- We're moving on.
- So, sort of lurking about.
So, and you two can't really see.
So-- - But I'm seeing it.
- You can kind of see, like you can make a,
like you have dark vision, so you, yes,
effectively you can see, but it's like still dark.
It's still-- - Right.
- But I have dark vision, so I can see it perfectly then.
- Right. - Yes, I suppose.
- And you see the biatch. - For all functional
purposes, yes.
- The biatch is nowhere to be found,
but we need to go in this other hole.
- Where's this gliatch at?
The glizznitch is over somewhere,
but I don't give a fizzuck about that.
We go in the hole right now.
Come on, I grab you guys and we just
come in a daisy chain through.
Come on, come on, come on.
All right.
Monkeys in a barrel, we fall into that.
We're all holding hands.
So as you guys walk through.
And I would like to land on Sullivan when we,
I thought it was in the bottom of the ground.
And it was a straight hole down.
You guys went down the hole.
Oh, this is not, this is just a side opening.
It's like you went down the hole
and now you're moving through.
- Okay, all right.
- And on your left, you see another passageway.
You hear kind of like manic sounds from that passageway.
Down the way, you, Ray William Johnson,
can see some kind of creature lumbering around
immediately in front of you, further down the passageway.
- If I could see it-- - That's the passageway
that has more of the yellow light.
- Does it look like-- - That you can make out to
at the very end.
- Does it look friendly?
- No.
- Okay, I'd like to run Sullivan first at it.
- So Sullivan's tied to you, right?
- Yeah.
- You're gonna run Sullivan first.
Okay, now I understand.
Okay.
Cool.
- Follow me!
- Okay, so you charge ahead towards this thing
and as you get closer, you can make out
that it looks like a bunch of different flat rectangles.
- I like to turn around, that's too scary.
- You're gonna turn around.
- You can just already tell it's gonna be crazy.
- Okay, you get a sting.
- All I make out is the rectangle.
- Yeah, you yell, and the thing goes.
- I hit him for doing that.
- Yeah, you hit him, he takes, can you roll a D4?
- That's not a D4.
- A 14.
- Stop that.
- Do you have a D4?
- It probably got thrown onto the ground by a one-throw.
- Probably got thrown onto the ground
by one's rude actions.
- Three. - You got three.
- Okay, you did three damage to Sullivan.
Where's Sullivan's HP?
I gotta go to the battle notes.
- He's dead.
- Let's go to the battle notes.
When I was in class, I used to take notes
and I used to take battle notes, two separate notes.
Can I overpower this teacher?
- I took babble notes.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause that's whatever my teacher was saying.
- I did not give a fuck about most of my lessons
besides math, science, and social studies.
- I didn't care, I--
- I cared about lunch, though.
I didn't even care about lunch that much.
- So you run up, and this creature now faces you,
and it has arms, it's all made out of these
spinning rectangles. - Whoop-de-doo, it's a cube.
- These spinning flat rectangles, and it--
- Paper monster.
- It-- - Use scissors.
- Lurches towards you, and let's roll for initiative.
- Speaking of, kinda reminds me of Super Paper Mario.
My dice got stolen.
- I've been playing Thousand Year Door.
- And it has the square guys.
- It has a few of those guys.
- And Cameron got a 21.
- Oh, you can't roll for me.
- And I got a 21.
- So does Super Paper Mario.
Yes, Super Paper Mario has more of those guys, so yes.
Like, actually has those guys.
- Natural 20.
- Where is initiative?
- Oh wait, then I got a 15.
- I got a natural 20.
- I got a six.
- How about, what do you guys think?
What do you guys think the initiative is?
- Does Scooter have light bulb eyes?
- Like the-- - Oh, this guy.
- Like the bug from Spy Kids 2?
- Oh, the little bug?
- Yeah.
- Is its name Ralph, or is that the name of someone else
who I know?
- It's the name of someone else.
- Just someone you know?
- Christ.
- Let's think its name's Ralph.
- I think its name is--
- With dots in between.
- I think it's Daphne.
- You're thinking of Scooby-Doo.
- Oh shit.
- Why am I crying right now?
- Just 'cause of, you know, how much danger we're in?
- Oh my gosh, I'm crying.
- You need to go rush to the hospital.
- You guys gotta--
- I literally said there are ways to get--
- You guys just ran at this thing.
- All right, what'd you--
- I turned around, I told you that!
- Ran at it.
- And then I ran away, dude!
- What is your, what initiative did you get?
- Oh, natural 20.
- I got six.
- Oh my god, it is Ralph.
- Yeah.
- With dots between the letters?
- Yep. - You got a six?
- Yep, so-- - You got a six?
- Look who's not crying anymore.
What's his name?
- You got a six?
- Does Scooter have Ralph powers?
- Does he have Ralph energy?
- No, Scooter is a nanobot.
- Does he have a flashlight?
- Scooter is a nanobot.
- You know who has big dick energy?
- Who?
- Jamie Lee Curtis.
- For real.
- I'm gonna kill myself.
- I heard she actually has one too.
- Pat, what'd you get in initiative?
- She has both, I learned that as a kid.
- 14 or something, or 15?
- Roll your initiative again.
You don't remember.
- Nice.
- I got an 18 then.
- Very nice.
Okay, I'm pretty sure it was a 15. I got a 20. I'd like to use my by the way
I already used my turn to do I would get first Emily Curtis would be the mom friend though
I would bang her right you would have to be the one who acted like a mom
I don't care if she's 90 years old stuck in the damn washing machine. Yeah, the washing machine. She'll die. She'll drown
She'll swim in the why the top load washing machine. She's
like this or legs and you walk in like
I'm gonna fuck the shit out of her.
I'll put my dick between the legs.
So yeah, you do go first for William Johnson.
Yeah, first I'd like to...
Crash your fucking shit.
So yeah, it does look like a bunch of cards
are spinning on axles around this thing.
Yeah, so I'd like to outsmart it.
What do you wanna do?
I just told you.
How will you outsmart it?
Describe it to me.
- Chess, chess, chess, chess, play chess.
- I'm gonna challenge it to a game of chess.
(laughing)
Yeah.
I challenge you, sir, to a game of wits.
- Hmm, intriguing.
(roaring)
That's a verbal yes.
- Okay, well.
- What the?
- A little cringe.
(laughing)
But I'll sit down.
- That's like what it says back, right?
- Yeah.
- You gonna play, is that what you're gonna do this turn?
- Watch this, I'm gonna trick it.
I'm already outsmart, I'm in the process
of outsmarting you right now.
- Okay, so it's the whole process.
- Does it accept my chess?
- No.
- Man, then I fucking shoot it in the head
with my perception. - You know what you should've done.
- Or no, sorry, my...
Oh, you know what I do?
- First of all, haven't seen this guy in a while.
First of all, I'm going to sneakily
let my huge worm that I have in my inventory,
I've had it in my inventory by the way for three campaigns.
- That's true.
- My huge pet worm that is always on my side.
I'm gonna let it out and slither down my leg, right?
And then have him slither behind him
and kind of sneak up on him.
'Cause I just want him to get one little bite.
but I'm distracting him with this whole stupid dance
of oh, I wanna play chess with you,
I wanna play chess with you, I'm crazy.
- The screech I did was stupid, this isn't stupid.
- No, the screech was amazing.
- Thanks, man.
- But I sent it my worm, and then right,
is he a little confused, the monster?
He's like maybe just weirded out?
- He's like completely intent on just killing you.
- Okay, well then, I'm going to,
then I'm gonna use this kind of SWAT team hand signaling
to my worm to be like, hold off.
- Worm understands everything.
- Of course, yeah, I know the worm very well.
We've done this for a long time.
- Yes, yes.
- I'm going to shoot my matrix beam at him right now.
- Okay, cool.
You can also send the worm around to do a worm thing.
- Well, the worm is going to, when he goes to attack,
the worm will bite him.
That's what I'm instructing with my hands.
- Cameron, show the camera.
- We'll figure that out.
- Battle camera. - I'm at a disadvantage maybe.
- While you're rolling that,
I just drew my second original meme.
- Oh, I got a five, I missed that, didn't I?
- Just show the camera real quick.
- What does it say?
- Oh, wait.
- It says, "Goes to party, stands in corner,
"and watches Vines," and it's a penguin on a rig.
- Socially awkward penguin. - Oh, 'cause it's the red.
No, the blue is the socially awkward,
that's socially, you made socially awesome penguin!
- Well, people like Vines. - Oh, true.
- Either way.
Anyway, I miss my blade, or my matrix beam, I gather.
- Yeah, you shoot at it, and it sort of just like,
kind of like, twirls its cards around in a way
where it kind of like dodges all the ones and zeros
that are coming at it.
- Asshole.
- Yeah, a bit.
And Patrick Yoda, it is now your turn,
but your worm is at the ready.
- Yeah, okay.
- The worm is like mouth open, like.
- Yeah, ready to eat.
- So.
Excuse you.
The fuck is that?
Stop kissing it.
Don't kiss the monster.
And I'm kissing the worm monster.
No, the worm is not the monster.
The worm is a friend.
Okay, then I am going to use...
You were the only one who actually had a pet.
I just remember Blotas, the monkey.
That didn't ever happen.
That just never happened, though.
That never happened.
Now I have a pet.
You have a pet and he has a pet.
And it's a nanobot.
I just don't have... I'm not responsible.
I'm going to use Yoda's lightning.
is
- It might do extra damage.
- Yeah, okay, then I will do that.
- So what does it say if Ryota's lightning?
- It ranges 60 feet and it costs four Technoslime points.
- And then what do you have to do to hit with it?
- I have to roll 4d8, no.
- That's for damage, what's the,
here go to your front sheet.
- Okay, my front sheet is on the front.
I have to do a spell attack for 2d6.
- Nice.
Wait, no, hold on, let me see your friend sheet, Pat.
- It says-- - No, I'm not remembering
correctly, it's been a while since you've done--
- Since you've used an ability.
- Pretty much.
Yeah, so it's a spell attack, so it's just d20 plus eight.
- Okay.
- And then you'll do 2d6-- - d20 plus eight.
- And then you'll do 4d8 damage.
- 17.
- Nice.
- Plus eight. - Yeah, that hits for sure.
- And then make sure you subtract four Techno Slime points.
It's not true, you know that.
I know you know that's not right.
- I don't know if that's right or not.
- He looked at me like, "Caleb, I did it, I did it."
- That's okay.
You can subtract four though.
- Wait, so my Techno Slime refills when I rest?
- When you rest or if you use one of your
Techno Slime refills, like pouches that you have.
- Yeah, okay.
- But right now you're gonna subtract from your total
and you're gonna now roll four,
actually wait, before you do that,
can I see your character sheet for a second?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, your spells.
I wanna make sure that--
- Okay, Mr. Kleptomaniac.
- We're using the right, that's not true.
- Yeah, and I wanna see your phone
and your keys in your wallet.
I'm robbing you.
- Do robbers take keys if they rob you?
- Oh yes, there we go, yeah.
- Yeah, and then they walk you to your house.
- Yep, that's four, I'm sorry, I wanted to make sure.
So it's four D8, right?
- You're crazy.
- So I roll four D8s?
- Yes, so the D8s are-- - It's even weirder
that it'd be cooler if you thought it was gonna happen.
- Yeah. - Okay.
Six.
- Keep going.
- Five. - Yeah.
- Six. - Wow.
- Three. - That's pretty good.
So that is 20.
It's 20 damage.
So you shoot this thing up for 20 damage
with your lightning.
The lightning, as it creases through,
you can start to actually see now what's in the chamber.
and you see like creatures like lumbering like zombies,
kind of like the zombies in Hyrule Town
in Ocarina of Time. - I knew exactly
which one you were talking about.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, those guys,
like kind of lumbering around.
- They look at you and they go.
(screeching)
- So they're slow zombies.
- They're slow, but when they see the lightning--
- None of this Last of Us fucking bullshit.
- When they see the lightning--
- 28 days later, not gonna happen.
- They do start to like--
- It's unrealistic.
- They will start to move more quickly when they see,
as the lightning creases through, lights up the area
and you start to see both more of the alien architecture,
you start to see more of those bulbs
like you had seen in Huge Ass Facts' lair.
- Hey guys, by the way, I've seen bulbs like that before.
- But there's no yellow in them.
Just say that as you're shooting lighting out of your hand.
- There's no yellow in them?
- Yes, in these ones.
- So it's almost like Huge Ass Facts took these bulbs
and ran normal electricity through them.
- Oh my God, it's like those yellow bulbs
right over on these here.
- I was drawing with the actual marker on my screen.
(laughing)
- It's fine, it's no problem.
- He's too faded.
- Faded than a ho, faded than a ho.
- Faded than a ho.
- I didn't want to jinx you completely.
- Faded than a ho, faded than a ho, faded than a ho.
Okay, cool.
Yeah, this thing takes some serious damage
and then takes extra damage as well.
- How much more extra damage?
- When you set it in light on fire.
Roll 2D4.
Nope, you just rolled--
- Snake eyes.
(laughter)
- He's rolled two D6s.
- Patrick rolled two D6s, a two and a four.
- Nope, these are still not D4s.
That is the pyramids, they're the pyramids.
(laughter)
- That's funny every time.
- 21.
- No, it's a three.
- Stop saying, stop saying.
(laughter)
- 21.
Okay, cool. Yeah, I mean this thing is like is lurching back in pain. It's not looking too hot
You are now. Oh wait. Can I do extra damage right now?
You're flipping them off. He doesn't really register it, but he's probably upset
Also as the light increases you see that the cards that are on it looks sort of like Yu-Gi-Oh or magic cards
But oh my god Kingdom Hearts chains of memories, but the pictures are all of like pulsing like vaginas
Just like like Georgia O'Keeffe postcards
Because they're all
Probably nutted her fucking jeans when she saw that yeah, she never did a penis
All of her pussy painting should have had in the corner a little discarded pair of jeans
(laughing)
- They should have had a little mini version of me
sitting on him doing a peace sign going,
(imitates gun firing)
- You're up, Blotas.
- I'm up. - Blotas.
- It's dark in the cave?
- No.
- Yes.
- Well, it was light a second ago.
- 'Cause of the lightning, bro.
Stop drawing.
- It's 'cause of the lightning.
- Well, okay, instead of yelling at me,
will you maybe wait and hear my action?
- Okay, I'm sorry for yelling and I'll wait.
action I open my mouth I say "Hey who turned out the lights?"
So it doesn't seem so stupid now to ask who it is.
The thing hasn't gone yet?
Hasn't had a turn yet?
Okay then where's all my dice?
I forgot to make Pat roll with disadvantage.
I'll run up to it if I'm close enough.
I'm just gonna hit it and I have advantage
and if I hit it's a critical hit.
- You have regular right now.
- What?
- You have regular 'cause you can't see none.
So you go from advantage to regular.
I forgot to make him roll disadvantage,
but I'm-- - I have regular right now.
I understand now.
But I'm gonna do it.
Do regular once.
And that is a 13.
- It's not enough.
- Okay, and I'm gonna do a regular twice.
- Wait, why come?
- And that's a crit.
Oh my god!
So basically I wasted my fucking 20
Oh my god
Wait, wait, uh
Oh yeah, because it hasn't gone yet
Yeah
21, oh
*laughter*
Plus, that's 10, do I double the plus 4?
No, it just counts
You always do such chunky damage
Yeah, he's sort of the DPS guy
I'm the DPS guy
- Don't say the penis sucker.
- I was gonna say dude's penises per second.
- That's too much, that's DPPS.
- No it's not.
- PPDS.
- Sorry, are you adding your things
or are you worrying about my language?
- I already added it.
- Okay, well then say it out loud.
- You did 14 damage?
- 14, I said it out loud.
- Very nice.
- Okay, well then just stop talking to me though.
- So yeah, you run up and you miss and then--
- Can we pause?
- When you miss, you get your pause.
- I have an issue I need to kind of figure out.
- What's your issue?
- I don't want to figure it out with you.
Why?
Can we get in our private room?
I think you take your headphones off.
Yeah, you take your headphones off.
And then talk. You have to whisper into my ear.
He needs to go.
What do you mean he needs to go? He's part of the campaign.
He's out.
No.
He's out or I kill myself.
I'd take him.
Cam, come on. Don't do that.
I'm gonna hang myself.
What are you guys talking about?
Don't hang yourself.
You're copying my move.
Okay, great. Pat's out.
- You're a copying flopper.
- Matt and Caleb are out,
or I shoot myself in the head on camera.
- Okay, so then it's just gonna be me and you,
what's that even gonna be?
- My Dinner with Andre campaign.
- Okay, I'm out or I kill myself.
- That's fine, yeah, you can do it.
- So you go up to this thing
and you just bat it with your lead pipes
and it takes another 14 damage.
- Are we still doing that?
- Excuse me?
- Are we doing a My Dinner with Andre episode?
- I'm open to it, we've talked about it.
- Yeah, all right.
And so then he takes damage and
Yeah, I mean this thing is is not looking great, but it is still up
So now it's its turn. I've said that before
It's its turn now
*laughter*
Hey baby, now it's it's turn
You had your go, now it's it's turn
*laughter*
(laughing)
- It's its turn.
Oh my god.
- Oh, it's its turn.
Okay, he said it's its turn though.
Sorry.
- That's so funny.
- Yeah, it's its turn.
- Okay.
All right.
- So it attacks.
Obviously it shoots fucking cards like gambit
Out of its vagina holes that are in the pictures cards
So all of you roll dexterity saving throws, okay? Oh my god. I
Don't have a 20 piece
Okay
I got a 12. All right. Just pick the good one out of these. I got a 9 I
Got a nine that's gone. No bag of dice right there patches
Oh, we've been missing we've missed lost a lot of dice wait on the bottom show then I should reroll with my own no
Just if you're missing too many which might be the case camera might be missing too many
I'm I can I get a new card sort of a full deck
He doesn't even like those rolls
Okay, and then what do you need pat d20?
Can you give me the darkest colored one you can find nope
Red oh my god, it's actually the one I wanted the ruby
I rolled a 12 23. I get a 20 really liar. No he got a nine
I got it like a four or something I got a rock both take 28 points of damage fuck you
I do and I are you mental?
No, okay. I told you yes, why you guys are here together 28, so I'm at do I take half or seven?
which is
14 I'm at 7 man
50 - I need to get in he's got healing 50 -
36 wait hold on open your phone. I did the calculator. Yeah, oh
For what
I did the calculator
Calculator has been done. It's 13
Not good at basic math man. We know I did this you know about it already. We don't have to keep bringing it up
Yeah, I just wasn't expecting that oh
Yes, oh instead so the
- Oh wait, I don't get any sort of blocking power
from having him on my chest?
- You know what, you're right.
- Man, fuck that.
I get half damage too.
- You do get half damage also.
Sullivan takes the other half.
- And my nanobot has a healing factor.
- Sullivan is knocked out.
Your nanobot does not have a healing factor.
- Okay, then he gives me a pep talk.
- So you guys can either--
- A pep talk?
- He gives me a pep talk.
- Let me do a death saving throw for Sullivan.
- Just one pep talk from Scooter though.
- Okay, that's a failure.
Okay.
Dude, are we gonna do it again?
Maybe. We're not killing him on purpose this time.
You just strapped him to your chest and called him a bulletproof vest.
As a cute nickname.
I guess it's an upgrade from shirt. He was shirt for a while.
Yeah, he was a shirt.
He was shirt. Now he's gonna be put on a shirt.
Yeah.
Either way, it is your turn, RayWilliamJohnson.
Okay, I would like to...
Eeweeweewee.
You've already done it.
You've done your eeweeweewee.
I would like to try my matrix beam one more time.
Let's do it.
Okay then, I'll do it.
19.
That's going to be a hit.
I saw it quiver on the edge.
Don't even say that, man.
Moist.
- Did I go there?
- Stop, don't say that word, it's so yuck.
- That's a one, I got a one.
- Yeah, but you have more rolls.
- Yeah, I don't remember how many I get though.
- Try like three.
- Yeah, try three.
- Yeah, it's in the sheet for sure.
- Oh my God, he said three,
I said three and then he rolled a three.
- And I was thinking two and he rolled two.
- You have more.
- How many do I have?
- I think you have four.
- Oh, you're right, okay.
- Can I do a guest roll?
- Oh wait, a celebrity roll?
- Can I do a celebrity roll?
- You can, but I don't get to add it.
- Yeah.
- But that would have been pretty decent.
- This thing is looking very bad.
- Yeah, you're telling me.
- Yeah, it was looking so hot
before we beat the shit out of it.
- Yeah.
- Patrick Yoda, you are up.
- I am just gonna hit it with the damn hoagie.
- Let's do it.
- 14.
- Plus.
Just, just add it.
No, you, just look at your attacks are in the top right.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sorry, top left for you.
So that is 14 plus eight.
Maybe, I don't know if it's--
Hoagie surprise, plus eight.
Is it really plus eight?
It says plus eight.
Oh yeah, I added it, it was--
2D4 plus four.
That's crazy I did that.
Yeah, roll 2D4 plus four.
Okay, that's a four.
And that's another four.
That's fine, I mean either way you would've killed it.
Describe your kill.
My kill is that, I mean it's a bunch of cards, right?
Mm-hmm.
I go to hit it with the hoagie and then I stop right before.
And then I cocks its head and then I poke it.
Oh no. And all the cards tumble down.
Ed, what do you say?
Finish him.
I say, fuck you.
No.
Was this your card?
No, you say.
Okay, I walk up, I say, 53 card pickup.
Nice.
And I say at the same time, sir, 52 card pickup.
Is this your card?
Was these--
Was these all your-- hold on, guys.
Was this card all of your cards?
I've heard of a house of cards, but this is ridiculous.
Yeah, were these your cards?
I know a thing or two about counting cards.
And there's 52.
Pick them up.
Is that good?
[LAUGHTER]
You tied them all together.
That was masterful.
So we're going to keep doing death saving throws for Sullivan.
We're just going to leave him there.
OK, he succeeded.
Keep walking.
He succeeded.
- Aw.
- It's gonna be every six seconds, so.
- But can't he just, if we already beat this guy,
can't Pat just get him up?
- Another success.
- I'm just gonna wait it out.
- We're just sitting there while he just gasps for air.
- It's two and two, y'all.
- Is Pat, you're not gonna help him?
- No, what, fuck no.
I got Scooter.
- He lives.
- Oh my god.
- He has skin of his teeth.
- I don't care about Sullivan, I got Scooter now.
- He doesn't have teeth.
- Yeah, but his skin of his gum, I know.
- More skin, God willing.
So he's just like passed out, barely alive, but pretty cool.
OK.
Back on my chest.
You put him back on.
You took him off while he was dying and just watched him.
Yeah, we had to see if we needed to--
We were all literally standing around him, watching him get
close.
[LAUGHTER]
And then he goes, whoo!
We're throwing down money like zero.
[LAUGHTER]
Cool.
So you guys killed this monster.
So you guys can-- so here's--
Well, we killed the queen of the gloaches.
That was not--
Maybe.
I'm going to leave.
- Was that it?
- It was not the queen of the cloches.
- So you start to hear some stirring from down the hall.
You might have made a little bit of commotion.
- Oh yeah, we're in the kitchen.
- You might have made a little bit of commotion.
So you start to hear some stirring from down the hall.
From the left you hear the same sounds
you were hearing before,
of the kind of like,
like kind of cheering from far away.
So it's up to you guys where you wanna go,
but I will say that like the stirring you hear
would suggest that something might be coming.
- Should we walk towards that,
or should we hide from it?
- Let's get the heaves out of here.
- Does it sound real, the stirring?
- Does it sound like?
- Wait, what do we know about the queen of the grotch?
- The queen of the greech?
- Yeah.
- So yeah, let's pretend that
Bear McGinnis finished what he said.
So that she typically hides in her cocoon.
- He was gonna tell us that?
- Yeah, he was gonna tell us that.
- So then let's go left, let's hide from this thing
because this is not the queen.
The queen's hiding somewhere.
- That's not a cocoon.
- Yeah, we want this thing to, I've played games before.
- We're gonna stealth it.
- We want this thing to walk past us
and then we walk behind it,
'cause it has something called a cone of vision.
So I don't know if you guys have played
many miniclip games, but there was one
where you had to hide from the teacher,
which I don't know, I never--
- And there was one called--
- Why are you hiding from the teacher?
- Are you a grown man? - Are you a ten-pump BB gun?
- What?
- Joe Cartoon ten-pump BB gun.
- There was-- - Another miniclip.
- All sorts of games. - My friend just showed me
game for Miniclip that we used to play. I forget what it's called.
Yeah, my friend. E-Bomb.
No, no. I'm playing that.
Etnies Downhill Jam.
So yeah, I'm going to grab them and we're going to jump into the left,
that little left turn, and we're going to wait for this fucking thing to go by.
And I'm going to use my, can I, we like all hold our breaths and...
Yeah, you can absolutely roll a stealth check.
Okay, all right. I'm going to do that then.
I can turn invisible.
You can turn...
Well, then do it, bitch.
Oh, and then I can put on my arcade repairman outfit.
I got to...
I got an 11.
Okay, go.
Okay, I'm putting on the arcade repairman outfit
and here's my stealth role.
It's not gonna affect anything you do.
I turn invisible.
I got a six.
Yeah, you turn invisible.
You're invisible.
You got a six, okay.
And you guys, so yeah, move your characters down the hall.
And I'm in an arcade repairman outfit, say that.
So this is that left turn area?
Patrick is in the arcade repairman outfit.
Yeah, so he can be, oh.
Wait, no, that makes no sense.
I could walk around here and say
that I need to fix the arcade in here.
- So you hear like the stumbling of,
not the monsters, but the Greeches themselves.
- Can I ask a quick question about how
Blowtoss's camouflage works?
- Absolutely.
- Is it how his invisible thing,
is he fully invisible, you can see right through him?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Okay, gotcha.
- It's not like super strong.
- So we can't hide behind him.
- No.
- Okay, nevermind.
- That's a good idea though.
- Oh, I see what you're thinking.
- You should try it.
- You're not behind him, you're just standing
out in the open going, "He he he."
- Oh, I forgot about that, that's like a kind of,
oh, that's cool.
- Active camo.
- Yeah.
- One, two, ten.
- Invisibility cloak.
- Maybe that's an upgrade you can get, huh?
- That'd be cool.
- Huh?
- But instead, oh shit, there we go.
- Talk into it.
- There's my timer, sorry.
So it's, you hear, it's some of the
Greeches themselves are like,
(guttural grunting)
and they kinda like stumble through.
- They just said, "What's up?"
- And they're like, they have their--
- What's up, what's up, what's up, what's up?
- What's up, what's up, what's up?
- They saw us, they're asking us what's up.
- So these are like former workers in the space station
who again were like corrupted by the poor air
and water quality.
And they've just been down here and they've just lost
their mind. - And they had to move
to the hood?
- Not quite the hood.
- So you would live here?
- What, no I wouldn't live there.
- Okay, so you're saying it's just short of the hood.
- What, no, it's not like any hood
that you've ever seen before.
It's the craziest, baddest hood in the world?
Yeah.
Damn.
Oakland.
It's not like any hood you've seen.
Walking around the campus.
This hood is not like any hood you've seen before.
One of those YouTube videos where a Swedish guy
walks around Oblok.
This hood is not like any hood you've seen before.
Just dark tunnels.
[LAUGHTER]
There's still a 7-Eleven.
But yeah, so they do see you guys
because of Pat's clumsy stealth roll.
And they kind of like,
they all wander towards you guys crotch first.
Are you flipping me off or the Greech?
- Wait, hold on. - The Greech is
'cause they saw me. - I'm going to,
guys, we pretend to be them.
- Oh my God, you're a genius.
- Duh!
Duh, I'm so stupid.
- Roll persuasion.
Roll performance, performance rather.
- Let me see which one I have a better one of.
They're tied. - Performance though.
Performance. - They're tied.
- Didn't count.
- I saw what you got, don't worry.
- A 20.
- Okay.
You are very convincingly just a greech right now.
Just like stupid and like--
- What's up, what's up?
- Just trying to stick your dick in things to feel whole.
You seem like an arcade repair man, Patrick.
- Don't worry guys, I'll turn him.
- Oh no, he's turning me and I'm an arcade repair man.
- Why are you--
- That's my bro, Rudy! - Drowning.
- Okay, so do they believe me when I say
I'm gonna turn him?
- They go and attack him.
- Bloody hell.
- But here's the thing.
Here's what I'll say about Greeches.
These guys are kind of like fodder.
- They're my dad?
- They're gonna roll to attack.
They're gonna roll to attack,
but if you dispose of them--
- That was good.
If you dispose of them quietly,
the monsters, who are actually pretty strong,
won't come checking on them.
- Okay, can I go--
- So they're attacking you right now?
- They're attacking you.
- I grab it by the throat.
- We want him to be quiet.
- I grab it by the throat and I scream.
- Shut up, bitch!
- Don't scream!
(laughing)
- Can I?
Can I?
- You're gonna get me killed,
I'm trying to do a stealth mission!
- We're gonna roll initiative.
- Trying to do a stealth mission!
- We're gonna roll initiative to determine order,
just me and you, Pat, right?
Everybody here's my idea though. I have an idea
Okay, yeah, you're trash
I got a 15
You'll do something yeah, you roll too cuz you're a part of the like you could do there in this turn order so
(gasps)
(laughing)
- You already looked like you knew
you were gonna roll a one.
(laughing)
- You're like, okay, you really want me to roll?
- Should I even do it?
- Yeah, go ahead, man.
- You really want me to roll, okay, cool.
- That's what you get.
- Yeah, you win.
(laughing)
- So they do go first, so they're gonna try to attack you.
They're very bad, I mean, like, even with this,
it's like minus their attack.
'Cause they're going, (groans)
like, kinda like, gumming, trying to gum you, almost.
Like, (groans)
- Yo! - I put my pants down,
I let it happen.
- Damn, wait, I never thought about wanting that before.
- Damn, okay.
Y'all seen Yes Man?
(laughing)
Why are you standing like this?
- You never thought about wanting that before.
- You're like, this is actual, I hate it.
Can I, because they think I one of they,
I'm one of them, can I kind of like let them walk by me?
- You're walking all the way over there.
You're far, far away from the microphone.
Far, far, far and far.
- Something's odd about you, we need to brush him to somewhere.
Can I let them walk by me and then kind of one by one
walk up to them, Agent 47.
- Absolutely.
- Break their necks.
- Just roll, roll, roll.
- Roll three D20s.
- Huh?
- Wait, no I listen to him.
- Just roll one.
- He's my boss.
- What?
- Just one.
- Just roll one attack roll, yeah.
- This one?
- Yes sir.
- Oh!
- Oh, bet you wish you were all three now.
- Bruv, you should have listened to me.
- You rolled a one.
- You should have just done it.
- Oh man, you got a one.
I do love that face. Oh shite.
I have a picture of you making that face. I love that face.
You should have just done what I said.
Get that dragon.
You go to snap their necks.
I just snap my own neck and I die.
No, instead you uh, snap it in such a way that it goes
fucking shit I say hello to you hey everyone shut up shut up right now you
hear you hear this thing lumbering lumbering down this hallway there is
here on the left here on the left we all were ready on the left here there is
Another passageway you could run down doing it. I'm running okay. I'm doing it fuck out of there
It's passageway. I'm and you see a pit in front of you. I jump I jump in I jump in I jump
I try to pull Sullivan's arm off like it's a parachute
Okay
We're all gonna take some damage now, so give me six
Did you not do anything? I'm invisible. Are you just standing still yeah, fuck yeah, or at least walking slowly, okay?
Can I roll to help myself?
What does that mean can I roll maybe a cushion? I'll help him can I roll?
Trampoline wouldn't that be acrobatics? I was gonna say you know it's a pit so roll acrobatics or athletics if you want
18 okay very nice what I'm small enough to jump on his back no no
We're just roll you're gonna mess up his y'all
- Can I roll for Scooter to maybe have a trampoline mode?
- It's a nano, why do you keep trying to give him stuff?
- I want him to be like my little cheating pet.
- He's ungrateful for his amount of abilities
and he wants more.
- Damn, you have so many abilities.
- It's a nine, it's a 10.
- Okay.
You take three damage.
- Not a big deal to me.
- You take six damage.
What are you doing?
- Honestly, I completely spaced out
when I was getting scared how skinny my wrist is.
And I don't know what's happening.
- Okay.
- So he rolled a one.
- It doesn't look all that skinny to me.
- It looks really small in the sleeve.
- You just have a big sleeve.
It's all--
- Yeah, we all look the same.
- Pretty much the same.
- It looks really like a skinny wrist.
- Yours looks big.
- Yeah, yours looks normal.
- Your sleeve is the right ratio.
But yeah, I don't actually know what they did to take--
- Oh, sorry, yeah.
- We fell into the pit. - We jumped down a pit.
- Yeah, okay. - Yeah, we jumped in a pit.
- You don't have to follow them.
Nobody knows you're-- - No one knows you're there.
- Yeah, you know what you could do
is you could go to the prison
and see if Sullivan is in there.
- New Sullivan. - New Sullivan.
- Okay, I'll do that.
- So, the prison, I mean, like,
you don't know exactly where the prison is.
- Oh, but I drew a map.
- That's right.
- Of a different place. - We've established it.
- Well, he can walk around.
- Yeah, you can walk around.
I mean, so how long is your visibility?
Like a minute?
- One minute.
- Yeah.
- Just run as fast as you can.
- So it's been like 15, like 30 seconds, let's say.
- So you wanna go back down this hallway, then.
- I mean, I could just keep moving past it.
- Once this thing uses it until, I have a few uses too.
So, that's all.
What else am I gonna use?
My other abilities?
I don't think so.
- Yeah, I guess not.
So, you two, though, fall down a pit.
Into, you would recognize Ray William Johnson,
Is sort of a toy pit like the one you saw earlier.
- Like the one that we got pushed down earlier.
- I'm scared for you guys now.
- And the sort of cheering and yelping that you heard,
it got louder as you like fell and when you landed,
you saw it's the Greeches all sort of yelping
and jumping around and like fucking shit
and what they're fucking is the toys
and also what they're fucking is a big ball
of Greeches and toys all molded together
like a katamari sort of thing.
- I flip it off.
- You flip it off?
And it is this disgusting ball of flesh and toys
and it turns to face you two.
And we're gonna roll initiative.
- What are you looking at?
I turn the same direction.
Look at it like this.
- We're gonna roll initiative for you two in a second.
First, you, Blowtoss, what do you wanna do?
What was that?
Is that a five?
- Nope.
- It was.
- It was a five, right?
I saw that you said it.
- I don't wanna keep it.
- Minus one.
- Let's not keep it.
- I, wait no, plus one, that's six.
- Six, it's a six, don't worry about it.
- I guess I'm trying to go to the prison.
- Yeah, sure, you certainly are.
- As fast as I can without being caught.
- So as you walk down the hallway,
you see the monster that lumbered by.
- I'm running, I'm making the most of my time.
- It was this sort of like stretchy, fleshy thing
that had like crackling electricity around it
and it had reached Manus' hand in Dark Souls 1,
reached for them and then lurched back.
- For those who haven't played Dark Souls 1, like a hand.
- Damn! - It's a specific
looking thing and you know that,
and yet you hurt me. - I'm getting it now.
- And yet you hurt me and my feelings.
(Justin laughing)
It was for a friend, you betrayed me.
So you go down the hallway like nothing.
(Justin laughing)
- And here, I'm gonna just redraw quickly.
- Ooh, snazzy.
- What the fuck?
Bro, you on another level tonight.
- I'm flippin' over the tiles, folks.
- Should this one be flipped too?
- Yes, it should.
Let's just flip all of 'em.
Fuck it.
- Flip 'em.
- Here, put 'em over here,
'cause it's just a continuity sake.
Continuity sake, kill me.
Here we go.
So-- - It's all green.
- So again, it's not really totally to scale.
I hate these greeches.
Me too.
They're not great.
They're making my life so difficult when I just want to reunite with my friends.
Just making sure I'm drawing the map correctly.
So you're really... Still I'm on a wild adventure.
And now I gotta fuck this ball.
Yeah, I have like no health. I'm at 5 HP. Are you sure this isn't exactly to scale?
Stop it.
Don't be mean to me.
- Oh, you're drunk.
Bottles are flying everywhere.
- I'm not drunk.
Stop it.
- Fucking, look at this.
You're gonna tell me that's not the drawings
of a drunk maniac?
(laughing)
Look at this, show this.
What the fuck is that?
- Stop it.
- Okay, I'll stop.
No, it's fine.
So yeah, you see a large chamber.
- I jump into the pool.
- It's not a pool, it's my fault.
You see also a large, huge bed.
It looks like fucking like 10 California Kings.
- Ooh.
- And it is just covered in filth.
And greeches are like fucking on it
and you see one monster also writhing around in the bed.
- In the bed, like lying in it?
- Yeah, while the greeches are like trying
to latch themselves to it.
The monster looks like kind of like part,
also looks like part toy, part monster.
- That is yucky vibes.
That is yucky.
- You see a stairwell on the left of the bed
that leads towards the prison.
- Okay.
- It literally says, "Prison this way," on top of it.
- I'm gonna run up the stairs if I can without my,
well actually, how long do I have left of my invisibility?
- You have like, let's see, I'm thinking about you
running down the hall.
You have like another 10 seconds.
- Do you think that's a reasonable amount of time
to get down this hallway?
- It's a reasonable amount of time for you
to round the corner to get to the stairwell.
- Because if not, I'll just wait and I'll recast it.
- I would probably wait and recast it
- What else are you gonna do?
- You're gonna run some risk.
- I'm gonna do that then.
- Okay, cool.
- 'Cause I don't really wanna be caught while I'm alone
'cause I'm scared when I'm alone.
- For real?
- What's so funny?
- You're so tired you became the him.
- What?
I didn't do anything.
He's drawing and laughing at it.
- No, it's an old drawing from a couple episodes ago
that I completely forgot about.
- Let me see this one.
- It's Cameron Spice.
(laughing)
- Cameron Spice.
- I do like that one.
- Yeah, that's a good one.
I'm being strategic, by the way.
- Yeah, sorry, just to avoid--
- You just are talking funny.
- So-- - I'm not talking that weird.
- Weird.
- He's not talking that weird.
(laughing)
All right, so yeah, yeah, you wait.
- Yeah, and then I go-- - Turn invisible again.
Okay, cool, you go down to the prison.
- Yeah, so, and then I think it may be one,
maybe one Greech sees a guy just appear for like,
one frame, and he's like, oh, oh, oh, okay.
(laughing)
- I have my pants around my ankles.
- So you keep going down,
and so we'll go to you in a second.
- Okay.
- And we're gonna go back to where you two are.
- Thank God, I was getting bored as fuck.
- I could tell, you started drawing.
- I started tracing actually.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm not very talented at drawing.
- Drawing.
- I'm gonna start saying drawing like you.
- Drawing, yeah.
- Drawing.
- And rum.
So, where you guys are again is this pit with this Katamari-ass looking ball.
I didn't want to be in here.
I didn't want to be in here at all.
You're saying that?
Yeah.
How loud?
But I'm whispering it.
It already knows we're here.
I didn't want to be in here.
So yeah, I mean we don't even have to draw this.
I mean this is just going to be a big ball.
Does it look like one of the guys from Doom?
Oh, the Cacodemon?
Yeah.
Cacodemon.
- Oh, it does sort of look like that,
but it doesn't really have an eye.
- Here it is. - It's really like
just kind of a-- - I was thinking about
the Elden Ring, but a big ball.
- It kind of looks more like the, yeah, like the--
- With the heads. - What are those?
It's kind of like a lich.
It's like their version of a lich.
- It's all those-- - It's like a failed--
- Heads, stone heads. - Yes, yes.
It looks like that.
It looks kind of like--
- That's good.
- That's actually perfect. - It's like a tape roll.
- Great idea.
So you two, you rolled initiative.
What did you get again?
- A five.
- Okay, which became a six, right?
- No. - No, I rolled a six.
- He became a six. - He got the six.
- He got the six, oh Christ.
- Plus one, motherfucker.
- Okay, and then for the Katamari.
Oh, okay.
- Does it have a mouth?
- No. - Shit.
Does it have a hole anywhere?
- I mean, it's a bunch of guys and toys stuck together.
So there are crevices. - All right.
- But nothing really.
- I don't wanna know what that guy's gonna do with crevices.
- So five, six, okay, and this thing got seven.
So it is--
- It's a dope-ass order.
- Yeah, it is rolling towards you guys.
So both of you roll dexterity saving throws.
That's what this is, for sure.
You got a one.
- Motherfucker.
- No, that's a seven.
- You got a seven also?
- Yeah.
- No, it's a one, I was lying.
- Add your dexterity saving throws.
- Okay.
- Well, not you, you're fucked.
- I said six.
I'm gonna die safely
Yeah, well, it's I'm dead
I'm dead. You don't know that yet. Don't give up. Hope yeah, you're dead
And you you had 21 HP right 18 you have 18 yeah
Cuz I took three damage from my fall. All right, you're okay
Just tell me bitch who HP now, okay?
Don't trust him. He did the math for you
Maybe I think I probably did die, but he's not letting me die
Potion
No, Scoot did scooter come with us or scooters in my
Fucking pocket sorry house Sullivan doing
Yeah
He's still he's stable. Let's just say he's stable, and he's not gonna just
Stabilized right well if you get hit if you get hit when you're like oh, there's a chance you
Breaking the rules to keep this fucking loser alive, and we can kill him if you want. I don't want to do anything, but I mean
Rules are rules
Let's just move on I think it's a counts as another dead
If he's stabilized or does it have to go negative HP. I actually don't remember
Let me look this up. Okay. Let's find out
Dead he's dead
I wish I knew this offhand
Yeah, being wounded so I think it's different for frogs. I think frogs instantly die when you look at them
You kill your knock you out you gain one level of exhaustion
This is why cuz it's all it's exhaustion crap, which I have exhaustion the exhaustion is like
It's like each point like has like a debilitating effect until the last point you get is like death
- What's next, fibromyalgia?
- Yeah.
- They're gonna add in?
- What's next?
- Yeah, they're putting exhaustion in.
This game used to be about flesh wounds,
cleaving limbs, and twain.
- And cleavage.
- For him.
- Now it's about, what, they/thems?
- Yeah.
- Dressing androgynously?
Wearing chest binders?
- I wear one of those, actually.
So I wonder, so then does that mean
do we restart the death saving throws?
- That's what you're talking about.
- What are you, get out of here, bro.
What are you doing?
It's not your episode.
- This is like mom coming down into the fucking man cave.
Shut the fuck up.
- I forgot to open it.
- Ah, get away from me, mom.
- I forgot you were there.
- Freaked me out.
I thought you were a goblin.
I'm liable to shoot an arrow through your head.
- If you're gonna talk,
you have to put your face really big on the blue screen.
- I'm not gonna do that.
- All right, whatever.
Wouldn't that be kind of funny if you guys found out
that I just wore a binder all the time?
(laughing)
Be kind of cool.
- You had Guy Nicomastia?
- I can't tell if it like--
- I did when I was a kid.
- I guess if it's stable--
- I'll get into that another day.
- I guess it restarts.
I guess it restarts, so he takes another failure,
is what that is.
- Okay.
- That's what I'm just gonna play it as.
- Somebody can DM me after.
I never deal with this shit.
- Now you can DM us and get off your fucking computer.
- Get on with it.
- All right, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- And now for something completely different.
- You're up, Ray.
- Okay, I would like to throw, I would like to,
I mean, I'm the only motherfucker alive in this bitch.
I would like to throw a sexual grenade
directly into one of the crackles.
- They have sexual powers, I've learned.
- It doesn't really matter because I'm just kind of,
it's just an explosion.
- Okay.
- It's an explosion.
- Roll and attack roll.
Plus nine.
- That does hit.
- Nice.
And then two D10s.
- Two D10s?
Oh dear.
- Yeah, for the sexual grenade.
Which is this one I found out.
- Yes.
- Nice.
- Ooh, it's an eight.
- And this next one is.
- Oh, a three.
- Nice, and I think also, what is the,
I always forget, what's the rule I have for fire?
for extra damage is a rough--
- For each additional two Technoslime points spent
before throwing, Raywill and Johnson can deal
an additional 2d10 fire damage.
- Oh, well that's if you wanna spend more.
I have like a Juicy ability.
- Yeah, I'll do that.
- So you'd spend two more Technoslime points.
- Yeah, that's fine, so then I'll have one Technoslime point,
but I have refills.
- Nice.
- So that's another 2d10. - So that's another 2d10.
- That's fine.
- Wow.
- Well, I didn't know about it, asshole.
- That's my fault, you're right.
I should have told you--
- Wow, shit. - Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
- Damn, okay, so what did you get then?
- 28, no. - Wow.
- Wait, is it 15 and then 18 and one?
- You got 11 the first time.
- Oh, okay, so 26. - Okay, well, that's very good.
- I could be 100% wrong.
- We'll just go with that.
- Yeah, you just-- - We'll take a 26.
- But then also, isn't there,
I have something where it's like,
you get sticky shit on it, I just wanna make sure.
- Target must make a strength saving
where the sticky cum reduces their movement
by half for one round.
It leaves explosive cum everywhere.
- Okay, cool.
(laughing)
- Everywhere.
- All right, cool.
So it does succeed in the strength,
so I guess it was to fling it off.
I probably should change out the decks,
but, or something else.
But anyway, it does take 26 damage,
which is pretty hefty.
And you see it sort of like,
like skitter away and like roll around,
which you get an opportunity attack too as it does that.
- Please just fucking kill it in--
- I--
We should blow it into smithereens. It's just gonna be your dong blade. Wow it does hit okay
That's gonna add you that but it is 1d 10 plus 5 mm-hmm
Where my d2 others?
So that's seven shit, okay, that's okay. Yeah, so you slash it as it runs away, and it's like it's like
Fucking it's fine, but it is like it skitters and like rolls away and kind of like stays docile for a second
Can I stabilize Patrick while it does that?
- Yeah, it is gonna skip its turn.
- Okay, I'd like to stabilize Patrick.
- So-- - Get my guy up and running.
- All right, cool.
So you can roll a medicine check.
- I can't use my foreskin on myself, right?
- No, you can't. - Roll a medicine.
- Bro.
- Nice. - 14.
- That works, so he is stabilized.
Roll perception as well, I wanna give you a little--
- Dude, I'm basically rolling.
- You're in a pretty dark place right now.
- He has dark vision. - Holy shit.
- He's the one who doesn't have supposed to have that.
He can see everything.
- No, you're in a dark place, I mean, in the game.
Like you're in a bad place right now.
I'm giving you a little gimme.
- Okay.
- Like, but you rolled a natural one.
- Well, he rolled a natty 28.
- This thing is a Katamari.
- That was it?
Are you kidding me?
No, he gets more than that.
- Let me finish what I'm saying.
You could roll it around.
- Does it?
- It is now stable.
It's gonna start up again
'cause you used your turn to stabilize Patrick.
- Quick sidebar.
- What is a catamaran?
- You roll it around.
- It rolls around, it picks up everything.
- It picks up everything.
- It's like a big ball of glue.
- It's a ball of everything.
- But can I drive it?
- Yeah, you can push it.
- If you push it.
- Oh, you push it.
But I can't get on top and run around.
- Just push it, push it.
- You could do that.
- Just push it.
- Can I get on top and run around
and like basically do a reverse?
- That is the exact--
- Like I move my feet forward
and it goes forward like in Mario Party?
- It's exactly like Katamari.
- Like bumper balls?
- Yeah.
- That would be an athletics or acrobatics check.
- Well, I'm not gonna risk it.
I'm just gonna get behind that thing,
hit it from the back.
- So right now, what you've noticed,
I mean, you got 20.
- So.
- What you've noticed is that it stops
and like sort of stands still,
and then you used your turn to get up Patrick,
and it kind of starts up again.
Stop, don't do that.
- Okay. - Stop that.
So it's going to come back at you again.
But maybe if you hit it, it will stabilize again.
You see what I'm saying?
But first, you're gonna have to roll
dexterity saving throw.
- Okay. - And you might die.
- Yeah, right.
I only have a negative one.
- Holy shit.
- I should've left my hand there
and let it bounce off my hand.
- Guys, it's over.
Show them. - We're all gonna die.
- Show them.
- You gotta create one, right?
- It was a 16.
- No, it was a one.
- Okay.
- Slank.
- Yeah, I mean, you're--
- It was an 18.
- It was actually technically a zero,
'cause of the negative one dexterity.
- Yeah, I mean, you're dead.
Like, you're knocked out.
- Bro.
- You're stable here.
- And I don't know any of this is happening.
- Mm-hmm.
- We're fucked.
Wait, wait, I have, oh my God.
- I'm running around invisible--
- Oh my God, it's Scooter's time to shine.
(laughing)
- It is Scooter's time to shine.
- Holy shit. - Does he control Scooter now?
- No, but Scooter--
- Ratchet and Clank?
- Scooter can run that. - Scooter can--
- Oh, I'm dead.
- Gouter can see this is happening.
- And let him know.
- And try to run up and get out of the hole.
- Can he just use my PSP?
- He can tap into my PSP.
- He could use your PSP.
- He could become my PSP like Rotom.
- He could, well he could just use it.
- In Pokemon Galaxy.
- He goes to your PSP and he types.
- Okay, I can't even have that.
- He is saving your life.
This nanobot, you made your friend.
- We don't know if he's saving our lives yet.
- Well, we'll see.
- 'Cause we have to start riding.
- Oh yeah, you do have to start rolling death throws.
Yeah.
So, not you. You're fine. You're stabilized.
Oh, I got a 19.
You're stabilized. There's no issue for you.
He's the one who might die.
Twelve.
Okay, we'll stop right now.
He's typing T...
Do I have service, guys?
You have service.
I don't know.
The whole thing, it's a big 5G station.
I was at a stairwell. I went down.
Blotoss, help, help, help.
New friend's dead.
Is my... Well, wait. I can't see my PSP. It's invisible.
- I'm fine with it. - Roll another death saving throw.
- Okay.
(dice clatter)
10.
- All right, that's two successes.
- Oh, not so funny now, asshole.
- You receive the message.
- Is my PSP invisible?
- I'm rolling another one.
I'm rolling another one right now.
So my clothes are visible then.
Three, three successes.
- Stabilized.
- What does that mean?
How long can we just stay stabilized?
- Forever.
(laughing)
- Really?
I kinda wanted to die.
I was kinda like--
- I don't know what the technical rule is for that.
I mean this thing--
- We finally go into our first actual mission
to not all die.
- This thing is gonna like charge at you again.
- So we'll have to--
- Okay, so I can get the message.
I feel the vibration.
And--
(mimics gunfire)
- Pick up your mic.
- What did you say the rule was?
If I'm already stabilized and he attacks me,
I have one more saving throw to see if I stay stabilized
or if I go back into death throes, right?
- Yeah, which reminds me that Sullivan is also,
you guys might all just die.
- I'm coming, I'm on my way.
I felt the vibration.
- I don't know.
- You're one minute away.
- You're like one minute away.
- Yeah, well then he'll decloak in the pit.
- Yeah, we're gonna do it where it starts again.
I think I like that.
So let me roll the two, the others for Sullivan.
- I can't teleport anymore, right?
- That's a success.
- Success.
- That's not a success.
- Oh, I can teleport.
- Sullivan is stabilized by some fucking--
- Okay, so what do we do now?
- You two are both destabilized.
You're one minute running towards them.
- How long does it take me to run that distance?
- 18.
- Okay.
- That's a fail.
- 10.
- Okay, success. - That's a success.
- Roll again.
- That's a success, two successes, one fail.
- You're stabilized.
- Stabilized again.
- Both are stabilized again.
- Great success.
- Wow, that's pretty lucky.
- I'm running in slow motion.
- You're running in slow motion.
You get to the pit.
I teleport down I jump down I'm belly flop
Five damage
Five damage I can hold that what's your what's your?
31 what the fuck I didn't take
All right, and you two are now a part of the Katamari am I oh
Unconscious do we have to do another one visible mm-hmm or ward off weird?
- No, you two are stabilized right now,
unless he's gonna attack him again,
which will cause you guys to--
- Destabilize you.
- And he will have to hit it.
- I run up and hit it.
Let's not stop beating around the bush.
- All right, roll damage.
- Damn, oh, okay.
- Well, I'm sorry, stop, stop, you tricked me.
- I tricked you.
- You tricked me.
- Nat 20.
- No way.
- Yeah.
- So everything's solved.
- Pretty much, he's gonna kill him.
- Well, you guys are gonna be destabilized again, though, too.
- Oh, from that?
But he would have three turns, right?
12 damage.
- Okay, that thing now stands still.
And so, you two, yes, you have three rounds.
Just take your failures, don't keep rolling,
don't keep rolling, don't keep rolling.
- One fail.
- Don't keep rolling yet.
One success for Sullivan.
Don't keep rolling.
One fail, one fail, one success.
Now it's your turn.
- What am I supposed to do?
- Yeah, what is this?
- What is this situation?
- You could try to peel them off the ball.
- They're on the ball, I peel you off the ball,
and I also push the ball.
Is there like a hole with spikes at the bottom?
Or a big hydraulic press?
- Do you start pushing the ball?
- Yeah, but I wanna push it somewhere away.
- You control the ball now.
- Okay, so then I command the ball,
I say, "Get my friends off of you!"
- Well, I mean, you control it like you can push it.
- Put his back on it.
- And as you push it, you add more bodies and toys to it.
- No, they're getting covered up.
- No, no, you peeled them off, right?
- Yeah, I already peeled off.
- I didn't, you didn't tell me I already could do it yet.
- Okay. - I failed again.
- Okay.
- Nice success.
- Sullivan fails.
- So that's three successes.
- No, you had two successes.
- And I have two fails.
- Stop rolling. - Stop rolling.
- You're supposed to roll one per round.
- I saw that, don't roll yet.
So, you can now roll up and it can pick up more bodies.
- But I don't wanna do that.
- You don't wanna do that.
I wanna save my friends, I don't know what to do.
- So do you have any healing abilities?
What can you do for healing?
- I have nothing, I have no healing abilities.
I have nothing.
- That's just gonna happen right in front of you.
- I could kill, I could put them in mind prison.
- To keep me forever alive in your heart?
- I'm a video of them having sex.
- That might shock me awake, like smelling salt.
- I have use object.
- Don't you dare.
(laughing)
Don't you dare use me.
- Okay, I'll try to stabilize them.
Is that medicine check?
- Yeah, you can do one at a time.
- Who are you doing first?
- Who has more failures right now?
- He does.
- Okay, I'm okay with this.
- I wanna die.
- That is a 15.
- Sorry.
- Oh, fuck you.
- Okay, all right.
That's two failures or one failure?
Do you want two failures?
I think it's do or I don't know that was one failure for you, okay, all right
Sullivan has two successes one failure all right now. I will do a medicine on Pat
That's a 17 Wow okay now the big one and now I push the ball away
Stabilized I didn't even notice all right you push the ball away the ball is still
Now you're just in this pit. I don't have any heal it. What do I do?
- We need to move our bodies around?
- Yeah, you gotta add us to the ball, bro.
That's the only way to get us around.
- Here's an action I have in my actions list, help.
- You could help, I use help.
- I use help. - With action?
- That doesn't make any sense.
- He could help me by getting the foreskin out.
- Yeah, can he pull his foreskin over me?
- Yeah, can I pull his foreskin open?
- You can pull his foreskin.
- That I like, there was another solution,
but I like that solution.
- Well, what was your solution?
- What was, no, no, no, no, no.
- Say it, I'm not gonna do it, but just need to know.
- Let's just do it, let's just do it.
- Roll the ball to pick up enough guys
that you can climb and get out.
- How's that help heal us?
- Well then heal us first.
- We can't heal you right now.
That's nothing you can do about that.
- Oh, okay.
I roll the ball around so it gets big enough to climb.
- No, no, no, I like the foreskin idea though.
- Okay, I do that.
- All right, it's gonna do half heal.
Let's do that. - That's all right.
That's fine with me.
- So roll, you roll the heal. - But then I can do,
but then everything gets-- - What do I roll to heal?
- The ball gets put in motion, if you pardon the pun.
- Get the ball rolling.
- Okay, that is for 1d10 plus four.
- So we'll do this and then--
- Eight.
- And then divide that by two.
- Well, eight plus four.
- Each of us get what?
- Oh, 12, so then each of you get six HP.
- Nice.
- And Sullivan, too.
- And now you guys are in this pit.
- Okay, we're all rolling the ball together.
- I roll the ball over them.
- And you roll the ball over the bodies
to make it big enough so you can climb out of the hole.
And next time...
It was a puzzle.
We will continue...
Through the future's lair.
Oh my god, it was a puzzle.
That's why we almost died, because it wasn't a fight.
No, that wasn't even a D10 that I rolled, that was fine.
Wow.
That was a fun little...
Was it fun?
I like, I like the whole point of D&D is being this close to dying every single time and
then being like, just kidding.
That was really close, you guys got some very good rolls.
That was, yeah.
I, you know, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I
That was a D10 that I was fine. All right, that's a fun
I like oh
I like the the whole point of D&D is being this close to dying every single time and then being like that was really close you
Guys got some very good. That was yeah, I
Bye
[Music]