[MUSIC]
Last time on...
Gun City, Abroad City, Playtime Continue Fun.
Seems Patrick Yoda ended up in a jam.
He read the minds of the mindless mocs, keep calm and chive on,
but found himself hung high by his own hubris.
Smashing an arcade machine with the hopes of repairing it.
He was chased out of Gaddy Up by burly bar bouncers
who bemused tossed him right back in.
Before Yoda could start licking his wounds, Ms. Janet Blowjob sauntered into the saloon
with legs up to here.
Some say she took a shine to the puny pet, who managed to score both her digits and some
very, very nice uppies.
Meanwhile, Blowtoss and Rey were...
sticking their things in a dead snake that attacked them.
Yep, we both did it.
Well, really it was just Blowtoss.
I didn't wait.
No, no, no.
The narrator just said we both did it.
is
Its hulls are made of some kind of supernatural material.
This would be in line with a lot of other stories.
Um, oh this was, nevermind I gotta keep going.
Now they have to go see Ebenezer Keech, a scientist on the ship who once worked for Papi Chuko's
Techno Slime with Tool Lateralis, and now heads up the R&D division on Pleasure Palace.
Doing a jerk off motion.
As the sec-
Juvia's jerking off while he's producing this episode.
I saw it on his video screen.
He's jacking his shit.
He literally just jerked off in his hoodie.
Stop!
Stop it right now.
Sit down.
Don't stand up when you jerk off at your computer.
He's got the deep fakes.
He's got those deep fakes of us on his screen.
I would believe that.
When Blotas and Ray arrived at the command center to find Ebenezer Kish, they were greeted
by Gumby Superior, the man shepherding Pleasure Palace, and a war hero who fought in the Vampire
Wars.
And what he said was curious, saying that playtime might not even be real and is instead
a convenient scapegoat, both for the Empire and for the Undercity to avoid addressing
the real problems found in huge-ass facts criminal enterprise, and that the detective's
beloved son, New Sullivan, was actually kidnapped so that the detectives would be drawn into
an unsolvable case and then murdered.
And apparently he's sort of intimating that he may want to destroy the Undercity.
Anyway, Patrick Yoda, meanwhile, was on the other line, because he's just always on the
phone with them in every scene.
Yeah, I don't like that.
Sharing all the hot gas to Gumby, from Gumby to Baby Gag.
And that's short for Gossamer.
The material.
material. Yes, and he's now armed with some serious info to improve his station in the
Huge Ass Facts organization. Meanwhile, it's been about three hours since Playtime's last
murder. So, he's killed two members of the Royal Guard today, right? He slit the throat,
almost killing our friend, he's a very close friend of mine, whose name I always remember.
- O'Neal. - O'Neal, right.
O'Neal, who also was not a part of a childless couple.
And so now it's sort of approaching evening.
So a couple things I wanna make sure
before we keep going and finishing off with the speech
with Gumby Superior was giving you guys.
Blotas, you got a 20 on your insight roll.
And so to round off on what you had learned
that I kind of mentioned in the recap
is that Gumby definitely believes all the shit he's saying
about how the empire is wasting your time on this case
and that the actual issue is Hugh Jass Facts crime syndicate.
He believes that, you can kind of tell.
And that he's probably a fan of the empire
but has no great admiration for it.
He's obviously using it as a stepping stone
for his own designs.
And then the main thing that rang true
was that when he said the name of Hugh Jass Facts,
he shuddered and like, there was like a real fear
his voice and that's really what the 20 by the way nets you, is that little detail
I'll give you that little hint. So yeah you guys are sort of finishing up he was
kind of rounding off in the speech Patrick Yoda we'll go to you and baby
Gad who just heard the the potentially pseudo genocidal plans of Gumby Superior
but um so Gummy Superior starts to say to you guys so all I ask before you go on
your merry way. Face me like a man! Alright I will. Turn around. Shit. Yep that's not what I meant.
Yep I meant fall over. Get somebody please. You are such a dickass. Lift me up. There we go.
Just keep going. You have to wait for me to. No he's got to be upright. The toys aren't real.
All I gotta ask is that you keep in mind there's a larger issue here and that
this playtime thing is a distraction and if you want your boy back he'll best off
be helping me root the crime out of the undercity but I've taken up enough of
your time you've heard me say my piece what do you wait what do you I don't do
you know where our boy is do you know where Sullivan is I wish I did but
you're saying that you know how to get him back so I feel like you're hiding
something almost I'm not hiding you're not hiding look at me in the eyes you're
not hiding anything I'm in this regard no what do you mean in this regard I have
my own another we have to have my own private life yeah tell me about it tell
me everything I'm not gonna tell you I much more about I think he's gay I'm not
gay you're gay in a different regard though not in this regard no not in that
regard in a completely different regard let's switch can we switch regards wait
he is gay in a different regard my god wait I'm curious I'm curious did you
count the high rolls is making gay or the low roll well that's a statement
mm-hmm that's a real statement because it would be better if he was gay yeah
it is well we're talking about a different regard but in a completely
different regard. Look, why don't you guys, look here, one of my assistants will
give you both key cards so you can access the guts of the ship and you can, we'll
have a lieutenant waiting down for you, they can bring you to Dr. Keisha's lab.
All right, we're gonna send you on your way. You've heard my piece, I hope you
consider it and you consider reporting to me a little bit more often than you do
Belinda. He doesn't know but you guys literally just tormented her the last
time. Okay yeah I think we could probably treat you a little better than you treat them anymore.
In one regard. Okay he really stuck on that word. It's funny. Yeah was it funny?
Come be superior more like come in your posterior.
All right you guys gotta get out of here.
- Yep, okay, cool.
Yeah, he gives you key cards,
or his assistant comes up and gives you guys key cards,
and leads you to the elevator
that's gonna bring you into the guts.
Before we do that, though, let's go back.
So just swap the set around a little bit.
Let's go back to, oh, nope,
you just knocked everything across.
We'll go back, anyway.
So Patrick Yoda, you're in one of the slum
uh... units and i a m in the my new you're kinda your new digs that you guys
have a video apartment yeah that you guys will be sharing that's
basically won't cost you anything studio apartment looks great patrick wow
and uh... let's get out he doesn't have to get a big added here is that he
doesn't think i may be getting here in the apartment
he put him up to see that the best i can figure
by far is this what you know
- Yeah, he's gotta be kinda front and center,
it's kinda his show.
So yeah, and yeah, you hang up on the phone
and baby Gadd is just like, holy shit, this is big,
this is big, this could be good,
this could be good for all of us.
If we bring this information to Huge Ass Facts,
this is-- - Were you recording
the phone call?
- No, it was your phone, were you recording the phone call?
- No.
Whatever, look, they'll bully- we could probably do a playback, alright?
It's- it's- this is a big-
Do they record all phone calls?
Uh, well, it depends on your carrier. Who's your carrier?
Record a phone?
They probably record that call then.
[laughter]
Okay!
Look, look, look.
- It didn't, didn't, what's her name?
Janet Blowjob, she came up to you, right?
You got a number, right?
- Handan Blowjob?
- No, Janet Blowjob.
You can't really make that more dirty.
- You can change the name to Handan Blowjob.
- What's a handan, no, why don't you walk me through
what a Handan Blowjob is?
- What about Mandan Blowjob, and she's Jamaican?
- Why does that make it dirty?
- Doesn't make it dirty, it's just dirty.
- That makes it gay.
- That's dirtier than a normal blowjob.
- You are in the room!
- If a Jamaican does a blowjob.
- No, mandem, like how they...
- But there's a blowjob, so there's already one man.
- No, I'm making it gay now.
It was dirty when it was mandem.
- And that's dirtier.
- Are dirty.
I'm just writing this down for your character
so I know what you think of Jamaicans for future.
- All right, continue.
- Have you heard that Skepta song?
- Probably.
- It's to the tune of "Transformers."
- I'm skeptical of your social justice.
He says mandem in disguise.
And it's a transphobic social justice.
That's fair.
So he says, Baby God says, why don't you contact her?
OK?
Patrick got an important text.
No, you don't have to read out what it says.
Just keep going.
What does it say?
I think I should read this.
Come on.
I think maybe I should put it up on the screen.
This is what the fans want.
- Oh wow, Pokemon deep fake porn hot anal sex twist stream.
Come on.
- Come on, I didn't, I sent that earlier,
I just went through it.
- Where'd you even find that?
- Why'd you read that?
That's for you.
- Where'd you even find shit?
- I don't know, dude.
- I'll just send it to you.
- I was just on Pornhub
and I just clicked one of those fucking ads.
(laughing)
- This is gonna come out in like eight weeks from now.
- That is a funny show.
- But anyway.
So yeah, I mean, he's asking you to call her.
He can, I mean, he'll go on like,
I can take you to the lair.
Look, if I have you--
- You want me to call her?
- If I have you vouching--
- I'm nervous to call her.
- What?
- She was so tall.
- Yeah, she is really tall.
- She was so tall, she gave me uppies.
- Yeah.
- Why would you be nervous to come in?
- You're not in the room.
You can't be talking.
- Well, if you're just gonna say bullshit.
- I'm not saying bullshit.
- Oh, he's just making conversation.
He's doing his character.
- All right, whatever.
look look look look look
get your hand off my TV
how about
*laughter*
sorry about that sorry
look how about this
*laughter*
sorry
TV is awesome
I got a vertical TV
this is what aspect ratio is on
9 by 16 everything is shot on a phone
look how about this
you, you call her
I can hold your hand, make you feel a little less scared
So you're saying I gotta feel gay to talk to women?
I'm saying that that-
In all the man's hands?
I'm trying to problem solve here.
Look I wasn't even listening to that phone call.
Okay, well I was listening.
And I need you to vouch for me.
Alright, fine.
But I'm not gonna give a shit about it.
That's- oh, I got that.
Crystal clear.
Okay, so do you wanna call her or do you wanna not?
Yeah I'll call her.
Yeah okay.
bring bring hello she has a bring tone what yeah you can talk about my bring
tone oh this is you like my bring tone this is improv hey fuck fuck fuck tell
You heard some news I've seen her nude no
Fuck what?
Nude
My friend he wants to see you no, give me the phone, okay
Hi, hi, hi. Hi. I'm not gonna do both sides of this conversation, but uh, I'll do the other side. Hey
Hey, so, uh, let's do it. Yeah, let's do it. Uh, uh
- So, Ms. Blowjob, Baby Gadd, you might not know me,
I'm sort of low on the totem pole.
- I don't know you.
- Okay, sure, but we got some news about
potentially something kind of big.
- Oh.
- Oh, don't do that, please.
- Do what?
- I just ripped off the leg of this character.
Please don't do that.
- Ripped a fucking headless dog's leg off, Jesus Christ.
Sorry, back in a--
- Okay, continue.
- Okay, well, it's about Gumby--
Do you think I do a good girl voice?
I think so.
Thanks.
It's uh...
Who's asking?
Me.
Okay, your girl voice is amazing, Ms. Blowjob.
So anyway, I got some news that I really think you should hear about.
I have it recorded on the phone.
Here, I could send it to you through a private channel,
and then I would really like to meet with you at the headquarters.
I'm too busy.
Okay.
I'm too busy doing my makeup today.
- Okay, do you mind, hold on, wait.
There's a (imitates phone ringing)
There's another call coming in.
(imitates phone ringing)
Hi, it's me, the character.
Yeah, I would love to hear about this from you.
- What?
- Wait, am I, did you kill me?
Am I not in the scene anymore?
- Yeah, sorta.
- Oh, okay.
- I would love to hear about this.
Send me over the thing.
And he sends the thing over.
- We should've just done one-sided phone call.
- Janet, Blowtop, and Babygad have the same voice.
Oh, what's that Mrs. Blowjob?
You volunteered to do the voice!
Well you said you weren't doing both sides.
Somebody had to step up.
No, she sorta talks like this.
He sorta talks like this.
No, you sound like that.
What the fuck did you just fuckin' say to me?
That's not what I meant.
I sound like this, man.
No I do not!
Shut up.
You're a little hellish.
back off slut fuck you can I have my phone back yeah yeah yeah here you go
he gives you the what did she say she said she was very interested in being
with us if if what the recording I sent is real and and and we should just go we
should go straight to the lair of I don't have to get naked do I know you
can do whatever you want I just come please come with me though I don't want
to do this alone. It's your phone. Unless you want me to just take your phone.
I'll go.
Okay. I would have taken your phone. So you guys are going to go to the lair of facts.
Okay.
And we'll go back to that in a second. Actually, you know what? We should probably just keep
going with that.
Okay.
We'll come back to you guys in a bit. I think this is probably better. I'm sorry guys. So
you walk further into the undercity. The lair of facts is at the very end of it. It's at
bottom tip of the Pleasure Palace. So if you guys remember from the map, it's sort
of a, you know, it's part of that bottom part of the sort of curve thing. You can
look on the screen, you can see like the the ship and shit, but um, the space
station I should say. It's about a hundred yards from the like outrageous
bay window that overlooks the universe. The lair itself though is below the
ground of the undercity, burrowing its way through the guts and can't be reached
without taking a circular lift marked by a garish chrome finish you can pick out
from across the way. But not before you'd see a military column of Don't Wake Daddies
and gently humming surveillance bots patrolling the area in something maybe more bizarre than
an underground lair in space. Overhanging the lair is a 15-story cascading grape cluster
of organic alien material that glows at an uneven pulse. The whole thing is easily 200
feet around, with the bottom-most grapes only about 15 feet above the area around the elevator.
So imagine a cluster of grapes and then some 15 feet between that and the ground.
They got homers.
Homers.
Grapes.
We're homers.
You need to put the Homer Brothers in.
I will.
We're the Homer Brothers.
We're two homers.
Us.
(laughing)
- That's very good actually, I'll back pocket it.
Each mammoth sized grape is made of a mix of pale yellow
and ochre with dark brown veins cresting through.
- Shrek vibes.
- Ochre.
- Like a brownish orange.
- Like a gang.
- Man, I don't know what the hell you're talking about.
- Like a Shrek.
- Like a Shrekish greenish color.
- Well it's really a clay but it's also a color.
- Ochre.
- Lifeless, pumping nothing, flaky and decrepit,
something glossy or viscous is inside of these things,
but on top of this giant cluster--
- It's jizz.
- Is a shaggy mound of bruised gray fur
that covers one of the topmost grapes.
- Yeah, jizz.
- It's not jizz.
Behind the cluster, barely visible against the dark sky
beyond the bay window,
appears to be a thruster of a lost ship.
So it's this giant grape cluster--
- With a thruster.
- And it's going fester and fester.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
But it looks nothing like any craft you've seen.
- And you said it was yellowish, like mustard.
- Yeah, the grapes are.
But the ship is near-- - Like Smucker's grapes.
- Like Vantablack.
But it's also, you can make out pock marks.
It's like a cyst-ridden foil, it almost looks like.
It's like very strange, like organic and metal
kind of combined. - Kind of like custard.
- Like a custard, organic and metal.
My first thought goes to custard.
The whole site together looks like a blown up,
exaggerated version of some of the alien structures you've seen. Structures? Yeah,
it's a bustard structure. It's a bustard structure made of grape clusters that
who lack that luster. Yeah. Can it cut the mustard? It can, but not quite like the
band Guster. You mean Duster? No. I mean there's a band called Guster and a band
called Duster? Why haven't they played it together?
- To Guster. - To Guster.
- Why haven't they gone on a world tour to Guster?
- Anyway, it looks like the Elliot structures you've seen throughout the
Downer District and Undercity, but kind of blown up in different parts of that map.
- Ruptured. - Ruptured, yeah.
As you reach the lift, which shuttles you downward
through the guts, gunmetal walls flank
your descent along with two-- - Do we go to the guts first?
No, they're going through the oh, okay. That was good. I
Was really good as far as those go you got me back. Yeah, I was getting pretty fucking frustrated, but that would go
Along with two surveillance bots that followed your descent you could tell
The lift reaches destination as a showy yellow door comes in the frame with Paisley like
Embossments lined with like a viridian neon so it's just kind of like like really kind of an abrupt stop
I'm not a screen abrupt er no must hurt that was a
This was a teaser for the garishness to come as the almost lurid lights of the huge-ass lobby
Reflect against the plain marble flooring so it's like super harsh lighting
Reflecting against his flooring this lobby looks super like pristine for some reason looks like the pyramid from Blade Runner 2049
I haven't seen 2049. It looks kind of like a
This Jared Leto is in I don't know anything about what Jared little dozen is off time, but it looks like a movie
He's a rapist. Oh, okay. I think he's a
blind
Wait is he blind he's got weird eyes is that why?
He doesn't know the age of women when he goes to them. Yeah, yeah, he says let me see the ID
Pretending he's seeing the look at all the graphics
They handed him a Lowe's foods card. He's like, "Oh, you sure are 14. Let's go."
But yeah, so the sterile, super expensive chrome furniture and siding along with the floor
to mirror ceilings all around. The lobby in front of you with its ridiculous furniture
makes about 30 feet from yourself and a reception desk behind which sits three beautiful V-folk.
of them spots you as you take your first few steps and suddenly materializes
materializes to your right so you walk out of this elevator that's kind of in
the central area right all around you in the lobby and then suddenly a V-Folk
from the lobby you see them in the distance and then they just blink and
they're right next to you. Welcome to the lair of facts! Oh I'm sorry sir I'm sorry I've been
I've been taking behavior medication that makes me act crazy.
Yeah, he's very sorry.
What?
I've been taking behavior medication...
I've been taking behavior medication that makes me act crazy.
...that makes me act crazy.
If you're here to make a query, we'll have you...
We'll have a chaperone bring you to the query booth on...
Sorry, I got the voices mixed up.
Query booth at your house.
road. Bring you to a query booth on floor B6. If you need consultant services, you'll
find those on floors B2 through 5. I want to see the big man! Oh yeah, sorry, sorry. My
friend here, we're kind of past all that. We're here, Ms. Blowjob invited us, the Queen
of Facts herself. Don't worry, they're with me. Oh no, what am I doing? No, I'm kidding.
Sort of out of the, you see someone else
from behind the desk come around, another V-Folk,
and they're sort of this stylish fop of a man.
They look like a bow-legged pixie stick.
And they come up to you and they go,
"Oh, I'm so sorry.
"My name is Kenan Thompson, I'm--"
(laughing)
How did I get 'em?
- So what, it's a white guy named Kenan Thompson.
- I'm personal assistant to Ms. Blowjob.
(laughing)
- Kenan Thompson, personal assistant to Ms. Blowjob.
- I'll be taking care of them now.
You can go back to your desk, Cynthia.
And you see this man says to you guys,
here, let me bring you two back to the elevator.
We'll be right to Ms. Blowjob.
You can skip all this queries and factoids
and all that stuff.
And he brings you guys to the elevator.
And we're gonna cut from that elevator.
- What about a robot named Dell Mitchell?
- I'll write that down.
To a different elevator.
- He loves the orange box.
- 'Cause look who's on.
Look who's, come on, man.
- We're also going down an elevator now.
- Wee!
- You guys entered a large circular loft.
- Also, the doors close behind you like the aperture.
- I just built the elevator,
can we spend a little time more in here?
- Come on, just let us get one minute in here.
- Okay, sure.
- Blowtos, I think we're trapped in the elevator.
We have to hit the alert button.
(imitates alarm)
- Hello?
- Oh, it's a girl.
hello bloat
elevator is empty we are the
we are the
controllers of the elevator
it's not stuck at all
and we need to patch it into a
male human
um hey
bro you should have heard this bitch
we were just having phone sex with
one second ago she was so hot
she thought we were
elevators she seriously thought we were fucking
elevators she fucking probably
Nodded in her chair
She was so fucking horny for us
Ball of goop on her floor dribbler fucking threw up you for you your access cards will grant you
Access fuck my pro my writing for this AI is so bad
Like AI to me okay switch back to the girl then
Your access has been granted to go to DJ. You granted us ass sex
- Oh, well we are not elevators.
- No.
- We are two very young men.
- The elevator glides.
- Very horny teenagers.
- We are potent.
- The elevator glides smoothly down.
- Glide.
- Oh yeah, I'm fucking gonna go.
- Your stomach barely drops as you pass through
about half a mile of space station.
- Wait, blowtoes, I am a computer.
Oh fuck.
- You hear the slightest creak
as you approach the bottom,
but the landing is mostly immaculate.
The doors open. - One, two, three, jump!
- I jump, I try and just crash the elevator.
- Roll athletic, roll athletic check.
- That's a natural.
- Oh my God.
- Your jump is, what do you, your jump is perfect.
- I'm trying not to knock the elevator off the cable.
(laughing)
- Oh, for real man?
Dude, I, no, I gotta--
- That's what I said before I rolled it, I have to stick to it.
- Do I have to roll?
You could roll to try to stop him I guess.
Nah, I rolled a... I guess like putt.
Tackle him?
Yeah, I mean I guess I'll... Alright, hold on, I'm rolling.
Holy shit!
Oh my god!
What the fuck?
Wait, wait, camera here.
Wait, oh my god, what do we do, bro?
I've never seen two nat 20s like dueling nat 20s.
I mean...
I guess it's sudden death.
Yeah, usually it's a reroll, but...
But I feel like it would be much more...
- You just don't want the elevator to fall.
- I mean, I feel like--
- That's a you, just a plain favorites.
- No, I would feel like it'd be much more interesting if--
God, what do you do?
Do you break it and then do you hold it up with your mind?
- I was gonna just try to shove my,
just distract him, like shove my face into his nuts.
- Okay, so in that case, what you should do is roll like--
- So wait, I jump up in the air and you stick your face
up in my nuts?
- Yeah, that's what I was saying.
Like, that's my quick thinking.
- Because I go, okay, so first of all, he jumps up.
- Hold on, you're not even processing
the elevator's about to fall,
you're just like, oh, he's in the air,
I want to smell his nuts.
- No, no, he goes up and I go RDJ Sherlock,
and I'm seeing every version of the situation.
And I realize that the only way that I'm gonna survive this
is if I stick my fucking face directly
into his stinky Grinch nuts.
- Okay.
- Yeah, I mean, I think--
- Who nuts?
- I think, let's do another roll again,
'cause like he did, that was like perfect.
- Let's just, we'll be rolling just to see if,
how this resolves. - You wanna switch dice?
- Let's do it.
- You're trying to get your head in his nuts,
you're still trying to jump down.
- Okay, let's roll over here.
- 15. - 15, damn.
- 11.
- But add your, what are you doing though?
- Oh, is it athletics? - Sucking his balls.
- It's your athletics or acrobatics for you?
- For me? - Mm-hmm, for you.
- My athletics is six.
- My athletics is seven.
- All right, he still wins.
- So you almost break the elevator,
and then your face is just buried in his nuts.
- Okay.
- And so it stops his momentum,
and then the door opens to like a hallway.
There's like people in there.
- I spit him like 30 feet out of the elevator.
- No, you didn't beat me by that much.
- I fucking owned him.
- It was very close.
That was about to be--
- This is what you do.
- We would have skipped some stuff.
- That's a trouble pick. - In a second there.
Which would have been kinda cool.
That would have been kinda cool.
Aren't you glad we spent a little time in the elevator?
- Yes, I'm glad now.
- But now we're out of it.
- It's true.
- I'm getting a call from Bicurious, Ohio.
- Okay.
- They've been calling, it says Bucyrus.
But I've gotten a call from there in the past four minutes.
- The door is open and you're greeted to first
a half-wide metal hallway of dark blues and grays.
The walls lined with dashboards presenting critical data
and some counter space with terminals
manned by crew members.
Some working away, others chatting amongst themselves,
looking towards the dashboards.
So it's a sort of like little dark blue hallway.
And then at the very end of that,
you see those crude fluorescents of a commercial building
that you're used to seeing with a large entryway.
- There's a dog man.
- This guy's here.
- They put patches in the fucking game.
- Nope, that's not me.
- That looks just like you.
- Don't do that.
- I'm not a dog man.
(laughing)
- It looks just like you.
- Look at the tail, look at it touch his tail.
- No, don't show your ass on screen.
Come on, you fucking disgusting.
- I'm sorry.
- All right.
- Did you just take off something?
- Yeah, I see your butthole on the thing.
- All right, anyway, so there's no, you know,
and you guys walk down this hallway,
I don't know if you do or if you guys
Also like fuck around down this hallway.
- No, we pretty much walk down this hallway.
- You can fuck around.
- I try and jump and crash the hallway, just joking.
- Okay.
- I just try the entire hallway.
- That was funny though.
And you're opened up to a full on operation center.
There's no vanity tech here like in the command center.
Everything is serving a purpose.
Light grays, the dominant color.
The room is wide and not that long.
Not huge, but big enough that workers can muscle through,
carrying large pieces of equipment
and fasten them to some machinery.
You see this from a top, a wide staircase,
leading from where you entered.
There's the initial landing after the first flight
that holds two offices on either side.
So imagine like a staircase, little landing, two offices,
and then another staircase, another flight.
Those offices have two plexiglass offices
on either side, right?
And one sits a couple of lab workers and a crew member
manipulating a holographic model, delegating tasks.
And the other office has just a sole technician
working at his terminal.
And then that other landing, so you hit that landing,
and then there's the other landing
where you'll see the lieutenant awaiting you,
Lieutenant Michael Quinn,
who comes up the stairs quickly to greet you both.
Commander Superior, let's get Michael Quinn.
- He's already on.
- Fair enough.
(laughing)
- How'd you get him to stand on his hind legs?
Hey, Patches, that's how you stand in real life.
All right.
- Hold on.
- So, Michael Quinn, go ahead.
- Sorry, I'm just getting another guy.
- All right, you need this guy and this guy, okay.
Commander Superior told me you'd be coming this way.
I'll bring you right to Dr. Ebenezer.
We've stressed the urgency of the situation,
so he will make time for you both.
Right this way.
And you walk through the station,
you see crew members toiling away with a hurried energy,
but there's nothing frantic about it.
You get the sense that this place is always like this.
Never a dull moment, keeping the pleasure palace afloat.
- I accidentally tripped somebody.
- You do?
- Come on, what is it, Ed?
- It was on purpose.
- Okay.
- You can do it.
- Okay, don't give me that look.
you know me i like a little old a couple you really do we're so fucking in love
let me tax it and i'm gonna actually trip somebody is okay with you that to go
through every time actually trip somebody in your lab i don't know what
you're right in used to write i'm sorry
i'm really just because we
no no there's been a lot of we don't even have to finish talking
yet because i think it's so sorry and you're so correct
you look at it and i get this is a very description have the episode by promise
it's building things up
and tearing them down
Seven okay, you do not trip that whoever that
Yeah, right
Stick your foot out
Like you just see like the it's like you the camera goes down you just see your foot and your other foot going over it
And it just doesn't make any sense
So just to give you guys a little bit more background the guts of the station this contains and
Pat you're kind of in the guts also now through the layer guts - we're in them guts at the same time
Yeah, I would not do that with you guys know the station's plumbing. It's where the prisoners only do it three ways in
electricity general piping they do
Movement of goods gas we got a run
Is that what you're saying?
whole matter of functionality
It allows a ship to run
Or a station to run and provide the whole city in the amusement park with whatever it really needs on the power basis, right?
There are two entrances to the guts you guys are in one of them you are in the other one
It's sort of a not sanctioned and ship entrance. There's another entrance in the downer district. This is like the under city entrance
It's kind of a makeshift one
And each containing full management teams of the ship operations headed by an elite member of Leo's guard along with the station engineer
The crew for each team is usually a combination of leprechaun trip ship crew member and then depending on the size of the team there
maybe middle managers, filled out again by crew members.
What did he write?
He wrote something.
- I'm just imagining some stuff.
- Are you making fun of the teacher again?
- No, he wrote Caleb Doran, Caleb Michael Doran,
Patrick Edward Fitz.
(laughing)
- I'm just imagining stuff.
I'm just imagining, I'm just letting my imagination go free.
I feel like that's in the spirit of Dungeons and Dragons.
It definitely is.
Patrick Caleb Fetter.
What if we all combined our names and we all had the same name?
Caleb.
So most of the operations are not handled in the command center.
Or even the station operations corridor.
It's managed here, in places like this, and further in.
There are three Tesseract cores situated at the two ends.
Wait, so I'm like on the opposite wall of them right now?
You're basically on the opposite side of the whole ship.
How? Oh, the opposite side of the ship.
Yeah. Never mind. I thought we were in the same room.
You're on like the opposite side.
The three Tesseract cores are each inaccessible except for all those with maximum security access.
You guys can't get to the cores.
The cores are responsible for powering the majority of the functions of the ship
and share between them enough redundancies that if two go down,
and one will be enough to keep everything running
if at a lower capacity.
The entrance of the guts,
you can see the core below you, actually.
You're kind of walking on this kind of glass.
- That's kind of cool.
- It has its own force field around it from there, too.
- Aquafina fetter, Hart.
Come on, bro.
Can we just stop bright and stuff?
- But yeah, so you also notice that most of the higher ups
and non-leprechauns are wearing
distinctive face masks down here.
You're not noticing that, Pat.
You, where you are in the lair,
actually has a decent air quality.
Where you guys are--
- I'm just doing this.
- You guys have actually bad air quality.
The electric--
- Uh-oh, that means something's gonna go through the vents.
- The electrolytic cycles are not enough
to keep the station full of oxygen,
especially with the more advanced kinds
of luxurious terraforming that goes on
in the Royal District and New Gunn City.
So technoslime, as it often does,
gets involved and supplements, right?
It sort of supercharges the oxygen
generated from electrolysis, electrolysis rather,
and causes the usual effects of technoslime
with addiction, occasional mutations, psychosis, et cetera.
So people who have gas masks who work in the guts,
if they're of a high enough station,
and other people have to kind of fend off
a potential mutation and addiction issues
that come with just basically a flawed process
of regenerating the energy.
And this is partially because they're making sure
all the tourist areas and residential areas of the ship
and Royal District has the purest, best possible air.
- Wait, you're telling me that this polished surface
might not be quite what it seems on the underbelly.
- You know what?
I don't know if you've ever heard of noir, but oh yeah.
- I hate that.
- Isn't that crazy though?
Fucking disturbing, but yeah, I was reflective of reality
It's actually all I mean things are fine, so it's oh yeah wait. It's all made up
But yeah, so that's the guts situation we'll bring you guys to Ebenezer Keish in a second
Let's go back to you because you're gonna meet your person now. See this one. This is very like yes really
It's just like Quentin Tarantino
Mini Mouse Fetter
- All right, put that on camera.
- Look at my drawing.
(laughing)
- That's me at my wedding in the future.
- Does that, you think that looks like Hitler?
Wait here, I'll show everybody.
I didn't, by the way, I did not put a heart over Hitler,
I just drew a little stick figurine.
- You drew a heart next to Hitler.
- No, that one says, "Caleb was Patrick,"
and then that says, "All my new future names."
- Come on man, don't put Hitler on the Patch's cam.
- I'm seeing double.
- No. - No kidding.
- So you guys are, so you mean one.
- If I was really me, I'd say I'm seeing one and a half.
'Cause Patch is a half height.
- Hitler's tall. - Hitler's a lot taller.
- Did you just say he's half the man Hitler was?
(laughing)
Come on man.
- So you Patrick, you're going down the elevator
with Kenan Thompson and Baby Gadd.
And when he goes inside that elevator,
he traces his index finger along the sort of matte paneling.
You hear gear turning on the outside of the elevator.
And with some certainty,
you can feel yourself move sideways.
- Whoa. - Even though that was
surrounding the lobby.
- Like the Luxor.
- Charlie Chocolate Factory vibes.
- And then sideways, and then down for a little bit,
and then sideways again.
That garish yellow door opens,
and this time to a marvelous bedchamber,
resplendent with treats and toffees and...
- Treats and bed?
- So, and...
- I try to dive into the treats like Scrooge McDuck.
- You succeed, you jump into a table
that was holding some treats on it.
(laughing)
You just, the door opens and you just break a table.
Do you hold your breath?
- No.
- Where is it?
- I breathe so hard. - Where's Kenan?
- Which one was Kenan? - I don't remember who it was.
I don't think you gave him a person.
I don't think I did either go ahead and pick
This is Keenan, that's Keenan Thompson
This is my I mean this is a very wordy episode
You guys have to entertain yourself somehow the tongue out that she does oh I see always think she has three lips
She does do that a lot. So yeah, you, you, and it opens up. That's Kena Thompson right there.
That's what Pat just said. And you see little mini robots assistants dusting and brushing
and performing constant miniature. Nanobots? Basically, but they're kind of more like mini
robots. Nanobots are like mini robots. Yeah, they're smaller than this. Miniobots, little
- Those are little Mexican boy robots.
- I don't know what that is.
- Little Mexican boy robots.
- Yeah, they're all Mexican robots.
- And they wear glasses and they have a hood on.
- Nobody can see Jubio.
- And so, yeah, 'cause he's so little.
And so you're--
- They're called Jubitos.
- It might now-- - Jubio robots.
- Maybe I will call them that.
But along with assorted robots,
- The Jubidos are performing constant,
miniature, hygienic and organizational tasks.
Moving little things on the desk
and Nick backs around dusting on things.
- Oh my god, now we can voice the characters.
- And finally, sitting in a large armchair
is Ms. Janet Blowjob.
Expectant, but casually--
- She's expecting?
- No, expectant.
- Why did you FaceTime me then?
(laughing)
You're directing this.
- What does, you said she's expecting.
- Expectant. - No, expectant.
- I think you know he said expectant.
- Oh, hell no.
- No, she's pulling her pussy out.
- Okay, yeah, I got you.
She is not pregnant and she can't--
- Stop!
(laughing)
- That's not the right way.
- I just covered my eyes instinctually.
(laughing)
- So I don't wanna-- - Showed her fucking hoo-ha.
- I don't know who she is, I don't wanna--
- We're gonna face her towards me.
- Yeah. - Okay.
- Hello.
(laughing)
Hello Yoda, baby Gadd, it's good to see you both.
(gagging)
Oh.
- I hit my head when I jumped into the table
and it gave me a concussion.
- Oh yeah, let's get you to lie down.
And yeah, she puts you on her bed,
she gives you uppies and places you on the bed
and tucks you in a little bit.
Says how you feeling, you feeling okay?
You had a long day?
Hmm?
You have a long day or no?
Let's get on with this.
So what do you have to tell me?
I don't remember. I think you remember a little bit.
Oh yeah, I hit the play button on my phone.
Yeah, cool. And so you hear Gumby Superior
saying to the effect of, "I maybe want to destroy the Undercity, I maybe
trying to go to war with you, Jasfax."
(laughing)
And don't tear the hair off, head off the woman.
- Woman.
- Whatever.
- And she goes, "This is interesting."
And you see baby guy go, "See, look, look,
"they're always going after us."
You know, that's what I always been, she's sort of like--
- My phone can do other stuff too.
- And she kinda shushes him.
What does your phone do?
- Brick breaker.
- Let me see.
- Do you sell Flappy Bird on there?
- I have Flappy Bird too.
That must be worth a roll a persuasion check this is very good seduction technique
19 nope
She like it from this angle it looks like I don't think you have
Flappy bird maybe you have raised though, but the thing you pointed to is a 16 - Riz
- That is, that's a 300 year old term at this point.
- So is basically every word.
I just wanna put that out there.
- No, don't put that out there.
This is my fault then in that case.
- I like to put that in there.
- Come on, man.
- Please leave her alone.
- Why is your tongue blue?
- Nerds.
- Oh, yeah.
- We had nerds earlier.
- Nerds.
(laughing)
- Nerds party.
- She says, this is, I mean, besides your phone is weird,
but this could very well be used to our advantage.
Of course, there'd be something in it for both of you.
- I have the settings app.
- For Gadd, we can make you into a factoid immediately.
No question.
Plus you'd certainly have the most esteemed favor,
Mr. Fax, for you and your friends, Mr. Yoda.
How would you feel,
well, unless you want to become a part of our organization,
which I don't think you do,
I can only guarantee perhaps some financial gain
via tokens. - Oh, I'm looking
for my nephew.
- You're looking for your nephew?
- Yeah. - Oh.
Who's your nephew? - Sullivan.
- Sullivan. - He's like a penguin.
- What happened to your nephew?
- Some shit.
We turned the light off, or the light turned off,
and then-- - Oh, was he the one
kidnapped by Playtime? - Yeah.
- I heard about a child-- - Do you know
- I don't know anything about him.
- Can you tell me the answers to every question I have?
- I can give you answers that I know,
but I can't give you, you know, answers.
- Okay.
- Okay? Is that all right with you?
- All right.
(laughing)
- You seem upset.
- Kinda wanted to find my nephew,
I guess I'll do this other bullshit.
- Well, look, I don't know anything about your nephew,
but I imagine--
- He was handsome.
- I'm sure he's very handsome, but Mr.--
He used to say oh yeah. He would go oh yeah. Okay that sounds fun. He played the
trombone and band in school. Did he? He was in a school many times. And then you said in the college. Did he play trombone in college?
In a ska band. He was a trombone ska player. Okay. Yep. That's perfect for him. I'm sure he was great. He was not good.
Very expensive instrument.
All personality.
Same price as getting into hockey.
He would call home and ask for us to buy him ties.
Checkered ties.
Checkered ties, yeah.
Yeah.
Really?
That cost stack up after a while.
He would play the impression that I get, but he would try to play the lyrics.
He would try to play the vocals.
He was like, "Oh, he's doing the vocal line with the song."
Yeah, yeah.
That's pretty, that's not a great instinct.
He would say some shit.
He would be like, "Yeah, I really like Bomb the Music Industry, but actually the band they
were in before, Arrogant Sons of Bitches, was way better."
- There's no way he would say that.
- I would be like, what are you talking about?
He said that sentence like one--
- Really? - Yeah.
- He only ever said, oh yeah and okay.
- To you, yeah.
- Yeah, to you.
- 'Cause he has the motherly thing.
- He's a mom.
- We talk about Scott a lot.
- I just didn't know nothing about Scott.
(laughing)
- Scott.
- Mr. Facts might be able to share with you
if you want to assist us in this potential war
with one of his most special facts.
The facts that only Mr. Hugo, Hugh Jazz Facts knows.
- Okay, can I record it on my phone
so that I can remember it later?
- No, no.
- 'Cause what if I forget it?
I feel like that's pretty important
for me to remember all of it.
- He never gives anybody--
- I have adult ADHD.
And I need to record every lecture that I get.
- Very seriously in the future.
- I need to record every lecture that I get on my phone
so that I remember it later.
- Okay, well--
- 'Cause if you say something like,
like, I don't know, like,
Okay, huge-ass facts. What's a fact I know?
The Super Nintendo was originally
Going to have a DVD drive. Was it really? And then it became that that thing became the PlayStation
Really?
That's a fact I know. I don't think that's true. See, I don't remember what the beginning of this conversation was about
I gotta record the whole thing. Well lucky lucky for you. This is all recorded. Well lucky for you
I've been recording the whole time
No, I had your phone. There's no way you were required. I thought I could trick you
Look what I'm saying is we can compensate you financially much more quickly than you would even expect and
Give you some information that very few people have that could maybe help you on your search for your nephew
Well, why don't you just say that?
Why did you distract me? You would distract yourself all the time constantly. This is me talking about
(laughing)
- So, why don't you rest here for the night?
We have guest beds.
- Or do you have a big hotel I could go to?
- I mean, we have guest rooms here, they'll be in this--
- Do they have video games?
- They do have video games, yes.
- Then I will go to the guest room.
- Okay, cool.
We need a guest room, 'cause we are, it is nighttime,
and you'll meet with Mr. Hugeassfacts in the morning.
You two are back to where you are.
You're being brought to you know who.
- Get this hoe out of my face.
- A combination of people.
- We're being brought to them?
Okay, Roblox Joe.
- Joe?
- Jane Ice Cream.
- Jane Ice Cream, is that her name?
- I don't know.
- Jane Ice Cream is gonna be Ebeneezer Scrooge.
- Okay.
- Ebenezer.
- Ebenezer Kish, you mean.
- Sorry, Ebenezer Kish, yes.
And that is going to be Ebenezer Kish's assistant.
- Why do they do this when we walk in?
- What?
- Why are they doing this when we walk in?
(laughing)
What the hell are they doing with each other
when we walk in?
- Praying to Mecca.
- They're facing an opposite direction.
- Mecca's right between them.
- Oh yeah.
- You see the assistant, the assistant is a
red haired young man who's clacking away on a keyboard.
He sees you guys walk in he goes
Mr. Kish, Mr. Kish and like like goes over to you goes over to mr. Keating. Wow. Wow. What are you on?
We have the visitors here and mr. Kish comes over. Dr. Kish really Toby Kish
And he says he says, uh, oh
You must be the ones who brought me the snake
Yeah
Well, I I thank you for it's a very interesting finding and here come come come into my lab
We'll just you clean the snake before you did any tests on it. Did you did they clean it in between when did you guys do?
a taste test
Do we do we clean the snake we clean the snake ready?
Yes, we did. We clean the snake. I actually in the snake with what?
What I'm with without cleaning tools
Okay, all right. Just make it sure I don't want any of my spunk lying around creating a baby with one of you ugly mugs
I'm pretty I am pretty paranoid about some ho bottling my fucking
Get out of the toilet and trying to turn up trying to turn me into a money machine bitch. You ain't getting my money
That's why when I jack off at a public toilet
I put it out of order sign on the door when I'm done and after I'm done with the condom I poop in it
Uh-huh, I assure you we we you're gonna have if we're gonna have a baby together. It's gonna be fucked
Definitely took your spunk out and sent it off into space space. Oh, that's where all the bitches are
What's after it was processed and reprocessed not just raw processed it's a raw spunk the raw spunk
You're gonna give my bro a baby mama
Dr. Keesh Huxtable.
Okay, sorry.
So you cleaned the jizz out of it.
And now, Dr. Keesh goes over and starts, um, um,
looks at the snake and says,
"Now I see why
people would think this is, um,
who is this? I can see why this would
escape the notice of the blue gopher.
He's a talented
I'm not a phenomenologist and forensics expert,
but this is just multi-processed techno-slime, really,
the synthetic material here.
This kind of thing, Lateralis and I would make
when designing armor for--
- This thing's made out of techno-slime?
- Well, at least the mouth and the--
- The goodies.
- Yes, I mean, that's from what I can observe here.
The pleasure receptors are just,
I mean, there might be something else there
besides techno-slime, but--
- It's run-of-the-mill?
- I mean, my estimation, yes.
It's a mid
Well, not me. Do you mean okay?
It's made
Likely an anomaly right it's it's it's a chemical reaction as far as the snake is concerned
perhaps a snake folk
Worker had an unhappy accident. He folked a snake happy accident someone could have much of an accident
I doubt somebody engineered this thing deliberately. There's there's lots of power being generated in the guts these types of things
Happen, I just wouldn't pay it any more mind is oh he didn't pay it nothing
I'll make sure that we're more mindful of this in the guts, but um, and you guys need a spunk shredder. I'm serious
No, we like I know that one of your
trifling yep lab assistants
shove that upper
Yep, well I will worry about that and you you won't have to but you know
This is just really an anomaly and we're going to look into it
But I thank you for your visits and your Intel, but um, that's really all that this is. Thank you
Wait, that was it. Okay, so no fucking reward
I'm ready. You can take that up with Belinda. I suppose I think we'll just take you. Yeah, come on
shoulders come here come on you're trying to abduct him yeah come on okay roll a
straight roll a riz check are you both doing it then 20 20 really yeah yeah you
just fling him over your shoulder yep I know I put me down put me down I can't I
got a perfect roll you're coming with me okay you start to walk out yep the
assistant is like freaking out like mr. Keish mr. Keish and then you
If you don't do anything, I will let you have a baby with my stuff.
Please, please put me down!
You see, some of the guards now, some of the royal guards are to assemble.
Around you guys. Guards, assemble!
I'm showing my detective ID, I'm showing that I'm on the job.
Pay him no mind, he just had a psychotic break.
Because of how... He needs to be, we need to run some tests on him.
we need to take him to the blue gopher don't worry about him and we're the
homer brothers
*laughter*
fine whatever i fucking throw him across the room
fuck you
ok yeah
but that was a pretty badass roll
alright where should we go now?
so this guy didn't give us anything
he was completely useless
no that was nothing
i didn't even get him out of it
and i'm not even certain that i'm not having a baby
baby in the near future yeah the assistant kind of walks up to you guys
now I'm ready and he says his name is ready mm-hmm look um if you really want
to know more I suggest you move further into the guts it's dangerous but I know
something is up I don't know if Ebeneezer wants to hide something and
He's afraid of the work he's been doing, but it's way too weird.
I'll turn a blind eye.
How about you just come show us?
Okay.
I will.
Okay, I'm going to try to pick you up.
What is that?
Sixteen.
He's going to roll to resist.
I have a d20.
Yeah.
I don't have one.
You have one, but you put it behind your computer.
I did.
Well, he got an 18.
Damn.
What's your strength?
- My strength is three. - He's three.
- No, he's still-- - That's a 19.
- Yeah, so he's-- - No, that was the other time.
- He still has more. - Okay.
All right, so he can just come with us then.
Don't worry about picking up.
- So he leads you to, further along towards the back,
you see like, Ebenezer Kiesha's kind of like,
he's focused on his work, he's not even noticing you guys
at this point, you're walking by.
Quinn is kind of watching a little bit more suspiciously
after you guys picked up the scientist.
and he leads you to a panel and he presses on the key code
and he goes, "Okay, let's go in here."
And he starts moving you further into the guts,
sort of ushering you guys along.
Don't make it, but they're gonna hear you, man.
And, nice.
- Nerd, said roll it dice. - Nice.
And roll perception. - Exquisite.
- Me too. - Both of us?
- Both of you guys. - Both of us?
both of all of us. 19. Okay. Dude, my rolls are insane today. 18. Oh my god, we're
fucking on fire. Okay. You both hear the assistant start to step out of the
doorway. Like he's locking us in there? I don't know. Okay, honestly. Bang! Bang, bang,
bang, bang, bang! No, no, I mean, personally, I don't give a fuck. So I will keep you.
- Well, okay, wait, no, now you see me, what's the movie?
- With the magicians?
- The cards?
- Yeah, now you see me.
- Now you see me too.
I'm throwing, I have a card.
(laughing)
- Hey man, I was wondering where this was going.
- And I throw it behind me,
and I throw it into the part where the door goes in.
So we can't close.
- You do not have a card.
- I have paper, though, or something.
I have enough things in my inventory that I can have a card.
- You could throw--
look within your inventory it's okay i feel my lead pipe
not okay let me read on my inventory let me see if there's anything that could be
useful to us read out what's written down to a patches written
uh... so it's a thousand credits that's not useful
bridge gun uh... lead pipe no technoslaves refills no
and i'm seeing less than here says
video patrick and caleb having sex
that
yeah i'm waiting and that's a saying handwriting
when did you know when did that put on their house from the first campaign
so i guess i've had the he's had a very good it's a little bit like a little bit
about this book that has a has a debate is state
uh... no i think it was like a dvd okay so you're right in person or not a card
yeah yeah that that would be a for the third one they should throw a dvd or a
great now you dvd
now you've got a little and the three of them already through all raised attack
okay is it as is it a grinch gonna tech basically
uh... be in terms of role
bonus
uh... and or they're not going to be not really do you know i think you're
proficient in throwing okay so what i had that is that your tax but don't
manager of the
that is a fourteen
uh... that is not gonna be enough to like
cost up a door from quote and again i'm not doing anything but you have to get
i don't care okay
the door then they can that dvd go through the door and is limited to
pocket does
you get it
you know he's like what and they like
presses a button, the door shuts,
turns into a chute, and you hear,
(imitates door opening)
- Oh my god.
- And then, so it turns into a chute,
but we just stay floating.
- And you slide down. - Oh shit.
- Star Wars vibes. - Bloody hell.
- So you're going, they're going to--
(screaming)
You're going into Playtime's rank rocket.
We went back up.
And then you land on a pile of discarded toys and creatures.
- Wait, wait, that laugh was Playtime's laugh.
I just got that.
So that means that that motherfucker was Playtime.
Or somebody was, somebody is him.
Somebody's him.
- Somebody is him. - Somebody is him.
- I still think it's somebody.
- So we're on a thing of--
Okay, wait, can I roll an investigation?
- So I'll tell you where you are.
You're on this ground floor where there's like,
It's like a, you see a bit of light
kind of coming up from the chute.
- Yeah, he just said you landed on a pile of discarded toys.
- Of discarded toys, but not just discarded toys.
- You're in his rancor pit.
- Kinda. - Sorry, sorry,
are you in the pit?
Because I don't think you are.
- There's discarded toys, there's bits of...
- Detritus.
- Don't you, don't you tell it to me.
- Bits of like discarded...
- Debris.
- Animal parts.
- Animal?
- Creatures parts.
we take creatures sentient
creatures from the future creatures
and will partake in the creek
for the only way to get out of the house
it's a good idea to put the credit
the
crazy
i wasn't even gonna say that i need your deed did that to me
he's done so so
listen
- What do we-- - Creature discarded?
- Animal parts and creature parts.
(laughing)
- Discarded?
Okay, so there's animal parts and creature parts.
(laughing)
And they've been discarded.
- When you say parts, do you mean heads and tails?
- Yeah. - Oh.
- And flesh. - Like hunters,
like does it look like they used all parts,
not all parts of the animal?
- It looks like-- - Awful OFF.
- So some of them, yeah, some of them are
partially grafted. So it looked similar to the snake or the moth.
Oh, okay. Like they were trying... Oh, well he was saying that he made the snake, basically.
He was denying it.
Yeah. I'm kind of thinking it's the assistant and not...
Yeah. Or maybe they're in cahoots already.
Can I do an investigation on the toys to see if they have any of my son's blood on them?
Yeah, definitely.
Or any of my spots on them.
You know your son's blood I
Used to taste it okay to see if you said your computer
11 wait, but what's my I think you have a very high investigation. That's a 20. Holy shit. You've a very high
You
Some of the shit down here, and it doesn't taste anything like new solvents blood what does it taste like
tastes like
Plastic and a bit of iron like blood
But not like your son's blood tastes like all kind. Yeah, it's so good - are we doing Homer Brothers?
Yeah, I'm looking a pencil that has an eye an animal eye or a creature
I read it like the never soft logo and I'm looking at like a pops. Yeah, and as you're
Investigating the trident so the tritis and creature parts of this. Yeah
makeshift rancor layer
Both of you roll perception again. This is gonna be easy
To get a 20. This is another net 20 for me. It's coming
That's a one. No, that's a four mine plus three
19 okay seven my 19
Okay, blow toss you hear just a faint like rush of wind and then you see the origin of it
And it's a fart you're not holding your mic, and it's a long. It's a
Fucked up looking tentacle you do not hear this you roll dexterity saving throw you're gonna get hit in the fucking face
Didn't need to cuss, but sorry buddy
I'm fired up
Which
Save us at the top mm-hmm. That's an 18, okay
You managed to duck out of the way to just like whips by him and wax you in the face and you take
You take...
*dice roll*
Okay, that's not so bad.
You take six damage.
Okay.
As you get whacked in the face, off to the side.
I'm at twenty-one.
And, what comes into view from the dark, is a just, one of the worst looking fuckin' squid monster things you've ever seen.
It has like a thousand vagina-like holes on its body.
Oh yeah.
I fuck it.
No.
I'm just kidding, I got hurt.
time we will roll for initiative you're gonna tease us like that with a thousand
with a thousand fucking hot ripplers Patrick it's the path Patrick Yoda is
playing video games where do we leave showing in the guest room bubblers I'm
playing I'm playing a game like spore uh-huh for humans and I made this guy
you made a guy who has a head and an upside-down body yeah yeah that is
pretty cool actually and so yeah next time we'll we'll do that fight for you
guys and we'll have you meet huge ass facts.
[Music]