Last time on Gun City Abroad City, Playtime continue fun.
You boys began your dogged search of the space station for playtime.
Investigating the corpses that lay at your feet from their most recent murder,
you discovered that the toys Playtime lodged into their neck wound were strangely strange.
Missing letters, and the book, and having melty faces on the toy.
The toy looked weird.
unfinished imperfect creations. You brought these things to the crime lab
where the crime lab expert Blue Gopher suggested that these toys could
potentially have
been come from the under city. The part of the space station that exists beneath
the lower half and the part of the downer district.
Where the fuck was I?
Since there was no way to trace them on their product history
So that's why you knew that it was probably from the Undercity.
There's no way that... It seemed like they came from nowhere, the toys.
After getting that info, you made your way to the Undercity the way that God intended, through space,
which Patrick Yoda thought was gay.
Um...
That was funny. That was the biggest laugh he ever took at me.
I forgot about that.
It was just him calling me gay.
Fucking gay!
I asked him how it was.
Woo, that was funny.
Yeah.
After you arrived in the undercity, or rather right outside the undercity in the Downer District, you reviewed the case files and began to investigate your immediate surroundings.
This was where the first murder that Playtime had done took place. You learned there was only-
Oh, and we found out it was the Grinch.
There was only one confirmed witness. No, there's nothing like that.
But it was Grinch. It was heavily implied.
Grinchian.
It was a Grinchian crime.
If it's not the Grinch, by the way, if it's not the Grinch,
- Mm-hmm.
- Then we know that you had to change it
because our camera noticed.
- It's the Catch-22 then.
- It's Santa, the Grinch, or it's the Auntie Claus.
- I will show, I will date my notes.
- Okay.
- And I will show you that it was never the Grinch.
- You're gonna go back and date your notes now.
- No. - Yeah, he's gonna
date your notes. - Nope.
Nope, this is a draw.
- I will date your notes. - You will get an audit.
First of all. - 'Cause you're such a nerd,
you would date your notes.
- You got me.
Hold on. It is too easy.
This fucking guy.
Okay, yeah, so anyway, there was only one confirmed witness there.
The shopkeep, O'Neal.
By being amazing detectives and even better racists,
you quickly assessed that he was lying about his being human and having just human skin,
and discovered he was half leprechaun.
To keep you guys quiet, he told you some info on what he heard that night,
but begged that you wouldn't reveal his dark secret.
He told you that the metal against metal scraping sound that were heard by
witnesses at the murder that you were there and saw was also heard here in
this first murder up on the roof in one of Baby Gadd's properties. Baby Gadd, you
also learned, had moved from whatever he was doing in Bullet Town to go up here
to the Pleasure Palace. You guys got into the building and climbed the roof, dropped
a magnet down a small winding pipe that jutted from the top of the building and out came a
crazy snake. Patrick swung and connected his sandwich with the snake, or hoagie, but before
he could even roll for damage, the lights flickered, the space station once again powered down
for a frightful moment, and this time O'Neal was the one who was attacked. You heard a
a
It's the Grinch as a monkey.
It's the Christmas monkey.
It's Dunstan.
What kind of fucking reference is this evil man?
I'm gonna crack it.
I'm gonna do a hundred guesses a minute until I crack it.
Well but the thing is he's just gonna give you nothing once you get it.
Right?
Well just knowing that I knew it ahead of time is enough for me.
That would be enough for you.
Let me guess.
It's this fucker Ron DeSantis.
I hate that red bastard.
I have to go home.
Run to Santa.
Fuck me.
Fuck me, that's good, lad.
Go ahead.
Okay, cool.
All I was going to say is, much to investigate after you deal with this deadly snake.
So Patrick Yoda, you did in fact connect your hit against the snake.
I have.
the middle of the battle, by the way. I have my notes from that battle up here.
Oh, fuck. Here they are for me. So yeah, the initiative order was Patrick first, then it's
gonna be the snake, then Blowtoss, and then you, Ray William Johnson. Patrick, we just
need to roll for damage. You basically connected with the snake and then the light started
kind of flashing. I'm busy. I'm drawing you. Damn, that does look like me. That looks exactly
like me. That looks just like him. Roll for damage. Yeah, roll for damage. What, which
one do I roll with? You gotta take a look at your sheet. I'm busy with the sheet though.
I know.
Shit.
Here, hold on.
Try to get less busy.
Nice.
You flipped it over, though, for those listening.
Wow.
I'm impressed.
That was good.
You flipped over the piece of paper he was drawing on.
Oh, it's a D. So you used your hoagie in your attacks.
It was a hoagie.
No, it was just a hoagie, not hoagie surprise, right?
The hoagie surprise is the hoagie.
Okay, I thought that was a different thing.
No, I apologize.
I thought there was one where I throw it.
You have your hoverboard, but you can throw.
He's stalling and I have to read the number of dice.
He has...
To take the dice.
I'm just going to throw it.
I apologize
You have your hoverboard
To d8 which is like the two
D4 oh my apologies
So just roll
No
The 2d force of the the pyramids the pyramids are the d4s so you'd roll those two those pyramids twice
And then and then you would add four to that
- 2D4+4 that picked up the beast.
- Look man, it's a lot of numbers.
- It is a lot of numbers.
- Well it's two fours.
- Oh wow.
- It maxed hit.
- That's very good.
- Max win.
- That's 12 damage.
So yeah you--
- Did I get to roll again?
- No, it's not like Monopoly.
It is close to Monopoly but not quite.
No, you got it, that's fair.
Yeah no, you connected--
- It should be like Monopoly.
There should be--
- I agree.
Snake Eyes! Well Snake Eyes is basically a crit one but it should be first.
Anything to make it not like Wizards of the Coast. Nope.
Don't even, that's the worst thing I could have said. I shouldn't have said anything.
Yeah. But this is, I mean, so speaking of Snake Eyes though, hey this is a snake if you're facing it.
And as you connect with it, one of the things that you notice is that it has this like big hood on.
That's the snake by the way. This marker.
I'll move you back a bit.
Why are you bent over?
I don't know why he's bent over.
That's how my guy is.
What the fuck are you doing?
So he's more like, that's not...
So, uh, but yeah, so it's, it's, again, I think I said it last time, 15 feet long, it's kind of plasticky and metallic,
and it's also, it has like a hood, like a cobra, right?
You can see some of these like plastic ridges.
They're multi-colored.
It's hissing and yelling.
It's yelling?
Wait, what's it yelling?
(Snake screeching)
Hey! Hey you!
Hey, do a different sound. That does not match
the way you look.
Hey! Hey you!
Leave me alone.
Well, that's what he's saying now because he's got a sandwich
his face 12 damage. Oh that sounds awful. He does not sound good. I would hate to have
that. Yep. So um. That looks like a sandwich doug. I think everyone, I think that looks
like it. You can't even see it on the camera. You should hold it up and let the folks at
home vote. Yeah. Does that look like it? Cut to the Patrick scam. Can we get him side by
by side. How's your face? Can I see the face? I gave you a lot more hair. I was joking.
I look like a bitch. This page is a giant blank square and you're like I need to draw
on the back of this. That's my notes. I'm sure you're going to fill that one up. I will.
this
so
this was going to be it
watch
we just keep this snake is now going to go
so uh... he's going to try to grapple
you pat since you just hit him in the face
with
bit off your balance, and so he's able to whip around really quickly and wrap around you
and you feel the sort of like combination of flesh and plastic and metal like starting
to constrict you for an initial 17 damage.
Wow you're headed to damaged city, population 17.
I can't roll again right?
No.
Oh what again?
Well, can I use a special ability?
Um, look at your rea- so here's the way you could do it.
I have Peace for Yoda, Peace for all.
Well what are your reactions?
So go over there, I have reactions for you for exactly this kind of thing.
I'm gonna say attack melee, if melee enemy moves.
So you have an opportunity attack if they move within range of you.
How many years have we been playing this game with specifically this- these characters?
Three years.
These sheets.
Not even like how-
Almost three years.
Yeah, right?
Specifically always the same.
Also it's obvious that you took a bite out of that champ's neck.
It's got T marks on it.
You did it.
Stop playing with it.
Please play the game.
Don't listen to Cameron, he's being mean.
Play the game.
You're so good at DnD, you're the best.
This is the one that just melted in my pants.
That's the one that I bit.
Oh, this was my snacking one.
Yeah, it melted in my pants.
It melted in my mouth.
It's so delicious.
Okay, he wants to react.
So what are your reactions?
Deflect a non-magic missile roll ranged attack.
So you can deflect ranged attacks with your hoagie
because it's kind of like a lightsaber for you.
But this is a melee attack.
So you have no reactions to this.
to this so this just kind of happens.
Okay.
But, um, I mean, so you take 17 damage
and the snake does constrict around you, so
there might be some lingering effects from there.
But Blotoss, first, it's your turn.
Okay, has the snake acted already?
Yeah, the snake has acted, and he's wrapped around
the Grogu. Can we just get the Grogu and the snake
just near each other?
Yeah, we should have got a piece of string.
I know, I couldn't find it.
here
so yeah like that
turned around right away
are able to have wrapped around
okay i'm gonna go up
and i'm gonna start getting i want this nato like open so i'm gonna start
getting it with my
and
I can feel it like a big wave.
Meanwhile, we're playing D&D more like an elf-fulfilling prophecy.
And prophecy with a higher emphasis on prophecy due to the fantasy themes of the game.
Yes, that's so good.
Damn. Let's see how much damage you do now.
That's 7 damage.
For my first attack.
Yes, because you have 2 attacks.
Okay, that's not so good a roll.
That's a 13.
Okay, yeah, that does not hit.
Okay. I accidentally hit Patrick, but in a prank way. It doesn't do anything.
I will say I've tried to adjust the enemies a little bit more so that they hit harder but
they go down quicker.
The battle's moving.
So, yeah.
I don't game.
Me neither.
I just play pretend.
I read a lot of gamer forums to catch up on the lingo so if anyone speaks gamerese to
me I know what they're saying but I don't know the first thing.
Yeah, the first thing you think when you see this whole, all these playstations is that
we gotta be gamers.
Real gamers loud.
Hey, well why don't you play this game instead of the other ones?
I'm not a gamer.
All these places to get gamers.
(laughter)
Real gamers lounge.
Hey, well why don't you play this game?
Okay.
It's your turn.
Well, first things first, my character turns around to look at what's happening.
Second things second, I'm going to use my...
Fuck it, it's my grenade, it doesn't actually matter.
I will use...
Is there... do I have a clear shot?
Or do I need to get close range and try to fucking cut that snake like the devil himself?
So the way that you could, yeah, I mean I would say just cause he's wrapped around him completely.
The range of the grenade, if I'm correct, it's 10 foot radius I think, right?
But I have my matrix beam.
Oh I see what you're saying, if you can try to like...
If I roll low am I gonna fucking hit one of these?
Yeah I think that's how we can play this, is like, cause normally you can't cause they're
connected.
But I would say if you roll high enough, not only will you hit but you'll also be able to
kind of like slice around Patrick Ewen.
- All right.
- So the idea would be to kind of like get like this angle.
How's the sound?
- Yeah. Can I give a producer's note?
Can you tilt the mic a little towards your mouth
a little more and maybe just be a little closer to it?
- Okay. Yeah.
Sounds good to me.
- I think that you guys are about to see
the first natural 20.
- I'm ready to see it.
Do you want magic fingers to help?
- Give them to me.
Thank you so much, Patrick Ewen.
- Okay. And you.
- He doesn't hear the snake.
- That's true.
- You are the serpent.
of
in
the comments.
things happen at once. First, Patrick Yoda, roll a perception check. Add your perception.
So you guys remember that you heard O'Neal kind of bleeding out, you heard people kind
of hollering over there, you were kind of up on this building, he's not too far away.
Patrick Yoda, you kind of can tell based on just you have this ability with the foreskin
to heal people, that O'Neal might die if you don't do something to him.
We gotta escape the snake.
Oh wait, it's my turn again?
And go rescue O'Neil.
Maybe he's seen this.
Peace for Yoda, peace for all.
Grinch him!
Read for me, peace for Yoda, peace for all.
Once per recording session, Patrick can create a realm of calm
or create a realm of mental stability
instantly calming any conflict he's in for one minute.
All enemies are unable to make any aggressive actions
towards Yoda and his friends
for the duration
unless
Unless they beat Yoda's spell DC.
He's had this ability for a while, but I changed it to be once per recording session.
You meant it so much about him himself, but not even a character.
Yeah, pretty much.
I was just like, "Pat can do this.
This will be fun."
So yeah, you do this, okay?
What does it look like when you...
Basically you're using kind of a battle meditation.
Don't they have to beat his spell save?
They still have to beat his spell save, so they will...
Well, no, this, it just happens, I think, and then like...
What did I write?
I say it just happens, I mean he has the roll to beat it after the minute?
Or is it just...
It just says unless they beat it.
Oh, okay, so he does have to try to beat the spell save.
What is your spell save?
It should be in the middle of your sheet, next to your spell attack.
It's probably kind of small font.
It's next to the death saving throws.
There's two numbers.
The DC?
Yeah.
16.
Okay.
So let's see how the snake does.
The snake is decently wise, but not that wise.
Okay.
Decently wise.
Alright, that's my fault.
that's my fault first
cool
damn he did he does have a +2
oh that's bullshit
so he's had once per recording session
that's it that's all he can do it for
guys I think I'm tired I might want to wrap this up and start again
here's the thing
here's the thing you can still try to escape this fight
you also have a hoverboard
that you don't use for hoverboard purposes
I'm gonna use the hoverboard then.
First you're gonna have to get out, you were constricted by the snake right now.
Then that's, do I roll athletics?
This would be a strength check first.
Okay.
Against the snake's strength.
That one.
That's a natural one.
Unless the snake gets a natural one.
You really bricked that thing.
You got an 11, that's almost a one.
It didn't roll at all, he threw it straight up.
Yeah, that didn't roll.
You're saying we are on a one.
Where's the dice tower?
Oh yeah, where is the dice tower?
It doesn't matter because it was never on camera in the beginning.
Yeah, it was last episode.
You can't see the result though, right?
Yeah.
It's nothing.
Well, I'm sorry.
So you're struggling in here.
You can hear O'Neal is in trouble.
You guys, though, obviously have a chance to free--
I'm just going to tell this snake I'm going to kill myself.
How about that?
It's a wise snake.
You probably have emotional--
Wisdom.
You said he was wise.
Wisdom is like awareness and ability to make decisions.
Wisdom is not--
I have--
You didn't say wisdom stat.
You said he's wise.
I know his mind.
Wisdom is next to insight on here, so the snake would have enough insight to realize that
he's about to kill himself.
Animal insight, is this a different critter control?
I put the gun to my head.
I found a gun, look at my character, he has a gun in his hand.
I found a gun, and I put it to my head and I say, "I don't care if you kill me, I don't
have anything to live for anymore.
Snake! Snake let him go he's serious!
He's never done this before!
I mean he's eaten 30 ibuprofen before and sat in a bathtub
but he's never put a gun to his head.
Let him go!
And I found this gun, there's no serial number on it, I could pin this on you.
Yeah!
But it's actually, no, cause it's gotta be, I actually don't care what happens.
Is that what you want to be, a murderer?
Well, uh, is it persuasion or intimidation?
Intimidation I guess.
I guess. Yeah, right? Intimidation with disadvantages.
19 is the first one. Okay, whatever your plus is.
And it went in that way. Oh my god.
So I think that we could, you know what, don't even tell us.
We know what happens. Yeah, why don't you tell me what happens.
I kill myself. Immediately. The ultimate intimidation.
No, you tell me.
The snake cocks its head curiously at you.
Does it look cute when it does that?
It does a little bit. I can't believe I let this happen.
Just kidding. I always let this kind of shit happen.
And he looks at you, Patrick Yoda, and it starts to uncoil a little.
So you would be free to slip out at the top of your turn.
Okay.
But it's still like a hostile creature probably to all you guys.
This is kind of a brief moment where for some reason, something inside of this creature
recognized your desperation.
Maybe it's heart group resize.
And I just earned a new ability called suicide threat.
Yeah, add that to your list of abilities because I did just kind of make that a thing.
Okay, so the snake's not going to trick you.
It's going to skip its turn.
I'm going to let that.
Insanely good roll
Yeah, absolutely, yeah, yeah, you got a 20 you will you'll get her back if you do it
So we're now it's up. It's it's your turn blowtoss piss
I mean, I guess I'm gonna run now now that I I'm thinking about O'Neill's poor leprechaun body
half leprechaun half leprechaun which half
Well, the bottom we know the back had our pubes so maybe split vertically
But pubes a little of each bubes
Hmm. All right. So you run you're gonna run. Yeah, I think I'll run. Okay, cool. Yeah, you can run. Can I like grab?
Patrick Yoda and run
Yeah, I would you you can try I mean, like I said the snake is not like
It's like relaxing, but I'm not gonna say it's like fully like if you yank the guy from its clutches would it like
Snap back in mentally like things like that you'd have to consider
If that makes sense, okay, what do you think I should do?
I think you should kill the snake because now it's relaxed, and I think that you could probably just chop it. Yeah
Okay, you all made it this attack. We're not gonna go save O'Neill and find out there's a great. Well. I can't you just do it
you do I don't have healing you're the one who has healing that was what I
said it from across the map your foreskin how far is me over the corner
he's not he's a little bit more than I would say 60 feet away what you could do
probably is hmm let me think about this how would you get there well there are
there you I have the hoverboard have the hoverboard shoot the hoverboard up in
the air and then just fucking grab onto it. You could probably do a kind of a rooftop style Tony
Hawk activity. Subway surfers. Subway surfers. Subway surfers. And roll an athletics check to
bound across the buildings up top. Okay. I will let you guys skip your turn so we could just get
this to happen. Okay. I think that's what we should do. Oh you'll let me skip my turn? That's
really nice of you. As a tent. So you take this opportunity and you slip from the snakes clutches.
He's kind of outside the turn order I guess anyway
With that ten you're able to get on your hoverboard bound down one building
You kind of stumble a little bit and you're going to take
Damage already done to you
You're not gonna take much more you're gonna take five more damage as you kind of like stumble down the building and you kind of land
And skid yourself a little bit like you like the hoverboard kind of like doesn't quite get it's like bearings on the billy
It's like you have to kind of Center it
That's right really good Pat so you get down there and
You see O'Neill and he's bleeding out
It looks pretty bad. We're gonna go back to you. There's something on his neck
He has no it's just a like a
Half of like a line kind of clean across. Oh, it's just a line. That's not that dangerous the lineman
Well, it's a cut I mean like no lineman did it it's the snake from the game snake
Which is that's what that's Harold's magic crayon. It's Harold. It's Harold doesn't play time boys books
It's oh my god. It's Elmo
This always whenever I do a mystery anything it becomes a guessing cuz 20 questions or 20 guesses
You don't even ask me quite. What's the best one?
I got you so good. You got me so good with the Konami code one. I obviously never fucking forgot that.
Yeah, I felt very dumb after that. I probably got you like 20 times, right? You did with the teleporting ability
I gave you and I forgot to give it a cool down. I guess I did. I don't forget when I fuck up.
We're trying to draw the next one out of you.
Fucking failure of storytelling. Oh, yeah, absolutely. Yeah, right.
so badly. Well, you know, if I knock these out now, I won't deal with it later. So we'll go back to you
and healing O'Neal in a second. Let's go now to your turn up here with the snake. So yeah,
I mean, you have an opportunity to run if you want. The snake might chase you guys, you know,
like, but let Patrick go. It had the sympathy for him. Okay, and Patrick's on his way to go. He's
at O'Neal. He's basically going to be like, if you look at in terms of like how the turn order works
in
to bring him back to life. I want to defeat the snake. Okay, well I'm gonna stay and defeat
the snake too. So Patrick can just go handle that. I trust Patrick to go handle that. In
a highly sensitive situation. Yeah, absolutely. Alright, so I'm just gonna keep whaling on
this thing. Okay, that is an 18. Yeah, that hits. Okay. That is 15 damage. Damn, okay.
Yeah, you, so the snake like kinda like loosened up for a second and almost like, you almost
I
always forget to roll twice or do I double it double it roll twice I mean
you can roll you can oh yeah that's snake eyes yeah that should count for something
this snake in his eyes go ahead Wow that's pretty bad the other way we can
do it maybe we can do this next time would be more fun you can take the max
of like your boy double the plus damage and then add no you just count that one
Okay, I mean still describe your kill. Oh, I do this
He grabs the cable
Holding it and I'm great on it, and I'm rip it in half and then yeah, I'm gonna sit in half
What do you do after that? I just ripped it in half under the table
I didn't want to show cuz I don't like damaging property. Yeah, I'm ranked as a wow. Yeah, you're really is really unreal
It's pretty scary stuff. Yeah, you just
obliterated that snake. I did nothing. I turned around. That's the only thing I did.
Yeah, you turned around and missed. No, the snake was, snake hits hard but doesn't, didn't have a lot of HP.
Let's keep a, at least a representation of its corpse here. Okay. Because that is still.
That's just, can I give you a kudos right now? You're the perfect distance from the mic and you
should keep this distance. Right here? You're great. This is the one? I love you. I love you too.
Okay, Patrick Yoda.
Yeah, you're in front of O'Neal right now.
You can whip out your foreskin.
- Yeah, I do that.
- Yeah, okay, everyone at first is really worried
about the sort of thing you're bringing to this,
but then as you're--
- If you guys think this is weird, I'll kill myself.
- And it works again as you drape your foreskin
over this half leprechaun.
And he heals for, well, roll,
I believe it's 1d10+4 for your 4-skin.
You can read the ability actually.
Bless you.
1d10+4.
Do I roll?
Read the ability.
It should be on the other page, your spells page.
I keep forgetting that +4 is not another dice.
It's just adding a number.
I wish they let you roll dice in math class.
You got 1d10+4.
Nice.
Alright, do it up.
10.
Nice.
And you add 4.
14 yeah he is like like it's like magic as your how does your foreskin work I
don't know I think it's pretty soon I thought so too like it's sort of like
it's a white cape okay what of Yoda has a white penis yeah
His doesn't matter
Just a white really white tip. It's got that line, okay
So like when you take the sliders on like a like color correcting something in Photoshop
Then it like makes like one like when you're color correcting penis. Oh, yeah
It's like that's a place that has the least blood in his body. It's like what you're painting Yoda's penis white
It's like what it looks like after that. Oh, yeah
All right, so it's a lot. Okay now because before I was like, but it's like painting his penis white. Yeah
All right, yeah, it's amazing this white penis comes out and it heals this half, and it's not my
Anatomical penis excuse me. It's not my it's not my it's not the one on my body
Which way it's just a penis that I have
This is not the cannon the cannon is at your
Cock I don't remember that
There's always that you have like this sort of magical technicolor
Dream skin that you kind of like can throw out and cover the party. Yeah weights on the end, right?
There's literally like a strength check people have to take to like get out of it after he heals
Yeah, it's like like when you do the parachute game in class with a substitute. Oh, you're substituted
It's like you'd you paint Yoda's penis white and you drape it over your substitute teacher. Yeah
Yeah, so he's good I mean you guys can run down how much does he have I mean he's an NPC just a regular dude not
10 HP
Yeah, I have so much of something that's not energy. I can't explain what it is. Yeah, right
I mean you guys want to look at the snake or do you guys want to run down there?
I want to look at the snake. I feel like I'll bring this
Leave his corpse there. I'm not gonna I'm not gonna lie. All right. I'd like to investigate the snake. All right
So you can roll investigation. You are the computer
But you had a nine I think yeah, yeah, so 14. All right, cool
so
Looking at the snake that 14. It's pretty good. I will say there's you can't get like a
Ton of info you might want to bring it back to the crime lab
Just because you're on first glance you're not gonna get a ton of info
We need to bring this back to the crime lab, but what you can get from this is that it is definitely similar in
General composition and look to that monster that you saw that you fought earlier at the royal district
We need to run an analysis on this snake
I'm one step ahead of you. Yep
We need to bring him back to the lab. I'm going like I'm eating it like corn on the cob
Okay, yep. Yep. Yep. We need to are you actually eating wait?
He's part computer. Can't we just like make the crime the crime lab
We can put part of the lab can't you like he can connect to any of the lab computers and then get all of its
like info there is a cloud upgrade that he can get if he goes to the right shop
in the game oh and we skip the shot let's just go to all the shops right now
can we just go to every shop you guys want to stop stop it that's just like
drop everything and go shopping I would love I'll surf I'll surface some shops
okay I'll set a 10-minute timer and we'll go what shopping as we can in that
time okay I have a thousand credits you do have a thousand we get a thousand
every day tokens yeah oh so wait so how many games have we played of this no it's
every day in game so it's been the same day the whole year - man I was gonna say
at least I have like at least have two thousand now you just have one thousand
that's why the other way to get money is to do gigs or jobs maybe a little bit of
window shopping because I don't think a thousand grams is going to go very far.
I'm gonna come shopping with you and I'm just gonna be carrying I'm dragging the
snake over my shoulder. So Patrick, did you leave O'Neal or are you staying with him? I guess I'm
waiting for him. I'm watching him I'm watching him run the he's like it's like
a now everybody that was around him has formed like a circle and they're all
watching him breakdance because he has all the energy. Uh-huh. And they're going
Okay, oh, yeah, it's your birthday
yeah, and
Yeah, O'Neill is sort of like kind of a bit
He's spinning around his head, but he's also like trying to get his bearings here a bit
Outside of that. Yeah right now. He's just in a complete. He's just in the he's in b-boy heaven. Mm-hmm
and he
he talks about
He's I mean like yeah, I guess well actually you know what he's just spinning on his head
- Yeah, you guys can talk to him if you want to.
You guys wanna go shopping?
You wanna leave O'Neal here to spend his night?
- I'll let him work out his energy.
- His energy.
- And I'll go shopping.
- You guys wanna go shopping?
Alright, go shopping.
So, there is a shop in the Downer District
you can go to right now.
Okay, cool.
- I'm down.
- Is that the one with the cloud upgrade?
- Yes, it is.
You're in the Downer District,
so that would make sense to go there.
So let me pull up my shops list.
Item shops.
Item that's the only one item shop. You have a beautiful hand
Which hand the one that one? Oh, thank you. Look at his hand
Then Seinfeld
Not a hard he says about George's a day a manual labor in my life
It's I think it's I think
It's the way that you how you pick you held it up and you went like this
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I'm sorry.
- You're supposed to go like this.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
(grunting)
- I'm gonna, oh!
(sighing)
Yeah, I'm supposed to hiss.
- That's what boys do.
(laughing)
- Boys bring out the claws and hiss.
- Boys do this with their hands.
- Yeah. - Right?
- Do do do do.
- And girls are like.
- I mean, I don't care.
- Okay. - And boys are like this.
- Mm-hmm.
- Boys dance.
- So, at this shop,
this shop there are three Technoslime refills you can buy.
Or there's three, yeah, three Technoslime refills
that you can get like as a pack.
Each of those are 1,000 tokens.
There's cloud mode.
- Shit, that's all my damn money, bro.
- Right, and that's the thing,
is right now that's all you have.
Cloud mode, that is 8,000 tokens.
That's where you can, you would move--
- 8,000?
It would allow you to move your computer to the cloud,
which will have a number of benefits,
including connecting to things like the crime lab.
And it will also allow you to--
- Can we rob this bitch?
- Control, allow you the opportunity to control the--
- What's your slate of hands?
- World.
- No. - Okay.
- No, it'll allow you to control the demon
with more ease whilst you can be separate from the demon.
I cast my sleight of hand.
I can turn invisible.
You can turn invisible.
He's gonna go invisible.
We're planning a heist for this thing now.
This also has an upgrade for Blotoss's Grinch Gun.
Which gives it tracker mode.
So you can shoot an invisible painless dart at an enemy or a target.
It sticks into them and you'll be able to track their whereabouts for 24 hours.
How much?
It's 4000 tokens.
And then there's a Patrick Yoda upgrade as well.
as well here it's only 2,000 tokens it's a foreskin adjustment you'll now be able
to give up to two pieces of your foreskin to your friends to keep as
healing potions. Can we just sit in this store for eight days? No can I roll
you will starve. I'm gonna roll my sleight of hand to try to nab this. Why don't you let me
turn invisible because let me try this first. I mean so these are sort of like I
mean they're not just like on a shelf this isn't like a medieval item shop so
So they're like in these like, it's like a Zordon case.
- So it's like in a jar.
- They're like in a Zordon case.
- So I still like to try.
- Yeah.
- You still wanna try.
- So I'm just trying to, what are you, you gotta--
- I know.
- Just get up, slide a hand, like slowly approach it
and then punch through the glass.
- Silently.
Is there a shopkeeper or is this like fully AI?
- This is fully AI.
- Shit.
- Yeah.
This is like--
- So you're a fucking computer, get in there.
- You could try to hack it.
- Yeah.
I added a tech skill.
- No, I wanna use sleight of hand.
- You wanna use sleight of hand really badly?
- Yeah, I really do.
- Okay, cool.
Roll sleight of hand.
Let's see what happens.
- I just need my D20.
Where is this thing?
Wait, patches, what's behind your ear?
- Stop it.
- Oh my God.
- Whoa.
- Tell me--
- Sleight of hand.
- This one's gotta be a bonus, right?
- Yeah, he did a sleight of hand on you.
- 'Cause you didn't notice, I did a real life sleight of hand.
- It was actually very good.
- It was very, very cool.
And I was holding it the entire--
- He gets to roll with advantage?
basically what 10 that's a 10 let's take a look at my worst we'll add one because
that was very cool what you did you move in kind of slowly and then you just kind
of like rest your hand against the glass what's in your mouth oh my god
sorry put anything there is an infection in there and you just here please
Please deposit the correct amount of tokens before receiving the item.
I work here too!
And I have to inspect this because I'm also a robot.
Please state your model number.
One hundred and forty-
You're a demon.
Six six six.
Five.
Calculated.
Six six six.
Come on, give me a number.
Give me a number.
Ghost.
One.
Eight thousand eighty five.
Two.
I am a robot too and I am here to open the case.
I am a robot repairman.
Wait, this guy isn't a robot.
Get out of here.
He's not even here.
God, I'm not insane.
Listen, I work here, the boss is me.
Listen.
Okay, listen.
We all know that guy's lying, but I'm a real robot and that's how you know I'm reliable
I'm willing to call out your right here. I'm not even a robot. I'm a robot, right?
You could have gone down a terrible life of crime otherwise you both saved my life give this man a promotion
Would you like to be my manager yes
Okay, bye-bye.
I'm going to make a request to see if I can make you my manager. Okay, you just get back to me on that. Okay
It's gonna get back to you in eight days. Okay, I'll sit and wait. Yeah
No, I mean, yeah, it didn't work
I'm just open. I'm just trying to open the key. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I mean you're gonna start drawing attention to guards
Okay, I'd like to have their guards first it was all AI now there goes I mean there's
I'd like to throw my ninja star dongle USB cable into
Something
Okay, here I go
What?
How do you roll like that, what do you mean?
You've getting the worst roles. I'm honestly cursed like I think
This happened last campaign. It's respecting the die. My life is shit.
You're disrespecting it. You have to treat it well.
Maybe a little. Yeah.
See I got a five.
Overhand is a good way to roll. Okay let's see it.
What'd I get?
No no you knocked over your own piece though.
Oh is it this one? Yeah. Two.
Getting better.
This is some sort of incremental improvement.
This almost isn't D&D.
I don't have any money for this thing.
I don't have any money for this thing and I'm being too...
So the way you can get money again is by...
Ruining everything.
Well, not by ruining everything, but...
Can I sell him?
By doing jobs for Giancarlo.
That's a good idea.
By potentially...
There will be other opportunities to earn tokens.
I think that that is not worth...
It's not worth doing eight of those fucking jobs just to avoid going to the lab.
They wouldn't each be a bad...
Let's just go to the lab.
The lab.
Let's go to the lab.
Let's just go to the lab.
(laughing)
- Let's just go to the,
can we please just go to the lob?
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- And do an analysis, please.
- Cool, you can go to the lob and do an analysis.
- Patrick, are you still with,
you're still with the,
- I guess we just forgot Patrick.
(laughing)
- The, what's his name?
- Patrick, we're going to the lob.
(laughing)
Bye.
- You could call him.
- Pat goes to a place called the lob.
(laughing)
He wasn't around to hear the inside joke.
- I'm with,
Duncan? What was his name?
What? O'Neal.
O'Neal. Duncan O'Neal.
You see O'Neal comes up to you, Pat.
I'm with him at the lob.
Yeah, the lob, the club.
No, you're with him at his sort of kiosk area there.
And you see him, and he's kind of like holding his neck,
and he's like, "It didn't even feel like a knife.
It felt like a...
It just felt like just a worm opening up.
I don't know how to explain it."
and you see it was gone
and i think that's the as he's saying that mister teen
handling saying that that is that all you see a familiar face you patrick you
see one
some stuff around here let's get
you know you didn't have a figure last time
you don't get that man a figure
areas well
you get patrick you know in your history again right there
uh... head
uh... man
I spent 30 minutes making that.
You spent 30 minutes putting this on his head?
No, but sculpting it with super glue.
Well, it's still there.
And you hear this guy-- this guy kind of shows up,
and you would recognize him as Baby Gat.
Oh, his shirt says BG.
Oh, nice.
Or it says BC, maybe.
That's one big baby.
Yeah.
And he sort of like tells everyone, hey--
he's like, all right, move aside, move aside, move aside.
He walks up to O'Neal, falls over onto him.
He knocks him down and sucks him.
This baby gad fella really is a baby.
Look at his balance.
He basically says, "Alright O'Neal, that's enough.
Let's try to not talk too much about this."
and he turns to you, Patrick, and he goes,
"I haven't seen you in a while.
"What have you been up to?
"Thank you."
- I don't even care what I, I don't know.
(laughing)
Just fucking, my nephew's dead or something.
I'm stuck on this vibrator ship.
- So you're investigating, right?
I've heard some rumors.
- I think that's what I'm doing.
- Look, if you could,
Um...
*clears throat*
Can I keep this?
Uh...
I just post- I posted it on Weibo.
*laughs*
I literally just made a post about this-
Please remove it from Weibo, if you can.
Every single one of my...
100 followers saw it.
Okay, fine. Well, whatever.
I have 100 followers on Weibo and they're all Chinese.
If you can- *laughs*
Did you post it in English?
Yeah.
Okay, well...
If could you-
I guess- I guess, unless they're...
Familiar with the language. Yes. Yeah
Social media app that survived from the from back in the day. Yeah, it really is
Yeah, well, you know the resilient Chinese as they say well
Look, if you could just sort of consider O'Neill and this whole thing your under your jurisdiction
You know, he's under my foreskin right now. I see that and he's bees
He's he's getting a little comfortable in there, which is a little weird to see but if you could just you know
I'm saying though right keep this out of the guards hands. This is why
It's a very good question
Do you want me to explain explain?
Well, we have a way that things run down here in the under city and we just don't want any trouble underwear I
Thought we were done with this motherfucking bofa
my bad continue so
Look let's let's put this way I can I can give you some information I can give you
Information can help you guys out with the investigator
I'm not gonna just I'm not just trying to get the
One word yeah, yeah anger angry
look I'm not gonna just give you look right
hey why you take it out your penis again what is this ride
stop put your penis away stop it reverse bride okay thank you look just if you
can meet me and my tavern meet set okay well that's good we have to walk there
where you - fuckers you always hang out walk and dialogue nothing comes of it
he's just standing there in his idle animation
yeah you got you see it your hide you see like a little exclamation point like
follow up with baby I don't remember any of this conversation. What did we talk about?
Oh man okay cool so you were the perfect person to handle that. So you guys are now are you guys
heading back to the lob then? We're headed to the lob to do it. Okay cool. I think I am going to go
with baby gad to figure out what's going on. Okay cool so we can circle back on that. You guys are
going to take the so actually how are you guys can get to the lob? You guys can go to whacking
to you take the city lou or you guys can go into space before if you want to uh...
which is faster is that the local will be faster and i'll say yeah i'm gonna
carry a big this is a fifty-foot stake on the trip to get back to the
and i think i have to have a blood the
justinian newt
uh... traffic signs on the sidewalks were doing a little you people sit on the
left of this line you see the red line in the middle of the sidewalk and to
to read like it always is a little bit
and the jury and i i i i get back to the world district as you get there
uh... you see a a solvent like walking out of the world is to use a car
the okay
yeah
to the world
i don't know where this is the
the
well i don't know what i got the past i got this great what turned out of the
guys told me to get the past
what that
all that's the wrong path yet but i think that
thirty scared me for a while
but i have a ticket is that the law
dot com for all of it
where's the uh... it's a big it's a big nope
i think it's or criticism the ages of the
is a trapped under the snake
okay dot
do you get the same copies are no good a better past where you're going to get
which the snake yeah
to where? I can't move, it's crushing me. Nope, nope. Take that snake, it's on you. Take it
to the lob. Where's the lob? The crime lob! Are you an idiot? The crime lob! Do you mean
a... Okay, yeah, definitely. Yes, okay. Wait, can we get the guys who are in this scene
on the screen? I'm gonna find a smoothie. What? There's gotta be a smoothie somewhere
on this ship right? Yeah I mean you could probably go to the mess hall. Is this how we're standing
now? Yes, Peppa Pig or me, my snout is directly in his ass. And uh, yeah and I got knocked
over. Okay, you know what, you're clearly too weak so here's what you have to do now.
Because you've demonstrated that you are useless to us, you have to go to the gym and get strong.
That is your new prime directive.
Okay you got it.
I'm going to be really strong next time you guys see me.
Oh yeah, you definitely will.
Okay bye.
That bought us a little more time.
Let's hit the lob.
Okay cool.
Lob time.
You guys this is the crime lob.
I don't remember the exact layout.
But let's add some blocks back in here.
Yeah it was something like this.
I remember saying it was something along the lines of this.
We got the blue gopher's back.
I love that blip.
Yeah, he's working, he's like, "I've been doing some rearranging, what do you think?"
Snake.
Holy sh...
I can't curse.
Lob.
Wow.
That is crap.
Oh, Lob Master, analyze my snake.
That is a...
Well, it looks just like the monster.
Hold on.
The monster?
I'm glad we took it to the lob.
Me too.
Yeah, analysis over.
- This forensic genius can handle chemistry.
- He picks up the snake very easily somehow
and dumps it into his snake analyzing machine.
It's over there.
- Nope.
I make the noise.
- Sorry about that.
Sorry, sorry Cameron.
- It's a silent machine and you're just sitting there like.
- Scanning, scanning.
- Pew, pew, pew, pew, pew.
the MRI. It's done! So yeah, as you're analyzing the snake you see a couple of
different things about it. One, it has stomach acid it would have used to
digest you guys if it swallowed you. Close call. And the acid itself is
synthetic. Yeah. So it's not whatever organic parts of it. I'm dropping that shit on my tongue.
Thank God. I almost let that snake eat me until I found out they had stomach acid in them.
Yeah, okay. You also notice that the plastic is made of polyethylene and
polypropylene. These plastics are often what make up toys as well. You'll also be
unable to trace, notice you'll be unable to trace this within the supply chain as
well. So any sort of the remnants of that plastic, the Blue Gopher is able to see
that these are not a part of the sort of normal supply chain of plastic.
The Toymaker. Yeah. Keep it 3thowl with me. He said yeah, it's the Toymaker. Keep it 3thowl with me right now.
It's Robin Williams. Okay.
The final thing. Is this a toy?
It is part toy, it seems like. Crap.
The final thing. It's a monster. The final thing.
It's like a monster. Is that the snake has erogenous zones.
Where? Where? Where? Where? It's a sex toy, y'all.
Damn! And that the erogenous zones
reveal highly sophisticated synthetic flesh as well as organic flesh melded
together that would require a state-of-the-art facility to produce at all.
I think that Cameron has a guess to wager. Lay it on me Cameron. Playtime was
the architect of the spaceship because the spaceship looks like a sex toy too.
Oh my god. Just you don't have to do anything. He's nodding. I want to put it
He's nodding! I like that guess. It's a cool guess.
I'm just drawing connections. I think it's Ron Jeremy.
Now, that's a guess I like.
That's what I think. I think it's Ron Jeremy.
Cool. So yeah, the blue gopher says,
"I hope this helps you with your investigations."
It's a very similar composition to the monster, but that one didn't quite have the same
erogenous zones as this snake, though. It's interesting.
where where are the origin of zones on the body of the snake?
It looks like inside of its mouth and on its
underside there was a... Inside of its mouth?
It feels good inside of its mouth? What kind of a creature would have that?
And then also on its underside... Are you sure you didn't accidentally detect a food zone?
Well it might also be... This snake was a hoe!
It's also a... Love sucking dick! There was also a
some kind of a labia
situation on its underside not its underside it's on the side oh I call I
just called bloat us okay okay under where what under where I grab was uh
wait what's up dog oh no I didn't do that okay I gotta go back to this thing
All right, we got what we need. Cut to him again. Okay, perfect idea. So, you are back.
We are back. We are family. All right, I guess we're at the bar. That's right.
So you're at the... This is the bar. Mm-hmm. Yeah, actually... Should we bring O'Neal with you guys to the
bar? No. Let's start adding some... I guess O'Neal is with me now. Yeah, well, if you want to bring O'Neal, yeah, I guess you can come to the bar.
Why not?
He's feeling that much better.
Let's add some people around the bar, guys.
He's a leprechaun.
He needs a drink.
Where's the bartender?
The bartender needs to be behind this counter.
Here is the bartender.
What did you just do?
The bartender cannot be a sheep.
Something happened.
It doesn't matter.
This thing.
Something happened.
I'll add these two guys in a second.
Just stop.
I fixed it.
Let's add these Roblox guys as well.
The big guys need to go in the front.
Oh yes, I will make sure of that.
Yeah, this is fine.
Can you guys help me please?
This is fine.
I don't think that we need this many people.
I think it needs to feel like a bar.
If there's that many people, they're not standing up.
Oh, there's a kid at the bar?
What the hell?
There's a kid at the bar!
The people are sleeping at the bar.
Don't worry about it.
Just start the scene.
And then these guys are there.
Make sure those guys are out.
They're going to come in later.
All right, let me get up my notes for the freaking bar.
- These guys are cool.
- From now on, the new protocol is me and Cameron
set up the scene and you can just start.
- Yeah, and I'll just start doing stuff?
You got it, oh yeah, 'cause people are gonna be listening.
- What kind of bar is this?
- It's Gaddy Up.
- What are they doing?
- It's gonna be blocked by these two big guys.
- Yes, it's a seedy bar.
It shares some of that look of Gadsville
that you guys would have recalled if you two were there,
but you would recall Patrick Yoda,
where it has those, you know,
baby guys clearly cashing in on his name here, right?
You have some of that blue and red boxy look
that Gadsville has with those kind of cables
running through it.
He has local Gadsville drinks on offer,
show tunes blasting out of the speakers,
but it's working, people are here.
It's clearly sort of a like theme bar
for folks on Pleasure Palace, right?
They're here to see a little slice of Gadsville while they're away.
Baby Gat has his face everywhere.
You know, he's got his face and his label, the Prince of Parties, right?
Because he's a prince.
And he's called the Rogue Prince as one of the drinks.
And it's really just a mezcal cocktail with chocolate syrup instead of agave.
And it tastes horrible.
And you see here, Baby Gat sort of starts talking to you about, you know, he's like, "You know,
They don't treat us right in the undercity.
You know, we don't even get the scraps, we get the scrap scraps.
You know what I'm saying?
Skip.
*laughter*
You know, you became a lot ruder somehow.
You guys were crazy rude when I first met you.
Interrogate.
*laughter*
What do you mean? I didn't do it!
What are you talking about?
Interrogate again.
You're out of your mind.
Press harder.
Okay fine, I'll spill.
What do you want to know?
All of it.
See a quest marker comes up and it talks about,
it's something about the Holocaust,
it's something about history of the world.
He says, "Leo's whole thing with the freaks
"is a complete political move."
Okay, so destabilizing Gunn City,
he's having his empire provide refuge for their shit.
It's all just a bunch of, I fucking hate this place.
You know, I wish I never left Bullet Town.
He's like sort of rambling about a bunch of crap.
And as he leads you through the bar, you see regular folks, vacationers who stumbled into the wrong place,
off-duty guards, which is basically most of the guard presence in the undercity, are just off-duty guys.
Whovians, robots, apes, and of course freaks.
There's an air, water, fire, and earth hockey table.
There's a... I like that.
There's V-Folk strippers.
There's two people doing it apparently.
There's two people doing it.
I still can't see it.
These people could also be doing it though.
So don't worry about it.
Okay.
And uh...
Uh, for a...
Collect the reveal.
There's a...
Pretty good reveal.
There's a rudimentary VR headset that lets you shoot up a bank.
Uh, what else do I have right in here?
A poker table.
There's lots of stuff you can do in Gaddys, in Gaddy Up.
Um, as you approach Gadd's office, and he was gonna let you in,
These two guys do show up.
Is that their names?
No.
Do show and up?
Their names are Keep Calm and Chive On.
Really?
Yeah.
And Gat sort of sees them
and you see his face kind of
grow a little white.
And he says,
What color was it before?
It was tan.
He says,
a second and I promise we'll talk and I'll get you I use Yoda's mind on them
okay cool um so they're gonna try to roll to resist that time this toy keeps
making me laugh I don't know I can't it's a very funny toy I found it at a
like just a random store you made that
I'm so glad.
I thought that was going to be a character from like Real Steel or something.
Yeah, I have no idea who that was.
I found him and I found two wrestlers who have the worst faces.
I'm going to bring them out another time.
But I found them together and they looked like a gang.
I was very excited.
But anyway, he's going to roll.
These guys are going to try to roll a resist.
Let me get their stats up.
Hold on.
but they have a bad wisdom.
Definitely, they're big jocks.
Yeah, they probably got head around on the head.
Yeah, they got CTE.
Football.
Head around on the head?
Head around.
Head around on the head.
Still doesn't really flow or make any sense.
Head around, head around, head around.
At least a level above head around.
Yeah, definitely better than head around.
You cleared your throat like you had something to say.
Yeah, no, sorry, yeah.
What are you doing?
You were able to read.
Oh my god.
Patrick just taped his eyes.
Oh, he has invisible eyes.
Well, you have to go in front of the blue screen.
Oh, he's trying to do a thing.
Or do it in front of something where there's something,
I guess.
You're just going in front of blackness.
Oh, is this kind of--
A little further, a little further.
All right, yep.
Perfect.
All right, Patrick right now has blue tape on his eyes.
Yeah, that's pretty good.
This does look pretty cool.
Yeah, rip that off his face.
It would be so funny if he had no eyelashes.
He definitely lost a few.
(laughter)
- All right, you are able to read their minds.
Read to me what Yoda's mind does.
- It's a mind reading spell?
Oh, I can read minds, blah, blah, blah.
I can either shift my attention to the target's thoughts,
and type a rope deeper.
- Yeah, you get those surface level thoughts.
- Yeah.
Oh, I feel like these two guys
only have surface level thoughts.
- They might have more deeper, but--
- Well, what are their thoughts?
Their thoughts that you're hearing right now, just like surface level impressions that you're
getting is that they're pretty pissed at Gadd.
Hot dog.
Hot dog and hamburger.
They're pretty pissed at Gadd.
Oh!
Fall.
I fall down.
And they're definitely wary but curious about you.
Yeah.
But they're pretty- I'm probing deeper then.
They're really angry at Gadd.
Okay, you're probed deeper?
Yep.
Here we go.
Look at the size comparison.
Wow, okay. Is that a wow for me? Yeah, wow for you. You did well there. So what happens when you probe deeper? Read that to me.
Okay, if you probe deeper the target must make another wisdom saving throw.
If it fails you gain insight into its reasoning, if any, its emotional state in something that looms large in its mind
such as something it worries over, loves or hate.
If it succeeds on this probing, well it didn't, so.
Well you did.
I've been out of the mind for 24 hours.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So you haven't.
So now, so what was the first thing there?
Insight into its emotional state.
Like I said, you kind of get to say it's angry, but not just angry.
You understand that they are here to get something from being a dad, and also to get something
maybe from you.
As far as their, what was the last bit there?
Um, does that one make sure?
They're, uh, something it worries over, loves or hates.
Um, they are worried...
Do they love each other?
They love each other because they're brothers.
They are, they are worried...
I didn't know they were brothers!
Yeah.
They are worried about people learning more about the operation that's going on with Hugeass and the scientists that works for him.
The blue... squirrel?
No, the blue gopher.
Okay.
for
of
No, no, no, well, no, that's a different guy.
But I mean, he has at least a similar look.
I don't know what that guy's called.
Isn't he called Moonraker?
No, Moonraker is the name of this--
stop, you're fucking with me.
You're fucking with me.
I'm so simple.
I'm such a simple little idiot.
No, I genuinely don't know.
I've never seen--
OK, his name is Huge--
Huge-ass Facts.
By the way, now that I know, it's kind of stretch.
I'm going to be real.
Huge-ass Facts, Hugo Drax?
It's a stretch.
It's not a big stretch.
It's OK.
Hugo gas where you're supposed to kind of like
I think we'd feel differently if any of us knew who Hugo dress. Yeah, that's a good point
Yeah, it was something from this all good Rick in decade you old bitch
I am an old bitch when it comes to this one moonraker does take place partially on a space station. Oh
My god, cuz he rakes the moon
Anyway, so
About finding out about what the Sun the scientists is doing you don't have too much more info these guys don't seem like they're capable of
No
Much about that. They look like visual learners
Yeah, go on can I can I have a you know like I
Have inside it so I can only hear their thoughts. I can't like
Probe any further and like like Jimmy Neutron like when you go through his brain
brain blast. It has a picture of the monkey and stuff. No, no, no. I can't brain blast.
It's not quite like that. Is that an upgrade I can get? No, but maybe, it's not listed
right now, but I can make that into an upgrade. That's a good, a visual learner or something.
Visual learner is a funny upgrade. I like that idea of an upgrade, being able to see what
they've seen in their minds. That's kind of fun. Alright, I was going to say, write this
down this is recorded so I will add that I like that um what I will say is I mean
this is this is enough info about their emotional state and what they're
concerned about that you could potentially obviously use this to your
advantage if they're concerned about the scientists and they're angry at baby Gadd
about in this case about what went down with O'Neal you know you can start to
draw your own conclusions or to figure out oh yeah well I know that's what
they're I mean I got like two good yeah yeah I'm like deep in their damn mind
So what are their, why are they here for GAD?
So I would say that what you're able to tell is that they're upset with how this O'Neill
thing is drawing attention to them.
They're upset with, they kind of want to make sure that something about GAD needs to keep
kicking up money.
And then something else about to gauge the interest of those three detectives.
So does this mean Gadd works for Hugeassfacts?
It's not that he works for him, you get the sense?
Okay, so it's like he gets shook down by him.
A little bit, yeah.
Okay.
He might have his own operation, but he's kind of their bitch at the end of the day.
Yeah, okay.
Alright, what else should I ask? Is there anything else I need to know?
I would say that's probably all you're going to get from them anyway.
Okay, alright then. I'm going to walk right up to them and try and stab them.
*laughter*
What?
Yep.
I'm gonna walk up to them and I'm gonna try and stab them with a knife that's on the table next to us.
All three of us are violent, crazy people.
You really...
Doesn't surprise you?
Really are.
You're the one who keeps putting us in fuckin' places of authority, making us cops and shit.
Yeah.
We do keep making you cops.
We're bad.
We're the bad guys.
We're hella bad.
You're gonna try to attack them then?
Yeah.
*laughter*
Okay, uh...
Do I get to roll with advantage because they don't know I'm coming their backs are turned to me
I would say that since you're 1/16 their size you're at a maybe
That is not to scale your friends are not here to help. Yeah, this is 1v2. Oh, yeah
Maybe you burst the whole I know what I still haven't healed up. So I don't think I'm gonna go
Yeah, I wanted to me. I mean I go up and I grab the knife and I go
Kind of make like I love it face. Yeah, I love how ballsy that was though
I like the world where you did that too.
Can we play that out for like...
Yeah, you want to do that?
You know where it's like...
Yeah?
Yeah.
Like where they've cut back and then it's the guy's like, "Hey, hey, what are you doing?"
You were zooming out.
Yeah, super bad.
We do one of those.
You know what?
Can we actually...
Can we end the episode on playing this out?
I want to do that.
Okay.
Roll a d20.
Let's see the attack.
Okay.
Let's see how you do.
Okay, not good.
Okay.
So you add your, I mean add eight to that, that's not enough for your AC.
You kind of like walk up to them, after reading their mind so thoroughly,
they're even maybe a little intimidated by you.
Like if you were standing across the bar like with your hands, do you just...
*laughter*
Like, they're just so...
You just walk like a psycho.
And then you just whiff.
Like you just like, basically swing your sandwich upwards.
And then they just like...
Do they even recognize a sandwich as a weapon?
Mean like maybe his sandwich. I mean he they've heard about you you can tell obviously they know you guys are
Kind of crazy and then one of them with a tail so initiative we'd roll initiative so we roll initiative
What'd you get
okay, so they got a
23 so they're gonna go first
Here's more of what would have happened
One of them would have taken out
Well, they're already wearing their brass knuckles.
Okay, what's your AC, Pat?
My AC is 14.
Okay, that hits. Let's see what also would have happened.
These guys are badass.
Okay, so that deals...
And this one's got DoodleBob's powers.
Yeah, that deals 13 damage to you.
And then the other one would have attacked.
Where you at in HP wise?
I don't remember.
Let's say I was at full health, because it's an imagination.
You would have died.
You would have died instantly.
You would have just been dead.
There would have been nobody there to help you.
Right now, cut back.
Yeah, cut back and you're just standing across the bar.
Wait, wait, wait.
Can I implant this thought in their heads?
No.
Like, like, like, like, like, uh...
Why do you want him to be like, "Get kicked out of you?"
Yeah, yeah, so they think that they beat the fuck out of me, right?
Then they don't view me as a threat anymore.
No!
I can't do like a, like a Professor X-style thing?
Who's they? You?
Yeah.
No!
You're at a bar, you're at a bar and you see a guy, you guy, you see a guy like, standing across the bar and doing, like, doing like the, the telekinesis thing at you,
and then you suddenly get a vision implanted in your head of you killing that person.
Why can't that go through?
Why can't it go through?
Why can't that go through by the ether into their brain?
If you could see the ship from where you are, you would see a beautiful, pleasurable shape
made of metal and black metal and yellow lights.
And if you moved in a bit closer, you might even see one of the dozens or hundreds of
windows really that line it.
And you'd see some of them flicker on and off, people doing things, different activities.
But you might see if you look closely enough, flickering on and off in a pattern, something
moving through these windows.
And if you listened closely enough, you could swear you could hear the faintest lullaby.
And the only thing you would know for certain is that it's something you've
never in your life heard before.
It's a some song. It's a song. Jigglypuff. I mean I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm gonna make it
and I'm gonna add it to the give it to Jubio. And it'll be playing over us
talking right now. Yeah. Oh, and it's Jigglypuff's lullaby.
Even over this part. Okay, well, I haven't heard the song yet.
God, Patges, this is the song you wrote? This song sucks!
No, uh... This song's a piece of shit! Hold on, it's actually...
Hold on, wait, this part's actually pretty good. Okay, okay, go Cameron, go Cameron.
Right, okay, good. Is there any feedback, any notes?
On the song? Yeah. Make it quieter.
Okay. Now make it louder.
Now, go back quiet. Okay, Jubio.
Now play it in reverse. Jubio, can you...
Add a little steel drum right here.
Okay.
Alright, I'm gonna go pee.
That's that mattress, man.
Jeez.
[MUSIC]
[BLANK_AUDIO]