[Dramatic music]
Last time on Gun City, the Temple of Tepenguin of Doom.
Our three adventurers fought against two mysterious ninjas, whose dastardly ways and
skillful combat techniques nearly foiled our heroes, but they prevailed using the tried and
true tactics of shooting someone until they are dead. Ray William Johnson by happenstance
and wanton cruelty discovered that there were traitor Jollibees in the ranks of Leo's security
force and quickly dispatched one with a powerful matrix beam. Meanwhile Patrick Yoda used his force
abilities to obtain the floppy disk and played keep away with the ninjas. Blotoss Piss was the
the one who shot them all in the head. After the ninjas escaped using dark magics of some
kind, the team met up back at Leo's pad, where he entered the floppy disk into his ancient
Dale computer and revealed a webpage that led to the club Penguin Island, where the island's
location it was discovered by a crafty way William Johnson was reflected in both longitude
and latitude of the land caves in the outer zone of Gun City, called Scope Zone, just
beyond the invisible unfinished wall. These caves should hold the next clue to finding
the Temple of Tipanguin of Doom and the fabled N-Word Pass.
Our heroes took Sullivan and Leo Skygallion across the high seas known as The Air all the
way to Gadsville, a small city in the Scope Zone that has jurisdiction over the Land Caves.
They arrived in Gadsville and immediately attacked some of the electrical wiring that
powers the city
afterwards they walked to the hotel that's what she said
when they made everyone who works there upset
and then finally went to their rooms
where they were quickly called down from
from the by a stranger super handsome
stranger v folk named beautiful simon who told them it was time to meet
with the cats
and so yeah that's what happened so
uh... i believe uh...
patrick
you know the screen
uh...
in excitement
and uh...
yet beautiful simons there they are just sort of floating like a
like a look like
casper but with uh... a jojo
like a judge as bizarre adventure
top some your some of your fans are as cool as me will know what that means
uh... and uh...
yes like scammering
and uh...
and the and they're saying uh... to you
the gads of some in june
come with me to the gateway cow
no one you know i and why should we believe the word you know
that's a good point
and uh... they have a lot of say that every n_p_c_
hothead
this a little more spice to the campaign yet
ticket tactic that they
the uh... hold out there at their hands in
out pops a uh...
a uh... little hologram
and it's the it's the josh dad uh... family so
the family that rules over gadsville right now
uh...
are the uh...
pop a dad mom again baby cat
and uh... you know they're
move very few are generations away from josh can't pop again it is is saying
uh...
we can't really invite you
to come visit
the dad family in our
wonderful
gag gateway cow
you had a porridge in there
uh... and beautiful simons like this it's it it's a recording so i'm not sure if we
have do you have any games at your house
well of course the gas family has and i was talking to mention to the guy
the hologram so i don't have that play again if you want yet again
let's see that again
see one more time
we cordially invite you i don't remember exactly what i said
no let's go on let's hear it i said i want to listen to it again patches
yeah can we play the recording again yeah sure so
play it in reverse yeah you can just cut that oh no i don't know how to do that
oh you're gonna have to say it again oh you see that uh the sweat it's
it's sweat coming down on the hologram just try to remember what it said
we partially invite you to visit the gas family in our
gateway cow
and i i i i just really like
okay we partially invite you to
did i say visit we're going to give it a big uh... so it seems like
it seems like this recording is faulty so i'm not sure we should trust you
but since you can't even simply replay
over again
you might be the dumbest guy i've ever met and there's just a name bullshit
over and over again
but the business uh...
i can't stress enough that i'm showing you a hologram
and it has some sort of faulty record we're not talking to you were talking to
the blue guy right now
the
uh...
uh... i'm still a bit the frog
we would love to go visit the gas and the uh... just that's cheating
but the way you know that i i i
uh... we just would like to have some additional
you verification of some kind just as a
yeah exactly what's all that says a let's watch that video like
ten more times
and then we can go
uh... okay uh...
do you do you want
so do you want to be in to describe what that's like what do you want to be a
safety at that point
wait one second i have to make some popcorn
i don't get a ride in a big bucket of popcorn and i think it's right i put my
a
i think you're asking for popcorn was called no no no i thought i was going to
be hot and some hot call popcorn
it sounds good
okay we watch it ten times yeah does your does your hologram player played dvds
let me see we have only h_d_ dvds which were discontinued i think
yet twenty ten we know right yet
here wait i
i think i have one i'll put on my wallet which is she a
only i remember i don't know i remember you stole that from leo the collector
yeah yeah i pull out copy of the employee of the month on h_g_p_ h_g_ t_v_
and i i i i i
it's easy h_g_t_v_ cut of the player the man
yeah
so we can we watch that
yeah you guys sit down and watch the h_g_t_v_ kind of employee the mind just
and halfway through I look up to Beautiful Simon and say, "So this is the Gadd family?"
"This is the best hall of graham ever."
You see Andy Dix stuttering over something and Beautiful Simon's like, "I got distracted,
this movie's incredible. Please, come out, I have a car for you all to go into."
So do the Gads live in that toilet paper fort or what are we doing?
though don't we all wish we lived in that toilet paper for it yeah so we get to go play poker
with them at the costco if we go could you imagine playing poker with andy dick how fun
would that be unless he tries to get you addicted to cocaine or something like that
all right i could handle it i jump in because i think i'm about to meet i think i'm about to
meet jessica simpson yeah so you guys go jessica alba you guys go outside of the of the hotel
that's what she said
is it jessica simpson or jessica alba?
it's alba
jessica simpson is from the simpsons patrick
no wait what's the um
no it's jessica simpson's
employee of the month
i don't know
yes it's jessica simpson
fuck dude
jessica alba is in the other world
look as long as i get to meet efren ramirez i'm fine
laughing
yeah just see the glow
of the i_m_d_p_ page on for pat
people's effort remears from nowhere and uh...
they want to talk to him about pedro
i would like to talk to him about peter but
a sorry that's the campaign the show so you guys go outside and uh...
you see that uh... it's uh... beautiful simon has one of those uh... because if
you recall gadsdale me as to forms of transportation
uh... those uh...
motorized scooters you get in wal-mart and trolleys
and this one has like the motorized scooter but it's massive and has the
giant
basket in front of it
has like this plus seating for you all the sit-in
and you see beautiful simon
the v folk their way into a click sort of zoom into
the machine
and you hear the machine go honk honk and you hear the machine say uh... you
know sort of like uh...
you know static e like it's coming from a machine uh...
pile in my basket
uh... i do it did you know that i have no question and there
you sure you need to see the hologram like on the other side of our d_n_a_
does go
jarred for a change my mind
i'm so i don't have any on the inside of the car uh... yes so
uh... beautiful simon drives you all along the roads of uh...
of gadsville
and you you you all go out sort of the outskirts of the town now where
uh... you know the buildings are are will be more sparse because it's sort of the
uh...
there's room for
helipads for different like you know air travel for people to land
is probably near the area where you would have landed your sky galleon
uh... and you see
the massive cow
uh... come into view
the massive gateway cow with josh gads face on it
uh...
and uh...
as you write the cow
uh... it's even more massive in cow like as you get a close you see a commel
walkway
search at out of the heel of one of the hopes of the founders
uh... yet does
what do they do
they're just sort of hanging out there they don't don't do anything right now
are they functional others or
you know some
now i want to ask you know i don't know how can i still fully she wanted the
others to try and like so that i don't don't shoot it is probably a lot of
in
the
you want to clap on the other side of the top line the others are pretty far up
you know i don't remember you can try though
i'm not gonna stop you
i would like if you do that
my character will stop at nothing to make sure you don't touch those letters
okay i want you know that before you make a decision
i'll try
not to do that
the
so you're that's why i was rather rolling up to the huff
is there anything you want to do is we're slowly rolling up the ice or yeah
okay
caleb kelvin uh... blue array william johnson role to see if you you're you're
trying to make yourself parts role constantly
uh...
picture
yeah i don't know i don't have anything in the tank
and i think you know i'm yeah if you got lower than a ten i'd say double poopoo
situation but i think i have gone with it
yeah i know it's good it's it's loud it's sort of uh... it doesn't sting your ass
you know as far as where it's like
and it's not like you
kind of
does it keep up something yet not like that at all it's a good news
again
and you see you see it it just it's you see solving just like trying
not to vomit
is it's a stinky
i'm sitting on a cloud of i mean i don't know how it comes out of
of caleb's ass and it just this flies right to sullivan and just
and just stays
he's like a person
sullivan's like running in circles and the clouds just following him
like oh not again
yeah you guys get to the hoof
beautiful simon sort of teleports out of the or phases out of the giant cart
giant walmart cart and you all sort of pile into this
this metal ramp onto it looks like an elevator beautiful Simon once again,
like phases into the like elevator like control panel and it starts to take you
up.
It's like there's a go up and you hear a music version of like frozen music
that that Josh Gad sings and you hear like music versions of that playing as
you're going all the way up the leg of this cow.
And there are vidi screens inside of it playing and replaying movies from the ancient past and beyond.
Josh Gad's movies, his son's movies, and their progeny, so on and so forth.
And then until everyone's attention span was obliterated, it sort of ruined the Gad's movie career.
That's why they moved into computer technologies, computer cells.
Because everyone likes Bites only. Everyone loves Bites instead.
and so you have to have a fun time and flies out of the control terminal
uh... for the elevator
and uh...
and uh... the elevator door opens and now it's like this to see this massively
long haul
uh... with just like a line with computers and automated workers with
the occasional can bone technician ensuring operation continues
beautiful simon says this is where all of the computer technology
that is used by the gads family for gadsville takes place at go
did you hear an echo
and uh... beautiful simon uh... laughs a charming laugh
haha
yes
well i'll find myself doing that sometimes as well
yes we have a hand patrick yoda
and i booked that can bone technicians belly
yet do it
okay do it
what i wrote that
you have to roll anything you could just focus belly
hey a a body weight going
by a book in my belly
i gotta see if you do in your job correctly
and on my job correctly is gonna watch you point the lights and then whenever
happens they just have to make sure that that one doesn't play i'm gonna be
honest
i thought you were a puppet
i shine i shine my i shine my great gun laser site onto that light to make it
look like it's blinking
the one that he said should never be okay
but the role to see if he realizes that uh... okay
uh... not very perceptive
she okay you gotta one you know god
on god is the polls on like uh...
fuckin like uh...
uh... like uh...
you know fuckin warning fuckin thing
what's the thing we pull a thing a levering
because i'll leave ur and uh...
and uh... you see like
you see a
really silly other can bones have pile around in
and they're all like on the computer now they're all making sure that the lights
okay
uh... and beautiful simon has to go over there and like
like
big please please
can bones please and like certainly a lullaby to them and the other
so i'm going to allow the understand is good
uh...
uh... i think i'm going over to each one of them in poking their belly button
and while i don't like panicking and then when you poke them to go to a
pat
the way hearing hearing them all say hey i realize that they they all had
different tones and I do funky town by poking all the right order
raw performance check okay yeah yeah it's a serviceable funky town with that
14 yeah hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey yeah yeah and beautiful Simon says
that's great but not now we need you to meet the heat the gads and you continue
after he uh... after uh... of all those can those calm down
uh... beautiful simon takes you further in
to the uh... uh... this hallway and so
they're saying like this is how we keep all of our technology proprietary away
from gun city
and as those able to remain as independent as a corporately run and
owned
uh... city-state outside of a major city camp
and uh... you reach the end of the waiting room is a large command center
why didn't you call it the gattican
they're not very clever and i think that i have a lot of it's not
the another like a command center
uh... you hear uh... uh...
more music playing out of it you see uh... other can bone technicians
sort of working them uh...
and it's like now is a good another elevator in the middle
as but it's like one of those open elevators you know it's just like a
platform a c_n_n_ you go in that
you go up
and then suddenly it's just like no more
lights electronics activity
and you're in just like
awaiting room like a yellow waiting room
and uh... you see people sitting down
uh... and you see a door and on top it says uh... to see the gads
and uh...
uh... you see a beautiful simon say
now just wait here in the gads will summon you when they're ready
ready yet
now they have to do take the requests of
all the dead citizens who've no
like uh... is this like a lauren michaels in like we're gonna be here for like
four hours
no not even the gads are that disrespectful
but i see a picture of one of the gads
yeah actually in this area you see like oil paintings of all the gads starting
from john i don't want to see an oil painting i want to see a photo
yeah uh... okay and i think you know what kind of photo i want to see
i don't know if i'm following
both in and out of games
you can't see them getting back shots
well we scrubbed all those from the internet years ago rats okay i'll just
wait here
after the eighth happening we had to
i can i start banging on the door
uh... yeah yet do it do it
yeah you can start the door you're just banging on the door
boom boom boom boom
and uh... as you are
uh... rolling dexterity saving them
world
method natural one
yeah
uh...
the door
kirk opens
and you fall right on your ass
and in in front of
none other for your calls on his ass is he
in the door with his ass
and he pulled the door open outward
and uh... i was banging on the door with my ass
he was banging on the door with his ass
so you fall right on it
uh... and right in front of none other than pennsylvania gym
oh my god i can't believe he saw that
this fucking guy
quickly followed by gerard de poupou
i can't believe he was here before us
well what do you do it's doing here
uh... off
all my god
you know i got what i did
i got what i needed so i can talk right off again on the occasion which is what
you get
what i get
yeah transfer for me for me to know when you find out i guess twilight
not the one who looks right at the camera and then to our date who
all
it looks like a little as many on fire to
and he starts bleeding
bleeding like a bird
because that's what i think of french people
and uh...
wait so i'm... can i pick uh...
pennsylvania jim's pocket
you know birds bleat yeah you can try that
uh... you can do a sleight of hand
it's gonna be tough i'll say
it's gonna be easy for me. because he's right in front of you
seven
yeah you gotta describe what you do
i've just reached
i'd just reach my hand directly up trying to his pocket but it is touches p
because the
but his missus part entirely
and uh... uh... yeah
yet this pennsylvania jim's dislike
well looked like i don't know if it feels in way about you but i think
that's all white are for the course i guess
and uh... he just steps over you
and uh... uh... walks towards that elevator
as a way out and he says uh... yes they had the guts for me
you know i just saw them i guess i will never mind
put your balls in jail you cocksucker
and he's a shit
and that's to it
uh... not i'm not fat politics when you're big fat ass
organized
you gotta i went to a round i went to brown is the bell there's it's going
down
uh... by god
yeah and uh... not going to be bothering us anymore
and you see uh... the uh... the uh... the uh... the jordi poopoo saloon
all
was he's going down the elevator
and then the door opens and you see a can bone
uh... the gazelle see you now uh... you three
i have to go to the bathroom is for a bus
and solving the frog
uh... better
that thanks thanks really
uh... he had to go to the bathroom that you get it
yet at this is a guest power move this is uh...
yet he has to go to the bathroom
yeah we have for thirty minutes
in this case and he's p_n_c_
yet
is it is it like stars there is a just like a personal bathroom
missus now yet the personal bathroom like alright well first thing i do is i
I take that lid off the back of the toilet.
- Okay, no way.
- And I find treasure.
- You want to do an investigation check on the toilet?
- Yep.
- Yeah, go for it.
Let's see what you find in there.
15, that's pretty good.
You find a lot of water.
(laughing)
- A poop that someone else previously took in there.
you have to go out here is a good way and so i think i could be a good
it might my plan now is to uh... it's get rid of that's a big it jim's upper
deckers those break doesn't
it's not
spree
it's a good idea you try to eat it
no i'm gonna throw it into the the bowl
yet touch a poop in your hand i'm going to use the force in the poop
okay yeah he had a good
Can we clip that?
Pretty good.
Yeah, so you use the force on the poop and levitate it out of the... and put it into
the bowl.
Mm-hmm.
And then you're gonna touch it with your hands?
No, and then I flush it.
Okay, yeah.
Meanwhile, outside, you see that Ken Bone is just sort of, uh, just staring, like, looking
really nervous.
This has never happened before.
I don't really know... how long does he usually take?
About this long, yeah.
the
deserting magazines in this bathroom
there's good housekeeping
paradigm i'm thinking of collage
this good housekeeping and i think that backstage enough
and i think i've been making a collage this whole time
okay yeah
uh... role is already in the bathroom to
the
there's no backer
no track record
all our way world investigation check
play what if you get high enough
uh... yeah i i i i i i i find this that's a record of the other distinct
yeah you got a t_v_a_ you fight you fight it it says it says on it like
uh... belongs to be
the don't touch
and uh... so i have for later dean
i have the glue in the macaroni and i'm yeah
people and i'm making a a big like collage
i'm making uh...
i'm making like a collage and it's the battle of the uh...
sub battle of at the bulge
okay i've made a collage of the battle at the bulge using good housekeeping
variety and uh... backstage yeah
yeah i believe that all the balls patrick
i don't know what it is i just know what it's called
the
yeah and uh... yet you come out of the bathroom the worst smell ever following
you for no particular reason and uh...
you have this collage
uh... with you
uh... i think it's important for us to remember history lest we repeat it
ourselves
so for it for you all i made this collage
the he says that everyone in the waiting room
*laughter*
and the catboat's like
please, please
if you kept them waiting long enough
i really gotta get you guys in there
i really have to go to the bathroom
*laughter*
do you go to the bathroom blow toss piss?
i say
i guess i can hold it
but when i walk in my legs are like crossed
*laughter*
So you're walk you walk in and the the the crown room so to speak of this Gadsville
Chamber room is like it's it's clearly like you're in the body of the cow now. It's like this giant hollowed-out looks like almost like a
aviator sort of a
you know
like hollowed-out aviator
Hangar like airplane hangar and it's painted like a cow on the inside
And you see all the way down at the end of the hall you see
Three thrones one for Papa Gads one for mama Gads
Then one for baby Gads and you see them all sitting there and you see Papa Gads
is waiting for you all as you slowly walk up and
He says I've been waiting for some time
What who are you three? Who what? What do you want? You?
Didn't you ask us to gum? Well, what hold on and then he goes like
claps his hands and one of the one Ken bone attendant like
Waddles over and he takes off his shirt and puts his back facing the gad and the gad is like looking at his back like it's
a list and
finger and turns a page
Really see if there's like any pages or anything like that. It's just and he's like, oh, I
I guess I did invite you in.
Huh.
Okay, well I don't remember doing that, so...
What do you want?
Why come here and beseech the Gadds family?
And you see Sullivan is already on one knee and he's like,
"Gads, Gads, you gotta bow! It's the king!"
"Konichiwa!"
And I give a big bow.
"No, uh, uh, uh, konichiwa, uh, Lord Gadd!"
uh... we are for
archaeologists slash adventurers open professors
and we humbly beseech
uh... you to we got
uh... guys
you tell me how do you we're going to the lancas right
kundalini uh... you know we gotta get into the
those games over there you were going well
you remember prep pennsylvania jim from thirty minutes ago
show or i remember him yes it is to do whatever it you did before him
later on right now
so you want access to the land caves then too
i'm gonna tell you
when i told that pennsylvania jim
if you're a gun city resident i don't want any gun city people
involved in my
case so
uh... we don't want to have from gun city at all of this i have this guy was on a
skateboard
i have dual citizenship
i've dual citizenship from suck a fuck a bop
uh...
all all three of you rolled deception i didn't say anything
what the fuck
well you didn't say anything just now i'm japanese
now roll deception i got a twenty one
i got a five
oh no
uh... he's like you are most certainly not japanese you are a demon
konichiwa
the
and you are not from gun city
and you
i don't like your face yoda
what are you trying to pull you're with two liars here
these are my cousins
yeah we're bad shit crazy
i pee my pants
(laughter)
i_p_ my pants like a bug but uh... to punctuate him saying he's batching crazy
okay
these your cousins huh
i got a twenty two by the way
when they are defense
yes yes i have to do it
never was for the fan straight up here
these your cousins
okay fine
maybe i'll believe you
if you tell me
we could
are they kissing cousins are not
they are kissing cousin and would you want to be
they'll do it right now for you
no no it's it's
it's fine i think it's
but but but it's good to know
okay
i can give you a pass in that case
your cousins though
they're from gun city i don't want them near our caves and we're gonna get
done for his uh... where his support
cousins so we have to be with the medically at all times.
So we can't leave.
I forgot my vest and he did too today. Listen, also if you don't want to give me a pass
that's fine. I don't need a pass. Okay, I respect you fully and I'm still peeing.
You can roll
deception with advantage. That's not deception for me. No, not you, Patrick.
Saying they're your emotional support cousins.
Nice, take the twenty-one.
at
for
that
Pennsylvania Jim who thankfully is not a gun city resident.
Yeah he is, no he's my neighbor.
Wait, what did he tell you?
Well he told me that he was from, he was from bullet town.
He's lying.
Oh man you got duped.
You believed him?
You believed that?
He's not from bullet town?
No.
Are you kidding me?
He's my neighbor, he fucking bangs, he bangs on the walls and stuff.
my
With my house. No, it's a whole thing
You get confused well, I don't oh I peed my pants this one time because we were waiting for so long and I've been that
I don't know
pants
You know what? I think you three
Give me enough malarkey today
Come back tomorrow. Maybe I'll give you a pass. How about you just how about we just ignore?
Everything we just said get out of my cow kingdom here
I I say okay
We'll wait until tomorrow and then I run around to every clock in the building and I and I fast-forward it
Exactly. Don't tell him to stop. Tell him to stop. No, I'm also a clock repairman
Why do we only have analog clocks in here? I need to
Because it's a static. No, I know why now but I'm thinking about it and you see how the baby the baby dad
Whisper something to the dad and and the dad the dad said, okay fine
Go go my son will escort you out and I see like an example of what the correct pass would look like
The baby dad waddles over to you for and
Starts walking with you out and he he says that was a pretty good show in there
That could have went a lot could have went a lot worse
That's a cool voice man. You like the baby from who framed Roger Rabbit. That's a cool last shit, man
Yeah, that's exactly what I was thinking
so look if
You guys want to get into the land caves I can get my dad to get you in there sooner with no problems
It's a very least I can get that Yoda in there now, but if you want all to get in there I
Got a proposition for you
Whatever it is, I'll do it
Marry a baby side of that or you got to break in somehow which could look at that. What's the proposition?
Okay
Meet me outside of
The toys are us. Oh, that's really easy. Okay, we'll do that. Oh wait
This job tell you it's the ideas of you're already at the door. I mean, I'll tell you more there
I'll tell you more there like you're saying no leave
Well, thanks, man. I appreciate you making the proposition so easy. Nope. Don't don't take my words. Then twist them around
I'm gonna cry. I'm gonna cry
And yeah, you guys leave the the room
So yeah, you guys could break in you could wait till tomorrow
Sounds like you might be able to get the pass
You guys did a pretty good job finessing the king or you can follow
And see what the baby said that you can do. I like this hard-boiled, baby. Oh, yeah
Yeah, he's got like scary Stewie. Mm-hmm. Yeah
Stewie I based him off of
Stewie Stewie from family's guy and then I'm the baby from the baby from
Baby's day out a little doing something a little peek behind the curtain for the fans
Yeah, well peekaboo behind the curtain if you kind of a baby. Yeah a little baby a little peek behind the carriage
These are a couple of baby references. Yeah
If you are a baby fan, please stop listening to this podcast go to the police
Yeah, we're pretty sure you're doing something illegal not sure yet though so yeah you guys
Go outside to the Toys R Us with Sullivan the Frog in tow who the whole time is like why don't we just wait till tomorrow
That baby was scary
and
And it's a massive Toys R Us and you see the babies there the baby gads and and he's in disguise
he's wearing a little bowler hat and a little over, you know, fucking a
Long trench coat and he's like glad you're glad you're wearing that bowler hat now
now.
Well, I couldn't, I couldn't wear it earlier.
My dad doesn't know about my double life.
Well, you were wearing exactly the same thing earlier.
Now you just have a bowler hat on.
It looks good on you.
I was just trying to say that it looks good.
Oh, well, thank you.
I wasn't, was I wearing the trench coat earlier?
It hides your preceding hairline very well.
I got to remember to change before I go back because if my dad catches me too many times
in
all
yes he has
no patrick you don't have a phone we established already the you three years
in a river and you don't have one i remember that 'cause it was very it was
very funny
i don't think that that's canon
i don't think that happens again and you have no phone
you have a poop on your head
yet i remember that you actually have another episode
and also you have to do like a a really racist voice you committed to doing that
and
thought of an imaginary guy eating a pizza.
You don't have to just yeah right and uh yeah so you walk into the Toys
R Us and uh you see uh the the the people working
behind the counters are like like hey baby gad and the baby guy's like
shh watch your fucking mouth and uh take you guys further in and uh to
the back room and uh uh there's a in the back room where
you think there would be like employee shit like a locker or something it
It said there's like just steps leading downwards and the baby's like,
come on, let's go.
And you guys walk down these steps and it gets darker and darker and
darker and you start to hear like a crowd almost you should to hear
like a bell to hear yelling and you realize that you were brought
to some sort of fighting ring.
Whoa, and and you see the baby gads like
Welcome to the Octagon. I know it only has six sides, okay, but it's called the
Octagon. And yeah, you see this crowd out there is just like fucking cheering like
crazy. You see there's a fight going on in the middle of the ring too. The stands are
completely full and he says, you know, in Gadsville we're not allowed to do
anything too unpleasant. Everything's got to be sing-song this, sing-song that. Well
I tell my old man that's why we got the Octagon. He says, what are you talking
We don't got any fighting rings and I show him you all show him. I heard you three are tough
I heard you three are real tough. I heard it from that, Pennsylvania Jim who by the way
Did you guys know favors when he was in there?
but
Talking to my dad. I mean, but I'm gonna sponsor you three and if you win the tournament today
I'll get you guys whatever pass you need free ride right to the land caves full access
this
What's up? What's going on with you? What's going on with the Yoda? Is he afraid of babies?
No! You can't fucking, you can't say that! I don't care, I don't care if you think you
can say that in here. This is an illegal fighting ring.
He thinks that you said Dagoba. Yeah, oh I said, oh, oh, okay I'm sorry. Yeah.
Did he not say that? Nope.
It's, it's, you know what? A lot of times, baby shit, baby talk just sounds like shit
that George Lucas made up, so I am very sorry about that.
Yeah, all right
I'm sorry for getting to hey, I don't get on your bad side
I've heard of stories about you three and they really kill killers of poppy Chuko. Come on. Everybody knows you three. Yeah, man. We're psycho
You're totally psycho you guys with detectives
Say you killed a guy and now you're archaeologists. Nobody can handle you. No, we just go nuts like that
Yeah, it's kind of our swag. I like you three, you know, you're not like the rest of these gads fucking weirdos over here
You're more like all it all the tough guys who live in here. Please stop saying good each one
I see in the crowd here. We have to we have two very fat looking zombies
Can we get confirmation that these are the same fat zombies from sawcast about trick? Yeah. Yeah, it's there
It's their great great great great great great
children.
They don't know each other.
Alright I just want to make sure, I think that's the last same universe thing we needed to tie
together.
I think it's all together now.
It's finally all together.
If anyone wants to make like a 20 minute fan theory YouTube video essay, you got all the
data you need.
Also zombies can have kids.
Yeah.
Oh, that would be, ooh, zombies can have kids.
speaking as says was some of this crazy bear s fool in the middle
on the back of the head
you can't let you ask
so you guys look into the ring
and uh... you do see this crazy bear s fool uh... you know for the viewers at
home there's a massive bear in the ring
uh... some sort of like where bear like it's like fifteen feet tall and like
you know did you say care bear
that doesn't sound so scary
and uh...
You also see in the ring some sort of hooded figure.
And you guys recognize that hooded figure from the auction.
The hooded figure who was there and then dashed out right after the ninjas showed up.
And you see the hooded figure and the bear in the ring fighting.
And you watch the bear like *roar* and just swipe at this guy and swiping like fucking
like you know he's just moving his giant fucking paw across at insane speeds and strength.
And the hooded guy is just like fucking dodging all over him.
And then the fucking hooded guy, at the one time the bear like slams his arms down like
on the ground and the hooded guy jumps up, lands on the bear's like paw and like jams
his foot in and then runs up the bear's, the bear's arms and just fucking like twist the
bear's neck and it just falls to the ground.
noted guy just like stands there and uh... the announcer comes to the ring
and goes
well
is
and i think it was a name sign
and uh... uh...
the fingers the the the guy in the hood is just like
so it was first
snitching
he's and uh...
uh... you see a crowd like the crowds like
game really pissed off as they all bet on the bear
like what the fuck and it's a sky where he's going to stop talking a little
initially the guy
uh... c_n_n_ sort of walk out of the rain now and the group
and uh... he sort of walks over to uh...
this area over here
he's trying to walk past you guys
as he's walking to uh... uh...
to do is dislike stand over here to collect his money
uh...
is what the winnings
and uh... that's happening
so do we have to like fight somebody or did you just wanna watch the fight?
what's up man?
are you talking to uh...
yeah where'd that baby go?
i'm right over here what are you talking about?
sorry you're so small
yeah i'm so small i'm not even on the map
yeah
sorry about that it's probably a little confusing for you three
yeah i'll add a token
perfect
i'll add a token for the baby
how about this one it's a gnome warrior
it's kinda like a baby
everything to uh...
they look good
mean but if you was at home is a little known how on the street
well that's me baby
i'm gonna realize to
where they all of it
let's put some of it on the screen so you guys don't ever get confused again
let's head so that the where's he
i don't know
and when i got a man actually
forgot to put him on the street
uh... worries also happen again
members are about that actually uh...
what the fuck
outstanding in the middle of the rain right now
and i'm yelling
i think i'd dropped contact lands he's somewhere in this underground fighting
ring
can't everybody look at the grounds nobody move
you see like the idea that's a hey hey hey fellas if you wanna fight you can
Fight but you just gotta you gotta wait your turn. Okay, does that sound like I want to fight you fucking idiot
I said I lost a contact lens
Sorry, that's all for this huge
Yeah, and you like start straight to escort you out of the ring and the baby kind of goes up goes hey
They do want to fight they do want to fight. Just give him a second. He's like, oh, of course, of course, baby cat
Shh, call me fucking scorpion when we're in here. Okay, I told you that
Call me scorpion for talking scorpion. No, just no don't call me the fucking scorpion
Number baby and fucker. No, don't stop this. No, don't stop this. No
See him start the well as tears
And yeah, you see the snitchy-bitchy guys at this point collect his money he's walking out of the place
Somebody stop him. Hey
No, he just keeps going stop man. Well, I gave it my all let's fight
Yeah, and yeah, you guys wanna you guys want to do this yeah, I'm gonna fight with us
If you guys need me to I can we need you. Oh
God, we can we choose our opponent. Can we fight Sullivan?
It's like wrestling. Okay, don't fake it's all real. I mean and we're gonna put a bunch of money on us
Kill you and we're gonna be millionaires
Sullivan if you think about it when you die, you're probably gonna go to heaven. Yeah, you're a good guy. It's gonna be great
You love must have died at some point right?
Yeah, actually
Any good people that you know who have died his name was Jonathan
Jonathan the frog I
Guess that that drag is your last name the frog. I
I always thought you were just a frog. I didn't...
Yeah, of course it's the frog.
Wait, then what are you?
I'm a frog.
So you're solving the frog the frog?
Yeah, I guess so. I never really thought through that much, but...
Is there a geneticist in here?
I'm a geneticist.
Hey.
Geneticist, uh, bursts from the earth.
*laughter*
He's a m- he's a uh, he's a fuckin' uh
mole, and he's just like
"Ah, I can help you. What seems to be
the issue, Patrick Yoda?"
"I'd like to get this man
Sullivan's DNA tested right now."
"Sure. Uh,
Sullivan, here, spit, spit in
this vial." And you see Sullivan's about to spit
in, and while he's doing that, uh
he scrapes off a bit of his skin.
*laughter*
Fuck it's like like hey you I don't think you've cursed before it's kind of weird
And he puts this bit of skid in the vial. He says I'll get back this this back to you next episode and
when we
When when we all confer what's solving the back row I care about the war, you know, I want to make sure
We're gonna commit to this. All right, see you next time. Okay? Yeah, I'm going back down, honey
he says to the hole and jumps in with a bit of Sullivan's skin and then yeah the
guys like alright you guys done fooling around you ready to fight or what?
I can fool around a little more maybe. Lord knows that that's true.
I get the I get blowtoss and Sullivan and Ray William Johnson in a huddle like
all right while you're doing this I'm gonna put $50 on both of you wait why
I
row fifty dollars like over the trip to it over the fence but it's like
floats down uh...
yes i'm not going to be runs away
the mark merritt theme song does start to play beginning of the arena
and uh... uh... is here as a it seems we have new challenger is courtesy of
the scorpion for twenty five karis not
i can use like that
and they are
the famous
poppy choco killers here
who here some cheers obviously too
uh... and uh...
is everybody who bought put your hand up
and he's the he's he like three guys put their hand up with his clearly more
people doing with regards like okay and i think it might be cited that
and you three
you know i don't you get in here you three are not in trouble because you
admitted to it
everybody else is a little bit about your back
uh... okay that's a fact that the uh... but i don't know who did it yet will
take you right now
and uh... you see the uh...
how about it
a mass fight to get the crowd
and to the crowd uh...
the crowd is sort of just like gets real quiet all the sudden that's what i
thought
and uh...
yes so in this corner we have
which guys group needs a note
you could be the poppy chico killers if you want but
and i would like for the records and i did not want to do with killing
poppy chico i don't want anything to be associated with that
and i see guys but you know just as does i did not kill
the man
you know the best friends
well
the best friends the best friends the other words
hot dog and uh... yeah
also i would say i would have been a friend of yours and all of them
uh... i mean i should have just said nothing
but i have been a shot dog and that really got a piss me off the point here
if you guys have ever
seen comedy
you know i should have known
that if i said anything are you still talking so i have a right to and uh...
you know it is we have
the best friends group
i guess
and in this corner
we have
the nastiest
meanest
grossest
but maybe sexiest lizard for a week
uh... and uh...
i'm a yoda
you feel and in the ratings
uh... that's not the lizard freaky whoops wrong as a guy
uh...
had put god
and you see the guy
trance for her mood suddenly
well he is just right on top of those are quite a bit not see him
in my
my assets area
and bill is a great free can you see this nasty lizard
in the ring
uh...
and you see a people would like lizard free t-shirts and they're holding up
lizard free posters
uh... it says freak the freak
uh... it says on cold-blooded are you but you know shit like that and uh...
yeah and uh...
and then after some separate the ring
and he says
are dark contestants ready
though
ok i'd stock
that
will late-game how
a few
you have to pee again?
hours
they they didn't give us time to put on our outfits
oh ok i apologize and uh... you see the
the baby
what outfits what outfits do you guys need? these outfits
i just pulled my pants to my ankles
alright we're good
sullivan looks down and he's like ah i'm already there
uh...
yeah you all take off your pants no they stay on my ankles
okay uh... you're gonna have a penalty for that for movement but uh... okay
yeah i put my pants on like it's a headdress
i would not be able to roads and i i took him into my underwear
yes okay
what do you say
uh... but i i i may and i make some
some whooping noises maybe okay
yeah yeah you just see uh...
you just see that the this cartoon has been removed from disney's archives
uh...
show from the screen we try to do that
uh... and uh...
and uh... the announcers like
okay
well
ready that so that just happened
they wear it on their heads now
uh... weird
uh... me thinks that's not how you wear pants in the whole fucking crowd of
gadsdale civilians are just cracking up
uh... and all these jokes
and uh...
is already
well
are a nation
and yet will finish
uh... solvents initiatives are you been rolled for
what a great
five
it's a five
and uh... uh... the uh...
the lizards is
uh... gonna go second patrick you know
is
Patrick can I switch with you because I have a special ability if I go before the lizard.
What's the ability?
It's assassinate.
If I attack before the lizard takes a turn it's a guaranteed critical hit.
Ah ok.
Then I use my turn to trade my turn to Cameron.
Can we switch turns?
Roll a d20.
If you get above a 10 you can switch turns.
Ok.
18.
Oh yeah.
I gotta stop letting shit like this happen.
Oh my god, I can't believe you gave him a 10, dude. That was really the fucking...
I thought it was...
Yeah, 50 people for the coin!
Even then, if he gave me anything higher than 10, like if he gave me 15, I still would have won.
Yeah, dude, that's pure power of will right there.
You're right, that was twag. My bad.
Yeah, it's all good, man. You're just capping.
My bad.
Let's do this. You go first, Blotas.
That's right, I do.
Oh, I also get advantage on attack rolls.
in
reach the lizard. I'm gonna run 30 feet towards the lizard.
Mm-hmm. Which is to I guess, it's annoying that I can't measure it and then see. I
think about here. Alright cool, so I move there and then I'm gonna, I'm like 10 feet away from him.
Super Pipe has 10 feet, yeah. Oh it does, okay. Yeah. I'm gonna use my super...
It's like stacking the pipes on each other. I'm gonna stack the pipes on each other. I'm
gonna use Super Pipe against him. Yeah. Also you guys, also you guys notice, by the
way before we even resolve that, we have the bars below your health bar and that's your
techno slime points. So you guys can sort of like manage that inside the token as well.
Cool. All right. I have advantage so... Yeah, I mean that hits. 20. 20 hits for sure. Roll
for damage. Well it's crit right? Yeah, roll for damage. So roll for another damage. Roll
uh yeah. Alright that's 11 damage. Yeah sick. Yeah. Describe how you hit this fucking lizard
with your blood pipes. Can you describe the anatomy of the lizard a little bit? Yeah sure.
It's like 9 feet tall, standing upright, this giant lizard freak, massive wide arms. Okay
I hit his arms. No no describe the anatomy of it. It's a prehensile penis. Okay. It's
a
three
yeah
you just fuckin like
uh... i hate it i hate his legs this time
yeah you just go bang on the one arm and you like whip it around and bang on the leg and the lizard's like
uh... this
that uh...
here
and uh... you need some fucking serious damage runners twenty five points of
damage
thanks patrick
yet lizards are looking fucked up
but uh... now it is the the lizards turn
and uh...
it's going to use this i can uh...
where's my lizard stats there
was it's gonna try to fucking uh... uh...
uh... call your ass
uh... 'cause you just fucked it
fucked him up so
he doesn't have to move either, he's got super long reach
super long lizard reach
so he's gonna try to claw you, uh, uh, blow toss
and that hits for sure
sorry
you're bullying us
got a very good roll, 17 damage
oh, shit, you're owned
yeah, and he's gonna go attack you again
with his claws
oh yeah
what?
well i bet that just hits you i'm sorry
it's another fourteen damage a_t_c_ is this
got to you with his claws
after you went up and got up on his ass
is that i think i'm a i'm a
nine health now yeah he's gonna kill me next turn
you know we got it we got a turn up here
yeah so i had not now it is your turn pat you know
uh...
the crowd screaming like
as i thought were going to fight down here and i was distracting
it's so sorry sorry about that
it's are you can hear me clap once
you're like everyone
alright
please shut up
bill false silence
and west and why is it the announcer saying any cool color commentary and
and i'm sorry about that i was getting a sandwich
and that amazing move by blowtoss piss i was shot to the arm and a shot to the leg
the lizard returning the lizard freak with his catnip
when he says that amazing shot by blowtoss piss i like turn to the crowd and i'm like
dancing and that's why i get hit twice
because i'm not paying attention at all
while blow tosses doing that doggies getting in close dot right into him from
this was there
who just as a right in the gut
four times with his nasty lizard free k
blow tosses bleeding everywhere
pretty good
thank you i'm not i'm burgers
to rubin
uh...
it's a little more during
you know a little does an islander here
all really
you know i think that that for you
so you're so far away
can you use you using the force to take the thousand-mile decision off his face
you know what was my wife always my mouth
my wife tells me i should shave the stash 'cause it's a good
crumbs con and i call it a flavor saver
you know what i'd really change my mind about you and so he
you know i think
okay blue fair enough
uh... yet to turn back to
all right so
uh...
might just do like a hoverboard
how much it's so he he got cameron got a pretty good rate
yeah he did twenty five damage yeah
put a quarter on
and
that's right
yeah i guess i'll just like uh...
hoverboard him from
where i'm standing
yeah that's eighteen minutes
all right cool
so
i had advantage on
that's fine to take the first one okay
that they did a hoverboard
for eight damage nice yeah you just like sling the lizard
as it's pulling its claws out of gross man you're slinging your lizard right here
in front of everyone i had to get it done
and the lizard is pulling its claws out of
uh... blowtoss
uh... this hoverboard whacks in the face three times
and swings back
you do have another attack if you want to get their tag or you can move or whatever
uh... i'll just do another attack
denies
that's not a hit this time
you know what i've been going to a nice when they're there
eight damage would be nice
would have been good
but he had seen swing the hoverboard around the same with her nose it's
coming in
is able to like back up he takes a couple steps back from blow tosses a little bit
more wary now and aware
that they're like three other people he has to deal with
really to other people and Sullivan.
So yeah, it's Sullivan's turn and Sullivan is going to be like,
oh no blowtoss and he's like going to run up to try to
and he's going to be here and he hands you a band-aid.
He's like trying to put band-aids on like the wounds.
He's like, oh god, I don't know what I'm doing.
He's like freaking out and that's his turn.
You're up.
So he heals me?
No, he's just, you guys just force the civilian.
and
to take you to a training facility.
Training montage facility.
Yep.
Oh boy.
He's still crying because he's like, oh boy, like he's watching
his friend bleed out and freaking out.
It's your turn to play William Johnson though.
Okay, I'm gonna I need to move over here roughly and then I'm
so that I don't hit Sullivan and blow toss and I'm going to use
my my matrix beam yeah do it pimp yeah that's uh not gonna hit with that
fuck me oh no yeah hey man in a couple seconds i'm gonna hit you but this time
uh but it's yeah but uh you you you still have another attack obviously so
never mind it's actually gonna happen right now
i'm gonna just try the same thing again yeah do it that hits
Big time. 21 easy.
Okay, nice.
16 damage.
16 psychic damage.
Shit, yeah.
Is that enough?
No, it's so close.
You just fucking shoot this matrix code out
and it just enters this lizard's eye
and it's like
trying to, like, it can't understand the code.
It's eyes are rolling back
in its head as it's being
overwhelmed by this matrix code.
a
Oh, yeah, sorry shit. Yeah, you're trying to kill me. I know you have a vendetta against me cuz I switch turns
I don't do not don't you don't don't don't you say that I do him now. No, I know
Did you dude? I never
By asking if I could do something you let me do it
Cameron constantly outsmarts me. I I have to I'd have to already hate him. You're kidding me. There's no way
I'm gonna take a step closer to the lizard so I can okay close the range and use my dual pipes instead of my super
Pipe, okay, do it. I'm gonna pie. I'm gonna pipe him. Yeah, I
Mean describe your killing pipe. It's gonna be a lot of damage
Probably eight damage. That's pretty good. Yeah, you got a little roll. But yeah describe your kill. Okay
so I
Put the pipe over his his slime mold penis like I put it like, you know, I like I put it so it's in the map
and then I just bend the pipe like like I just turn the pipe like and I just snap his little his little right off and
And blood sprays out everywhere tire his entire circulatory system
Like a
is getting fire hose of blood his eyes cross
haha
goes
oh mommy
haha
he just blood just kinda
and he just deflates
to this like pile of scaly skin
and I'm gonna collect that skin and use it to make a jacket later
yeah you see the announcer like wow holy shit
that was
so I did not know that about their anatomy
I don't
wow ok
so is there a heart there
or
like what's going on and i think there is all there and i was a week we wrote a
paper on this were archaeology is set up
that's what we're fighting for our geology
graduations to the uh... the winners are the best friends
and so in the frog
that he had you all do it for that
is a story of how
and uh... uh... yeah that was there is no more
and uh...
yeah i_c_s_
all baby gets a
alia you guys did great
okay get ready is going to be another one coming out soon
and that's
and i don't know that i know that got the lead what the fuck
uh... and uh... so
and uh... yeah as he's saying that
that amazing showing from the best friends but can they keep it going
now
if you would you like you'll meet
does
in this corner
we see coming out from the underground
the nasty stinky
do we do we
purple
and his giant purple worm first from the ground
and uh... i thought it off
Yeah, yeah, it tries to flip you off and it gets sad because it doesn't have hands and gets confused
So does it roll things with disadvantage now?
Not what happens
Yeah, it's like a postman. Hey, that's a nice try but ain't gonna happen
And we're gonna keep the uh, same initiative rolls unless you guys want to reroll initiative. No, that's okay
How about this if you want to reroll you can but this is your one reroll
now i'm not sure
okay i don't like that
mcconnell and the undead
right we're rolling for the purple worm
into the purple worm is going
interesting is a gun first
blowtoss you are still first
all right uh...
so this purple worm comes out it's looking real nasty and gross and share
i uh...
I don't think I can go into, I think I need to back off some because I'm low health.
I'm going to back off a little bit.
I'm going to shoot at it with my Grinch gun with advantage because it hasn't gone yet.
Okay, go for it.
Nice, that's a hit.
Okay, and crit damage is 10.
Nice.
Yeah, you do 10.
So you just shoot at this worm and the second it pops out, it's like, "Worm!"
It just takes those Grinch bullets.
Now, I'm trying to...
One second.
I'm trying to look at my Sikkim ability.
Yeah.
So, your Sikkim ability should allow you to toss your monkey, and then the monkey can
just sort of like stay on top of him and continually do damage.
Yeah, and it gives him disadvantage on attacks, which is mostly what I'm interested in. Yeah, so I'm gonna use the second ability. So
So yeah, you use that and so he has to roll a deck saving throw. So let's see how he does
he does make the save unfortunately for you, so you throw your monkey and
the worm just like
That's a mother. It's just like knocks the monkey into the wall
And monkey like like scurries back to you running
But it's you still do
If I'm correct about the second ability, which that to be thinking Luke
oh
Yeah, it's you still do 1d 6 damage because he's monkey like did knock into him. So roll d6 just doesn't stay on all right
Five yeah nice
Yeah
So the monkey when he hits into the monkey the monkey does like claw at it for a second and he comes back and he's like
Like showing you his hand like like did I do good did I do good? No you suck
Just like crawls inside of your your little vest upset and now it's your turn Patrick Yoda
I
Hate this worm so much
I'm just gonna hover board at it
Nice, dude, that's a hit. Yeah, that's right with six damage
Yeah
Closer
Mm-hmm go on
No, no, no, no keep going. I was just gonna say. Oh, yeah, the all I was saying was I'm moving closer
Okay
Yeah
You sling the hoverboard at him and you hear the announcer goes and there goes
Patrick Yoda's hoverboard once again
And it flies in the air and like you like just like sort of like slinging at it like a straight shot
It just like gets the worm in the head and it's like
Like kind of like seeing stars a little bit
uh... it's it's dead now
it's not that
worth a shot
uh...
the as a good try
the confused him
the a_t_f_ use me for a second there was a good said yes it would have had to
count
yet but i think i can't use it is that yes really fast so you can't just try to
keep tricking me that were says what
he he he
how
now
uh...
or did
is in my turn
uh... no in less than two thirty you have an a another tactic of another attack
uh... everybody's
every other on the hoverboard again
or other heads
that's what i want to be
yeah robert and with eight damage
nice yet you slated again and i just like it the warmest same fucking spot
and uh... you see a little blood squirt now and i was had what colors are a lot
of blood homes were a lot of
friend link
yet
that's right only
and uh... yet
worms blood is green actually greens better come out of purple worm i think
uh...
and uh... yes
whatever you can i got a lot of reason
and answer
okay you guys say purple is that what i was you said purple and then you change
it so whatever man
you know what i don't know
i don't really know what this friendly shit is so i'm gonna try and draw as much
stuff on the map to obscure everything as possible.
Don't do this to me.
Whatever.
It is now the purple worms turn.
Andy, skip my turn.
It's not, I didn't skip your turn.
You skipped his turn, what the hell.
You skipped his turn.
Stop doing this, it's not what's happening.
And the purple worm is going to uh, uh, fuckin' uh, do a little nasty thing.
thing so he's gonna
come over here
to you patrick you know that after those two hits
no
and he's gonna try to wrap his body around you you see like
like swing his whole body into like
wrap around you
and uh... let him do that
yeah let's see how he does that i don't want him to do that again
oh yeah it's gonna be here he comes
so what he's gonna do is he's gonna try to attack you
and if he hits
of edits
i'm sorry
is twenty four
uh...
and uh...
ccd damage and then we have to roll strength saving through
what how much damage to the two
but find out
detain damage
who from as a failure
now you can't just right dead on it
on the screen it is right that he's eyes eyes across that is coming out of the
is
instead of what happens that all that shit is that patrick you know that
gets uh...
wrapped around and uh...
it's worms wraps around your little yoda body
and squeezes
uh... just ten damage to you
and then doesn't do that
no he does that
uh...
you gotta
come on man
you can't do this to me again i'm not going to not going to undo it again
and uh... instead what he does
uh... instead of not doing that what he does
is uh...
he uh...
stops doing it and reconsiders
he takes you underground
and you in the worm get burrowed underground
uh...
i thought you were going to say you learned kindness or something
i wish
and now
it is and uh... the guys like any of the national
all boy
that is never good when the word does that sometimes the word does that the
summer people who work here in new well we don't see them again so uh...
okay well
hopefully that you know that it's out of that and uh...
now
it is solvents turn
it's almost like all god all god
all-time
uh... insults in a role investigation to see if you can find where the word is
uh...
he's pretty good investigation so
let's see
uh... yeah
and solve any seesaw than a uh...
run over here
is yeah i think i think i think you know and uh... now it's your turn really
johnson
is over there
you know you have a lot of around over there
yet meanwhile patrick you know that all you're seeing is just blackness and
rocks are just like in dirt is like just getting in your way and uh...
as it sucks
it's a happy for just like this so
made this so much home
okay so i'm looking at my inventory and by then
god's infinite wisdom and divine providence
yet we have
a huge were in my inventory from the first campaign
so
and i'm gonna do
is i'm gonna throw the
and i'm i'm gonna put i'm gonna put a bikini on him
and some lipstick
and
and i'm gonna do the only thing that worms know how to do and i'm gonna make
him bait
i can't say no to that you have to be able to do that that's on me for leaving
the huge worm in your inventory
i have to take that out of your fucking inventory well now he's on the ground
so we definitely have the all the stuff we used to have in the old
uh... and all campaigns can
yeah
but i still have a video
in the game i'm pretty sure you get rid of the huge were
by still in denial thanks i have a lot of that maybe got another one in prison
the i_d_ ice on and i am in indiana jones type and i actually swapped it out for
different worm obeys again i have that and he's wearing a bikini
that's a little i put him right about here
the figures of the gears that have been turning in my head for thirty minutes
finally
like click into place in my eyes lit up but i go
warms why did it have to be work
her
yet
about a second worker here
okay okay so he's he's like right here and he's a he's a role to eat he's
He's gonna roll a...
Or a fuck, or whatever the worm does to him.
I don't care.
The worm's gonna have to roll a wisdom saving throw to resist...
I worm or he's worm?
He's worm.
This worm, the purple worm, has to resist the charms.
What color's my worm?
Okay.
So this worm, who should know better, instead, pops out of the ground, and Sid goes "OOOH
LA LA!"
And Patrick Yoda also is popped out of the ground.
"BLEEEEGH!
THERE'S A MUDDER IN MY MOUTH RIGHT NOW!
THERE'S A MUDDER!"
I say, "You can look, but you can't touch the merchandise, kid. Not till you pay up.
Give me that Yoda." And you see the worm go, "Oh, come on! Come on!" No, no, no. Okay, sorry to add
Patrick Yoda's character back in unexpectedly for me. Goddamn. And yeah,
And so the worm is like and just releases Patrick Yoda and just like is making
like heart eyes at the big worm and the big worm it's just like making it's like
a you know like starts playing my worm is like not sentient at all and it has no
facial features.
It might as well be like it's like it's like Lady and the
Tramp if it was just like it might as well be like a like
a like a mock that someone's confusing for a woman with
bombs for tits and it's just like yeah, so it's just like
distracted by this worm and it did release Patrick Yoda this
turn, but that's that's that's your action.
You still have a movement though.
the commission of the movement
uh... on the minimum of which i have a way to heal
blowtoss i don't think i do
now the healer patrick you know that has uh... for skin
is a healing move
terry
you know i'm okay then i'm i will move within striking distance of the worm but
not too close
no one interrupt
the magic
payment
now
it is blow tosses turn
yet
uh... on the next day where i am i'm not get any closer and is going to use my
grinch gun again
twenty-two
that fucking hits brother
five damage
the use fucking
shoot at this war while it's like making hard eyes at this uh...
this not sentient worm
and it's just like
we can get right in the fucking side
uh... yeah you get a little bit rich going again
doesn't have to go as far as why
uh... i don't want to buy the sexy work
yeah
this guy's dead
uh... yeah i think i think i think the audience
that you know you're the uh... let's go
well that's got a smart
uh... that guy dies right next to him
uh... and uh...
yet they can still move in shit but that's not not going to move
this was uh...
their patch gator it's your turn
and uh... you see that guy dies by the way and then you see
uh... patrick you know you notice on your turn
uh... that uh... uh... you see uh... your for your friends marie stain and rex
are are also in the crowd
uh... now this is a good thing
uh... patrick gillis good to see you
and i don't know
but he did it
uh... well uh... if you must know rex loves to watch these things
uh... he he bets on them and his his blood just as well as he recklessly
all-year-old
violence is a slight loves watching this
well you guys
yet that's us
we're also here we just roll it up
you're crazy
we are after this
uh... we're gonna get some drinks if you want to join us
baby
okay now in the end of the bed but if we die or not
well yeah that's a good point all-night low-cost
What you know I was there I I just what you can see the ring it's oh
No, I know, but I just thought you were focused. I didn't wanna. I don't want to bother you. He seems like he's got no
It's not my turn. Don't worry. Okay. Well. I'm sorry about that. No, it's fine. Don't worry
Anyway, I'm gonna run away
Yes, you just run yeah
All right, then I I run away, and then I just you know just gonna hit him with the hoverboard
the
it's it's it's not looking good you guys are doing some fucking serious damage to
it now do I have one more move after this yeah you got one more attack if you want
to use it all right I'm gonna do now that I've done the hoverboard that many
times I'm gonna go one time with the hoagie surprise okay yes you run away
16 you run away and then you run back up to him with the hokey sandwich and yeah
roll for damn I was getting speed I was I was uh yeah yeah I was doing like a
a happy Gilmore like when he like swings.
What about ooh?
Yeah for nine damage.
Yeah, you fucking just like and you see that you hear the
announcer goes.
Oh baby.
I want to eat that sandwich and the z like fucking clock this
worm and some of its teeth.
You already are eating one right now.
I know but I want yours you gave it a knuckle sandwich.
Is that you don't want that track?
You don't want this sandwich.
Yeah, he realizes that it's like 300 years old.
and so stale
uh... yet you do another nine damage and this worm is like looking fuckin beat up
you see a mike whispering sweet nothings to the other worm
it's just like in flight hushed french
solution but it was good to put it
places like
like like his final words
as he's looking really fucked up
his final words
that but he's looking back but it is his turn
and he is going to uh...
uh... attack you patrick you know you're up on him
there's no try to attack you again
how did you find that
but this time
he's got ready to ask
uh... now
so role
any dexterity saving throw
seven
as i do it
this worm
whispers sweet nothings to his his worm and it is like those like just
what dislike like
which is like mouth over you
like a fucking to
and does uh...
uh... does quite a bit of damage with this move i think
so it's you know
let's see what he does
you know it's not too bad
he got some more roles we did eleven damage
uh... to you
and now you are inside this worms tummy
and uh...
and uh... i get the one you can you can try to break out
on your turn
uh...
if you don't break out
i mean you're gonna either way you're gonna take
uh... you're probably take some stomach juice damage
as he's digesting you
you're you've just been fucked up by this worm this whole match
uh...
we take another ten damage so you're at fourteen now i guess unlike uh...
and uh...
the worm now with a full tummy
is gonna run up to you too
over here
is gonna he's got a pop out of the ground and with his tail around to try to hit
you
both with it
uh...
and uh... yeah that is both of you
uh... now
finally
it is a ten-page actually
and on that one
that was pretty close to that uh...
c_n_n_ your your
yet and so now patrick you're just followed by the worm
it's now uh...
uh... solving the frogs turned
He's like, "No, Patrick!"
And, uh...
He's gonna try to, uh...
He's gonna try to run, uh...
Uh, up to the worm and just start whappin' it with his fist.
He's like, "Bring back my friend!"
And he's just like, banging his fist on the worm's stomach.
Uh, which is just doing nothing.
And now it's your turn, Ray William Johnson.
Um...
Since I'm so close...
Uh, I'm gonna dong blade this- this motherfucker.
Fuck i'm point blank range. I miss yeah, you swing the blade at it, but it just sort of like I think it just
Sort of glances off the worm. It's skin's too tough. I swung with my eyes closed because I hate gore
Yeah, yeah, you can attack again though you have another attack I spit I just spin all the way around and do it again
23 oh, we got a crit. Let's go roll for damage easy. Holy shit
Describe your kill
uh... it is waiting where is my beautiful warm that i gave him
he abandoned it
server here
okay well i was gonna die so he told it goodbye
and a magic you know that to save to save that were some heartbreak i slice
all the way through
the purple worm
and then i also slice my worm that i put down
my big worm dissociate he or she doesn't have to or they don't have to deal with
uh... the loss of my work of the
all what a weird ritual from the demon with the computer on its back down weird
and so we've had
patrick you know that just like
tumbles out of the world
like covered in slime
uh...
which he just left while he's got a bad day better go to use so if you bookings
to be a good say anything you just got up and walked away from the uh... was
yes bitch boy
So yeah, what happens, Pachacuta?
Would you get cut open out of the worm?
- I throw up.
- A man in a tauntaun, yeah.
You just vomit everywhere.
There's worm stomach juices around you.
And yeah, the worm is no more.
Sullivan looks up, thinking that his fists,
he's looking at his fists like they split the worm open.
- I look at Sullivan like, yeah, you did that.
- Oh my God.
- Yeah, I didn't know you were so strong.
you're the front lines next next time now
alright ok i'm gonna fight use my new fist powers to punch punch everybody
i think your dad was the devil
no way i think so
i think uh... well look i didn't have to wait and see what the geneticists
says next episode
i didn't have the best relationship with him but i wouldn't have called him the devil
you know
nothing
uh... are
is like another
or starting victory by the best friends
and uh... you see uh... rex river to get his
you guys are fucking killing it
but uh... you guys gotta be careful next was pretty crazy and see the baby uh...
the baby dad
you know you guys
okay you guys got this the next one is really tough but if you win
we're all going to be very
very popular
not be a lot of any healing and
uh... no i don't think so
you have any gum
yeah i got gum if you have got ok we have you have done yet to share with all of
us
all okay well dip
all that money just the checks is like
and i think i like to pieces well you know i have any healing abilities
wait all the you guys gum heals us
we are going to be able to do a hundred
points of h_p_ yeah i mean i wrote the twenty most now
uh...
for
that one is healing
you know who are you doing
you're the one who has had healing this whole time
you have not i think
that yes
it i don't know it's on your thing thing i get it
it doesn't hold on
they click the wrong patrick you know
now
uh... that is okay
and i'm a heal everybody
okay yeah uh... let's give me three t
yet no sign points
uh...
so but before you do that
uh... what you should read is that that's good news he meets for one t ten
plus four
and you can also recharge techno points like techno slime points for them as well
however their next round basically they must make a strength dc of of 12 to break out of this like
foreskin that you put over them okay so if you heal them now
they will have to basically forego their first turns do it put me in that puppy yeah okay guys
as
uh...
floats forces skin is at the foreskin or is it like your penis or was your your
forces penis
it's the shorts for the it's my shorts
okay so it's your shorts shooting out
and that near the announcer like okay i don't know
i mean it's a lot like that's my roads into my my underwear before we started
this is a lot of his friends
there's a lot of people are a you know with the violence and uh... looked like
there was some sort of
non-consensual warren stuff going on but this is a little
and uh...
you hear a lot
a if you wanted to if you wanted uh... maybe
here underneath your foreskin right now which is yelling this
maybe
if you think this is too graphic
you let us
uh... just when the next one about that
yet we don't win those national we're gonna keep doing weird stuff we're
gonna get weirder than this
role and i just i didn't get out of my penis
role intimidation check the d_c_ is so i have this
you know yeah he's just like he's a site that's a nice try but you're not going
to threaten me with your foreskin not like
some other people and uh...
uh... then he's goes and now
coming up
the champion of the arena
the one that no one may have a house that we feel sorry
oh yes i'm uh... patrick in a row one d ten
plus four
so just uh...
and then add four to that
so you guys all get four
swag and we get techno slime right? yeah roll 1d4 and plus one
you can't over heal right? or plus two rather
no uh... no you can't unfortunately
so roll 1d4 plus two
two also petrkuda
okay so four
so yeah you gain four techno slime points back uh... okay how many do i lose
three
the
That you didn't know were there and it's just like a really giant creepy zombie hand
That is just like master handing over you all like just doing its little like fucking floating master hand kind of shit
But it's like decay
You weird
Yeah, very weird. Yeah, very weird gives you a shocker brah at that
Okay, you cool
And yeah, it rolled and it's gonna go first so you're all now trapped in this foreskin by the way, uh
And you have to make a strength saving throw on your turn, but for now
It's the creepy hands turn
So, let's get this going hold on a second we get the creepy hands shit in order
Okay
It is going to
It basically sees all of you and it its hand like
Wait, it has a hand -
Has a hand its whole body
rather
wretches upwards and you see in the middle of the palm a like butthole and you see the butthole just
like open up and then you just see us you hear
And a swarm of locusts come outside
of its hand. And I need all of you to roll a wisdom saving throw.
Crit 20. 9. No, it's a crit 1.
Let's see how Sullivan does.
Okay. Okay. So, the people who saved, you know, who got, so are Cameron,
And both of you are going to take half damage and you will not be frightened by the bugs.
Half of our HP?
No, half total damage from the attack.
No, don't worry, not half your HP.
Not yet.
That was a close one.
So you're both going to take four.
Patrick Yoda and Ray William Johnson, you take nine points of damage.
And you're also frightened of the bugs.
So now these locusts that are around you, they're just like, you have to be at least like 30 feet away from them.
Like you have to move away from them.
and you're having trouble moving from them because, you know,
you're trapped in foreskin, and so these bugs are hovering around you in the foreskin,
and then also you have disadvantage on any attacks while these bugs are in your line of sight.
But you can make a wisdom saving throw at the end of your turn also to try to shake off that fear.
But that's what the hand does, and then the hand does one other thing,
which is that it
uh... it
it uh... does the thing
where you guys ever see somebody like move their knuckle
around
it starts moving its knuckle around and you have to roll another wisdom saving throw
it was too creepy thirteen yeah it's doing the weird thing where it moves the knuckle around
oh wait that's not a saving throw i'll have to add
oh that's the same that's the same modifier as a saving throw okay eleven
yeah
uh... blowtoss piss
you are stunned
you see this creepy got hand moving its knuckle around
and it's freaking you the fuck out you hate when people do that
uh...
and you are stunned which basically means you can't move
you can only speak falteringly
attack rolls against you have advantage and you automatically fail any strength
dexterity saving throws so you can't even get out of the foreskin now
until you're able to do it
they were gonna die
senior stunned for
uh... one around
okay so
uh... now
at the hand did its thing
now it is your turn blowtoss
you can't do anything you're just trapped in this for skin stunned by the
way i can speak falteringly
i think we do
the head so yeah
patrick you know that it's your turn
you're not a lot of force can i should say
patrick you know that because you know any who put it around your friends
so you can move around you just have to get away from the bugs that are like in
this area
on the road to this corner
set carry all them with me
now the budget is hovering around here
yet it is a carrier there my four skin
now so we never really even like figured out what that was like a call it's like
a corn husk
we don't know what's what's for you
and it's it's it's floating it's probably blue
and i'm stuck in it
i thought it was on my penis
that that would be disgusting
uh... it's like a cocoon
are you trying to see if that's you're gonna google that
yeah google foreskin
google foreskin gone wild i just want to see what comes up
what comes up man
are slash for skin
some people have longer for skin than patrick you know that
no way
you look at this one
can we
is
we get to the next
okay next time
yeah i mean
but i mean you can i can i
uh... right so what should i do should i get a with uh... the hoverboard
that's one of you got a good abilities
you have uh... one of the abilities that you know i got a hoverboard boomerang for
seventeen
that's good that hits you have used a force which is very good
uh... it basically just powers you up
uh...
uh... should have done that before you hit yet should
but your business
so this is not a report every time
yeah
well
yeah i mean you sling a number of or did not have any and
uh... not seem chips and they always like
and makes a noise similar to the word
packets of the inmates mail
uh... you see it like doing like the you know
uh... front way the back way it's against nails
uh...
and uh... yeah i mean you have another attack to if you want to
i should say shit fuck israelis
is your freedom bugs near your line of sight
do disadvantage in these tax uh... so do i re-roll that yet yet strong and
maybe you'll be okay
and maybe
call
it's too bad twenty four was a correct but you get to get the lower one
c still do damage at least
okay uh...
but you can roll you could do another attack
with disadvantage and you can roll the c_d_ no longer be afraid of the bugs
a
the
uh... now this is like your one
your superset your one super saiyan transformation you have okay
but it's pretty good so patrick is the forpia uses the force uses the force for
thirty seconds
uh... which basically is five turns in d_n_d_
self uh... is a_c_ increases by two
your movement speed is doubled
and you can fly up to sixty feet vertically
your physical tax all due plus two additional damage
uh... based on a wisdom d_c_ check and then based on the size of the object
patrick you're taking also move things around
uh... and as a passive ability
uh... also patrick it gets advantage on all saving throws this is why this is
also a good move
because they're gonna have an advantage on this was the same thing you're about
to do
and
finally
patrick gata
can do it at new attack
uh... force lightning
this is forty eight lightning damage
and also you can do like another move do a bunch of shit and then as a bonus
action just do the lightning instead for two d six
so when you when you
when you tap into the force what happens you betcha
i can't just sit there like
you know you know you know you know you know you know you know you know you know
yet you hear the anthro
i can't tell if this is racist or not but it's getting crazy and yes i would
grow with some saving throw with advantage now to be no longer afraid of
the bugs
okay with some through with the community
to a very high with twenty seven
you dislike stare at those bugs and you're like
you can't scare me
and that's right you tell those books
yeah like no thanks and now
by the way as a bonus action you can shoot lightning now to
let's go
so you can't you know i guess you lightning
the roll.
That was real time how long it took that sentence to get into Patrick's brain.
I thought you were talking to camera.
I'm sorry.
So where do I, what do I click to roll the lightning?
So it's not in here so what you just do is just do hokey surprise, that's the same attack
bonus.
Okay.
And then, holy shit.
Oh, crit.
Okay, roll 4d6.
Okay.
is
shoot lightning out of your hands and just fucking
on this god damn hand you get it in its butthole palm
and it's like
oracle it's like fucking
you fucked it up pretty fucking good you visit that
absolutely not
why not
this is a story to be done
how much it is very man
uh... has some some left
how much left
is a bloody dear
it's not bloody that's the key words there
now it's not uh...
so someone someone wrote dead and did that who did that i didn't see it's the
same dead from before nobody wrote so attention somebody patches somebody
wrote this on the board
no wasn't pointing at the hand before so who wrote this on the board while i
wasn't i dragged it out i mean somebody dragged it over
patches you don't say it
you're all gonna get detention if you sit back down in your chair and don't
look at it
okay okay
there's nothing pointing on a promise
uh...
okay
what do you mean
i didn't attack on your
on your chair
it's in all your
okay all right what you're saying it's and i'm serious
well rolling out of the check on me
mk
messy
well i well sixteen
i guess i believe you there that's not a
you yes
mister patches is going to keep my fucking balls
all
and uh...
yet but now now they were back to the back to reality k
sanity reality
you know
it is now
uh... solvents turn
and he's just like trying to climb out of the force can disturb
he he he
uh... he's been hurt by the bugs he's not looking to get i'm still stuck in that
and that they are
and he gets out of the force can easily
uh... it's a pleasant self-reliance he said practice doing stuff like that
no i don't know i shut up
you really know your way around the worst in our near me so that i'm not
talking my character voice no uh... what's the u_s_ schizophrenia so i'm
i think you know the doctor
the hotel to put a needle in you
it's a problem runs over the hand it's like
are you is my newfound powers is that the bottom of the head
and it's is doing nothing as far as he's concerned is a girl who have to wait
one more time that's not going to happen
and uh...
and you're terribly william johnson
i'm so stuck in the four scandal
so i can do anything yeah
uh...
well so i'm just got a force can move so
nasal and how do you do that
just got a role strength saving from
well i suppose i really i was getting some friendly and
right now and i see your out
your other force can
uh... let's go
that you can move uh... used to have all you know
that's your action though yeah okay i'll move uh... over here
just for fun cool
that sounds good to me okay
we're back to the top of the order
it's the hands turn
uh...
and the hand is just like looking at this little frog
any hold up his finger to flick solvin
uh...
and let's see what he does
the a_t_f_ solvent
uh... no
to you
this is a very nice uh...
so i was like
he gets flicked
so the flies still the other side of the pocketbook and uh... he's out cold
uh... some death saving throws for some of those is second
uh... okay and now it is the head is now uh... approaching uh... you ray william
johnson
one of them
and it's going to try to figure it's like you know
and uh... it's gonna try to uh...
attack you with a big slap
so uh... here goes
and it misses that we just like to slam some ground
and just like you're able to like sidestep it pretty easily
uh...
and uh... now
it is your turn blowtoss
okay i have to try to escape from the thing right
uh... yeah you're no longer stunned so now you can
a crit fail
yeah you just are like
you're like what is this thing that you're trying to find your way it's like
Like you're trying to find your way into a sheet and you just see more and more force
in it.
Oh no.
Um, yeah, you can't get out of it.
You're stuck in that force game.
Oh fuck, everyone's gonna die.
And uh, yeah.
It is now your turn, uh, Patrick Yoda.
Okay, um, what I'm gonna do...
You are now, you have the lightning attack, and you have the lightning bonus attack, and
you have
is
I
Roll 2d6
6 nice. Yeah, you just fucking uh
Yeah, you fucking beast this guy you fucking like it's like the other arc goes over it
but then like you Maria just and you just like
It's like shoot it again in the butthole the butthole on its palm
It's like like fucking like spazzing out in front of Ray William Johnson
like a fucked up dance almost
Go white boy. Yeah, it appreciates that
And now it is
Okay, cool. Yeah. Yeah, you you've you've bloodied it officially. I'll tell you guys
Yeah, that was a clutch move to use tough force. It is now Sullivan's turn. He has to roll a death saving throw. Oh
Okay
All right success, so he's doing okay
He has he has to either succeed three times to stabilize or fail three times to die. So he's doing okay right now
But now it's your turn Ray William Johnson
okay, I I
Look at the hand
Like I said, I think he's dancing. So I'm like damn brother high five
Okay, and so do you hold out your hand for a high? Yeah, I got my hold of my hand for a high five
I'm trying to get a high five me roll a
Roll persuasion with disadvantage because you are fighting it
- As a-- - Fuck.
Alright, well, I'm not even gonna roll a second one.
You said, "Offering your hand to this hand is a slur in its culture."
- It is just so-- - Down low?
(laughter)
Okay. I'll let you try to attack it still, just 'cause that was funny.
- That made me laugh. - Okay.
I'm gonna go for a...
for a Dong Blade attack.
Yeah, you just, like, insult it and then just whiff with the slur.
it and just with the site will be one of the worst terms of my
uh...
but kill me soon so uh...
see you next time buddy
the uh... yeah uh... now
it is the hands turn again
and it is going to try to fuckin stop you
it turns to a fist
to like fuckin bop you
uh... so here goes
it does hit you
does uh...
does thirteen damage
And you are now in the ground like half your body like a bomb like a cordiand down. Yeah
I'm yeah, okay, and
Yeah, and so you're not gonna be able to move
Until you roll a strength saving the best of this game and oh good. Yeah, and
You also might have to deal with some mealworms as well. Uh and now
It is going to fly over to you Patrick Yoda because you've been doing a lot of damage to it. Oh, well
It's gonna walk on its fingers. It doesn't provoke an attack of opportunity from Caleb. Oh, you know what? Thank you
Feel like a bad DM it does
So when a creature moves out of your range and you have a reaction you can use it provokes an attack of opportunity
You can use an attack on it
So for you that means you can use dong blade on it as it's moving on a wrench. Thank you Cameron for keeping me honest
But I'm in the ground
Yeah, but like you got it Caleb. Just do it
Stuck in the ground
No, it's your your your legs you can't move but your arms are totally fucking available brother
All right. It doesn't feel good, but I will do it. I
pen
Okay, you whiff you're just like
Swinging it around it like as it's like going by you
But still not bad, but Patrick Yoda not bad
You know not bad for missing I guess and Patrick Yoda. It's now it's now coming after you and
You see that it's going to try to flick you the way it did solve in the frog
And it misses it just like flicks against the wall of the arena because you're up against the wall and it's like going like this
like
do what I will let you do is run over and try to stabilize Sullivan. Yeah I'm gonna
run over and try to stabilize Sullivan. Okay. That line represents that I moved
over there. Okay I'll move you over. So roll a medicine check. Okay. 19. Okay 19 you
stabilize him. So Sullivan is a Sullivan is stabilized. He's still unconscious
though. But he's not gonna keep dying now. Yeah. And now it is your turn Patrick Yoda.
I'm gonna hit him with the lightning. Do it brother. Why wouldn't I do it?
I'm gonna hit crit one. The lightning just like...
I hit it 22. Okay yeah, yeah okay. Roll 4d8.
48 damage. No stop doing that man, come on.
I heard what you said.
Twenty-six.
Oh!
Shut up.
Just genuinely embarrassed.
I just feel like I'm in middle school.
Describe your kill on the creepy hand.
It's just a normal kill.
Finally, dude.
Finally, we get a normal kill.
I
you should lightning just sort of like
you know
it's not a
uh... is but all just
uh... the guys it's a bit
yet falls flat
but it's it's a mound of shit so it's just like i don't like it
i'm set up a couple inches yeah i was resting on the shit
and you see the announcer go
i don't believe what i'm
seeing
that one the best friends gang as well and and uh...
you know audiences cheering and booing
c rex's fist pumping in marie stain is like going to
like whistling with her
you put your fingers in the mouth to do that whistle
and you guys are just like
bloodied and battered solvent is unconscious
you see the baby
gathers like
you did it
i'll get you guys
whatever you need for my stupid dad
i'd i will get you guys those passes you don't have to worry about that shit
anymore i promise
and uh...
he says uh...
just meet just come back
to the gateway cow tomorrow
you have my word
okay i'll go
and i'll get you those passes
and uh... uh...
yeah he says that to you guys
yeah you guys uh...
walk out of the camera you still going to take a picture of him
the
You know how hmm so your back his back is turned right as
He's walking away. You can do that. But then obviously the disadvantage there is that then so what is it?
Just a little man in a coat
but
You could do it from the front I will here's what I'll say it's it's an arena
There's a lot of commotion like it's it's doable
And I and if you fuck it up, you just have to play it off. You see what I'm saying?
Yeah, okay, but it's up to you cuz yeah you could do should I should I do it and then try to play it off like
I'm retreat taking a victory. Okay, wait, we're gonna
We'll huddle up shit. We're gonna huddle up like we're gonna be taking a victory selfie
Okay, but the camera is facing the other way
Okay, so roll
Okay, I'm trying to think of what to roll here and roll performance check
Do it dude, okay, I got a 45
I've a really I have a bad performance score though. We got this. It's easy if all of us roll. There's no way we lose
Yeah, it looks pretty obviously like you're trying to include him in the frame and he's like no no no no
You can't you can't have me in the frame. Okay, I can't have my dad seen. Come on you. Oh, sorry
You're like our coach for this win. I pour a Gatorade bottle on him.
Oh my god, I'm all sticky and like he's like crying a little bit like a baby.
Just come back to the cow, we can deal with this then, alright?
Alright, I just can't be seen anywhere, okay?
Okay, okay, we'll get you the passes though, okay?
I'm gonna go, I'm gonna go. I'm all fucking sticky now, it's disgusting.
He's just, starts to walk out of there.
Okay
Yeah
So it's a nice try but like I think the method in which you did it is enough that like he's not suspicious
Like if you did it just like trying to sneak a pic. I think that would have been a little bit more obvious
yeah, you see Marie and Rex and
Rex is like boys. That was a hell of a show
Look look Marie and I were gonna get drinks. We meant it will get you guys drinks
You fucking killed it in there the way you took out that hand
They banned me from this because I I tried to play jump rope with one of their spines
but you guys uh, you guys have fucking avenged that for sure you guys are incredible incredible fighters and
Marine says those are my two lovers and their friend and their frog. That's what they're like
Can you guys order me a drink that gets me out of the ground
Everyone laughs
It's the end of a thing.
It's the end of an episode.
[Music]