[♫ "Interior" by Kool & The Gang]
Interior. Shane Dawson maximum security prison for the criminally insane.
Evening.
The scene opens on a tight close-up of a familiar face.
A Yoda who has seen better days.
Face pressed up against the unobtainium bars that keep him from escaping.
Around his head is an Adidas force suppression sweatband.
That keeps him from unleashing hell on the unsuspecting jolly bees who guard his cell.
So, um, yeah, I described you, Patrick Yoda.
My name is Dr. Patrick Yoda.
I'm the first Yoda to ever get a degree in archaeology in prison.
I hate detective work so much.
Too much finding new dead bodies.
And you don't even get to play with them, neither.
I hate it.
I used to accidentally walk on all the dead bodies all the time,
and everyone would get mad at me,
as if the dead body wouldn't still be there after I stepped on it.
You're tampering with evidence! Don't step there! Don't put your hands on that!
Hey buddy, you're tampering with my fucking good time! I'm into old dead
bodies now. Mummies, dinosaurs, mummified dinosaurs, all that crap. I'm the number
one Yoda archaeologist in all of the world and it helps that I'm so small. I
can get into places that other archaeologists can't. Anyway, I only
I only learned archaeology when I was in prison because I was bored and the other guys seemed like they already knew about it
So that's why I did it. I really don't give a shit about anything that I do
I just do it because I'm bored and it seems like it would be fun
The last two years have been a blur really I'm amazed that I remember even half of this stuff
I don't even remember why I'm here something about some guy named Sean McDonald's and a bunch of fucking Jollibee's
I don't fucking care. I just want to see a weird thing
That's what's so great about archaeology. It's just a bunch of old weird stuff
Anyway, I think we're having slop for lunch today and the guy in the cafeteria told me he would sell me some cigarettes if I let
him have mine
So yeah
Patrick Yoda is now mysteriously an archaeologist. He's behind bars
We pan over to another cell where a young who V and crime fighter sits in a windowless room
Diagnosed with Joker disorder a court-sanctioned ball was given to him to toss against his wall
His monkey sits idly in his own smaller room within the room slowly losing oxygen as he rereads in search of lost time
so
Botas
My name is professor blow toss piss
I am a who from whoville and I am known worldwide for my impressive hands-on knowledge of Christmas curios and Arctic artifacts
I uncovered the lost tomb of Fred Claus, stole back the crystal present from Hanukkah bandits,
and watched the third Harold and Kumar movie 18 times.
I was a part of SEAL Team 7, the team that went in after SEAL Team 6 to retrieve Osama
bin Laden's legendary snow globe.
I alternate weeks between spelunking into the Krusty Krab's walk-in freezer to search for
Spongebob's bones, and teaching advanced cultural defilement at Yule University, where I have
never had any inappropriate relationships with any of the ugly students.
The past year or so in prison, I have been trying to play the two rival gangs against
each other by telling them the other one insulted them, but it just made both of them beat me
up twice as much as they would have otherwise.
Also, pet monkey named Patrick.
Okay, cool.
So we have another archaeologist.
He didn't even, doesn't seem like he ever was a detective.
We pay it one final time, much further down the hall, due to complaints from some of the
female guards, to a room made of mirrors, where a computer-hacked demon stares vacantly
at himself while jacking off.
This has completely occupied the demon part of this creature, much to the dismay of his
logical, computer half.
Sup?
You know the drill by now.
I am a computer, attached to the back of a demon.
How do I make that fit the theme you ask? Well, I I guess I'm like a I'm like a sundial or
Like a Mayan sundial
And I guess instead of like a demon I have like some sort of
Like Nazi like you know, it never mind. No, I'm just gonna I'm just gonna stick with the computer thing
Still a computer on a demon's back, but now I'm an archaeology professor and I do adventures and fucking titty fuck my students
God damn, I love college.
These three have been placed in Shane Dawson maximum security prison for the murder of a one
PapiChuco CEO of PapiChuco's TechnoSlime as well as resisting arrest murder of a civilian
breaking and entering in private property
Impersonating a celebrity which has been outlawed since Pete Davidson quote-unquote impersonated former president Travis Scott
and at least three charges of Yoda trafficking.
Their court-appointed lawyer, Alan Iverson, failed to show up for a single
trial, which by default, as per Gun City's Kamala Harris truancy law, means they
receive the maximum sentence.
A cat screeches over the loudspeaker, meaning it's time for dinner at the
Shane Dawson maximum security prison, or to have a conjugal visit. For our three
heroes,
it's their last meal
i think i'm gonna have a conjugal visit
so for your last meal you're gonna have some
some pussy? i'm not eating pussy for dinner. no it's not even pussy
oh not anymore
not when you're done with it. i'm having a conjugal visit with my slop
okay yeah your slop so the slop gets slid under
the under the bars of the jail cell
And what do you do do you just do you go to town on it?
Yeah, yeah, you see somebody like pull a curtain falls over
You can still see through the bars, but there's a like please knock
You're like
Yeah
Okay, cool. What's your last meal blowtoss?
candy cane. You had a candy cane? Yeah. Yeah, so your windowless room is unsealed and a giant
candy cane is brought in and a smaller one is brought in for your monkey as well. I didn't
want a big one. Take this back. Okay, boss. Takes it back. Do I get a small one though? Yeah,
give me five minutes. You, Ray William Johnson, what's your final meal? Did the demon pick or
- Who did the computer pick?
- The key to my cell.
(laughing)
You see one of the Jollibee's, says,
"Nice try man, but it's not gonna work this time."
- Alright, fine.
- You almost got me last time.
- Okay, chips.
- Okay, fine.
What kind of chips?
- Kettle cooked jalapeno chips.
- We don't, that's so specific.
- This is the worst prison ever.
- It's not great.
- Oh, fuck.
- You can see how much I get paid.
- Alphabet soup?
we got that actually oh no I regret it
comes look as you're handed your last
meals once you finish eating them a
teleporter beam like appears in each of
yourselves and you hear a voice over you
hear first you hear why stop Shane and
then you hear please step in here and
then you hear a voice a please step in
here for your execution sponsored by Uniqlo. I jump in. Okay you jump in? Yeah.
I just kind of... But I hold my breath. I'm not done. I have a feeling that's gonna pay off.
I am smoking a cigarette and the slop is also smoking a cigarette and we're kind
of in the bunk beds together. If you do not step into your execution beam
sponsored by Uniqlo the beam will come to you. And I say to the slop, I turn to
the slap and I go, "Was that good enough? Was that as good for you as it was for me?"
"Yeah man, it was pretty good. Might as well sound like Meerod."
"I guess so, yeah."
Alright, that's all I needed to hear. And then I jumped down the bunk beds, but for me, because I'm a Yoda, it's so big.
Yeah, sure.
I jump down and as I'm jumping down I go, "BRAAAA!"
[laughter]
Just like, both your legs.
Right at the beginning.
You fall into the beam of screaming.
Blowtoss, do you go in?
- I throw my monkey in first, just to see what happens.
(monkey screeches)
- And just flies in there.
- Yeah, fuck it.
- You don't see it yet.
- I don't even wait to see what happens.
- Your execution will be in a massive coliseum,
filmed live in front of millions
on the 24-hour execution channel.
You all have the coveted 805 to 807 spot,
the primus of prime time.
Do you guys have any last words before I kill you?
school sucks I love college and hate all the party or I hate college but love all
the parties that guy took both of my ideas
for appearing in a Coliseum but but but but but rather than that you teleport
into a sparse gray room which you recognize immediately to be the
warden's office the warden Barney the dinosaur looks up from his desk and
greets you might as well just throw him in there he's got to be in there guys
that would he I didn't look it up before this I'm Barney I'm Barney have you
enjoyed your time in prison so much yes behind Barney's been the best two years
of my life is a strange and slender Anglican gentleman dressed to the nines
in new Victorian garb. It's N-E-U, Victorian. Imagine Jonathan Davis style
dreads with black patchwork pants topped with a long Victorian coat with flame
decals, skull cufflinks, buckled like scaly like dragon scale boots and a
completely black monocle.
You're an eyepatch really.
Well it seems you have lucked out.
I uh this gentleman over here has decided that he has enough money to release you
thank you so much Jamiroquai my name's not Jamiroquai well that's what I'm
gonna call you well I'll take it my name is Leo the
collector and thanks to my considerable wealth and influence you three are
conditionally pardoned of your crimes and free to live your lives in gun City
but those conditions for this I can explain on the way over to my face
except well that's good but you sure you sure you don't want to hear I'm just
looking at something on the other wall over to my floating island in the sky
would you like to join me it's either that or you will be executed I have to
make that sort of clear it would be crazy if you chose execution now that I think
about it as a DM I shouldn't have given you three that that option can we take a
few years to think about it and just like Jill outside the jail require what
funniest outcome oh if we do that it could be a ghost campaign and I'd have
to come up with it out of nowhere
the only reason I'm not saying you don't have a map for heaven
drawn also you're actually in my apartment and I'm afraid you'll hit me
yes I accept your offer what what kind of what what is on your island my island
has anything you need all right well hey I'm sold sort of figure of speech what
do you need do you need like insulin we have that just checking why are you
asking him why you asking me about that I just meant like things you wouldn't
No, it's you specifically
Patrick Yoda was canon, you know looks like
What oh, I'm sorry, that's must be quite difficult. I'm actually not I just wanted to see what you would say
Well, you see that I'm quite polite. I won't be so polite. I think I don't trust you. No, that's fair
Hey guys, you got to see this. There's a picture of a kitten hanging on to a branch and it says hang in there
Oh my god. You see Barney walk over to that.
Yes, that was my favorite painting that my niece drew for me.
Pull the painting off the wall.
We're gonna- wait, boys! We're escaping this goddamn place.
Come on, get some spoons!
Wait, I- can I take Barney's suit off?
Now that we're not in jail anymore.
You try to grab Barney...
And it's just- it's his neck and his head and it's everything.
Okay, sorry, I thought it might be a costume.
No, that happens all the time. Normally I would have you killed, but again, this guy paid me a lot of money.
Okay, you know what? I just got one question about his island.
Sure.
What do you do on there? Do you do weird sex stuff on there, or do you just kind of have it there for like bass fishing or something?
No. No.
Yeah, then I'm not going.
I mean...
Do you have a statue to Moloch?
No.
Hey, no for me.
Well, you know what look I can't say looking at your weird shoes
And I think that maybe your island might have some crazy sex stuff for me, so I'm gonna go well
I can't deny that people have come to my island and have done things and I've looked the other way so if you hold on
Legal sex stuff that's crazy. Yes, of course let me make that clarification on this podcast, okay?
well then
Can we can we go?
So yeah you uh yeah you all follow Leo the Collector out of the the the Warden's
office down the hall up the stairs to a roof where you see his giant airship that
looks like like a British wooden galleon ship from like the 1700s you see him take
out a remote and press it and like a *creak* like a door opens up that even though it's
like looks like it's made of wood you can quickly assess that it's just designed to
look like that.
That's a Wii!
Oh my god he's got the wooden Wii!
I do have a Wii if you'd like to see one.
They're quite great.
I collect all manner of old consoles, Wiis, PS7s, anything you could imagine.
Do you have the N-Gage?
The N-Gage escapes my grasp yet again.
One day, one day.
I like this one, he knows what the end gauge is.
So yeah, you load onto his boat, it's lush, there's leather and velvet and all those types
of materials you use when you describe lush things.
First thing I do is fuck that couch.
Okay.
Roll a performance check.
Do the first roll of the campaign.
As if he could fuck a couch again.
Yeah, absolutely.
with the same respect you all are 12 at your performance so that's plus 3 plus
3 15 you fucking good yes you roll perception check quickly 3 mm no never
mind what a funny joke about your couch moan but you don't hear it so it's just
a regular kids regular couch yeah yeah so you fuck the couch Leo quickly like
locks down that room, like, finds a way to do that.
You fly for probably about, like, a little under an hour
to a, like, massive island in the sky.
And so some stuff you guys would perhaps know
about part of the world of Gun City
is that there are very, very few people
who can afford to have an island in the sky.
You have to be so astronomically rich.
So he, and it's not just an island in the sky
that, like, just has his mansion.
you pull up to it you see a massive mansion and you see like another
building that you can't quite make out what it is yet you see what is clearly a
private school a hospital like you see that he has his own sort of town here
and you pull in the ship pulls in you see the island like makes the same noise
one of the only noises I have for doors opening opens up and like the island
like it looks like rock on the bottom of it like a floating island opens up and
lets the ship in and it sort of situates itself in there and you file out of
there and you're in this like massive hangar you see all these Jollibee
attendants running around and like helping make things work and they say
"Well welcome back Master Leo!" "Well thank you, thank you Jollibee." "And these are
your servants?" "They are..." "You have slaves?" "No, no I do not have slaves." "But they called you
Master." "Yeah they said Master." "Master is just a formal title in England."
there what the hell is England? Sky England! Is that what this place is? Well it had a
different name but now it is. First thing first I'm gonna ask one of your slaves
to get me Apollo back. Oh what excuse me? From Jollibee. Oh sure I'm not gonna say
slave one even though that was the first thought. Jollibee come! Hello can you get
whatever it is he said? Apollo back. Apollo back. It's not that hard to pronounce.
I just haven't heard. I just personally haven't heard of it before that's all.
Brown shrimp spaghetti. Patrick I got it. Do you want to do a hungry hamster all over again?
Patrick's favorite thing to do is whenever Patches starts describing
something that's happening Patrick goes okay first things first
yeah that Jollibee runs off to get it he brings it back Apollo back what is it
what is it describe Paul back to me so I know seafood pasta yeah it's like a
brown sauce with like vermicelli pasta brown thing you get a plate of poop and
yeah no you get you get the you get it and it tastes like nothing you've had
before so you know Gun City doesn't have...
Oh my god!
The couch sneezes somewhere.
The food in Gun City, you know, it's on planet E-Bomb. It's sourced on planet E-Bomb.
It's not the best food in the world. It doesn't taste like how Jollibee's food
tastes in our time. But this swears, if you could imagine a time like 2020 and
and you ate some of Jollibee's food. This tastes like it.
This is amazing! Oh my fucking god!
Yes, of course. The finest cuisine in all.
Right this way, please.
Can we just stay? I don't care what you need us for.
Can we just stay here?
Alright, we're leaving him behind.
You certainly can for a time, but...
I'm your new slave and I'll do whatever you want.
Well, all I need you three to do is try...
I'm a better slave than him.
Well...
I would be way better.
I'm like the number one slave in the world.
I don't care what happens.
There's enough of me to go around to have you as slaves.
Look, let's just first come with me to my mansion, come to my chambers, and we will...
No, I saw that face. The podcast can't hear it.
It's not sex. I'm just English. We just all sound like monsters.
What kind of slave do you take me for?
And yeah, he walks you out of the hangar.
You walk outside the hangar and into this...
Just clearly you look around, you can see there's like a biodome
and like an electric fence around the island.
Like massive towers that are like protecting it.
And the biodome keeps in this perpetual foggy London weather.
- That he loves. - It keeps in Pauley Shore and Billy Baldwin.
Yeah.
And you guys walk into his mansion and a Jolly B greets you there, of course.
Um, and it's as big as you can imagine, it's as amazing as you can imagine, but what you
really notice that makes this mansion different from other mansions is the amount of artifacts
that are everywhere.
And like, artifacts that you guys have heard of.
Some of them you know of and you didn't know who owned it, but you knew somebody did.
Some of them you've heard of in legend, but never seen them before.
You see Wii's, you see, uh, you see like, uh, SNES.
You see...
That's an artifact.
Yeah, oh yeah.
You see Panasonic televisions, you see Sony Walkmans, you see like all these famous artifacts
in Gun City lore that you've heard of on Earth but like have never really seen.
And as he walks you up the spiral staircase to his chambers, the door behind him closes
and he locks it.
he says, "It's only a precaution, I promise. I need to talk to you all about something."
And he starts spinning around a globe, but it's a cube, and it's something you've also
heard of. And he says, "He's got the cube globe, you guys. Holy fucking shit, you guys."
This guy loves items. "Oh my god."
"So, I... we need to talk briefly. I have something interesting I need to tell you all
about. I'm sure I don't need to tell you all this, you're three of the most
renowned archaeologists / adventurers / professors on the planet.
Oh yeah. I bat my eyelashes at him. On my eyelids it says "love you".
That's from the first Indiana Jones.
But before earthlings arrived on planet E-Bomb, there were many a civilization.
but none as storied or has lost the time as the Tamagotchi people. Thought of as
almost mystical in nature, recent discoveries have been made that suggest
they do indeed exist. I believe some of you, one of you, have written papers on
this. It was me, it was also me. I did. All three of you wrote, only two of you wrote. I just did
whatever they were doing, I don't know if it was Tamagotchis or whatever the
hell that's it there is a ton of got you playing farm bill bro don't tell them
about that I spent you know what I'll say it I spent $20 on the adventure
capitalist do you remember that game oh yeah I do that fucking cookies like a
cookie clicker yeah no yeah I spent $20 on that you know no I haven't touched it
in two years but I did open it the other you see like the scene in those it's
just frozen as like that said there isn't a ton of scholarship on it but you
You know that the Tamagotchi people were famous for being really needy, and much of their
infrastructure helped sort of lay the groundwork for many of the smaller city-states outside
of Gunn City and on the rest of planet E-Bomb.
Like Palestine?
Like Palestine, yes.
Yeah, baby!
You caught me!
That's my real character!
Um, but the most...
That's the only reason I asked.
The thing that I have been...
I have been collecting for years now.
After I made my money doing this than the other thing.
I have been collecting for many years.
And...
The treasure that has eluded me,
besides the end gauge,
is another treasure.
That I have been laughed out of all types of collectors circles,
insisting that it is real.
But I know it is.
And all three of you,
of you roll a history check with advantage to see if you know where it is.
16.
Roll again.
15.
Roll a d20 though.
Is this not a d20?
No.
Oh, it's a d12.
I don't even know what that roll was.
Hold on.
Oh.
This is insane.
This is a disaster.
13.
Or no, 12.
You guys can move this table closer to you.
I don't need it.
Shut up.
closer to you I figured my 16 okay that's pretty mine was 12 I got a 1 yeah you
didn't pay attention yeah to this part of the I already said I didn't know yeah
yeah yeah you're you're completely backed up based on the rolls what did you get
your eyes 12 you know anything above a 10 knows what this this is I'm playing
with a thread in my wall as you see Leo the collector talking about this mystical
treasure that's allegedly connected to the Tamagotchi people the two of you
know exactly what he's talking about and the second he says it you also say it at
the exact same time. The N-word Pass. Chocolate chips. No? I knew you two would be familiar.
I'm very familiar, yes. The mystical N-word Pass. He's maybe a little bit too
familiar. I don't know. The Tamagotchi people apparently spent hundreds of years
developing the correct technology and magics to create an actual n-word pass.
Do you understand the implications of this? Don't explain what the implications are.
Caleb Pitt. I understand them and I'm worried that we might get too far into
the implications during this campaign. I'll tell you what, that is up to you. And
And it's a different N-word, right?
Moving on!
It's not the one worth thinking?
Nutella? No!
I thought it was a word for...
Tamagotchis.
After Papa...
After Papi-chuco...
Can I say it?
There was a great gap in power over the last two years.
of control of the city. I'm not saying I can fill that same void, you know, my
businesses wouldn't certainly be able to fulfill such a thing, but if I have the
N-word pass, if we, three of us, four of us, you too Patrick, have the N-word pass,
we might be able to do a lot of good. And the worst part is there are
also other people going after it, and I know this for a fact because I have to
admit that I did consult archaeologist Pennsylvania Jim you guys would know
Pennsylvania Jim. FUCK! Yes he is all three of your rivals. Scott! I fucking hate that guy. He's so sexy but it sucks.
yeah his shirts always unbuttoned the correct way god damn it yeah he has it
buttoned at the top but he leaves two buttons at the bottom and his stomach
kanks out his stomach is so good cuz beauty standards and ebombs world are
different than Earth's yeah that's unfortunately true but yeah you would
know Pennsylvania gym is famous for saying stuff like Dwight what are you
doing
Pam, uh, look I just want to see your pussy and things like that.
Um, so and I love to see-
Yeah, he stole Pam from Ray William Johnson.
That's right.
But I'm gonna get her back.
Back when he was going by Roy William Johnson.
[Laughter]
Now, Pennsylvania Jim, look, you three were in prison.
I felt the urge, I felt the need to know more about it.
So I hired him for some time.
All he could do was translate some of the writings that I had discovered and he couldn't quite narrow down the location of the N-word pass.
But there is an artifact that will tell us where it is.
And it will luckily be at an auction that I'm holding tomorrow evening.
The auction is going to be hosting about seven to twelve objects.
Probably closer to seven.
Looking at my notes, how many jokes did I write? Seven.
So, um...
And those... I found out that that's the appropriate auction number according to Google's...
- Seven? - Seven to twelve.
- It's a little light, I feel like. - I thought it was light, but I feel...
I don't know who that advice is for.
I feel like we could break a record for longest auction pretty easily.
Yeah, I'm excited for that.
- Twenty. - Um...
Uh, so...
Leo goes on, he says, "This auction time hosting will be in the events building."
And he points, and you see outside the window that that building you saw
is like a building he has for where he holds events.
It just looks like the Pokemon Stadium.
It looks like Pokemon Stadium.
Now it, now it...
I have like a description for it.
Oh, never mind.
On the outside it looks like Pokemon Stadium, but then...
Yeah.
And
He says tomorrow night there will be an auction
it's we where there will be seven artifacts up for grabs and
The last one will be the floppy disk that holds
Del Isola de penguin
which apparently has within it the location of
if not
The temple where it the inward pass exists at least a clue to where the temple is
that's of course based on some research and then some things that the Pennsylvania gym said but I
Need that artifact tomorrow night the penguin of doom the temple of two penguin of doom
Wow, that's right. I
Just I
I'm just guessing on the Spanish translation but well I mean you you do
know that's the name of the campaign oh I didn't know that when he says the
temple of the penguin of doom I just fall over backwards onto my ass yeah yeah
good I pick him back up I fall over again I keep trying to pick him back up
and he keeps you guys over doing that while Leo keeps talk it turns it turns
into sex yeah that's the thing about Patrick Yoda this campaign he's a
Casanova that's good there will be some dames so I'm looking forward to it
the Leo continues he says the auction tomorrow night will be held in my
events area there will be other wealthy collectors there of course but Kevin
Garnet. Kevin Garnet. Yeah, a hundred percent now he's gonna be there. I can't believe I
didn't even think of that. I wonder what he's gonna be doing. Um, so, um, but, um, I
will, I will be in my mansion watching on my viddy screens and I'll have a
representative there, one who is a top auctioneer and not only that, a brilliant
collector in his own right Sullivan and out from like within a closet come
Sullivan the frog dress in his typical dandy outfit but he swaps the bowler hat
for a classic Indiana Jones hat and new slave just dropped hi boss nice to see
you hey who's that I'm somebody I want to be best friends with I'm Sullivan well
hot dog that'd be real nice what's up you stupid motherfucker oh no I just look
into my eyes and I go he's our slave now intense deja vu to being emotionally
abused who knows anyway you suck you pussy you're my best friend Sullivan the
frog will be able to will be my representative at the auction. Your job
is to not only protect all the artifacts at the auction and to ensure that
Sullivan gets the the artifact that I want, the floppy disk, your job is also
to... hmm I guess those are the only two jobs. What else was I thinking of when I
started this sentence? Now... have fun. Have fun! Hey man, take this. I hand him a Xanax.
"Thanks brother" and he takes his, and he thinks you're black, and he takes his
and he takes his annex, he says "Now I prepared the quarters for all three of
you. You can stay here for the night or make yourselves welcome,
explore my island, but tomorrow evening will be the night of the auction. We'll
meet in the events area around 830 p.m. You'll meet and greet, there'll be some
cocktail hour afterwards starting at promptly 9 p.m. will be the auction and
from 9 to 950 the auction will go on and approximately 950 the floppy disk
Adelie's all of the penguin shall be up for grabs at which point you're raising
your hand Patrick you're a can we push can we push the auction back a little
bit I would the fuck what do you have I have plans you just got out of we didn't
We thought we were getting it.
I made plans with the couch.
Are you streaming with K-Zone again, Patrick?
To do what?
We were going to go see Uncut Gems.
Put the couch in your room.
Well, that solves everything.
Okay, good.
Well, I don't want that couch in my ship anymore.
I'll tell you that much.
Hey, I don't blame you.
Sullivan, would you
show these gentlemen to their quarters?
Yeah sure okay and Sullivan leaves you guys each year like three separate I'm
walking behind Sullivan I'm just stepping on his heels.
Just flat tiring. I'm spitting on the back of his head.
I keep putting dollars into his pocket.
He keeps thinking I'm pickpocketing him but I'm actually being very nice.
I'm spitting on him and telling him, I'm pissing on him and actually telling him it's raining.
well it sure it sure is rainy and inconvenient but wealthy out here today
all right well these three are your rooms these were gestures are all like
three adjacent rooms similar to your like cells you just pan down oh I was
thinking we would all stay in the same room if you if you certainly if you want
to slumber party again I have plans you try to do my voice I'm not well I mean
we don't think you guys can do together well I mean Sullivan clearly I guess
I'll stay in my own room a bit of a stickler for you know a slave I love to
follow the rules so I well I do but that's not the point
um yeah so yeah you certainly can go into a room and spill beer again at your
apartment you can you can go into a the same room together and Sullivan like
like goes underneath the bed and like pulls like a couple of like like levers
and configurations in the beds are the same noise becomes like a triple bunk
bed and which one do I get Sullivan opens a closet and you hear him like pull a
a lever and he turns you patches in there if you want it and buddy I'm
already got it's gross and he he says if you guys need anything like you know
glass of water or anything at all.
It's just you get me another.
Yeah maybe you sing us a sleepy time song.
warden always did oh well what sound would you like to hear just pick a song
Jesus Christ okay sorry
steve and knocked hi league and knocked why do I know I'm sorry I knew that was
German I mean I knew I just I didn't know why that was the first thought that
came to my mind I'm really sorry I did choir um in Germany so yeah and he sings
to you in perfect German nice a silent night as a three of you slowly drift off
to sleep and then Patrick at around 2 27 a.m. gets up sort of looks around and
goes to fuck the couch in the closet yeah that's fine with me two of you roll
roll perception though to see if he actually roll Constitution saving throw
to see if he wakes you up oh that's a crit one he wakes you up you hear
everything I'm going oh yeah here every you here cuz you got a crit one you hear
like a darker Eldridge thing about sex that you didn't know about yeah he hears
just like everything in a regular way yeah wait tell me when I hear I hear
Patrick's penis whistling.
As it moves.
So you guys all, you get a great night's sleep.
And you
wake up next morning
Jollibee's attend to your
every need throughout the day.
Is a Jollibee washing my feet?
They are! They are washing your feet.
They're giving you back rubs.
They are kissing you
when you want to be kissed.
I'm kissing them back.
You're kissing them back.
back surprise yeah they're feeding you hollow back surprise while you're tied
by your ankles from the ceiling because that's what you like and they are weird
normal for a Yoda I regret sharing a room with you and we didn't have to share
rooms as the evening I'm trying to fix this approach it I mean you guys can also
walk around the I should give you this time yeah okay so so the island has I'll
I'll give you so so so what's on the island Leo's New England in the sky has
an event center he has his mansion he has a shopping center that's but with an RE
of course he has a hospital a private school I'm in the helipad or like like a
hangar where you guys came in from that's sort of a the broad strokes of
Leo's Island it's about you know I don't know like like two mile by two mile it's
a huge-ass island. Matt has been holding his hand up to ask questions which is
actually such a much better system. Yeah. Okay what do I have to roll to go
into the hospital and steal all the fentanyl? That's what I was gonna do!
Okay, me and Cameron are going on a mission. I was gonna say I was gonna go in the
hospital and look in all the cabinets and also in all the patients
pockets. That's gonna be a number of rolls. So me and Cameron are gonna go,
you're gonna look I'll look in the pockets I'm gonna look in the cabinet I'm
hitting the gym in the gym okay yeah there is a gym in the shopping center
awesome so well first first I have to see if they're gonna be able to steal
fentanyl whatever I guess nobody cares it'll be whatever you tell us me no
slime fentanyl okay right so you guys walk into the hospital it's like
state-of-the-art hospital meant for Leo and any of his guests who come visit him
They have a Wii in the lobby.
They have a Wii in the lobby and they have a Wii U in the garbage.
Oh my god.
Because it sucks.
Let's go!
Yes!
And yeah, so you guys walk in, you see a beautiful Jollibee nurse receptionist.
It's a nurse joy Jollibee.
Woman kind of thing behind the desk.
Says, "Welcome to the Jollibee..."
Nope.
Can't let that be canon.
to Leo's hospital how may I help you I am actually I'm the brother of all of the
patients so I just had to visit them roll the seven check with I guess just
it's gonna be really hard to win this oops what is that 12 plus minus one I'm
telling you now was gonna be a crit 20 for her to believe that you were the
brother of everyone in here okay but I am the brother of one of them okay I was
lying before but... Alright, roll, roll, roll deception with disadvantage now that you've
said something crazy. Oh, that's a nat 1? Yeah, she's just like, "hmm, okay."
Leo said I could walk around. Roll, roll deception with disadvantage only because
he just did all that. It's an 11. Alright, you'll add your disadvantage and you can
roll again. Okay, what's my disadvantage? Your deception. Oh, deception. It's plus
three okay so roll one more time and we'll take the lower number nice all
right so 14 she says she says let's actually have a roll insight instead of
just me saying shit I'd much rather prefer you saying shit yeah she says uh
she says okay yeah sure what's your brother's name
Leo. Wait what? No, there's no brother in this situation. He just said Leo. I said Leo said I could walk around.
Oh sorry, I thought, I thought, no my bad, as a DM. That's also a great answer.
Yeah she says, now she has to know, she has to be the Leo's brother. If you're Leo's guest, please walk around, just don't interfere with too many of the patients.
and a lot of them are trying to get some rest.
I just follow behind Patrick, even though I'm definitely not allowed to.
Yeah, she assumes you're with him.
He's Leo's brother too.
No, he seems...
Sorry, I'm actually here because I have a medical condition where I lie to nurses.
So I'm really sorry about that.
And I can tell that's a lie, so please go.
[Laughter]
all right so first room we hit you guys are in the hospital you're walking around
we hit is somebody who's in a full body cast so I know there's something good in
their medicine in the middle of their heist cut to ten seconds yeah let's get
let's do it three plates yeah roll roll yeah so you go into this gym and it is
it is like it is a it has like CrossFit it has cyber CrossFit that's new I do
do that yeah you know no I have to come up with it let's do it that shits gay
okay everybody who does it is gay you have to be gay I guess I do it then do
it everyone's gay in there and it's it's fine I'm not making a joke about it and
you're all doing cyber CrossFit you're doing like so imagine doing like a
intense high-intensity workouts with the ropes and shit but uh it said the ropes
are lasers and yeah there's a there's like a it's like a you've been to um
Disney you know those movies where you're in the seat in the screen so it's
like the screen is like showing like a like a 4d movie yeah it's like a 4d
movie that you're experiencing there's like you're watching back to the future
Future 9 and it's like you're like you are Marty McFly.
You are trying to change age of consent laws in the United States in the year 2005 and
like there's just like lasers going by you as you're trying to work out.
Roll strength check.
Just straight strength.
So just add your strength.
Uh, six.
Okay.
Yeah.
You get pretty winded from this workout.
Not strong.
Yeah.
It's pretty hard to do this.
Your demon is like, okay, like trying to like work out and fitness is about the
journey not the results and you see a guy come and you go that's right I'm the
instructor and also I'm in an anime I guess is the voice I chose keep going
you got this yeah all right that's another gym there so we cut back I'm I'm
I'm bent over I'm bent over the guy in a full body cast and the place where his
pocket would be I've bored a hole using a pen by spinning it between my fingers
And I'm sticking my finger into the hole and wiggling it around trying to feel if there's anything in his pocket under the cast
You're gonna roll stealth check. I mean, there's not no I don't care if he notices. No, I mean just okay
I see any staff. Okay, I mean like I don't care about that
There's not that much of a chance nurses go on rotation. You're fine. Okay, you gotta get 23, I think yeah
No, yeah, I got a 23. Yeah, I think okay, so I'm in the medicine cabinet
Does he have wait does he have anything in his pocket? Oh?
Yeah, that's a good question. Yeah. He does he has
He has keys to a Volkswagen Jetta I
Try to I try to pull them out through the hole
But they don't fit and I just rip a giant chunk of his cast off of his body without him. No
Yeah, it's all fine. He's had a full body. Yeah completely passed out
Yeah, you get keys for that though. Those are technically an artifact see maybe you can sell them
but yeah what are you doing? What are you doing, Pascado?
You're just rolling and not telling me what you're doing.
What I got, 12? But I don't know what you're doing!
I'll tell you after.
I've opened... Alright, so I'm in the medicine cabinet. Yeah, you are.
I'm in the medicine cabinet. I guess you kind of mentioned that earlier.
So I decided that my role determines what I find.
and I should have said that I was my favorite part about this is that Patrick
is the dungeon master yeah my favorite parts about playing one of those it's
collaboration you know yeah reads exactly a breed we're both the dungeon
master yeah we have both of peas yeah name beginning of our name but uh so I
yeah so what do you find I'm in the I'm in the what do I add to that so it's a
15? I guess investigation. Okay. Oh cool so that is a 17. 17 okay wow yeah you find
some like choice techno slime pills. Oh fuck yeah so I just pocket those
immediately. Yeah so add to your inventory five more techno slime refills and I
guess I guess if they're a first-time listeners I should have said this maybe
Yeah, explain techno slime. So techno slime is sort of the catch-all
Opium for the masses in the world of gun city and
Everybody has it everybody takes it to some extent. It's sort of like Adderall if you're a rich kid
Everyone's doing it and it gives you a little bit of an advantage, but there's a chance you can get addicted to it
So there's an addiction system
But they need techno slime to cast like cast quote-unquote spells, but basically do special abilities
But they need to refill it and every time they do there's a chance they can get addicted and so we'll see that addiction system
Throughout this campaign or this arc I should say
All right, and yeah you find that both of you roll a perception check
So it's dirty 20. Yeah, hmm
10 plus
I got an 18.
Okay.
Yeah, you both notice that like if you stay in here for much
longer, there are nurses that are going to come in and check
on this guy.
Yeah, I mean, I hop on camera and shoulders and walk away.
Yeah.
Yeah, you get the sense of the rotations kind of coming up.
Yes.
You guys start walking away.
You walk out of there.
There's now just a taller Yoda walking out of the hospital.
You make it out of there.
Yeah, you're still in the shopping center, Ray William
Johnson's anything else you want to do?
There's I mean name something.
I'll let you know if it's there.
It's that kind of place.
I'm going to Brookstone.
shit all right there's a brookstone yeah what do you want to do with the
brookstone I'm getting a massage for free yes yeah you go to the brookstone there
is a a massage chair there ready for you to go yeah I'm like pretending to the
person who was working there I'm like I'm seriously considering buying this
Yeah, sure.
Alright dude, that's great.
I've really been thinking about spending...
I've really been thinking about spending $180...
I wanna go to the mall should Roll Deception.
I'm a massage here right now.
The mall is a place where you Roll Deception.
14.
Yeah, you see the sales rep, he's like, "Oh, sick! Great!"
Yeah, no, dude, you're gonna get a sweet commission on this.
No, I really, my quote has been down last quarter.
Dude, you're gonna get like 15 bucks super soon.
like 15 bucks super soon. Let me just let me just check, you
know, I'm like halfway through the massage. Let me just see how
it ends, you know, and then I'll commit. That's a good one. It's
a good choice, right? It's a good one, but I will do that for
you. I mean, just kidding.
It's a kind of chair to that like has like a slot for your
PC tower. So your computer is like massage.
Seriously perfect for my body. Wow. No, I'm really thinking of buying this
It's funny like it's your PC or tower goes into like a slot. That's like cooled. So your PC is
Yeah, it's like liquid cooling sort of zone
Yeah, and then I just wait for him to look the other way and I just run out of the store
Roll a stealth check. I'm so stealthy. This is see if this poor guy news easy for me, dude
Six
He's like, oh chip. Okay, man. Enjoy being a slave. See you buddy. Oh
Man I hate being a slave and yeah, we cut away from that and
Yeah, you guys sort of spent the day
stealing drugs from a hospital
stealing the hearts of salesmen and fucking up at the gym and
Starting to get around dusk. And so you head back to Leo's mansion and
You walk in there you go to Leo's study or his chamber or whatever the fuck and you see him there
He says it's almost time for the the auction so head over to the event center
Bring Sullivan with you and be on the lookout
I I've recently received some intel from some of my security detail that there are people who might be trying to steal some of the
artifacts that are on display
And I would assume that the floppy disk that can holy shit
That contains...
In fact, Stevia did.
Sorry.
Yeah, Stevia gets you.
Really?
That contains the, uh, uh, Isola de la Penguin.
Uh, is that what I said?
Might be there.
They might be stealing that one in particular.
That one that we need to know where to go next.
Did everybody also get the Apple News notification?
I think I did.
I guess so.
Or is it Twitch?
It was Twitch.
Is Jubio?
Jubio's live.
Shout out to Jubio.
- Yeah, we all got the notification.
- I see, that's huge.
- Yeah, and Sullivan the Frog sort of comes up to you all
and says, "All right, so it's about 8.15 now,
"so we walk over there, we'll get there by 8.30,
"just in time for the cocktail hour.
"They're gonna have those little shrimp things."
- Shrimp.
- Shrimp cocktail?
- It's different, it's different than just shrimp,
and I didn't hear what the other--
- I said shrimp cocktail.
Oh, perhaps, but I didn't see that.
What did you say?
Shrimp at Touffee.
Shrimp, bottle, box, or brides?
Definitely not, just 'cause I don't know what that is.
Small pieces of shrimp.
Small pieces, he might.
I'm sorry, I said shrimp, I guess.
He walks out and you follow him.
Coconut shrimp?
I'm listing off new types of shrimp to him.
Even though I don't know--
You're just doing the bubba gup.
Even though I don't know where we're going,
I walk in front of him to assert dominance.
(laughing)
yeah you keep like walking towards another I'm going down any any alley that
I see he tries to guide you it's this way I know where I'm going
ok ok and he knows I know and ok and yeah you guys end up at the event place
and you see the event the event center Leo's event center and it's like a place
that you see that it's like a concert hall right now it looks like a concert
Hall and when you see a Jollibee as you guys walk in you're the first people to
arrive pull lever and you watch and watch it all like sort of morph into now
like an auction house like there's a large atrium in the center a balcony a
balcony sort of like on the in like the on the overlooking sort of the the
center like a skylight now as well and like sort of chairs that are like kind
of like fold out looking chairs but like kind of a little bit nicer and then like
little stage. Men in black chairs? Men in black, I don't know whether there's a men in black.
Just say yes. And I don't know why I asked, that was so stupid. Why would I do that to you?
How long you been doing this? He says that and you're just asking questions.
No go ahead, elaborate. Please elaborate Patrick. I'm sure that won't derail us.
Yeah, so it's a center that it's a concert hall, a circus tent,
whatever the needs of the occasion, except a quinceanera because of a pending lawsuit.
The way it is currently configured, it's like a large open atrium in the main area.
There's a skylight up top, a balcony and circles the whole of the main area.
I said that already. And on the ground level, there's also like a large hallway.
So there's like a main area in the center and then like several doors.
And if you go out there, there's like a long hallway that sort of also
encapsulates it. On the outside it looks like Pokemon Stadium though. Some of the
rooms off that hallway are devoted to kitchen and staff. Some of them are
like bathrooms and some of them are private gathering rooms and one of them
is a storage for some of the artifacts that are gonna be on display.
Okay. Who's in charge of the auction? Me. The auctioneer is his name. Okay. Can I
walk up to the auctioneer? Yeah sure you walk up to this sort of... How tall is the
auctioneer can you hold on he's about five nine okay and he's uh he's sort of
out he's dressed in like a tux he looks like a yeah I'm still in prison
Leo laid out for you guys like fancy clothes I did not change I'm wearing
black and white stripes and a black V and Johnny Cash concert.
I took a sharpie and I drew a tuxedo on my prison uniform.
There was a tux in front of you and you were just like, "Nah."
I looked at it and I looked at it just for reference because I thought that was really nice.
While I was at the gym I flexed too hard and I ripped the entire outfit off and I'm naked.
You were wearing a tuxedo at the gym.
Yeah, and I'm naked now.
That explains your role, yeah.
Yeah, you're, you know, you're like, you look like a Chippendales dancer.
Yeah, I'm naked but like a Winnie the Pooh is naked.
Yeah, that's right.
It's you and Sullivan.
It's cute.
It's very cute.
Sullivan sees that and he's like, "Oh, hello fellow travelers."
Shut the fuck up.
Okay.
And uh...
Don't talk to my friend like that.
So you go up to the auctioneer.
I go up to the auctioneer and I hold up the Volkswagen car keys and I say, "Can I sell
this?"
Oh, let me...
Oh wow.
Can I sell this?
Well, yes you could but don't think at this auction you could.
Why not?
What the fuck is wrong with this guy?
I have a sinus infection.
Oh, alright, I bet you do, yeah.
Bitch. And that Volkswagen GTK. These would be excellent for-
We have all the items are frozen as it stands. We can't add any more.
I hid it with my freeze ray.
You-
You don't have a freeze ray.
Whaaaaat?
I just got a freeze ray.
So, perhaps for another auction we could-
Okay, I don't want to wait though, so just put it up there.
it up there I need money now I just want roll a persuasion check okay
Oh No seven he says I'm sorry sir and while you do look as sticks and like a
distinguished guest with those black and white stripes I should be sarcastic
right now I could have you thrown out of here I'm rolling rolled inside check to
see if he's being sarcastic.
Uh... 15.
He's not, he's just sort of using it to fault answer.
Can I roll to say that he's selling them for me?
You can roll a deception check.
Okay.
But also, what's your goal?
Well, my prison jumpsuit has a tuxedo drawn on it, so I'm hoping that tricks him.
Into what?
I'm gonna have him roll an insight to see if he can tell it's drawn on.
all right I'm gonna roll deception 18 he can absolutely tell you're actually
drawn on and then so but 18 plus 3 okay yeah so he he definitely believes that
you are selling the Jetta for him for you yeah but he does not think that's a
tuxedo are the are the guests for the auction here yet they're gonna be
trickling in oh yes I should mention that actually good call so something to
note about this auction. I'll be keeping track of everything you do after this
weird interaction with the auctioneer and I'm going to be asserting, assigning
time values to it. That's not good. So I'll be letting you know what's going on.
It's 830 now. The final, the time for the auction is gonna start at 950. So between
now and... An hour and 20 minutes? Yeah but it's not gonna go that far. Let's watch Freddy
got fingered very funny but yeah between now and 950 minutes so you I mean you
guys are very early you're basically the first people at the cocktail hour which
makes sense because you're also there on sort of like an official duty there are
other Jollibee guards around you and but with you'll sort of see who's gonna
to arrive and I will let you know every every sort of time stamp like what's
happening so based on what you're doing I'm going to be keeping track we have a
little time okay yes you have time so one of you right now this is this is
sort of outside the realm of time this one of you guard guard the artifacts
that we're supposed to guard one of you take care of Sullivan the frog and I'm
gonna stand by the front door and ask the auction guests if they want to buy
this car for $10 wait wait wait hold on wait can we play out what happened
because I wanted to sell the car and he's selling it for me yeah I mean I got
what he already said no he's no wait wait I have an idea
hey hey Pat come with me okay just trust me I'm going with you all right all
right so yeah hey auctioneer fellow okay hey buddy how are you hi hey again love
your voice listen thank you so I have an item that got peanut butter in your
mouth I don't don't listen to him I was talking to him it's almond butter you
must know very fancy listen I have an item I think you might be interested in
why what is it a jewel no it's not okay I have this Yoda that I've been trying
to get off my back for quite a while I was wondering I mean not traffic but you
know in Leo Island or whatever this place is called I understand that Yoda's our
property I'm trying to get you in if he hears that's fine so what do you say
about putting this bad boy up for auction I can't buy a man I'm a girl maybe then
I'm a yaddle roll deception that's an eight
no you're not yes he is please take it
this advantage oh my god it's okay I'm
gonna win this easy I can't even
describe to you how difficult this is
for you to do well it was a six all
right yeah so that's and yeah six yeah
he's like please sit down we can just
Man, I was trying to help you out. I
I don't know how you man. Yo, fuck you man. We were trying to make you more money. I was trying to make you rich
Oh, yeah, we're gonna make you rich tonight. Now you blew all that shit. What do you mean make me rich?
We can't tell you now. Yeah, you see
We start walking away really slowly
No, no, we're just gonna leave
Go to the bathroom. He's not trying to implore you
He starts a little quiescing about like, "Oh, just like when my wife left me, another missed opportunity."
God fucking damn it.
"Another thing I am... Why you... You're shushing the air."
And you guys...
I'm backing up while I'm shushing.
And you guys sit down at the auction. You guys sit down and...
And people start coming into the auction.
What's up?
one of the people you recognize right away is Pennsylvania Jim I lunge at him
let's let's wait a minute okay one of you roll to see him now we have to do a
one-off where Pat is the DM I would love first of all I would love to play
You would have to teach me what to do.
No, no, just knowing exactly what you know now.
Yeah, no, no, no, you should not read a fucking thing.
Okay.
I will not help you.
I will not explain to you anything.
I'll just try to roll with whatever it is you're rolling.
That's a really good idea.
That sounds crazy pants.
I'll have to like hold my tongue.
Anyway, so you're, yeah, you see Pennsylvania Jim walk in.
Behind him you see sort of a foppish looking man with like just a giant
rosacea nose. All of you roll a history check just to see if you know who this guy
is. You feel like you've seen him before.
8. 23 or 22 sorry. 15. Patrick Yoda and William Johnson you know who this is.
a blowtoss pissed you think this is just some ugly guy some ugly guy holy shit
guys I didn't know my cousin was and you two from your time as archaeologists and
collector archaeologists and professors and adventurers we know this is one of
the most prominent collectors and likely Leo the collectors rival Gerard de poopoo
(laughter)
- A famous...
You see him walking with Pennsylvania Jim,
as if, so, seems like Jim is his treasure hunter,
almost to his collector.
You see them walking in.
You see Pennsylvania Jim recognizes U3 right away.
And he sort of walks up to you, says,
oh, hey, what's going on guys?
I thought you were--
- Shut up, bitch!
- All right, okay, Dwight.
I'm not Dwight, I'm Patrick.
I'm just sorry.
I will admit this, not to side with Jim, you're being kind of a Dwight today.
I'm not being a Dwight.
You're being a bit of a Dwight.
I hope I'm not.
Dwight is just something I've coined.
Something I call people who are just kind of, you know.
And he makes that face.
Yeah, and I glare.
He just looks out the window and makes that face.
You see a Lakitu holding a camera?
I'm snapping in his face.
(laughter)
I started snapping in his face, I'm trying to...
"Hey, you're looking out the window again."
I went to Brown and I love the CIA, you can't make me do anything.
"Hey, that's a veiny gym, you're making the face in the window."
You see Gerard Depoupou, he goes, "Oh, so this is the...
These are the treasure haunted hills that Leo has howled."
What?
*laughter*
What did you say?
I sound like a motel.
Speak English, you motherfucker!
This...
accent will be better when I'm less...
DRUNK.
*laughter*
Next session.
*mimics the accent*
I see you are here to auction, and you have this little frog, man.
Er, hi there.
I'm a Yoda, not a frog.
I wasn't talking to you.
Well then I...
I'm sorry for interrupting.
That's okay.
It's the first time you've ever apologized to me for interrupting.
I apologize for all the other interruptions.
This is a serious breakthrough.
I could cry.
We're making progress together as player and DM.
You see Jim say, uh, uh, Jim sort of, uh, Pennsylvania Jim looks at you all and says,
Well, if you guys are here, I assume Leo, I guess, needs your help.
No, no, we're just here.
We're just here because we like to be here.
Who's Leo the collector?
Never heard that name.
Yeah, who the fuck is Leo the collector?
Jim looks right at the camera and Jor-El De-Pu-Pu says, I believe we will take our seats now.
I'm because I am French my seat is very gay that's right it's a throne and
Gerard a poo-poo in Pennsylvania Jim take your seats Jim sort of looks at you
guys and does the like to two fingers to his eyes one finger to all you kind of
like I'm watching you yeah this whole handout it's like three fingers and
anything you like real realizes Sullivan is there and has his pinky and yeah he
walks off unless you guys want to say anything else to these two you know what
I'm gonna say to Pennsylvania Jim I know what you are bored of mine he's too
goddamn good you see here you see his back pocket is it says at the school of
peewee Herman handbook I turned to Ray and I turned to blow toss that's he's too
good you guys he's on but unbeatable oh my it's okay it's okay man yeah and yeah
they sit down um so you guys have a little more time to get some cocktails
before the next sort of time break in this thing loaded what kind of cocktails
Can can I check on the artifacts and make sure they're okay? Let's do
You're getting loaded. I'm getting loaded. What's going on? I head to the bar and I say give me 50 Shirley Temple's
Yeah, sure, whatever you need pal. In a big gulp
Okay
The bartender starts making you that he says uh, I was I was about to say what's your poison, but I realized I'm making it
Just try to find mother bartender phrases. How you doing this evening is the worst day of my entire life
Oh, man, same brother. I miss prison
Doc I'm really hot's in a cot. Are you joking?
Dude, don't even get me started. I
Loved prison and we move on to uh, what are you doing?
So I am just following the hors d'oeuvres guy around
I'm a little Yoda, but the hors d'oeuvres guy is like a giant troll.
He is a giant troll.
He has like a Costco sample-sized plate of hors d'oeuvres.
Do you want an hors d'oeuvres?
And I'm jumping up like, "Ahh!"
[Laughter]
"I want the shrimp carton up!"
"I want the snails and bacon!"
"I wouldn't normally do this, but we need to save some for the other guests."
"Oh, come on! I ain't fucking hungry down here! I got a little yoga stomach!"
I have a little yellow stomach! Come on! Give me the fuckin' food!
Okay, okay, okay.
If you have a ye-little stomach, I feel like you would like- you'd want less.
Don't tell him that.
Roll a, uh, persuasion check.
See if he can give you more hors d'oeuvres.
Yeah, that's an eight.
[Laughter]
He says, "Look, I-I-I-I can give you one more shrimp, but after that I have to cut you off."
How big's the shrimp?
Shrimp-sized.
Jumbo!
No, sorry.
Fuck!
Okay, well that's fine.
I'll take it.
And you want to look at the artifacts?
Yeah.
Yeah, okay, so you go over to, so you want to go to the storeroom in that case, yeah.
You walk out to the hallway area to see the storeroom.
You see it's a pretty bland hallway, blowtoss.
Let me make sure I'm doing this right.
Okay, cool.
So yeah, you walk out to the hallway and you see some kitchen staff walking around.
around, you see some appraisers sort of coming in and out of rooms. You see the
artifact room as well, and you see like a jolly b guard outside of it, and
I mean you tell him, you get you at this point you're a part of the, they know
you as a part of Leo's crew. So you're able to go in there, so you're able to see some of the
artifacts. Can he go in there with impunity or does he get followed? What's
impunity mean that I know what are you doing
yeah he's right so you see the art of the artifacts all seem fine right there all
there
they're all there on like a table yes ok so I put the car keys next to them
he's too fucking good
the kids unstoppable today god fuck fuck you
I'm not even gonna make you roll for that
It's just too smart.
I can't do that.
He's not outsmarting your characters, he's outsmarting you.
Yeah, he literally... fuck man.
I thought you were gonna do a thing.
Okay, amazing. Yeah.
The car keys are there.
It's not even a question.
Okay, I go back and I get drunk with keys.
Put the car keys on the table.
You go out, back out there, you're getting drunk.
Okay, cool.
845 at this point so now you start to see more guests coming in so it's a new
timestamp. Who are some of the guests? One of the people that you see is which one
of you mentioned that you dated your your student? I think it was you both? I think me and
Caleb both said that. I didn't date these hoes. You both see the girl that you
dated long ago or whatever it is you did. Marie Stain and she comes in and she
looks as ravishing and as student-like as ever. I don't remember her face but
then she spills a Sprite on her chest and I'm like "Oh yeah!" and with her is a
massive bodyguard who you don't recognize but she comes in and she she recognizes
you two and she she she goes up to you to you both you're both getting drunk at
the bar and she says to both of you uh well I know where you two would be of
course you're both getting drunk it's good to see you fellas
she's a stupid that pet name never got old
how are you doing I'm way too drunk he I ordered Shirley Temple's and he was just
drinking like pure Jameson.
Yeah.
I was like, "I'll match you on that one."
Well, I'd like to introduce you to my--
I just throw up on her immediately.
She's like, "Oh, well."
Just like old times.
I walk by while I'm following the hors d'oeuvres stroll,
and I look at Blotas, and I say,
"Ah, that old Irish whisperer."
As he's throwing up.
Well, I'd like to... she's like wiping vomit off her shirt. I'd like to introduce you to my bodyguard, Rex.
And you see this guy, he's just like a hulking brute. He looks... he's got a blonde mullet, he's got a tight black t-shirt, he's got jeans.
And yeah, he's just sort of nods to you both.
Um, is he here to help me with the auction?
I'm looking forward to getting something of some use, you know.
Back in the day when we were, I was just your students, both of your students
in your co-teaching class, we both taught together.
I remember that.
Yeah, well I do too.
The clay molding studio.
Well, he, uh, I I've since then become quite a successful adventurer myself.
And now I'm a collector and a Catherine Hepburn impersonator as well.
(laughing)
- But it is good to see you both.
I wish you best of luck at the auction
if that is what you're here for.
What are you here for?
- I loop around and they go,
hey real quick, can I ask you a favor?
I need some more hors d'oeuvres and your new face here.
(laughing)
The troll has not seen you,
so can you just give me one shrimp cocktail please?
- Whole persuasion.
- 14.
She says, "Rex, make sure this guy gets a hors d'oeuvre."
He goes, "Yeah."
- Yay!
(laughing)
- "All right, I'll make sure that you get that."
And you see Rex goes over to the hors d'oeuvres guy
and like taps him on the shoulder and goes,
"Yeah, can we get a shrimp cocktail
for this little green guy over here?"
- No, tell him it's me!
(laughing)
- "I guess just for me then."
And she says, "What are you guys here for?"
We go back to the bar.
She's asking you what you guys are here for.
- I'm chilling, man, what about you?
- I throw up again.
She says, "Ah, just what I thought,
"as evasive and strange as ever.
"Well, I have to go back to my bodyguard
"to make sure he's okay.
"He does miss me when I'm gone."
- Yo, check this out, Blowtiles can do the worm.
(laughing)
- Can you really?
last time you did the worm you cried so I'd love to see it. I fall over and a tooth comes out of my mouth.
Go blow toss. Go blow toss. It's your birthday. It's your birthday. Mouth full of shrimp. It's your birthday.
Oh you boys never cease to amuse me. Well I'm a girl and this is my only
personality so I'm gonna leave now and she walks off so it's about 845 at this
point you guys have been sort of getting drunk talking up friends of yours
old friends of yours and old lovers of yours and all three of you roll a
perception check two of you of disadvantage the two drunk ones with
disadvantage. I'm not drunk. My die fell next to you. I'm fucking drinking soda.
It's a three. I got a 14. I got a seven regardless. Dude I got the most even
though I'm drunk as hell. Yeah you guys are just having a good time hanging out
nothing unusual is going on and yeah so you guys have another you know yeah yeah
And it's around 9 now you guys kept drinking you kept hanging out can be more derves
And the auction is beginning people are sitting down
Everyone's sitting down
Gerard de poopoo, Pennsylvania Jim Murray stain rock Rex. They're all there
You also notice one other guest who's in a
cloak
black cloak
He's probably a normal guy. It's Darth Sidious. It's Dracula.
The first item comes up from the auctioneer. He says, "Our first item is a
Thanos vape pen. This pen was said to have been used by Josh Brolin himself.
After which he was said to have muttered, 'That tasted weird.'"
one dollar we have one doll the starting price is 100,000 tokens hold on no one
told us about token what's the token this dollar do we have do we have tokens you
don't you don't have I mean like maybe you have some tokens when you get out of
jail yeah yeah yeah like let's say 200,000 I mean I mean let's say 5
million look this is supposed to be like an even more you know what white
capitalist world in the world we're in oh my god oh my god yeah so yeah you guys
have no money and they keep doing at the auction I'm still I'm killing seven
million tokens even though they know that I have not just ignoring you he's
wearing poor cancelling I'm outbidding blowtoss I'm like 7 million and one we
have 7 million oh I know what you're doing now yeah the next item comes
somebody gets it next item comes up we have discontinued monster energy flavor
Arab surprise a spicy flavor but perhaps too spicy after CEO hologram Clint
Eastwood in Gran Torino took over the company. Monster eagerly pushed this
flavor to market but just as eagerly pulled it off the shelves for being too
racist. It has been unopened and kept at room temperature for over 400
years. It can be yours now, so the starting bid of 230,000 tokens.
And then the auction keeps going. All of you roll a perception check. Do I still
of
last campaign. Hear weird footsteps in the hallway outside of the atrium.
It's Jafar.
Look, I'm gonna just get out in front of this. It is Jafar.
Yes!
Oh my god. Real life 20 perception tech from Patrick.
Yeah, you hear that. So.
Can we, okay, well.
It's up to you what he wants to do with that information.
tell us
what i do is i write down on the t_v_'s dot dammit
just the worst guy
uh... here
i don't know where you are picking up on the microphone and we were in the
auction so i write down on two pieces of paper a rate it's your far handed
ravelly johnson
it's a little bit and i just look at him like
the for you
and i had to try and a piece of paper to blow toss by the time this airs a
- That's a Jafar joke is gonna still be rocking hard on the door.
- So I'm sitting there with the two pieces of paper. As I'm handing them the paper I say,
"It's Jafar."
(laughter)
- I, when I hear the word Jafar--
- You like how the note says, "It's Jafar - Patrick Yoda."
(laughter)
- When I, when I hear the name Jafar, my eyes open all the way and I'm completely sober.
And I dash out of the room into the hallway.
Okay, yeah, so you guys run out of the room. You run out of the room to the hallway. Do you follow?
I jump in his back pocket. I want to see who wins the fucking monster.
Okay, yeah, you stay for the monster part of the auction.
You two run out of the hallway? I jump in his back pocket.
Yeah, yes you do. And yeah, you jump out. You guys run to the hallway.
You hear
Sorry you here in the main room, and you hear this obviously directly in the main room Ray William Johnson
Next is the full mummified skeleton of the man the why you know guy was based off of
Real name was Martin Kaplowitz a Polish American who walked into a manhole and died making this expression
And yeah, you guys are in the hallway now
But I'm in the hallway. I go to the water bubbler. I take a few sips. I sober up I
Sober up from the water bubbler. Yeah you okay. Yes, you walk in the hallway. Do you see a bubbler there?
You alcoholic shrimp cocktail. Yes. Okay. It was a vodka sauce
And I'm drinking out of the water bubbler a sip at a time at the bubbler and you
Blowtoss piss roll perception check while he's at the bubbler
I'm jumping up at the bubbler and like
Nine okay
Yeah, you're sort of like surveying the area trying to get a sense of what's going on right now. There's nothing that's too suspicious
but
You're still like kind of wary like you're still reason to be wary
The go cut back to the auction Ray William Johnson you're there
You hear the auctioneer said now you see me too on
Blu-ray a movie that some thought was lost to time it includes the extras where
Woody Harrelson admits to taking the virginity of a high school girl when he
was like 40 and yeah it cuts back to the hallway yeah what do you guys want to do
so you certainly can like try to understand where the noise is coming
from or you can just generally investigate or yeah I'm looking for
clues personally yeah I'm gonna follow Cameron around I'm looking for clues but
in an archaeological way and not a detective way that's right okay yeah so
roll a investigation check all right do I have to roll too because I said I was
doing yeah roll roll as well you can sort of help them out here very old
clues 18 you got a 5 I got an 18 okay with that 18 blowtoss you sort of have
like an inkling you think like you know what buildings like these and you sort
of like put your ear to the wall and you hear like sort of like footsteps in like
a vent like you start to get the sense that there is people maybe in like a
ventilation system like okay like you get that real hard oh can I send my
monkey into the vent absolutely you can
He didn't actually get drunk like the game said.
So you roll in, you run into one of the rooms,
one of the conference rooms, there's nobody in there,
and you see a vent up top, you pop it open,
and you toss in Patrick Monkey
up in there.
Hmm, this is interesting. I guess I have to roll for Patrick Monkey now.
Let me do that.
Yeah, Patrick monkey sort of scours around he looks for clues and stuff and he sees that somebody was definitely up there and he scroll
He's he goes
And he sort of like makes his body look exactly like another person kind of thing like a cartoon yeah like Jafar literally
He sort of like communicates that to you
But you don't know where they're going or like how long they've been in there
You're just getting the sense that like people are in the fucking vents
We cut back to the
Auction house way William Johnson. You're just like pleasantly smiling and like getting drunker and drunker
Sit yelling bigger and bigger numbers
one million dollars
Here the masters to the cabbie song the master recordings to the cabbie song and
What cabbie song I
Don't want to sing it you want to sing it
Is it the mega 64? Yeah, but the one...
Oh, okay.
(laughter)
(singing)
And you see, yeah, and somebody buys that real fast.
And then the next one is, he says, "Special Edition Brickleberry Wavebird Controller."
(laughter)
And, um...
Just Mad Libs that joke.
And the yeah you guys are now sort of you guys hear the the the so you can you can
explore the the vents or you can sort of try to assess where it's going it's up to
you to what you guys want to do with that information. But yeah obviously that's
like sort of the last auction option before the floppy disk. Well there's the
keys that I put on the second it buys us time right that's an extra action we can
take him like I gotta let you do that it was good role-playing and I try to
reward that as a DM okay yeah you see you see you see how the auctioneer goes
like uh and I I'm this is new I suppose and he realizes what it is like Volkswagen
Jetta keys starting muffled from the other room you just hear me yo one
brilliant yeah so that that does buy you guys time yes a couple more actions you
can do between now and the the final I'm a tiny guy yeah oh I want to can I throw
- Yeah, so he throws me into the vents.
- Absolutely, that happens.
- So I follow, okay.
So I follow whoever is in the vents.
- Okay, yeah, so roll a perception check.
- Nice, I'm gonna add your perception.
I think your perception's pretty good.
I think you probably got an 18 right now.
- Yeah, my perception is plus eight.
- Yeah, oh fuck.
Okay, you got 21, okay, nice.
You quickly pick up on, using your Yoda ears,
they're like, peep, peep.
They like tweak a little bit.
you hear sort of the traces of somebody.
Somebody's out of the vent,
but you get the sense of where they are
using sort of like the force a little bit.
And you quickly like sort of scurry over
into that direction.
And you look below you now,
you sort of like get the sense,
okay, the trail is stopped.
And you see a grate below you.
And below that, you see two people,
well you think at least,
in sort of like black ninja garb.
Oh, no, and they seem to be in a room and you're guessing
because you went up a little bit on the top of the masks
the balcony.
The balcony floor.
He says that out loud and I just hear it echo back down
the mat.
I hear a whisper come on the go PJ Masks.
So what do you want to do?
Um...
He's not reading his buying time.
He's just looking at the paper going, "Uh huh, yeah."
Because if I use the force, if I use the force in the vent, then I could jump down and have
an advantage.
Yeah, definitely.
And attack them.
But if I use Yoda's mind, I can read their minds.
You should use Yoda's mind.
Nobody else is with you, so you'll probably get your ass kicked.
So Yoda's mind.
I'm going to use Yoda's mind.
So they will roll against...
You have a DC of I think...
What is it?
18?
What does that say?
Up top.
It should be on the top of your sheet.
Armor class?
No, your DC.
On top of your magic spells sheet I made you.
Oh, okay.
I have a DC of 16.
Okay, cool.
So they're going to roll against that to see if they can resist.
So do I roll too?
No, you don't roll.
Okay.
You read their mind.
Oh, I do.
Oh, okay.
So, with Yoda's mind, you're able to peer into their mind.
You get the surface level thoughts before going deeper in.
Yeah.
You hear something that is not, you hear a couple of things.
You hear, "Gungan."
I don't know if they're gungan.
But what I can, actually, role perception.
You're hearing something in another language, which is a different language.
So, you're hearing something in another language, which is a different language.
here.
I don't know they're gungan.
But what what I can actually roll perception
because you're hearing something in another language,
which is not as illustrative, but 17 plus.
17 plus 8.
Oh, okay.
Despite you not understanding the language and reading those
surface level thoughts.
It's malintent.
You sense.
You definitely get a fucking vibe there.
Yeah.
It's it's it's they are dressed in Ninja Garb for a reason this
time.
Not like your birthday party.
Were you attached?
Not like my PJ Masks birthday party.
Yeah, so you can certainly try to probe deeper.
Can I?
Okay.
To get like exact words, but that said, you got the sense that
it was a different language.
Because Cameron, I'm in the vent so Cameron could jump through
the door and the camera guy could confront them or blow toss rather so
you're pretty far away uh-huh you could crawl back to get him to come but I can't
say not a good idea I know okay so for sure they won't lose them if you do
yeah so I guess I guess you probe deeper okay they're gonna resist again okay
Shit, they get the same roll.
You hear...
Because it's still in a language you don't understand.
Yeah. But roll a perception
with advantage now.
17. Roll again. 20.
Nat 20 or dirty 20?
Nat 20. For real?
Yeah, I saw it. He's not lying.
But for some inexplicable
reason, despite a
language you don't understand, maybe it's something
with the force, some sort of like a deeper primordial connection to the to the
connection we all share with other living beings, you know they're trying to
steal that artifact. For fucking sure. And that is what they're here to do.
Hit them with the needler one time. That's a good idea. To do that, I will
mention, there is a grate above you. Okay, can we tell, do we know where the vents
our relation to the race thank you so meanwhile I'm in the auction room and I
say to the person next to me just drunk at my man I'm like that be humped a huh
they're like they're like I do say it is Wednesday that's a good boy and I'll
I'll have both of you, actually, no.
Yeah, both of you roll a perception check
to get a sense of your surroundings.
- 16.
- We'll get a, we'll sort of like,
square that a little differently.
- Oh, okay, all right, so it's six plus eight,
that's like 14?
- Yeah, I mean like, so you both get a,
so you both kinda know where you are.
- Okay.
- You know, blow toss, that Patrick Yoda,
So in relation to you, he sort of went to the other,
so four walls, right? - Yeah.
- He went to the wall, one of the walls near you,
like one of the walls adjacent to you.
- Yeah, so it's not like in the,
they're not like next to the auction room,
they're like near me still.
They're near the storage room?
- They're near one of, they're near the bathrooms,
but like, they're near the auction room
in that like, it's part of the balcony,
and it's one of the rooms off of the balcony,
but they're only like 35, 40 or so feet from you,
where you are.
And you, Patrick, you oughta have that sense as well.
Like you felt yourself make a turn, like a hard right.
So from whatever, like sort of like,
of like the square that you were in,
you were in one side of the square
and you went like sort of like
into another side of the square.
You could feel that, but you're not that far
into that other side, if that makes sense.
So like, you have a sense of where you are
and you know that they are trying to like jump down,
probably like they're gonna try to approach the items.
Like you went to- - Are they in the vents?
- No, they're down from the vents.
They're in the room.
But like you know that like- - It's been so long.
- Yeah, so you blow toss,
you're like on like the left side of where the auction house,
of where the auctioneer is and like the items.
And you are like on the wall,
right where the auctioneer is, like by the stage.
- Oh, okay.
it in the vent and they are above it in a room on the balcony okay so they're
there you can see that what they're what their idea might be to like like
apprehend it yeah okay is there any way we can commute communicate oh yeah wait
what can I just walk run into the auction room and yell there people start trying
to steal the artifact you absolutely okay yeah I'm gonna do that okay so you run
out and does he have to roll for that? No. Okay. Running out and rolling. Why are you trying to
sabotage me dude? I'm asking if... And you climbed up so he's right on the ground floor so what do
you say? Well I don't know they're ninjas and I guess I don't know with certainty that they're
trying to steal the thing. No you don't know almost any of this. Yeah. You said there's something weird going on.
Yeah. Guys there's something weird going on there's Jafar is in the vents and I think he's up to no good.
Don't listen to him, he's fucking drunk out of his mind.
What?
I am more sober than I have ever been.
So the auctioneer who's gotten kind of used to ignoring you is like, kind of taking notice
at this point only.
He is going to feel like an asshole.
He's like, Jafar is in the vents.
There's somebody in the vents and I have this weird feeling that they might be trying to
steal something.
And Patrick Yoda.
What happens now that he said that?
So, you see them perk up and start to move.
I'm gonna give you the opportunity,
because you got to jump on them, you were so stealthy,
I'm gonna give you the opportunity
to make a reaction of some kind.
So that can either be an attack, that can be a--
- Can I make them crap their pants?
- Trying to grapple them?
I don't know if you have that ability,
but you have the hot rod ability.
- I do have use of the force and Yoda's,
I think maybe, no, because Yoda's mind was the fourth, maybe the hoverboard?
Go for it.
So you can do a hoverboard attack, so you can bust through the gate, the grate, and do a
hoverboard attack before they bust out of the room.
I'm going to give you that option.
Okay.
So roll, it's going to be an attack roll, so you're going to add whatever your hoverboard
attack modifier is.
I can help you with that in a second.
That says attack bonus plus four.
Okay, go for it.
yeah that hits both of them roll for damage
ok it's not going to be the D20 that is 7. That's not the dice.
Check out those sheet. I should tell you. Which one is that?
So whatever the damage is. It says 1 D8.
ok there you go. Which one's D8? The one that looks like a triangle but not a
small triangle. Two triangles together.
Yeah.
That's her.
It's me.
Oh my God.
You're right.
I think you add to that too.
Yeah, that's a d8 plus one.
Okay, cool.
So you so here's what happens you see those guys start to like
they hear blowtoss go.
There's something weird going on and like they like sort of
look at each other and bust out of the room.
But before they do that you like stomp on the great and kick
your board down and it goes.
and hits both of them for nine points of damage
and they like fall out of the door
uh... and all of you will see is this
who sees this everybody or just me just you see the hit happened they all see
the guys
will like fall out of the door ok
uh... and all of you will roll for initiative
uh... about to be a fight
and uh... eleven
we can stop it there
Okay, well I got an 11.
We'll deliver that.
Maybe you want something more.
Happy Halloween everybody!
Happy Halloween!
[Music]