Okay. All right, you ready? Make your announcement really quick. Okay, today's
episode, first things first, today is the no swearing episode. There will be in-game
penalties for us if we swear. Every time you swear. You can swear if you have to,
but you do lose, we'll say, 10 points of damage. If Patches swears, then we get a benefit.
If Patches swears, all of our HP gets raised by a point. That's a good idea.
answer one question of ours that is not like yeah like a major plot point yeah
we'll we'll we'll work it out yes I think that's fair and then if you guys swear
something bad happen we lose one HP every time you swear that's not enough no
that's it needs to be fine okay we have if we swear all right okay this is by
the way we're doing this the rest of the time and that we do D&D forever this is
like our twist on D&D is there's no cussing no and if you're mad about it
It's called Patrick's Law.
So yeah.
Who would be mad about that?
Some people like
c-c-crussing.
Some people like crussing.
Alright, do this.
Last time on Gun City, a broad city.
Playtime continue fun.
Whoopsies, looks like
the fellas got in the trouble.
After accepting the task of
clearing the Greeches out from the Greech Queen's lair
from Bear McGinnis'
kind gang. Our heroes barreled ahead into danger. Not without Patrick Yoda first
making a surprising discovery about Janet Blowjob's double life as Bam
McGinnis' girlfriend. Blowjob is a swear. Is that a swear? I'm gonna take this to
Julio. Julio, we need a ruling. Is it a swear or what? It's not a swear. Okay.
Alright, yeah it is a last name.
Okay.
*laughter*
Can we say swears at their names?
You can say swears at their names.
We're gonna figure that out.
But no time for that.
Into the Greech's lair they went.
Immediately being way too loud and attacking a guy made out of Yu-Gi-Oh cards.
Blotoss handily defeated them.
But soon after, Greech's and Monster's started coming down the way.
Blotas went invisible and Ray and Patrick jumped to escape into a horrible pit of toys and flesh
where a big katamari ball slammed into them, nearly killing them I think three times.
And Sullivan.
Luckily, Patrick Yoda's new best robot friend, Scuta, made a quick dial to Blotas,
who was just about to enter the Greech prison,
where they could discover more about the mysterious Greeches
in the connection to their missing son, New Sullivan,
in playtime with the serial killer.
Flotas dropped what he was doing
and heroically, invisibly sprinted through the greech lair
back to the pit and saved his friends
using Patrick Yoda's amazing foreskin.
Once the end--
- It's anatomical.
- That's anatomical, yeah.
- It's on your eyebrows.
- But he did say it was amazing.
- Foreskin.
(laughing)
- Which a doctor would never say.
- It is literally amazing.
- A doctor would never say, "Amazing foreskin."
- Well, if you had phimosis and you got surgery
and then it healed up.
I think a doctor would say it after.
- That is the exact scenario we're in right now.
- Yeah.
Once the DM decided to not let them starve to death
in the pit of toys,
they rolled the Konamari around and around
and climbed it up out of the pit.
With more lair to go, will they even survive?
Will I throw them another bone like that?
I think that's one bone too many.
Next time, they might not be so lucky.
So, yeah.
You guys, you're probably in pretty dire straits.
I don't even remember where your health is at.
I think it's pretty low.
- Mine is six.
- Yeah.
- What's my health?
I think I'm at six too.
- And you had--
- Yeah, it says six on your list.
- You should subtract the techno slime
that Blowtoss used for you.
- Okay. - I'm at 31.
- So look at the cost of the foreskin
and make sure you're subtracting that from what you have.
- We'd have to do a checkup on that
'cause I did not subtract it last time.
- Yeah, so I think you did that like,
let's say you did like three, I think you did like,
let's say like two times at least.
- Okay, let's see, so that is three technoslimes.
- 'Cause you did other stuff too.
- Minus two, three minus two is five.
- You got this. - Negative five.
- Three minus two is five?
- No, negative five.
- Hold on, that's not what's happening I think.
- Three minus two is negative five.
(laughing)
- Okay.
- Hold on, let's think about this.
- It's negative one.
- No, because you had--
- No. - It's negative one.
- Oh, wait, let's try that all.
- If it was two minus three.
- Yeah. - Well, it was two minus three,
yes, but so it costs three to do that.
So it's two times three. - So it's negative three.
- So it's six, you're subtracting--
- It was negative three minus two, which is five.
- How much total TechnoSlime points did you have?
- 15. - Before this.
So we're taking, and it costs three to do the healing?
- Yeah, so three, so I did it two times.
- So you're doing it twice, so it's minusing six from it.
- Yeah.
- So you're at nine.
- I said that already.
- It's one of those, like,
I don't think you're that bad at math.
- I think, honestly, I could not.
- I think there's just like--
- Three minus two is negative five,
and I'd be like, no, it's negative one.
- It's like you go on your gut.
It's like you go like a gut instinct.
- Yeah, it's like whatever sounds right.
- Yeah, I will say, Pat, it is at the point
where I really don't know if you were kidding there or not.
I really have no idea.
- And you're not gonna know if I was.
- I know, I know, but it really elicited
almost no reaction out of me.
I really was like, okay.
- Well, so yeah, it kind of blew my mind
'cause I heard him say three minus two,
which usually he says something out loud
when he's working through the problem,
so I was like, oh, he's working through three minus two,
and that's what got me initially.
(laughing)
Negative five.
- Just imagining like a techno-slime meter on the screen
(laughing)
- Just going up and down.
- Just like not unsure.
Okay, so where you guys are is you crawled out of that pit,
which was kind of like a side,
like you entered the Greach's Lair,
you walked through a bit, there were kind of two paths.
One was towards that pit,
one was down further into the lair,
which you already kind of sprinted down,
so you have the lay of the land of that.
- Damn.
- Booyah.
- So I can tell you what, some of what you saw.
- You know that there is a sort of like stretch,
Armstrong kind of monster, like fuck monster,
that's kind of like--
- Whoa!
- I didn't even think about it.
- Yeah, you didn't think about it.
- That's right.
- Dummy.
- So how do we kill him in one hit?
- Wow.
- Yeah.
- I'm actually, I'm like, that's not good.
- Yeah, have another drink.
We get that, yeah, wait, what is our question
we're gonna ask him?
- How do you kill it in one hit?
How do you kill all the monsters in here in one hit?
- There's not, it has to be something that we think
'cause he's just gonna say,
his answer's just gonna be, there is no way.
Like we need some kind of actual information
that we know exists.
- He's like a genie. - We need a known unknown
that we can actually-- - He's like a genie.
We have to think of like how to--
- What was the darkest room in the group?
- Why did we come in here?
(laughing)
- Oh yeah, we didn't do a recap.
We didn't do a recap. - Yeah, he did do a recap.
- I did kind of have the last session.
I mean, I could give you a little bit more time.
- No, no, no, no. - No, no, that's not
the question we want. - We know exactly where we are.
- We know why we're here. - The problem is
- There's one obvious question that we have to ask,
but it's the solution.
- What is it?
- I mean, who is the killer?
- No, but I--
- I know we said no major plot points.
- I know, but that's the only thing I care to know.
- Okay, so I would say--
- What's the first letter of their name?
- I would say, is there anything, wait,
so we should ask about the Stretch Armstrong thing.
Is there any fatal flaw or huge weakness
that these monsters have?
- No one was paying attention, I said an F.
So I have one health point.
Okay, subtract it. That's very honorable of you.
Yeah, thank you. I didn't even process it.
That's how that's kind of how inundated we get with swear cussing in our day.
Like this is what we need. We don't even notice it.
We should just go. We should do one year of no cussing.
No cuss. We should do one full year of no cussing.
We have to. What is today? Can we put a swear jar on the table for the rest of the year?
$100 a year. My mom has one in our house.
We literally need to put a swear jar on the table. It's getting out of control.
no matter what is in our wallet we have getting really out of no coins you got
to put a 20 and I almost wanted to say the f-word right then it's getting out
of control she turned it into like it's $20 every time and that is that has
helped me a lot when I'm at home yeah all right well then we'll figure out
that we will be doing that and we are doing a fully no swear podcast for the
first I think so um so you asked me is there what is like a main weakness with
these monsters yeah they are they are insatiable there are ways in which you
can distract that we asked the killers first name we could we could throw down
some stuff from our in there like areas food yeah they're pretty I have a
relationship in that and this is a stealth level like it's not just a
sexual appetite I had the perfect distraction and everyone these are
creatures Wowed what is it missing something you know I have in my
inventories to every Xbox game ever. That's not food. Do you think that they
could be fooled easily by a worm? There are some Xbox games. Your weapon is a sandwich.
Yeah but I have every Xbox game. Leisure Suit Larry is an Xbox game like that
would maybe get them. I could throw the disc. They could be fooled by a worm. A worm could
certainly fool them. Skinny donuts. Simpson's Hit and Run.
Simpsons donuts. Simpsons Hit and Run disc is a donut. Oh the disc looks like a donut. Okay let's just
empty out our pockets like like just random lint and crap. Okay, in care, in care. Crap is good.
Wait, hold on. That's a good, that's good. Take that off. Does that count? No, no, crap is, that was me saying it because I wanted to say the S word.
Crap is, you're saying, we're saying C is okay. That C. What, wait, no. No, well, which. That C, the C we're
talking about right now. Crap is okay. Crap is okay. That's okay, right? If it's a proper noun.
Well that's not a crop, that's a semi crop.
Either way, bring it back to D&D. I want in character, I want you guys to be
emptying out your pockets in a circle talking through this. Okay I just want to
say one thing, the planet that Patrick Yoda is from, Dagobah. No? Oh it had a
different name. It has a different name. And also, no I'm Italian.
can it be said no because you have to bleep yourself out okay we're gonna know
Yeah, I say that again we can definitely say
Okay, I'm a bunch of peep and I'm gonna be all over it. We need to we need to we need to put a
trail of
goes
Off into a different direction to distract him. So
because they want to beep it!
and I can't get out of the beep voice!
(laughter)
He's stuck in the beep voice!
I'm stuck in my beep voice!
You have to stop beeping!
Get me out of the beep voice!
I need you to beep me, get the beeping voice!
(laughter)
Okay.
Get me out of the beeping voice!
(laughter)
- Yeah, like paper clips and some of his video games.
And I'm not gonna sacrifice my whole worm to this
because the worm was really, has come in handy so much.
- If you cut off a worm's tail, it'll grow back.
- That's an amazing idea.
No, I won't do that to my worm.
- I'll do it.
- No, I do, no.
That's off the table.
But maybe I put, maybe I squeeze him like toothpaste
and get a little poop out of him or something.
I put that on the ground.
- I got a bunch of lint.
- Okay.
I have feces in my pocket.
That is a sensory overload of a pile. I do like that.
So how are you gonna present it to me?
I'm gonna have a pizza.
Am I a ventriloquist?
Like in the game, do I have ventriloquist abilities?
Can I throw my voice?
In a way.
Am I invisible still?
I could just walk over and be your voice.
Definitely make sure you check your technical sign points.
because you've got invisible a couple times now if you can go over you also
have refills you can use you go over and pretend to be the pile of beep and say
just like random random oh that's a pretty good idea actually yeah then what
do I do I think I still I can be in the pile I can be part of the pile I still
have enough to go invisible. You don't have to do anything. You get to be a ventriloquist, he gets to be the whole evil eye.
It's not we don't get to do anything, we're just trying to get out of here.
And he's not even doing anything, I'm just doing it. I stole it from him. Can I have a soda then?
A soda? Can I just have a soda to drink? Is this in real life or? No, just in the thing.
Does anyone have a soda in their inventory they can give me?
Sullivan does but he's tied up on Ray William Johnson's body. Okay. Oh, yeah
I use pockets. Mm-hmm. So what? Yeah, you have these pockets. Nobody keeps you can't keep soda. Okay, I'm invisible. I'm in
In your inventory, no, he has he has like a he Sullivan doesn't wear pants
And he has so he has like the cartoon like pocket like kind of shows up as you reach
Or he has exactly a soda in there. Okay, so I guess the whole thing
I guess we're making everything up Mountain Dew typhoon. Yeah, it's Mountain Dew typhoon because he knows it's Patrick
You're his favorite. That's BS, but I do appreciate your
You are you getting all
Managing, you know
Are you doing that for drink your be? I?
Don't I almost am feeling like it's worse
Yeah, cuz you're making me say the word
also I'm gonna say that like I think there's got to be a limit on that too
what the number of like cuz then you might as well just be cursing yeah yeah
I think no letters I think it's more creative positivity and if we're
replacing swears with shorter swears what that is going on okay yeah so here's the
thing about here's the thing about cussing cussing is instead of maybe
instead of saying what the you know you know I would I would replace that with
something like I can't believe it yeah I can't believe this I'm impressed yeah
we need to say what we mean and so saying so we're saying right now it is
not language has degenerated nowadays we have a word like the four-letter word
that I won't say that begins with LGBT it begins with the same letter that the
word fun begins with but it's a lot less fun than fun yeah is that means
everything nowadays why don't you roll for a check on that
that was incredible that made that basically people say let's go eat some
f-word let's go do some f-word people do talk like that these days they use it
like it means anything that's a four all right but I thought it was good so
four plus 20 okay so let's get the - - one a persuasion it's a 23 guys let's
get out of here okay all right so you guys have the pile out it's on the the
thing like it's like it's by the it's like sort of near where the the stretch
armstrong thing started lurking around I definitely got a wit not a whiff I guess
a whiff of you you know a witch
they got a whiff of you but you need to just go over there how do I smell more
than this pile of I mean a whiff of you I meant it was good I was gonna say like a
figurative sense and that like you were running figurative with you're running
by it invisibly make it all right so it's on alert this guy uh-huh you know
it's you move it my I'm a pile I'm a pile of you know what all right now even
the roll even the bees are a little crash roll deception okay with advantage
okay he's not gonna think this pile is deceiving him okay that's a 15 all right
nice so yeah this thing is is wandering over there it is engaging with the pile
it's like trying to see oh yeah yeah it's gonna try it's gonna try to hit it
that's also dirty it's gonna try to dirty it's gonna try well this is this
- This is a very dirty campaign.
- Oh yeah, I'm a pile.
- No, you can't say oh yeah, we're making that--
- You can't say oh yeah?
- What are you talking about?
- You can't say oh yeah.
- Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
- Okay, you say oh yeah, I guess.
- Oh yeah!
- Okay, booyah, I'm a pile.
- There we go, that's good.
But you can't be like, oh yeah.
- I didn't do that.
- What about boom shakalaka?
- Booyah, I'm a pile.
- Boom shakalaka, I'm a pile.
(laughing)
- This thing is distracted.
- Boom shakalaka, eat me.
You guys can roll stealth with advantage to get by it.
- That's not sexual.
- Right now.
- So his head, his mouth is fully in the pile of stuff.
- Yeah, he's like eating it.
- Dung is okay.
- He's eating.
(laughing)
- Spore.
- Dung is fine.
- Wait, he just said dung is fine.
- Dung is definitely fine.
- You like dung?
- This guy likes dung.
- Okay, so we just need to get around this guy?
- I love dung.
I'm just gonna sneak then I don't have any kind of thing, but I have a still I mean
I have any other things you want I guess I could try you have an advantage on a stealth role now
You can also do others, and I'm invisible
Okay, and an eight so so 19 do I roll yeah?
Yeah, if you're trying to sneak by am I invisible have to roll
Did you spend on that yeah? Yeah? Yeah? You're invisible. Yeah, then you don't you you don't have to roll, okay?
You'll just be fine. I mean roll. Let's see if you don't get a one. I got a 13 and a 16, okay
I got a one. Alright, roll again because you have an advantage. Oh my god, you better not get snake guys.
I got a one. Oh my god!
There's no way you just rolled two ones back to back.
What did you say? He said if he gets a one, but he had advantage so he had two chances to get anything but a one.
I thought he said D though.
- Yeah, it's a one out of 400.
- Wait, wait, wait, did you say D?
- Well, no, I said man.
- Okay. - Okay.
- D's, can't say it, but--
- D's friends. - I'll put the idea
in your head. - I'll say you're even
invoking. - Wow, that is--
- I think invoking's fine.
- D's coconuts. - That is crazy.
- Okay, so you two sneak by very easily.
- Yeah, and he's invisible.
- You're invisible. - Yeah.
- What do you, do you just like make the pile?
- I'm just still doing the pile voice.
(laughing)
- He like sees, oh, I'm a pile.
- He sees your teeth like a Cheshire Cat
saying, "Oh, I'm a pile," right next to it.
- This thing whips around. - I'm a sneaky pile.
- And you are gonna roll initiative against this thing.
- Oh, Lordy Lou! - You two don't have to.
- Well, but we might have to help him.
- Can he just flee? - I can't help him.
I have one. - I wish I had a stretch
Armstrong thing, that's what I wanted to get.
That's we forgot we have this crab
That will work
What did you get on the 20 but not a natural 20 that's still wonderful though for real
All right, you're gonna go first for sure. This thing is gonna try to fight you for real though. All right
I'm gonna kill it. Okay. Kill? No burping. Kill is fine. Yeah you can kill. No burping into the mic.
You can't, yeah that's bad manners. I'm sorry I didn't know we're doing a manners thing.
Can I give you guys some more buff debuff abilities? All right well I'll just fight first.
First off, I'm still invisible too so I should get to automatically hit it. And then me and
me and ray william johnson are on the sidelines going like go cameron
saying cameron
oh i have advantage though because i haven't yes yeah i know yeah okay okay so that's a 24 yeah
- Yeah, hits, so you get a crit.
- Okay, and it's a crit.
- Nice.
- So they gave you that crazy ability,
but it's been cool, folks.
- Seven, and I just double or I roll?
- Keep rolling.
- Okay.
I always forget.
Okay.
13. - Six, more fun.
- 17, 21.
- Wow, blackjack.
- On the first attack.
- That's great, and then you get another attack.
- And then my other attack.
- 'Cause your whole character is about being crazy.
- Okay, that's gonna hit right, 23.
- Okay.
- All right.
Seven.
10.
- Is it both attacks? - 12.
- Probably. - 16.
- You just, this thing whips around and sees you.
You're going like, "I'm a pile, I'm a pile!"
And then you just go crazy on it.
(laughing)
You just start whipping it.
Like just like insanely hard with your pipes.
It is looking really bad.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, yeah, it's got real low health.
- Wow. - How do you like that,
mother?
- Whoa. - U-G-L-Y,
you ain't got no alibi, you ugly.
Uh, uh, you ugly, go blowtoss!
- Roll a dexterity saving throw.
- A what sterity?
- Dex, sterity. - Okay, yeah, close.
Seven, 18.
- Nice, okay.
So this thing swings at you with,
it's like stretch arm.
You see there's also little arms kind of come out of it
with like, with a little thumbtack,
so try to like, stab at you, but it misses.
It's gonna swing around one more time.
So roll another dexterity saving throw.
- 13.
- Okay, this time it is gonna get you.
- Oh.
- Oh my.
- No it doesn't.
- Oh my, Lanta.
- That would be my version of that show.
- What?
- My Lanta.
What show?
There's a show called Oh My Lanta.
You take 17 damage.
17?
Yeah.
There's a movie called The Ringer where that's from.
But you're back up again.
You guys, I mean, look, here's the thing.
I'm doing the worm.
If you, okay, 'cause I could have you guys rolling.
I don't wanna die.
I'm being completely--
You're not participating in the combat at all?
I'm just on the sides.
Yeah, I've already shuffled by.
You guys could get a surprise attack.
We're trying to do a two-man pyramid.
Okay.
Dude, for cheerleading.
- Low toss, you're up.
- All right.
- In that case.
- I'm gonna attack.
And that is a 11.
- No good.
- I'm gonna attack again.
And that is a 24.
- That's what happens.
- And that is a 12 damage.
- Also, describe your kill on this little crab here.
- Okay, I will first--
- He's stretchy, remember this.
- Oh, he's stretchy.
He's not a, I was about to describe a kill on a crab.
- Oh no, no, no.
- Sorry, yeah.
- Stretch up.
- I messed up.
- Mr. Stretch.
- I wear him like clothes.
- Oh my goodness.
- I'm wearing him for the rest of my life.
Fashion, I strut my stuff, I'm like this.
- Whoa.
- Oh my god, you have your hand on your hip too?
- Dang.
- Watch me, now watch me strut.
Now watch my fashion.
Now watch me strut.
And yeah.
- Let me get the fish.
- Basically that tears into a trillion pieces.
- Dang. - Letters away in the wind.
- Dang. - Yeah.
- I love how many-- - Disposable bag.
- How often when you describe a kill, I just instinctively say the D word.
- Oh, did you say it? - I just said "dang" twice,
- because I said "dang." - Nice.
- Because I say it slow enough that I can catch the last two letters.
- All right, cool. So you took care of that.
You took some damage, but you're all right.
- Taking care of business.
- All right, guys. So you guys can keep going.
You guys bend up back in that sort of--
- Try this. - Wow.
- Wow. Okay, yeah, that's better.
- The main area.
(laughing)
- It's a little scary.
- With the bed that you saw, that disgusting giant bed
where creatures were writhing, waiting for monsters,
greeches waiting for monsters to scoop them up
and embrace them, and the door to the prison.
So there's a door to the prison,
then there's another door that leads somewhere else.
But you were about to go into the prison
'cause you were trying to see if there was
new solvent in there or something.
- Oh, we were trying to break out those
fucking leprechaun. Oh, you're dead. He's dead. He's dead. He's dead. He's dead. How did that happen?
All right. That was so bald-faced. Roll d20. Wow. You guys can try to stabilize him. That's a
failure. He's gotta do this by himself. All right, keep going. Five. I'm as bad as a customer. Are you
You're gonna die?
Nat 20.
Wow, okay.
So it's two and two.
Two wins, two fails.
Oh wait, then we should stabilize him if he's on the edge of a bank.
He was on the edge already.
Hold on, wait.
Pat, before you do it, do you guys want to stabilize him?
You should probably stabilize me because I am not, I'm not getting, there's no luck.
This could be it.
I mean, we could try.
Yeah, I'll try to stabilize him.
What do I do?
Just roll the 20 as your medicine.
He did it.
Medicine, 11.
Okay, cool.
He did it.
You're stabilized.
I rolled a 20 as soon as I did that.
- Okay.
- So, he would have to use his four skin again,
so subtract three from you to get some health points back
if you wanna be conscious again.
Yeah, so God, I guess, just struck you down for swearing.
- Yeah.
- You just had like a little mini heart attack.
You had like a stroke.
- Your second one, by the way.
Me and Blowtooth haven't had a darn one.
- I just love that F word.
- Yeah, you need to go to therapy.
- Yeah.
- Go to rehab.
- You need to go to rehab, that's wrong.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. - What you did was wrong.
- Did you? - I'm really excited
to know what comes next. - So how many, wait,
how do I, how do I get the points,
my health points back?
- So, oh yeah, it's using your force gun
when you're knocked out, I think we did it,
oh God, I don't remember.
- Do I get six points?
- Lord's at the end of vain.
- No, that's Christian, that's different.
- Wait, wait, Andrew said D. - That's Christian.
- What? - Is it God, don't?
- You said God, D. - I don't remember.
- No, you said, you said, you said God.
But you said it like, God, you didn't mean like,
- Yeah, you were kind of cursing.
- Not that he said G-Date.
- Is it okay if you say, so we're not supposed to curse,
right, if I were to say like, curse you Elon Musk,
like I'm cursing.
- Well, politically I wouldn't do that.
- Let's not get into the semantics of this.
Or we'll stay out of the semantics.
- Let's get into some antics though.
- Let's get into some crazy A antics.
- Yeah, maybe you laugh.
- Crazy butt antics.
- You almost did it again.
- You almost did dead butt.
- So I think what we did, and I don't remember
'cause I should've listened to the last episode,
I think what we did is that when you use a Foreskin,
when someone uses a Foreskin on you
while you're knocked out, you heal for half.
I think that's what we did.
- Okay.
- And it's also gonna subtract the--
- So I roll to see how much I healed.
- Well, so first look at your, on the sheet,
how much heal you, it's not there.
- You said sheet.
(laughing)
- It's not that sheet.
It's the next one over.
- Yeah, three Technoslime.
Okay, so I heal all allies in range for one D10 plus four.
- So that's gonna be roll one D10,
add four of them, divide that by two.
That's her.
- I have 70 health points.
- No, okay, you're rolling a D100, so plus four is 11.
So it's 5.5, we'll round down to five, so you get five HP.
- All right.
- It's like he never swore at all.
- Wow.
- He got five back.
- But you also lose those three Technoslime points
for using that.
- Yeah, I said that.
- Oh, did you subtract it?
- I subtracted it.
- Okay, sorry, I'm sorry.
So yeah, you guys are about to go to the prison.
- Yeah, let's go to the prison.
- After a heart attack and you have to
put his foreskin over his face.
- Yeah, he is, I will say he is one cuss away
from just being back to dying.
- Yeah, back to that, so just be careful.
- All right.
- I at least have a buffer, six health.
- So you guys go down into the prison.
It's similar to everything else.
that has that yellowish glow that you saw
in Huge Fax's lair, I guess.
Can we say?
- No, I guess it's a name. - It's a name, right?
It's a name, right?
- Huge A Fax. - Use the letter.
Use the letter. - Use the letter?
Okay, Huge A Fax lair.
So that same yellow stuff.
The same yellow stuff you saw above his lair,
and the same yellow stuff you've been seeing in here,
and now you see a bit more of it too inside this prison.
You see some of the leprechauns in there,
and they're going, "Oh, oh, over here, here, let me out.
Please, let me out."
- They have to swear. - Racial stereotype.
- Wait, what happens if we make--
- Oh, we're gonna do that?
- Can we force NPCs to swear to kill them?
- Yeah.
- Oh.
- Well, you're out if you swear.
- No, but that's just gonna affect me.
- That's what my great uncle did.
- Wait, do you think this--
- Okay, so wait, yeah, here.
- You say this applies to anyone.
- How much do you want the leprechauns
that you think that these--
- That's a very funny idea. - These people
should be kept in prison?
'Cause we'll let them out if you swear as them.
That's what my uncle did when we were at a Christmas party when I was six.
He said I had to say a swear for a piece of candy.
What?
He had lined all the kids up and made a swear for candy.
I want a cut at you right now.
I'm just saying we could do that.
You don't line up on candy.
You just spit all over me.
We could make a game.
It's like the Dark Knight Joker boats.
Okay.
PG-13 reference.
Huh?
You reference a PG-13 movie.
- It's after 9 o'clock.
- You're right, that's a very good point.
- Finding a stranger in the house.
- So basically, we'll let out the leprechauns if they swear.
So you have to show that you care about your characters.
If you don't want them brought in jail as leprechauns.
- Yeah, this is going to work.
- A very clear caricature of a racial group.
- One that all three of us are affected by.
- So if you think that they should stay in prison,
then go ahead and don't swear.
in prison then go ahead and don't swear.
But if you think that this real life group of people
deserve to not be in prison for the rest of their lives.
- Do you want to say that?
- Do you think leprechauns should stay in prison?
(laughing)
- You're saying that in front of three Irish laddies
right now, so don't forget that.
- I don't really follow.
- Okay, we give up on it then.
(laughing)
- I just don't know where my incentive is yet.
- You don't have one.
(laughing)
- Okay.
- It's friendship.
- Oh.
- It's about the dark knight.
say that that does work on me I am simple that way so do you want to let them out
or not no okay we'll let them out of the aisle accidentally let them out yeah
I lean on the bars I'm so strong accidentally rip them apart yeah they
- They wink at you, they're like, "Oh, very coy, cool."
And they leave.
They leave you free, the leprechauns.
They're gonna try to find their way back.
All of you roll per--
- Careful now. - Perception.
Per diem.
- Daronette is a bad word that starts with per.
- Perfidy?
- Perjury? - P-E-R-S-S-Y.
- Those are bad things to do.
I got a two.
- Wait, what are we rolling?
I got a 17.
- Perception?
- Wait, wait, wait.
- Nine.
- 17 plus eight.
- I got a five.
- Wow, 17 plus eight?
- Yeah.
- That's 25.
- Yep.
- As Blotas is letting out the leprechauns.
- Blotas will.
- Accidentally.
- Well, piss is not a curse.
- P.
- Say P.
- Oh, he said it.
- We're not gonna punish you this time, but say P.
- Come on.
- Yeah, he had to make the rights.
- Yes, really.
- Would you around your nephew or little, little cousin,
would you say I gotta take a I say it around if you and no you say I have to
go potty if you say that's trashy if you say I'm a save pee around your nephew I
even to be quite honest I say I don't say that one of my biggest regrets so
they say blowtoss bathroom say Pete blowtoss urine you can say pee or potty
you can say peepee yeah peepee or TT or TT or I guess tinkle dozer
yeah tinkles good so blowtoss tinkle leans on the on the prison opens it up
like baby leprechauns come out and as as he does you Patrick Yoda notice a
photograph an analog photograph one of the very rare ones you look down I say
"What the flip?"
- You start to notice that, I mean,
this prison isn't just a prison,
it was, it looks like it was a lab at some point.
There's sort of like beakers strewn about,
there's broken centrifuges, you know,
there was like all this equipment that's been
covered in grime and time and age and all that stuff,
and then the yellow goop as well.
And you see this photograph.
- Said the G word.
- Goop is not a, come on. - Don't worry about it.
And you see this photograph and it has on it,
- Goop.
- You just liked saying it.
- A picture of, sorry I'm finding it here.
Yeah, a picture of--
- Careful now.
- Oh, and I have to roll the dice too.
Okay.
A picture of the scientist, Ebenezer Keech.
He looks younger though.
As well as a younger Tool Lateralis with him.
- Oh, we like him.
- They work together at, if you guys remember,
they work together at Papi Chuka's Techno Slime.
- We miss him, we miss Tool.
- And a third person who's a woman
that you don't recognize with red hair.
And you--
- Wait, red hair?
- Mm-hmm, and you, Patrick.
- Is it Janet BJ's alternate persona?
- And you, Patrick.
- Can I wipe the dust off the mirror window frame?
(laughing)
- Picture frame.
- What are you talking about?
- Doesn't look like Janet BJ.
- Okay.
- But you, Patrick, you also recognize a younger,
less sort of like, you know,
if you remember Huge A Facts has these sort of like
shifting eyes and like weird kind of alien--
- What kind of haircut does he have?
- At the time he had a bowl cut.
- A bowl cut?
- Yeah, now he's got a cooler haircut.
- It's called a surfer cut.
- But you see him when he's younger also,
and they're all smiling in front of a facility
called Playtime Industries.
- Whoa.
- OMG.
- You can call Tool Lateralis if you want.
You guys are his friends.
- Oh, heck yeah, we can.
- Oh yeah, let's call him up.
- Let's call him up.
As soon as I see this picture,
I take out my PSP and I hit the speed dial
for Tool Lateralis.
- It's time for a late night buddy call.
- That's right.
- And you hear him, he's--
I was buddy calling my friend.
Dude!
*laughter*
I was up late night getting a buddy call.
Don't you buddy call me.
A buddy call?
What am I just?
*laughter*
Ryan, another buddy.
Am I just a buddy call to you?
*laughter*
A buddy call?
Um, anyways, so you call and um, you do this buddy call.
Uh huh.
And keep in mind, so like, you guys are on this space station, right?
And so this, he's, he's all the way back.
He's service bad.
Um it's it's not bad. It's just like he just sounds a little bit. I'm on the ship's right by yeah the Wi-Fi is pretty good
It's just that you're where you are in the ship is kind of like in the gut so just like a little bit weaker
Where the servers are well stronger? Let's get to the thing we don't have to worry about this
Hello
Pat Patrick you was up
Oh, it's good to hear from you. What what the flip is uh?
Make sure to call me on
You know I am I am still in hiding, but what's going on is everything okay?
I'm looking at this picture you right now, bro, and you are young as F
Now it's that's on the line. Yeah, you're kind of where you take two damage. No. Where did you get this what picture?
I oh, I'm in the guts of a ship
Okay, and it says in the picture says playtime industries, and you're there with
with Dr. Ebenezer Keech and this woman, I think her name is Jessica Brownlee. That's just an
educated guess though. Her name was Maude. Maude Brownlee. Marge? Maude. Marge? Oh, I
got you on speaker by the way. Say what's up yo. No he doesn't, that's why I can't hear
what he's saying. I almost always assume I'm on speaker if I'm on the phone with Ebenezer
any of you three.
- Yup, smart move.
Even if the other two aren't there,
maybe just sitting on the bus with you on speaker.
- What?
- Sitting on your butt?
- On the bus.
- Well, where did you find this picture?
- Prison.
- Yeah, I'm in like a prison for leprechauns.
- It's underground.
(laughing)
It's underground, but there's no,
I guess it's not ground.
Under chip.
Yeah.
Greach.
Oh, are you on?
Okay, so you're on...
The pleasure dome.
The pleasure palace.
Palace.
Oh.
Okay, this is...
Well, the play time is...
What are you watching?
What?
What are you watching on TV right now?
I can't hear that.
Chips.
Yo!
Okay.
Yo
Okay, don't you have a Boston? It's like the oldies. Yeah, this is a new I like the new voice
I we did a new thing with beeping and I gotta keep my
Normal well, okay
So playtime industries was a company that Ebenezer and I started
Uh-huh. So and mod Brownlee was there and so mod ready. Yes mod ready. Yes
I was close. Um
When we were and then this guy with the bowl cut he was our benefactor facts. Yes, Hugh. Yes huge huge a fax
Can the character no he can't right?
Good
When we worked together at Papi Chuko's Techno Slime, we were close working partners and,
you know, like most companies in Gunn City, and after Stakem's labor statute was passed,
it was at-kill employment, so they could kill you at any time if you tried to leave.
So, we managed to get out, though, thanks to this wealthy benefactor, Hugh J. Fax,
who worked for the New England Federation.
That was before it was an empire,
it was a federation run by Leo and he had subsidiaries
and all that.
Obviously you know how that worked out
'cause I ended up working for Papi Chuko's Techno Slime
and making the C-U-L-O-S Rift,
if you guys remember from the first campaign.
Can you spell it?
Yeah, I remember.
C-U-L-O-S Rift.
Actually, that could be a chicken, so you can say that.
- The Coculus Rift.
But anyway, Ebeneezer and I were given this opportunity.
- I got my voice back.
- Because the benefactor, via discovery made
by the New England Federation,
he gave us access to a mysterious alien ship.
It was floating just out of orbit of E-Bomb,
and it was remarkable, and the resource they were using
was just like Techno Slime, but it was more chaotic.
- And it was glowing yellow?
- Yes.
- Holy Moses.
(laughing)
We called it Star Goo.
Star Goo.
Okay, so if I eat this Star Goo...
Do not do that!
Do not eat the Star Goo!
Okay.
Do not eat the Star Goo.
Why?
So wait, wait, wait.
Where on the ship that you're talking about that has the Star Goo?
Do not eat the Star Goo.
Okay, but you didn't answer that last question.
Why?
What will happen if we eat it?
What happens?
Because I think I might have ate some a long time ago and then I had a crazy dream that
showed me where...
Oh, we lost our nephew.
Oh, we got we have so much to tell you
Yeah, we have a nephew now I have
They have son will text you okay, so just just
When we were working on this I
Started to get cautious the ship
Was weird it made these weird noises and there's an alien species that live in the bowels of the ship called the Greeches
Well the greet I don't know what creatures are well
We've been dealing with them all day reaches are if you remember creatures are people who were on the ship
Oh, yeah
work
Who were workers on the ship and who got corrupted over time by the lack of nourishment and maybe this goo?
Okay, so there's a let me fill you in there's a
It's a group on this ship, and they were old workers, and they maybe have been affected by the goo
And they're called Greeches.
The point is, listen, we think that Maude is a serial killer.
Or you are.
Or Hugh J. Fax is.
No, I think it's Maude.
Well, Maude...
Oh my god, did Maude eat the Starglobe and become part of the ship and is a serial killer?
I think Maude died and turned one person into a serial killer from grief.
Well, I...
So...
Or it's an entity.
If it'll help, I can tell you.
Yeah, tell us.
At the time, I started to get boxed out of the project a little bit more.
Um, Ebeneezer, he may seem demure, but he's the real maverick, or he was back then.
He was the one who said we should leave Papi Chuko.
He was the one who found Hugh J. Fax.
And soon he and Fax were doing lines of the goo together, just snorting it.
And then they brought on an assistant who was mawed ready, and she was...
She was brilliant, but she was very much taken by Ebenezer,
and soon she was into the goo,
and I was getting frustrated.
The plan was for us to develop technology
that could power a space station the size of a county,
though it's good to see that it seems,
if the goo is there-- - Yeah, we're on that
spaceship right now. - Maybe that didn't happen,
but-- - No, I just said
that we're on it.
- Oh, well, yeah, so that's,
well, Maude got pregnant at one point.
- Okay.
It all stank of startup stuff, you know. And did she have the baby and maybe it
was a really bad circumstances? I left the project. So you don't know at all?
There was no serpents involved. A snow serpent was involved. It had a serpent stance, it was a wiggly baby.
That's actually really scary. I was trying to track down this alien ship, it
did not... the project had lots of strange things. The sounds were coming out of the
There were artifacts. I was trying to track that down when you guys were doing that heist.
It was uh, there was an artifact kept in the ICUP facility
Run by Fatima Mankizziface. Mommy Goodlegs was supposed to help me with that. I don't know what happened, but
Just if you're on this ship and
I'm assuming Ebenezer is there. I had heard he had taken a job there and that this ship is being now being powered by this.
We've met him. I would just be
Careful then I don't we a buddy we are not being careful at all on here
I have not one pretty like I have time. I feel like I have to say it, but we keep dying pretty much
Yeah, I had a heart attack as I said F. Yeah, okay
Don't I guess don't say that you whoa just that one
Well, I just just be careful do not eat the goo
It might destroy your mind permanently
I don't know what'll happen.
I suppose if you see Ebenezer, tell him I said hi.
- Can I ask him who Maude is, or will he get all weird
and start throwing--
- I don't know.
- Or the bio flask said maybe--
- They were together when I last saw him.
- Is he gonna get all crazy?
- Was Maude with him?
Did you meet Maude? - I'm pretty sure Maude
is dead. - Okay, guys,
let's go find Ebenezer.
- No, we gotta get these leprechauns out of the jail.
We already got the leprechaun, we have to get the Greech queen.
The Greech queen.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I don't really care.
There's some bull crap we got to--
look, if we get the leprechauns at it--
I don't know.
The leprechauns are already gone.
Oh, they're already gone?
No, they're Greech food right now.
That's not our problem.
We did not kill the--
We did our job when it comes to that.
OK, let's go kill the queen.
Tool, it was good talking to you.
What's up?
Hey, it was good catching up with you guys.
You give me a--
Really?
Seriously?
If you guys are ever interested in more weird science
kind of adventures you just hit me up I always got stuff going on. You're just one of those
guys were like I always thought we would be pretty good friends if we like made the time.
It's one of those it'll happen one day like we don't have to I like I do we're on the
same page about this. Okay okay. Yes you're very on the level okay take it easy. Do you
smoke that sh- he hung up. Wait hold on. Didn't say it. You have to take 2.5 points of health.
I don't have to take. You said the first two letters. You have been you have been a whole
He's been squirting too much.
You've been squirting too much.
Thank you, Julio. I agree 100%.
You don't know what I was going to say.
Listen to this.
You've been doing it the whole night.
You've been swearing more than usual.
I just said BS.
Like BS the words BS.
Like the letters BS.
You're fine.
I was going to say, do you smoke that sherm?
Get out of town.
Why can't we say stuff like that?
- Sherm. - Yeah.
- Just keep it in mind, in the future from you,
you will, the rules will be stricter.
- You got one more chance in like--
- That was last strike.
- In a reasonable amount of time,
you can't be doing stuff like that.
- Yeah. - You know what I'm saying?
In like a reasonable amount of time.
- It really is like, I am surprised at how upset I am at you.
- Yeah, I'm like really angry.
- Like he's skirting the rules, it's not fair.
- I could take it out on you.
- Because we've been trying really hard.
- Yeah, I wouldn't do that, I'm kidding.
- I don't even know what you guys are talking about,
what the flip you guys are saying.
- Take two damage.
- What are you talking about?
- DM says take two.
- Take two damage.
- That's right.
- That's absurd.
- That's like when you just got sent to your room
and you slammed the door one last time.
- That's so...
- Your mom said, "Don't slam the door!"
And you opened it and slammed it again.
- Yes.
- And you went like this.
- But you did one of those slams.
- But the door was closed.
- You did like maybe almost a slam, but it wasn't.
- You were gonna say that, I'm not touching you.
- Yes, yes.
- Yes, you did though, yeah.
- I didn't slam it.
- A level of slam that like maybe--
- What are you talking about?
- We can't say what the flip now?
- Uber driver would get mad about it.
- It's just the amount you're doing it,
you're just like rubbing it in our face.
And it's like we're all trying to quit cursing right now.
- You're toeing the line.
- And it's like--
- You're really trying to toe the line.
- You're like looking at us
who are really trying to quit cursing and you're going--
- You're literally, you're like a guy--
- I can do it any time I want.
a guy who comes to Narcotics Anonymous and tries to sell heroin.
Definitely.
Because you are making me want to cuss so bad.
You are the heroin dealer at Narcotics Anonymous.
So enjoy your three hits.
I guess I just won't say anything.
Why?
Because you're incapable of talking without cussing.
Because that's all you say.
You swear.
That's all you say.
It's all swearing.
I'm not going to say what the flip.
I'm not going to say what the fruit.
- The fruit.
(laughing)
- Oh lordy.
- Okay.
- Alright, cool.
You guys wanna go to the,
you guys wanna go to the,
- Yeah, we'll go to the queen.
- You guys wanna go see the Greech Queen?
Okay.
- Alright, we're gonna take her down.
- Yeah.
- You walk out back into the sort of main lobby area
and see some of the Greeches,
they distractedly are like,
kinda trying to paw at you.
You guys can like, literally like run,
just run through them very easily.
- Yeah, do we, oh, who do we distract with the pile?
- I thought we distracted all the Greek guys.
- Stretch killed the guy.
- Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. - You killed the guy.
Yeah, you guys run through that other door,
down these stairs to another hallway.
And I will say, before you sprint through--
- Can we take a long rest?
- No.
- Can we rest at all?
- It's like in Elder Scrolls, you can't rest
in where enemies are hostile kind of thing.
- I can't take, do I have a potion of health?
- I guess you could try to rest
- We and Caleb have potions of health.
- You can try to rest, unlike in Elder Scrolls,
you just might get interrupted.
- Okay.
- You don't have any health potions.
I said there were health potions at the shop
and you guys were like, let me look at the shiny thing,
and I said you guys can't afford that,
and you're like, aw man.
But you now have 25,000 tokens,
so when you leave here, you guys can go shopping.
If you--
- When did I get 25,000 again?
- 'Cause you gave that intel to Hugh J. Fax.
- Oh!
- And now you have to kill the general.
I'm at 6 HP, but I still I need to fight we have to fight okay. Yeah, all right fight. It's fight in time
so you guys get to the hallway, I'm gonna do a hit list run and
You walk down and you notice that the the sort of like makeup of this hallway now is like a little bit less
Because it's the Queen
But when you get to the doors and they open up you see sort of a long
bridge like 15 feet wide about 45
- Why, is this like the Borg Queen
in Star Trek First Contact?
- It's more like the power core area in episode one.
- Okay.
- Where they have the Darth Maul fight.
- Got it, got it, I know exactly what you're talking about.
- Star Wars, oh who knows what Star Wars is?
- Is it like that thing in Toy Story 2
where he jumps on the little--
- Or maybe it's like a football field.
- Yeah, or maybe a race car driver track.
- Or maybe a footy track.
- Maybe a footy pitch.
- It's a lot like a footy pitch.
- Or a beautiful banquet table filled with meats.
- Yeah. - And breads.
- Okay, that one I'm down with.
- And it's a large atrium, and you will notice,
'cause you guys have now seen this
from a couple different angles,
you guys saw it from up top, on the top part of the ship.
You saw it from when you were in Hugh J. Fax's lair.
This is a power core, one of the three power cores
that power the whole ship.
- I would like to destroy this.
- Yeah, I wanna shoot it right now.
I wanna shoot my hoverboard at it.
- I'm gonna use my atomic bomb.
(laughing)
- I forgot I gave you that.
Really bad idea.
But you don't just see that though,
I'm sorry, I'm like drifting from the mic.
I don't know what you're gonna say,
I'll tell you this right now, I'm gonna riz.
But you see also a undulating flesh,
flesh creature inside of where the core is.
- Underwearing?
- With flowing red hair and this sort of spiraling
- Oh my god.
- Mouth of like, sort of like,
- I should say oh my gosh.
- Labia is kind of like going inward, inward, inward.
- He said Edward, Edward, Edward!
- He said it!
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
- After a certain anatomical word.
You saying that n-word made OBS crash. No it's not that's definitely not what
happened. Uh-oh OBS crashed. Did we lose that recording?
I don't know just keep going. Okay. So no first of all no. No I did not I said
n-word I N W A R D. Yeah. It's that's not my fault. You just spelled N W A R D. I didn't.
(laughing)
- That might work on me.
- But it's okay to describe sensitive parts
of the female anatomy though.
We're ignoring that part.
- Yeah, without her permission by the way.
- He's saying inward labia.
- Okay.
- At the $10 tier.
- At the center of the--
- It's what he's saying.
- I almost wanna make you take a swear to your head.
- At the center--
- What are you talking about?
- I'm saying you were taking the opportunity.
- This sort of like--
- You reveled in it.
- Yeah, you did.
- This sort of like--
- You reveled in it.
- Uh-uh.
- Yeah.
- Like inward going like circles of like these
like fleshy holes are a dozens and dozens
of shiny yellow eggs.
The same yellow you've been seeing throughout this ship.
- I tap Ray and blow to us on the shoulder
and I say that's the same.
- You tap that?
- That's the same yellow we've been seeing.
and you start to notice that the power core
is kind of similar to that.
And you see her vomit up these eggs
and you see these creatures start to writhe inside of it.
You see a GI Joe head pop out of one,
and then you see a tongue sort of like pop out of another.
And then you see them start to like
become these like weird fleshy,
kind of like, almost like they're like crawling fetuses
of like toy flesh.
- Wait, there is no playtime killer.
It's these toys that are killing.
- It's toy eggs.
- And then the Greech Queen, when she faces you,
now she like turns.
- I look at her and I point and I say, "Maud!"
- You see, whoa.
- That, can music play?
- That would be powerful.
- Epic.
- She,
she has, so it's like, she's like basically like a hole,
like her whole mouth.
And then she has these slivers.
- Yeah, that's nice to say about a woman.
- That's not.
- She's basically like a hole.
(laughing)
- And she has these slivers.
- And a queen, no less.
- These sort of slivers.
- Even above a normal woman in terms of--
- You're calling this queen just a hole.
- She has these tiny slivers of blue eyes
that are kind of around.
And when you say mawed, you kind of see her,
she kind of recognizes for a second.
- I'm friends with Tulle Lateralis.
- And you were pregnant.
- And it's gone.
- Okay.
- Whatever that recognition was is gone.
- Why?
- Then we're gonna play golf with your mouth.
- She has these legs that are like
these floppy tentacle penises,
they're flopping around.
Sometimes they'll get hard, randomly.
- Mother of Mary.
- And just shoot seed, is that okay to say?
(laughing)
- You have to say semen.
- Semen out.
- Seed is biblical.
- And you'll see it shoot across the entire thing,
like the entire, this giant room you're in,
and just hit the wall and start to dissolve it.
- Ugh, blast.
- Yeah, it is a blast.
And then you hear--
- Crikey.
- Over the speakers,
like the speakers that you've been hearing
when you've been hearing this voice.
- Yeah.
- Say, "Mama, can you turn out the lights?"
And then you hear--
- Whoa.
- That laugh.
- Wait, that was the same voice as Two Lateralis.
- I'll work on the voice.
(laughing)
- What laugh?
(imitating baby laughing)
- I'm scared in the dark.
- Oh wait, mama, 'cause Maude is the mama,
so the laugh is the baby.
- And she walks out of the power grid,
and when she does, that's when the lights go down
like we saw just a second ago.
And when the lights are down,
you hear the voice say,
you monsters, you'd attack mother.
You know, that kind of character.
- No, we wouldn't.
- And he says, now,
that's the Snow and Play time starts.
And...
- I said we wouldn't.
I told him we, I just told him we wouldn't.
- Okay.
(laughing)
- Scary.
- That, the whole light thing scared me so bad, by the way.
- It put me on edge.
- Putting the lights down, I'm like,
I cannot believe that scared me.
- You flipped that one.
- I did not flip it.
- And he just pointed at me.
- I saw you flipped it.
- I saw you flip that one.
- For audio people, he just pointed at me and did nothing.
- Sorry.
- He flipped the dice.
He flipped it.
- You're just saying flip 'cause you know what we're thinking.
- He's so scared that he's just talking through it.
like you're gonna get your your back with the back to one
why you flip in them it was it was not on one
what the biggity dog mama you're dead I'm dead
haha you're a wait wait I have six HP he has three
your throat it was just luck of the roll your throat
cuts open blood squirts out
I'm
Roll for initiative.
Well, I said mod.
I said mod.
OK.
He's-- could die.
Roll for initiative.
OK.
Fuck.
I got a two.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
You need that health.
Fun times.
Fun game with--
I got a--
Say it.
What is that?
I don't remember where my initiative at.
You have 15.
Okay, and would you get Pat? Oh wait? I got a three and you know you roll over as well as episode
Why do it you roll initiative as well? Okay? He's dead
Yeah, but still he's on the turn order 14, okay?
My heart is I
Said the lady's name, and I said that we weren't gonna attack her when he said you'd hurt mother. I said no
Yeah, and my stomach hurts. Yeah, and this is gonna happen now, and you're giving him fucking pain. Oh, I'm dead
(laughing)
- No!
- Oh my god!
- It was all leading up to this.
- Okay.
- You are lucky that you go first.
- The only way you're gonna win this
is if you somehow induce him to swear.
- I'm so scared.
- You have to grab Pat's foreskin.
That has to be what you do right now.
- Okay, that's what I'm doing.
- You have to heal them or you will be done-zo.
- All right, all right, I'm running to heal Patrick.
I have to heal one at a time, right?
- Okay.
- We'll have to stabilize him first, I guess.
- I have six techno slime points,
so after that you can't heal anymore.
- With the four skin, you can just wrap it over his head
or wrap it over his head.
- Okay.
- If you will do half heal, he can do full heal
when he does it.
- So I should wake him up first, probably.
- Well, the only thing though is that you know
he's sooner in the turn order.
The way, yeah, so it's up to you.
I'm just giving you the information here.
- Okay, I will get him because then both of us,
one of us could get him back up.
- Yeah, okay, cool.
So, Pat, you roll 1d10 plus four.
- 1d10?
Wait, I didn't get to do that?
Is this one?
- Yeah, you could just, that's like basically your action.
Let's set this up, by the way.
Sorry, I didn't really make this all...
- It's so hard to-- - Oh, a scary monster.
That's maud.
- She is.
- I got a Greach Queen. - I got a three.
- I got a three. - I got a three.
- I got a three.
- You got a three total?
- Yeah.
- Three plus four is seven.
Seven divided by two is 3.5.
Three health for you, Blowtoss.
- Three?
So was I, did I just go down to zero?
- Yeah, you went down to zero.
- I just went down to zero?
- So you give yourself three and a half.
- Three.
- Can I get three and a half?
- No.
- No? - No.
- Go ahead.
- Well, just 'cause it's not,
just 'cause it doesn't work that way.
- I would give it to you if I could.
- If you could.
- You could do it.
- No, I can't.
- If I could.
- Game doesn't let you do that.
- Yeah, fair enough.
- Okay, cool.
- That looks better.
- So, you're up, Blotas.
- Okay, I guess I will,
so did we see the person whose voice that was?
- No.
- You just heard them.
- And also what, my throat just got slit?
Or did anybody do it to me?
- I can tell you, so I can tell you a little bit more
what you experienced, 'cause now you have,
similar to, oh lordy, O'Neal?
- If it's your turn first, you should get Pat back up.
- Similar to that Irish guy who got his throat slit
by Playtime and Liv, you're the second person
to have done that.
So it was this warm feeling that glid, glid.
- People, they always make it whenever--
- Glided across.
- They always make it sound like it's so good
to get your throat slit.
- Yeah.
- Or like, you ever hear someone talk about
getting stabbed and they're like, yeah, I had this warm feeling.
Yeah.
I kind of want to get stabbed.
Yeah, that's kind of what I'm trying to do for us here tonight.
So you get your, he felt that warm feeling and again, it didn't feel like,
it felt kind of just like a opening.
Like it didn't feel like you were getting like, it was jagged through.
It felt very just like, this is just a natural way.
Just what happens.
Yeah.
It's just what happens.
Come on.
I actually felt bad just now.
Please put that away.
I'm feeling bad.
- I was raised way too Catholic for that.
- I was trying to get him to swear.
(laughing)
- I was too Catholic for that too.
You also felt that what had like touched you,
'cause something had touched you besides
that whatever the throat slitting was,
it felt--
- Slit, really?
Okay.
- Did I say slutting or slitting?
- Whoa, now you know.
- Oh my god. - Slut is not.
- Slut is not. - Yeah it is.
- Yeah it is. - What?
- That is a curse. - Could you say that
in front of a kid? - You were fine
until you said it wasn't. - Yeah.
- So now we're not gonna get you for two,
we are gonna get you for one though.
- That's fine, you can get me for one.
Let me finish describing this.
And the feeling of this person,
whoever this was,
that moved by you as they slit your throat.
(laughter)
Felt kind of like they were phasing through you.
Felt kind of like they were like
clipping through you a little bit.
- Oh my god, they're part of the ship.
- Don't yawn after he tells a detail like that.
Don't yawn in his face.
- That's kind of cool though, to do that to me.
- So what's our question?
- I would say, our question is,
is there any way to, because the big thing is
we just need to avoid damage,
because I think we're at 10 HP between the--
- Can we keep-- - Yeah, the lights,
by the way, are just flickering.
- Yeah. - Yeah, so is there any way,
is there any way, what would be--
- We know her name. - What would be
a good distraction for this thing to--
- Think you kind of unlocked it a little bit with him.
- Or is there somewhere to hide, I guess, in this room?
- You could run away.
- We can run away?
But we're supposed to kill her, though.
- That's what the leprechauns want you to do.
You don't have to do anything.
- Yeah, but if the leprechauns--
- You could retreat and come back later even.
- Maybe we should tell Tool Lateralis about this.
- Yeah, oh my God, get your phone out and call him.
- I will say this got way scarier than I thought.
I thought it was gonna be literally
the cow fight queen for Women's Day.
- What about her hearing Tool's voice?
Wouldn't that like--
- Oh, that's a good idea.
- That's a really good idea.
- That's a wonderful idea, we need to get you awake.
- Okay, I'll wake him up right now.
- You can just use my phone, you don't have to do that.
- But I still will wake you up.
- We didn't have that idea, we need you to be awake.
- Okay, so roll another D10.
Keep in mind-- - Chill.
Seven.
- Keep in mind-- - Seven.
- The only thing I'll say though,
I mean, we'll commit to that as the heal.
Seven plus four which is 11,
do that with two so it's five again.
But we'll commit to that as a heal.
Before you do it though--
- 11 points, I could have been fine.
- Hold on, before, just remember that the next turn
is Mama's turn.
Mod's turn, not your turn.
- But I could still, I mean, someone could still,
using a cell phone is not--
- Is that a free action?
- That is a free action.
- Oh, what you just did?
No, that's your act.
- You can be--
- But is using a cell phone a free action?
- We have done a bunch of--
- So then I'll dial two red arrows.
- You'll do it?
Okay, fair enough, you got it.
- Yeah. - Yeah, good job.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, okay, call him.
You call him.
- Okay.
- Beep, beep, boop, boop, beep, beep.
And these are not swearing beeps.
- Thank God.
- It's Morse code.
- Boop.
I'm gonna call him.
Beep!
Blowcast!
Wait, you're already over them.
I'm also gonna beep!
I guess I got the wrong...
Don't hang up! Wait, don't hang up!
Am I alive? I don't remember.
No, you're not.
Okay.
Speak your phone.
Put him on speaker.
I don't know how!
Okay.
I'm pressing the button and...
Beep!
Okay.
Can you hear me now, Tool?
Yes!
So we're here with Maude. She's a monster.
What? Maude?
Yeah, so we're just gonna kind of throw the phone towards her,
and if you could just say something to save our lives, that would be great.
Okay. And I toss the phone over towards, maybe within a couple of feet of Maude.
Yeah, you like us. Here's the phone.
I was gonna pick something smaller.
That's how big the phone is.
But yeah, you slide that over.
Mod! Mod is that you?
I have a mod on my phone that I have a subwoofer attached to it.
I think she can probably hear it.
Mod!
And Mod sort of like looks perplexed.
We're going to do a little bit of a, we're going to do a little persuasion check here.
And as he's saying that, you hear over the like, the sort of like loudspeaker thing again
Uh, uh, like, "What are you doing? Stop! Stop it!"
Um, as he's talking...
Okay, that's a nine plus two, well...
And what is her... I mean, it's really kind of like that.
She kind of like pauses for a second and then kind of like...
Kind of pushes the phone, like, further from her.
Um, so no dice just yet. So it is her turn.
Um... - Uh-oh.
- Tool, stay on the line.
- I will, I will.
- So he says he will.
And let's get her attacks out here.
- Holy guacamole, what's coming next?
(laughing)
- Well.
What does it say?
- Say the F word or I'll kill you.
You're not supposed to, it's between me and him.
Okay, well, you know, read that.
- Blue's Audio Podcast. - Blue's Audio Podcast.
- Don't read that.
- I don't even think the video worked for this one.
- Yeah, the video might not work.
- Don't look at it.
It's not for you, 'cause it has my stuff on it.
- Okay.
- And we'll do Maude's turn next time.
- Oh my. - Oh my God.
- What the flip? - By the way,
I would like to say this is the first time
I've ever not wanted you to say that.
I was a little bit excited, but we'll see it next time.
- Yes.
- Bye. - Bye bye.
I got a count. I got an official count. You got a count? I swear I count. Okay.
Oh yeah. Pat looses with three, Patches two, Kaleb and Kemp zero. Wow.
See? That's about how I thought it was gonna be. Very good.
[Music]