[Dramatic music]
Last time on Gun City!
The Temple of the Penguin of Doom!
Our heroes rode motorized Walmart scooters
down the mountains of Gadsville on the chase of a lifetime,
narrowly avoiding the attacks of Ken Bones,
nagging mothers, weird birds, and Nickelodeon slime.
After making it through the gauntlet,
They arrived at their Sky Galleon, where they made a call to break through the Ken Bone Barricade
by riding on that loop-de-loop Ken Bone, avoiding the gateway utter lasers and crashing into
their Sky Galleon, and flying up into the sky instantly.
While safe aboard the Galleon, Sullivan was pressured into eating out a penguin statue,
which gave the gang a direction to head next, deep into the Soy Wastes, to the town of Hoo
Town.
Unfortunately, the ship was tampered with by Pennsylvania Jim, leaving our heroes to try
to prevent the ship from crashing.
They did as best as they could, which meant the shields did not go up in time, and our
heroes plummeted to the earth with a massive, horrific thud and the icy, harsh, desperate
wastes of soil, left to nature's devices as the world turned black.
So are we dead?
We died, the world turned black, like all of us are dead.
Like hell?
We're all dead.
So it's opening in hell.
I'm just kidding.
I don't want to be in hell.
So you guys, you're a demon.
Nevermind.
I want to be in hell so bad.
Yeah everything went black.
If we do go to hell, can Caleb get like a huge buff?
Yeah, he would definitely be able to navigate in there, probably know some of the folks
in there.
They'd be like, "What's up my demon?"
Alright, let's go to hell.
Well, you guys can try to do that if you want.
I want to now. I don't think we should die.
So...
Well, can we just like, maybe Caleb opens up a portal?
Can we maybe like, just open up the ground a little bit?
Yeah, let's open up a portal. Let's look in.
Do I have a portal ability?
And we can go to Caleb's room to grab something.
How far underground is hell?
Okay, so where's hell?
so
uh... i hope i feel a lot of pressure to establish a kind of a little bit now
okay are you know i don't know how i need to say is that it's thirty feet
underground it's about and it is the underground and it's a little bit too
for the whole
you know you can't and i don't know what it has a little bit
okay wake up
that would i actually do you want help okay i wrote seven one hundred twenty
wake up if it's above one i'd wake up now you can't do that okay i so it is
the
get a 20 I get to go to hell I think I think you did that yeah I hate that that
like tricked me for a second all right cool so rolling now rolling 10,000 d20s
I'm being a good boy this episode and I'm letting Patches do his thing.
Honestly, he loves Patches.
I'm intimidating Patches.
Yeah.
Um, I guess you remember that you persuaded me one time and so now you're trying to find
a new-
Yeah, and you've been spamming every channel in the Discord asking people if they remembered
when you persuaded him.
I didn't spam everyone, I asked the people who are patrons and I asked the Gun City channel.
That's it.
I do remember what you did.
It was so you could use a sword in a particular way.
I don't remember that exactly.
[laughter]
So, yeah, everything's black.
Honestly, pretty good move, I'm gonna say.
Yeah.
And as you guys sort of go in and out of, like, consciousness,
you feel, like, the frigid soy air around you.
You feel yourselves getting dragged occasionally
as you sort of half wake up, half go back to sleep.
Then you sort of like half come back and you see a cloaked figure sort of by a fire and
you see the cloaked figure come towards you and it goes back to being black.
And then it comes up again and the lights come on like again, like you kind of gain consciousness
again and you see the cloaked figure bent down and you recognize the cloak a little bit more
clearly now and it looks like it's snoochie-boochies and you sort of fade back into blackness and you
think you almost see like some sort of face underneath the hood it's hard to tell though
it looks like it's deliberately obscured not just by the hood but by almost like their face itself
and then everything goes black for a long time and then you hear uh uh patrick patrick patrick
and Patrick you are being shook violently as you come to by her ex who is shaking you.
Marie goes over to you, Blotas and Ray William Johnson.
My two wonderful professors who groomed me, I thought we lost you forever.
And there I wake up and I instantly throw up on her.
Oh, Blotas.
I'm like 10 feet away.
but I walk over and also throw up on her. I have a concussion and I'm throwing up but it's...
I have a concussion so it's making me projectile vomit. Rex is just like, "God,
damn it!" He's shaking me and I'm throwing up and it's spraying. "Oh my God!" It's only going on her.
"Stop vomiting on her! Oh my God!" And she's like, "It's all right, Rex. It's just how men say hello."
I said, "Hello."
We barbershop quartet.
Hello, hello, hello.
Roll a performance check.
I got a 14.
I got a 13.
I got a 15.
Yeah, yeah, it's
Flat you kind of you kind of mess up a little bit on the like hey
Hello like that kind of gets is a little off. But other than that like you pretty much got it
the
Rex is just like I'm kind of impressed. But that's are we going to Hollywood?
What can I say we have style
We fail upwards mm-hmm
so uh as a
You know yeah, you guys do your barbershop quartet you see Rex has the Yeti skin on him
And you guys notice that you're you're sort of also wrapped in some Yeti skin
And you you do also feel that the cold is is like
piercing like it it hurts you to walk to like be in the soy waste.
It's why it's been mostly uninhabited because it causes physical damage also,
which you'll start to notice and we'll talk through this a bit more but you all have for at least a temporary amount of time -
- 10 to your max HP because of how fucked up you got from the crash.
you can get your shields up in time.
So, um, at least temporary, you have -10 to your max HP.
You're just like, kind of like, fucking banged up.
But you're at full health, I should note, as well.
You're just weaker.
So I'm at 31?
Yeah. So keep track of that too, so we can obviously put it back up.
I mean, I guess you'll just add 10, but...
Um, Rex, uh, says, uh, um, to you all,
We, uh, you know, we, after I killed the Yeti and we got the, uh, and he holds up a little
Batman beyond action figure, got the artifact.
Uh, I, uh, we started, uh, trying to find a cave to rest in for some time.
We found this one and I saw that, uh, Snoochie Boochies over here and I thought he was trying
to kill you.
So I went to, I went to go put it, put his head in his ass, but, um, he ran, but I realized
now he was actually probably helping you.
So I feel a little bad for almost putting his head in his ass.
But you guys got healed up by that guy.
Yo.
And Patrick Yoda, you feel around your robe.
Oh, I'm feeling around.
All right.
Sorry.
But I've been feeling around this whole time.
Come on.
on
uh... homes
and singing
appealing itself up you also find
a note
uh...
it says in in on the on this little this piece of paper in my perfect gray l_c_a_
pixel five i got a digital watch
uh...
Road D
car 16 Road D
717 oh
Yeah, I've had this on me the whole time
Think I don't remember. I have a concussion
Was just like a grocery list. I think it is
Well what you would recall all of you potentially
but
Is that you did have to go to?
the Wendig station
to take a train to get to the Hu town, where the temple is rumored to be near that Hu town, which is the last stop on the Wendig Express at Wendig Station.
The only sort of transport that is actually functioning in the Soy Wastes.
You would also know, by the way, just a little bit of background on the soy wastes, is that soy is sort of a, it's kind of also a drug in its own light.
If you like snort it directly, your mouth kind of goes open for like a bit and you get a little bit of a buzz.
Sort of like snorting, like if you snorted caffeine, it's like kind of a similar kind of experience.
Does that make your mouth open?
No, that's the soy.
The soy does that.
Okay.
Is that still okay?
Like it's a joke in 2021 or is it kind of because I made it
because yeah, you think it's all right.
So yeah, yeah, so yeah, so that you would also know that's
about it for the details on that.
But yeah, so then you have this note in your pocket.
It's written in this like LCA pixel font.
um...
the air uh... your your your couple miles from the train station if i turn the
note upside down to the senate think funny like a calculator
it says boobs inexplicably
uh... you know
you can't have a little
or it says car sixteen roadie seven seventeen and i think it's going to back
over again
as you're turning it there's like no difference it really doesn't hurt it so
it's completely one eighty and then it just says boobs
like all that it's a you know
and all my god
uh... i think this i think this is a little bit of a little we need to find
some boobs
we found the local ticket and i found two right here
are you know more than a year earlier over the main war
or and i don't know i have a concussion
and i think uh...
i think we should head to the train station all the meanwhile his head is in
the ground in this feeder dangling up. He must be scared of boobs. I start
tickling his feet. I don't like that. I slap his feet. I didn't like that. I
pull him out. He is like his mouth is like completely a cape. His eyes are
bugging out
what happened
i don't remember
we were in the ship
and
where did we come from
i ate out of the statue
and then we crashed
yeah sullivan you crashed
the ship
with a real persuasion
yes i knew i was getting
advantage on that shit
you guys pretty much always have advantage in bullying sullivan
I got a 10.
Oh, I guess the set free.
Anyway.
You didn't do advantage.
You're right, I forgot.
Yeah.
Nat 20.
You got a crit.
A nat 20.
Sullivan's like, "Oh, God."
You fucking dumbass.
I always do.
Your arms were too small for the wheel.
You're the reason we're in this situation.
I don't know why I insisted on driving the ship.
I know how tiny my arms are.
You would try to.
To make it up to me, you can give me a piggyback ride to the next ship.
I don't know why I insisted on driving the ship.
I know how tiny my arms are.
You would try to.
I don't know why I insisted on driving the ship.
I know how tiny my arms are.
no i don't know how tiny my arms are. To make it up to me you can give me a piggyback ride
to the next destination. Okay if you insist. You're so much bigger than me. I know. I climb
onto Caleb's back before Caleb gets on. Yeah and I'll give you a blow toss, a piggyback
ride, and then blow toss you get Patrick Gill to a piggyback ride. I just physically I don't
think you'll get to wherever you want to go. Okay that's fine ship destroyer. Hey ruiner.
Okay, I'll try my best.
I hop on his shoulders.
Mm-hmm.
I hop on Cameron's shoulders.
I mean, he's already, like, crushed.
[laughter]
He just instantly...
He's just already flattened.
That's what does it.
Like, he can't lift you up.
He's like a pancake.
He's, uh...
Okay, I pick him back up and I blow into his mouth to make him 3D.
Okay.
And then we continue.
Oh, heavens!
the
(laughter)
- Smart.
- Anymore?
I did that before.
- I don't need no fancy escort, I'll take a normal slut.
- Hot dog, she says.
Yeah, so you guys can walk to the--
- I start sliding Sullivan along the ice.
- On the snow. - Curling.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, he's like, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
a
about like an hour walk. Okay, you're gonna also take some
damage in that time. But not too much because you're you have
the Yeti cloak on also. I'm I was born in ice. So I don't
take any you are resistant. You are going to take half damage
because you are and I'm a demon. So I take even more damage.
I wasn't going to have that be a thing, but you know, I'll
take it yeah I yeah and Patrick Yoda you take just the average amount of damage
simple man I don't need anything special yeah um so yeah as you guys so let me
roll for that actually I now brought out my I've used my physical let me take
I'll take like five times the damage that's you just want to go to hell I
and
will
above my head so that snow doesn't touch him that means he doesn't get caught. I give him my coat.
Okay all right Sullivan takes no damage. You guys have persuaded me. How much extra damage do I take?
We've had we've had a Sullivan death scare like twice an episode for the past few. Yeah I'm gonna
try to make I'm gonna uh I'm taking Sullivan back to the lab and fine tuning him to be a little bit
I'll take an extra four damage then.
Yeah.
And I want to take damage.
So the next night I'm trying to prove them tough.
Yeah.
I'm also wearing cargo shorts in the in the freezing cold.
And so as you as you guys sort of like approach the station,
it's like this blistering freezing cold and soy like you kind of
almost have to resist your mouth slowly opening up as you walk through it because it's just
like coming at your face so hard.
Hell yeah.
Floppy flu.
Pause.
And you see sort of like the unmistakable, you know, gaping maw of the Wendig Station.
It's the face of the eternal enemy of online public libraries.
This lone structure that sort of punctuates this godforsaken place.
Do any of us have books in our inventory? I just want to make sure.
Yeah, just make sure to protect those.
They like vanish the second you...
Didn't we kill him?
Well, so this is actually a very cool moment for me.
Two little war things we have to talk about.
I'm so excited. So I love the lore one part is that we have sort of in the year 2300.
We have that first gun city adventure now whether or not that is like officially Canon at this
point or if that is sort of an alternate universe gun city adventure because that is technically
like 55 years in the future from this these events that have happened. There's that and
so that's where Chuck Wendig was. Then...
Ah, okay.
Oh, so we're going into it...
We're going to kill him.
So we're going in a time machine at the end of the...
Yeah, we could do that. That's fine too.
At the end of the...
But then, um, uh, then...
That was our character. Our characters in the first Gun City were old, and we didn't
realize it.
Or they were our sons.
Okay, I like that.
Or they were your sons. And you all have, like, sons that are just...
Yeah, sons that are exactly us.
I'm trying to make this work for you Patches.
No, no, no, I think that's so funny.
Yeah, let's do that.
These are our identical twins.
Identical sons.
If there are any...
This is my identical son.
We were born 30 years apart.
If we have any autistic fans listening, this is a very big opportunity for you because
you can do some really nice actually is to other people on yes
room we actually like character is his son and I want to close on yeah I we
really heard the fans that can do that and hurt we need an artistic army don't
hurt people but the the other thing the other bit of lore so that's perfect
identical sons I that's canon for me that's cool that's golden the next thing
is
I thought you're talking about the place I came from.
Right, so you're from Whoville.
So that's what I'm interested in.
WhoTown is sort of like an outpost, because again,
very few actual communities in the Soywastes.
So WhoTown is sort of a small outpost that just has Whovians in it.
Do you have any relation to them?
Do you know them at all?
You're not from there then. You're from Whoville.
In this case, right?
Well, no.
Okay, so...
So my identical son is from Whoville.
Right. So that's why I'm-
But I am from the year 2011.
Because my father was a guy named Soldiers Wrath.
Wait, who's your father?
That's my father.
Who had a half-human-
The Christmas episode?
Yep. And you remember at the very end, the post-credit scene, he had a son and he said,
And he said, I'm going to cryogenically freeze my son.
Until I forgot about that.
Fifty years. So where were you from?
You're from who I was born in.
I was born a long time ago.
Yeah. And who?
Becca's then. OK.
But then I was cryogenically frozen.
I was, I guess, woken up in the preschool.
We all went to.
How are you? Futurama shit right now?
Yeah. So.
But so I was I was cryogenically frozen the minute I was born.
Right. Yeah.
So I don't have any memories of the past.
So do you know where you were?
I don't even know anything about the past.
Okay, so that's good.
We can keep it at that because, you know, maybe there's more we want to do with that.
But you know, you were frozen.
And get this, in the Christmas episode, that son, it was twins.
And my identical son was actually also frozen for even longer.
And he was frozen for 50 more years.
So my identical son's actually my twin brother.
Okay, I have a normal identical son.
None of this fancy, cryo, Walt Disney shit.
I just had a son that was just like me.
I mean, I'm a Yoda. I can live to be like 900.
- No, we already... - That could just be you.
We already said there's identical sons.
No, Patrick was around back during the Christmas episode.
Yeah.
So am I the only one with an identical son now? This is getting really shitty.
No, I'm not saying Patrick doesn't have an identical son. Maybe he does.
I'm an identical son. I have that was the identical son on the adventure, but I go to was retired. Yeah, okay
Yeah, yeah, all right. It's my identical son on in in the first one
Mm-hmm, and then I mean I'm still around I'm just I'm at home
Okay, and also I just want to say every episode it's a different care. My guy is a different guy
It's like James Bond yeah, I'm blue this episode also right there
Yeah, right cool. I'll get Joey or Kai on that. Thank you
All right
So I just wanted to know where we were at with the the who town thing mostly
But I'm glad we also cleared we chopped a lot of stuff up right there. Yep. Yeah. Yeah, so we'll see how much of that
People give it for yeah
so yeah, you approach the
the
station and
Let me see where all y'all's passive perceptions
Patrick Yoda is insanely high.
Yeah, Patrick Yoda, you pick up like sort of like there's like this sort of,
you know, I see staircase that leads up to the
pick up the stairs.
You pick up that there are these like sort of like a
the wanted posters on the wall next to that staircase.
It's really crudely drawn drawings of the four of you.
I still have a concussion right now, so I pick up the...
I take one of the wanted posters off the wall and I say, "Who the fuck are these guys?"
I say, "I think it's those guys." And there's a bunch of guys who look like stick figure versions of us.
this
better luck next time
yeah uh... uh...
and you also see so that people who who run the train station up here so you
know it's it's a it's a more industrial
kind of uh...
you transition compared to most of the like more sleek sort of cyberpunk e
stuff
uh... that you would see in gun city
so there's
just a bunch of snow myseries who run the train station
uh... he misers that kind of help for with the fuel and heat the
The the fuel that sort of powers train station and then conductor
misers that sort of conduct.
Trains and stuff.
All right.
Yeah.
Yeah, I made sure it worked.
So yeah, and yeah with the scene is one posters Patrick Yoda
and then you sort of as you sort of turn the corner towards
the staircase you see there are a lot of just like armored
Ken bones sort of inner just sort of monitoring and sort of
like putz and around.
but they are there
you know uh... uh... i did say that there was going to be potentially
consequences for this actually so they're they're around
okay
so you need to get tickets we need to get disguises
well i can disguise myself
i could buy a bunch of ticket i could buy i could disguise myself and buy
tickets for us
that's a good idea that's actually not a bad idea at all
okay i'm gonna do that
okay cool who do you want to discuss yourself as?
uh... an arcade repairman
(laughter)
okay yeah you're an arcade repairman
okay i'll get back into the maid outfit then just in case
i don't remember what i did but i do that
i don't remember what you did either. i think i was just me i don't think i did anything
i think you were like dusting a bitch with a feather. were you also an arcade repairman?
Can we just add Arcade Repairman outfit to our inventories?
I guess so, I can't not allow it at this point.
Because I did a whole thing with it.
Yeah, go into the ticket booth.
Mmm, okay.
Again, I'm just cleaning shit.
You see, Ticky the ticket bot is there.
Um...
And he's like, "Can I help you?"
Hello, mate!
I'm here to buy three tickets for just me.
And I'm here to repair you!
Who are you?
I don't know you at all.
I'm the Arcane Rebam.
I'm your twin brother.
I'm the Arcane Rebam man around here.
I slap him.
Ah!
Just good old...
So many officers start to turn, just notice what's going on.
Like, over there.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry. Someone hit somebody.
I'm like out of focus in the French maid outfit in the background.
Yeah.
There's something sexy behind you.
Where?
Um, you want three tickets?
Yeah, I reckon that's right.
And I'm here to repair you.
That'll be either coach or first class.
What's the difference?
First class is ten thousand tokens per ticket.
it
take on debt. What? You take on debt? I don't make the rules. Can I open up the control
panel in the back of this robot? You can certainly try. You're not a real arcade repairman. Well,
I don't have time to do some routine repairs I reckon. Yes, indeed. What? What are you
trying to do? I go up and start poking his eyeballs so he looks like an arcade game to
anybody's talking about. I'm just poking the lasers.
Yeah, I'm hitting it with the hammer, I'm opening it with the wrench.
Yeah, I'm opening the control panel. You want to do this, you have to do
slight of hand to make sure nobody notices. You guys
should set the first class ticket price to a dollar.
I got seven. Cameron, your turn. You're also an arcade repairman.
I clicked it, it won't work. 13. Okay, yeah,
you see uh uh one of the uh officers sort of like notice what's going on that somebody's got a
wrench and it's applying it to the ticket box and like hey okay but what's going on somebody wearing
an arcade repairman outfit so yeah no i know that's happening hey what's uh what's going on over here
where i see uh just a spot of routine updates i reckon indeed oh i think i dropped something over
for
are
causing a bit of a wreck is some of the snow misers are getting nervous.
All right, righty out.
Game, game on.
And I tell your friend over there that you know, if she's called you can have my coat
whatever no big deal.
He said he can have his coat.
Well, what are you are I reckon?
And what's your your coat?
My name is Ken.
I got I got it. I got to go. I'm I'm blushing to add these.
Get out of here. You big hunk of shit. Oh boy.
Um, um, it's often by the way is by the stairs like waiting for
you guys to get the tickets.
I forgot we needed four tickets.
We can we can we can do more repairs.
I can hide him in my big.
Did our repairs lower the prices at all?
the
to
Well is this, is this coin, this Mike Pence coin I have, can I convert that to, uh...
The dollars?
Can I convert that to dollars? Because it's a vintage coin and I know vintage coins are, uh...
They are, they do go for quite a bit.
Yeah, they're worth...
They go for quite a bit.
And this is from 2021 and we're in the year...
You know what, do a, um... shit.
We're in a later year.
You should be able to do a check where you could sort of appraise it.
sort of an archaeologist. So just do a...
I'm a genius. I'm a genius putting this in my inventory.
Let's just do I guess a history...
no, insight. No. Yeah, let's do insight.
It's history check, history check, because it's sort of like a... you're appraising
historical worth of it. Six.
You can't quite like properly... I appraise it with an 18.
Okay, yeah, you're able to appraise it very well. It's about 75 tokens.
75 tokens? It should be worth more than that.
Oh, it's like you've been carrying it around.
You know, Patrick, I have to say, I've just appraised this item and I think it's worth about 300 tokens.
Oh!
Awesome!
Ah, you landlubber!
It's about worth about 300 points!
Beautiful, mate! Beautiful!
the
it
Some of you can go into first class. Yeah, but I have one
Yeah, you have yeah, it's first. So I have one is 100
Yeah, you have 100 and then you appraise the coin for three. Yeah, it's seven. No, it's 75 and then 50
and then
Okay
Wait, no, I thought we would get around that
That's pretty close. You could get two of you in first class. I want to is there a camera go in first class
Is there enough for?
for them the other two people i can't do this bathroom you go in first class
yourself it's okay
i don't want to go first class i want to see i want to see how going first class
along with the other hand i sent patrick to first class alone
not only did patrick in the gun first class the argument there meant to go
well yeah i think it's going to better in this county a
he had waited until i got a little bit of a discount
I reach into the overall pocket of my outfit and I take out my arcade repairman ID card
as part of the disguise.
And everyone has to salute you as you board the train.
And I swipe it and the price goes down to one token.
So blow toss, blow toss, and I like the idea of blow toss and Patrick Yoda going to first
class and then we can have Ray William Johnson and Sullivan in coach.
Seems like good, safe parries.
a
I know it's you.
Don't tell anyone.
Crikey!
I want to ride coach with Sullivan to make sure that he rides coach and doesn't try to
sneak up.
Do you guys need money or what's going on?
Righto.
So what do you need, like $50 or?
We need $400.
$300.
$3,400.
the
enough though now yeah yeah I think so too except except I'm not sure it's
enough for Sullivan to ride first class now that I think all right he gets good
even if we have the money just want to go to yeah okay and I want regular I want
frequent cutaways to how he's doing okay can I get the seat like you know what
like on an airplane where it's like divided like first class and then coach
coach
experience entirely. Okay. I just wanted to be able to taunt him. Which is pretty funny.
I think he'll be okay. But he will be alone. We're sending him coach. We're just gonna
make you do scenes. By myself? Yeah. You have to voice everybody. We can play the other
characters and coach. We're gonna be busy enjoying ourselves in first class. We won't
be able to voice anyone. We'll see. We'll see how, we'll see. We're sending Sullivan and
coach it's decided. Who's enjoying, who's, uh, I guys can't see at home, but I'm tempting
my fingers. Who's going to enjoy. You look malicious. Yeah, I'm delicious. And you were
tempting your fingers, but you're tempting my dinger. If you know what I'm saying. That's
really good. That was good. That was good. The conductor miser says, uh, all aboard, all
aboard. So most of the trains in the station by the way, there's
only like a couple of passenger trains. So you know that like
whatever train you're going on is probably the right one. There
are 15 cars that are coach two cars that are first-class.
The other trains are mostly carrying resources to and from
the first-class cars mostly are going to have like sort of kind
of business magnets who are kind of striking it out on trying to make some money off of
the soy wastes, which is kind of this unenclaimed, sort of unmanned territory. Now, excuse me,
so I bet that might. Your experience getting on to first class, it's lush, there's, you
know there's a box there that can give you guys food and stuff the only other
thing is that there are pretty frequent Ken bone officers to around and so we'll
have to address how you guys sort of continue to avoid them your disguise
lasts how long again forever the whole game the whole train ride I don't think
it has a duration let me check it's an outfit is it the same right duration is
five minutes but I will say it is an outfit. It is in my inventory. Okay but I can keep
the disguise on and maybe it doesn't work quite as well. Well basically. Like your face is
back to blow toss. Yeah. So yeah as opposed to the face of an arcade repairman. A dirty
coal covered face of an arcade repairman. Which will sort of like you know I'll do some
like checks on my end but that's gonna start to potentially cause you problems since they
are actively looking for you guys. How long do we know but it's a it's going to be about
like an hour and a half. Okay, it's fine. Like it. Yeah, I'm sitting in the bathroom
the whole time. And then on Sullivan side is coach where most of the passengers are.
So coach is a very different experience. It's a lot of worker bots and bones that live and
sleep there. Some of them never get off their stop and then they just get fired and they
live inside of the train. They trade stories and Yu-Gi-Oh cards, other cheap artifacts as
currency. They eat SpaghettiOs and snort soy. Sort of like a hobo community has developed
there. And it's just like a massive place and it's just filled with burly, stinky people
And Sullivan is just sort of now also in there, just kind of pretty out of place.
Yeah. So that's sort of what's happening there now.
Now you guys are, you know, there's two cars up in first class.
So one of them has presumably one of them has
at least somebody you're supposed to meet
at some point, perhaps snitchy
boochies based on sort of the order of events.
so yeah we as we do you're you're in the car now you haven't
shrimp cocktail
i have a martini
case will have a a sort of uh...
uh... area of area dapper looking can bone can i come up to you
on what can i get you all
today's shrimp cocktail
well me next and you
I'm super nervous now cuz I know I fucked up my martini.
Okay, and you gentlemen arcade repairman.
Nothing for me love.
Oh wait.
I think my my I'm sorry.
I got something to say.
I like one shrimp cocktail.
The thanks of a job well done is enough nourishment for me.
You didn't hear me earlier.
Do a perception check.
You don't notice anything in particular.
All right.
Oh shit.
So is it right right away then sir?
And so yeah, the love the dapper.
Dapper camp don't go little heart and
Meanwhile in
We're meanwhile in in coach we Sullivan is just sort of a
Trying to hang with everybody and it's all these sort of like like dude. It's like a completely different. It's like brown and murky
It's like the area and snowpiercer like the the broke area. He's like suddenly in peasant clothes
Yeah, yeah, and he's just like he sees some SpaghettiOs on the floor and some guy goes, "Hey, eat it!
Eat the SpaghettiOs! It's good for ya!"
Okay, he starts eating it. He's like trying to enjoy himself and
And he also notices that there's a
there's another man who sort of like saunters up to him. He's sort of this uh
Is this white guy with like a messy brownish blackish hair and he's got sort of a long coat on and
he's got with him some bucks some Victorian broad and
He goes up to this frog and he picks him up by his shirt and starts lifting him up and he says
I know you from somewhere and someone's like
We cut back to you guys
So you're in
First class you guys start to notice that there is somebody else here that you do recognize
a
Dapper little man
Not Sullivan a different dapper little man
Someone who you were once business partners with a former Sullivan the frog impersonator
Oh, it's his identical son Gary C
Oh
a
Hold on, hold on, don't drop the...
Ahh! A Vastian Landlubber!
[Laughter]
Okay...
Gary C. Enterprise!
Hey man, it's me, it's me, picture me.
Ahh! I haven't seen ya in many moons!
Oh my god! You guys, I can't believe it's you!
No! We're down there!
Sorry about that. Sorry about that. Sorry about that.
Wow.
I'm here to fix the GANACA machine.
To fix the... you wanna...
Is this... is this...
Shut up. Shut up.
Sorry. Sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Do you have a space invaders cabinet I can fix?
I... I... is this code?
Gary C. Enterprise.
Look, I just... I just wanna know if I should play along in some way or if this is coding.
Just quiet. Quiet.
Do the voice.
Do the voice back
Oh, uh, give me one second
What you got to do here?
That's Borat
What?
Bow-wow-wee-wah
No, wrong
Don't like Borat
You sound like Borat and Wada
What the fuck
Are you under way to the arcade repairman convention as well?
Yeah, I can't wait to go to Dodge
Stop just copying whatever voice
I like your unvoiced
I had my own voice until you guys told me to do a new voice.
Security, there's a copycat here.
Don't call security!
I'm a little following the law.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom, mate.
And when I come back, me to figure out what the fuck.
The actual dumbest episode we've ever done.
Already.
I'm gonna repair the arcade toilet.
I think I will help him.
You guys can go to the bathroom together?
Hey, how about you come with us, Gary?
You can tell us how the business has been going.
Okay, I'll come with you!
What are you doing?
I don't know anymore.
He's playing your parrot.
Okay, what to repair?
We can show you how to repair the arcade toilet in the bathroom.
he not
and
give me one second car so on
bring that's right
of course uh...
and uh... you you uh... you see he leaves the play the shrimp cocktail dislike on
the floor right outside
any currency you really got it
do you want your martini also by the bathroom who would you like it just on
the table no i'm i'm ok i'll just take it right here
okay
bank god
uh... yes you guys finally needed to we need to talk to gary enterprise about
anything
on the city you want to i want to get in with the other two dogs and hot
noodles
and uh... yeah or cut back to coach now
and you see uh... solving the frog is uh...
uh... was being held up by his uh... collar
and now you see he's being uh... jostled around the seems like a buddy of this
guy
and skies disguise like uh...
now i know
and all we want to learn the frog
the catch a picture
if we are the guys because all across this year tree my name
now is the roy peter putter
the mayor
to get to hear you gotta show your friend of the working people
bones in the box
some filamentals
andy's as old and like uh... uh...
okay i just i just want to make sure that my friends are okay there
they ended up in a totally different section they said that they were in at
a ticket so
well i'm still concerned
no i i understand but you see here that we can have cops on the street train
they don't like what we do we okay
we got this whole boat society it's a beautiful thing
display tears of the
the paradise okay
and when you got
coppers walk around
back here okay i feel we want to call them a cause of the people
okay instead do do
all right i'm not a friend of the poopoo
and look at you looking at this is my wife abigail peter putt
my name is abigail peter but i'm one of leroy's three hundred wives
and she's the parties the rest of my system being honest
the mice when you get in the sack
uh...
he meets the saki puts them in to hit some of the rabbit so i will have to come
out of the night
i don't talk to my such as mariam
can make that clear enough.
And then what does Sullivan say?
Sullivan just goes, "Okay."
Sullivan looks at like a mice that crawls by and he's like, "How do you do?"
He's like, "They ain't gonna respond, trust me."
Now look, what I'm saying is, if you and your friends are on this train, okay, you're increasing
The number of poopoos on this train.
I got a half a mile to turn y'all in just to protect my people here.
I don't need poopoos making a sneaky mess of my operation.
Code name diaper.
Dialectical intelligence apparatus.
People eating real food finally.
OK, we're just trying to get some real food here.
We've been eating synthetic SpaghettiOs for about 50 years now. OK.
So look, if you can get me the camera cuts back to
to me eating like, I have like 16 shrimp cocktail in the bathroom now. I'm just eating them
talking to Gary Enterprise. Like I'm just throwing tails all over the place.
He gets a dipalma split screen and we just see you like bathing in it.
I unzipped Gary C. Enterprise's backpack and while he's not looking I'm eating cold hot
dogs out of his backpack from behind him.
Now you get me some of that food from first class.
I can take care of them poo-poos for you.
So they stop messing up my diaper, making a mess.
I hand a hot dog across the split screen.
Oh man, I am tempted to just...
Roll a d20 if you get a 19 or a 20.
Oh, yeah, you try to hand it the hot dog just like explodes.
I just put my hand out.
Who did that?
He's like looking around.
He's like getting nervous.
He looks down at Sullivan.
He's like, I couldn't be you.
You're too sweet.
Now go get me some food.
I can get the popo off your ass.
this
the
through we actually first we cut back to Ray William Johnson who's just politely
drinking a martini. Yeah my legs are crossed. Yeah. I'm just drinking the martini so
beautifully in my maid outfit. Yeah, Ray William Johnson you look past the window
into the next car and you do see the hooded figure of Snoochie Boochie's in
there. You can sort of make that out now that you have like a moment alone with
No external stimuli.
This guy very clearly sees one car over in car 16.
And then cut back to the bathroom.
So you guys are harassing Gary C. Enterprise.
Like, "I'm really glad you guys are here.
As you can see, I stopped being a Sullivan the Frog impersonator.
I've decided I've got to have my own voice.
Got to be my own character.
And I have you guys to thank.
The business is doing great.
Now I don't just sell V-food. I sell real food."
Great, the business is doing great.
So where's our cut of the money?
How'd you guys get out of jail?
Wait, hold on, hold on!
Hold on, hold on!
I'm a big Caucasian man.
Well, I was donating most of the money to...
You were donating the money? What the fuck?
The free you guys, the free you guys!
Who told you to donate that money?
You did. You said every cent...
You guys were being hauled off to jail.
You said if a single cent of this doesn't go to getting us free,
Go to getting us free. It's your head Gary
Donated to a free the free the free the poppy killers fund
He takes out his PSP it shows you the Kickstarter page just like a tasteful video of the three of you guys like
Some of them hit the hit the highest goals you can see here now you do have to take out a few people to dinner
I'm afraid hold on one sec
God so can I get a shrimp po boy in here?
I'm caging now by the way. He's rolling dice - that's a bad side
Yoda by birth occasion by the grace of God
Okay, yeah you hear a knock on the door and
It is not Carson. It is a Ken bone guard who takes up the entire width of the door
Well, he can't you like wait if he did he open the door already cuz I mean the doors closed were in the bathroom
It's a lot. Yeah. No, that's what you see sort of I should say. That's what you say. Okay, so I turn invisible
Okay, just before anything else. Yeah, I
Open up Gary's backpack and I take out his spare suit
I put on a blue suede suit.
Now I'm a different guy.
I'm no longer an R. I put my arcade repairman suit back.
I put on Hatchik's arcade repairman suit on over mine.
And it's Yoda sized so you just, it's like you're wearing like...
There's like so much rustling that you can hear from outside the door.
And you see the Ken Bogart he sort of sounds like the
the
City 17 guys in half-life 2 but like with a Ken bone voice being put through and it's like
Cuz this one's like a suited up boys. Like there's a real right in there
Yeah, yeah, yes, sir
Why are there two people I tap it was shoulder
Excuse me, ma'am. Hey, you want to join the four and a half foot high club?
In a different bathroom, that's what I meant
Roll persuasion. I just kind of assumed we were in a big bathroom. Stop talking. Okay
He's like we're moaning cuz I thought you were big character as the kid. Okay was I was
He says uh, hmm
All right, um
There's no food you want to go to the bathroom the other cart. Oh
Yeah, this one seems occupied. Yeah, I don't buy at least two or three two or three guys. I think we're having sex
All right, all right just just don't tell my supervisor, okay, I really shouldn't but you guys
I definitely won't let's go. Yeah, you guys go to the other cart as you're walking by you see Snoochie Boochies
He doesn't you know, he doesn't know you but you guys can kind of know each other to see each other
They're kind of, you know, there's like an acknowledgement,
but you're wearing a French made out.
Yeah.
Yeah, he might be a little confused.
And yeah, so you're going to end up in the bathroom there and
I will cut back to that soon.
Meanwhile doing some roles for Sullivan on the side.
See how he does.
Yeah.
I just started pretending to be Sullivan.
I
I want to, um, Hey, uh, Gary, I mean, now that, now that we're here, I think, yeah, sure.
What's going on?
I think it makes sense for, uh, you to give us all the money you made.
Yeah, that's a good point.
I mean, it's the fund is that we were here.
No, no, no, no.
You've got it.
You've got a good point, fellas.
Here's what I could do.
I can open, I can open up an account.
All right.
I'll transfer the money in there.
It's gonna take one in three days, but you'll see it all in there in one in three days. Okay, how does that sound?
So so we can get like a joy I can give you any cash I have on me
I mean not all of it. I need to you know, I don't win the account
I'm scouting out a location in who in who town actually gonna be to try to have the first
Gun City restaurant in the soy waste. Huh? Where do you go? Yeah, pretty big and our names are gonna be on it
Well, I yeah, of course your plaque is up on every restaurant
It's as a three guys who murdered a guy
How many other locations guys who murdered a guy maybe that's what I should call the restaurant
Well, how many other locations are there yeah, there's there's three in gun city right now, you know, it's a small chain
You know sort of a boutique sort of chain. Oh, so how much weight how much money do we have? Oh
Oh, well, you guys have probably a couple hundred thousand tokens.
Yeah, I mean, put it in the account.
Couple thousand each.
Oh, yeah. You just couldn't access it because you were criminals.
Can I get your phone number to?
Yeah, but you put your phone on my phone and we can exchange numbers
because that's how it works in the future.
Yeah, of course. Everybody knows that you guys stack your PS.
OK, but for me, my phone doesn't have that.
My PSP doesn't have that functionality.
Could do like 10 years ago.
I'm going to need you to say your number out loud for me to write it down.
Sure.
555.
Okay, I know that's a fake number for movies.
I'm not stupid.
No, no, we're in a movie all the time.
So I'm going to need you to read out your number for me out loud.
I put it in the chat.
Not sure who you're talking to anymore.
Oh, okay.
Here is the Enterprise for your phone number.
910-228-0664.
Okay, thank you. And I can call you any time of day, even in the middle of the night.
Especially in the middle of the night.
Cool, thank you, Gary.
Yes.
Is that okay?
Yeah, I don't care. It's already...
I've gotten 180 texts since we started.
Holy shit.
I'm up to 1700 texts today.
It's probably fine.
Yeah, it's fun.
The phone company is going to reach out to you sometime.
Good.
And be like, "What's going on, man?"
I'm popular.
What's going on?
Do thousands of people have your number or something?
What's happening?
No.
Yeah, my friends.
Yeah.
All right, so what's going on now?
Yeah, so you got Gary C. Enterprises number.
And hundreds of thousands of tokens.
Some serious money is on the way for you guys.
Wait, one second. Before we leave the bathroom, before we cut away, I call the number just to make sure he's not
trying to pull a fast one.
Yeah, his phone rings.
It's of course, yeah, it's a yeah, what's the ringtone? 910
Mm-hmm. Two two eight
Oh six six four, let's call this here
Let's see. Let's see if Gary C enterprise picks up. Hello
Hello. Hello. Gary. Is that you?
Yeah, yeah, it's me
Yeah, no problem buddy
the
uh... up
in
uh... i i
i like it
well what do you into big boy you want to be blindfolded
Oh wow, I never um...
That's like what I'm into is blindfolding guys.
Yeah, hey, whatever floats your boat, baby.
Alright.
I take a very sexually take off one of my stockings.
Oh hot mama.
Wrap it, shut up, and wrap it around his eyes so he can't see anything.
Okay.
Wow.
These are not translucent, they're opaque.
Yeah, opaque stockings, yeah.
They're very expensive.
[laughter]
A lot of material goes into that.
Okay, now next step open your mouth.
Ah, why am I saying ah?
Here comes my vagina and I slowly insert my sword into his brain.
Okay, yeah.
There it is.
Roll an attack roll. It's going to be an auto crit.
Yeah, so just do an automatic crit attack roll on this guy.
Where is, what should I roll?
So just roll the attack and then you can just press the damage in chat.
So that's, okay, so that's 22 points of damage.
Uh, he is just concussed. You just like, fucking like,
fucked up his brain. He's just like,
*pfft* *BURP* and he's just like,
smashed his head on the, on the uh,
sink. And then I flush him down the toilet.
*laughter*
You're gonna try to do that?
I would like to.
Okay, um...
Stealth check, if you're gonna try to flush a whole man down the toilet.
Well, you sound like I'm shitting.
You sound like you're shitting, yeah.
Why don't-- wait, why don't you chop him up?
I'm not gonna chop-- that's disgusting!
What the hell, dude? Ugh.
What's wrong with you, you fucking psycho?
What the fuck, you're a freak, dude.
You're weird. I-- I gotta tend.
Yeah, by some miracle, they don't really notice you.
Um, just stuffing this man in a toilet.
uh... and down
you know you push it down as we all know what happens in flush someone down
the toilet and train
you just hear like underneath the car
uh...
perfect and then i a the train tracks are covered in shit and now a couple of guys
and then i i uh...
open the door to the bathroom and i close it i start waving my hand in front of my face
the you do not go in there
yeah cuts that that there was just like
just like so much blood it's like it
uh...
snitchy buchy's is uh...
cc walking away in doing a p_q_ thing we will in johnson
and you hear me goes
easy to
uh... or you're looking for a of beautiful fringe made
are you one of the four
the four
beautiful french maids that you
no
yes
but can you can and i can camera and i go over here now he had course okay
yeah i'm still a little bit able to do but i'm still disguised as as sullivan
now
i'm still alive
i'm still going to arcade repairman outfits
and i'm
I bring Gary C. Enterprise with us.
Okay.
Yep, here's the fourth one too.
Yep, here he is.
You're being confusing.
I know that that is not the fourth one.
Who are you?
I forget myself.
My name is Snoochie.
Please sit down.
We can talk more.
Okay.
I do not wish to cause a commotion.
All right, well, if you want to.
Yeah, you guys sit down.
He says, "It's good to see that you are all healing from your wounds.
I was concerned. I have been tracking you for some time.
I know that you are..."
Do you have any Jell-O I can eat? I'm sorry, I'm just so hungry right now.
"No, only that the cursed Jim has the Jell-O."
Oh, right, I forgot about that detail in the story.
"Yeah, it was just a very nice coincidence.
I
Have been tracking you for some time. I know you are searching for the n-word pass and
He sort of looks around the train cars, he said nobody's kind of looking and he takes off his hood and
His face is like inexplicably a Tamagotchi
He puts his head like not like a Tamagotchi device
Alright, stand back, I'm going to repair it.
*laughter*
He looks like a Tamagotchi creature, not a Tamagotchi device.
Oh, okay.
He looks like one of the creatures.
Never mind, I mixed up what I was seeing.
I thought you were a device.
*laughter*
And, uh, so it's like his pic- it's like a pixelated face that's similar LCA screen, like digital watch screen.
Like in inexplicably existing in real space
And then he puts the hood back up. He says I am the last of my kind
All of us have died out these
He's of course just what happens the passage of time
however, I
Believe I have a chance to bring my people back or at least
Maybe live out my days and not so much
lonely destitution
You see Tamagotchi sorry mortal. However, for some reason my brethren have died
But the inward pass you
This is a great concern for me as well. Yes, I
Need to be fed. We all did I
Can't hot dog
You see him like ravenously like I'm gonna give him another hot dog
I give another hot dog. Stop. You're going to make me grow
No.
(laughter)
You see, the N-word pass holds a great power for the Tamagotchi people.
It is not just some common artifact.
I know your employer desires it, and I understand this.
But I can help you get it.
And if you will allow me to have it, I could perhaps give you a counterfeit one.
Your employer will not know the difference, but please, for the sake of my people, and
most importantly, you must keep it out of that Jim's hands.
That is a man I can see as ill-intent.
He works with the Crayola.
The Crayola, they despise the Tamagotchi.
They see us as fads, and them as eternal toys.
As what?
Fads.
Don't you, motherfucker?
Okay.
the
I humbly request that you help me. I promise I
Can I can make it right with your employer and whatever circumstances you'll need please as men of archaeology
You must understand why this is important. I
Don't remember why we need to find this
So we don't go to jail, oh right
But we got a lot of money
To get out of jail. Yeah, that's true - true. I'm kind of fine to go back to jail now
Yeah, you know I kind of like it. I'll help you out snitchy-boochie
I kind of liked it in there better if if jail is your problem
I promise to help you escape it this time. I got you are noble people. We do not back down on deals
Okay, it's a deal. All right. Well
Thank you. Why do you need this pass? Wait? Can I do an insight check to see if he's telling? Yeah
is
it
I guess okay. All right. I'm going to glean I glean
Okay, this is a clean chai roll to glean. I got a 24
Okay
Yeah, blow toss with that for you think you can't tell what he could he could be thinking anything
It's scaring you a little that 24 Ray William Johnson
You can tell he's earnest and he means this he's earned. I think he's earnest and he means this yes sort of is his
Hey, I'm just like don't want to talk
That is this heart is like set on doings on on on
On getting this this n-word pass and that he really believes it can it can help him
And he doesn't wish to do wrong by you. I shake his hand. Why do you need the why do you need the pass?
Why did he Tom I got you man? He said that it will keep his people alive. I
I
Why does the other guy need it
The n-word pass has the incredible ability to and then before he can reveal it
You hear freeze and
Then you see a trash can
into the door
with Sullivan the frog
tumbling out
handcuffed
and you see a couple of Ken Bones flanking you guys
mmm I'm so I have an idea
some in the back I have an idea me
okay you guys hide Sullivan now that I'm disguised as Sullivan
the
well for initiative
the the the the
the the the the the
Probably.
Or should we go over to the website?
[MUSIC PLAYING]