[music]
So, after we determined that we needed the blueprints to the I-Cup facility,
we met with that architect, John Architect, who then told us to go to the Black Rock Development and Real Estate Association building
where we managed to retrieve the blueprints.
The other items we need to gather in the next 5 days are
1) A way to perform a successful biometric scan matching Fatima Von Kissyface, the head of the ICUP facility
2) Quantum crypto credentials that we can use to download the funds
3) Love Slime that Barry Gee can use to build a bomb to blow up the vault
and golden bullets that Travis Ocelot can use to disable security system in the facility.
We're gonna need at least the quantum cryptokronidges probably,
but without the other items though, this will be tough either way.
After barely making it back,
without alerting every officer on the Jollibee Fort,
and almost losing all of my blood
to a reimagining of a children's toy as a security guard,
we were greeted by none other than Mommy Goodlands.
Me and my three best friends knew her from our time as private investigators.
Back then, she sort of played us a bit.
Not being honest with us about being controlled by Papi Chuko,
that she knew about the Calculus Rift,
that, you know, she wasn't being honest about Papi Chuko because she knew about that,
that she had a former business relationship with him,
that sending us into the Matrix 2 was almost certainly going to lead to our deaths,
but allow her a chance to escape.
Other than that, she's great
And it also seems that well, she looks pregnant. So that's I guess good for her. But what was she here for?
And so yeah, mommy good legs has showed up at your door
She last you heard escaped south
away from gun City after all everything that fell out of
fill out of control the end of the
Broad City the uncle's Falcon Ark
And now she's back and she sees you all and she says hello boys
You became so fat to me
Can I see if I can hear the baby kick from the back? I put my finger in your belly button
To do an experiment on your baby
It looks like you ate a balloon
*laughter*
Good to see you haven't lost any of your charms.
Do you bounce?
*laughter*
We have to test if you bounce.
Please, please don't test if I bounce.
Get over! Bounce on the ground!
Bounce. Bounce.
Bounce. Now. Bounce.
I know you could do this to most of the other NPCs in the game, but I'm not gonna bounce.
I'll fuckin' kill your baby, I don't care.
a
'Cause he put a baby in her
Alright, let's hear him out, but Sullivan has to go in the other-
Let's hear her out, 'cause Sullivan has to go in the other room.
'Cause, uh...
He's- he's eyein' her weird.
Do you guys mean that?
I think you're right.
Do I have to go in the other room too?
I think Sullivan's in her belly.
We need you if shit goes south with this baby.
What do I do if shit goes south with the baby?
You kill the- you kill her.
her. Okay, what's her name? What's going on? So yeah, very key and Travis, you probably
both wouldn't necessarily know. Travis, maybe we don't know. I don't know. Yeah. Yeah. So
she was just like, she was like in the first gun city arc. She was the which was sort of
the
that too. Yes, you do.
That's what I didn't say that.
Yeah, no.
So yeah, very key.
You probably don't you probably don't know her.
I mean, maybe you do. I don't know.
You've been around a while.
She did own a famous nightclub
that then belong now belongs to Jamal the worm.
and
And, uh, she says to you all, um,
well,
your break in into the black rock building,
I was noticed by one of the young men who's been working for me for some
time. You see, uh, he was there as well,
retrieving something from, for myself, the way I see it.
I don't know what you guys are up to,
the
we got a steal? Yeah, what are you gonna do, burp and fart? Oh, that was a good one. Wait.
That gives me an idea. What if we hid in your big fat belly? And you walked into the to
this? What is it? The store? That could actually work, I think. Money store. Well, I guess
this
But I offer some information, and then you guys can tell me what you're up to.
Does that sound alright?
Yeah, I guess, but we won't be listening.
We'll be playing video games.
All the better for me, I suppose.
I had a gentleman go in there and look into another building that was developed recently
under one of poppy chukos pseudonyms
which concerns me because i-
what?
was it choopy poppy?
it wasn't choopy poppy it was...
i wrote this down
okay...
do we have to-
do we have to listen to all of this?
*laughs*
you could certainly tune me out like blotas is
who's playing video games
like what game are you playing blotas?
i don't know
*laughter*
I just don't wanna listen.
I'm playing a game called "Controller Wars"
I throw the controller at my friends.
*laughter*
The point is, is that
I'm concerned that Papi Chuko's still alive.
He might not be.
Might be somebody else, but
Choopy Papi.
Didn't I punch his head off of his body?
Well, that's right, but
you know, we have enough money. There's a lot of things you can do in Gun City.
the
That's fine. Is he alive or dead? I think he's dead, but he could be alive.
Look. I don't care about this anymore. Okay, yeah, listen, listen, bitch.
You better have that baby right now or get the hell out of here.
I want to see what's inside of her. I hope the baby's a frog. I'm gonna
I'm gonna roll insight to see like, cause she kind of betrayed us before I want to see if she's uh
Yeah what do you want, what specifically are you trying to read into?
Um, well I, it seems like
Like a part of her story or, or, or um, yeah sorry go on
I guess the fact that she like noticed we were stealing something and then came to us because of that seems fishy
that maybe like she is trying to get us caught or something
So I want to search for evil intentions in her brain. Yeah camera, that's amazing
That's the 13 you have a mind reading ability and you don't know
I was gonna use it after
Okay. Yeah 13. I mean from what you can glean and you know
Obviously mommy good legs is a pretty practiced con
Artist to some some extent but from what you can glean with the 13. She seems to be her attention seemed to be
the
I'm gonna try and make her water break.
*laughter*
Through poking her.
Uh huh.
It's just not gonna make my water break, Patrick.
You're doing an ath-
I saw a butterfly outside.
You're doing an athletics check?
You're rolling athletics, Patrick?
Yep.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to make the water break.
Yeah, you just sort of
poke her stomach continually.
it's not gonna make the... it's not even where the... it's not like where the water...
is...
where is the water, Patches?
I don't know, isn't it like lower than that?
can you tell me where the water is?
so I can...
where is the water?
isn't the water lower than that?
you're such an expert
where's your water?
hmm
googled "where is the water"
getting a lot of swimming schools
the water tower bar
doesn't matter so
uh... that's what you can clean from doing an insight check though camp so
yeah
yeah i mean is normal
we can tell you i see if she's lying about being pregnant
uh... you certainly could be a
i mean that's
i don't know i guess it's a medicine check really is what that is
So keep that rolling.
She's not pregnant.
I mean, yeah, I mean, she gave you some information.
She was wondering if you would give her information in return
and see if she can help you or you can help her.
You certainly don't have to.
You can just refuse her help.
What information do you want from us?
What did she get out of it?
Does she want a cut?
Can I study her belly?
the
setting my belly 13 how do we get out of this scene you know what here you can
do whatever you want Sullivan go back in here you talk to the big fat man what
Why we are here.
You tell Santa all about it.
Do you really?
Okay.
I guess Sullivan just explains it.
He explains the situation.
Explains what?
So he needs to be, he needs to be kind of bashful and embarrassed.
As he's explaining it?
Do you want me to?
Yeah.
Do you just want me to do it?
Okay.
And he needs to cry.
Well, uh.
the
Vomit watching you cry get the fuck out of here
listen, bitch, we gave a bunch of money to a fucking charity and
Now we're scared. So we're trying to get it back
He's scared, okay
Okay, you're trying to get money back from a charity. Yeah. Yes
No
Do you have gold bullets
a
So where do I go?
You have a baby.
I'll give you that information if I can get your assurance that when I need you and I
call upon you, you'll come.
Well for what?
We're just gonna say yeah.
I don't know how to deliver a baby.
I'm not gonna help you with that if that's what you're asking.
I could do that.
You can deliver a baby or you're going to accept what I'm saying?
I can deliver a baby.
We'll do whatever you say whenever you want.
Yeah, whatever, I don't care.
I got, I got, uh, all the, I got, I got the force or whatever.
I don't know.
Okay, but it can't be, it can't be like ridiculous or stupid.
Like it has just, so just make it something normal.
Okay.
It can't be like a, like a test.
Yeah, we can't, you can't be like tricking us right now.
Okay.
It's not a trick.
It's just, I don't know what I'll need to get done.
What I need to get done.
Right.
And if it's more than 10 minutes from now, the deal's off.
the
okay guys smile she goes okay are you familiar with the Cabrera sisters
mmm yeah Tamara mm-hmm close Mary Kate and Ashley Cabrera they were cyborgs
you work for the Mad Suckla, who now have the territory divided up at the slums.
If you go to the slums, I'm sure somebody there can point you in the right direction
if you just have to encounter one of the many runners that are on there, that are down there,
figure out which one of them knows the information, you can shake them down.
Specifically if you go to a particular territory, I'll mark it on your map here, and she marks
it
the
Oh my god. Okay, I'll give you a cut.
Yeah, I'll cut the baby out.
I'm going to give you a cysterian section.
I'm going to use a Jedi mind trick right now.
She doesn't know how much money we're going to steal, right?
We can just sell her that.
Yeah, we will give you half of it.
Yeah, we're going to give you all of it, actually.
No, half.
You want to have your baby right now.
You're offering half before I say what I want.
Okay, what do you want?
I want to have my baby.
Now I want half
You have half, you get it
You're gonna have half
Roll deception
You're gonna be so embarrassed about how little money we are trying to steal
Do you get advantage though, Travis?
After you roll deception
I roll deception then
My thing is a loading
Why am I deception so low?
God damn
Goddamn because it's tied to
Your charisma, which is weirdly low, but you get advantage so you get to roll again
Yes
You're right on all deception checks time to trick the expecting mother
That was a six
Okay, she says
Look if you can't give me a half a quarter just a quarter then I
Got a quarter right here. And that's all the same
Quarter. Yeah quarters. Yeah quarter for sure. You'll get a quarter of it. I guess she thinks she won
You know what you'll get you'll get 75%
All right, fellas shake on it
the
and
credentials now I can go into details for this but I think we're done I think
we should go to the slums yeah so I think it's slum time do you think so I need to
be there right now okay all right but first let's let's sort of fan the smell
of her farts out of the room yeah we need to do it like a sage cleanse so that
the baby spirit isn't hanging around in here.
Okay, you're gonna do a sage cleanse?
No, let's go to slums.
Athletics for the sage.
My core, yeah.
Okay, cool, yeah.
Athletics?
Yeah.
So yeah, you guys head to the slums.
You guys would know about Mary Kay and Ashley Herrera, because you guys did meet them very
briefly when you were in the Mad Suckler's den.
The slums have been constantly warring for some time, though with the Mad Suckler's death,
you know, by the hands of Papi Chuko.
Now the Cabrera sisters sort of divided up, betrayed the Sucklist, divided up his territory,
control the Techno Slime market and are kind of an arm for many of the businesses in the
city.
And while Papi Chuko's company is sort of cycling through CEOs, can't really get their
shit together, they still shirk the kind of criminal, they sort of shirk the criminal
warlords, they don't have the discretion or craftiness of the Sucklist.
So they've kind of just been sucking the slums dry of all instead of, you know, sort of distributing
that kind of the pain that you can distribute when you're running a criminal enterprise.
And so it's kind of like the buffer that you would normally have of having a slums that's
indebted to you is kind of gone here. It's a little bit more lawless than from the last
time you were here. A lot more, a lot more.
There's no laws?
What?
There's no laws here?
is
the trash can and I try again.
Okay.
Roll another athletics check.
Ten.
Ten, okay.
You get like the same spot and you just dent it in a little bit more.
And then at that point now you see somebody, he sort of like pops their head out of the
window of a building.
He goes, "What the fuck are you doing?!"
I throw the trash can at him.
Alright, he's pretty high up.
Roll athletics though.
Nine.
You just, you throw it on the top of the car, and it just bounces on the other side of the
car.
What the fuck?
And he sort of, he shuts his window and he goes downstairs.
You hear him go downstairs.
You hear him come to you.
Uh, he comes outside.
And he starts to square up with you, Patrick Yoda.
It's just, just a regular guy.
I pick up the trash can and try to throw it at him again.
Okay, he's gonna try to stop you from doing this.
So he is standing in front of you.
I point both of my guns at him.
Oh no, stay out of this.
Let him, let Patrick deal with this.
Don't be an asshole, let me do this!
the
involved anymore. I was gonna show you a trick, look, and then I start juggling the guns.
Um, all right, I'm just gonna, you know what, just, just, um, I'll move my, I'll move my,
do you know any criminals? Fucking no, I'm just, I don't know, are you a criminal?
You literally came down here to try to pick a fight with a guy who was doing,
basically nothing, destroying my car. I bet you've called the cops on at least one guy.
You know what the trash barrel can at the car
19 goes through the driver's seat window. I asked him to give us all the information we need. Yeah
What you want to know just please stop throwing the fucking drug where is the water in a woman's baby?
Yeah, we want to know where to buy golden bullets and we want to know
*multiple people talking at once*
I don't know what the fuck you're talking about, Golden Bullets, I don't, I don't...
Yes or no question, who is the worst person in the whole area?
Oh, that's actually a good question.
Uh, that was me, the DM.
Um, uh, uh, well, I...
*sigh*
Dougie Freeze?
Okay, we're going to kill him now. Goodbye.
Where did you live?
No, no, no, just, just, just, uh...
We're gonna tell him that you told us to do it.
Fuck you!
We will tell his whole family, especially if he has like brothers, that it was all your fault.
Yeah, if he has a kid, we're gonna tell the kid that it's your fault.
Unless you tell us who the second worst person in the whole entire area is and where we can find him.
And if I can take your car radio.
Don't, why you...
I don't know who the second worst person is.
Can I have the car radio?
The guy who runs the bodega down the block, he sucks.
That's all, I mean, Dougie Freeze is the worst guy, probably anybody who works under him.
Okay, okay.
You're avoiding my question.
I'm not taking my fucking car radio.
How would you get the car radio out of the car?
Hmm?
What are you gonna do with a car radio?
Listen to music.
Okay.
What are you gonna plug it into? Not my computer ass.
I have I have a hoverboard that has no radio and I wanted to put a radio in it
just
Fucking get your own
Why are you destroying my life?
Maybe because we don't have any money because we accidentally
Donated all of it to a charity that we're trying to steal it back from I gave you what you I'm go
I'm just I gave you what you want. Which which direction is the bodega again? No the freeze guy. Where's the freeze?
Oh, he runs about
Where is Dougie Freeze? He doesn't know I don't know where he is. He's just fucking around. He's just a bad guy
Who's around a neighbor?
Okay, go to the bodega, but you have
Dog freeze I'm marching on I'm clanging the trash can
Okay, okay go into the bodega then okay, yeah and I get your car radio I
I guess you could do anything right now, I guess. So yeah, go ahead. I don't want anything
Never mind, I think I actually wants it when it's slowing down the scene
Yeah, you guys want to go to the you guys want to go to the bodega then? Yeah
I don't know. I want to get I would think we should called for Dougie freeze a bodega. Good. Did this guy?
He's the same. I know he might know where this okay
I'm gonna be screaming Dougie freezes name the whole time. I'm walking in the bodega. Mm-hmm. Yeah
that
the
Hey you.
What do you want?
Where is uh, where is Dougie Fresh?
Freeze.
The fuck you saying?
Dougie freeze.
What the fuck you say to me?
Get the fuck out of here.
Freeze.
I don't know what to say.
This guy right here, this guy in front of me, he wants to fight him.
No, buddy, put your fucking gun away.
Freeze.
What the fuck?
And he goes, we are the police.
And he reaches below the counter and he pulls out a shotgun.
He goes, fucking fuck off.
I put the barrel of the gun in my mouth.
I'm sorry.
Do it!
Pull the fucking trigger!
Where's Juggie Freeze?
Intimidation check.
Intimidation check with advantage.
Go for it.
I love when they do that in movies.
Yeah.
It's awesome.
It always works.
There's no way this isn't gonna work.
With advantage?
I mean...
Oh, let's go.
24.
Wow, fuck.
Okay.
Uh, yeah.
He's like
You want your pussy I
Pull me where doug leaf
Do you pull the trigger? I?
Reach out to pull the trigger
Okay
Yeah, what's my DC
No, roll, I guess you would just roll sort of against charisma just do a charisma check, okay
Yeah, yeah, you're pretty freaked out
Okay, okay, all right everybody I put my sniper rifle in my mouth
He puts away he puts away the gun
He's like look if you want to talk to doggy freeze he's
Come by come by later tonight. I give him a call. He'll come here and say I got to give you something
He's got to pick up something for me. He'll come here. Okay. Oh
How he how he usually kills time in situations like this
Well, there's a Lanta City that's about it. Oh, whoa
What?
Atlantis City casino underwater casino Oh Atlantis. I don't want to go then
Why going we're going we're going we're going okay, you're gonna go to Atlanta City
And I tell I told the bodega guy to tell
Mr. Freeze to meet us there when he gets back. Mm-hmm true, okay
I'll let him know just please get the fuck out and you and he points to the guy who you guys just abused
Before you can even finish that sentence. I shoot that guy in the head
My bodega I would like to plan a bomb on the cash register
before I leave.
*laughter*
Now we're not gonna find Dougie Freeze!
This is the only guy!
*laughter*
He's freaking out.
I'd say the sleight of hand, you got away with that with that 11.
He's fucking frazzled as hell.
Like he's not noticing someone calmly putting a bomb
on a cash register.
I asked him if he knows where to buy gold bullets.
He's not even
close to like a human
in
the
We're ready go to the fucking casino
He has a lot of money it is cash free as his cash register he is not called Dougie free
Can I do an investigation check to see if maybe he has a Rolodex or something with with Dougie freeze his phone number yeah for sure
27 okay
27 yeah, Oh
27 yeah, I mean you can look through sort of like on the side of the cash register
It's got like has like, you know different initials and a number next to it and DF is one of them with a number next to it
That you would assume would be Dougie freeze which someone he probably has to
Give money to or something. Okay. I I'm gonna grab his phone. I'm guessing he has a phone somewhere
Yeah, he had a phone on him. You can take his phone. I'm gonna dial Dougie for Dougie freezes number
Okay, yeah, you wipe the blood off the phone. I'm gonna kind of put my does it does anybody do like a good impression of
That guy's just killed
I could probably do
That makes sense you're about as worthless as that fucking fat Greek piece of shit here
Okay, I hand I hand Sullivan the phone
Okay, Sullivan's on the phone. He goes. Yeah. Hello. How's you?
the
is
gonna have to roll charisma cuz he's fucking this up you're fucking this up
mm-hmm I'm late it's this I was it's all of it you gave the phone to solve he's
doing a perfect voice impression he's fine it's just because he's saying weird
shit the guy might be suspicious okay he's like I just did me I come alone
and
My boobs are big.
And lots of beautiful girls.
Oh my water's breaking out of my ass.
And I bring the money.
Oh.
Okay.
And he, Hulk Sulvin hangs up.
He's like, I'm still a girl.
You're not a girl.
I'm not done being a girl yet.
I'm hitting, I hit him with my pipe.
To the side of the head.
He.
You can roll an attack roll.
Meet us at Dinero, a diner outside of Conchie's Palace, which is the main casino.
Oh, you just hit 13 damage to Pat.
Like, you just bl-b-b-brained him, basically.
Is he still a girl?
It's up to Pat, really, at this point.
Where did you hit him?
Oh, wow!
Oh, he's normal.
I was pretending to be a girl, but now I really am one
That's too low you don't hit him, but he still lost a good amount of okay, that's gonna hit
All right, we are
Was 41 minus 24 where we are
You're at 17
I'm the bell of the ball!
Oh jeez!
Stop hitting him, Scott!
He's dead. He's dead. He's dead.
He's dead. He's dead.
He's dead. Pat, we're gonna have to roll initiative
so Pat can roll death saving throws.
Um...
Okay...
Let's just kill Pat.
[Laughter]
Okay, uh...
Thanks for letting me wait to roll initiative
roll initiative until after I kill you.
*laughter*
When you picked a clear side.
Pat, roll a death saving throw.
Okay, that's one failure.
Alright, you guys wanna do- hold on, before you
roll another one, do you guys wanna do anything to stop
Pat from dying? Is he a girl?
*laughter*
I can't answer, I'm dead.
How did you-
Are you lying on the ground like, like, girlishly?
I don't know.
You look like the Black Dahlia.
There's no way to tell right now.
There is a way to tell, because you can tell us.
How girlish are you right now?
I'm behind the counter, you can't see.
You're dead, we walked over there.
I'm peering over. Am I looking under your dress?
I grew a dress.
Easy girl, still. Let him die.
Alright, roll another death saving throw, Pat.
Okay, it's two failures. Alright, this is the last chance. He'll actually die.
Is he still wearing a dress?
I give him health by healing him.
Wow, I guess Travis likes girls.
*laughter*
Okay, yeah.
That is the gayest thing I've ever seen, bro.
You hug cooties, bro.
Travis, roll a medicine check.
Okay.
but he has to be my girlfriend if I bring him back you have to get above a 10 to
stabilize him okay take forever all right medicine my medicine is one that's a 9
so he didn't stabilize him Pat roll another death saving throw 12 okay he's
He's alive, he's so far so good.
Pierce, you want to try to stabilize him again?
I think I like him like this.
Sullivan is going to try to stabilize him.
I thought he did stabilize.
Nope.
No, I'm sorry.
Sullivan's going to try.
Sorry, I'm going to check.
Okay.
All right, Sullivan got a 17.
Whoa!
Sullivan stabilizes you.
Okay, does anybody have potions for him or something?
Cause he's just gonna be knocked out right now.
No, I don't have anything.
I would pick him up by the scruff of his neck with my chimp arm.
And I'd pick him up on my back.
Okay, we'll let you, Pat, get up to 1 HP by the time you get to Atlantis City.
Um, you almost died.
So yeah, you guys can go to Atlantis City, where you'll meet Dougie Freeze at the Dinero.
the
a
at night. So it's kind of actually good timing. But the
movers and shakers of the slums often go to Atlanta City. So
that kind of makes sense. There's a couple games you can
play here. If you go to conscious palace, we can talk
about going to conscious palace. When you guys go in there, you
get like a little like a bubble goes around your head so you can
breathe. And it's as beautiful as you imagined Atlanta City to
be you know, spires, just tons of just broke people from New
Jersey. You know, beautiful gold paved roads, a couple of casino
buildings. But yeah, what do you guys want to do? You're in
Atlanta City is
why first things first, we got to get my boy Patrick Yoda some
hot dogs.
There is a cold dogs and hot soda stand here. Of course,
each cold dog heals only one HP so he has to eat like, like 40
the
a roll of 40 no so you're just gonna you're gonna have I roll to these
bunnies and then whatever number shows up is how many hot dogs a is rolled yeah
yeah I think that's actually not a bad idea I actually kind of like that yeah
roll 2d 20s roll let him roll 40 10 oh no you got so you can only recover 10 HP
after your 10th cold dog you just start vomiting but you're up with 10 with 11 HP
now. Or we could do 25 if we want to be a little bit more generous. I think that's fine.
Yeah, what do you guys think? Even after he throws up, I'm forcing the rest of them down
his throat. To make I feel bad. Okay, cool. So yeah, you guys are in Atlanta City.
I started eating my puke. What do you guys want to do?
You just have brain damage.
*laughter*
You just turned into like a disgusting demon.
Awww. I like this.
*laughter*
He's definitely not a girl anymore.
That's true.
I think something changed when you shot him in the head, Blowtooth.
I want to go on the arcade.
the
She will be here.
(laughter)
She has brain damage.
And then you put a face filter on the picture too to make her look beautiful.
Yeah, Dougie Frees
hearts the picture of Patrick.
I am beautiful!
Cool, yeah, so you guys head to the arcade.
There's all manners of games here.
There's slots you can play. There's other gambling
and
3 games you can play, there's pig, where there's a number that the house declares you're trying
to reach, you can roll a bunch of d6s until you reach that number, if you get a 1 though,
you lose, but you can roll up to until you say stop, right?
We forgot to take money out of the cash register, right?
Yeah, you guys did.
You guys took it.
We did?
How much money was it?
A million dollars, yeah.
that
the
There are three rounds and three games per round.
The way it works is you pick either a d12, d8, or d4.
You roll, and the highest value against other players rolling their chosen dice wins.
You get different point values depending on which dice you chose.
And the dice actually explode as well, so when you get a max value on it, you can roll it again and add it up to it.
it
the
the register. I got 741. I brought my own dice with me. He's rolling his personal 1000 sided
die. So do you guys want to play slot? We're going to play pig and then we'll start with
pig. So pig, we roll two d20s to pick the number. I will do that now. I'm going to also
a
the
How much did I win on a $62 bet?
$62 bet? Did everybody meet him on $62?
Wait, I thought you guys weren't playing pig. Everyone started to play pig.
Yeah, I decided to play pig because it sounded fun after you said it.
I know, but then everyone else started rolling. I thought it was only you and me playing.
Okay, let's try again.
Oh, is that why you lost? Because you thought that it was only you and me playing?
No, I just, I mean, we lose a lot of money if everyone has played pig.
But how much money do I win from that roll? Because I could just...
to
one
the
everyone
you know
the
so that's not what is that one of the world ten
i want to rule
all my money into slots on the at once
uh...
okay uh... i don't know what's on the needed to release slots slots
Okay, so you're gonna- okay, well hold on.
So, yeah, the way SWATs works is it is-
it's just two tokens to play,
and then once you play, the way it works is-
Two?
What?
Two tokens to play, not one?
No, it's two.
Is that okay?
I guess you can keep talking.
That's right, yeah.
So, it's gonna be two tokens to play.
Shit, where is the-
There they are.
If you get- if two match,
then you get the value of those die together.
If three match, you get the value of all those die together
or times two.
- Okay.
- If you get all ones, three ones though,
you're locked out of the machine for the month.
- What?
- If you get three 20s, you hit the jackpot.
- Okay, I'm ready.
- I've been following Blowtoss around
'cause I think he's my mommy now.
No, I'm not a girl.
I can be your daddy.
Mom.
OK, roll three d20s.
Nope.
Nothing.
OK, so I'm down to 60.
Eight.
Oh, you got eight.
You got a payout of eight right there.
Barry got eight.
OK.
I got nothing again.
I'm down to 15.
I keep rolling 34s.
nothing nothing down to 56 19 nothing down to 54 nothing down to 52 nothing down to 50
oh my god pat got a pat you got the 38 38 tokens your way mommy all right i'm
I'm looking around for guys who might have the name Freeze.
Yeah, so uh yeah, I mean as you're doing this...
Oh, I won 14.
I'm back up to 16.
I actually have no idea what this guy looks like and he thinks that we're a big fat Greek guy.
Yeah, so...
We do need to figure out how to find him.
You should send a picture of the... where we are right now so that he comes to mind.
Okay, I sent a picture of the... just a small section of the repeating pattern of the carpet.
And I said, "We are here."
What's the biggest thing in this room right now?
The biggest thing in this room?
It's a good meeting place.
Yeah, there's a big statue of Mary-Kate Cabrera doing a strongman pose.
Okay, you should take a picture of that and say "meet us here."
the
Yeah, yeah.
Strongman pose?
Like, like what, like you do it.
What's the...
Yeah, like that.
Like that.
Okay, I'm sitting on top of the left hand.
Mm-hmm.
Why did you need patches to do that?
'Cause I wanted to see.
*laughs*
He was thinking he was gonna do a different strongman pose.
I thought that, I thought that patches would maybe roll his sleeves up and show me his biceps, but...
I'm fine with what I saw.
So, uh, yeah, you go over there and just...
I think I know what pose he wanted patches to do.
to do. I can't even say it because it's so nasty.
Why would I do that? Why would that be my first instinct?
What? What was the nasty pose? I don't need to
know. So yeah, you go to the statue.
I'm up to 104 tokens, guys. And you go to the statue, and yeah, you see
this sort of Rutger Hauer looking guy with slicked back, very bleached, bleached blonde
hair, sort of sidle up to the statue, sort of looking around, and he turns his attention
the
the fifth
*laughter*
Okay...
Ice cream!
Where's Nico?
Oh, I-I think he lied over there
to the freeze guy, and I say, uh...
"Your friend is in the bathroom."
He's taking- he said he had to take a huge shit.
Oh, it's so stinky over there.
Ice cream.
the
Why do I got a really cool way that we basically tricked the whole game and and get free money? Yeah
It's awesome. And we heard that you like shit. Yeah, you can see it if you want
We're not ready to let you in on it, but you can watch us do it
Where's an eco?
He said to hear he's in the bathroom
He wanted us to talk to you to entertain you and he thought that we might be able to become friends even
ice-cream bar
Deception me. Yeah, but you got one of you guys can give me
You guys can give him advantage. How do you give me advantage? I'm giving him advantage by working basically by helping him which is which they are
critical failures
If okay that helps
Deceive him I thought he was a screwed man. His name is mr. Freeze. Okay, we can roll again Caleb. Okay
All right, so he does not buy it he's like, all right this is too weird
I'm trying to see
Guys, I really fucked that up, but I'm gonna cover for us. I actually don't know these other four guys and I'm a crazy
homeless guy
I'm just being really weird
So you should talk to them and I'm gonna go over there sit his tracks and he turns around
Are you really a crazy homeless guy?
I'm gonna suck your cock off
Blalalalalalalala
Alright
You don't know these guys
What guys?
Ice cream bar
Blalalalalala
Casino being breakfast
He goes to you Travis
What is this then?
We uh
Want to buy things
From you
the
I'm
I'm starting the swap one more time right before we walk away.
You hear me in the background, "Bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla
I'm trying to communicate with him because I completely understand what he's saying.
Yeah, so yeah, Ray and-
So I guess only me and Gary and-
And Botas are going, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, Ray and Pat are sort of doing their own kind of twisted buddy comedy.
What happened to all the people in both cops rooms?
Gabby Gifford.
Oh, yeah.
And so, yeah, you three are head to the back of the arcade.
There's a little elevator.
Security guard nods to Mr.
Freeze and moves aside.
He lets you guys in.
The elevator takes you up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
And you guys are let out into a very lush, red, velvety room.
the
says uh mom you're not you're somewhere else here [ __ ] yeah that was that i was outside i
think cameron wasn't around so i guess it's the brain dead guy screaming bomb in a public place
i said mom i'm looking for cameron okay and uh mary kate sort of gets up and sizes you you you
the
guys were doing a favor for the manslaughter.
Whatever.
Cool.
She says, my friend here tells me you guys want golden bullets and love slime.
Yes.
And a brain damage remover.
And an ice cream bar.
Do you want an ice cream bar?
Yeah.
But if we get the brain damage remover we don't need the ice cream bar.
That's true.
Ice cream bar!
Wow that guy is really loud down there.
I don't know what I could do about a brain damage remover but um...
If we're talking about golden bullets and love slime...
I might got some people for ya.
Ice cream bar!
Yeah, why don't we go to the ice cream bar?
Yeah!
Don't make us get really nasty.
the
- What's the deal? - Green bar!
- So, if you want, you have to go to-- - Blah blah blah, all you do is talk, just tell us.
[laughter]
So the guy who has the bullets would be Goldbeard.
- Ooh! - Now...
- Oh! - Goldbeard has not been seen in a while.
But...
I can make him appear very easily.
*laughter*
Are you catching on? There's gotta be something in it for me.
Oh!
Oh, uh, well I am like...
How does four dollars sound?
102 tokens, yeah.
We all have four dollars.
Ice cream?
Okay, um...
Bye!
How much money do you want?
Depends.
What are you going to have whenever you're done with whatever it is you're doing with
those things?
We are doing it for fun.
We like to go to the desert and shoot stuff and blow stuff up.
Roll deception with advantage.
My deception never works.
This is going to suck.
Not bad.
Roll again.
Yep, you have advantage.
Advantage just means that you get to do it twice?
Yeah, twice and you take the higher number.
Yeah.
Okay.
I guess I should just have my character sheet open, huh?
I'm such an idiot.
What? You've been closing it every time?
I'm an idiot.
What?
Alright, so yeah.
Alright, fine, whatever.
What about a job then?
I'm not gonna give you money, what if I got you guys to do a little job for me?
You can have twelve dollars!
*laughter*
I have somebody I need- I have somebody I need to be shaken down.
If I tell you guys who it is, you do it for me, you get back here.
I'll get you gold beer, I'll get you the bullets, I'll see what I can do about love slime.
Fine.
Okay. As long as it's that pregnant lady.
What pregnant lady?
The one we wanna shake.
*laughter*
Alright, what does the guy look like? Where do we get him?
Alright.
Um, hold on, sorry, I'm pulling my sheet.
You're gonna take a sheet?
Nasty ass.
Oh hell no.
That's just... eww.
No, it's not what I...
You disgust me.
Okay.
His name is Shiny Andrew.
*laughter*
He's a, uh...
Investor in my operation, and he owes me some money.
You can go- you can find him up in the main district in Gun City.
Oh, wait! Shiny Andrew?
Oh yeah?
Yeah, I think I heard that he killed the guy who owns the bodega, or runs it, and-
*laughter*
Absolutely a deception, that is an ocelot move.
I love that. Yeah.
Roll deception with advantage on that too.
*laughter* I fuck with that.
It's like the bodega, dude.
*laughter*
It's all good.
We're having fun. I love that.
Roll again, roll again, get advantage.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Whoa.
contact freeze
um...
niko's dead
i thought you guys said he was in the bathroom
no that crazy homeless guy said he was in the bathroom
and also yes he died in the bathroom
died in the bathroom
oh fuck
so
we're just gonna go do the job
you don't worry or do any roles
about this
it's all dependent on
if you guys stop saying crazy shit
the
You do have to figure that out.
Go find shiny Andrew for me.
How much money does shiny Andrew owe you?
A lot.
Yeah, we'll go find him, but can you give us like...
How much?
Like an amount of money?
I think we need, like, where are we looking for him and what, is there anything we need
to watch out for?
You want us to kill him because you really fucking shot your friend in the esophagus
or something.
You don't give us any information, you're setting us up to fail and that's bad for you.
All right, all right, all right.
Shiny Andrew.
We want your coolest weapon too.
Shiny Andrew is a quantum crypto investor.
So he's frequently around the Wall Street district.
You probably have to find him there.
is
weaknesses or sexual proclivities?
I don't know about his sexual proclivities, but I do know that he does not like the dark.
He's often only out during the day.
How does he feel about bombs?
He might be pro or anti-bomb, depending on sort of his distance from them when they're
exploding.
the
is that? Oh, so we shouldn't kill him? Well, I want you to rough him up. Yeah, but how much
money do you owe him? Yeah, don't kill him. He does give me money when he's not. Okay,
but how much money is he going to give you? How much money is he going to give you?
Why do you need to know that? Just so we know how much money is in his pocket so that...
It's not going to be in his pocket. Well, it's how much money does he owe you? I feel like that
determines how persuasion persuasion who has good persuasion I think I do
fuck mm-hmm got crit one so he goes you don't need to know that information just
go find him rough him up come back here all right I'll help you out all right I
have an idea we should we should make Cameron gamble for like an hour and then
We just bring back that money and pretend that we always thinking too, but now I don't know how much money it is
We can just guess you wouldn't tell us
Wait, yeah saying this out loud
Yeah, all right, let's go find a shiny man whatever and let's go I think that homeless guy from earlier seemed cool
So let's leave with him
Just know that we're trying to get him a decent meal in a shower later
Yeah, they both give you thumbs up as you guys leave
Yeah, you guys leave you go down the elevator. You're back in the arcade room
The game room you see Patrick and Ray. What do you guys what do you what have you guys been doing during this time?
I have my whole hand in my mouth
Look completely homeless
Long beard I'm covered in blood and diarrhea
the
I find this guy named Shiny Andrew and the person also said that
um, that Sullivan the frog needs to give a bunch of
money and if he doesn't win over 1 million tokens gambling tonight
he will be killed. No, really? Yeah, they said that.
So you better hop to it, buddy.
(laughter)
But okay. And yeah, Sullivan just goes by the slot machine and starts
I saw Blotas laughing and I've just been laughing for...
I haven't stopped laughing.
Um, yeah, and uh, yeah, you...
I'm starting to treat him like a child.
Because I really miss Cool Sullivan, who's away at college.
all
There's five day time limit on the mission. No, I thought I'm limit
We can be over like four days 20 hours
Honestly really fun and I'd like to play it again. Yeah, let's play more big. Okay. All right
What do you guys want to bet in? What do you guys want put in?
all everything
Money that he owes then we could put it all on pig. Oh, that's actually a way better idea. Let's go do that
You're gonna go beat up this guy and we can like quadruple the money
Wait is shiny Andrews number in Nico's phone
We just check
Yeah, it's actually not a bad idea
You can have it meet us here
Mm-hmm. We can play pig until he gets here
We could get we could get just like everybody
Yeah
Of that place that we have to do the heist on we could probably like contract like a construction company just move the heist building in here
Okay, you guys want to play one more round of pig or do you want to stay
Definitely check the phone. There's no way right? There's no way
Yeah, no, I mean no, there's no reason why Nika would
Yeah, you can call 4-1-1
All right, cool, so what are you guys putting in money wise?
I'm gonna do money. Well, how much money just Sullivan have I?
Mean you guys didn't split any of the money with him. So yeah. Well you said he was pulling slots
So how much does he have he's like seven tokens? He was I pick I'm putting in his seven tokens
and
Okay, what do you have?
We still have the 300 whatever right?
What is it now?
Cam I feel like you'd be keeping track of what it might how much I had was 102. I don't know anybody else
I had I think everybody
Books. Hmm. I knew everybody had said 60 at the start 62. Yeah, but then we made you made more
I was keeping track of mine. So I have like 70
the
of
roll
The house gotta roll now.
It has to be one roll.
OH!
OH SHIT!
The house gotta run!
No way!
That's the best call I've ever seen.
Fucking hell yeah dude.
Alright, yeah.
That's the most incredible gambler ever.
We put the money right on the table.
How much did I, oh I'm not splitting it.
This is mine.
How much is it?
I don't know.
We all put 70 right?
Like 450 right?
Yeah.
How much did I- oh I'm not splitting it.
What?
This is mine, how much is it?
I don't know.
Like, 450 right?
Cause of the bonus.
Yeah you get the bonus, bonus 100 on top.
Okay yeah, 450.
I un-pocketed that, that's all mine.
Into my inventory.
That's so badass.
I'm so good at Pig.
Alright, cool.
What do we do?
[Music]