the
alright episode three
him
so
last time on him were found
the game
uh... road on a motorbike from uncle shredders to
uh... wisconsin brooklyn wisconsin
marriages for moving around the whole map now killed
and killed all of them
and uh... then uh... they harassed and
they went to a uh... a brooklyn wisconsin bodega
and they got room in court
uh... there
they're very cute animals
then they
went to the bus stop
in rational man
that's where i want to do it arrest and uh... guidance guidance
to mention to lose though and tell them that they wait on the bus and gets the
blue so that they can go to the stained concert which is tomorrow the stained
concert but their family is gonna be at say mr. family because this is also this
is homework and after that they wanted to kill some time so they went to the movie
theater where there was a rerelease of homework bound the hungry hamster got
into some got stuck in a vending machine and when a teen tried to take him up by
this
right
and it's in
it's ok listen it's ok to kill a teenager using some kind of unmanned aerial attack
if it's to protect your interests in an area
that's true yeah
yeah that happens
that's it yeah yeah uh they're getting it's politics about list again
but uh yeah so um so then they went uh and hid out back in the bodega after doing some
clever roles, the hamster, hungry hamster was able to make the cops dance and nae nae their
way to viral success so that they could escape. And then they head down to the bodega and they
took the bus and the bus driver then died because they ran him over with the bus and then there
was man bear pig showed up. Oh yeah I remember now. Man bear pig went away. And they convinced
bear pig to only eat or kill people. What if he comes back? There's no way. Also we're not
people so we're safe. I'm sure he has a very long memory that works for statements like
that. Yeah, he'll remember that one. And so they kept driving the bus but because they
didn't beat a very high DC I had up to get to Duluth because they're animals. But it doesn't
requires high of a DC to operate a bus apparently. They ended up sort of at this
creek and a river with a little rickety bridge and then Dick Van Dyke was trying
to get an Uber and so Pleasant Parrot tried to talk to him but because of some
behind-the-scenes DM ass roles the CIA showed up, attacked the Pleasant Parrot
and the battle has begun between the CIA agents and the homeward bound
hamward bound characters so we're gonna we're gonna take down the whole CIA
we're dismantling the CIA from the inside out we rolled initiative for
everybody so Patrick Yoda oh shit that's your name in the thing what the hell I'm
so fucking sorry the hungries hamster
it's your turn
uh...
or there's three of them
how are you seeing other things
uh... they are
uh... from you
forty forty five fifty five
great 'cause what i'm gonna do right off the bat
famous dance
near here in india
uh... so overpowering yet
I'm
a single other fight in this game. Do something, we're gonna convince every single enemy to go away.
Do a new dance. Do like the A-B-A dance. I'm doing the renegade from TikTok.
The renegade from Jay-Z and Eminem. Yeah, the Jay-Z, Eminem renegade.
They had that dance. Their famous dance.
okay
and
so uh...
two of them and it's a resist
uh...
uh... but one of them is struck by dancing fever
and he is the nearest at the holy hamster
i'll give him a a a little mark
so that you know that about him
uh... in roles twenty
i'll give him a a skull mark uh... yes it's a change one of them to a clown
uh... yes you can use them
and see if i have a clown and said for you
you better did
and you know that i have had that you've been there and i don't know i don't
have a clown
picture
marines and when i search plans
the dealership
that's correct that's perfect
he really don't know why you
(laughter)
Okay, so one of them is a Kneedler now.
One of them is the Kneedler from Halo.
Alright, cool.
So yeah, uh, yeah, I mean you can still move
and shit, but that's basically
your turn.
Okay, I'm gonna
hide behind the bus.
Okay, cool, perfect.
Alright, it is now
um,
the, uh, uh...
Pleasant Parrot's turn.
here
and
If I attack him, does he snap out of dancing?
Um...
[laughs]
I should have added that, but no.
Yes! Okay, cool.
I'm gonna fly up to the dancing guy.
Um, and I'm gonna...
Uh...
I'm gonna use my, uh...
My Talon's ability.
Okay, cool.
My Talon's attack.
Yeah, so roll an attack roll against, uh, their, uh...
Eleven.
Okay, yeah, that's not gonna hit this guy.
as
a
miss with with town a stand from and that i think they're also they're also in
you know stand for american dad
would to what he talks like these like it just some
he's like uh... that's a big for a little bit voices stand
uh... we set up a little bit so it's a little bit for the day i was just trying
to be patrick warburton
is that
mineral
little bit
merit so
you may assume with your talents
uh... yeah believe it or not is your turn normal dog
all my god easy
uh... i i use my ability crime dog
this was uh... which you have categorized by the way as a racial ability
minor racial to let me tell you what's that about me i don't know that i can
let you address it and i use are you trying dog
to investigate if you have cyanide molars
okay
uh...
Yeah, so you have advantage on that, so go for it, investigate.
I'm an investigator.
14.
Yeah, 14.
Uh, yeah, you can tell they have cyanide molars in case they have to talk, like all CIA agents.
Easy, dude.
Alright, I'm gonna use, I'm gonna use tackle and I'm gonna specifically try and knock their
cyanide molars into their mouths.
Fuck yeah, okay.
So yeah.
That's a believe right there.
So you are, yes, you tackle this dancing guy.
So he's still trying to dance while you're on top of him on the
ground and he's doing the worm right now.
He's doing the worm and with crime dog.
The other part of the crime dog ability is that if you're first
to attack an enemy you have advantage on all attack rolls for
the rest of combat after that.
Oh my God.
Oh, yeah, because you were the first to attack him because that's
not what I'm famous dance is not an attack.
it's infectious dance
you do have a bit
but now it is their turn
uh... so
c_i_a_ anything
they're afraid
the c_i_a_ agent in the back
is going to uh... with you know it's get your ass over here to your own top of
the
uh... the c_i_a_ agent in the back
is going to
try to shoot a uh...
a curious looking gun
uh... similar to uh...
a pistol
in this case it's gonna shoot, but different.
And again, Pleasant Parrot, roll a Dexterity saving throw.
Okay.
19.
Nice, yeah.
So he shoots a gun at you, this guy in the back here, and it's like a net,
and it shoots out, but it misses you, it goes wide.
And then this other one over here is going to shoot at you
uh...
without normal dog with a gun
that patrick's predictions
yeah and that's what i told you to you
uh... yet he's a big this is cuz i'm in law enforcement
uh... and not cuz you're on top of my friend
uh... my mom i have a great agent you know i don't like it dog
yet and uh... you know it's right from and uh...
he does
uh... ten damage to you
jesus christ
uh... okay pistol gun and then i need you to roll the i think i'll try to be bad
regional strength strength saving through just to see if you can stand up with us
i can stand up twenty four
yeah you're fine do you just get shot you're like easy
yeah until
uh... and now the other guy who you've tackled
uh...
all he could do is dance and move half the speed so he's just gonna stay dancing
down there for the rest of this turn.
And now we're back to Hungry Hamster.
Alright, so I'm still behind the bus.
I come out from the bus.
I come out from behind it again and now that I can see that there's some stuff going on,
I think I might check my inventory to see.
Alright, so I'm going to check inventory.
So I just roll a 20.
7, ok, let's see.
It's a rocket launcher.
the
you
Thank you!
Okay.
At $8, your inventory wasn't buried.
Alright.
This is good because Hungry Hamster owed me.
Owed me $8, actually.
Mm-hmm.
I just wanted to get this out of the way right now!
I know this is kind of a bad time!
I appreciate that you remembered and didn't need any reminders.
This is why you're my best friend!
I love you!
You're my best friend, too!
Okay, guys, cool!
I love you! I love you, dog!
I love the dog too, we're all best friends!
Alright, now I feel included. Continue!
The parrot has taught the animals to have currency.
The concept of it and share it.
Yeah, the CIA agents are reporting.
Um, uh, and uh, yeah.
And uh, it is now, uh, your turn, Pleasant Parrot.
Okay, so I have a question about my Polly Wants a What Now ability.
I could, I, my speech can be used to command one human at will to perform a specific one-word task
that is not immediately harmful to the human.
Yes.
If I command one of them to like, to chew,
to bite, so like, to bite down,
is that immediately harmful?
Uh, that's a very good...
'Cause I feel like it's definitely indirectly harmful.
That's a very good Dungeons & Dragons question.
Um, I'm gonna say that because they are aware
that they have cyanide tooth,
that they would be considered harmful okay weren't aware
it was too good to be true
yeah yeah
all right i'm gonna i'm gonna fly to the guy with the gun that's not the net gun
with a real gun
there's no attack of opportunity there because he's pinned to the ground by the
other animal dog
seargle
and then i'm gonna use treddy's my talents on this guy
twelve
not going to do it all my god has a quick
uh... yes you go to perch on his shoulder
and uh... the c_i_a_ agent uses expert uh... c_i_a_ maneuver called a atork
torture brownchild and uh... visible dodge
very easily
uh... how it is uh...
your turn normal dog
okay so i don't know how this guy pins and on the ground okay i mean i just
keep i might as well
yeah i might as well just like
just use bite
i'll just like fuck him to death
yeah yeah okay
it's on the attack i have here but
uh... we'll see it's tackle but you know what i'm really doing
yeah that hits
nice absolutely that hits
five five damage
and so you've already done
what to this guy? six
six and five okay yeah
so he's still standing but he looks fucked up as you take your weird little dog dick
and uh...
uh... his fuck his crusty ass dude and fuck his crusty CIA ass
it's like if james franco in one hundred twenty seven hours got stuck and started
fucking the rocks
yeah
it's basically what's happening to his body
just dust everywhere
he's like oh god i've been compromised is what he says and i say in dog
You're goddamn right you have yeah in dog. Um, yeah, and so you're just fucking this guy to death. It is now your turn
CIA agents, oops. Okay. This guy over here is gonna shoot another net at you. Wasn't parrot
All right, roll another dexterity saving throw
21 yeah, you fucking dodge that shit pro like he can't capture you. He's having so much trouble
the
take out your bones
you are a good idea all they want as long as they don't touch my friends
I respect you so much
pleasant parent you thank you I respect you more
the not a competition
and so he's gonna do a I what's your AC pleasant parent
the I'm 1515 yes shit to go see attacker so yeah he connects
with a karate chop to your neck
woah
this guy's trying to karate chop a bird
what kind of a CIH agent is this
that's fucked up
you don't do that
that's not tactical
if we're being honest they all know Krav Maga
yeah so it's true
he does 7 damage
again political
politics on the list again
he does 7 damage to you pleasant parrot
oh my god I'm at 5
the
I don't know if I want to do hamster ball or...
Because it knocks every...
Yeah, you know what?
Fuck it.
Hamster ball.
Do it.
Let's see it.
So the thing with hamster ball...
17.
Yeah, that will hit them.
Yeah, shit.
I guess, you know what?
I didn't put any restrictions on that.
So here's the thing.
What you have to do is roll...
So you...
Yeah.
Yup.
Okay.
Oh, enemies roll against actually. So I'm actually going to roll against that. So don't even worry about it.
Hold on one second. Actually, also, so who, which CIA agent are you?
So I'm going to... Alright, one that's... Don't you dare touch this one I'm fucking.
I won't. Don't touch any of the drawings we made. He's mine.
So you can use your full range of movement with hamster balls. You can hit the two in the back if you go...
So what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna hit I'm gonna go. All right. I'll actually use this thing for real
The freehand draw so what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna go up I'm gonna hit this one and then this one
But I won't hit this one because that's Caleb's that's right. Yeah, they both fail their
Saving throws against you too. So what happens is is you roll up into?
I roll up like Sonic the Hedgehog.
I feel like it.
In your little hamster ball, you knock that one over in your hamster ball like Sonic the Hedgehog.
Yeah.
And you roll up on this one and knock him over.
And so they're both knocked prone now.
Yeah.
Which means they're gonna have to get up on their turn.
And then I...
It's gonna take half their movement.
My head like pops up.
And I...
And I fall in the water.
Yeah, you do?
Because I overshot it.
I fall into the creek.
But I'm kind of just floating there.
No, because I was gonna say, if you could still choose to do this, but I would feel
unfair as DM if I didn't say, "Those are raging waters."
Okay, then never mind.
Okay.
I hit that one and then I do like such a screeching halt towards it.
I almost fall in and I'm, "Oh shit."
And I'm sitting there and I'm going like, "Whoa!"
And I almost crawl into the room, but I don't.
It's the power of friendship.
Yeah the CIA agents when you knock them over they sound like bowling pins.
They sound like a bowling strike.
Because they're hollow on the inside.
What?
Oh my god.
Oh no.
Pat is single handedly destroying the CIA.
Yes.
Wow.
Yeah and so they're knocked on the ground, they're seeing birdies around their heads.
They're like alpha, alpha, beta, alpha, delpha.
Yeah they're spelling Abba.
yeah
yeah and uh... they are now you know you can now
attack them with advantage everybody so you're up pleasant parrot
okay uh...
i'm gonna go ahead and
uh... amnesty pack this time on the guy that i'm right next to it with the gun
do it that is not prone i get advantage rate
you know you have fourteen
legal do it and all my god should not gonna hit a single attack this whole
game he's to be a that's the problem yeah i really i don't really want it is
the problem up
yes you're just like pecking at the ground and you just like kind of like
you you don't estimate
uh... how close you are to the him on the ground like to start like
uh... use kinda just shy of him
uh... and uh... it is now your turn nor normal dog
okay uh... dog
some hidden from the back and i'm gonna fuck my
i'm not going to my bite attack on his ear generous generously calling we're
doing fucking
and uh... you're gonna play uh...
three to buy right now
the with the one that i'm fuckin
you down in the dirt with the arcade role for damage
twelve have your kill describe your kill in the sky
Um, i'm i'm i'm again i'm hitting from the back
And I use my long dog neck and I sort of wrap my mouth around
Right and we start tonguing
And I yeah, he's like I don't I've never felt this way before. Yeah. Yeah, he's starting to like it almost
Are you and I maybe i'm a white woman and I say shut the fuck up and take it and I pop his
Tooth out with my big tongue. Ooh
Yeah, and he starts bubbling
Yeah, he starts bubbling up and his face turns purple with poison and his veins start bulging and you watch him just asphyxiate and just collapse on the ground.
Owned.
Yeah, so he's done.
That's yeah.
What the fuck are you guys doing?
I killed one.
When you guys you guys I you killed him because he had disadvantage because of me.
So these drawings are getting fucking crazy.
You like him?
You like all of them?
You like that we figured out how to use the drawing tool on your beautiful maps.
[laughter]
So, now it is the CIA agent's turn.
They're all going to have to get up.
So they get up.
This one gets up and tries to karate chop you, hungry hamster.
And so he does his attack on you.
And that hits, that hits baby.
And he does damage now.
He does eight damage to you, hungry hamster.
So he gets up and like sort of sees you
and he's like, you little hamster freak.
And just like, tries to kick you in your ball.
And he kicks you in your ball
and you just like knock around in there
and get some concussive damage.
And now this other CIA agent is going to get up
and go after pleasant parrot
uh...
so yeah it was another cronies shop
as could kill me very easily
all yes you are meant to heal you that time but i got so caught up in fucking
that kind of thing
uh... which by the way my most members woke fuck in one of these
one of these d_n_d_ campaigns yet
yeah i think i thought that cop to death instead of like a b
uh... yeah but he doesn't hit he just barely misses to uh... he's he goes in
for a uh... and over the head shop
uh...
but uh... uh... your period very easily able to move where you're just barely
able to move out of the way she said
and now it is your turn again hungry hamster array so
patches just got so cool
you know i don't actually don't care started
well
problem
and
uh...
patrick
i think it's cool that you got to cool he's literally do you go as cigarette
uh... and patrick whatever your name is a little bit so i'm at the i'm right next
to this guy so i'm just answer by them
actually you know what maybe maybe i'll check inventory first
as always a good man yeah are accepted
for it so is it cool movement haha
price a sober that that's a cool i'm not i'm not saying brother
uh... you say you are
and it's implied
unknown
and what do i get a little bit or when i check one
thirty magazines
who okay you know what you know that that is a lot of yeah i give that to the c_i_a_
agent
okay
at the role again to see if he jacks off to it
you know what do you what do you try to communicate
and um... i'd pull it out of my my little cheek
i've pulled a little bit
this is a little
skin i've pulled out uh... well i did get a one so i will uh... one is hustler for
sure
a one is extreme lactation is magazine
but
but i pull that out and i handed to the c_i_a_ agent
and uh... all role to see if you're going to use the c_i_a_ agent so obviously
something like that
is going to be his thing to turn him on right now as he's a farce a roles so
patient
okay
they'll be tough because he's already fighting you you already heard him
yeah but uh... so do i roll with this event uh...
and
i don't think cool patches like says i guess he's momentarily so here's what
happens
a little after polls and the mag out of his cheek
and uh...
you can hold it up to the c_i_a_ agent is a recovering from you knocking him over
uh... near
uh...
but you just hold it up and just waving it at him
but i was like
and for for a moment
uh...
and uh... i'll say that you have
uh... that everyone has advantage on tax on him for one ref
because he's a little distracted by this duty that's all i'll give you for that
okay
that's it is good
that inspired piece of roleplay uh... home
uh... okay
and it is now
pleasant parents turn
all right so if i fly away from the guy i met i provoking attack of opportunity
right so i can't go to patrick's alright so i'm just gonna peck this guy
go for it
thirteen i will never hit an attack you never hit an attack
you just keep missing uh... you keep misjudging where your mouth is
you forgot how long your beak is today
yeah it's been rough i'm just in a weird mood today
the he had his sort of feel you can feel off
yeah yet some of the vibes are different
yeah yeah
uh...
and yes you just fuckin with and is now your turn normal dog
okay i'm gonna use whimper
on uh... attack the guy that that that pat away no no no no no no i'm not i'm
i'm actually gonna i'm gonna save
pleasant parrots life with a woman
all
i'm such a good guy
yes you can reach in with your tongue
My big-ass tongue.
Is that-- one second.
You can--
We're pretty close to each other.
I think we're all--
That's five feet.
[LAUGHTER]
Yeah, the five-foot tongue.
Sorry, do you have a problem with that?
He is a retriever.
Yeah, I'm a retriever.
So I hit a 10 plus-- I hit a 13.
Nice, dude.
Wow, you--
Whoa, I'm back up to full HP.
Nice, dude.
Yeah, you healed--
Thank you!
I love your tongue!
[LAUGHTER]
Yeah, you do love that tongue, don't you?
I love your long, wet tongue!
Yeah, I bet you do, huh?
I love when you lick me!
Kiss it back!
Alright.
And then I roll it back up like a fruit roll-up.
Mmm.
Daddy like.
I'm from the CIA, Jitsuha.
This one is distracted
by the
nudie mag.
So he's gonna try to attack you,
and
We'll draw that on the map, don't you worry about that Patches, we'll take care of it.
Okay!
Yeah, he fucking whiffs, he gets a 1.
So he is just like fully thinking about lactating and what it would be like to lactate and feel
like that and maybe he wouldn't have, maybe she wouldn't have left him if he could lactate
and things like that and he just misses you completely.
Meanwhile, this other guy is going to now whip out his own net gun and try to capture the Pleasant Parrot.
See how he does.
Okay, and Pleasant Parrot's AC is probably not right.
Yeah.
No.
So he tries to shoot it at you and he just you just are able to like fly through the little netting and then it was a little
too wide when it like sort of splurged out and he is just capturing some bait bass some
base some bass that are in the river.
This is bass in the river.
No, it's bass.
Bass in the river.
Yeah.
Boom, boom, boom, boom.
And it is now your turn, Hungy Hamster.
Alright, so I think what I'm gonna do.
Mr. Hungy fella.
I think I'm gonna bite the guy who's trying to jack off.
Okay.
So, let's see how this goes. I'm just straight up gonna bite him.
I got 12.
Nah, dawg, you fuckin' whiff.
Do you try to bite him with your teeth?
Do I still roll for damage?
If you want to, it's not gonna do anything.
Nice, that would've been good. That would've been 7 damage.
I know.
But yeah, you try to chomp at him.
Well, actually, you know what? Because we said for one full round.
i would say that you get another
you get advantage on this attack all of those are that is it i guess i'll
yet they had a role with the damage
that is advantage that is a man is just realize you know it's not
okay so now it's your turn uh... plus inherent
all right i'm gonna pack and this time really going to do it
you got a
sixteen
that's a hit
yes yes
ten damage
clock yeah you just fuckin
pack this guy's shit up
what is your damage patrick do
what did pay damage patrick do
damage said
i never
looks like you didn't roll for damage i did i got a seven remember
no hungry hamster hamster ball
uh... yeah click hamster ball scroll up to click hamster ball
holy shit what the fuck i got
they should have been dead already had a we just time travel
uh... no you just killed this one though for sure
uh...
uh... cameron you just killed him. how do you peck him?
uh... i
describe your kill
i fly down his throat
and uh...
i
i fly down into his body, i fly down into his feet
and i peck his feet from
i'd take his feet from the inside to make him walk into the river
how
mood
yeah yeah i think i had to miss so many times to do is such a complex
and you know that i was thinking about this the whole time yeah i guess is
will he just ends up in the river and i fly out before it gets in the air i fly
out of the so
you fly out of his big toe
and he just fuck is a bit
he's fuckin like flies down the river
you know the only map by accident
uh... and he's he's he's like just like the fucked up corpse line here
uh... yeah
it is now
i want to
is now your turn
uh...
normal dog
i met him with a swag del by this last guy
you go for all i had a seven god damn
that's and that's a natural one so
create one
yes you just like try to bite him and you end up just sort of like also catchy
right catches the dirty mags and you just heard yes he sees white women is
biting those
yeah yeah it is written in the shreds yeah yeah like my owners gone
yeah
uh...
but it is now that agents turn
and he is going to
c_n_n_ is is all his agents are are are gone he's going to sort of uh...
uh... triple all the stops here
okay he's going to uh...
to think he's gonna fuck up
he was he basically took out a uh...
the uh...
laser gun this time
and just read the shoot directly point blank at the dog and he just fuckin
misses
uh... you just see a tree behind the dog just fuckin vaporize uh...
uh... and now it is your turn hungry hamster
all right so
i think
i might check inventory one more time
uh...
missus has a good fucked up
i mean yeah i'll check inventory just just for the idea that it does tell you
like your free to do that uh... okay
seventeen move that means it's a good idea
you got jetpack
what
all you know what you know i do is i use the jetpack
and i go
Yes. So the jet pack allows you to do that. It gives you like 30 feet of movement or 60
feet of movement total. Okay. So you could basically use it and then it runs out of fuel,
but you're able to fly. So yeah, you were able to do that. So that was, yeah. And it's
only like 30 feet to get over to the other side. Yeah. So you're over the other side with
your jet pack. Oh, I guess that guy should roll an attack on you because you ran away
from him but um...
he does get a hit
uh... well alright so he hits the jet pack and i kinda go like
around yeah but i do cross i mean it still gets you still get the other side
just take twelve damage also. You're just leaving us alone dude?
twelve damage. That's your punishment for leaving us. Can my tongue reach across the river?
no, that's skilled
your tongue is only ten feet
uh... pop-up but that means
uh... if you are
uh... but it is an h_b_ now
your turn pleasant
all right amid
let's it what ok
i don't know if you maybe you can tell me this but
now the c_i_a_ is already got to a staff to worry about summoning the c_i_a_
still
uh...
further detail that
but i think it does it does that mean that i do have to worry about it
yeah like you're gonna have you're gonna have leeway because they've already sent
agents
uh... right
uh... this has been discussed a bunch of damage so i'm not going to use my big
my big thing on this kind of
uh... at the rectangle to a large but to square
uh... i'm gonna fly over the last remaining c_i_a_ guy
i'm gonna pack 'em
sixteen yeah that's it
ten describe your kill
okay so this is a little high concept but i
i fly down his throat into his feet
uh...
you see him like trying to like take a notes on this and report this back as
like a as a characteristic attack of you
uh... before he like plunges into the uh... that's called a disinformation
campaign some never gonna do that again
Yeah, and so he flies down past amazing boobs River, which is
apparently what this River is called if this roll 20 is to be
believed and yeah, he's dead.
And so you've defeated the CIA agents is first wave first wave
the could bring your side, but yeah, you've defeated them.
So yeah, yeah very easily.
and so uh...
you guys are now
bloody bruised and battered
uh... may i'm a full health
except you your full health
uh... you're welcome
hungry hands are you guys
hungry hands on the job
you're out of uh...
you're now out of check inventory for a little while
unknown
because i've missed a little s because use it three times
uh... from correct
uh...
and i think i used it more than three
you might have but let me do it which is okay
uh... and uh...
normal dog let's see how many licks you have left us to make sure
okay if three years for short rest so you're good
uh...
so you guys can uh...
yes you guys are here the buses at a gas those c_i_a_ agents are gone
ticket i just did
dick vandyke is dead there's a finally did
Yeah, there's a river and a rickety bridge, but your buddy got across obviously here.
But he can't check his inventory three more times to find a
jetpack unless he takes a long rest. A long rest will be eight hours and you have about a day until
the concert and then you don't know where your family's going to go next after they see the
the
I
is a bridge it is rather rickety so the uber does show up so yeah you guys can say you
guys wait like half an hour what's the uber driver's name I wait half an hour which is
so long for what's the uber driver's name now okay Doug okay thank god it's Doug he
that's right
uh... cool
uh... yet that shows up in this pocket right uh... home
the rickshaw
the uh... it's not that that's what his name is done goes up on a radio flyer
wagon
uh... looks like a tesla to me
the adventures of the new tesla
uh... you look so awesome hangout with
uh...
So would he be crossing the bridge too?
No, he sort of showed up from this direction, so he hasn't crossed the bridge yet.
But he's looking for Dick Van Dyke.
Oh no.
So I'm gonna say, I'm gonna say you guys have to go find his phone.
Yeah, I wanna go find, or who else is good at investigating?
Can I cross the bridge?
You can try to cross the bridge.
What's your investigation, Caleb?
so is added to the national investigation acrobatics across the bridge
you can use acrobatics
if you want to
uh...
uh... yeah what you very easily cross the bridge it feels rickety a ship you
make it over the time and here i have no weight
all right
normal dogs now
sniff out dick van dyke's phone
if i got you bro
use crime dog
and i don't know you investigation
nice yeah your eyes light up
uh... you're looking for crime
uh... and it's not
racist
and you find a phone
uh... and you see uh... at the uber app pulled up
with a bit of blood over
dick dick van dyke's profile face on it
and i i show my show the phone to the uber driver when you bring in the mouth
yeah
what i've got an idea
pleasant parrot
pickup dick van dyke score
uh...
okay i like this like this is going to know we're going to weekend at the
clinton
x_-nine and we're going to do that uh... alright i think i would have a lot of
it
because i was going to say this is going to be hard to convince it but if you're
going to try it i will let you guys try to pull this off
you have to describe to me how you're doing this and we need to do some roles
Um, alright.
Well, I'm a tiny hamster, so I'm gonna imitate the heartbeat.
By just hanging off of his chest hair,
and going occasionally doing this with his shirt.
Like, stretching.
Like he's in love with the Uber driver.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's not a bad idea. He might charm him.
I'm a tiny hamster.
We might not have to tip.
Caleb, you sit Dick Van Dyke down so you can walk around.
be the legs. Alright, I'll be the legs. I'll hold his arm. I start like jumping in the air
and touching my feet together. Like the chimney sweep. Yeah. And I'm gonna hover above him
holding his hair, holding his head up. Okay, so. Okay, couple of checks. Oh no, Patrick,
you should control his mouth. Oh okay, yeah. And then I'll talk while you move his mouth.
i'd go in between like i'll scurry up his shirt and i like
for the bottom lip you know it's like that he's got like a just as wisdom to
take it out of the home just i don't know i can't check in with all and the
first thing i have a lot of the first thing i say when patrick's is to move
his mouth around as i say
hi i'm dick van dyke don't mind my pets they're just helping me
uh... okay
okay so
of
with the you know this world uh i'm gonna need you all to roll um dexterity checks
okay basically to coordinate is what i want to see which one do i roll so just roll go to your
abilities there's just a dexterity just dexterity yes 14 i got 21 nice please i need a roll one
on
you would have to roll something like this for something but I didn't know it was going to be
a weekend at Bernie's thing. Yeah, so you're all pretty convincing like his head is kind of
straight up, his legs he's doing a little feet clicky thing, the only thing it's a little weird
he's sort of talking a little slurred he might be drunk is what he looks like. That's why you call
call
it
a
to
Come on, it's easy. He's got this.
[laughter]
Oh boy.
So...
If this one takes it out. Come on.
We did so well.
Alright, I'm gonna give him...
Okay.
And he smoothly glides
over the bridge.
Oh my god. He puts on the Tesla autopilot.
Yeah, so you, uh...
Yeah, you're on your way to Duluth.
Bypassing
So many things that I prepared for you all.
And um, uh, which you know what? I'm learning as a DM just right alongside you guys as players.
Um, so yeah, Doug is just sort of in the car driving. He sort of turns to me and says,
"Yo, I'm a big fan! Big fan of your work, Mr. Van Dyke."
Me too!
That's that Van Dyke wit, you know?
the other by the moves like and the amount of the chattering
like uh...
like chatterbox yeah
well you seem like you get your local back there i could turn the heat for
everybody
and turn a c_e_o_
he has a wolf wolf
it's a good idea to my penis
here's what we get here's additional parking
uh...
legal was that what you're animals that's helping you
now that's my penis
the
well okay well i don't mind me i'm not going to judge anything like a penis
you know i stopped at seven eleven
are you
well i don't know
let's go to seven eleven
yes you are you know i can uh... i could do that yet for sure this could be one
coming up here on a
i
three eighty seven and uh...
He sort of pulls over, there's a 7-Eleven, and he says, "You know what? There's a pandemic right now.
Do you want me to get you something and I'll bring it into the car, or do you insist on going in?"
"No, my animals will go in for me. I'll just stay here in the car, remaining completely still,
and seeming as if I'm not breathing, but it's just how I am. If I start to smell really bad,
or if you see any bugs on me, don't worry, it's just how I am."
His tongue is out of the side of his mouth and his eyes are just complete X's
Far be it from me to make you roll again. Go on out
Okay, so you guys go out of the car you head to 7-eleven. I guess you have to steal something. Oh we have eight dollars
Yeah, let's have eight dollars. I do. Don't we have sixteen dollars? Yeah, we have sixteen dollars
Can you try to give it to the car? No, no the cop pocketed it. Oh, right. All right. Okay, we got eight dollars then
Yeah, okay.
So I'm taking the bribe.
That's that's three hot dogs.
That's three hot dogs and one slurpee.
I'll get a hot dog.
I'm at 25.
Who is making the purchase?
Which one of your animals?
Come on.
Yeah, I I fly.
I don't speak because I don't want to break.
I was gonna say we're gonna start rolling again.
So yeah, I I don't I flap over and I drop the $8 on the counter and then I I look at the
seven eleven employees name tag
what was it what do i see ok
uh... and i fly over to the to the little hot dog rolling area and i pick on the
class three times
okay honey let me get that for you and she had a walks over there she waddles
her
big
and so it's not going to
all
animals
the
she bends down
heard her she's pretty good
sixty seven
and she gets the hot dogs
i think that uh... i think the loudest like answers we take
the what's going on in the world and i don't think there's any other way i can
you do it
yes we can then you just breathe didn't
i was trying to do a whistle
the loudest hamster breathing in sharply
uh...
yet keep trying not to tell you how yet
like your
i think
you will never be a prospector
but i want to do try to do the lake
eat pussy
and just your but so you're trying to devour it you're trying to try to do the
the
and she says now that'll be exactly eight dollars for y'all
now he's one of the dollars
old yeah way i eat that i a i eat the hot guys wolf down the hot dog and i take
the money back
okay uh... and i dropped a hot dogs in the uh...
i drop the hot dogs to my friends
the other two hot dogs i'm not a lot of it i'm small enough that i get into the
rollers and i eat all of the cheeseburger dogs
this is a really
i'm not stolen from a seven eleven so what do they do in this happens
they don't even know that the uh... i don't
they live like a
yes she she is she she comes out what you guys are doing this
and she taps on the uber drivers window
you see her complaining that dog about something
uh... do you guys run out with the food in the i open the cash register
uh... yeah
smart
yeah you find uh... another hundred and three dollars in all my god
it were rich for an all my god like seven hundred dollars in dog and i kept
eight dollars because i took it back so that's a hundred and eleven
yeah quick uh...
yeah and so quick maths from from from and i'm gonna go out of the uh...
yeah you guys go at the seven eleven to go to the car and uh...
she sees you all and she's she's she's now like she's like looks like she's
about to vomit
uh... and uh... she's like what is wrong with the supercar
we try to figure out what the smell is
not realizing dick van dyke is in the back very dead i give her a dollars
as she says that's all i ever wanted to and uh... you know pile back to the car
to go back in your way
can you drive in you drive
and uh... dilute this is is uh...
uh... not too far from where you were
uh... you cross over state boundaries and end up
into lose for the first thing you see is welcome to dilute stained is playing
here tonight
well they were permanent sign of that the other
every night
uh... you pointed to lose you know you see the signs advertising that stained
is there
and you're greeted by a just uh... beautiful perfect little city
uh...
dilute minnesota is a
magical place that's a forty four killed role i've actually really d one hundred
k
that's a big dice you're just thinking about one hundred
way down a role in those two yes he would get some higher one
uh... nominee you get a sixteen cam
well after all in now yet you know you know you've had a real good
seven-year-old
Oh my god. Here, Patches, try your hand.
Alright, sure, I'll give it a shot.
I'm gonna cut this out of the episode.
No!
Don't!
Leave it in.
83. Now you have to cut it out.
Yeah.
So you pull into Duluth.
You're greeted by a beautiful, perfect little city.
Duluth, Minnesota
is a magical place
full of grand spectacle, wonder
peace, zero homeless people, no gang violence, 5% Asian American, 80% Iranian, 15% none of
your business.
The city is hustling and bustling.
It's 2003 or 4 and we just finished laying off the entire Iraqi military.
The usual activity has also spiked because you guessed it, Stained is here, outside of
the shops and sort of malls that you would see you know multiple malls you'd
see merch tables to selling a limited edition I got stained in Duluth
Minnesota t-shirts like you know wristbands shit like that sorry I'm
deleting shit so I can get you guys here okay and yeah and like vinyl LPs of
stained albums even though no one looks like really want that this looks like
earthbound it's from there just take the screen shot from earthbound no I don't
believe you that you can buy this yourself yeah I mean well thank you you
You can buy masks that look like members of the band too, like Scooby-Doo masks.
With the original lineup that has John Wysocki as the drummer still.
You also see a number of children wearing these masks and they're playing around, running
around.
To get into the concert you have to get tickets.
It's sold out, of course, they're the biggest band on the fucking planet.
All the scalpers have been beaten to death and robbed of any extra tickets.
You look up a bit ahead down DuPont Street and see that the line to get into Jafar Stadium
is already formed.
People have tents and blankets.
Someone built a small villa in the time they've been on line.
You see one woman who got in line, she was 38 weeks pregnant and now she's giving birth.
So it looks like it's going to be pretty tough to get in, but here you are in the wonderful
city of Duluth at last.
Your Uber driver drops you off.
the
How much underwear can a hamster steal?
Probably steal a ton of all of it.
Well I am the hungry hamster.
I think your mic is pretty loud Pat. You might want to back up.
Yeah let me, let me.
No it's in audacity. It's the problem. Hold on.
Yeah there we go. Alright. How about now?
The audacity level wouldn't affect your mic at all.
No it does. It does.
If I turn the recording volume down
it actually works.
Oh ok.
I believe you. It does sound better now.
Yeah it does.
I go into Duluth Trading Company and I eat most of the underwear, not all.
Now you're eating it?
I'm the hungry hamster, I gotta do something.
Alright, so, uh, do you wanna-
What kind of fucking excuse is that, man?
Are you trying to do this-
You're going in, you're eating underwear, you're gonna blow our fucking- you're gonna blow this whole thing.
I'm hungry!
Are you trying to do this stealthily at all?
No.
No, I get into the factory and I'm-
Fuck you, hungry hamster.
the
Why did you think it was an underwear factory?
You said you were going to the training company.
Yeah, you're making all this up, so...
What is it?
Look up Duluth, you don't know Duluth?
You don't know Duluth Trading Company?
Yeah, I go to the store and I...
It's a factory now and I eat underwear.
You don't know Duluth Trading Company, the underwear company?
No.
You said it was a factory.
Will told me about it.
Now this is a specific thing that you're talking about?
Yeah, of course, right. We should have known.
We should have known.
American white men working on the underwear factory line and putting
the finishing touches on the tighty-whities and you see the conveyor
belt and you scurry up there you start eating them one by one as they come up
like loose Lucille Ball with the chocolates. That's exactly what I
thought I was doing. Yeah, yeah, yeah. So you're just filled with underwear now and
and uh... nobody's really noticing 'cause it's just like it's not my part of the
line and then eventually someone
starts to realize that they're part of the
line that they're not seeing any underwear coming down
so uh...
i'm gonna run away
yeah i was gonna say i'll give you a chance if you want to try to keep eating
no i know my limits
if there's anything i'm a person that knows my limits
i have an idea for how to get to try to get into the concert to sneak in
if i talk
if i talk to a person but over the phone does that still work the c_i_a_ of the
person can't see that it's a pair of talking
and on
well the c_i_a_ would probably tap the phone right there but no it not if it's a
pay phone without c_f_b_i_ here
the uh... the f_b_i_ and everyone knows that they were there on the outside all
our care about their it's ok all all our
tonight
neither or no
i got a hundred and three dollars in my inventory well you know i i i have to
break one of the dollars. It's all in quarters, we just didn't mention that.
It's perfect then. Where are we keeping it?
Well, okay, no, I can screw a cheese. I fly into a store and I take a quarter out of the tip jar.
With that 17 stealth, the quarters that were usually jingling at 20,000 decibels
about yeah hundred and three dollars worth of quarters
jingling chubby cheek okay can i may use a
the pay phone to call the trading company in place
and or order for underwear
to the backstage of the state himself
yeah and then we can all high and then we can all hide under the underwear
and i will do it where you are
come on
i will say though you're gonna want if you wanna have to the
does c_i_a_ did not notice that a birdies
taking the like one-and-a-half minutes it would take to operate a pay phone for
them
uh... that you might want to try to like to have got an idea
we dress up
caleb in person close
and i don't like it was a good idea yet yes it looks like he's the one making
the call
that's a great idea
let's do it
how do you know it's not hard
and i i pull out a bunch of underwear from my shoes
I pull out all the underwear I just ate and I make a little like...
Yeah, it's stuck together from your saliva into the shape of a shirt and pants.
Into the shape of an Adidas track suit.
Okay, all of you guys roll a perception check.
Oh, I'm scared.
Nat 20.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god, you're beast, dude.
19.
Yeah, I mean...
How'd you do, Hunggy?
okay what just happened? roll perception check. roll perception check. okay. goddamn yeah
hungry hamster you're too busy just like ripping underwear. let me roll that again cuz my dad
no no but uh pleasant parrot you notice down down the street in a little alleyway
the once again you you you notice the faint hefty steps of a of a stocky man
whose steps you would recognize right away as mr. grab your damn dog from the
last time I think you heard 20 no oh he's around I tried to the guy who tried to
to get us.
Who looks like Joe Pesci.
Joseph Pesci, yeah.
He's around the corner, I don't think he knows.
I think we would be able to spot him from a mile away, he has no nose.
That's a good point.
That's a really good point.
Yeah, he looks like a jack-o-lantern.
I immediately started winding my legs up to run away.
but it is a little bit of a kind of like winding them up so I can run really can
we can I I'm just sitting I'm still trying to make a shirt out of the
underwear or whatever I want to hide an eavesdrop on him okay
yes throwing up okay the trip has finally gotten to me I just start
throwing up a lot of people late car sick a lot yeah a lot of people are
seeing me throw up too. They're like, "Oh my god, this hamster's on the street throwing up!"
Okay, I gotta roll to see if he notices that.
Oh, right.
You mean, "Oh, right."
Wait, then not a lot of people...
We're gonna run away, we're gonna hide.
And you're like, "I'm gonna do something."
Not a lot of people, just one person.
Okay, so it's a inconspicuous kind of vomiting?
Yeah.
Okay, yeah, you start to see the I will say that I mean dog dog normal dog and pleasant parrot you start to see
That there's some stirring back in that corner where you thought you saw them and
After hungry hamster started vomiting and they uh, they sort of saunter
Out and they see people saunter they saw when and they saunter and they see you guys
What?
Um...
Is this my fault?
Yeah.
Damn it.
A hundred percent.
Ah, shit.
Um...
Yeah.
I'm gonna just drop in some tokens in here, and then, um...
Uh, Joe Pesci, aka Mr. Grabbed You a Damn Dog, and Skeletor are gonna say,
"Let's get 'em!"
And then we're gonna roll for initiative.
No!
I got 13.
I got 7.
I got a 9.
I go first.
All right, and they're gonna roll for initiative as well. I will defeat them and it's not gonna be close
Yeah, i'm gonna kill joe pesci
finally
He every role he does is with disadvantage because he has no nose right
It's just not and he's short. Uh-huh and he's italian. Yeah
All right, that's it
And he's bald across the line. Okay
Uh, it is actually your turn
uh... hungry hamster alright so
first thing i do i see i noticed jill pesci
and she referred to it as a great that's a great that's a good that takes up an
action to have at the time
no that's your action in your movement so i see jill pesci
uh...
first thing i do
is that like
scurry a little bit second first thing you do
no well then you know that i don't know if it was not just them
so i see jill pesci and then i i immediately i'd jump up and i try to
jump into his nose hole that i made
okay let's see what the uh...
you could definitely try to do that but c_n_n_ r_c_a_
if you use your full movement
and then to a uh... uh... enrolled e_-twenty
the
let's do it and they were the twenty at your acrobatics
can you get it
let's go
and then a 23
you gotta crit 20
so you just jump
i mean i can't stop that
how i play dnd
so you just jump right into this guys face
ok i control him like plankton
oh my what the fuck
oh my god this is worse than when deniro did this
and now i control him like plankton
ok yeah
Okay, yeah, sure. I'll let you try to control his legs like this.
Does Plankton jump on someone's face?
No, he goes into SpongeBob's brain, remember?
I would have said Ratatouille, but...
Yeah, I would have gone Ratatouille.
I would have gone a lot of stuff before Plankton.
You know, we're being a little nitpicky on Pat.
I'm gonna pull off.
Ease up.
No, buddy, you're crushing it.
Dude, I rolled a 20 and a 23.
You're crushing it. Dude, you're the best D&D player ever.
What are we talking about?
Just let you play it all.
Alright, so, I am controlling him like Ratatouille now.
That's your full, like, turn.
Okay.
You can't do anything else.
I can't control him like Ratatouille yet, but trust me, it's coming.
I'm gonna let you try next turn.
I think it'll be a certain couple of rolls.
Um, you are up, motherfucking Pleasant Parent.
Alright, so I'm gonna fly a little... wait what's my...
Cameron, come in here.
I'm trying to remember.
Hey, blessed parrot, come in here!
Yeah, I'm close enough to get to Jafar.
Oh, okay.
Not Skeletor.
Yeah, so I fly to Jafar.
God damn it.
And I use my Talon's attack on him.
Okay, yeah, do it.
Ten.
Yeah, it's not gonna hit.
You try to get in there and it just clacks on the bones. He's like, ah
You can't pierce these bones
You should have known he was bones
Geoff's bones are clearly bones
He's made out of bones
It could be a soft bone. It looks like a Halloween decoration
Looks like bones, but he's made of flesh
I
Don't know any of those guys
I have a cousin you think like in the freak show. There's a guy like that
There could be a guy who looks like he's made of bones, but you touch him and he's just a guy
I've never met a guy like that
No, you're thinking of more suits no, that's what a guy looks like he's made of a suit
Guy in a skeleton more you thinking of Phoebe Bridgers
she's got skeletons on her shirts all the time.
Never think about Phoebe Bridgers!
Are you sure?
Yes!
I'm thinking about Phoebe Bridgers.
I'm thinking about her now too.
Me and the hungry hamster high five.
I poke my little hand out of Joe Pesci's face and we do a little air high five.
Okay it's your turn Norval Dog.
So, upon seeing that, the bone man, I just get so hungry and I go in for a bite.
That's right son.
I gotta take a bite of these bones.
19.
Yeah it's...
Roll for damage.
11.
Oof.
Yeah, so you just run up, your tongue is wagging in the wind, and you just like fully launch
at this uh skeleton freak and jump right into uh his hip bone uh which is that uh weird
looking one that's around the hip area yeah the scariest part of the skeleton yeah for
sure yeah and he's like yeah my hip what is joe pesci i told you he had his hip could
be made of meat that's a really good character it doesn't taste like meat it tastes like
bones
okay but alright
that's his favorite food i would like to know i'm a dog
and uh... i'm gonna roll to see if joe pesci can get you out of his nose
uh... union
he can't
uh... role a uh...
really dexterity saving through because you try to avoid him
picking your nose
at all needed not you get the first one i'm sorry uh... twenty-two yet he is
able to pluck you out of his nose that sucks
yeah uh... like you did
and uh... you know what i do
it's not my turn yet but the apneas it will pluck you out of his nose
and toss you aside that's gonna be his full turn
uh...
and uh...
skeletal are now is going to raise his staff in the air
uh... and try to cast some sort of magic's
on uh... on uh... you normal doug after you get him
and he just only fuckin
with city just with the completely for canada and then uh...
uh...
i guess you're all over there now so all the role perception check
well
maybe there's a third guy
fourteen
for
reception
an actual zero. He got a natural zero. A natural one minus one. He literally got just like a
hard zero. He rolled a zero on the die. Created a new side just for him. Hungry Hamster, you
don't really know if you're alive or dead. You're sort of in... He can't even perceive
your own blood. You're existing in a liminal space right now. Like I always do. Yeah. And
And uh, but you two, um, uh, normal dog, you're focusing on Skeletor.
Pleasant parrot, you're the one who notices, out of the side, comes motherfuckin' ManBearPig.
No.
Wait, maybe he'll help us.
Yeah, we told him to only kill people.
Who swipes at Skeletor.
Well, it's not really a person, but I'll let you, I'll let you kill a ManBearPig.
That's, he's more of a skeleton.
It's what's inside of a person.
It is what's inside of a person.
a
just
crushes him in his mouth
uh... joe she's just a couple of running away
and i don't think i think i think it was a looking man bear pig and i think that
there's a so scary
uh... so-called i get it but yeah i don't know the scooby-doo run again and
i'm out there did uh...
i'm fucking kidding wait i got an idea wait wait wait i got an idea and it is now it is
now uh hungry hamster's turn i do my famous dance uh okay yeah go for it oh wait actually
i have to resist it i'm sorry yeah um let me do it hey you don't give in yeah you have
to do it i do i personally don't have to do it and i will never do it it's terrifying
you just have to do the dance do it right now do the nene i'm not doing the night come
on
to death inside of ManBearPig's mouth and Skeletor starts dancing like no one's watching.
Okay, actually seems kind of fun. I'm gonna get in.
Okay, now that Caleb's back, now that normal dog is back, I run away.
Okay, you can try it. You can run away. You'll provoke an attack of opportunity
for anyone who's trying to attack you, anyone who's near you.
you
a
the
are
member pig listening to your pleas as you're sort of like
like trying to play with him
and you see member pig
uh...
i ask if he remembers us from the bus
and member pig nods
and and i say hey we gave you all those good tasty people in brooklyn with
wisconsin
we have a member pig starts around his tummy
uh... remembering all those people yeah yeah you had fun eating all those people
and destroying the town and roll a roll a perception check inside check sorry
yeah hungry hamster roll an insight check I got a nine okay
member pig starts to hold his his fist out to you I bump it yeah member pig
nods. Oh my god. Can we add ManBearPig to the party? Maybe, we'll see. I call being ManBearPig.
So anyway, it's now your turn PleasantParrot. Okay, I use Peck on Skeletor. Do it. 16. Yeah,
it's
I tell I tell man bear pig I'm making it just the way you like it
Please don't do this to me. He's like freaking out. Meanwhile, I'm right on the head when he says that yeah
You do a damage and I think what you already do you already did 11 right normal dog? Yeah
Yeah
you just like start pecking him in the sweat and like the forehead like
And it's just like starts to make a crack and the crack starts to splinter wider. It's killatory's just like
He's like not looking very good at all
It's your turn normal dog
I'm gonna tackle. All right do it who 12 skeletal. Okay, okay, that doesn't hit
Actually, wait, no, we should give our pig the time
Anyway, I'm wrong actually because you were the first person to hit Skeletor
So you actually have advantage because of your crime dog ability so that does hit so roll for damage. My life is brilliant
Yes, nine. Yeah, describe your killing Skeletor you kill
All right, he's just a bunch of bundle of bones to me. So I start digging a hole in the ground
Cuz I'm gonna bury his ass. Don't bury him. Don't bury that man bear. No, no
To eat him don't bury
Fetch well, I already started burying no
Uncover the top of Jimmy Hoffa's head
and then I throw him into ManBearPig's mouth.
Yeah, you do. ManBearPig already has Joe Pesci in his mouth, so the bones just like shoot up and like ManBearPig...
I kind of bukkake him with bones.
Yeah, I'm gonna see him fall and explode on his head.
I'm gonna give ManBearPig a chance to try to grab onto it.
I'm gonna roll a straight... I think that's dex, basically.
It's athletics.
It's like catching grapes in your mouth with like which he's
very good at so yeah people know that about.
Yeah, so he just like makes like just enough space and you
start to hear Joe Pesci's voice again because it's been screaming
headfirst into his throat.
So he'll go and then you like you see like the skeletons just
all kind of fall into his mouth and he's just chewing on them
and they're both going to go.
They're going to try to get out of this situation there.
will actually no sorry just your passion is going to try to get out of the
situation he's in
uh... he is unable to
evidence man bear pigs turn
uh... he's going to use to
on joe pesci
stability he has
yeah he's just gonna eat joe pesci
and he just devours joe pesci
and skeletal or
so
and uh... they're both gone
wall
and uh... uh...
you see uh...
man bear pig uh...
now it's a sort of wiping the blood from his mouth
uh...
here i remind him that we fist bumped in that were friends
and uh... he he sort of like that doesn't really regard that he'd like and then he
uh...
he reaches down
and uh...
uh... feels around for like a pocket
and he finds a good
part of his flesh like in between
bear and pig and pulls out like a note
this slimy note
any hands it to you
and hungry hamster and then he just sort of walks away
uh...
war and it says uh...
thank you for everything
i love people they're delicious
also
also metal man told me
that uh... metal man
metal man told me that candy hamster is gonna hurt you
so be careful i love people they're delicious is a pretty soon bumper
sticker yeah
metal man metal man maybe that's like a friend of the command
uh...
that must be shredder
there's no way that's not
i think it's metal maria's there's a man let's it's metal maria
yet or anything it might be better than they're paying right
could that had someone else of written that for
uh... someone else might have helped write him right that's more than we do
anything you know about that in my mind i was a section channel analyze the
handwriting yes absolutely do an insight check
okay can you all of your
always yeah yeah fuckin advantage on all investigation and percent yet to it
the crime dot
sniff out the handwriting i don't know how to tell them just role like
investigation or insight or whatever and just take the higher number.
Okay.
You will just get advantage on it.
Thirteen.
Yeah, that's, you're able to tell that like ManBearPig probably couldn't grip any writing
instrument known to humans to make that out.
And you can also start to see that, well with that I think that's mostly what you can tell.
Does anybody else want to try to see if they can understand it?
I'll try it.
try to see if you can. 15. Yeah, I would say that like between Crime Dog, Crime Dog's Caleb
and Pleasant Parrot, you can start to realize that like all the eyes in that note look like
knives. Okay, okay. Alright. I think I know who wrote this. Look exactly like knives. Jeffrey
the
and I'm sorry. You better be. So yeah, you guys now are kind of rid of your rivals as far as you can tell.
But it seems that the candy hamster... Okay, I've got a great idea. Ready? What are you thinking?
I pray to God. Okay, which God? Which religion?
Flying spaghetti monster. I did make you proficient at religion because I knew you
immediate failure doing that.
Wait, who do you pray?
You pray the flying spaghetti monster.
Yeah. You just see like a green text reply in the sky.
It's very funny.
And the green text tells me what about the candy hamster?
You know what? I'm going to
don't let him win.
No, no, no, it's fine.
It's that hungry hamster roll a history check to see if you can remember
anything about the candy hamster.
*laughter*
You are pretty sure he was made of meat.
Yeah guys, I'm pretty sure he was made out of tendons.
The meat hamster.
I might be remembering a different hamster from my life.
No, you're thinking of Skeletor!
No, he had bones.
I think I might be thinking of the tendon hamster.
And you see you start to see the crowds around you
The earthbound looking suspiciously earthbound looking characters crowd around you start to go
Towards you see them more than now towards going towards the the stadium and getting in line
So like the concert's gonna start like fairly soon
Pleasant parrot roll a wisdom saving throw just similar to what you rolled very early on in this campaign
Okay. Mm-hmm
Fifteen.
Okay.
Your...
What the fuck is that?
I rolled a fudge.
You rolled a DF.
That's a fudge roll.
So you, uh, you, uh, feel your head shake similar to last time.
And that cryptic sort of words that you heard, the "wish you could last" comes back in, but
This time you also hear "I'm waiting for you, pleasant parrot"
and then it goes away.
That's the lead singer of Stay.
[laughter]
He's a vampire.
[music]
[MUSIC]