(upbeat music)
- So last time on a Hamward Bound,
which is just becoming less and less
like the source material it was based off of.
You guys bested ManBearPig using your sheer wit.
- Easy.
and seriously unfortunate roles on my end
uh... you drove the bus to to a creek where you beat up the c_i_a_
uh...
you weekend at bernie dick vandyke to get my ride stole from seven eleven
and you made your way to dilute minnesota finally
beat up
mister graham dan dog
and skeletal words and fed him to fed them to me and their
then left me
cryptic note
about a candy hamster and then Pleasant Parrot had a strange sort of sensation like he did
in the first session.
I heard a vampire speak to me.
You heard a vampire talk to him.
And now you guys are trying to get into the concert without a ticket and you're three
animals and so you get to the front of the line after walking for about thirty minutes.
Can I do something real quick?
Yeah.
With some of the underwear that I had in my cheeks, I make t-shirts that say "service
animal."
Okay.
Oh.
That is the smartest thing you've ever done in a Dungeons and Dragons game.
I'll let you do that.
Yeah.
Okay, yeah, you make those t-shirts, you guys come up dressed as service animals, underwear
service animals.
Jafar Stadium comes into view.
- Mine is like, mine is like, like black lace lingerie.
(laughing)
- And it looks like, exactly like the palace in Aladdin,
except Jafar is a defense contractor based out of Duluth.
So that's the name, why the stadium's named after it.
When you reach the front of the line,
you see security's fairly stacked, electric fences,
barring the entry, security guards
that have been patrolling up and down the line
as you've been walking.
And then machine gun turrets on top of the security
sort of scanners, checkpoint scanners,
which are designed to scan for not only
whether or not you are armed,
but if you have intent to harm stained.
- I feel that.
(laughing)
Just kidding.
- You don't see your family in line though.
So they've probably already gotten in.
Oh, yeah, that's what's
Mm-hmm or yeah, or they missed the concert or whatever
They gotta be in there. Oh
Please let them be in there
I feel like I could sniff them out feel like we're close enough
Yeah, go for it. You could try it for I'm gonna use crime dog. Yeah do it. I'm gonna do investigation
I did insight last time but I didn't realize that negative one. So I'm gonna do investigation this time
16 nice. Yeah, and I hit a nice sniffer you catch the feints scent of a blagojevich
About
How much is a click a click is 1,000 light-years?
Okay, so about a point. Oh
Of a click of would just say one will say one click is one
Okay, really? Yeah, why do they say click?
it's about .1
[laughter]
ok, it's slang
it says a click or more appropriately click
with a k
is the slang or short term for one kilometer
ok
about .1 clicks
how many miles is a click?
1 point something
5/8ths of a mile
a kilometer is 5/8ths of a mile
a kilometer is smaller than a mile
Yeah, Patches said there was more right then, like insinuated there was more and I like panicked.
Like my entire world was upside down.
You can actually use the Fibonacci sequence to estimate how much...
Oh, okay, shut up! Shut the fuck up, nerd! Shut the fuck up!
It's pretty cool.
Now that's pleasant parrot.
Yeah, it's not pleasant.
So yeah, you can sniff them. They are inside.
Okay.
Um, you can sniff, sniff out their, their cool...
What does a Blagojevich smell like?
Oh, you don't wanna know.
Is it like the stink?
It smells like malt liquor and, and Di Serrano and Draco Noir.
Smells like stadium foreskin.
Foreskin.
Yeah.
It smells like spraying Draco Noir in your foreskin.
Actually, everyone can smell it.
everyone's walking around like others
stadiums are
i don't remember the way they smell it
i think it was a vicious here
so yeah what do you guys want to do
can
your service animal now you guys look like service animals so you know you
could try to cozy up to people or something or you can try
anything
i do see i'd see a very conspicuous icon of jafar standing in line
what i do
mhm
is uh...
i want to go to defy i don't know what patrick's about to say i'd i'd i'd do a
couple cartwheels
yeah i figured that they had a good
and i think that's a far
yeah you go to jafar uh... two fours is standing in line like everybody else
very excited to see stained
island on the shoulder
you know
who hello there pleasant parents
I'm I don't know my name I just mean you seem like a rather pleasant
parrot.
Is this what you far sound like without being raised a bit?
Yeah.
No, wow.
Okay.
I think I have some crackers for you when he goes into his robe
and has Jafar would never have crackers to far could have crackers.
He has a young ago.
He could do whatever that's true.
Yeah, he likes parrots.
He doesn't like Iago the he but he likes parrots.
He just doesn't like that parrot.
it's a lot more if you read it
i should have read the book
you know that on sunwiki media
that's my bad y'all
and he takes out some crackers
and he gives it to you
pleasant parrot
i'm just gonna wait this out
mmhm
ok, what about you two?
i just start sniffing
sniffing fucking pussies and assholes
yeah i'm still doing
still doing cartwheels
I'm going behind every single person.
Yeah.
And then I also, you know what, I think I have some money in my inventory.
I hire a blind guy like for ten bucks to just every time somebody gets mad that I'm sniffing
their asshole.
Can I jump into a purse or something?
Okay, a couple things to resolve here.
No, you know what I do is I go to the front of the line.
Okay.
We're in the concert.
We're in?
No, you're in the line to get off the stadium.
Oh, never mind.
we
What did you want to do as a dog?
Um, I wanted to hire a blind guy.
Is there any blind guys around?
Roll an investigation to see if you can find a vision impaired individual.
It's easy, you can tell just by looking at them.
Three.
Well, I guess I can't.
Yeah, I mean you can see some guys that look fucked up, but you can't tell if they're blind
or not.
Okay, I walk up to every black guy with sunglasses on and I ask if they're blind.
Yeah, they all ask.
Oh fuck, I'm a dog!
dog.
So you just go up to black guys.
Jafari seems really friendly and not evil.
Now to resolve the hungry hamster thing.
Well, you're just a dog that it seems to be hunting black men
with sunglasses on.
Have a musical air to them.
Hungry hamster.
You try to crawl into someone's overall pocket so I can only
assume is a farmer and there.
it's a somebody who it's a hipster who's going to see stained ironically
okay so they're just like oh get out of here you
furry bitch and just start slapping at you
and you're not able to get into the pocket um
uh oh man that sucks i'm uh i'm with i'm with uh
where's my frappuccino i'm what a 45 year old comedian thinks a hipster is
I hate hamsters I'd rather be on my app.
This hamster was trying to touch my phone.
Hamsters are so mainstream.
Yeah he says all that in a row.
He's there by himself.
by himself
he's doing an ironic bit it is two thousand four so there's no like social
media is composed by on a forum later yeah i'd try to go to a college i did
touches nokia engage
mhm
yeah
so uh... you had a line moves up a little bit more
uh...
and uh... the only way really indicate that is jafar
uh... moving up a little bit more
uh... already
uh... to bring president there it here too
is impossible there's too much uh... folks at home i put too much shit on
this world twenty map so
uh...
and uh...
before we have resolved that too
hungry hamster role a uh... uh... additional stealth check because the
guards are starting to notice that your
sort of crawling into people's pockets
the cartwheeling
okay yet this one starts to sort of come up to you
uh... and uh...
and say i say sh
he's uh... the hamster holds a finger up to its mouth
and that's the session armed to guard
uh...
he's like
anyway put his put his head finger to his headpiece
insert saying something into his headpiece i say she and her
meanwhile uh... normal dog
you go up to uh... one guy and i'll say that like
enough time has passed by that you've successfully found a blind guy
uh... he's just really far back in line
uh... yeah
yeah and you see the blind guy was like
on man
well we can cut because he's
is by a service animal
i left my was gonna call now of my dog at home and other blind are glad i found
this random lady when he's a blind dog to
not only people bob line people of blind pets
okay otherwise they get jealous of the pets and she has made the whole i get it
Yeah, and then meanwhile pleasant parrot and Jafar
Try to go into the scanner right and so
The
You get into the scanner pleasant parrot with Jafar Jafar is like I just found this parrot
But he seems awful nice and the scanners start going off like crazy when you go through them pleasant parrot what?
And the guards all turn around to face you and
And at that point um pleasant parrot roll a dexterity saving throw wait a second. I'm a bird
Cameron can Cameron try that now no way
you're already fucked up.
This is too funny.
I can't believe that.
That's insane.
(laughter)
Yeah, electric fence isn't like a thousand feet high.
I got a twenty.
Okay, um...
Okay, you are trapped.
What?
I can't express to you how high this next saving throw needed to be.
and you are trapped inside of this
a sort of cage you see all the guards like "FREEZE! FREEZE!"
we have somebody we have something coming in with somebody coming in and
you see somebody run up to you and inject something
in you, Pleasant Parrot. And you start to feel your veins fill up
and get syrupy. You start to slowly drift off. Meanwhile, Hungry Hamster
you, um, the guard is now chasing you
So you are running away from the guard.
Um, and uh, I need you to roll a dexterity saving throw as well.
This is getting so dramatic.
Woah.
Fuck yeah.
Yeah, so this guard tries to grab you and you just are able to scoot out of the way and skitter along with your little hamster reflexes.
Now this other guard has now completely targeted you, normal dog.
The hell? I have a man.
uh... this is now this isn't they are now alarmed at all of your presence she
and this could this uh... uh... uh...
guard is now going up to you roll a dexterity saving threat is even get away
from him
this is a resort of it like that
means a layup to me
where you at
yet twelve twelve that's this is this car is able to scoop you up
and just jam of i'll jam at some of some shit inside of you
hungry hamster you keep running over running away
normal dog you start to pass out
certificate dream lazy dreams about being a regular as dog
hungry hamster you run away as far as you can and as fast as you can
and uh...
you guys are both asleep now
and you don't know where you're going to be
hungry hamster
what's going on with going to your head
so what what's up with me right now both of your pals is got
looks to you abducted
cuz i could go into the concert i'm fine right now
you i could go in
and solve that all this crap by myself
but i think the power friendship will prevail to
so it's a good call that's a great that's a great interest in the uh... the
power friendship is you know it's very philosophical yeah uh...
as I'm thinking maybe I could pray that they're just bringing them to
a they the my two friends accidentally just one
a backstage passes I could pray for that
we are what do you mean for him
that's right yeah that my two friends accidentally was possible what we got
flagged for backstage pat what do you think we think prayer
does it begin what you're getting all things can you get any in Christ
you doubting the power of prayer I have so I'll
in this game I'm not real life kinda sus dude
yeah I'll maybe I
role stealth and then hide in the pocket
of one of the guards that
I'm gonna have you do with this advantage cuz they're hunting you know let's do
with advantage
Hmm, that's not what I said.
He's just gonna do it.
Let's do it with double advantage. How about that?
It's not even a thing, really.
Uh, it could be.
We could make it a thing. I could roll like 6 d20s.
You could also pull some items out, too.
Oh, you know what? I do my famous dance in a place where everybody can see me.
Where do you go to do that?
I jump up on top of one of the guard towers.
One of the guard towers.
Yeah, you have to crawl up the guard tower. I'll say okay do this. So so
So stadium with a guard tower. Oh, yeah now it is. So you see a guard so you see a guard tower
You're gonna have to do a couple of things
You're gonna need to be able to avoid the guards. I can get to the tower
I can do that and then climb the tower don't know about that one. All right, so
Let's do I'll say that with that crit you're gonna keep avoiding the guards
I'm not gonna stop you from having to do that
You're gonna get to the so you sort of like - pass the guards you go in between one of their legs like like a cartoon
You're like skittering around like you see people in line like watching you go by and then you reach
You go all the way to the right of this area and you see the one
What's up, this one? I'm moving my characters that here
Let me sorry I want a different page now my bad. Wow. He's he's online shopping right now. Yeah
No, I was on a different role 20 pay. I'm never gonna online shop. And so it's on Amazon looking at boobs the movie
You're looking at girls gone wild box
Know what that is and it would be funny to buy one of those
A girl's gone wild DVD in 20. They're like they're like 50 bucks. Really?
They were so expensive that's why I never bought him when I was a kid. Yeah, okay
Anyway, the turrets are shooting at you now. I'm gonna say again with that with that crit
I don't want to belabor that you're you're able to dodge a turrets the bullets pretty easily
You know shooting at this hamster and now roll an athletics check to climb that tower
Can't hide that for me you got a five. Oh, why'd you roll? No, it didn't it wasn't
I don't know what was going on, but it wasn't like...
So you start to crawl up the tower, and you just sort of like fall...
You reach a loose brick, and in this tower, this guard tower,
and it just slips out of your hand, and as you're falling...
Yeah, the hungry hamster died, actually died in the stand concert.
As you're falling...
He fell off the guard tower.
[laughter]
As you're falling, your hamster ball deploys to protect you, but you just hit the ground.
But people can still see me, right?
You're falling from the...
Right, but there's guns shooting at me.
Yeah, well, hold on. What are you trying to do while you're falling from the tower?
There are guns shooting at me, so obviously people are going to look to where the bullets are shooting, correct?
Yes, yeah.
So, as soon as I hit the ground, I do my famous dance.
No, so when you hit the ground, okay, when you hit the ground, you're gonna suffer a
concussion.
Is that what you're saying?
Nah.
I'm at full health, right?
Uh, yeah.
Okay.
I never updated it on my chart.
You hit your head, and your tiny little hamster brain rattles around your skull as you bounce
around your ball.
And you black out, too.
You almost had a chance.
Nah.
You almost had a chance there.
Uh, that's not what happened.
The first time that Patrick has ever been told no by Patches.
I know.
History.
I like to reward creativity and creative minds.
He sure does have a creative mind.
And you all start to come to and you awaken sort of cramped and cold.
Hungry hamster, you are all cramped together.
You're starting to get a sense of where you are.
Hungry hamster, you're just sort of like just waking up and you feel something on your head
And as you touch, you realize it's normal dogs, balls are on your head and a normal dog.
You start to come to and you feel a kind of a, it hurts, but it feels like residual pain
from Pleasant Parrot's talons, just like scratching into your floppy ears, but you don't really
feel the pain too much anymore.
It's like almost like you're number now and Pleasant Parrot from where you can see on top
of this pile and this dark, cold, weird mess is that there's sort of a, you try to squirm
around and you brush up against cold steel.
And you can start to see in a window, it looks like a window as you're trying to make it,
trying to see through and what you realize now is this like goo, it's like bluish, cold
goo.
You start to make the figure of a man, his back turned to you and he seems to be fiddling
with something.
juices inside this container making you feel like woozy and drunk you guys are like numb
like it's um you try to push your way through are we all in the same place my balls are on
your head and uh what the fuck are you talking about and um what yeah what your balls aren't
on my head he just said my balls are on your head nah he didn't say that my balls are i'm
I'm just, I'm fucking rotating your head with my balls like a machine.
You thought he was just saying a place that we were all there?
Yeah, I thought he was just talking shit.
As I often do, folks.
And you can't really feel your head, your heart, your blood is thick with like this.
And this man now turns. And really only Pleasant Parrot could see it because he's by the window.
And, um, Pleasant Parrot, you start to have flashbacks.
to being inside a tank just like this many years ago
and I call him pleasant 11 you remember this man as
Schmidt the Schmuck leave
okay, Schmidt the Schmuck leave
he goes over to the no relation to anybody in particular
that
yes i know that's cd cutlieb is hungarian and american born
but what if he was it's been a shmup
and it is
you allegedly i guess not really allegedly he was a scientist in the m_k_
alter experiments
google it
he's a uh... smitty schmaltzy was not
you think the sydney got madly small it was part of spam smithy small truck
she did not have a
the okay so he's
you'll my most successful experiments in such men's mission will try
program
but i don't understand why you call it that
i think it's a great i don't think that i think that's a real ring to it he puts
finger to the container and he's just like, "Shh, shh."
You'll see, and he walks back to his lab station,
"The Iraq war is not going so well.
And so, there's a rise of a Shia organization led by Tony Danza,
who seems to be getting increasing popularity.
So I have been tasked to once again
Creating an army of animals and you have brought two
wonderful specimens with you
Shut up, bitch
Yeah, no, yeah, you tell them normal dog
Yeah, you fucking stupid bitch and you all came to this concert
You heard me you got nothing to say you definitely heard you have no comeback. I
Like it. Okay. I don't I don't have a comeback. Is that what you want to hear?
Stupid ass made up name, Shmim Shmay Shmultra
It's not a made up name
It's a made up name
It's like a jash
That was my-
That was like shit
That was my grandfather's name
Your grandfather's name was Shmim Shmay Shmultra
No, no, he was Shmidney Shmotleyb the third
His name was shit
Yeah, like Bullshmit
No, that's pretty good
Yeah
Yeah, everything you've ever done is Bullshmit, bitch
I am look I feel it. Yeah, you're a bitch. That's what you are. Yes, the cat operation should not go well, bitch
But all right now we'll let you continue
He goes to like Paul lever
and you guys feel the juices now getting really warm and hot and you start to feel like your bodies are like
changing and like your cells are like
mutating and it's like you have uh... normal dog you have like an alligator
tail for a second and then you have like a you have uh... diane lane space and
hungry hamster you turn into
like uh... hot i'll i hungry hungry hippo for like
like a full minute and return right back to the hungry hamster
i'd like that
yeah it's just like this
transformations happening around you and you hear
uh... shimmy shmotley continue monologuing
as a candy hamster has been very kind to the c_i_a_ overseers
i mean the shimmy i a
provising intel on all variety of supernatural animals
but it's not quite like you three
and he's got some poll
lever down one more
uh...
and it says
yeah uh...
and uh...
uh... suddenly
flies into the room and just punctures his throat and Schmitty Schmottlieb falls over
dead.
A flying knife!
Oh my god!
And you see your friend and uncle, Uncle Shredder, and his PIC, ManBearPig, storm into the room
and fuckin just fuck up six shit shimmy shimmy
and uh...
just eat him and ruin and will mostly man bear pig does that
and you see uh... uh... man bear pig
runs up to the container
and just rips it off
uh... in freeing you guys
and you see uh... you guys are still a kind of woozy
and you see a shredder go up to you
he says
i was in such a rush to get you guys out of there
so you would get caught by the cops i forgot that my friend let me that bike
so i've been following you ever since
i met this fellow here while he was killing people and it may blow that up
what i was gonna ask what happened to
the we'll have a bike on the side of the road i think that the reason that it was
covered in bs would have happened to the by then
mhm
well
uh... anyway i'm glad i followed your trailer found you here
shimmy the shimmy leaders of the
and this this poor man bear piggies troops padding its head and scratching it
like it's a
sick was subject to the simpson were experiments that you three are just
undergoing
this this center was developed by the candy hamster and it's underneath the
concert venue
if we get out of here
we can still storm the concert and stop the candy hamster before it's too late
he's gonna try to kill all three of you were turn you into my list c_i_a_
zombies anything to get you away from your parents
james eats i hate that guy
you know it's like you guys didn't even notice that he wasn't in the farm with
you when they drop the animals off so
he's been just doing this the whole time
i think i'm going to have a just for god's sake is that
i was just in the bathroom
checkups can be hamster
uh... old trick in the book
anyway i'll worry about my bike later
i'm sure it's my friends bike i'm sure it's fine
now you guys want to bust out of here what
no i i want to put it somewhere
i guess i had to wait to i saw my alligator says what you guys want to
stay here
uh... no you don't
i'm better and i don't have it
uh... yeah i guess we can leave
yeah let's go
uh... yeah you guys uh... leave
this c_i_a_ which may be smartly be just see his like tell his left now member
picking goes
but for a person just like you see his tie comes out
uh...
and uh...
you guys rush up through all these weird catacombs
he passed by other experiments uh... that you didn't know about but if you
just took five seconds to google you'd see that they happen all the time in this
country and you guys and you guys reach the the concert area.
So you're in the crowd of the stained concert is packed with
people you guys are like arrive outside of the the CIA or
Shamiya a tunnel that exists underneath Jafar's Palace.
and uh... when you get there
you see the crowd before you and you start to interpret it
maybe based on levels so
uh... how can i
what i've done
is this so you guys are all
to go to each level
you're gonna roll was that
so i kicked the thing okay
uh... my son you're gonna roll a stealth check
uh... each of you all of you
And then you're gonna see and before you do before you do well, I'm gonna take that
All right. So yeah, I mean take that that's fine. But um, so and
But this is why before you do but just keep that one you can declare how many levels you want to go up to get to
The stage where stained is
Okay, so you can stop the concert and find your parents. You're gonna need to go up these multiple levels, right?
So there's four levels in here for the four levels of tickets you could get.
It's sustained.
Don't worry.
Oh, okay.
And if you say you want to go up two levels, there's just going to be a penalty on the
stealthiness of the roll.
Because if you go up only one level, if you go up a level and the CIA perceives you, you're
going to get into a fight.
But so if you go up one level at a time, it's easier.
There'll be less of a penalty.
the penalty will be minus 5 on each roll,
depending on the number of levels you go up.
So if you go to 2 levels, it's minus 5.
If you go up 3 levels, it's minus 10.
So that's really the only options there.
And if you get into a fight, you can flee the fight,
which will bring you back down a level if you feel like it's too tough,
because the fights will be sort of randomly generated,
their level of difficulty.
uh... but you can also fight through it and then you'll make it to the next
level or to whatever level you're trying to get
so it's like blackjack
yeah it's like this is the name of the guy who i was a service animal in the
line
yeah
and what were you gonna say?
what's it like
cameron
do we start on level one? you start on level one okay
and around you this is where the losers are these freaks can never get close
is
and
be good hygiene. Yeah, they could be scratching off dirt. Amazing hygiene. Yeah, for animals
that's amazing hygiene. Yeah, scratching shit off your ass. You guys all interpret it as
fine right now. Yeah. So this is where the cool guys stay. I just want to stay here all
night. It's just like the back of the bus. You guys are like my new family. Yeah, you
see a person go bark look right at you.
A human?
Yeah.
Um, but yeah, so the CIA are hot in your tail.
So what do you guys want to do?
How many levels you want to try to go?
I go up to level three because I'm at level one and you said if I get.
Oh no, you got to reroll now that you know the rules.
There's no there's no fucking way that you know, you got to reroll.
I rolled the 21 so I get to go up to level three.
No, because you don't get to gamble money that you that you.
So you guys could try to...
What do you mean?
I mean, I...
It's like getting a fucking...
It's like hitting 21 in blackjack and then being like, "I bet $1,000."
That's just exactly like how every billionaire at Vegas works.
No, but here's the thing though.
So all your self-rolls will be done.
What?
No, pause.
Okay, there's a couple things that we just unlocked in Patrick.
the
a
accumulated his billions. First off, he bought the Venetian.
Yes. Okay.
He grew up in Dorchester too. And then every day, he walked in.
No, he has the Boston mindset. And he would bet after he gets this to hand.
He grew up in Dorchester, he has the Boston mindset, which is how this makes sense.
Okay, it's the Boston, I'm sorry, it's the Boston mindset.
Exactly. The Boston mindset.
Who is incorrect. Exactly.
That is the Boston mindset, right. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. We're
not going to not go by the Boston mindset in this D&D campaign. I'm sorry. I'm sorry, but
and
not
so my other top unit they talk a lot of the street they talk is to a citizen
they taught you that i did
but it's held in a dozen makes his bets after he
he had a blackjack
yes they taught me that sheldon adelson is evil but i don't want to get into why
this is that
this is the
the same daddy gave you fries
you know you that right
yes stirred
yes so i mean the thing is you don't roll stealth check
added up and i'm gonna roll a
a perception check against that
uh... with despise so we are all together still got a twenty one so i don't know
what i think there that you're getting
well so no so wouldn't be a go up to level three you choose how many levels
you want to go up and then you suffer a penalty on your own okay but i got a
twenty one so i don't suffer any penalties it's not no so
either way you're gonna get to the front of the
this is part of the
i mean which you have but you know
(laughing)
- You guys wanna try for level three or level two?
- Oh wait, we do it as a group?
- Yeah.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah, I'm sorry.
- That makes more sense.
- Yeah, okay.
- All right, then I would never have gone
into the Sheldon Ableson group.
- I'll try for level three.
I got really good stealth.
- Okay.
- Me, not.
- 18.
- Okay.
- Caleb?
- 12.
(burps)
- Bringing the team down here.
- I think that averages out to a--
- So you guys all trying to go to level three?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
you guys do you get up to level three
but
nara for levels just i don't know if we mention that all you guys get up to
level three but not without
a fight
uh...
because uh... you guys were in stealthy enough so you guys
we're navigating through it
uh...
we're gonna have a few more of these hombres
let's not
because of the
role that's cheating you're literally cheating and i'm not cheating
and she has really made it into six those times doing that uh... to illustrate
that they were
so picking up the season yet you know what i'll i'll give it to him he's using
sheldon adelson's boston myself
so you you guys are you guys muscle to the crowd you get past the second level
uh... everyone there is pretty regular
they wanted above ground pool may have uh... fantasy team
they like chicken nachos the occasional joint
you know
nowhere in not just nothing saying the regular
they're all wearing two tops even the men
uh...
okay hold up
each of them are
i don't want to be to the make exactly eighty three thousand dollars a year
if their taxes go up the say slur on face book now me but i a m yeah
there that there they're great that second-level people
third-level people are the worst people in the world they're not staying fans
that's where this hipster this coffee drinking avocado fucking hipster is
a bunch of rich posers that they get school to be in to stain
where they get ironic to be in to stain they've lost the plot
they own three buildings each
in downtown duluth insist on hanging out with the tenants and always ask you if
you're clear friend you have over a single
uh... they're constantly thing each other and screaming that they're nineteen
while doing coke off of max out credit cards
there are no black people in this area of the of the this is not it's all
all asian-american iranians of my interesting that you would choose to
eliminate them from this area patches but
i guess you're the d_n_a_ it's all iranians here
so maybe that's maybe that's my way out of the i'd have no
i do our go
did you are go
yeah i haven't seen that movie can you describe it to me
I don't remember it very well.
Okay.
So I don't know what you did there.
It's any Ron.
Roll for initiative, you know.
Okay.
Will this help me to Argo?
In a way.
I got 11.
No, don't we all.
I got a 23, bro.
What do I roll?
I roll a 20.
Oh, you got a crit.
So unless somebody else gets a crit, you go first.
So I roll a d20 or initiative?
Initiative.
My life a movie.
Yeah.
That's right.
Caleb.
Uh, okay, cool.
First, normal dog.
Yeah, you got the jump on everybody.
So you navigated through the crowd, you hung out with some of the chill people there, and
then sort of spotted the CIA right away when they spotted you.
So you got the jump.
Hmm.
And, uh, also I'll say, normal dog, roll a constitution saving throw.
I got a 19.
Whoa!
You feel your body start to react from the experiments that were happening earlier.
But you're able to resist whatever it is that's happening to you.
And now you get to go.
Okay, can I use my vicious ability?
It will work no matter what.
If you roll a 19 on a crit, you just get a crit.
And then you get also a triple.
Oh, okay.
And I roll the attack three times?
Yeah, it's just a combination of a couple of critical abilities.
I just don't know what else to say.
Oh, okay.
Alright, then I'm gonna go for the old...
I'm gonna go for the old bite on the nearest one, this guy.
Do it.
Fuck his ass up.
Fuck his ass.
14.
No, don't, guys.
Come on.
Fuck his ass.
Fuck the guy.
Fuck his ass as a dog.
Yeah, no, that's fucking ridiculous.
And that doesn't hit anyway, so...
Well...
Well, it hits...
it would have been a fifteen damage. It would have been very good. Your loss buddy. It's
not literally. Let's get the twenty one. Let's do the twenty one. It's literally your loss.
Instead of the fourteen. Not my loss. No I think it's our win. Well it's actually the
CIA's turn. Hey buddy is it? They don't wait for anyone's turn let me tell you. The C guys
say. That one tries to attack you, the one you just tried to bite at, and he just also
whiffs, so it's a very anime fight. They're just missing each other, being cool, missing
each other. How do you miss on a dog, dude? Because you're fast, you're a fast dog. I
just wanted you to say that. Just admit I'm fast. And now the other ones that are there
are gonna try to uh...
uh... she shoot at me and their pig spotting a somebody that they should
probably
and
and member pig just fucking like
fuckin
takes all the bullets and they just fall to the ground
this is not a problem at all
well the bullets fall to the ground not a member of the other no haha when i was
like dami died instantly thirty two
member picks up
he's gonna fuck this guy up that shot him uh...
he's gonna do his uh... by also now
yeah that hits
let's go he just like tears into the c_i_a_ agent is just in his fuckin mouth
he's chomping on a means like
he's like stops for a second you hear
you hear him say ronnie
and uh...
keep chewing
uh... and while he has this guy in his mouth
he's gonna walk over
uh... shit sorry
and he's gonna walk over with this guy why is this happening
because
hold on sorry d_-dust again
i got the dust
for being uh... the great d_n_a_
and uh... he's gonna swipe at this this other agent while he has the
the other one in his mouth
uh...
so he's gonna try to do that you guys have uh... a stacked crew now
so it's gonna get an idea
i said i'm so glad we made friends with you
you know it's a surprisingly good move
he just slashes at this guy and i guys like already like almost dead
like a little walking like
jazzy claw into him like four times a click
because a bloody mess never mind about my idea that yeah and now
and now it is a on key shredders turn
and he's going to
pick up his uh... uh... from a shirkin
and uh... throw it is a little bit shirker
it's really a good
that's what it is
uh... whatever you said it's the food for the jury at
and he's gonna manage to hit
ice
he's gonna hit
you can throw it is gonna hit uh...
these three guys in the front with its own xd store around
and and kills this one
was already hurt we're doing it kills it
killed in member pigs mouth and some member pictures walls and now
kills this guy who just got caught by the world
and hurts uh... this guy over here
uh... many comes back to him
and now it is your turn pleasant pair
i love my friends
feel all the people who just killed
the
the a_c_ people the crowd are just too insisting right now to notice that this
this is
I
tell me how you packet him
i'd take you well i see it is i con his agent smith
so i take his sunglasses and they shatter
so here and he has a really stupid looking at it is a good idea
yes it is a really long girl eyelashes and then we all laugh at it as many
men who are less is my secret my secret is gregerson i'm a pretty
confused girl and then as he does any keeps he keeps blinking in his eyes
make it oh lord I'm a secret white woman and now it is your turn
hunky hamster okay now that I know he's a secret white woman okay good yeah I
I take him shopping.
No.
(laughing)
- Dude, you come, yes.
Dude, I mean, come on.
- Wow.
- Woo!
- Yeah, dude.
- Now that I know he's a secret white woman,
I just point at normal dogs.
- Yeah, you pointed me.
- No, what am I gonna do?
He's not actually a secret white woman.
- No, he's not.
He just looks fucking weird.
- Okay, so checking inventory, does that count as a move?
uh... yeah but go for it
i might i might check inventory
so also uh... i can use that in tandem with sharing is caring right hunger yes
a hungry after sorry role uh... a before you do anything more consistent or
seraphically that for you
not you not you was apparent yet yet has already been through that shit
movement the hell and back
and i i i i i kept going
Yeah, hungry hamster. You feel your body start to shake. You
remember being a hungry hippo for like 5 seconds and you feel
your you feel like like your tummy start to rumble and just
start to expand in size and your AC goes up by 5 points.
okay
world
what's fourteen plus five
nineteen
tiffet
okay yeah
i have to just ignore that
yeah so now your turn now
in
okay so at all the uh...
who who has the most damage right now can you point out on the uh... yet this guy
you would know just based on the roles you've seen
uh... what i'm gonna do is hamster ball at him
all twenty-eight you do it rolled for the answer that
fourteen
you kill and i think it was great to kill
i hate the hamster ball goes right up his ass
uh... so i go up to the answer ball up his ass go all the way up to his head
replaces brain with me and now i'm ready to eating him okay
you're ready to leave all allow it he's uh... ready to lead
uh... he's so i have a gun right
so now i have a gun
right will wait on that
yes i guess so
uh... and now it is back to being normal dogs turn
uh... the second most damage
yeah i'm gonna hit that guy with the with the tackle
go for it
always our constitution saving their first
now
that's fine
the constitution saving their helps eleven rick
k_s_ so you start to feel your body change and get to you feel like your
head turning slowly back into uh... diane lane in
and you feel your cells are to realign
and uh...
you feel your tongue in your head
that was already five feet long.
- Big tongue.
- You feel it grow and roll up and grow and grow and grow.
It feels like your tongue could maybe go on forever.
- I try that.
- Okay.
You feel inside that you have two things
you can do with your tongue.
Something called the tongue of tranquility
and something called the tongue of madness.
time
I couldn't have written it better myself.
Let's see how they do.
Yeah, so their tongue, the tongue, your tongue, not their tongue, goes up all these guys buttholes.
Yes.
And you watch them just like, like make like anime noises.
The ultimate pleasure sounds.
And they suffer from two levels of exhaustion, which...
In Dungeons and Dragons parlance, I'll show you guys what exhaustion is.
Their speed is halved?
And they have disadvantage on ability checks.
They take both.
Okay.
Wait, what does a six death do?
If you get them to six levels of exhaustion, they die.
So you're telling me I gotta keep licking these guys' fuckin' assholes 'til they get to-- 'til they die?
If you want to, but right now they also have disadvantage on the ability checks they want to do.
Okay. Now I know how to win.
And their speed is halved. Yeah. And we'll get into how many uses of that you have after this fight, but for now, consider yourself Golden Ponyboy.
And I'll-- yeah, you'll see. You'll see. It'll expand. That's your turn now.
Okay.
uh... it is now
uh... look at the it's now the c_i_a_ agents turns
and their there's there is a look sluggish they look tired they just got
their spot holes like that affect the c_i_a_ agent agent i'm inside of
retired he's dead i mean too much we had he's dead but that doesn't affect like
my moves right now you're fine he's looking at guys but he has his assholes
are e_x_ big zoomed all the shit yeah it's only exhausted uh...
what's up sorry
somebody else said some shit.
Are they are they exhausted from just like coming too hard?
Like their legs are twitching?
Yes.
Okay, cool.
That's what happened.
Nice.
Their mascara is bleeding down.
Yeah, all of mascara on cool.
Yeah.
Yeah, they make the head.
Hey gal face.
Yeah, there that's why they're all cross-eyed.
And they're going to try to move in on this one's going to try to move in on
man bear pig, but they move so sluggish.
They have like half movement, but this one's gonna try to go after you pleasant parrot
And pleasant Perry you roll a constitution saving throw while this guy's coming after you, okay?
Nat one, okay. No
No, that's so first of all, okay, that's all right, that's actually good in this case as you've seen
so your eyes roll all the way to the back your head and
and then back around and back to the back your head again
and that does that three more times
you hear
this this
cry
that says uh...
now i thought i would go to work and uh... if you feel
yourself grow stronger your h_p_ goes up by ten
wallow your a_c_ each
your a_c_ goes up
to sixteen
and the body, this is actually very funny, the body that Patrick is in right now, that
Hungry Hamster is in, comes back to life, but it seems to be under your control.
And you sense that there are maybe other bodies that are coming back to life.
I'm
Yeah, he just like tries to attack you and just like a blue force field just like comes up and just like
and he's like
what and
Yeah, so yeah you added that and so this is the the thing you said though
Whenever you did whatever it is you just did and
now
It is who's fucking turn is it man?
Whose fucking turn is it man? Oh, yeah shit. It's uh, I skipped their turn. So let me go to their turn
Oh, no, I didn't it was CIA agents turn. So now it's a man-bear pigs turn
And he's just gonna come up to these two fuckers and he's gonna try to clap their heads together
who
He should clap their cheeks together
He's gonna try to
Fuck me. Yes, and let's see how he does. Yeah, he does
That to them both. Oh my god
God yeah, and this one dies immediately
This one is still alive though. And now it is uncle shredders turn and he's gonna throw his fubu shuriken again
Nice
Yeah, and he's gonna just fucking
Slice that guy's God slice these two guys heads off. Holy shit
And now there's just that one guy left who's already dead anyway, so you guys made it to the he's under my control
Yeah, you guys are in the third level and Pat's inside him and Pat's inside this guy
So yeah, you guys fucking bested the CIA agents pretty handily
You realize now and and all your bodies now that resisting you were doing earlier you stop resisting this change a hungry hamster
This hamster is getting kind of hungry
You know, you're you're feeling real hungry the popular beloved desired hungry hamster. What would you be without your appetite?
You'd be just a regular ass hamster. That's what so your hunger has come to define you but now it shall define the world
You are what you eat hungry hamster. Why not eat the whole dang world?
Okay, world eater hamster activate and you feel your body
Turn into the world eater hamster
So you just become a perfect sphere and you and your mouth can just take up your whole body. I'm a whole tire. Yeah
speak of curvy
uh... normal dog
this dog is feeling kind of strange
the normalness of your soul starts to wash away no not wash away blended to
something new
maybe it was your time in shimmy niche motley spanked and confusing you with
residual do
from failed and kate shman kate schmaltz experiments that he feels a peculiar
maybe it's for chilling with man bear pic is really random
you feel like a
Total spaz of freaking weirdo.
Maybe even a little epic.
Maybe a little neurodivergent.
Strange dog.
- Erm.
- Activate.
You are now a strange dog.
Yeah, erm.
You keep saying erm instead of woof.
- Yeah, erm.
- You're now a strange dog.
So for both of you, your effects,
world eater hamster plus 10 max HP,
your AC is 19.
You saw that happen to you during that fight.
All your attacks do double damage.
And now you have access to the chef's specialty item list better items
Plus if you eat the item you get their abilities for the rest of combat
So if you ate the jet jet pack you would just have the ability to fly at a speed of 60 feet
Right, or if you ate the beehive you'd be able to squirt out bees
We figure that out
Strange dog your HP is up by 10. Your AC is now 20
All attacks do double damage and you have as you saw before the tongue of madness
But now you also have the tongue do I get my do I get my HP restored cuz I think it was it
Yes. Yeah, you all are restored full HP. No HP
Cool, you also got the tongue of tranquility which heals all allies with your psycho butt licking tongue for 2d 8 plus 4 hit points
2 uses
Evan tongue of madness lick your enemies butthole if they fail DC 15 wisdom saving throw they suffer two levels of exhaustion
You have four uses of that
And then you have the exhaustion chart, which I sent you and
pleasant parrot
Neurothal rule on galois
Jekar T. East how like an affair the real hook you've three uses of whatever the fuck that is plus 10 max HP
AC 16
And what I'm sorry, but I'm still pleasant you're still very pleasant cool. All right
Hey, you're the big stuff on
Yeah, and so now
You know, I'm very pleasant parent. You're extremely pleasant parent. Yeah, the most pleasant. Yeah. So how do you guys feel in your new bodies?
What's going through your head? Yeah shredder a man bear picker like damn you guys look awesome now
I look I look down at my penis and I'm like I feel calm and pleased damn that thing that thing got a little bit
Smaller, but that's fine
It's the price we pay I remember when I chopped off mine
What what never mind? How do you feel dog?
Weird. No you how do you feel strange dog?
My tail start. Hey, hey, he's weird. Tell him not weird. I'm not gonna don't fight. I'm not weird
No, no, what if you what if you guys are the weird ones and I'm the normal one?
That's weird. Oh
Tell patches he's weird. No, don't tell me I'm weird. Hey patches. You're weird. No, what the fuck? He's weird
You guys it's just a random guy dancing in the crowd
He's like six foot three and
He says and he says fine I'm going back home to Carmen Electra and he's crying
She dumps chum on his head
yeah and he's like oh that's my fetish thank you carmen is the uh...
they continue to walk back to him and then he does and and and and and and
and it's a bit it's a stupid thoughts on the way home
but he's very happy when he does
and he'll take a hill take that be and i think i don't think it was a hell
yeah with his is he's a happy and all this is like a pretty mama
yeah and he's not simply a good
here a
This is what happens to patches in this story.
This is so weird.
Oh man.
You guys just ran ragged with that.
What was I supposed to do?
There's a guy named Cameron in the crowd and we high five him.
Oh my god!
You could have just done that to patches.
I fly over to the guy named Cameron and I give him the $103 from my inventory.
I'm just going to get up and check my wallet really quickly.
We could use that dude.
I
in
DM now. No, we got a level 4. Let's go. Let's go to level 4. What do we roll again? Stealth.
Yeah, roll stealth. Nat 20. That's not a nat 20. It's a dirty 20, but it's quite good.
Nat 9. Okay. I start showing my friends Joker inspiration memes on my phone. You
don't have a phone. I do. I have a dog phone. It's shaped like a paw. You had a dog phone the
whole time. Yeah, I forgot to use it. Why don't we just use the GPS? You guys. Wait, yeah, what's up?
You guys. Oh no, maybe I forgot. Maybe I wanted to learn more about you guys as friends
on our journey. With your new. Yeah, it's messed up. New abilities and shit. You guys just barely
stealthily get by with blood all over your bodies. Okay. Stealthily getting through the audience. You
get to the fourth level of the concert. This is where the best people in the show are.
The Stained fanatics. The best people in the world.
The Blagojevichs?
The classes, races, and creeds. They come to see Stained. They are super excited and
so excited.
Creed was the opener.
Their love of the band with you. You can't help but feel welcome here even for a little
while
there
they're all hanging out together
so yeah
you guys wanna rush over them
now you know what i do
i take caleb's dog phone and i call rod begloyavich
what are you talking about? what do you mean caleb's dog phone? he just talked about it
i think patches was gone when i talked about having a dog phone
maybe patches missed that but we have to talk about it before we rush over
i invented that i had a dog phone
it's okay yeah you call ron go yes
and wait what do i roll for that
found a solution
you're all persuasion of the phone
as you know that goes
and eleven
you don't have to roll persuasion on the phone man you call the number
the
okay we all done that the phone picks up
okay so that world doesn't care you see rob a good image dance he's gonna pick
up his phone in the middle of a concert yeah i'm walking away
sees phone buzzing in his pocket yet though that's why i'm persuading him i'm
persuading him to pick up the phone you can see waited on the phone
now that he's wearing talked about the only he looks at his phone he sees
unknown number and just like puts it back in his pocket it's his unknown dog
yeah
and he's like well it can be my dog and he puts it back in his pocket my dog
doesn't have a phone
Before we rush over to the family. Can I do like a perception check to see if like candy hamster is lurking around somewhere?
Yeah, absolutely
With that even with the blaring amazing music of stain right in front of you
You can start to get a sense that candy hamster is nearby because you see
little bits of
Candy corn just and I sputtered around this the stage right in front of you
to
You also see the candy corn. I you know what I'm gonna also
Investigate this and you do have actual advantage with yeah, I'll try to follow if the trail of candy corn. Yeah. Yes. Yeah, okay
Yeah, I'm gonna get the sense sniff that yes do that that you'll okay gonna be a lower with the for that
Perception you're gonna have an easier time with that
Yeah, I mean even with that ten because that was a pretty smart move to follow that trail
You you set you sniff it
He's backstage
hmm
So we could probably run up to our family right gotta figure out how to get backstage
Don't you see our family stain stops playing that song for the 800th time?
And they thank you you guys and he goes to the microphone the singer of stained and he says
Thank you all for listening to that awesome song 800 times
Thank you all especially to our level 4 fans. This is not a cult
now
We're about to play our number one song. You know it I know it
It's been a while and you see
You the tune our guitars
And he starts playing he starts doing his guitar
It's just gonna take us 20 minutes.
He starts fingerpicking the unmistakable opening riff to "It's Been Awhile"
and you see like Rob Bogoyevich in the crowd, his eyes are welling up with tears.
And then you see Candy Hamster come out from backstage
and you see him start to transform.
Um, you guys rush the stage, couldn't find a picture of Stain so it's disturbed, he looks
pretty much the same though.
And uh, you see Candy Hanzo and he said "I WANTED YOU THREE GONE!
YOU BASTARDS!" and he starts to transform.
the c_i_a_s injected me with so much shit
i'm crazy with it
and uh...
starts spinning around and around and around and around and around and around
and around and around until the sugar
he turns into
his final form
which is a
cotton
candy
that's dog
I couldn't find, I could not find, I could not find, I could not find, I'm not accepting this.
Just let him turn into a cotton candy dog.
Get a new one.
Cotton candy Pomeranian, is that what you mean?
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah.
And he's like, "No, I will kill you all."
Why would he be scared of a seed?
Wait, he's made entirely out of food?
He's, yes, he's made entirely out of cotton candy now.
Yeah.
You fucking moron.
but it's a lot of people
it's a and now
the guy who was hungry is not the whole
his cancer of all time
you will be hungry when i don't because you'll be dead he'll still be a
everybody i don't know what i was thinking about it
but in answer to that drawing on my face in world twenty
please stop it
and uh...
this is the big one
all right imagine intense jrpg boss battle music play
hey the candy hamster has a penis and a vagina
and that's okay
and that's what we drew
i got ten
on initiative
i got
twenty two dude
he's really strong
i'm like not
not fucking around with the candy hamster
you guys it's not gonna be an easy fight
okay
uh...
it's going to be uncle shredders turn first
he's gonna run up
as close as he can
and throw his fubu shuriken
uh...
it's too bad for him
yeah he got twelve
uh... and it just like
goes right through
candy hamster
uh... cotton candy layer or should i say cotton candy dogs
cotton candy layer
We'll put a picture of that up so this is making a little more sense for people to see.
And it is now, that's kind of all he can do really, so it's now your turn, strange dog.
You feeling a little weird?
Yeah, I'm a little weird.
So I'm going to exhaust this fool with my tongue of madness.
Okay, use one of your four uses.
he's gonna he's going to roll a wisdom saving throw against it hmm okay he
doesn't oh let's go dude we have and disadvantage on ability checks oh yes
we're gonna win so yeah the tongue goes into his butt wherever that is you want
to cut on a cotton candy and he's like where the stick goes in the not my stick
No! It's just like, you see him just get visibly tired.
He has two points of exhaustion on him. He turns to a different color.
So now, it is his turn though.
And so he's got a couple things he's gonna do.
First thing he's gonna do, you're gonna watch him, he spins around faster and faster and faster,
until he becomes a blur.
are
see
so
to them in any way, you might be subject to some sort of a Twizzler-based attack.
That's one of the scariest attacks, I think, to me.
And now he's also RIP Mac Miller.
This whole time Patrick has been working really hard to write letters.
And yeah you see the candy hamster is going to start to move.
We're at half speed though so only over here.
And now it is your turn world eater hamster.
Well I'm the world eater hamster.
This guy's made out of cotton candy.
I think you know what's going to happen.
You're going to try to eat him?
Like you said it, not me.
Let me pull up the ruler real quick.
Do I have...
They're like 50 feet from the stage.
Does my thing go up because I'm the world leader hamster?
No, your movement's the same.
Okay.
Do I have like an inhale move?
You don't, but I feel really stupid for not adding that in.
in
of
double move over here and do it next turn okay wait so is there anything i could do right now that could
oh i can hit him you could do uh hamster ball uses your movement so you can do hamster ball
you can also do get item and try to eat the item and see what you get out of that too okay i'll do
i'll do what i mean so hamster ball would count as a movement yeah yeah hamster but it would make me
closer to the candy hamster. Yes, it would be a movement and an attack. Hamster ball allows
you to use your full movement as an attack too. Okay. But there's no saying that I can't
inhale him in my hamster ball. There's no rule in the rule books. No, but I'm going to say
because you're using the hamster ball as your action, that's going to stop you from doing
inhale which would be an action. Okay. Guys, what do you think I should do? Just take your
turn. Yeah, I know, but I need help with my turn. Be your own man. Just make a decision.
I'm trying, I'm trying. Just look at the stuff you have that you can possibly do and then
do one of the things. Maybe just pass to the next one. Could I do the famous dance on them?
You could certainly try. Okay, I'm feeling this is going to be a hard one to pull off.
I'm doing the famous dance.
They're the hardest boss in the entire game.
Yeah, they got a grip.
They are just like, "DANCING IS STUPID!"
I hate candy now.
I'm only gonna eat beef.
NO!
You're the keto hamster, dude.
I'm the keto hamster.
You're the Michaela Peterson carnivore diet hamster.
Yeah, exactly.
Oh, okay, yeah, he went.
Oh, okay, yeah, he went--
Okay, yeah, it's your turn, Very Pleasant Parrot.
Okay.
Um...
I'm gonna move a little bit, just so I have, like, line of sight.
To, uh...
To the Cotton Candy Monster.
Um...
Oh shit, sorry.
I think you know that's not his name.
Okay, sorry, before you do that,
and I'm sorry about this especially to, uh, uh, the World Eater Hamster,
uh...
role a dexterity saving throw
world leader hamster
at eleven
you roll up on this guy you start to do your little famous boogie dance and you see he
resists it
and then one of the twizzler stalks
just fucking scoops you the fuck up
no! he's trapped in this twizzler forest
you bitch
oh my god
and uh... yeah you're just
trapped in there right now
uh...
uh... you might be able to get an extra
now
very pleasant
okay so i'm just gonna get line of sight on them
cotton candy creature
and i'm just gonna go ahead and use the left for a year
the original
uh... well i don't know all you all use the new one the uh... do it
dinner at the long gone low-level
yet your eyes roll the back your head eight thousand times like uh...
fucking slots
and then you see uh...
before you
all of the c_i_a_ agency killed so far
come back from the dead
check out the
think you killed a
no
it's a sex
plus three so really not
and then also in addition to that
the
I'm not acting like a baby!
Do your homework!
Yeah, please!
And so yeah, that's, that's uh, that's
that's your turn.
Okay. Now, uh, but now you have
all of them fighting on your side, so we're gonna roll initiative
for them. Nice!
I got ten... ten...
squad ten deep.
That's what, you know, that's what you get when you're pleasant.
Lots of friends.
that's what these are these are your friends yeah yeah disinterred corpses
mm-hmm and so here comes man bear pig he's gonna go to the frickin Twizzler
forest and he's gonna try to break you out hungry yeah and he's able to just
slash you out of that yes so it still is there but you're now outside of it and
he's gonna still have to
it and this is a c_i_a_ agent or does it mean they're picking
i hope you think that
yet he did is able to resist
the twizzler comes out of the room
and so it was a small white it just takes a big fight
uh...
and now and i think you might be my new best friend
that's what's up
and uh... it is now
on the shredders turn again
and uh...
He's gonna try to, uh, charge for the, uh, candy hamster.
And take out his Fubu Shuriken again.
Um...
He just throws his Fubu Shuriken and the candy hamster is able to...
With also his increased, uh, ability to...
To be, uh, ghost-like, he's able to definitely get out of the way of it.
But now it is your turn, strange dog, once again.
Um, I'm gonna do- I'm gonna do my fuckin'...
what's it called the odd tongue the tongue of the
who's the odd tongue
I'm gonna do my odd tongue once again
do it
okay I'm doing it
right now yeah I gotta love D&D
I'm doing it right now
yeah he's able to resist it this time
oh
alright
when i guess i just sit back
okay yeah you just be a chill ass dog sticking your crazy tongue out
well but i'm strange now so i'm listening to tech nine
as i like sit back
and now it is the candy hamster's turn once again
uh...
he starts to spin again this time faster than he even was already that made him a
blur
and everybody roll a dexterity saving throw
Including the agent Smith's and the team
11 12 so uh
Man-bear pig uncle shredder
World hamster world eater hamster and normal dog you all take 21 points of damage. Oh
That's a lot no
Fuck I have one hit point as I'll heal you
I don't
take
Now, uh, uh, the candy hamster is going to move in closer, um, and shoot a payday missile.
*laughs*
Ah!
Uh...
That's so many peanuts!
Uh, right at, uh, uh, the man bear pig.
Um, so let's see how he does with that.
And he's... the man bear pig is able to just like, to tuck and roll out of the way of the
missile.
it explode into a disgusting peanut mess behind him.
And now it is your turn, motherfucking...
Oh, the squad!
It's the squad's turn.
So they're all gonna just roll up on him and try to surround him.
That's right.
Squad.
Squad up.
And so the squad of CIA agents that are now under your... that are now like your allies.
I'm
he's spinning too fast with that spin ability except one of them is able to hit him which
stops the spin ability in its tracks so that's no longer an issue you no longer have disadvantage
on those attacks nice and the candy hamster takes a sizable amount of damage actually
so you see all these CIA agents like trying to karate chop him and then one of them just
like bops him on the nose and the candy hamster's like like just in pain so now it is your turn
in
If you're thirsty, you can just drink water and revive.
You don't have to get it in the game.
No, I'm saying that the natural enemy of cotton candy is water.
Also, the...
Wait, hold up.
I feel like the cotton candy hamster is a lot closer to me now.
Yeah.
So...
What's the best thing I could do?
I think...
Okay, so I could check my inventory and then share it with somebody?
Or use it against the...
Alright.
Alright, you know what?
I'm
It does 3d10 + 5 attack damage and it has advantage against evil aligned creatures which this guy
is.
And you have double damage right?
Yes.
Oh my god.
So you just have this shiny, you reach into your mouth and pull out this shining gleaming
blade that you immediately know how to wield and is super powered.
Okay.
And I can use it right now?
Yeah.
Fuckin' let's go!
Oh no wait, sorry, shit, yeah, check inventories in action.
So you can't use it yet.
But you have it ready to go.
But your next turn's gonna be so lit, dude.
But I haven't moved, right?
No, so you can move.
So let's say, theoretically, I have the sword poking out in front of me while I move 15 feet.
You know what, write a persuasion check on the DM.
See if you can get it.
*laughter*
Woah an 18!
I think that's a fuckin'
I think that's a go!
So you see the DM looking at
what you're saying and
he's thinking about how many times he's let you do
just insane stupid shit
and he's like
and he's sort of just like
I don't wanna be the no guy
*laughter*
I kinda pride myself on
being the DM who can hang
*laughter*
I throw him a beer.
Come on! Live a little!
I give the DM one of these clown shoes
space cake double IPAs
and because it's a 9%
ABB he drinks one
and he's too fucked up.
Yeah, the DM is a baby's tolerance.
He's like, you know what?
Roll a straight D20.
If you get higher than 10, you do an attack.
a
3 D10s plus 5.
I should have said that was going to be a plus 7 to hit too whenever you got to use it.
What did you do?
I rolled 3 D10s.
You set a cap that they have to be greater than 90.
Oh wait, wait, wait.
I didn't even know you could do that.
How did you make that happen?
Pat just made it so that he rolled 3d10s +5 and it had to be greater than 90 for him to succeed.
He rolled 3d10 +5 and the result was zero successes.
Well now I got three successes.
You are teaching me so much about rolling 20 times.
How are you doing this?
I now have three successes.
Fuck off.
That's like the first value.
It's good.
11 + 5 that's uh 14.
16 wow i'm having a patrick moment and we're gonna times that by two
You do 32 damage you fucking run up to this thing after persuading the df
And you just cleave through its cotton candy. Yes, and the candy hamster's like
Like just like in so much pain
um, uh
And it's like hanging now a little bit from its giant cotton candy body
Oh, yeah, I should have mentioned put this in cameron earlier. He also grows to like 30 feet in height
and 25 feet wide this giant hamster in size you know what i mean oh yeah penis exactly the same
looks crazy brother little hamster no no it's a twix bar look if my penis was any bigger it's
aerodynamic enough to do that last move so no no not you the candy hamster grosses out wow wow
Wow, what a narcissist.
Every hamster is you.
Look, every time we talk about a hamster's penis, it just grew.
I thought the candy hamster turned into the cotton candy dog.
Because he's a dog on the screen right now.
Just keep up, Patrick.
You are so dumb.
You're dumb like every human.
This makes so much sense.
You have the IQ of an egg.
Yeah, okay.
And an egg that hasn't even hatched yet.
After letting you do that.
It is now the very pleasant period.
Okay, um, hmm. See, I don't think any of my attacks are really good enough to justify
getting into melee range. Because I'll just die if I get hit, most likely. So, I might...
Is it safe to assume that if I use that new ability again that nothing's gonna happen?
Yeah, no. He's already resurrected everybody.
He's already resurrected everyone.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
Um, I'll just use the old crazy ability.
I'll use the old Farina.
I might fly away a little bit, actually.
Dennis Farina is what the ability's called.
Yeah.
Now.
After doing this Farina.
Do it, yeah.
Alright.
I mean, I don't know what to...
That does say...
Oh, yeah, sorry.
Rolled straight D20.
Oh, okay.
My apologies, love.
Oh, yeah.
Alright.
the
right here. You just tell your eyes turn white again. They don't go like slots though and
you just teleport in place. You go to the ethereal plane. You see like you see like the
everyone looks like blue. Yeah, like you're seeing through it and then you just appear
right back in place. That's what happens to you with 10. I throw up motion sickness. Yeah.
It is now ManBearPig's turn.
After resisting the Twizzler Forest, he's gonna try to approach Candy's Hamster.
Fuck his ass up.
He fucking does awful.
He tries to bite him.
He tries again though, he's got two attacks.
Yeah that does hit.
And so he does damage now.
He just takes a chomp out of Candy Hamster.
He's like "Ahh!"
Like more of that noise.
He's not looking too good.
He's getting pretty fucked up right now.
We could do this guys.
We could.
We could really pull this off.
We're taking him down bro.
But you also see Candy Hamster in this fit.
You see him like his cotton candy.
of it start to repair and starts to heal. He's like, "Now you're making me mad!"
I had a system I developed for this, okay?
"I had a system I developed for this!"
"You developed a system?"
"I told him, shut the hell up."
I had two HP values and whenever one of them reached zero, that one would then be reabsorbed
into the big... nobody... I don't care.
"I don't even know what that means."
I'll show you guys later.
And uh, it is now, yeah you see his like, his cotton candy starts to fill up with other colors,
it's like he's repairing it with like, other kinds of cotton candy.
Um, and it is now Uncle Shredder's turn.
He's gonna try to now run up on this guy, he's pretty close, and use his uh, his shredder
claws.
Um, um, yeaaaaah.
Yeah he fuckin' hits him alright, yeah he fuckin' just slices him up, Uncle Shredder.
like this is for all the uncles everywhere and it's just like slicing up this hamster.
It's for my brother Rob and uh that's right I'm uncle shredder blakowicz and uh
YAAAAAAA
The reveal.
Everyone in the crowd at the concert starts cheering.
This is like a break dance circle at the STAN concert.
the song whatever uh... it's been a while
it's been a while
yeah they've just been trying to keep their cool
uh... and it is now uh...
strange dog
uh... ok although i am strange and i may make odd decisions
uh... i do need to
i think i need to heal the hungry hamster with my wound lick
yeah you're you're you have a new ability is one h better you have a better
healing ability again i'm weird and i do what i want
yes so i'm gonna use the good one if you use all of us
hey guys i'm trying to stay true to the character and i'm supposed to be weird
so yeah it's weirder if you're weirder than you to use a psycho butt licking
tongue that's what it says in this new ability
y'all might be kind of right all right i use tongue of tranquility
Yeah, it heals everyone for 2d8 plus 4 hit points.
So roll for that to see how much you heal everyone.
So I roll 2d8s?
Not you!
No, no, no.
Just, just, just, just.
Sorry, are you the weird one?
Yeah.
Just strange dog.
And add 4, so 15 hit points.
So your tongue scoots around to everyone's butthole on your team, including all the agents.
Do I put something in their butt?
No, you just lick it in a way that is really healing.
he
yeah yeah yeah oh my god it's amazing dude yeah and uh yeah you heal all them good
it's like a royale with cheese which is what i call a hamburger oh you you're so strange i'm weird
i'm odd i watch weird movies you're really out there yeah what'd you think of momento i thought
I thought it was bleh bleh bleh bleh bleh bleh bleh bleh bleh bleh bleh bleh bleh bleh bleh
*laughter*
It's the other candy hamster's turn.
And uh, the candy hamster is going to uh
*growls*
He's like squeezing out these uh, uh
A couple of uh, things are sort of starting to squeeze out of him.
These uh, motherfucking gumdrop villains appear on the screen.
*laughter*
Gumdrop villains.
and they're these like 10 foot by 10 foot nasty scheming looking gumdrop villains
these guys look sick
I hate these guys already
and he squeezes out two of them
and they're gonna have to go for their own initiative
and they're in the turn order now
and you see them go "go my gumdrop villains"
and you see them go
and they're just like
like just plodding
are rubbing together. You see little gumdrop juices are sliding out of their hands as they
rub them together. It's very upsetting.
Um, yeah, you see them doing that. And then, uh, Candy Hamster's like, you can see he's
starting to get desperate. He's not looking too good. And so he, uh, he says, "It's time.
It's time to unleash the ultimate attack. I'll never let you have parents. They're my parents!"
And his cotton candy body turns completely silver like Metal's Mario.
And then you see everything around you turn into a black space.
And you see from the sky a giant Tootsie Roll appears as a meteor.
just floating in space in like 3D like PS2 graphics and all of you what is your
least favorite kind of candy? Necco wafer. Baby Ruth. No you can't trick no you're
trying to do a trick here. Trying to do opposite tees. It's not gonna work in the
game
who come on
i don't know if you try to get so close to a baby route and i know you like a
baby
okay then my then it finds out that my least favorite candy
silly rancher is is zero bar
until they respond to the white line
the exact same way
it's a you are brainless it's pretty confusing i i think i think the problem
is i'm a hungry hamster and i like all the candy
you see a foot then
up here in your mind
and uh...
what's your least favorite candy?
uh... i don't know i guess uh...
i mean the neck away for the kind of a gimme but you took that already
uh... i don't know where it wax bottle
yeah that's true yeah a circus peanut
okay yeah you guys circus peanut and you have a wax bottle and echo wafer
that's what you're all seeing in this giant three d media
flying and it's another trick
i know it's a good
and uh...
i don't actually mind the wax bottle all of you role wisdom city chile
I
The
psychic damage
that you guys are experiencing it's pretty pretty phenomenal
the giant you see the giant three d thing come down from you in this new space
fuckin uh... world that that he's created
the candy hamster
and you feel the salting your tongue
and just turning it into a
a hell for that world of candy
pleasant parrot
and
strange dog you guys only take half damage you take 20 points of damage how
much help did I gain from the tranquil tongue 15 you take 40 points of damage
you're dead oh my god the hungry hamster is gone and now now you don't even have
you don't have to worry about this Patrick you know I mean hungry hamster
but you're, yeah, the psychic damage of a foot in your mouth just like exploded your skull basically on the ground.
Yeah, you could still come back if people were biting you, but...
Okay, I refuse to revive you.
Normal dog, a strange dog I should say, with that saving throw, you're also now paralyzed and frightened.
Paralyzed and frightened?
You're incapacitated, you can't move or speak.
Any attack roll against you has advantage.
Any attack that hits you is a critical hit if the attacker is within 5 feet of you.
You automatically fail Strength and Dexterity saving throws.
You have disadvantage on Ability checks and Attack rolls.
All the source of your fear is within line of sight.
And you can't willingly move close to that source of fear.
Okay, but can you at least admit that I'm a bit weird and I might like something like that?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I can admit that.
Okay.
For you.
Moving on.
And you, you managed to resist it though.
a pleasant parrot, very pleasant parrot
close one
and now, now
it is the squad's turn
so they're gonna try their best to beat the shit out of this guy
please squad
please squad, please revive me
can the squad revive me?
these are my woes right now dude
I need a revival from the squad
and that's on period
I'm with my woes right now at the at the stain concert. Can I get a can I get a revival from the squad and that's on period
The squad instead of doing that continues to beat up on the hungry hamster
um
And all they know is I mean, sorry the candy hamster and the candy hamster is looking pretty messed up
No, stop get away from me. They do like a solid 18 damage to him
um, and now
it is
uh... world leader hamster
we're doing death saving throws
so what this is, we haven't done this in the game yet
or we did maybe once? We did it once, I think.
so you roll a d20
if you get above a ten, it's a success, if it's below a ten, it's a failure
so crit 20 you get two successes
crit 1 you get two failures
if you get three successes you're revived, if you get three failures you're permanently dead
So roll a d20.
Me?
Do it.
Yeah.
I thought you were talking to Cameron.
I got a 14.
That's a success baby.
You feel yourself fighting for life.
Like, and you're able to sort of catch a little bit of breath maybe as blood starts to build
up in your throat.
You're starting to maybe come back.
I feel like blood building up in his throat is not a great sign.
Yeah.
Maybe he'll swallow it okay.
Maybe you like blood.
I don't know.
Hey, I'm hungry as hell and that tastes like a steak to me right now.
That's right.
Very pleasant parrot, it is now your turn.
Okay, I look at strange dog and I use my Polly wants a what now ability to give him a one word command.
And I say, um, unparalyze.
Please.
I can't, no, it's not how that works.
I can't let you do that.
Wait, say antidote.
That makes even less sense.
No, it's a paralysis antidote.
It's not a command.
You can't make someone antidote.
No, you can.
Oh, can I look at Patrick and say "Live"?
Wait, that could happen.
It's not quite how the command spell works.
Yeah, I figured.
Man, I don't really--
Wait, look at me and say "Revive."
I think it might.
I think it's not going to work.
I uh...
There's really not much I can do to help my friends.
Wait, wait, look at the candy hamster and say "die."
It can't be harmful to them.
Well, then say "eat what you're allergic to."
Okay, I'm going to move on with my turn.
I think probably the best thing I can do is not get killed because I don't have anything
that can help.
I don't have any healing or anything.
We can take care of ourselves.
Yeah.
You guys can.
I need help.
Big boys in hell.
I'm weird.
Man, I'm just going to use my Dilophoran again.
Yeah, do it.
run again. Yeah, do it. Okay. 17. Okay. Oh boy. Okay, yeah. So here's what happens. Your
eyes turn white once again with this dark power. You don't know where it came from.
You don't know how it happened. You start to remember some experiments and stuff. And
outside of your mouth comes these incredibly strange energy beams
that carry with them a dark necrotic power
and they begin to
flood out of your open beak
and corral around the candy monster
and squeeze
and drain it. You see its skeletons start to poke through
the cotton candy elements of it
what kind of candies a skeleton made out of?
cookies and cream bar
carved into a skeleton
uh... and
uh...
you watch the candy hamster die before your eyes turn to it
and you also watch it
come back
god fucking dammit dude
no no no
literally as a zombie that fights on your side
uh... photos i guess what literally got the other spell that does that
uh... point doesn't allow it against what
i don't know you just have to do it
wayful take on top of the trump
no
it
uh... you see your family brought up in a hug you guys
candy hamster they do mouth i don't have to do mouth-to-mouth on you know
of
and hug you.
I'm supposed to be doing the King Tut.
Yeah, you hear the Homeward Bound music swirling,
you see the gumdrop villains vanish,
the Twizzler forest that killed about 37 people in the crowd
also vanish,
the agents start to poof away.
I can't believe you got this.
No!
And you see now the candy hamster just like hovering there,
mouth agape,
Um, and it does this for...
He's on our side but we should still like beat the shit out of him just cause he can.
Yeah, actually yeah.
Yeah, the candy ham- the candy hamster turns around and just starts chasing after the band, Stained.
Um, cause it just goes after the nearest person to it.
So it just starts running after Stained.
And Stained just is running from this undead candy hamster.
And your family runs up to you and "Oh, we were so worried about all of you!"
of you. We found out you were missing after Uncle Shredder said he told you to run from
the cops. We love you so much. We'll never make you guys go homeward bound again.
(laughing)
- Thanks, man.
- And it fades to black.
Comes up. - Oh my God.
- And you see a beautiful house,
once again, just outside of Chicago.
It's now the winter, winter-ish, fall-ish.
You see a big turkey in the kitchen window.
it's thanksgiving
uh...
and and uh... uh... you're all sitting at thanksgiving table
uh... eating delicious thanksgiving food
man bear pig is there too
he's learned since had a heat
not people
you guys it took a while
to teach him how to do that eating john cena
man bear pig is there but john cena is not there
- ManBearPig rubbing his tummy
and you see Uncle Shredder putting his arm around ManBearPig.
(all laughing)
And what do you guys say?
- You hear like an audience,
you hear like a full house like, "Aww."
- Yeah.
- What do you guys say as the credits roll on "Hamward Bound"?
- Pass the stomach!
- Are you full?
- I've already eaten most of the dinner.
I'm smoking a cigarette outside.
Yeah, you're now strange.
Yeah, I'm strange.
Yeah, I get I'm strange.
I'm wearing a leather jacket.
They had to make you see what's dinner for me.
I'm smoking a cigarette with all my cousins
outside at Thanksgiving.
And just being like, "Uncles are bullshit."
I put my wings around WorldEaterHamster
and StrangeDog and I say, "I love my friends."
And John Cena, little John Cena Blagojevich
and Scrooge Blagojevich come out
and they say, "Come on guys, you're gonna miss the turkey dinner and we think ManBearPig's gonna push!"
And they run inside.
And yeah, you guys go inside and the end.
It's the end of Hamward Bound.
Another masterpiece.
Wow.
Beautiful.
The greatest.
A clump of cotton candy blows behind the winds like a tumbleweed.
[laughter]
Perfect.
For Hamward Bound 2.
Yeah, yeah, right.
Yeah, yeah.
It ends with one of those Hans Zimmer bass hits.
Yeah.
A piece of cotton candy.
See that popular idiot face?
Yeah.
Oh, man.
Great.
All right, great.
Good shit.
Yeah, great job, guys.
Thanks for sticking with me.
I'm going to stop there.
Of course.
Yeah, great job guys. Thanks for sticking with me.
[MUSIC PLAYING]