[Music]
So, you guys, um, so you guys were enjoying living with the uncle Robleg-
Can I ever say his name right?
Blagojevich.
Blah-boblio.
Yeah, hey.
Bob-blah-blah.
Bob Lob Lob Lob Lob
John Cena and the other nephews. Yeah, did you guys ever watch the rest of development?
Yeah, and
Then they dropped you off at the at uncle uncle shredders farm. Yeah, and
Then there was a break-in
Looks like Joe Pesci and Skeletor. We're trying to capture. Yeah, or Jafar. It wasn't really confirmed whether it was
I feel like and yeah, I feel like we didn't really couldn't get a clear look at him. Yeah. Yeah, it's hard
it was hard to tell in the dark in the dark of the game and
Shredder said he'd seen this before and
sent you guys on a
Motorbike with two sidecars one that was a hamster ball and one of them is filled with candy. It's filled with candy
Yeah, I think Cameron has opted to fly. I mentioned. I think I licked Skeletor's asshole for quite a while
Yes, also normal member really it was 15 minutes ago. Yeah, yeah normal talk like skeletons asshole. Yeah, uh-huh
So now you guys are on the road trying to drive to Duluth yeah, so
I'm gonna have you all roll straight intelligence checks just to see if you can read signs
Because you are 18
I'm a dog. What am I pretty smart? So just whatever and then plus intelligence. Yeah. Oh, no 10. Mm-hmm
Where is it? It's on the left side. It's zero. So I just got an 11. Okay, cool
And what'd you get
18. All right, cool. So you two, you know with your and we can kind of make out letters
It's hard to tell though, but pleasant parrot. Yeah
You're you're pretty much able to tell kind of where things are where to go
And you're able to kind of help steer things. Are you driving the motorbike - or is the I think I'm flying a bit
So you're helping so yeah, I'm pointing. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, no, I love you, all right, then I'll do it
So yeah, the power of love he guides you guys a little bit closer to Duluth
Because that's what being pleasant is, is saying you love your friends.
Yeah, it's very pleasant to be around. But then suddenly it's like...
Oh.
And the bike starts to stall.
Patrick farted again.
And the bike starts to stall a little bit.
The hungry hamster didn't fart and I did it.
And it's in the middle of like a road that is sort of like very wooded area,
You've got lots of woods around you,
and the motor car with the two side cars breaks down.
You can either try to push the car a little bit further.
You know, Perry, 'cause of that role,
you're able to tell that a town is probably 10 miles away,
so you could push through.
It'd be tough, but you could do it.
- I think we have to set up camp.
- Or you can go into the woods, set up camp,
and figure things out from there.
We have to set the bike on fire immediately.
Hungry Hamster you should jump on my back and we just walk into town.
Alright, so we gotta set the bike on fire.
What about your candy?
I ate all of it.
He absolutely ate all of it, yes.
Oh, I was, I guess I didn't look.
My eyes were closed when I said that.
Well we gotta set the bike on fire immediately.
Okay, alright, shoot the gas can.
I saw this on Mythbusters.
- Okay, do you have a gun?
- So you have-- - I don't have a gun.
- Hungry Hamster, you have check inventory.
- Oh right, okay.
- So roll a D20 and I'll let you know
if you pull out something that can destroy the car.
- I got a 19.
- Okay, one second, let me pull up--
- Wait, 19 plus anything?
- No, just 19.
- Okay.
- Let me pull up the table I made for you.
Oh God.
Okay.
- Okay, this is awkward.
- Okay, this is a little weird.
- That awkward moment.
- You said 19, right?
- Yeah.
- Okay, you pull out of the bag a beehive.
- What?
(laughing)
- I got 19.
- Yeah, you pull out a full beehive.
That's what's on the list here.
(laughing)
- It's not gonna help at all.
- Shoot the bees out of your mouth.
Put 'em in your cheeks and then shoot 'em at the gas can.
I'll let you try to do that if you're all athletics.
Well, what if I just
stuff the motor with a beehive?
I'll let you try that too. Explain what that could mean.
Stuff the motor with a beehive.
The thing is I understood what he meant too.
I did not.
I said I'll let you try that.
I was like, "Oh yeah, that would blow up the bike."
[laughter]
I've seen stuff on TV.
So you're gonna cap the gas can.
No, you know what?
Mr. Motor over here.
One of us would have to turn on the bike,
and I don't want one of us to explode.
I'll do it!
I put the beehive in my mouth, whole thing.
Okay.
Whole damn thing. And I shoot all the bees
at the engine.
Okay, I guess
that's gonna be cool it's gonna be cool for sure it's gonna be really cool I'll
let that be a constitution and then an attack roll constitution is just to see
if you can maintain the bees and the beehive all that in your mouth you tell
the bees not to sting you before you put them in. These bees can be pretty high. We can speak to them
because they're animals okay so some of you may die. That's 12. Okay so you're not
really able to keep the beehive in your mouth it's sort of like they start to get
and you start like sort of moving around in your mouth.
Move it up!
So I'm going to say you could do the attack roll on the motor, but with disadvantage.
Okay, so what do I roll?
Roll a d20 and add your dexterity.
So then add dexterity?
Yeah.
So it's nine.
And then roll again.
Wait, wait, wait.
Twice.
Hold on.
Is that six or a nine?
The dot is at the bottom, so that's a six.
Okay, so.
No, well, oh, you mean the butt?
Like the circle or the circle B?
The little dot is where the bottom of the number would be, right?
Yes.
Yeah.
Oh, so that's a six?
I apologize.
So it's an eight.
Okay, roll again because you have disadvantage.
You take the lower number.
Oh, that's lower.
That's right, he rolled it off the goddamn stool.
Yeah, so it would be eight.
Yeah, it's an eight.
Yeah, so you just shoot the beehive out of your mouth and it just sort of like plops
like three and a half feet in front of you.
It's covered in your spit.
And the bees are mad at you.
Yeah, yeah. The bees are starting to sort of get a little bit angry.
Quick, let's go to town!
We gotta run!
Okay.
I'll be my bat.
I'll do that.
We're in the town or the woods? Where are you guys going?
I love the big city.
I wanna go on a shopping spree.
I get on normal dogs back too.
Okay, so you're both on normal dogs back.
You can fly, you fucking freeloading piece of shit.
I just love being close to you.
Get the fuck off me, you freak!
I love you.
I don't like him because he doesn't have a human asshole.
Yeah, there is now just like a motor--
Abandoned motorbike and a beehive
covered in saliva in the middle of the road.
Not our problem.
And you guys walk into town.
You walk into the town of Brooklyn.
What the fuck?
How did we get there?
Of Brooklyn, Wisconsin.
And it's sort of a small city, about a thousand square feet, and everybody's sort of living
on top of each other.
You know how cities are.
And there's a bar, not a tavern, of course not.
There's a bar, there's an auto repair shop, there's a few houses where residents live,
a grocery store, bunch of other shit.
A mayor's office, so you're in this town, it's bustling, you're three sort of lone animals,
it's kind of early in the morning, like 7, 7.30, not too many people are out and about
right now.
But yeah, right now a parrot, a hamster, and a dog walk in.
Let's get a chopped cheese!
Do we order, yeah do we order anything?
You can get a chopped cheese, where do you want to go to the...
Oh I can't wait to go to the famous Brooklyn Bodega.
- Let's go to the Bodega.
- You're gonna go to Brooklyn Bodega?
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- We're gonna go to the Bodega.
- You go to the Brooklyn Bodega,
which is a massive, massive establishment.
Yeah, it's about 40 feet high and 40 feet deep.
It's a perfect mecca cube.
- Perfect Bodega.
- And it's massive, 40 feet.
And so you go in, you see a guy there.
He sees three animals walk in,
two of them sitting on top of the other.
and he turns to his son, he's like,
"Mikey, get rid of these guys,
"get rid of these animals out of here."
You see sort of a, "Oh, okay, dad."
And sort of a gangly kid starts to comes out
and starts to push you guys out with a broom
'cause you're just three animals.
So what do you wanna do?
- I use whimper.
- Okay, now we're talking.
- I'm gonna charm this target.
- You're gonna charm a boy?
- Yeah, so with, I take it back.
He's not a boy, he's like twenty-something.
Yeah, he's like twenty-something.
So you can charm a target of any species with this ability.
Roll 1d20 plus a relevant charisma skill.
So, what kind of whimpering are you doing?
Uh, sensual.
*sniff*
Alright, man.
Yeah, so you're, I guess...
Do it.
Batting, yeah, do it.
*oooh*
You have to look at me.
So...
I do have to look at you, the fucking dungeon master.
Roll a persuasion, add your persuasion to this.
Roll it.
- 12.
- Plus persuasion?
- Yeah.
- Okay, that is, okay cool.
And so he's gonna try to roll against that.
Okay, yeah.
His eyes start to well up and he's like,
aw, you seem rather sexy.
(laughing)
dad let's just keep them in here for a little bit you know maybe they can just
be sort of like our Brooklyn broken bodega animal yeah I'll be the but they
get dog here's a yeah you heard him chop cheese cheese yeah I'm already eating a
bag of like through a bag of pork rinds okay the dad see here's you say chop
cheese like now you're speaking my language he starts making a chopped
cheese and the sun kind of goes to you and he's like well don't don't eat the
bag please only from the food bag yeah just like he's keeping you know what to
do yeah he picks you up by the scruff of your your hamster ass neck freaking the
fuck you're very cute okay yeah and he puts you back in on top of a normal dog
lucky let's be back on top of the dog yeah put you back on normal dog jump
into the into the counter that is the gum I start eating I eat a whole thing of
bubble tape and one somebody's saying I jump into the gum and I eat the gum
uh...
i can't point traces best to stop you
i don't think you know these very dexterous i think you can really get at
you
uh... the job you can see come to me how do you do that your hamster
to my vehicle and i hold up says strip part of the bubble tape
uh... rolling uh... persuasion he's trying to understand what you're doing
that's twenty
what dirty twenty fifteen nineteen plus twenty five yeah
uh... money for the uh... yeah
he's like
all when he takes the gun research showing is in the search union
so yeah
this is just one of the government of world deception
starting a role persuasion not to mention you really want to swallow it
uh... fifteen
he's a small stuff
yeah
i don't know what i don't know
You're dumb as shit.
Alright.
Uh, hold on, okay.
Okay.
Uh oh.
Okay, so.
I shouldn't be talking so much.
The chopped cheese comes out.
Uh, I was like, alright, who wanted the chopped cheese?
Fuck.
I'm the only one.
He's the only one who can talk.
I don't want to talk anymore because the CIA is going to come get me.
Okay, I say, "Rough."
I do a back flip.
Yeah?
I do a back flip too.
You do a back flip.
I put my head on the ground.
In the ground.
put my head on the gum area. Nobody sees you do it.
You're just where the trident is. I start wagging my tail. That's a yes.
Yeah, yeah. He hands you the, he's like, "Oh, alright." I fly down and I
start eating bites off the other end of it while Caleb's eating it. I hope I'm eating the middle.
You guys are eating the chopped cheese, uh, uh, uh, and uh,
the sun is like, "Aw, Dad, maybe we can keep them for a little bit
while they're here. At least until they get to going where they're going."
They do seem to be on some sort of journey
And dad's like oh, all right. Why not my weird son?
Yeah, he started the dad sort of walked out from behind the counter and opens the door to sort of the back room
And you see like there's like a little doggy bed and a birdcage
And a hamster cage. It's like it's tailor-made for us
Well, you know we should do nothing but trust them I call the birdcage
So yeah, you guys have like a little abode now in the town of Brooklyn, but um, you're still pretty far from Duluth so
Getting there on foot is gonna be tough. I've got an idea now that we're in Brooklyn
Let's start a podcast
Yeah, we go to Radio Shack to get podcasting.
Okay, yeah.
So, I'm trying to think of what...
This is our way out.
Yeah, you guys head over to a Radio Shack.
It's out of business.
Oh, fuck.
Then you guys go...
When did this happen?
Let's go to Animal Radio Shack.
You guys go to Animal Radio Shack, thriving.
It's a little door on the bottom of the...
like a Jerry the Mouse. Yeah. And yeah there is there is a guy behind the
counter. How about a woman? How about a girl character? Hey, thanks Patches.
You know what? I'm about it. And there's a girl character behind the counter. I look
her ass. God damn it. It's like demographics. Like what do you want for your
listenership like what do you want guys like me dude so there's behind the
counter and she's like welcome to animal radio shack how can I help you you three
animals we want to start a podcast and uh yeah vaguely vaguely leftist politics
not really sure what we're talking about cultural critique well-meaning you know
yeah she she goes up to the back he's like oh I have just the thing for you I
understand animals. She goes out to the back and she gets out. How big is this woman?
She's giant. Give me the proportions of this woman. What's her bust? I don't want to say anything.
Compare to us. That means huge. She looks like one of the two broke girls.
Okay. The stacked one. Okay. That's right. Yeah. How do you like that? I like that.
Yeah, except her face is upside down. I don't like that a little bit. And yeah, she goes out to the back and she gets out
three
Audio Technica mics, okay, and XLR cables and a Zoom H6 audio recorder.
And she says, "Let me get you a fourth one in case you want to torture someone."
one.
Okay, that's good enough for me. We can leave.
That'll do it.
So yeah, she leaves confused with the mic. You leave her confused with the mics in her hands.
And uh, yeah. So,
Duluth is
a little bit far away.
part of the thing is that it is a tour
so they might leave Duluth and then...
so time is of the essence. Is there a travel agent in Brooklyn?
No, there is not. What the hell? It's 2020.
What kind of city is this? I thought it was 2003.
It's always... it's a bit... it's somewhere between there.
Travel agents aren't the thing anymore. It's 2000 and X.
2000 and X. Alright, is there a...
Is there a guy who loves sending animals to places? Yeah. Is there a guy who likes to tell you
where to travel. There's never a circus. Hey, you know what?
Roll an investigation check. Okay, I'm really good at investigation. You're
looking for... what are you looking for exactly? A guy who can help you, but in what way? Or
just a guy who can help you? I think a guy who can who can help us figure out how
to get there. Yeah. A transportation guy. Yeah. That is a...
11. Okay, yeah. So you can't really pinpoint exactly where somebody is with
in 11. But you get the sense that like, at the very least, there
is a, you know, there's a tavern in like a town square and like
between those two places, there's enough people there, you
can maybe find out where somebody is. Yeah, but within 11
you can't know you don't know exactly where someone is. I
would say you sort of like, basically as a parrot, you kind
of like fly around and try to get the sense of where people
are. The only other place you know of is because you know that
there's an auto repair shop. And that could maybe help you repair
the bike. Oh. Did we bring the bike with us? No, it's 10 miles out of town. Let's go back
and get the bike. We could send them back to the bike. That's true. We could tell them
to go get the bike. Do I have triple A? You do not have triple A. What kind of fucking
game is this? You have triple D's. Do I have triple A? I have triple D's? You have three
double D tits. Okay, I go to the strip club. Okay, you go to the strip club with your own
Yeah, with a resume.
Okay. Alright, what does your resume have on it?
Dog most of my life.
Okay. We're gonna move on from this bit.
What were you saying, Cameron?
Nothing interesting.
Alright, cool. That's a good start.
Um, no, what do you guys want to do? Sorry.
Hmm.
Is there like a guy delivering
something to Duluth today?
There's gotta be a train in this god damn town.
Yeah, or like a bus. A bus stop, maybe.
There is a bus stop, yes.
- Oh. - Yes.
- I, so you can go to the bus stop
and try to read the schedule.
- Yeah. - Yeah, dude.
- Yeah, I can read. - Let's do that.
- Yeah. - Okay, cool.
All of you roll intelligence checks
to see if you can read the schedule at the bus stop.
If I were the bus stop, it's like pretty abandoned
for the most part.
You see like one old guy there
just sort of like sitting on the bench.
- I got a 10. - Okay.
- I got a nine.
- And this is intelligence? - Mm-hmm.
- I got a six.
- Okay, none of you guys can really read the sign.
- Oh. - There is an old guy there.
I think it says sub. Maybe he can help you. Yeah I fly over to the old guy and I
smile at him. You smile with your bird mouth? Yeah. Okay. How about a little you scratch my back I
lick your asshole. Yeah he sees the dog in the parade he's like hey hello.
uh... where you lost
the looms you're trying to go to the news
so scared of returning to a little bit of a return i talk uh...
and trying to go to do you know for all my well
the bus for do you feel becoming in some point probably tomorrow
what do you
well i'm my name's old man
no way
or do you know you all who are you heard are you lost
you were heard
the man who had been answer it all get a parent
this is all they have a good student is the old man have any food
uh... he has been for a head to his pocket
it's pretty well pockets
i'm sniffing out that
okay uh... investigation
no you know there's bread and okay you got that squared up a interest you know
it's a member or i'm gonna go in his pocket
okay yeah uh... you said the crawls pocket
all black rule and he does this sort of like swat you a certain things you sir
a rodent. So roll a deck saving throw. That is 14. Yeah he's not quite able to swat you
away so you get a bit of bread. That's all I wanted! Just get me some! Oh heavens! Well
if you want to get busted to loot you can just wait here. I'm just trying to wait for
my bus to back to Chicago where I'm from. The only place in my brain. I can hear your Chicago accent. Yes of course. I sound like this because I'm from Old Man Chicago.
His name is Old Man Chicago. Are you Old Man Chicago? Sorry I can occasionally understand what you're saying.
it's not much my bad as the DM what's up
me yeah I don't remember what I said yeah so so yes yeah let's let's do
something fun in the city while we wait for the bus to Duluth for tomorrow here
let's see a movie yeah unless let's see we're back right so we said we're gonna
see a movie or something yes you're with the old man the bus bus stop yeah and I
was like we have to we should kill some we should have to do something fun we
should kill someone kill someone so you just said that's a kill an old man
I did not say that. We have to kill an old man.
Patches said that. I guess we do have to do that now.
I just heard the voice of God and it said to kill an old man. I didn't say that.
I mean I'm gonna trust this parrot because he only speaks English which is something I
very much value. And this old man could be God he's bigger than me. He certainly
we could you could try to kill this man nah we might be worth the smoke this old
man is just like eyes glazed over not realizing these animals spit on him I
spit his face okay yeah see oh you what did he sound like just old yeah damn dog
bitch and he starts trying to swat away at you wiping the spit the dog spit
from his face flicking it off his fingers and he's like get get with you you're
worse than the man bear pig
okay is it a character like South Park is it talking about South Park do we have
to worry about a man-bear pig now maybe as a little intimidating you're worse
than that damn man-bear pig that's been terrorizing Brooklyn
Oh, it is.
Ferret groans.
Oh.
Well, yeah, but you're still at the bus stop.
You still have time before the bus of Duluth shows up.
Can I roll an investigation to see if I see a man bear pig footprint?
Yeah, sure.
Okay.
You fucked up by saying that shit, Patches.
That was a nine.
Okay.
Yeah, no, there's no man.
Like, as far as you can tell, you can't really see any man bear pig.
I think this guy's got crackers!
That's pretty good.
Didn't you guys like that?
Stop talking in front of him!
I wasn't speaking English, I was speaking animal that time.
Yeah, it's animal, I can see. I can tell.
What do we do, man?
Let's go watch a movie.
Clearly there's no such thing as the man bear pig and we won't get attacked by it during the movie.
All right, let's go to the movie can we investigate again?
Okay
I'm gonna investigate the man-bear-pig hub in the middle of the town. That's labeled very clearly with a sign. I can let that
What movie should we see let's see it's 2004. Let's see homeless bound
He's back in theaters for a limited run
Started it. There's a limited run homeward bound playing in the theater in Brooklyn. Maybe we'll get some ideas
Okay. Yeah, you go to the theater
You're at the ticket booth
one dog, please
Yeah, I take a move person's like
Hello, will you guys?
your animals
Look I look him in the eye and I say you're dreaming
(laughter)
Roll deception.
Okay.
Uh, eleven.
Okay, uh, he's like,
"What? No I'm not. This is-
That was fucked up.
What you did, but I'm not dreaming."
Uh...
You're dead!
Woof woof.
Woof woof!
I can't allow animals in. I can't lose another job, okay?
I fly in.
You fly in? Okay, uh...
Yeah, you just fly in. I mean, he's behind the booth.
Yeah.
You don't need to do anything.
Yeah, we don't need tickets.
Yeah.
Fuck you, man.
I just walk in.
Yeah, me too.
[laughter]
Okay, you all walk in.
Did he really think looking at the animals and saying, "I can't let you in" was gonna work?
[laughter]
But I want some concessions.
I get... I swoop down and I...
I want a bunch of crunches.
I swoop down and I pick up a box of Bunch O Crunch for normal dogs.
This is one of the best days ever.
Yeah, I love chocolate.
At this point, there are a couple of employees at the Regal Cinema
who are trying to nab you in a cartoonish way.
Dude, dog nabbers?
Fuck this.
So, I'm gonna...
So one of them sees you going for the Bunch O' Crunch, Pleasant Parrot.
Roll a Dexterity saving throw.
Um, 16.
Yeah, Pimply Teen tries to swipe at you and he's not able to.
You're able to grab the Bunch O' Crunch with your talons and fly, continue to fly away.
Now there is one other guy trying to grab you, the Hungry Hamster.
I'm already somewhere else.
I'm inside the vending machine.
[laughter]
I hopped into the vending machine and I'm trying to climb up.
Are you tra- you're just trapped in the vending machine.
Yeah, I'm trapped in the vending machine. I'm trying to climb up the rings.
So I guess I'll have to roll for accuracy.
Yeah, do it!
You gotta!
That's a 16.
Yeah, you're doing a great job!
You should take some quarters while you're in there.
Do you fuckin' rock those rings?
I ate a whole thing of Famous Amos already.
I mean, you roll a, uh...
Yeah, the entire row, all the way back.
Roll a...
Athletics check.
What'd you get?
I got a one.
No!
A crit one or, like, one minus?
One, the number.
So, is it like a dirty one or, like, oh, you rolled a one.
So, uh, this big guy comes in, one of the bigger employees,
your employees are shaking the vending machine and your your little feet are
sticking out of the famous Amos pack and you tumble over and fall down and you
take five damage whoa fall into the down and he grabs you and he picks you up and
you're like you're in between his hands he's like look a little fella I can't
let you in here I'm the biggest teen who works at the movie theater he tries to
He starts to move you outside of the movie theater.
Nobody hurts my friends!
Okay, yeah, what are you gonna do?
I'm gonna use Dillifreen.
Okay, you're gonna use your eldritch powers?
I'm gonna turn evil.
Okay, yeah, roll a d20.
This is what happens when someone tries to hurt Patrick.
That's a six.
Okay, and roll another d20.
20.
Okay.
A natural 20?
Yeah.
Okay.
(laughter)
This is scary.
I'm going to use this at least once an episode.
Okay.
You have to.
You can't give me something like this.
Okay, hold on.
Hold on.
I wasn't sure if something like this would happen to this.
Something like this?
Do continue.
I have to check some stuff first.
Sorry.
Okay.
Okay, roll 2d8.
14.
Describe your kill.
Oh my god, dude.
You, I'll tell you as much and then you can describe the rest
because I do like to do that.
Your eyes roll in the back of your head.
Yeah, you hear
(gibberish)
and um
uh, your beak opens wide
like shoop de whoop
and out comes a beam
of ice cold
energy that um
shoots at the teen
it kills him, describe the rest
yeah so it freezes him
completely solid into a block of ice
and then I start flying back and forth
you know like a samurai in a movie
cutting it and when I'm done
it's an ice statue of Frosty the Snowman.
Yeah, it's Frosty the Snowman, but you carved it out of this teen.
Yeah.
So he- it's just- it's a mess. It's terrifying.
Uh-
I'm gonna start screaming.
Everyone in the- everyone in the movie theater who's-
*Screams*
is screaming. Uh, fire alarm is pulled.
Oh my god!
You're safe now.
I was just about to ask.
Yeah, yeah, you- yeah, the teen drops you, you land, uh, uh, uh, you- you take one damage, but you're fine.
You're just on the ground now.
I look at Patrick and I say, "I love you!"
"Thank you!"
"I have to go!"
"Oh my god, fuck!"
"Oh my god!"
"Before we go, I bring the popcorn machine with us."
*laughter*
Are you trying to bring a popcorn machine?
Yeah, I put it...
It's one of those
like wheelie ones, and
I've attached it to a leash.
I've tied it to a leash that's attached to Caleb.
Roll a sleight of hand
to see if you could do all that shit.
I got a six.
Okay, you were not able to tie it to the dog.
He tied it around like one of his feet.
Let's just get the fuck out of here.
You tied his feet together by accident.
He's like trying, you're like trying to drag the popcorn machine
without your back legs.
The popcorn machine does fall over and I do eat most of the popcorn.
Yeah, you eat the popcorn.
I'm still counting this as a win.
I'm not going home empty handed.
okay and alright okay and uh... yes you all all are you talking here what you
know me in the fall
uh... running out of the movie theater this team is just a frozen bloody mass
looks like frosty
uh... uh... you're running out of the movie theater
uh... uh... you know
it's a pretty animals that you know i've heard in the the peter that's right
and uh...
uh... and uh... you hear that so what do you want to
i mean we get his career and i think it would be a good time to talk to them
about this and if we have no it's not only did you know i don't believe
apparently this
what
that's a good point and i think that what we've got to do
let's just go to the best off of what you have a plan
Just go to the back of the place.
No, we can...
I wanted to watch the movie!
I got a great idea!
Let's open the fire exit and go watch the rest of a movie.
Okay, yeah, let's just do that.
Yeah!
Okay, um...
You're gonna go to the fire exit,
which is in the back of the theater.
Check your inventory for fake mustaches.
I got a seven.
Okay, let me check your inventory.
I bet this item helps us loads.
Machine gun.
Yeah, there's no way this is like a fucking toy kitchen or something.
Sorry, hold on.
It might be.
Uh, you said seven?
Yeah.
Okay.
Fuck, sorry.
Wrong one.
Okay, it's eight dollars.
wrong one okay it's $8 that's enough to buy the dollar store we go to the dollar
store okay fake mustache so all of you to do this without getting you know
noticed by police you'd have to do stealth checks I'm gonna heal what I
have an idea what's your idea we should get instead of fake mustaches we should
get one of those you know those cut those like tiny dollar store like cop get
ups. Sheriff's badge and a little hat and a gun. I'll allow it. You should absolutely try
to do that. We're all going to dress up as cops. Pot of Bellows cancelled. That's a six.
Okay, you're a very loud little hamster. You're screaming and running, you're still chewing
popcorn. The police are coming after you guys. The Dollar Tree next to the movie theater.
running towards the Dollar Tree this hamster is too loud the cops are
squaring up on you guys. The cops are squaring up on a hamster? Can I bribe them?
You could try but they're like hungry hamster. You have eight bucks. Hungry hamster and friends.
I'm holding eight dollars up to the police. Roll a persuasion check with
disadvantage please Patrick to twenties to twenties
was a friend of the six
okay no way those in nine plus your persuasion now
away in what's it was not was
514 14 says 14 that's not bad
all
we have him 18 plus I
I'm so very scared the 14 yeah the cop
considers it. Okay. And then his partner's like, "What are you doing?"
And they're like, "Freeze! Freeze, hungry hamster and friends!
We don't know what happened exactly, but we're very suspicious of it.
Of what could have happened here." What if the jail is in Duluth?
Yeah, let's go to jail. Is the prison in Duluth? This is a let's go to prison
riff now. We just switch movies. Yeah, switch movies.
uh... we can't get a really good idea of where is arrest animals
you know that
i know that
i'm very smart and i know that they've arrested animals before traveling to
ship well they killed yeah yeah they can't let me know yet so maybe
everything we should use yes and we're in a sticky situation because so i was a
really really your friends
like three cops
you know
Can we try to outrun them?
I just say I don't know.
Are you insinuating we commit more murder?
I would never... no.
Against our brave boys in blue?
No, especially not them. No.
Okay, I bite his balls off.
Okay, roll for initiative.
All of us?
Yeah.
13.
8.
20.
No way.
Nat 20.
Really, Nat?
Yeah.
Okay, I like...
Why don't you take Patrick to the fucking casino, dude?
I do nat 20s always go first unless somebody rolls a nat 20 that has higher deck.
So that's good for initiative.
All right, nat 20.
What'd you get?
Sorry.
13.
What'd you get?
Eight.
Okay.
One second.
We roll for, when we roll for these pigs.
Um, okay.
All right, cool.
Um, hungry hamster.
Nom, nom, nom.
You go first.
I do my famous dance.
Fuck yeah, dude.
Uh, okay.
No, you're good.
Okay. So you do the disco dance? Yes. Okay. Let's see what happens here.
All right. Uh, okay.
All right. They're all unable to resist your famous dance.
They're all doing a little disco dance. I've just made the cops do a flash mob.
This is going to be great for their PR. Yeah. They're like, Oh no,
I thought we were only supposed to do this around black children.
And they started doing little dances. Um, and where are the cameras?
you're looking for cameras. They're doing their little their little cop dance.
They're gonna do this for a minute. Oh my god. That's enough for us to get back in the movie theater.
Let's get away, yeah. Let's watch 30 seconds of the movie and then spend 30
seconds hiding. Okay, deal. Alright, that's what we do. Yeah, you absolutely do that.
You watch the first 30 seconds of Homeward Bound. Describe it in detail.
Okay, hold on one second. Yeah, you watch the logo come up, you hear Michael J. Fox
start to speak and then it's then that's enough for me your alarm goes off yeah
and you run out of the movie theater people are terrified of the parrot and
you go into hiding all of you roll a stealth check with advantage to hide
somewhere 11 okay 14 okay 23 yeah so you all successfully hide where do you guys
hide in the town of Brooklyn the sewer Wisconsin I got a sewer I got a 23 so I
I hide in the on the the homeward bound like giant piece of cardboard poster that
has like all the you like put your face in the dog's face. I just put my dog face there.
Okay yeah yeah yeah your dog face is there you look like oh yeah that's just
a poster where the dog is. Yeah like well you can't be the dog. Yeah it's gotta be.
Where do you hide? I'm in the sewer. Okay you're in the sewer. I flew down a
- You guys two are great.
Okay, and yourself?
- I just go back into the vending machine.
(laughing)
They can't find me in there.
- You're where the famous Amos was.
- I'll just eat snacks instead of them.
- He's doing the same gag at me, but with famous Amos.
(laughing)
- Yeah, you're all hidden, by the way.
They couldn't find you.
The cops look for like three or four minutes
before they're like, "Let's go get donuts," and they leave.
So you're all hidden.
but keep in mind any obviously if you go anywhere
people are are are looking for you
you did you look at the movies you did kill a boy well i didn't kill a boy
right
you know it was patrick's for you
it's my fault was that the fall for getting picked up by a boy
i was just trying to save him from my fault
so i feel like we could get into some standard ground law here
it i think i did and i'm up
it's a listen it's not going to wait a little bit it's brooklyn law
that if you're if you're a homies getting getting moved on
you can turn bad you cannot argue that you can bus back yet
and if the regulate exactly
the
to regulate that's that is the brooklyn law yeah right through
the plan a west coast song nothing yeah
makes no sense
uh... yes a year you're all where you said you you were
yes it works
support down posturing
and back in the pending machine couldn't get can hold myself
hold myself back so he's too hungry I mean a couple of things obviously you can
wait till the theater closes it's probably gonna close down for the day
pretty soon dead child in it he's not a child you said he was a teenager it's
something you're right sorry the Parkland children if they those got
killed that'd be worse but uh yeah I mean like and eventually the you know you'll
be able to move eventually so like there's some time you can wait until
things are sort of calm down these are kind of closed down if you looked at the
bird news you would see news about some sort of mysterious murder bird and it's
sort of nighttime people don't know where you are it's over the place is
closed you're the only one in the vending machine you're the only one by
the poster you've been holding that pose for a while yeah I've kind of been doing
like scooby-doo painting eyes though back and forth I made friends with the rat
You make friends with a rat.
"Hey, how's it going?"
"Cool."
"I'm a rat.
I'm the rat character."
"Nice."
"I always sound like this.
In everything, rats always sound like this."
There's never any...
Yeah, okay, you make friends with a rat.
His name is Charlemagne.
Yeah, so now what do you guys want to do?
You can all meet up, maybe above the sewer grate.
First thing...
Right now you're safe.
I clear out that god damn vending machine.
You take it to the tent.
Oh, man.
cleaners. What snacks you eating there? All of them. Name them, name them, go. I start out I eat all of
the mints. You're at the bottom row. I'm at the bottom and I go to the top. I eat all the gum, I eat all the mints.
Okay good. Then. Well you eat the candy too, the straight candy that's down the bottom too. Yeah I get the candy too.
Like Reese's too. Yeah I get all that and then the one above it is always the premium chips. Yes.
So like the Gardetto's and stuff, I get those out of the way.
Yeah, what are those called where they're like, they're like different colors?
Do you eat the headphones on the top row?
Yes, I do.
Yeah, you eat the iPhone 7, it's worth $57.
Yeah.
Yeah, I just clear it out and then I go about my business.
You commit theft. Yeah, you eat the entire vending machine.
Yeah.
It's not theft if you're hungry.
It's not theft, honestly, you know, a lot of people would agree.
And so you're, yeah, you guys are here.
Your stomach looks crazy.
- Mm-hmm.
- You two are there.
Your face is kind of permanently frozen
and sort of a dog smile.
- I just kind of look more like the Homeward Bound dog now.
- Yeah, you look more like a shadow.
And you smell a little bit.
- Nice!
- Yeah.
- That's not good.
- So what's up?
- I love this!
- The bus is gonna come probably in like another
four or five hours, so if you--
- We should sleep a couple hours, right?
We're tired.
We only need to sleep for exactly three hours.
Because we're animals.
Is that true?
My dogs only sleep three hours.
Your dogs sleep three- how do you know-
Nevermind.
I don't want to get into this right now.
Your dogs sleep-
Dude, my dogs do not sleep three hours.
Dogs sleep for a long time.
They sleep like during the day.
Cats just take naps.
Are you just saying facts now?
You just said like all animals.
just said like animals sleep three hours most animals do okay we just go to sleep
yeah sure first go back to the bus you guys go back to the Brooklyn Bodega we
take the back door into that room so they don't see us the back door I mean I
don't know they're pretty friendly I think the back door you hear the news at
all yeah trust the news no they don't yeah they're wearing tinfoil yeah yeah
You go to sleep in the little bed
And yeah, the bus is gonna be here in a little bit. So you guys can go hop on that bus if you want to
Yeah, I'll wake my ass up make some breakfast. Yeah make for breakfast dog. I make a croissant
Homemade I'm totally different layers and putting butter in you know what you know what a
Motherfucker you call me on it. Yeah roll a just roll straight
Dex and roll straight intelligence. I want to see you make this motherfucking croissant.
I would love you to succeed at this.
Okay, so it just might look fucked up.
And then a... where's my fucking intelligence?
And then an 11 intelligence. It's like pretty gross,
but it works. It's more like pie crust. Yeah, it's like pie crust.
Yeah, I don't give a fuck. I should get an award for this.
I just baked something.
Yeah.
Nobody recorded it.
It's like somebody who's like, "Oh, if you put a little salt in it, it tastes better,
but you put too much salt in it."
People, I'll eat it.
Yeah, dogs literally lick their own fucking assholes.
This is the only thing I've eaten besides asshole this entire game.
I eat all the spiders out of the back room.
Yeah, there were a lot.
I ate the cage I was sleeping in.
I wasn't even conscious when I did it.
Your body looks so crazy now.
I did it in my sleep.
Do we get to restore our hit points?
Yeah, everything is restored.
It was really a short rest, if it was only three hours.
But it's dog years.
It was really a long rest.
So let's restore it back.
Okay.
Alright.
Now for the bus, boys.
So, you guys head out in the back door.
You go to the bus.
You see the old man
is no longer there.
back to Chicago it's just empty can we let's have a quick cutaway to his life
in Chicago yeah absolutely so his life on the south side yeah yeah he goes he's in
Chicago he gets back to O block he revs three on a he gets off the bus and
somebody I don't wanna I don't want to get into all the characters he meets in
that case cuz then I'll be in little Reese yeah no he uh he gets off the bus he
immediately like he gets strapped up again he's he's like murder capital of
the world yeah Chiraq did you his voice when you're saying all this that's what
he sounds like he sounds like me you know and he's code-switching yeah he's
good from old man to me there's nothing else he's code-switching - and yeah and
then he peacefully dies in his daughter's home oh he doesn't get wet up
widow daughter yeah we were really talk to you people talk to us things you're
You are you died because he died because he didn't have enough bread. Yeah
You see he gets on the bus he's strapped up and ready to take down
You know another gang. Yeah
But he feels around his pockets for bread and he's like, oh god, I have to see my daughter
Yeah
sugar got too low and he didn't pump his insulin. So now we're back in the real world.
In the real world, Eddie. In Chicago. Yeah, back in the real world of Brooklyn, Wisconsin. And
you're all waiting for the bus and the bus shows up and the bus door opens and the bus driver is
sort of like, "Huh?" Like, you know, it's three animals there. Yeah. You guys walk on the bus.
I got an idea.
Say sir, we're service animals.
I think he's just gonna let us on the bus.
Nevermind.
He lets you on the bus. He's super chill.
Uh, well, yeah, he lets you on the bus.
I can't back away from that now.
He lets you on the bus,
you sit on the bus,
the dog sits on the bus straight up,
three of you sitting on the bus,
you guys sort of look at the
signs up top, looking for Duluth,
roll an intelligence check, Cam.
Oh no.
How'd you do?
That's a 2 plus 3.
That's a 5.
You're having a real hard time telling where Duluth is and where it isn't.
I think we're on the moon!
You see people starting to get off of the bus, yada yada.
And then all of a sudden the bus stops for, like it doesn't look like it had a stop.
You sort of pattern recognition, this doesn't look like the places the buses usually stop
at.
And then you see people starting to get off of the bus, yada yada.
And then all of a sudden the bus stops for, like it doesn't look like it had a stop.
You sort of pattern recognition, this doesn't look like the places the buses usually stop
at.
And then you see people starting to get off of the bus, yada yada.
You see people starting to get off of the bus, yada yada.
And then all of a sudden the bus stops for, like it doesn't look like it had a stop.
You sort of, pattern recognition, this doesn't look like the places the buses usually stop
at.
You see the bus driver get out of the bus, he's out of the bus, he's out of the bus for
a little while, for a little while longer.
Can we see him?
Through the window?
You can no longer see him.
Uh oh.
Oh no.
I think I know who.
in
you kind of get handling before before we do that yeah yes I'll be next
well yeah and before we do that you so what you get a sense of is that to drive
this thing it can't just be you you need somebody else to do one of the other
things that this thing is the the feet Cameron is my eyes okay I want to be the
eyes you know my life is a dog sucks yeah do you want me to fear the eyes you
you're going to tell me about it?
Fine, I'll be the eyes.
What?
No.
I didn't know.
I'll be the feet.
I'll be the fucking feet.
You can't reach to the be the eyes.
I can, I'm really long.
No.
Yeah, I'm one of those running dogs.
No?
You say you're a Labrador.
Can one of you just be the feet?
Isn't that the same thing?
Is that a running dog?
I'm looking out of the front of the bus and I say, "Look guys, we're in Duluth!"
I'm the eyes!
I pedal to the metal then if I'm the feet I'm having fun. Okay, and you're steering. Yep. So you're giving him directions
That's the plan. We're about 90 miles an hour in this
There are other passengers
They are their typical bus patrons, they're just sort of like whatever
the Chinatown bus stopping at Burger King. Like, whatever. Yeah, like, until the third
strange thing happens, I'm okay with whatever's going on. And you start driving a little bit,
you feel yourself go over something and you go a little bit more. We hit the bus driver?
I didn't say that.
Can I see what we went over?
Roll perception.
Sorry.
Uh... 18.
Is it the bus driver?
It looks an awful lot like the bus driver.
What was he stopped at?
You can't tell what he was stopped at yet.
He's helping an old lady cross the road.
And all of you now roll perception.
another 18 for mm-hmm - I got - you're literally just like you're like straight
being a dog complete dog. I guess it would make sense. He's the eyes. He got an 18.
Yeah, he got an 18. That's right. You pick up a sound of like something rattling from below.
You can't quite tell what though. Hmm. I think it's a rattle. Come on, you got an 18.
I don't know if that's how he told me.
There's a rattle!
I think it's a rattlesnake.
That's better.
I trust that more we can at least talk to him.
Sorry, no, that'll be for next session.
Oh no.
Keep going.
What do you do?
Well, you gotta do something about this rattle.
You told me about the rattle?
Yeah.
I slam on the brakes.
Fuck yeah.
Okay, yeah.
You slam on the brakes.
You all hear like a *fwoosh* *fwoosh* and like you see rolling out of the front, very
good move dawg, a terrifying thing.
Part man, part bear, no!
No!
Part mother fucking pig.
Oh my god.
It's like from South Park.
Oh.
Jesus Christ.
It's even scarier.
What if it says something irreverent?
What if it's weird?
Yeah, so ManBearPig rolls out from underneath the bus or something that's part man, part
bear, part pig.
And you see it, it took some damage from that because you guys smartly knew to brake when
you heard him underneath the bus.
and you see it start to get up and it's like
and it's sort of standing its ground in front of the bus
here's a quick question about man bear pig can we talk to him because he's part man
but he's also bear and pig he's more human than he's more
but we're we're animals yeah yeah you absolutely could
okay okay hey i love you i love you too so you're in the bus so he's
is
Really loud hamster noise.
Yeah, wait, hold on. This is what the passenger is hearing.
Over the loud speaker.
*Hamster noises*
You think that's what a hamster sounds like?
*Laughter*
Like really small guys in movies?
Sounds like 645AR.
Yeah, I got bit by the same thing that bit 645AR.
So you say, would you say "Hey, what's up?"
Yeah.
Hey, we don't know that he's bad.
He's covered in blood.
Yeah, he says kill.
Kill who?
Kill.
No, he thinks for a second.
Every kill.
He's never been asked kill who before.
Okay, just kill people.
There are some there's a lot of people in that city.
Yeah, you want to go kill those people.
Go pass the bus.
Roll, roll, uh, persuasion.
Okay. Who?
All of us or just Cameron?
Oh, um, I guess just the hungry hamster
'cause he's the one on the megaphone.
Ooh! 22!
Okay, yeah.
[laughter]
Alright, Pat, just what do you got?
*laughter*
fuck off, ok
oh man
*laughter*
fucking hate, hate games
uh, you see the mad bear pig
um
think for a second, kind of an "oh bother"
type of stance
um
that's the bear part
on it.
Hmm.
Maybe just kill people?
Yeah, do that!
Do only that!
And he starts to wander off towards you guys.
And, hold on.
I can't believe how good Pat's roles have been in this campaign.
I know.
He literally doesn't notice any of the people in the bus.
us
we killed all the people in brooklyn milwaukee
it's a neighborhood in milwaukee
did we defeat him?
exactly we did
try to find people
so we got experience points for that
uh... yeah i guess so experience points and so we get out of the lake have a
hundred experience points yeah man
connect you hundred
i guess three hundred
so that it was the work
you need to do a lot of the work there
yeah uh...
yeah and so it
yet member pics behind me like i can't
i can't as a d_n_a_ set the rules are really can't
but it would be a lot right well you tell that
see a buddy
yet so i mean that doesn't mean you won't come back but it certainly means
that the for now he's just looking for people in brooklyn wisconsin
uh... carried peace to hit a check for it he had a chance to notice people he
literally got a one
so he i can't
reasonably like say yes i miss you walk by the bus like i can't
uh... so
you guys can keep driving
uh... my god there's another man bear
I I accidentally put the car in reverse and I just keep following
Yeah, you certainly can I was a Brooklyn I was really about these people yeah, I don't care about Brooklyn's keep going forward
All right. Yeah, okay. Yeah, so you guys keep going forward?
You keep driving. So what we need to do now since you guys don't really know
So where you're going?
I'm gonna have you
Camera since you are still the one who's like navigating the bus. Yeah
roll a
Yeah, roll straight intelligence check again to see all right you can um
I'm the smart one tell where Duluth is cuz you just sort of reset. That's a 13
Yeah, I mean the thing that's tough is that you are a bird I said the DC for this pretty high
You could have you definitely had a chance of getting it, but you don't know where to lose your you don't know how to see
lines
on
you
'cause you're the third one do not continue to ruin my night.
I have negative one intelligence just do it again.
Can we add those scores up?
Yeah, you can add them up and then divide them by three.
Can I make up a score?
Okay, that's would be less than 17.
But so yeah, you you keep trying.
You can't you keep driving.
It's kind of hard to find a loose the people on the bus start to kind of notice that like
You're not stopping because you don't really know what buses are.
You're not really stopping for anything and eventually the bus just literally runs out of gas.
You just drove and drove and drove for hours until nightfall.
There wasn't any gas left in the bus.
You see all the people just get up and go...
And they just like get up and just all file out of the bus and just go their separate ways, but you are now
at
this bridge here
so
Did anyone who got off the bus call an uber? Oh?
Good question
Yes, one guy did can we get in the uber with him you can try for sure okay? Can we convince him?
Yeah, so there's this guy there
the
Okay, go for it.
Okay, so I roll a d20.
Oh yeah, you're, oh yeah shit, because now it's not.
And then a dc12, I don't know what that is.
Oh, that's more for me, so I have to roll against that.
I rolled a six.
Oh great.
You don't have to worry about that.
Fuck me.
Don't worry, don't worry, don't worry.
I'm worrying.
Okay, yeah, you just roll a d20, add your charisma, or it's dc12, whatever's higher.
higher so in your case DC 12 is higher so I'm gonna roll against that Dick Van Dyke's
charisma probably a bad choice for you guys because he's pretty good charisma.
That's true.
Yeah.
One of the most charismatic men alive.
Nah he's old.
That has to be a negative.
Alright I'll minus one to it instead.
He's just putty in our hands tonight.
Now he sees you whimpering and he's like oh hey there fella you did a great job.
job driving the bus and he scrubs your head and then he just goes back to ordering his
Uber.
Oh my, how about driving me somewhere?
What are we trying to get him to do?
We're trying to get in the Uber dude.
Uber hasn't arrived.
We can wait for it.
Go.
What's up?
I have an ability too that I can try and make him do something.
Yeah, go for it.
Polly wants a what now?
the
*quack*
Where's Duluth? Take us to Duluth!
Um, and...
Okay, at that...
'Cause, uh...
Rolly dexterity saving throw, Pleasant Parrot.
Oh no.
Okay, uh...
Nine.
No, it says 21.
Uh...
No, it's a nine.
Uh, you...
Uh...
Uh oh.
It's not good.
Anytime it takes longer than one second, it's bad news for us.
Right, you know something really bad is going to happen.
Yeah.
You take six damage as a bullet comes shooting out of the air and into the side of your bird
body.
Oh my god.
Each bird can take a bullet and be alive?
I already got hit with a bullet on the last episode.
I'm not going to lie.
can take a bullet and be alive. I already got hit with a bullet on the last episode. That's
a sturdy bird. I took 6 damage right? Yeah. And suddenly you see 3 CIA agents come out
of the brush. Can one of them be Stan from American Dead?
Oh no! What? Can one of them be Stan from American Dead?
Yeah, they're all like, "Hey, I'm da Stan!"
Okay! Hey, alright, cool, I'm glad I said that.
Yeah, alright, so we have three Stans.
I'm Stan! I'm da Stan!
Yeah, I'm da Stan. They're kinda arguing around each other.
other
and
a
Van Dyke start to run away and the people start to run when they see a bullet.
They shoot Dick Van Dyke when he runs.
Dick Van Dyke, dead Van Dyke.
Dick Van Dyke.
He starts talking like his Mary Poppins character because his brain stops working.
By the time this comes out he might be dead.
So yeah, roll for initiative because the CIA is now after Pleasant Parrot.
I'm fucking ready.
I'm taking care of this one.
I'll take the other end.
There's a man who leads a life of danger
To everyone he meets he stays a stranger
When every move he makes, another chance he takes
Odds are he won't live to see tomorrow
Secret agent man, secret agent man
♪ And, baby, giving you a number ♪
♪ And taking away your name ♪
(upbeat music)