[MUSIC PLAYING]
I just keep releasing the background until--
yeah, all right, cool.
So, um, this is the second, uh, this is gonna be the second arc of the official D&D arcs
in the Potabatlas universe, and it's a little different.
Yeah, no more Gun City ever again.
Yeah, we're, yeah, I got, we got the feedback, we get it, you guys don't like Gun City.
I handed it.
I had a lot of people DMing me thinking I was Sullivan the Frog saying horrible things.
So we decided to abandon it and do something a little different.
Introducing Hamward Bound.
It's based on nothing in particular.
And I'm going to sort of kick it off and then I'm going to ask you three to reveal who you
are.
Yeah, we're in person too, by the way.
Yeah, we're all in the same room.
Yeah, we're all in the same sauna.
We're all sweating.
Sweating a lot.
sweating a lot.
yeah, i'm sweating too much too.
so okay.
put all the stones in.
you don't sweat too much.
you don't sweat.
here, i'll put some more thingies in the middle.
i'm crushing caleb's penis with one of the stones.
yeah, why do you think i just wore a towel?
mm.
okay, so.
the uh, camera comes in from the sky.
And it starts gently gliding down to a lovely suburban abode in sort of a... one of those
suburbs that has a lot of property ground.
You can get like an acre of property for yourself.
And you begin to hear a voiceover.
"Hi.
My name is the Candy Hamster.
I know, it sounds odd.
But most names do if you think about it long enough.
Maybe even yours.
I was formed through dark magics from rotted nerds rope mixed with radioactive josta and
Joel energy drinks in the carcass of Ronald Reagan's hamster racist Michael.
I did my best I could to survive in the harsh streets of downtown DC, doing things I am deeply
ashamed of and am unable to remember without blacking out completely and bleeding from
my ears.
It was a tough life growing up, but lucky for me, I was eventually adopted by a wonderful
uncle and his beloved nephews.
The uncle and his nephews took care of me, bathed me, clothed me, even helped me get
over my pill addiction and opened a line of credit for me to start investing in futures.
Whatever that means, I love my life here.
Or at least I DID love my life here.
See, today is supposed to be the most holiest of days between an uncle and his nephews.
A nephew's adult risk.
Everyone gets together and watches the Rugrats Moses episode, and then drops trow to get
their worm done upright.
However, if there's anything that can ruin this day, it's the three loudmouth pets adopted
recently by the uncle and his nephews.
Right now they're locked in the animal room.
And hopefully they'll stay there for the whole ceremony.
I wonder if they were to introduce themselves, what they would sound like or talk about.
Oh how I hate them.
Oh how I want to know more about them.
A lot of this was just, I was writing this at like 6am.
We'll all be waiting here, the ever faithful Candy Hamster, to stop them from getting out
and ruining this adult bris.
So, uh, the candy hamster is standing guard outside of the animal room.
The animal room is just a blank room with toy blocks on the floor.
Okay.
Uh, no, well there's a door and there's a window and you could-
We get a window?
There might be other things-
There's a window so you can see outside in the back where the adult press is happening.
Oh yeah.
I'm looking.
Um, yeah.
And uh, the, the, the three of you are in there, the three of you animals.
been locked in there just like in the beginning of a different thing sort of
kept away from the ceremonies as well do mischief yes and the candy hamster has
been tasked with the with outside a bunch of adults put a hamster in charge
of watching an animal like it's not the brightest bunch you know Patrick it's a
game stop come on come on you're ruining it yeah
Pat plays Monopoly and he's like Broadway wouldn't cost $1,200.
I'm in character right now. My character is very analytical.
So yeah, I mean it sounded like the Candy Hamster wanted to know a little bit more
about you guys. Yeah. And so would I. Yeah. Start over here.
I am the Hungry Hamster. Okay. I was picked up by the uncle and the
nephews when they were bored one day and they thought it would be funny to buy a
hamster that ate a bunch of stuff. They've been feeding me a bunch of food ever
since I was born. They've been feeding me pretty much too much food for a hamster. I've eaten things that
hamsters shouldn't eat. Like... I've eaten a tire. I ate a whole tire one time. It's pretty
crazy. You'd think as a hamster I wouldn't be able to eat a tire but no. I
I ate the whole thing in one fell swoop.
Does that mean one bite?
What do you mean one fell swoop?
What?
For me, bites are fell swoops.
Yeah, definitely from now on we're not gonna write character descriptions.
I have to just work with this kind of reality now.
By the way, the uncle is Rod Blagojevich.
Just a side note, because this takes place in Chicago now.
This sure does. Well it's actually funny you mentioned a place in the Midwest so
you already cracked the code. So yeah so for Patrick and for the benefit of
the audience I think, yes he is the hungry hamster. You have your character
sheet in front of you Patrick. You should see you have a few abilities that you
might want to key in on. So you have the hamster ball.
That allows you to deploy your hamster ball, start knocking things over. We can
talk through that when we get to that. You have hamster bite. That's just a
little nibble. You know what a young hamster would be doing.
You have, which you told me to add to your abilities when we first talked about
about this, check inventory, which I did make into something where you're just
gonna, basically you have a ham tote, it's a little bag, and when you want to check
inventory, you're gonna roll a d20, you're gonna pull out just about anything.
Okay. You have sharing is caring, which is another thing you told me to add and
didn't explain, and it allows you to just share any items that you have as a
free action at any time.
Okay.
So, yeah, you can see sort of the synergy between check inventory and sharing is caring.
Yeah.
And then, of course-
Sharing is caring just sounds like a thing you could do.
Well, it's up to 120 feet.
So, it's like he can sort of like mentally just email it.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
It's like a walkie-talkie.
Yeah, a mental email.
Yeah, mentally, of course.
Thanks, sorry.
Yeah, no, I forgot where the-
Yeah.
Then you have your famous dance.
Famous dance is so infectious and if people fail that saving throw, they will have to do
the dance for a full minute.
At which point your bite is going to be stronger and they can't do anything besides dance.
They can move a little bit.
So you have some cool builds.
That's exactly what I was imagining when I thought of famous dance.
Yeah, I hope so.
But yeah, so you're hanging out in the room.
Are you playing with the blocks?
Are you trying to eat something?
I'm spinning around in the balls so fast.
looks like I'm gyrating when you did I'm in one of those it's it's spinning when
you did the first gun city you you basically said the same thing except you
were like flipping on a skateboard yeah you're always doing something I'm in the
hamster wheel I'm running around in the thing I'm yeah yeah you're in like yeah
yeah no yeah yeah yeah no I'm sorry yeah you guys always got questions I'm just
I give good judgment did I'm sorry so
The game we have the hungry hamster who else do we have here? We have I believe somebody else. Yeah, I I'm the pleasant parrot
So I'm kind of like a parrot. I'm a macaw
Actually, okay. I am the white parrot. No, that's colorful. Oh
Do you have anything else to add?
Are you friendly?
Yeah, I'm actually very friendly. I'm very pleasant. I grew up on a pirate ship. Mm-hmm the
the pirate ship from Captain Phillips, the pirate ship that Captain Phillips was
based on, where they kicked me out because I was too pleasant and too
friendly to those evil nasty pirates. Right. Bad vibe. Yeah, they kicked me out to
Chicago where this adventure is set. Where I was adopted by John Cena who's
another one of the the members of the family believe it or not. Wow.
Yeah, Blagojevich.
That's the first name I thought of.
Family's growing.
Yeah.
They're actually related in this universe.
Okay, Rob Blagojevich and Blagojevich, okay.
Yeah, and I'm just a cute little happy little parrot that's just lovely.
Okay.
Yeah, you're a sweet little parrot.
I'm just that lovely little friend.
So interesting thing about the pleasant parrot.
So the pleasant parrot, you have a couple of things going on here that I gave you.
You have speech, so you can mimic human speech.
This is huge for you because none of you guys can really talk to people, as we'll learn
when we meet Caleb's character.
Caleb is giving me the Kubrick stare.
I'm chilling.
And to, so the thing about your speech though is you are really smart.
You're a little too smart for a parrot, so you do have to be careful about how much human
speech you do.
I'm going to do some secret rolls depending on how much speech you're using, which will
determine whether or not the CIA is interested in you. You have probably
want a what now, which is an ability that allows you to basically
use the command spell in 5e in my own sort of like jacked up version of it
where you just sort of get to say one word command to somebody and they will
be compelled to do it. So convincing is your silver parrot tongue. You have
talons that allows you to basically like perch on somebody's shoulder like a
pirate parrot but instead of being nice to have on your shoulder you hurt them
and you stay in there and you continue to do damage to them. You have a Noi
which is basically allows you to taunt them and get them the enemy to focus on
you and then have disadvantage on attacks. And then you have Delafrana
which is a you're not sure what this does but it terrifies you. It just says
question marks next to the stats. Yeah it's yeah I can use it three times per
long rest it says.
Yeah.
So.
Interesting.
Dlafurna.
You're not sure what that is.
It really scares you though.
I just have an ability in my brain.
And you have a knowledge of it.
Yeah.
Alright.
So yeah, what are you doing in the blank room with blocks that is the animal room?
I'm flying up to the hungry hamster and I'm saying, "Hello, how are you?
Nice to meet you."
I'm saying hello.
I'm saying even that to you.
No, that's just what I say because I'm pleasant.
Oh, first-hand.
That's what being pleasant is like, right?
I'm telling him how hungry I am.
You can just tell him how hungry you are.
I'm so hungry right now.
They bred me to be hungry.
I love you.
Thank you.
I'm hungry.
I'm your best friend.
You're my best friend.
Oh, that's nice.
The camera pans over to what looks to be just a regular dog, but instead he's a what now?
I'm the normal dog.
[laughter]
Should we be doing character voices?
I chose to do one.
[laughter]
I'm the normal dog, and I...
My...
old owner's name was Steve.
And he used to smoke salvia and blow it in my face
because he thought it was funny.
And then I got adopted by...
I guess...
Rod Blagojevich and John Cena.
Yeah.
[laughter]
And I like hanging out and I love my friends more than anybody in the world. Yeah
So the normal dog has no ability what kind of dog are you
Lab mix fuck you more more than anything
I'm a nice guy
With a beautiful smile and blue eyes
so the normal dog was dropped in from the the right movie into this game and
Let's get some so you're you you are normal dog. You're you're pretty tanky
So, you know you have and you and you hit can heal you're pretty competent
little pooch
You have a bite and tackle as your sort of baseline attacks. You're gonna want to use
Tackle also can knock somebody prone grapple and restrain them
What that means is that you basically you know how dog jumps on pounces on you and lick your face and you're like, yeah
It's like killing you this time and then you have wound lick
Which you can heal 1d 10 plus 3 health to anyone in range of your tongue
In range of my tongue
We could talk about that so
You have who's a good boy, which means any white woman is fair game
Nice you've advantage on all charisma checks and saving throws involving white women
Crime Dog, you have an advantage on all investigation and perception checks that involves your sense of smell.
If you have the first attack on an enemy, you have an advantage on all attack rolls for the rest of combat.
Like if you're like the first one to get them.
You have Wimper, which is another sort of charm ability.
Allows you to charm anyone of any species.
And then you have "Vicious", which is sort of like, uh, Ork's savage attack,
um, mixed with, um, the other fucking thing that gives you different kind of critical...
Whatever, you have 19 and 20 for you as critical, rather than just 20.
So you basically have a double, percentage-wise, chance of a critical hit.
- Oh my god. - And then you also get three, uh, instead of rolling just twice your attacks, you roll triple.
- Whoa. - So you're, you're, yeah, you're, you're pretty beastly, um...
- Can I be his character too? - Uh, no, you have to be your character.
Uh, Cameron, we talked about this.
So you guys are sitting in this room, the window outside is showing you-
I'm barking at the window because I think it's a TV.
Okay.
Yeah, you're barking out at the window, you think it's a TV.
You see as you look out the window, the adult brisk going on.
You see Rod Blagav- I can't say his Polish ass name.
Just say blah blah blah.
Blah blah blah.
You see Rod blah blah blah beginning to give a circumcision to John Cena, who's his nephew,
you see, you also see a, you would see a 30 foot long, three
foot deep, two feet wide, just giant fucking trow filled with
the Ben and Jerry, Ben and Jeffrey Epstein's Island Time
ice cream, which has nougat caramel, chocolate chunks,
something called Satan's Love, and a full legal defense
strategy by Alan Dershowitz, all sort of in there. So it's like
It's everyone's favorite ice cream.
You see that in there and you see everyone's having such a nice time.
That's what you see out there.
You hear the hungry hamster from outside saying don't go thinking of doing anything.
You mean the can't I'm sorry the candy hamster.
Don't we start the whole thing over?
You see the candy hamster outside.
Is that clean take?
Yeah, that was the candy hamster outside and you don't see him.
But you hear him say don't go thinking of going out there.
I'm gonna stop you 'cause I'm the candy hamster.
RUH!
Shut up, bitch!
*snickers*
You shut up, bitch!
You're my- you're my friend!
Uh, no, I know, he's a tricky fucker.
You're my friend!
Uh, you're- no, you're trouble, that's what you are.
How are you?
I'm- I'm doing okay.
Bitch!
I love you!
No, I'm- you're a bitch!
You're the bitch!
I'm gonna- I'm gonna sit down here and plug my ears.
Dumbass hamster-looking motherfucker!
You're a hamster-looking motherfucker!
You look like a hamster!
*laughter*
Yeah?
Oh yeah?
Yeah you do!
Shut up!
You shut up!
I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna punch you in the mouth.
But better not!
I will.
I will open this door against orders and punch you in the mouth.
You better not come in here.
I will, I maybe I will.
Oh you wouldn't.
No, I maybe I will.
Roll a persuasion check.
Which one is it?
Uh, d20 and then just add your persuasion.
No, it's the, the...
Oh no, it's the one with 20 sides.
Sorry.
I got an 8.
You got an 8?
I got an eight. You got an eight? Okay yeah. You're like, "I'm, I'm, oh you almost got me there! I'm not, I'm not going in there though! That was a good try! I gotta give you that!"
Try again, bitch! I will, I will not try again. Try again! I'm, I am, I am gonna- Candy ass bitch! I have a candy ass and I love it! You candy looking motherfucker! You wish you had this candy ass! You look like more candy than a hamster!
I look exactly in between those two things.
You look, you got nerds rope for a tail.
I have nerds rope for a tail, I have nerds rope for a heart.
What do you have?
Hungry bitch.
I got a regular tail.
I'm a normal hamster.
Oh yeah, you're a normal hamster?
You're shaped like a tire right now.
I, so?
So what, bitch?
I'ma roll my shit on you.
You're shaped like a hamster, hoe.
You owe ass bitch.
I'ma roll shit on you, bitch.
You're a slut.
Fuck you.
(laughter)
- This fight has left the hamster characters
and turned into a real fight.
(laughter)
- He's talking shit.
- So yeah, that's happening.
- You would never come in here.
- So that's happening.
- Talk a big game outside the door.
(laughter)
- So yeah, what do you guys want to do?
- Sidestalk smack at the candy answer.
- Hey guys, I think we should go try and eat
that black and white ice cream outside.
yeah i think it was your idea
a bitch
i'm not responding to that i'm not responding to that
okay maybe
i didn't work
my idea didn't work
i was going to tell you to shut up
sorry i'm not i'm me
now
okay yeah so what should we do
i uh... i try to fly out of the window
uh... okay yeah so
Me too.
*laughter*
Oh shit, okay.
Uh, you can...
Well, uh, you can try to fly out of the window and roll a, uh, strength check.
Just a straight strength check to see if you can break it.
Okay.
Uh, that'll be pretty hard for you 'cause you're a parrot.
*laughter*
I can do it. I fly beak first.
Okay, yeah, go for it.
Alright, let me...
Is that... you think the beak first helps you?
The beak is the hardest part of my body.
You know that a bird's beak is the most sensitive thing in the world?
*laughter*
I would do anything for my friends to get out of this room!
That's right.
right this is two very nice characters in one whoo that's a well it's a strength
right yeah so that's a 14 okay yeah so you get up to the window and you kind of
crack it a little bit but like like you get like pretty you do a pretty good job
but it something that's made of harder stuff than you thought
but yeah let me give it a whack yeah go for it you can do it okay I give it a
whack what do I do strength check yeah so just keep in mind so what are you doing
to go out the window kung fu so are you gonna try to hit it with your paw are
you gonna try to jump through it or what's the plan jumping kick oh I go
for it. Go for it. Seven. Or no, sorry, plus five. Thirteen. Seven plus five is twelve.
So, yeah, you try, you do a jumping kick. You sort of like use all four of your legs
to kick it and it does bust it a little bit more and then you just fall like, like sitting
up. Like a dog sitting up. Okay. Are there a lot of people at the bris? Yeah. Is there
anyone close to the door no because you guys are like on the second floor which I
should have mentioned because I didn't want okay if you wanted to if I if I if
we start if could people hear us yeah you're saying like if you look okay I
get I get really close to the wall and I go
roll deception roll deception okay and roll deception with advantage - okay
Because it's all people out there.
I think it's plus pretty high for you.
Persuasion.
Deception.
Plus two, 17.
Yeah, okay, so you see, you're yelling help, help,
and you see a little boy turn around and look,
and he looks just like Rob Blagogovich,
or whatever the fuck, who does have a little boy haircut.
He does look like a little boy, yeah.
And he starts to sort of wander away from his parent,
And the parent doesn't notice and the kid looks back, he looks to you, and he sort of rushes into the house.
Yes.
Um, yeah. And so you hear your little footsteps.
[footsteps]
You can put that in, right?
Is that what footsteps sound like to you?
I haven't walked in years.
[footsteps]
So you hear all those noises that the boy is making.
You hear, uh, and you hear outside.
[kissing]
And you hear a little boy going, "Aw, come on, candy hamster, let me in!"
(laughing)
Which you guys can hear as like,
bitch, get the fuck back!
The same for you.
- Let him in, bitch!
- No, 'cause the boy can't see you,
and you can't really talk.
So I'm trying to figure out--
- I'm hearing him say, get the fuck back.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So the candy hamster yells back at you.
He says like, you fucking stay out of this, okay?
This is not about you.
- Oh yeah, what are you gonna do?
- I was a pet first!
You three came in here, the shiny new pets.
- What are you gonna do?
- What am I gonna do?
- Yeah, what are you gonna do?
I'm a slap you.
You got nothing.
You have nothing Patrick.
Come slap him.
Sorry?
[LAUGHTER]
Come slap him in the room.
Yeah, but you come slap me.
OK, roll persuasion again.
It's going to be a bit harder because you already tried this.
But roll again.
I got to wait.
And then I add that with what?
Persuasion.
It's in the skill list.
All right.
I think it's a 10.
10?
Yeah, now he's still like, I'm not going to do it.
I'm not going to do it.
you see the little boy says is anybody need anything in there is everything okay
help we need water and food
ok yeah to be free ok roll roll I need to vote roll deception again with
advantage
oh my god ok
yeah the little boy is sort of like I don't know I I feel like I'm gonna get
in trouble
uh hold on wait one second your skin sucks
Here's Footsteps walk away.
Man, fuck this kid.
And here's Footsteps come back.
And he cracks open the door a little bit.
And he starts to push in a bowl of water.
Go, go.
I'm gonna give you guys all an opportunity to figure out what to do here.
This is all me.
I push the water back.
(Laughter)
Yeah, you push, you use your like,
snout and you push it back.
I'm telling him to rescue us in Morse Code.
He just has to put the water back in.
So I can finish the first letter.
Uh, yeah, you push the water back in, and little boy's like, "Uh, oh, uh..."
And he tries to push it out again, he's not sure...
I fly through the crack.
Okay, yeah, uh, uh, yeah, you fly through the crack, and the hungry hamster...
Oh, sorry. I was really sorry.
It's easier to say.
The candy hamster fuckin' freaks out, he's like, "Get back here!"
And, uh, roll a dexterity saving throw.
Oh, you're fine.
Okay, yeah, yeah, 23 the candy hamster slings a nerds rope at you and and whiffs it as you fly out
Yeah, what do you want to do all my homies eaten? I'm gonna open the door
Okay, I'm gonna do our bro. You're a bird. I fly into the door to tease your talents to open a little handle
I use my talent you use your talent. I'm gonna use my talents. Okay. Yeah
Patrick wants me to you're gonna have to roll for initiative in that case cuz you're about to fight the the candy hamster
What? I don't want to fight the candy hamster.
So if you're gonna try to open the door.
Okay, wait. I fly down to the candy hamster and I say, "Do you wanna hang out?"
Ooh.
Okay, the candy hamster, uh, he needs a friend right now.
No! You're a stinky bird and you're... I don't like you.
Hey, don't say that to my friend, bitch!
I will end you, you hungry bitch!
You're the hungry one. You made out of candy.
Oh my god, that does not... maybe it means I'm full. You ever think about that?
that candy bitch you're more candy than man and the hamster have more candy than
man that's right you're not met you're no man at all
I'm a hamster what were you saying bird I love you I don't love you I don't know
you you guys just came into my life and ruin my sweet my sweet fucking
relationship I have with you should come in here and you should talk to me about
it I'm a nice guy with big ears what is the boy doing yeah the boys are sort of
watching this situation unfold he's kind of a little freaked out by the parrot
being out if that boy walks in I'm gonna attack him the boy is sort of backing
away at this point it seems like a like he's like oh no he feels like he kind of
screwed up maybe the the yeah roll a persuasion on the candy hamster actually
wait what are you doing exactly with the candy hamster? I'm just trying to calm him down
I'm just trying to make him chill out okay hold on one second just fight him
you pussy I don't want to fight him without my friends I only like hanging
out with my friends oh my god he's a baby I'm gonna touch your tummy so what you
baby is too pleasant what you could try to do to you try to manipulate him
You could try to do Polly wants a what now?
I could, but all, listen, all I'm gonna say is
if a parrot can fit out the door, a hamster can.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, the door is slightly ajar still.
The candy hamster is not. I've got an idea.
Okay, what do you think of him?
I'm gonna call the candy hamster a bitch again.
Okay, go for it!
Bitch! That's it! And the candy hamster
runs in there
to just fucking fight you.
His nerds rope are spilling out of his body.
He's so enraged. Okay, guys, come out, come out!
quick quick no no around the candy hamster yeah roll a roll a decks trade decks
oh wait is that a different one no no just add the dexterity number seven plus
two it's nine okay yeah the candy hamster fucking like boxes you out he
fucking like pick and rolls just the pick part I just yeah he said to pick okay
thanks I just walk by him cuz I'm he a dog I'm huge yeah sir yeah roll
intimidation with advantage to see if you just like act like he's fucking
nothing like you're an eldritch God that was a bad roll I'm gonna reroll that
right that's advantage oh yeah yeah yeah the candy hamster just shit out fucking
milk duds. He is just... I started eating the milk duds. Don't you hate this guy? You're eating his shit now?
Hey man, I'm hungry. He's like, "Oh my god, I didn't realize how big a Labrador would be."
Yeah, word counts. Yeah, and yeah, so you guys all are able to sort of walk out of
there. He's terrified. I fly into the door to close it. Okay, oh god, a poor, poor
candy hamster is now trapped in there he's like I've been foiled again the
candy hamster that's right bitch you're a bitch I hate you
this is what I got from the episode. I can't tell which hamster is evil at this point honestly. I didn't I chose to sound like him
because he's a hamster too you're both kind of evil yeah so far I'm just hungry
you guys are now outside the door. I need to get you some food. I say to the candy hamster I love how determined you are you're so strong
I'm getting sick of this fucking parrot
So yeah, you guys are outside there you're in the house you can go all right, I go straight to the kitchen
Yeah, you see the kitchen. It's like a pretty nice kitchen
This refrigerator. There's a what are the part of encounter in the middle in the where the party snacks a role investigation check
See if you can figure out where that is
What'd you I got a 20 I got a natural 20 serious. Yeah, I don't believe him you are in the same room
I don't need to look I trust you
So one that's a 20, okay. Yeah you I'm sorry Patrick
Do I add to that? No, when you got 20, it's a crit 20. So you uh, I sniff them out
Yeah, you the snacks. I'm on the charcuterie board because they're rich and they were each charcuterie. Yeah, they do. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, Raba Baba is very rich.
And so you eat the shit you find this her good or you're bored
and you eat the shit out of that.
I eat everything including the plate.
Including the little serving plate.
Yeah.
Okay.
So what do you guys do?
I go.
It's going to be the toilet for old normal dog.
You mean toilet for you?
Yeah.
Okay.
So you go to the bathroom.
It's a small it's a first floor bathroom is not that big has
like a little sort of just a little sink and toilet are pretty
close to each other.
What are you doing there?
You're just going right in the bowl.
I mean I'm just licking water from the-
Yeah you're licking water, you're drinking water in the bowl.
I got a little bit of poop in it still.
What do you sit on?
It has like the things where the poop is-
Yeah I sit on it like a guy and start reading a newspaper.
Okay yeah, you're reading the Epoch Times.
For some reason, it has a thing where it's like the poop is sort of on the, like still on the outside of the-
Yeah.
It's like someone like really did a number on it.
Yeah, it's like a salted margarita round.
Yeah, right.
What do you have to, Pyro?
I go sit on the couch and watch TV.
Okay, yeah, you go to the remote and you start to click through it.
What are you trying to watch?
The bird news.
Okay, so that's channel 305.
So you have to get up there.
So I click on 305.
Yeah, you click on it. It's the bird news.
You see a reporter. It's just a sparrow.
He's like...
[chicken noises]
Is that a chicken really though?
No, all birds sound like that.
Except for him. He speaks English for some reason.
Like a pigeon on the ground reporter.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's what's going on the news.
There's just a pigeon in New York City getting ignored by people
walking by.
With a microphone.
He's in a suit and a microphone.
I can't believe what passes for news nowadays.
Yeah, BNN.
And so you're, folks, you're all doing this.
time the boy's father comes in and he's like he's like he's like a Scrooge?
Scrooge where are you? And he sees this hamster. Scrooge the boy. Scrooge McBoy. Scrooge Blagojevich.
Yeah he's Rob's nephew. And he looks over and he sees this this noisy little hamster
was hungrily eating all the charcuterie and he's like "uh oh my this isn't
sanitary at all!" "What you want bitch?" So for him he's hearing *tongue clicking*
"Okay so are you gonna try to to charm him or anything or you just want to tell
him what's up bitch?" "You should attack him." "I do my famous dance." "Okay yeah you do
your famous dance uh uh let me I have to roll for that not you and let's see how I
I do on that. You gotta crit one. Oh man. So what? Is that good? It's good for you.
What is... Not for my poor man here. What is your famous dance?
Well it's the hamster dance. Which is?
- Dee da do, da dee da dee da do.
- What do you do physically?
- I just basically do like the Saturday Night Fever thing.
- You do like the--
- An extremely goofy movie disco scene?
- Yeah, pretty much.
- Okay.
- So you're doing the extremely goofy movie disco scene
dance and this guy who was like, "Scrooge, Scrooge!"
And I'm like, "Huh?"
And then he just starts to slowly do the little dance
and he's like, "Oh my!"
and uh... uh... yet he is going to be doing that for a full minute
you can
you do whatever you want this point but this guy's name
as guys name is the robbers are still going on only can do anything to dance
for one minute
don't have had a sudden i think what's this guy's name squid
the
we've been doing it
problems but i ran out of the bathroom i search sniffing is black
yeah he's just like he's like oh dear like I go down I will to get down I have
to grab the zipper of his fly and I go down and then I bite his I buy his
shorts like a drug sniffing dog and pull him down so I while yeah you do that
while I'm doing that I go down I tie his shoelaces together okay a couple of
checks here so you're gonna bite his butt well I sniff it first that's fine
And then I bite his shorts, and I pull him down. I'll have you roll. It's on it's on an attack
I guess it's technically an attack roll. You're not attacking him, but just roll a straight. I just want to lick his butt sure just
You can do that without taking the pants off. You're just roll a d20 and add add three to it
Ten okay, yeah, you pull his pants down. It's not like a hard thing to do
I like his butthole and before you lick his butthole you're flying you're going on a zipper
I grabbed the zipper so I can get down roll an acrobatics check
At 20
God you perfectly go down his zipper. It doesn't clip his penis at all. He's like this is the best fly on zipping
He's doing a disco dance while you do it you fly down you you you there's no issue now with any of the pants
He was at it's a really down. Sorry to interrupt you. Yeah, and I roll again to do a backflip on the way down
Like you got 20 if it's an acrobatic check and you got a 20 you do a backflip on the way
I'm doing a flip and yeah, you're doing a flip. He's his pants are down and you're now licking his butt
I'm gonna lick his butthole. I fly up his shirt. Yeah, you fly up a shirt. You look at his butt you fly up his shirt
I'm doing George Carlin alphabet with my tongue
Cuz I got a minute it's like what I do George Carlin seven dirty words or
this guy barely holding it together he's going to bust your dog lick my ass
discovering something about himself your head pops up next to his collar freaking
out he's making all this noise you see Rob Lagogovich is like his knife is like
right next to John Cena's penis he looks up though and he runs out over here and
they all see you guys doing this and they're like oh my god these three
fucking pets and they're all like oh the kids are laughing they're still got his
shoes tied together right you tied his shoes together just wanted to make sure
sure and yeah he's just comes right his inky ink right on the ground it's taken
away by like he gets put it he gets put in non-steel it fades to black it says a
one week later the camera opens up on a newspaper that guy is in jail yeah it
pulls back it's a crane shot you see Rob Legovic reading the newspaper you see
John Cena reading a child's newspaper because he's the kid he's a nephew in this
one of the nephews and it takes place in the past yeah
John Cena was still a kid. Rob Legovic is rich it's like 2003 yeah
yeah it's everyone's having it. Rich as hell. Yeah these embezzling hard. Yeah you three are in the
kitchen with them it's a it's like a morning you're just eating breakfast
You're eating your dog food, normal dog.
Parrot's eating his parrot food.
I'm eating whatever I can find.
You're eating just about anything, my friend.
The candy hamster is eating a...
Do I get to eat out of their food bowls?
If they let you.
And if you can.
So would you guys let him do that?
Sorry, Taylor's peed his pants.
It doesn't matter if they let me.
I am the hungry hamster.
I gotta do it.
I don't think it's my choice.
so then there's no role just make you just do it I'm making it bad for everyone
and yeah so yeah the hungry hamster just starts devouring the food from your food
bowls any food that you guys have not finished eating roll acrobatic check
those and see if you can reach his bird feed the parrots bird feed 11 wait then
I add the 11 plus 4 this 15 yeah you can reach it you can get up there that's fine
yeah you sort of like do a little bit of like you sort of like a swing on like a
drawer handles like just to get out there like in a fucking like ps2
platformer yeah Sonic's yeah yeah yeah also pleasant parrot roll a d20 and add
your wisdom to it you'd be pleasant enough to share with me 16 okay you you
your head starts to rattle a little bit and you hear *weird noises* and then nothing.
But you're you're you feel okay this time. Okay. And yeah so it's that morning you
guys can hear the people talking but you can't really understand what they're
saying really. Well actually I mean like Pleasant Parrot you can roll a straight
intelligence to see if you can understand what the people are saying.
I'm gonna do that. You're you're probably able to do that. That is a 14. Yes you can
Kind of make out or sing over you in the concerts. Yeah, you can't really quite understand it, but you're a good word concert
That's something you hear a bunch. It's like a word. You're not that familiar with but it is new
But you guys can't really understand what they're saying. You see the kids have kind of like sadder faces on it
They're like being really attentive to you all right now and like you can't quite get it
so a few minutes later everyone finishes or they're big English breakfasts and they
Load up in a in the mystery machine and they all are driving away the now all the nephews right and Rob
John Cena is just like a lot bigger than all the other nephews
John Cena who is uh, was that uh, that was a yeah your owner right right pleasant parent
So he's like petting you right now. He loves you very much
the dog normal dog you're sitting in the middle and like sort of like
I'm kind of like looking up like a and the little nephews are like poking at you. Yeah. Yeah, you're me
And the hungry hamster is and the candy hamster you're you two are squaring off in a hamster cage just like
Fuck you. Fuck you. I'm not going to sleep. Yeah, you are. I'm not going to sleep
I do that first then we go better. I'm gonna put no one. You know, you're gonna go to bed
I'm gonna put your nose under your nose and you're gonna sniff it
You're not even gonna be able to fucking breathe tomorrow.
You won't breathe.
Are you actually gonna have a Hitler poop mustache?
I will not, 'cause he's gonna have something like that.
He said he will.
No.
I said he will and it's gonna happen.
It's not how it works. This isn't the secret, bitch.
I feel like I already see it on you.
I'm not gonna manifest it.
I can manifest Hitler poop on you.
Oh, yeah?
You do have a little darker hair where Hitler would have his mustache.
But that's just a pattern of my fur. That doesn't mean I'm Hitler.
Does that mean your dad was Hitler?
No, it does not.
I think his dad was Hitler.
literally not Hitler. I am a candid hamster.
His dad was Hitler.
And you guys are driving along in the mystery machine and the car sort of starts to slow
to a stop. It's been a few hours and you see everyone's...
This is so long to be seen.
You see everyone's loading out of the mystery machine and you see Rob Bogogovic is like,
"Come on, come on! My little boy haircut. I have a little boy haircut. Come on, I don't
know anything. I don't know that much about him." And he lets you guys out.
Me neither.
And I have friends who are more into Chicago politics than I am, and I don't live there.
And you...
Wait, what?
You have friends who are specifically in Chicago?
Specifically, they're from Chicago.
So they would know things about him.
I don't even know who that is, to be honest.
He's like some guy.
He was some guy who was on the Apprentice.
I'm supposed to not like him because I...
Yeah, because he has a freaky last name?
Yeah, because he's Polish or something.
I think he had too much swag and they kicked him out of Chicago.
Yeah, too much wagons?
Yeah.
Too much ass?
Too big of an ass?
He's too damn thick.
Yeah.
So yeah, his wagging ass is a waddle and out of the car.
And, uh, you guys, uh, are, are sort of like, like kind of, kind of come on out
into this and you see this big old farm, uh, that looks like it's made of knives.
It is the sharpest looking fucking farm you've ever seen.
It is kind of terrifying.
And there are just like knives everywhere and swords everywhere. There's like a fence and all the pigs look like they look like they're dressed in some sort of metal garb.
And you see come out of it is Uncle Shredder. And you see Uncle Shredder is talking to your family, sort of going back and forth, blah blah blah.
Uncle Shredder! Uncle Shredder!
And then you see all the humans come to you guys.
And they all have tears in their eyes and they're telling you they love you so much.
They're hugging you.
You don't know really what's going on.
It gives you a cracker.
One of them gives you like a prime rib just to eat for yourself, normal dog.
Yeah.
And one of them gives you another tire.
[Laughter]
It's a Hot Wheels tire.
It's smaller.
They don't want to have--
You got anything bigger than this?
What the fuck?
And then you see everybody pile into the mystery van.
You guys are behind this knife fence and they drive away.
And you see Uncle Shredder.
WTF?
I'm gonna love it here!
And you see Uncle Shredder and he says to you all, "Hey, so make yourselves at home.
I'm really sorry about how sharp everything is here."
And you start to realize all the pigs are dressed in like the Foot Clan outfits.
Can we understand us?
No, you don't he can maybe get a sense of what you guys are saying, but you guys you say all that's wrong
Tense and purposes. It seems like your family just like left you here. Oh my god, uncle shredders
We exposed his brother for being a pedophile
He was a pedophile. He just likes when dogs eat his butt fucking freak. Yeah, he's weird. Yeah weird
I was just testing him. I didn't like that at all. I hated doing it, but sometimes you know a greater good
I guess.
Helco's right here.
Hey.
Comes out, he's like, "Uh, sorry, these are all the snacks I have."
Wait, wait, let me be clear.
I seriously didn't like doing that.
I don't blame you.
I don't blame you for doing this.
I mean, it's just, you know.
I think he deserves it.
It just felt right in the moment.
That's not what I mean.
Yeah, this, well, I got something for the little gay dog and the other two.
You know, I'm not gay, but I'll take your present.
He brings out a Knive-O's and it's just, and he pours it out, it's just a bunch of thumb
tax and he's like I'm sorry I don't really have anything else I'm starting
to understand this guy if you're gonna start eating a roll roll a constitution
saving throw just a constitution check really 18 okay yeah you're fine
easily slide down your goal at the thumbtacks just like slide right now
okay yeah roll a constitution okay this is a constitution check see if you can
eat stuff - Patrick before okay and yeah you take four damage all right as you
try to swallow the thumbtack, but I'm pridefully like, "This is really good!"
Yeah, and you see Shredder is talking and he started talking to
himself, talking about what was going on. Pleasant Parrot, you can kind of make out
what he's saying. Something about like a, something like the family are just a
bunch of stained brains, so they're going to follow Stained for a couple months,
and they can't really like so they left you guys here and like you can kind of
make that out but as animals you can't really understand why they would do that
I heard our family gives crazy brain okay that's good no but that we won't see him
for a while so I don't really you know yeah it's not huge for us and everything
I know about Goblin. Everything is really sharp here. It's unpleasant and it's
sort of a few hours go by, you all try to watch TV but the remote is really sharp.
You figure it out and now it's nighttime. And how do you guys all sleep by the way?
I sleep like a cow. Yeah? I'm just standing up. I sleep like a bat.
You're like a bat? I sleep like a hamster. How does a hamster sleep? I guess I
sleep on my back no I sleep on my back in my hamster belly yeah just kind of like
see like a dad on a couch exactly yeah yeah and that's how I sleep that's yeah
you're sleeping and you're sleeping on the couch you're like on the couch it's
like your account I have a tiny couch yeah yeah yeah it's it's nice and all
you roll perception check is gonna be cash money for all Caleb what the fuck I got
a 40 million I got a sick shit I gotta start rolling in there got a 20 yeah oh
god damn okay yeah shit okay so yeah I had no I don't know you got a crate you
got a crate I have negative one perception so I subtract one night you
get it if you get a crate you get a great all right doesn't matter so yeah
you hear you two are like you're still sleeping a normal dog and a pleasant
parrot a hungry hamster you're alert you're you're a trained hungry hamster
warrior you hear like you hear some like whispering noise you hear like a little
bit of movement and you hear and you see he no movement and and you wake up and
You can kind of hear something coming in from the kitchen.
That was almost bad.
Sorry, yeah.
It could have been really bad.
It almost spilled a lot.
So, yeah.
So, I hear somebody in the kitchen.
Yeah.
Well, I'm already hungry.
Okay.
I might as well.
So, are you going to approach stealthily or just like just want to walk right up with
your big belly out?
Yeah, I guess I'm going to.
I guess I'll stealthy.
You don't have to.
I'll go stealthy.
Roll a stealth check.
Fuck.
That wouldn't be what you roll anyway, so it's okay.
It's the wrong dice, so roll a d20.
The one you've been rolling.
I did roll the d20.
It just...
Oh, it knocked over the other one?
Yeah.
Oh, what'd you get then?
I got a three.
Okay, so that's how I get it now.
Uh, yeah, you try to walk...
Hold up, three and then...
I got five then.
Okay.
Yeah, so, uh, you're...
I'm too fat.
You're too fat.
I can't walk stealthily.
Tuba is playing behind you, a la the family guy bit.
And you hear that movement stop suddenly.
And
okay, yeah, and
you hear some more movement coming towards you. You start to see a shadow.
And it's a person. It looks like sort of like a, kind of short, kind of like a
stocky looking person. He's like, "Where are you? I'm looking for you.
where are you? You little hamster.
*Gasp*
Where are you?
We're asleep. We just both just had a nightmare at the same time.
So he can't see me?
He can't see you yet.
Hmm. Oh, what should I do then?
*Groan*
What does the guy look like?
He just looks stocky from what you can tell.
It's kind of a silhouette. Short and stocky.
Short and stocky. What size are his pants?
His pants are...
What size are your pants? Probably like a 38. 38 inseam?
Like you know. He's short that's pretty big for an inseam.
That guy's f*cking huge. He's got a tiny torso then.
Yeah he's got the smallest torso. So say 28 inseam,
30, 37 waist. Okay.
Starting to look like, so he looks like me.
I think that's it about it. Yeah. Huh.
I'm just, I'm talking in my sleep and I'm crying in my sleep.
What fit are the pants?
Like are they slim fit or are they very loose? No, they're like regular slacks. Just full-wearing bootcut. Yeah
You got a 2004. I feel like not loose fit pants. You got regular pants. Just regular cut. Yeah, I'm gonna grab the cuff of his pants
I'm gonna go behind him and grab the cuff of his pants. Okay, go for it.
This hamster has no fear. You're trying to do a sneaky like?
Yeah, so just so like you know how like they put the Millennium Falcon on the back of the Empire Strikes Back the Falcons
Go on they put it on and then they go through the garbage shoot. Yes
Yeah, so I do I do one of those I grab on to him did like kind of stealthily hide
and see what he's doing.
Absolutely.
Okay, roll stealth and then roll sleight of hand.
Okay.
So it's a nine for stealth.
Okay, roll sleight of hand.
We'll see what happens here.
All right, cool.
Nine.
Okay, nine and nine.
Okay.
So you start to go up to this guy's pants and see a theme
here and he's like, what the hell's going on?
And like he starts moving around and it's like kind of big
stomps to you because you're a little hamster and so you can't quite get even
get a grip on his pants and he's like oh and you start to realize he looks down
because he sees you now and it looks like exactly like Joe Pesci but you see
his name tag and it says Joe Pesci aka mr. grab your damn dog and
no you know I'm the only dog in this I'm here for him you're asleep and and you
start to and he's like you little hamster and he starts to try to grab at
you so he does nose oh he knows your hamster no I eat his nose he tried to
eat his nose yep okay we got roll for his face his face was in my face yeah roll
for initiative and that you know what I'll finally do it in this little bit
both of you also roll perception perception so that's a which one would
that be so just as your initiative is up top okay so that's a nine okay my
perception is 21 okay well I got a four okay I sleep you wake up you hear all
this commotion yeah you're about like 40 ish or so feet from the action mm-hmm
but you can kind of get a sense of something's going on somebody's here
you're fucking you're you're sleeping like a rock I'm much rather yeah and
that shit yeah I'm some fucking fat okay so you should also roll for initiative
because you're probably pretty alarm all right and you're gonna be part of the
turn order 22 yeah yeah yeah yeah okay cool so and then sorry one more am I
dreaming of something cool you're dreaming of Dracula goes to college whoa
yeah scary but intellectual I'm just eating that guy's butthole over yeah I'm
like I hate this this isn't for me not sure why I did this first thing yeah so
So you're actually first a pleasant parrot.
Oh boy.
So you can kind of get a sense of what's going on.
You see a struggle between your friend the hungry hamster and what looks like some sort
of Mr. Grab-Yo-Damn-Dog-Shaped Joe Pesci type MF-er.
And you also, with that 21, notice somebody much taller than Joe Pesci a little bit further
back in the kitchen.
Whoa.
You're going to have to be able to sort of look through.
Yeah.
It's your turn though.
Okay.
So, my movement is 30 feet, so I can't get to Joe Pesci, right?
You said he's 40 feet.
Well, you could do 60 feet of movement, but you just can't do an action.
Yeah, yeah.
All right.
So, I'm going to start out by...
When I mimic human speech, can I mimic a voice?
Can I try to sound like a specific type of voice?
I would love for you to do that, yes.
Okay.
Let me think here.
I use my speech ability and I go, "Stop! This is the police!"
Okay, uh...
Just from the dog bed.
[Laughter]
Okay, uh...
Let's see what we're gonna want you to do.
So, I'm gonna say that this is sort of a, uh...
Okay. Yeah.
Roll...
[Clicks tongue]
Okay, I have to roll against that, actually.
So, hold on.
I have to roll a couple times actually. You're such a diva Patches.
Okay. You're a diva buddy. He's always rolling.
Okay. And okay. Yeah. Joe Pesci stops in his tracks. He
used Polly Wants a What Now? and Joe Pesci just stops in his tracks.
He's still trying to go after the hungry hamster. Did I land a blow to his nose? But he can't move.
We're gonna resolve that in a second. Okay. Sorry. No you're fine.
And he stops in his tracks. He can't seem to...
He's like trying to move but you can tell that he can't move. He's like, "Agh!"
He's still trying to reach for the hamster, but he's not being able to move.
He's like, "I gotta stop! I don't know why! I'm Joe Pesci!"
Um...
Uh, yeah. Is that all you want to do? Or is there something else you want to do?
Well...
I guess I'll, uh... I guess I'll fly 30 feet towards them.
Yeah, yeah, you fly 30 feet towards them. You fly towards them.
[laughter]
That way I can attack them next time.
Is he 30 feet away?
therefore okay okay it's a massive house
uh...
it
is there anything to do with the
you
so it was a big i guess it is a barn huh
the okay mass
and yes it you
you fly past all the way about the not a shredders done well for you
uh... yet you fly past all that shit
on which reminds me about
This really is the house of my imagination.
Okay, cool.
(laughter)
Okay, you fly, um...
Yeah, you fly a bit closer.
Uh, uh, uh...
You see Joe Pesci sort of looks up, he's like,
"You... you parrot, bitch!"
And like, uh, uh, roll again,
uh, uh, normal dog.
Another perception check? Yeah.
Please wake up. Please wake up.
I mean, the difficulty class gets lower and lower, so...
I got five again.
Okay.
Oh my god, you're so close to waking up.
Yeah, the dream of you eating that man's ass is just so vivid.
So the long guy in the back now.
The long guy?
The long, Mr. Long Guy.
Yeah, he walks up and sees you, Pleasant Parrot.
And let's see what he did.
He takes out what looks like...
I'm scared!
Okay, and he...
Okay.
Fuck yeah.
He takes out a staff.
And you can just make out now that he has some sort of like,
very gaunt looking face.
And he goes, "Ahh-HA!"
And he slams the staff on the ground.
And, uh, uh...
And nothing comes out.
And he's like, "Wha?"
And he just starts stabbing it on the ground.
and he's like looking inside, he's trying to see what happened.
And now Joe Pesci, Joe Pesci goes and Joe Pesci,
Joe Pesci is going to try to grab at you, Hungry Hamster.
And what is your AC, Hungry Hamster?
14. 14.
Okay. Yeah.
So he tries to grab at you and he just barely misses.
Like you use your wily dexterity to get out of the way.
Yeah, your tire framed to roll out of the way.
I'm gonna be like, "You son of a bitch!" and he's trying to grab at you.
Um, but it's now your turn, Hungry Hamster.
Alright, you know what?
While he's down there, round two.
Go to bite his nose off.
Okay, you're gonna do a bite?
Mm-hmm.
Go for it.
Roll a d20?
I'm gonna eat his nose.
Okay, I mean, so there's an attack for this.
Add two to whatever you just rolled.
Damn it.
Uh, that's gonna be eight.
Yeah, no, you go to try to bite his nose and you sort of like, you sort of like get your
first your little front teeth on his nose a little bit, but he's able to like go, "Wah!"
and like just like sort of shake you off.
Do I break skin?
No, you don't break skin.
Can I try one more time?
No, you cannot try one more time.
I'm hungry, man.
I need to eat his nose.
You cannot try to bite his nose again, but now it is, uh, roll perception again.
Please.
Guarantee I make it this time.
It's a normal dog.
To the top of the round.
And there's been some more activity.
14.
You finally, right when that man is about to,
it turns into your dad, I mean, he comes,
and then you wake up from the dream.
(laughing)
And you're sort of where the Pleasant Parrot was.
You see sort of the activity going on.
Roll for initiative now, so you can get into the order.
- 14.
- Okay, cool.
All right, cool.
So you're up, you sort of see, hmm?
You sort of see what's going on.
- Yeah.
And now it is still Pleasant Parrot, it's still your turn.
I just wake up confused? That's my whole turn?
Well it wasn't your turn, it was just you waking up and getting into the order.
You should have woke up earlier.
Yeah, I should have.
With a 14 though, you're going to go before a couple other people, so that's pretty good.
So you're up Pleasant Parrot.
Okay, I fly into Joe Pesci's face and I use my talons on him.
Do it. Roll a talons attack.
okay
that's a sixteen
yet that hits
so roll for damage alright that's
to d six yeah
so this is where we get those other guys from
well
mhm six of the six-sided
and we're not the same size it's confusing
you know the six in that bag
it's that's where is i mean it is part of the alleged one of mine
it's other
You should keep this part in.
I'll keep this part in.
Okay.
There we go.
Four plus
five, nine. Nice! Yeah.
So you just, uh,
so where are you digging your talons in? Describe what you're
doing.
I dig my talons into his nose
to flex
on hungry hamster.
Bitch, what's up?
You dig your talons into
his nose. How are you? I love you! Thank you! You're my best friend! And let's see what he's able to do. Yeah, he is able to, you take your
javelin out of his nose, you do nine damage, you puncture his nose, you're basically creating a
couple other nostrils, but he is able to shake you off his nose. He's like, "Oh my
god, my Italian nose!" And he's just bleeding out of his nose. He's like, "Ah,
fuck shit like you know cursing like Joe Pesci and yeah is there anything else you
want to do not much you can do but yeah I already moved and attacked right yeah
you're good so now this other guy this long guy now you're a lot closer because
now you're up on Joe Pesci's you jumped on Joe Pesci's nose you're sort of
flying at about head level this guy and you realize that it's Skeletor and
and he's gonna slam his staff on the ground again and just go "HA HA!" and it's
just like he's jamming on the ground and like he's just like smelling it he's
trying to figure out what's going on with his staff it's not working
yeah he's trying to figure out what's he's trying to figure out what's going
on with his staff okay and it is now uh uh uh
Jafar I loved your work as the evil genie I'm not Jafar it is now a normal dog
it's your turn you almost said Ray William Johnson I sure did I'm gonna I'm
gonna bite this long fella mm-hmm yeah so I roll 2d 8 yeah your your base
movement you're close enough to run up to him and bite him 6 plus 3 you got a
roll roll roll first so just roll your d20 god d20 plus that 18 yeah that's for
sure okay and now I roll 2d6s mm-hmm yes oh this is way worse and you have
advantage on this guy for the rest of the round because you're the first person
you attack okay that's part of your vicious so it's 2d8s plus 3 so it's 11
nice yeah you run up to this guy where do you where you bite on him he's the bite
because I want to pull his pants absolutely you bite around his bony
skeleton but he's like oh my goodness he man I assume yeah yeah you chomp on his
bony butt okay it tastes great can I pull his pants down as I'm doing it
absolutely roll a roll slight of hand slight of mouth see what you can do bite
of mouth and eight yeah you sort of start to tell you this robe a little bit but
it's like it doesn't quite go down yet yeah can't make sure to not kill him
until at least like two more turns and now it is Joe Pesci's turn and he is
going to ignore the hamster for now and he's gonna try to attack this bird that
just stabbed him in the nose. He was out of smoke. And what's your AC? 15. Okay yeah so he takes out his
gun and he shoots at you. What kind of gun is it? It's a 9/11 Kimber handgun.
1911 Kimber handgun and he does one damage to you.
Aww.
That's one tough bird.
Yeah.
He's like, "You son of a bitch bird!" and the...
Oh shit, I should roll again now.
Fuck, alright, yeah.
Okay, uh, moving on.
You are up, Hungy Hamster.
Alright.
Where's Joe Pesci right now?
Joe Pesci is still like right in front of you.
You're a little hamster.
more time.
You're trying to bite him?
I'm going to eat his fucking nose.
Do it.
Roll, because he's standing up now, so roll acrobatics to climb up his bod.
Okay.
So just a d20?
Mm-hmm.
Plus acrobatics.
Okay.
17 plus 4.
You're good.
Yeah, I get up there.
Okay, now roll an attack roll.
All right.
Do I add anything to this?
Yes, add.
19.
19, what do you, well, it doesn't matter.
I mean, you succeeded.
You did it.
For sure, you succeeded.
So now roll 2d6.
OK.
That's this one.
It's square, it's cube.
Oh, right.
No, I get it.
It's weird.
Two at the same time.
Two girls at the same time, brother.
Amazing.
Yeah.
So you run up and he's already like mangled nose and you just continue to gnaw at it.
You like, like trying to bite it off like that scene in Master Disguise.
And he's like, "Data Carvey, my worst enemy!" and you're just gnawing at his nose, you're
finding the little marks that the talons already made and just like making it a lot worse.
He's like, "Fuck, this is brutal."
- Oh man, I'm biting around.
- No, it's brutal.
- It's like amateur surgeon, I'm going around the thing, the lines, the dotted lines.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, you're just like, you're finding out where they are, you're using them
as sort of your guiding light for this attack.
Yes, you're all up on this guy's face. It's pretty bad, and it is now back to the top of the order
So it is your turn Pleasant Parrot
Okay, yeah, you got you got clip. You've got a little clipped
By a Kimber yeah going on pimp hmm
Let's see here
Should I try to love Serena
I mean, why not? I want to know what this shit happens.
Yeah, can I use defleer- defleernia?
Yes, you can. Give me one second.
The bullet made a big explosion in you.
Yeah, it exploded my ideas.
Okay. Of what to do. You can keep this in.
Of me looking up the table I made earlier.
He made a table. He made a table for your ability.
Are you flattered? Or are you a piece of shit? I'm scared.
All right, roll a d20 right now.
15.
Okay.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Okay, roll another d20.
Nine.
Okay.
Your eyes roll in the back of your head as,
and, hold on.
Okay.
I'm sorry, I'm doing a bunch of secret roles,
so the tension's here.
And you feel like a beam is shooting into your head
from nowhere, and out of your mouth,
you just start speaking in tongues.
You're (speaking in tongues)
And these two beams of pure acid shoot out of your eyes
and miss Joe Pesci, but melt a part of the kitchen. And now roll
one more d20. Plus your constitution saving throw.
Oh, no, that's a two.
Okay, cool. Yeah, you take two psychic damage from that.
That bad?
Yeah,
you became unpleasant.
Yeah, okay. Yeah. So, um, uh, there are, I'm going to tell you
as a friendly DM, there are two ways that the CIA can figure out
where you are. So, so far you're okay. Yeah. The other way that
the CIA, yeah. Yeah, man, I'm a pleasant parrot on the outside,
but I got another side to me. Yeah. I've known Cameron for
actually many years now. And, um, what I know about him is that
he has a really dark side. An evil side. An evil side that's dark and scary and so I
wanted to make sure. You know when someone's trying to hurt my homies it
brings the bad me out. Yeah Cameron's a little bit of a bad boy. They tried to get with
Patrick and he turned to a savage. Yeah so when that happens though you hear
Chope as you go "Holy shit!" He takes 100 points of fear damage. That just means he
His pants like a hundred points of poop damage. Ask me
It is now Skeletor's turn
But before I do that throw one other role
Okay. Yeah, so okay. So all right Skeletor's first though
Before what just happened happened and Skeletor once again is gonna try to activate his staff and this time use it on you
Normal dog since you fucked up his ass real nasty. I'm gonna do it again. He's not careful. Yeah. Yeah, he he
Stabs a staff on the ground and you see a
to
Two sort of orbs shoot out and they shoot out towards you
But you're able to like just easily dodge them out of the way you see
What?
And
You also hear downstairs you hear some noise now
It sounds like a guy with a bunch of knives is walking through his own house
You hear that a little bit, but now it is
Your turn normal dog. I try pull his pants down all right go for it roll a attack roll
Just straight attack roll add strength. That's just a d20. Yeah, that's right
16 yeah his pants come down. I like his butthole
Is he bones under it I'm I do I let you lick his butthole - is that count as another action?
Yeah, that's a bonus action you like his butthole yeah, and he's like oh god he man
It's like fucking milk
Strong bones on this boy's ass tastes like milk. Yeah, you're looking at milk. Yeah doing no damage to this turn
It's more of an intimidation thing than anything.
You know what?
Roll intimidation.
That's crazy.
Yeah!
You know what?
Roll intimidation.
That's a good idea.
I don't give a fuck.
Okay.
It's just video games.
Patches is that crazy ass DM.
I'm that crazy ass DM white boy.
Crazy ass DM that'll make you roll your shit.
Eleven.
Okay, yeah, no, he's more pleased than intimidated.
Yeah, but you don't really like it that much, do you?
Of course I like it!
This is my thing!
like that other guy who went to jail I'm already down here I already lost the
skeletal voice okay hmm I'm already down here he's also can understand the dog
yeah um and all these bones yeah it is now it is now Joe Pesci's turn and he's
feeling pretty demoralized so he's gonna put the gun right at you hungry hamster
that's where you are so you son of a bitch pull the trigger you coward yeah yeah
yo this nose about to come off bitch what you doing okay he shoots it just missing
you and Phineas gauging himself fuck it up his cheek he takes a couple more
points damage he's not looking too good you're still like hanging on his nose
while your teeth swinging back and forth.
And it's now your turn.
Rip it off.
Yeah, that's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna rip it off and if I do it well enough,
I'm gonna do backflip.
Just to be cool.
That's five.
You try to bite his nose again and you just bite
like if there's a perfect hole in it now and she just chomped between the hole
like you don't like there's an apple bite sound effect so yeah yeah so do I still
do damage or no it's just sort of like you just taste a little higher you suck
it's not a prank you've done oh my god you like doing that at this point you
just kind of like it no no bacteria if you do it again you're gonna get
addicted no way yeah I forgot there's another addiction system in this case
it's a licking asshole I'm just so glad I get to hang out with you guys and okay
top of the order and now you see a coming from the the the metal work you see it
looks like shredder uncle shredder he's like oh god and he takes out a sword and
he swings it at Skeletor that never happened to me before okay sorry
privacy screen covering patches so we don't know what happened also it rolled
like in between the dice rolling like platform I have in the DM screen so it
just was like hanging no one cares um yeah he fucking chops Skeletor dealing
seven points of damage just fucking like slices at his arm and he looks down at
you normal those good job you got his weak spot and a sculptor is not looking
ideal it is now your turn pleasant parrot I'm gonna fly into the hole and Joe
Pesci's nose fuck yeah is that gonna be a peck attack yeah do it
15 that's yeah it's gonna hit roll for damage 1d 6 plus 4 8 okay just describe
your KO on Joe Pesci it's not a kill not yet okay I fly it my head
fits like directly into the hole in his nose and it plugs his nose and he can't
breathe because he can't breathe through his mouth medically that's just the
thing Patrick didn't mention about the care yes sorry yeah so yeah so yeah so
why all Italians sound like yeah yeah the opposite of mouth yeah yeah yeah so
my head is just is just perfectly plugging his nose and he just passes out
oh yeah yeah he's like it was enraging bowl and he just falls falls to the
floor passed out yeah I'm still stuck in the hole though yeah you're just like
face up in the hole like your little tail and it is now Skeletor's turn he's
gonna try to turn around and hit Shredder okay he hits as he turns around
my head and body moves with his ass like a tail yeah that's like literally what
happens and yes shredder gets hit by these like strange orbs again he seems
okay but he seems like he's brushing it off but it looks like it bruised him a
little bit and now it is your turn normal dog I guess I bite his asshole
yeah absolutely do it with advantage since you've been licking it yeah it's
like locking on so first an attack roll mm-hmm
that was a 12 oh you also have an advantage anyway because you attacked
him first keep going though oh yeah so do I do another d20 yeah 18 yeah it's and
then doing it on the floor so you can feel 11 damage 11 damage Jesus okay all
right yeah describe for you how you a ko Skeletor I came I KO him you KO him okay
I stick my tongue all the way up his asshole.
- You can describe this as a bite.
- Through his mouth.
- Okay.
- I bite him first.
(laughing)
And I stick my tongue all the way through his asshole
and then it goes all the way to his mouth
and then I use my tongue as leverage
to make his mouth say, "I'm knocked out."
(laughing)
- Okay, yeah.
- And then he goes to sleep.
- Yeah, his non-existent eyes roll in the back of his head
and he falls over and he like hits the ground
and becomes like a, like it sounds like a bowling pin
is knocking over.
(crashing)
And then I go back to just normal licking his ass.
Yeah.
Yeah, so now...
He hits the ground and as his bones fall it plays Twinkle Twinkle Little Star on xylophone.
Yeah, so now the scene is like bloody beak, bloody hamster mouth, a dog with a tongue full of bone ass.
With a poop ring around his mouth.
Yeah, and Shredder is looking at this and he's like, "I've seen this before."
And he comes down, he kneels down to all of you, and he tries his best to like explain to you all.
We can say, "You need to all leave from here. Look, I can get you guys out of here real fast."
Like, okay. And he sort of leads you all outside and he shows you a motorcycle with two side cars
that are made for animals. One of the side cars is a hamster ball.
Yeah. Yes. And he's like, and he's like, he's like, "You guys got to get out of here. Okay?
The cops are not gonna like this. I can't have this heat on me. I don't want this heat on you.
Go. Go to Duluth. That's where your family is.
Duluth?
Duluth.
Okay.
Minnesota.
Or Wisconsin.
Where are we?
We're somewhere near Chicago.
Okay.
I don't know why I can understand you, but I can.
Please, fly, my children.
What about the bike?
I don't need this bike
Now we gotta fly which one of us drives a bike though. Yeah
Animals I'll pedal it. It's not one of those bikes is it? Well, there's a motor for us. How we even gonna help?
You just fly. Yeah, you don't need to be on it. I think I think I should get both the seats
Okay. Yeah, so
Can you put some candy in the sidecar?
Absolutely, and he brings out knife candy and he puts in the sidecar. This is again my favorite!
Yeah, so you guys are you guys gonna take his bike and his two sidecars?
Hell yeah! There's candy in it. There sure is. Yeah. Yeah, okay.
And so now you're on the road to look for your family.
[music]
[MUSIC]