Come here come here come here. Let me see your butt
What the fuck is up
Hi
We are so glad to not be in Fort Worth right now. Oh my god yesterday
We opened for a Led Zeppelin cover band. Yeah, not a joke. We opened for a fucking Led Zeppelin cover band named so so
Show went well. I was gonna go nuclear option and say Google Laurie Maddox, but
Didn't have to do that
Yeah, I've never opened for a Led Zeppelin cover band before I think it may we just start playing Led Zeppelin music just on stage
Yeah, before they go up. They were so good though. They were fucking
They were so sick. They were so good.
We did the show in Fort Worth and the guy was like,
he was like, "Dude, that was great. That was such a great show."
And it was so great.
You guys can like stay for the Led Zeppelin band for free if you want to.
I really wish we did.
We should have, yeah.
I wanted to share a green room with them like so bad.
Me too.
They would walk by and like look in and just be like, "No."
There was a guy with, he had like bright green hair and a motorhead shirt on
And he kept like dropping every drum. He picked up like you pick up a piece of a drum to just break it
Yeah, he was fucking awesome. It was really cool sick. Yeah, we like Austin a lot more. I'm really glad you guys came out
Thank you. Yeah
For keeping it weird yeah, it is I did notice. It's a bit weird here
There's a kind of a weird vibe.
I'm seeing some odd people with funny shirts on.
Seriously, some funny shirts and some odd hats.
Yeah, yeah.
Maybe, yeah, kind of baseball or dad hat style.
Yeah, why would you wear that? And big pants too.
What's going on in this weird-ass city?
Yeah, that's weird.
[laughter]
That's really weird.
Pat's been on a bit of a shopping spree during this whole tour.
Oh yeah, yeah I have been.
What are the things you bought?
I bought, well, so the venue we went to yesterday was downwind from the Dickies factory.
I could smell the pants.
I could, oh, I sniffed them out.
I sniffed them out almost immediately.
It was, I bought some really big shorts yesterday.
Some terrible birth defects in the communities downwind from the Dickies factory.
Yeah, they're all wearing coveralls and shit.
Yeah, but I made us go 20 minutes out of the way getting here because I found it.
Do you know what the whole shebang is?
The whole shebang is a type of chip they only sell at this specific private prison.
So they make like three types of chips.
There's like whole shebang, there's like whole shebang fully loaded and then there's these
ones here which are called delicious.
>> Really? >> Yeah.
>> Let me see those. >> I figured make it special.
>> Live taste test. >> Do you want a live delicious chip taste
test? >> I've done it enough on the show.
>> What's on the side? >> It says chips original flavor.
>> It says chips original flavor and it also says ingredients.
says ingredients. >> Well, fuck, pop them open. I'm hungry.
>> Yeah. >> Here. I'll hold your mic for you.
>> Okay. Thank you. >> Oh, my God!
>> I really thought that was going to jump out into the audience.
>> I thought that was going to do a lot better. >> I really thought that was going to kill
somebody. >> I thought it was going to pop out.
>> It's going to be awesome. Somebody is going to have the snake with them. They get to take
it home. >> It's going to fly into the ceiling.
>> I thought it was going to fly way higher. >> Going to shoot a hole right in the ceiling.
>> Whoa! How weak are you in ways? >> We had a whole joke written about how it's
the only joke we wrote. And now it's ruined. Why even do it? I don't know.
>> Well, that's the end of the show. >> Thank you. Good night.
>> We are doing a list. We're going to do the podcast actually. We're not just going to do
props. No, that's for the Vegas show. We're opening for Carrot Top, very big.
We're doing it for six months straight, that's all we have. Yeah, we're doing the thing that
bands on tour do where they share gear. We're sharing all of Carrot Top's props.
Yeah, that was one of them. That was one of his props, the snake in the gym. He updated it for
the modern era because no one's buying peanut brittle anymore. Yeah, so we're
doing a list and we actually do have a special guest with us. You
may be familiar with him. He was just on stage. Please give it up for Pierce Campion everybody!
Keep it going for Pierce! Keep it going for Pierce! He's from before! Hi! Hi Pierce! Turn
his mic on please, hi! Hi Pierce! Yeah! How do you like Austin so far? This is awesome!
That? I don't think that was here before us.
This is my favorite city I've been to.
You think it's... okay.
Dude, I wish that they sold those in prison.
Me too. Those people deserve one more thing bad happening to them.
If you ask me.
I wish the snake was real.
Yeah.
So, we're doing a list today.
People in prison should just get pranked.
That should be the whole sentence.
Maybe you should have an option to do half as much time,
but you get pranked at least once per day.
If you get pranked every day.
Like you'll just open a door to the bathroom,
you've been fucking stamping license plates for 19 hours.
Caleb, I do think a lot of people get really badly pranked in prison
when they go in the bathroom.
It's so interesting.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Prisoners prank each other. Can you imagine such a thing?
They don't even get paid to do it.
They do it for the love of the game.
Well then, all is well in this beautiful world.
I'm fine with it then.
Yeah, we're doing a list today.
It's called Top 10 Deadliest Big Cats from thetop10s.com.
you guys like big cats or something what's going on with you
across america europe asia and africa all over the world the top ten deadliest of
the amazing family the big cats
i would say the uh... kennedy's might be the most amazing family personal
well okay i might say the card action s
uh... all right so number one here
bengal tiger
yeah okay
what i think
uh...
It's orange, right?
Why did you pick this list?
I picked it because...
Tiger, biggest cat on earth, very agile, fast enough to hunt in wild, thunderously striking,
fearless roar of tiger, often used for voiceover of lion in cinema.
His most scaring noise can hunt anything that come before him, live lonely while lion hunt
with its pride.
Most sharp teeth and strong jaws, tear off easily, fur of brown bear or lion.
My favorite tiger.
Wow.
Fur.
Yeah.
of people who feel really really strongly about a lot of different big cats. I had
no idea. I didn't either. I don't think I've ever even seen a big cat in person.
I've seen, yeah you did. We went to alligator adventure. Did they have a lion there?
They had a bobcat. I thought they had alligators there. A bobcat barely counts as a big cat.
That's a big cat. That's a medium cat. A bobcat's a big cat. Well fuck you, no a bobcat is a big cat.
It's a medium cat. It's three versus one little guy. That's bigger than a house cat. What are you
talking that doesn't mean it's a big cat is a small... fuck. Would you call Garfield a big cat?
No it's not real. He's bigger than a house cat though. A house cat is a small cat. Yep. What about a dog? Would you call that bigger?
A big cat? No it's not a cat. Bigger than a house cat though. What about a giant rock? Would you call that a big cat?
You probably would. Yeah a bear. Yeah what about a bear? What about a cat the size of the universe?
Yeah that's a big cat. That is actually a huge cat. That is probably the biggest cat ever.
I don't count a bobcat or a lynx. Those aren't big cats. Yeah I don't think I would count them either.
>> Then you're stupid. >> Huh?
>> The beast! >> Sorry. The beast.
>> The beast. >> That's a comment on tiger?
>> The beast. >> Okay.
>> Yeah. The beast. I don't know if they're trying to say the beast or the best.
>> I didn't even consider that. >> Could be both.
>> The beast. It's funny. Bengal tiger kill many people. In British India, one female
tiger killed 400,000 people. They are deadly as cats. They can easily kill a lion. Lion
is a baby in front of Tiger. Learn something new every day. I didn't realize 400,000 people.
400,000 people. One tiger. The same tiger? It was one female tiger. One female tiger killed
400,000 people. They're so awesome and strong they can kill the tiger equivalent of a baby.
That's true. That's a good point. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Actually that's really logical of you.
Yeah. Yeah. We need you for the logic. Right. It's actually not impressive if you can kill
a baby. Even a baby lion? If you're a tiger, it don't matter. It says lion is a baby in
front of tiger. Right. So to a tiger, killing a lion is killing a baby. Oh, yeah, it's not
that impressive. It's cruel. Yeah, it's actually really mean. Thank God they don't do it. It's
like doing a backflip for tigers. I think doing a backflip is harder than killing a
a baby. Like a human doing a back flip is like. Listen, I could not do a back flip. I could
probably kill like a hundred babies in a minute. I'm just, I'm trying to find an equipment here.
If there are babies above you and below you. If I had some kind of machine that I don't
have. Um, two lion. Yeah, the lion. Some woos and some boos. Some tiger fans, I mean it's
>> Very polarizing. >> Controversial list.
>> What's this legal tigers, what's this fucking, I keep seeing these billboards that say like
law tigers. Yeah. >> Was it illegal to be a tiger at one point?
>> Oh, okay. >> I keep seeing, you know what? I saw that
in Virginia. That's not here. I love loin. I do too. Please vote for the king, I am just
a child. He wishes he could do more. He wishes he could be out on the street corner. He's
not old enough to vote for it. Yeah, that's exactly. That's really rough. But when he
grows up. He'll vote for loin. It's going to tip the scales. Lion's going to be number
1, not tiger. Disgusting Bengal tiger. Lions are born killers and will always be killers.
My most favorite movie is a Lion King movie called The Lion King 1, 2, 3 by Rahul S. the
Dinosaur Boy. I think the Dinosaur Boy might be number 1 deadliest. Yeah. That's all the
evil in a dinosaur and in man yeah yeah that's that I mean it's not a cat but if
it was a dinosaur cat boy yeah that'd be really it might be really deadly and
terrible who will name Rahul I feel like if you're a lion fan you have to hate
Lion King mm-hmm cuz that's why cuz they talk they eat all kinds of they love
little toys did you guys think that Nala from the Lion King was really attractive
growing up? Yes. I actually rooted for Simba. You are fucked up beyond all repair. No, I
rooted for him to get Nala. Should I have rooted for myself instead? You thought I had
a cuck fantasy. Yeah. What's the S in Rahul's last name? Stegosaurus? I don't think it's
>> I want to go over there with them for the rest of the show.
Number three is Siberian tiger, different tiger.
>> Yep.
>> Looks the same to me.
I don't know.
>> No, actually there's snow in front of it.
>> Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that's a good point.
>> That's just the projection.
>> I like this tiger.
Third place is great.
I'm glad first place is a tiger.
I love them.
Go, go, tiger.
So nice and sweet.
That one's just nice.
>> Yeah, that is very sweet.
>> Made me smile when I read it.
Also this one.
the tiger is 500 times stronger than a car. >> What proof? A car?
>> What proof do you have? >> I feel like if you hit a tiger with your
car ‑‑ >> If you hit 499 tigers with your car, your
car would break. >> I think the 500 ‑‑
>> If 499 cars hit a tiger, they would all break. But if 500 hit a tiger, they would both
break. Okay. Now I get it. I get it now. I love it. I can watch you two do math all fucking
day. I can just sit here. I'm actually like so good at math. I can tell. Four. That's
what comes after three. Oh my god. Jaguar. It's looking at you guys. It's coming for
you after the show. I hope nobody hears a bad weather. It should have been a jaguar,
hotter. Oh yeah. Or a house cat. Or a woman. What? What's, yeah, the thing that lives with
you, what's sexier than that? That's a very good point. You covet what you see every day
folks. Especially when it's showing off like that. I just saw a video of a jaguar jumping
into the river, going underwater, snatching up a crocodile and dragging back up out of
the water and into the jungle. A crocodile has to be one of the top ten baddest water
animals and a jaguar went to his turf and won and it's like it wasn't even a big deal for
the jaguar. Me and my friends used to argue who would win in a fight, Superman or the
Hulk but now we all agree that if we watch them fight a jaguar would just jump in and
snatch them up and drag them off into the jungle. I don't believe that. The scenario
is so funny to me that you're imagining a fight between Spiderman or yeah, Superman and
the Hulk and your friend's like no a jaguar would just come out and eat them both. Yeah
those two characters are fighting next to a jungle.
Yeah.
Just outside.
It's the same as saying like, like Spider-Man versus Batman,
but the police would stop them.
Yeah, exactly.
Obviously, the police would win the fight.
Yeah, yeah.
Then we got--
Which they would.
And also they should, like, I don't
know why they let them do that.
Yeah, it's actually really not nice.
This baby has something we call total control overnight.
I had no idea.
I say that all the time.
Five, Liger.
>> That's a cheat code on them. >> Yeah. So it's a crossbreed I guess between
a lion and a tiger and as this person says, it halved tiger, halved lion. And I don't like
crossbreeding but the ligerism makes them my favorite animals.
>> I think you should analyze that. >> I want to hear more from this person.
>> Yeah. >> But you don't have anything from them?
>> We don't have anything from them. A most moronic animal.
>> Come on. He's out there trying his best. >> Yeah, he can't help it.
>> Yeah, he can't help it. He's a freak. They're infertile, right?
>> Yeah, I think so. >> Ligers?
>> Yeah, I don't know. >> I saw a liger when I was a kid. They had
one of like a renaissance. Yeah, I saw Napoleon Dynamite II. I saw a real liger.
>> You said you saw the liger? >> I saw a liger. I don't think there are
that many of them though, although that could have just been something they said at the
renaissance fair. I think it's like blimps, I think there's like three in the US. It was
so fucking big, it was probably like ten feet long. Do you think the lion, is the lion,
it stood up on a ladder. What's up? Did it juggle? What? Did it juggle? No. Did it eat
something? There was a guy who juggled, but it was separate. I don't believe you saw a
liger at the renaissance. They probably said it was a liger. It probably was. I was a child.
Yeah. So it was big and you were a child. They called it a liger.
Okay. They said this was a liger. Do you think the lion is like stoked to fuck the
tiger? Maybe. Yeah.
Um. Yeah. They're never going to do that unless we make them do it. Right?
Yeah. So they might be like, well, fuck. I guess they probably don't cross paths
that often in the wild. Do you think, okay, well, do you think the mom
Was a lion well so the dad's the lion the dad has the head the cool hair yeah
So what if okay, so here's what I'm thinking they probably painted the lion
No, cuz feet okay hold on what I forgot no
I forgot what it looked like I thought they would paint the lion to look like a tiger no
They put a wig on the on the tiger. I think I think that's how they you're getting hung up on
Which one is the boy and girl it doesn't I don't think it matters. I'm not sure I think it matters
I think it matters a little bit. I don't know if it matters at all.
But I think what does matter is whether or not they painted them.
Yeah, I think it might be easier to paint a tiger.
Because it's just one dip. You could dunk them. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's actually such a good point.
Number six is a snow leopard. Great.
A lot of snow leopard fans here.
You guys love every cat. Yeah, what's up with it? All right.
>> Snow leopard mostly live in snow. Just a little background information for you guys
about the snow leopard. Same as leopard because same spot.
>> Again, another important fact. >> Another really good point that I didn't
think about before I was looking at this list. But number 7 is normal leopard.
>> Boo! >> Nothing but normal leopard.
>> Fuck this leopard. >> It's a less cool snow leopard, I have to
say but this person says, leopards are very fast, dangerous, smart, clever and cunning.
They have no respect for lions. They are found in most of the places. They are mostly night
hunters. They have very sharp teeth. If it attacks you, won't survive. In fact, journal
will die in few seconds. Mostly they are not afraid of bears. They attack gorillas but
nothing can kill them. They have a good power of smelling and has a sixth sense. They have
very deadly nails. They can attack four people at a time. They are good swimmers, excellent
climbers and best hunters. >> What's the sixth sense?
Telepathy, I think.
Oh, okay.
It might be telepathy, yeah.
That makes sense.
Yeah, it could either be telepathy or maybe cat sense.
I would say the cat sense, yeah.
Whiskers.
Whiskers might be whiskers.
The sixth sense is whiskers.
I like that it can attack four people at a time.
Let's do it.
Yeah, it's like the...
Let's go, there's a zoo here, right?
Let's get a leopard in here right now.
Mythbusters, we should reboot Mythbusters.
Trust me, I would take one down.
Every myth is, "Can an animal attack four guys at a time?"
It's just us four walking into an animal's cage.
No, we only got two.
It doesn't say it can win against four people.
That's true. It says it can't attack.
I can attack four guys, you four.
It's because it has four legs.
Yeah, it just spreads out like this.
Yeah, as long as the...
It can jump up and do like a matrix kick.
Yes.
Yeah, but with all four legs.
It's like the Mike V of animals.
Oh, okay.
That I... There's one person who laughed, thank God.
That's all I needed.
Number eight is a different kind of leopard I never heard of.
of an Amer leopard. >> That's not real.
>> I don't know. Might not be real. I'm not sure. But they say, I think they are the most
dangerous cats on the planet. Even though they are endangered, they still have the same
right to earn a top place. I read online and saw a picture that an Amer leopard killed
15 birds, five wild cats and two humans. Trying to make the third.
>> Let's make it three tonight. Let's go. >> I misread that. I thought that it attacked
two humans fucking. I thought it was they attacked two humans. I like that it's ambiguous whether
the leopard was trying to kill a third person or if this guy really wants to get killed by
a leopard. Yeah. I'm trying to make it a third. He's talking about how many kids he's had.
He's like two, going for three, I don't know. We'll try it out. I don't like this leopard.
Yeah.
I don't either.
It attacked two people trying to make a third.
Leave them alone.
Number nine is Cougar.
Yeah.
Yeah, these are pretty cool.
I don't know.
Was responsible for Feathertail's death.
Rose Weasley.
Who's Feathertail?
Don't know.
Warrior Cats.
What's Warrior Cats?
Oh, he doesn't know Warrior Cats.
What the fuck are you?
You're making shit up.
Did you write this?
(laughter)
(audience member speaks)
- Oh, that furries were--
- I don't think they turned,
I think they were born that way.
- I thought concussions turned people into furries.
(laughter)
I didn't know it was a book.
- Or poor home life.
- Yeah.
- I thought divorce made people furries, not books.
- I thought it might be poor boundaries with pets.
- Yeah, that too, probably.
- That turned people into furries.
Poop, they poop a lot, that's what I think, ha ha.
- Yeah, true.
probably true number 10 smilodon what that is a saber-toothed tiger it's an
extinct big cat this isn't real now this is not really was real it's not real
anymore now you have to draw a line somewhere cuz if you can just add stuff
that's not real do you say you have to draw a line somewhere no let's go the
The Smilodons are probably extinct because they killed sometimes their own kind.
If you look O images of them most look very unfriendly, so I am Hwessing the Smilodon as
most dangerous cat.
That's Hussein.
Hussein.
So I am Hussein.
I am Hussein, the Smilodon is most dangerous cat.
Can't be that deadly, it's extinct, LOL.
That ain't nice brother.
That is kind of fucked up.
Yeah it is, it is kind of rude.
I think they were very deadly back in the day probably.
I don't know.
Is that not the same thing as a saber tooth?
I think it's the same thing.
From the Ice Age movies?
I think saber tooth...
Yeah, that's Dennis Leary.
I think saber tooth tiger is like a colloquial name.
Because Smilodon wasn't like good enough?
That's the best name I've ever heard.
It's a cool name, yeah.
Because it makes me think it smiles.
It kind of does.
Okay, so this is the contenders, the ones that didn't make the top ten.
There's a few of these here.
Number 12, the cheetah.
Cheetahs are beautiful, lovely creatures.
My friend and I are both very fast.
Therefore, Cheetah is our shared nickname.
Does that mean there's Cheetah when it's the two of them?
Yeah, but if it's only one of them, they don't say anything.
You can't say, yeah.
There's Debbie.
Fast Debbie.
She's fast, but if she was with her friend, they would be Cheetah.
Yeah, she's fast by herself, but you should see her be Cheetah with one other guy.
That would be awesome.
They get into like a Cheetah costume.
It's like one half.
Oh yeah, yeah.
It's like one of the horse costumes.
Yeah.
Number 13 is Tigon.
These only exist if it's a female. The males are ligers.
If I'm wrong, these don't exist.
My dad's an animal sensitist.
I believe them.
Yeah. I think this person might be an animal scientist, too.
- Yeah. - Sensitist.
- Sensitist, yeah. It's different. - Sensitist.
Yeah. It's someone who's sincerely interested in animals.
Number 16 is Jaglion.
A hybrid between a jaguar and a lion, a very, very strong cat.
strong cat. Sounds interesting. Suck me off! >> Yeah.
>> Suck me off! >> That's just rude.
>> Are they saying suck me off like this would never fucking exist.
>> What I want to know is why somebody went on this list, scrolled all the way down to
number 16 before commenting suck me off. You could have done it right at the top.
>> Do it at the first two, yeah. >> What is it about jag lion that makes you
want to get sucked off. >> Because you're jagging your line.
>> That's a really good point. >> Because you're jagging your line off.
>> And they're like suck me off. >> Number 19 is saber tooth cat. These aren't
cats. Sorry on top tens it's hard to get the period key on the keyboard to work so I use
exclamation points. They're not cats. I looked it up too.
Isn't that only use one exclamation point they'll use to
Better math it's Caleb was better math. Not me. He can't even get to - he's very stupid. Yeah, you're not gonna clap for me
Okay, fine
Yeah
That happened nowhere stupid that was crazy. Oh my god. All right this next one's the last one
But it's probably my favorite one on here. Is it white tiger? What is it?
Guessing I that was my first guess
Stop stop. Okay. Okay. Wait, actually you get one more guess. Yeah, one more guess. You're not gonna I promise you won't guess what it is
black panther oh
No wrong. Okay, here it is. Number 20 is giant cheetah
People you need to stop adding random cast of this list. There is no such thing as a giant cheetah
There is a giant cheetah search it up. No giant cheetahs exist
There is giant cheetahs check your facts check in the net you people yeah, it's fake
There's no such thing as a giant really I was I got so excited
I really my heart skipped a beat well the biggest cheetah in the but that's like a
Like there's if there's like a record for like biggest I'll say it every fucking cheat is giant to me. Yeah, also that
Cheetahs actually aren't that big so you must be really small. I think maybe the coolest the coolest cats actually probably the blue blue line
I feel like that I think that blue lion might have been on there and I just
didn't put it in because there was definitely there was a bunch of ones
like this they were like yeah the crazy lion the evil tiger you run out of cats
pretty fast yeah there are only so many yeah yeah but so that's that's the list
that's the list everybody everyone makes it a round of applause for Pierce please
thank you for coming yeah what's happening for me come here come in let
me see your butt
monster
how's everyone what's up Chicago how are y'all doing excited to be here excited
this is that's you we're very excited we made some big changes I got a haircut
cut yeah check this out
dude bend over bend over show him show him the whole thing
i don't need that i don't need it anymore just look at that
check that out hey do you guys think he looks like eminem
just like he looks just like eminem i look like b rabbit
i bleached that this morning he did it's sick dude
it's completely bright orange turn that way i i missed right here
He missed a big spot.
Yeah.
You look like a scary older man at a Brockhampton concert.
[laughter]
I feel like a rapper.
[imitates rap music]
Damn.
You just got dissed.
[laughter]
Fuck, dude.
Couldn't even hear him. He's the fastest rapper in the world.
That's a good idea.
You'd be the best battle rapper ever because you rap so fast.
They don't know if it was good or bad.
They gotta slow it down. It's like that guy from the Micro Machines commercials.
Who's old here?
[laughter]
Who's the oldest person here?
What are you talking about?
It's, I, you know, it would be fast.
I love the eighties on VH1.
It'd be like, you're like, you're like a samurai
where you you're doing a battle rap.
You hold the mic up to your mouth and then nothing happens.
You put it down and then all the rap comes out
after you put it down really fast.
The screen flashes red.
That's smart.
Yeah.
Yeah. They'd have to slow it down
to even know what I'm talking about.
So they might just declare me the winner at the battle
before they even listen.
Well, he's probably.
All they'll have, they have to like go to the back room.
Like they have to, they have to like rewind.
Yeah, big referee comes out. I have to hear what he just said.
They're like circling your mouth with like an arrow.
It's an instant replay of the projectile, like the path of my
tongue.
Yeah, like a golf ball.
Well, at this point in the rap, he said that his mom was gay.
They weren't supposed to hear that part.
That was supposed to be mixed in.
Oh, man.
We came here to rap.
Yeah, we're mostly here to rap.
We hear this is a great rapping show.
Yeah. Yeah. So we're excited. I ate an Italian beef last night.
We went to Portillo's. I had so much diarrhea.
Is that like a good place?
Yes!
Because I feel like fucking shit.
[laughter]
I feel... It was so... It was perfect, but I'm paying for it.
Yeah, it was a bad decision.
Yeah, I know. I'm feeling really, really bad.
And then they had the gall to put hot peppers on top of it, too.
I was like, I'm already eating two whole cows in one sandwich.
Yeah. Yeah.
this is bad
i think that also maybe you feeling bad might be because you're in a closed
bathroom with fumes for an hour i don't think that was it i don't think uh...
i did have a tied trash bag on my head to keep the bleach from getting anywhere
uh... my mouth was in the trash bag
as the bleach is sitting on my scalp it was a full trash bag
i forgot you're supposed to get like a shower cap or something
not for me i had a walgreens bag
yeah no it wasn't it was a it was a green bag
it was i was worried that the bag the dive from the bag
the only other thing i would rather bag it had a green bag they don't have a
green bags and walgreens thanks i don't like it with ball greens pretty thankful
to have a green bag and what a great true
yeah that's a good fucker not answering you
uh... much we had to hop into the list unity uh... uh... yeah i guess we have
anything else we are talking about
i don't know
do you have any anybody else and i think we need to talk about
that i think we can do the show i think that's a lot of our we got a list
everybody
we're gonna do it for real others and we're saying worse last name after did
this and me and can i have a scene of the other side made this morning
yeah
uh... when you hear me the quicker okay here you go
right uh... are you know how to use it you just press the next but i guess it's
uh... cool
so who did this one
I don't think it's not. Is there is it not working? It's not going to read to 80%
of the people in the room. Pat, you're putting a green light on my. Yeah. All
right, then move. It didn't even read to me. And you guys see this, this crass
thing. He's doing has a green laser in it. Yeah. Holy shit. No, but seriously,
what is that? Where did that thing go? No, where does that though? What is it?
Let me grab. Let me hold on. Wait, where'd it go? I don't know. Where is it?
It's right here. It's right here. It's, um, can you get that?
He got it.
So this is the top 10 worst last names. Uh, so number one here is,
uh, I mean, I feel like this is probably obvious. Okay.
Uh, Bieber. Yeah. Yeah.
Yo shots fired. Um, I don't know if we got, got any believers in Chicago. Is he?
Yeah, I know. I think he was born here.
Well, is he? He was?
I think.
She was?
Damn.
That's right.
That's right, dude.
No, thank you.
So, first one is Bieber.
Here's what somebody had to say about this.
"Yuck, this reminds me of Justin Bieber. Too much."
And, "I think he sings like a little girl."
I think maybe Caleb wrote that.
I know.
I didn't because it would have sounded like...
Due to my rap ability.
You know anything that reminds me of Justin Bieber reminds me of Justin
Bieber too much. Am I right? That's right. Yeah, fuck you. I do like that.
They didn't think immediately like oh yeah,
it's not that's not who this is named after right off the bat. This is not
who it's about. I got this reminds me too much of him
that couldn't be him. There's not another Bieber that I know of except for
his hot mom. His
does he have a mom and his and his wife.
She at least acts hot.
Yo, imagine marrying Justin Bieber and taking his name.
Hell no, it couldn't be me.
That's right.
Worst last name ever.
Number one, it's on the list.
Yeah, it's the number one worst last name.
That's the only reason I wouldn't marry you, you fucking beautiful ass.
Yours too.
Here's something somebody else said.
I think someone is called Jamela Bieber.
Not the best name to have.
Ha!
They're right.
I think Jamela Bieber might be the best name to have.
I disagree.
It's got the...
I think maybe a little better.
His name was Jamila Bieber.
We would probably be doing Lincoln Hall instead of Shoebus.
[laughter]
We'd probably be doing the freakin' bean.
Yeah.
That's right.
You guys know the bean?
Yeah!
The bean!
Yeah, that thing is awesome.
What is there to say? It's a perfect thing.
It's big, it's round.
You can see your mom, but she looks 30% fatter in it.
Uh-huh.
It's fuckin' cool.
still haven't seen it. >> What were you expecting to get for that?
>> I was expecting a sympathetic -- >> The entire crowd --
>> I was expecting the entire crowd at unison to say go see the bean.
>> See the bean. >> See the bean.
>> Okay. >> Bitch ass.
>> You guys have malleable brains. >> Next one here.
>> I'm still not sure how to pronounce it. >> Bi-aber?
be Iber be Iber be Iber be Iber a be up your something like that yeah
something along so that was the last of the way you the way you pronounce it is
paper, because that's how he sounds okay. That's fucking fire plus that's gay to
sound like that yeah yeah I'm have to add you to my rap crew. Yeah, that
sounds fun, so the next one, not you, you're not. I know I'm just saying it
sounds fun. Yeah, the next next worst last name any guesses
>> We're starting really high. >> Bieber's number one.
>> Hitler! >> Yeah.
>> You guys are cheering for Hitler, yo.
>> What the hell was that? >> What the fuck is wrong with this city?
>> What the fuck is wrong with you guys?
>> You immediately -- >> We're releasing only that clip.
>> Yeah. >> You guys are not us.
>> Yes. >> Individually we're going to January 6th
you, we're going to fucking -- >> Go to their house.
>> Full combat gear at their house. >> Each one of your houses.
>> I call being the shaman. >> So the first comment here, I feel so sorry
for any Germans who have this as a first name or a last name.
No I feel sorry for anyone who has this for a first name or a last name.
And then another comment here, anyone with this name would be taken as a joke because
he has a he was a German dictator during World War Two. This last
name is just sad.
Hitler is a first name. I think we can say now just from this
list. The worst name possible is Hitler Bieber.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's because I never considered Hitler as a first
name because like I mean anything can be a you don't need
a lot of Hitler's you got a good point that yeah, anything
could be a first name.
If you have weird enough parents is the thing.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah, that would be I feel like that just be top 10 worst
his parents. I think I've talked about this on the podcast, but there's a guy
in my hometown. His name is Branch Leaf Olive. Oh yeah. I think I also told you
guys. Oh, he killed a guy. I just remembered.
He was breaking into a guy's car and the guy was like, "Can you knock that
off?" And he stabbed him and he killed him.
That's sweet. Branch Leaf Olive. Yeah. Imagine poking him. I told you guys about
that. That's such a peaceful name. I know. The guy who ordered from the
store that I worked at named Swastik Car.
>> Here's another comment here. I knew some bastard would make Hitler number one. I guess
it was number one at some point. I've heard way worse than any of these such many American
presidents and several commies, scumbags, not to mention Churchill, also Jackoff, and
he was a captain, so Captain Jackoff, also Buttram, who was a sports announcer on a local
television and Mr. Fox, my physics teacher.
You cannot go into teaching if you're your last name's fun.
Yeah, now they should literally they should that should be like
they should say no, you can't do that.
They should have a bar from entry like an occupational.
Like it's so easy to change your net.
Yeah, you should know like the test you they make you take in
in high school and guidance where it says what job they need
to like screen for that and it should say if your last name is
like fucks or I had a math teacher in high school whose last
name was cow sick. Oh, yeah, they should literally just tell you
you can't it's like a litmus test because you're already so
stupid. You didn't change your name by Yeah, it's for their own
good. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Somebody replied to this and said, the three names you
mentioned jacked off fucks and butt ram are unfortunate
sounding but Churchill Are you serious? Hitler on the other
hand is a hideous name to have what can I tell you?
Yeah, which yeah, no, they're like what? What kind of what innuendo do you get out of Churchill?
What innuendo do you get out of Hitler?
Oh, well, hold on. So he was a dictator.
And it's a sad, it's a sad, it's a sad name. Yeah. Yeah. All right. Number three, number three
is hooker. Okay. Seriously, who would want to last name that means you sleep with people for money?
It's a cool name.
It is kind of a cool name.
It's like Captain Hook.
Yeah, with that ER. It's even cooler.
I guess that's true.
Isn't there a blues city?
Yeah, I see a lot of blues fans in the audience.
There's a lot of blues fans here.
I can tell you guys are blues heads.
John Lee Hooker? Yeah.
Holy shit, there actually was one.
I didn't even have to say it.
Oh my fucking god.
Huge blues fan here.
The city's as stupid as people said it was.
[laughter]
This is awesome.
Um, what else did they say about this?
"How just what a hooker really?"
Yeah, pretty exasperated.
That's what I thought too when I saw that.
Yeah, "How just what a hooker really?"
"How just what a hooker really?"
What?
Oh, okay, I see it now.
There's supposed to be ellipses here.
"How just what hooker really?"
Yep.
You didn't see that before?
No.
You thought it was a full, complete sentence?
that was a normal sentence here. The next one here is brown.
Oh, okay. Wait a second here.
What the fuck, Pat? What the hell's going on, man?
It's not a bad last name. Not as good as white. Not white enough.
Read that shit out. Last name equals mass name,
which what the fuck does that even mean? And then, because Evan is a dick.
Nick I like to think that this is a conversation that they were having.
Yeah, yeah, last name equals mass name. I think that that's that's a what is
that I can't even guess actually. Yeah, yeah, I was gonna put that in there
because I was really fucking confused. That's a good reason to put something in
a live show. Yeah,
and it confuses you. Yeah. Why'd you put the one through two and three?
I don't know.
>> Okay. Just checking. >> What's the next one here?
>> That's good but if you're making up names. >> Yeah. They should have a filter that cuts
out spam of people just mashing their keyboards. >> 15 more Zs and people are going to believe
it's Polish. >> I think there was a comment on this one
or no it's another Polish last name. They're not really, not really cool the Polish last
names on here. This is my art teacher's last name and it's pronounced Shabilsky. Which I
don't know, is that true? No? Not at all? What's that pronounced Pat? Go ahead and try. I don't
want to. No go ahead just give it a college try. If you want to do the racist list you
have to do it yep this is all you nope
what's the next one here this is crap crapper rapper my last name is crapper
and I own a cracker, I am awesome for my like freakness, CC.
- Damn. - Wow.
- That is a bad last name.
- Yeah, that's rough.
- Yeah, but I don't think I've known anybody named Crapper.
- I don't think that's a last name.
- It is a last name.
- Unless someone here has got the last name Crapper.
- Anyone?
- Anybody? - Anybody.
- Crapper, reference?
- Damn. - Crapper.
- Crapper. - That's fire.
- That was shot here. - Yeah.
- Wow. - Yeah.
- Anybody in the best show of your life.
uh... what's this next one here uh... rapidly
rat hood
makes you sound homeless i think it makes you sound like a rat
with that notes mister ratburn
i'm thinking of
from arthur
the other guy at the game
yes
is that a chicago
things are third are that's a place in chicago there was that here yet
Did it take place in a real city?
No, we walked by him earlier today, dude.
Oh, that was him?
Yeah.
I didn't recognize him with different clothes on.
He is different now.
Yeah, he changed.
He grew up.
What, they just canceled that?
Did they just cancel Arthur?
What the hell?
Did they cancel Arthur?
Did they really just cancel Arthur?
What, didn't it just have the last scene?
Did they actually cancel Arthur?
Can somebody answer me?
Next slide.
He's a boss. Come on. Yay. I think this is an awesome last name. I love gay people
because I'm bisexual. I really want this last name. And then two people said you
are awesome and I respect you. That's nice. Yoshi dude. Yeah. Respects gay
people. Would you ever date somebody just for their last name? Yeah. Just to
try and take their last name. I'm bisexual. So I date people whose last
>> Yeah. >> Here's another one here. Obama.
>> Yeah! >> What's wrong with the president? What's
wrong with this? Well, somebody answered. They said worst president ever graduated from
the drunk sailor school of economics in Greece at the top of his class.
>> That's fucking right. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. >> The drunk sailor school of economics in
Greece. >> I love like when a kid clearly is just
just repeating whatever their dad said.
- Yeah, it's the best. - Perfect line.
- Yeah.
- And just see, like, obviously fucked it up.
This is not what his dad said.
- Yeah.
- He was just saying this at school.
- I actually do know somebody who graduated from there.
- Really?
- Yeah. - Who was it?
- My Uncle Paul.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
- Pretty. - What'd he graduate with?
- Not the top of his class, but.
He was there for an art major.
- It's a bad art school.
- Yeah, it's a terrible art school.
This next one here is Fokker.
It's pretty gay.
Yeah.
Yeah, I've never heard that last name.
Well, there's a couple movies.
I want you to see really.
Yeah, I might have to check those.
And let me tell you one of the guys first names.
It's pretty out there too.
Yeah, I can't wait to see you.
Here's a hint.
I hope it's poop or something.
That'd be really close.
Really?
Oh man blooper.
Is that what you said?
You hope it's blooper Fokker.
I said poop.
Oh,
all right.
That's better than that's better than blooper Fokker.
>> Here's the other one here. Pingas. >> We got the pingas clam showed out tonight.
>> The whole pingas family. >> Edouard pingas as usual I see. Everyone
will be embarrassed by this sentence. >> It does also remind me of a YouTube poop.
I can't remember which one. >> Here's another one.
i don't like the amount of stars on this one
yeah me neither
but no it's fucker
at first i was like oh ok that would be a really bad name
it's obviously fucker
that's
i think you're right
i don't know
and i want to know what their last name is
they thought theirs was bad
yeah true
this guy must have a really bad last name
hitler
yeah
ah
drew
yeah
here's another one here
coin
If somebody called you coin, then you must change yourself into a coin.
I never thought about that before, but that makes a lot of sense.
And that's the last one I could find on that list.
Okay.
Well that's the list, ladies and gentlemen.
That's the list.
That's it.
(audience cheering)