Okay, hi everybody.
Um, so uh, I'm gonna, this is something for you to listen to at night when you're getting,
you're having trouble sleeping.
And, which happens to me sometimes, because my stomach, I got kind of a sensitive stomach.
And sometimes the guys will make me eat stuff that I don't really want to eat, like, um,
like lint
and pieces of wood and so then my stomach gets all upset
because I got a sensitive stomach so
um... why did I start talking about that?
oh yeah I have trouble going to sleep sometimes and so if you're somebody who has
trouble going to sleep
then this is for you. This is for you to listen to, to help you sort of get your mind right
Um, uh, really, uh, uh, try to, um, be in your body.
And, um, so we're gonna start with a little, a little mindfulness, sort of meditation.
And then from there, uh, I'm gonna tell you a little story.
And then, uh, hopefully, hopefully, not even by the end of this, hopefully by, by the middle of it, right?
Like, like when you're just hanging out and stuff, or listening to me and stuff, you fall asleep before, before even,
It even ends, because then I know it worked.
So yeah, let's start with some mindfulness.
Um, okay.
Hold on, I just gotta get...
I gotta get a...
I got a little bug lit here.
Okay.
Um...
So, uh, um...
Okay.
So start
by settling into a comfortable position.
For me that's a lily pad. Allow your eyes to
close or keep them open with a...
that seems confusing. Or keep them open with a softened gaze.
Start taking some long
slow deep breaths. Okay go on Mike.
you know and so I settle into that and then on
what you and really really pay attention to how you're breathing
so like I breathe through my skin and stuff
so you if you breathe through your nose and your mouth you you should focus on that
focus on how it goes in and then
when it goes out okay
and also notice where your mind wanders to so if like you start thinking about
Going to the bathroom. Well, you should probably go to the bathroom.
You don't have to. Yeah, go to the bathroom.
Actually wait. Yeah, hold on. I'll wait. You go to the bathroom.
I mean you could actually just pause. I don't want to
wait. But if you might want to go somewhere else like you're thinking about your job or
your best friends and where they are and
why they told you to record this, then stop.
Or just pay attention like oh, where's it going? It's going over there, then go okay.
Now I know that I often think about how
Sometimes I'm confused about what I have to do from day to day to keep my friends happy
And I know I think about that so I can you know
avoid that
Okay, great
now
Now start relaxing. Imagine it from your toes
Imagine your toes getting relaxed and then keep going up your body. So then that's your foot and your ankle and
Well, then you got you got your calf and then your knee and your thighs
and
your parts
You got your stuff if you have stuff or if you got the stuff area
and then
Hold on let me look at my I guess okay
Then it's my stomach.
What about your backside? Hold on.
Doesn't say the like, because I said calf, but really that could, that shit was supposed to be shin.
It's like where do I,
where does it start then? Because, because I don't, if I just relax my front side I'm gonna freak out.
Because then I'm like, oh no, where's, my backside's feeling crazy.
Okay, yeah, and when you when you're ready open your eyes
And come back for I skipped ahead now telling you how to wake up. Why is this tough?
All right, I was gonna go to the story
Okay
So if that didn't work nothing that didn't calm you down which happens, you know
Try listening to this story. I'm gonna tell you
Once upon a time there was a
Little
cat and
His name was Stuart
little and
He was not the mouse though the mouse is a different guy in another story is a cat named that
and he really
wanted to
Drink some milk, but there wasn't any milk around so
First thing he did is he went to the milkman and he said, "Hey Mr. Milkman, you got any milk for me?"
And then the milkman said, "Yeah, of course." And so he gave him the milk.
That's good.
So now that he's got the milk, so he goes, "Okay, that's awesome. Let me go
back home." And so Stewart goes home, but when he's going home, okay, yeah,
danger.
Danger happens.
These three other cats who are much bigger, they come up to him and they go
"I see you got some milk there, Stuart"
And Stuart says "Yes, I love this milk"
And the three other cats say "Well, we're gonna take the milk from you"
"If that's cool"
And Stuart's like "Yeah, that's fine, I mean, can I have some of it?"
And they're like "Yeah, that's no problem, we'll share it"
"How's that?"
And then they agree
They agree on sharing it
on sharing it and so the four of them now are sharing the milk.
And so then, but then, a beautiful, a beautiful other cat that's very beautiful, like a woman
walks by and she says hello and keeps walking.
Okay yeah
and then out of nowhere three
other guys come up and their names are Roy, Blitters
and Patrick.
And they come up to the cat, the four cats that are hanging out and they're like
where's Sullivan? And then the cats
go who is Sullivan?
and those three guys go never mind you are just four cats
we're gonna keep going but if you see Sullivan tell him we love him
and the cats say yeah we can do that
and they're like okay we're gonna go find our best friend Sullivan and tell him we love him
and so the cats are done with the milk now
and the three bigger cats go
Thank you for sharing the milk, take it easy
And he got the other cat, Stewart goes no problem man
No problem guys, you guys take it easy too
And so Stewart's going home and he's
He's got a belly full of milk
And then
Then there's a
He gets home
and he lays down on his couch
and he's going good to be home
with a belly full of milk
but then he gets a call from the doctor
and the doctor says Stuart you have cancer
oh man that's way too dark
I don't know.
I was trying to come up with conflict.
The doctor calls and says, "Stuart, you have to come in for an appointment because you might
have cancer.
But we're pretty sure that it's all good."
"Yeah, all right.
That's fine."
And Stuart goes, "Okay, let me come in."
And Stuart goes in the doctor and he's in the waiting room.
There's all kinds of people around that Stuart's very nice to and they are very nice back to
him.
goes doctor what's that tell me what's happening I'm really worried that I have
cancer doctor says we just double-checked you don't got it and so
Stuart breathes a sigh of relief he's like okay that's awesome thank you so
much doctor and doctor says no problem however and Stuart goes what's up
Doc says, "However, there is a lost crystal deep inside Mariana's trench and you need
to swim down there and retrieve it or else the Dark Wizard, Math, is going to hurt everyone."
and the cat, Stuart, goes
then I will have to do that. Thank you so much. And so Stuart goes and
he goes to his nearest scuba instructor
and he says, Maria
can you help me? I need to go all the way down to Marietta's Trench.
I need to get the lost crystal and if I don't get it
then Matt is gonna just hurt everybody
And Maria says, "Okay, but it's not going to be easy.
While you are a cat, so you hate water, you are also very brave.
So I think you can do it."
And so then Stuart and Maria start working together.
Maria's getting him really good at swimming very far down.
And he goes pretty far down.
And as he gets about 30 feet down one day.
And Marie is like, "That's very good."
So just for reference though, just so you know, while 30 feet is really good, Mariana's Trench
is about 10,000 or about 11,000 meters.
So that's like 36,000 feet.
So we're going to need you to go a lot deeper.
And so then the cat, Stuart, is like, "I don't know what to do.
I can't even imagine going down that deep.
What do you think I can do to make it easier?
Maria said, I didn't want to suggest this because you were paying for the lessons, but
we've grown very close, and so I don't want you to feel like I'm ripping you off, but
you're going to have to get a submarine.
And he goes, and Stuart goes, great, where can I find one though?
Maria says you're gonna have to go to the store to buy a submarine.
And Stuart goes okay. And so he goes to the store.
But first he goes to the milkman because as we established earlier about his
character
he very much likes milk so he's drinking the milk and then he's gotta go to the
store.
So he heads over to the store to the sub- where the
it's not like a store where they sell submarines. He's gotta build it.
He has to build it together. So first actually he doesn't go to the store.
Sorry, sorry about that. He does not go to the store first. First he goes to his engineering friend
Rick and he says Rick I need to build a submarine
And I need to go to the store to get parts. Can you come with me?
Cuz it's gonna be very difficult otherwise
For me to figure out how to build this thing and Rick goes. Hey, man, you seen the news lately?
That'd be crazy. That doesn't go where you should go to the government and tell them you need the submarine or like a
defense contractor, somebody.
And Stuart said I don't have time for that. I need to just build it myself.
And Rick insisted that it would take less time to do that.
If you could prove how dangerous the crystal was, I'm sure you could get resources for it.
And Stuart said, Rick, you are way too uptight about this.
I just figured out how to introduce conflict into a story and I really need this to keep going.
Why are you fighting me on this? And so Rick goes I'm not fighting you on this
I'm trying to make sure that there's some you know realism here, you know, I mean you're a cat
I'm a guy I think
So, I don't know what you're gonna want from this cuz cuz this is already off the rails like like
Let's try to just have something to hold on to and then Stuart says well if I'm already a cat and you're a guy
What are we holding on to why are we even stressing about that?
You know, it's just the final points right and then Rick goes look
It's just about just just get through this part right? Leave me alone. Go to the store here. Here's a list
Here's a list of stuff
I told you to get and if you need to bring me back you can in the story
But try not to because you've you've created this sort of avatar
That's gonna
to critique yourself
and it's a very bad scene
it's gonna be very bad for you
Stuart
and Stuart's at the store
and he's getting all kinds of submarine parts
he's getting the tubes
he's getting the siding of it
the submarine
with the metal siding for it
and uh
he's, then he goes
back to his home
and with the milk
got me rock while he was doing this and he starts putting together the submarine and
he turns on the TV because he doesn't want to just do that by himself.
You know he wants something to own at the same time and he sees a commercial for this guy
Luciano and he's a professional explorer and Stuart says oh man I got to tell this guy about
this because I'm just a cat and I've just been given this very difficult task
because the information my doctor told me about so maybe I'll talk to this guy
Luciano I mean he's gonna he'll help me learn how to explore so let me give him
a call he's got a 1-800 number on the television I'm looking at so I know I
can call him and so let me give him a call and so Stuart goes to
was
Doctor and that's a bit. Yeah, there's a lot of things he already did. I don't have to worry about that
so he goes to his phone and
He goes to it and he calls the 1-800 number for Luciano
And he says hello, it's me Stuart. I'm here to talk to Luciano
and there's of course there's somebody the line is like one moment, please and
So Stuart waits a little bit and then Luciano picks up the phone and he goes hello to you Stuart
My name is Luciano. I'm an amazing explorer. What do you need? And Stuart told him the whole thing. He said look
There's a there's like some kind of gem at the bottom of the Marianas Trench
And we got to get it before Matt does
And so then the guy goes that's okay, let me help you out with that in that case
Why don't you come to my office? It's
one two three
Street
And let's just come on back
and so
Well one two three party Street because I'm always about partying. I love to party and I love to explore. It's actually sorry
It's actually one two three explore Street
Come on back. And so Stuart comes back
He knocks he gets milk when he goes out and he gets it and he goes and then he goes back to the store
as well to get more submarine parts and then he goes to
Luciano's yeah, and so he goes to Luciano's
He knocks on the door
Luciano opens up he goes come here and then he goes in Luciano's house and he got on the wall. It's like
Again, like a big squid he attacked on the wall. He's got like a picture of him
In the desert with the gold and he's got a picture of him
also with the Dalai Lama and with Alec Baldwin and also
Obama
And so then Stuart goes wow you've met a lot of very important murderers
Luciano says
Pay no mind to that. There's lots we have to do today my friend
Tell me more about this
journey
And Stuart doesn't really know much more about it than when he already told him over the phone
So it's sort of kind of a moot point and Luciano goes. Okay, no problem
Let's see. You've already started building the submarine. That's great
That's a really good start and you should be proud of yourself and don't let anybody tell you otherwise
however
It's not gonna be enough
so
I'm gonna need to get my team together, and they're gonna be the best of the best and
Also, they really did intelligent and they've got your back, so don't worry about anything
Let's let's do it and so first to go to get Maria the scuba instructor from earlier in the story
And he goes Maria. I just do it goes Maria
I didn't know you were part of Luciano's team.
And Maria goes, of course I am.
Why do you think I know how to dive and stuff?
I gotta know how to do that if I'm gonna be an explorer.
That doesn't make sense.
That's sort of a backwards.
And then they go to Rick's place.
And Zurich goes, Rick, I didn't know you were part of Luciano's team also.
And Rick goes, of course, how else am I gonna build everything?
I gotta build everything to be a part of the explorer.
I did the logic backwards, but you get it.
Like, they knew Luciano, and now they're with Luciano and Stuart.
And then finally, they get the last guy.
And it's Doug.
No, no, I'm tired.
Let me come up with a different one.
I liked Luciano. That was fun.
His name is...
Her name...
Is...
Macchiato.
No, it's coffee. Okay name is
Balthazar and he and he
Is a
Magic
Me opposite light wizard he's the light wizard and Matt's a dark one
And so we gotta go find Balthazar because he's gonna be able to in the final battle naturally
we're gonna need them to fight so and
Luciano said this guy and I've known Balthazar for a long time
He can just about beat anybody
In a magic fight so he's gonna be great but to get to him
We're gonna need to break him out even though he's a very good wizard and kind but he's also
mistaken from for crimes and so we're gonna for
Murder, and so we're gonna need to break him out of murder prison
and
And luckily for us we got the gang all here we got me the mastermind we got
Rick who can build stuff and we got Maria who can dive
And then we got used to it. And so it's like me. Well, what can I do?
and
Luciano says you are the key to it all to be revealed to you soon
Let's go
To prison first though. So we're going to prison we get to prison now. We get to they get to prison
And Stuart's like, "This is maximum security! How are we gonna do this?"
And, and, um, Luciano looks around and he says, "Okay,
we're gonna have to do this a couple fronts.
First, Maria, you're gonna dive into the sewer system
and use it to, um,
get inside the prison, after which you will steal a guard's
uniform and you will say, 'I'm taking this prisoner for a walk.'
and you wink and then you take out Balthazar
and you bring him outside
of the prison and then Brick's like okay well then what am I gonna do? Sounds like she's doing
everything and then Luciano says
oh you would think that because of what everything I just said
but what I didn't say was that
the only way that she's gonna be able to
get out of the prison completely is if you
undo the technological
powers on the doors because then that's gonna let her out with
a prisoner even if she dresses a guard that doesn't make sense so
you're gonna have to hack into the system because you not only build submarines
and source parts at a Home Depot but you also are an amazing hacker
so you're gonna have to do that and then Stuart goes but what am I gonna do
and he says, Luciano says Stuart
you are going to go into the prison and also be a prisoner.
And so that you can tell Balthazar what's happening.
So he's in on the plan before Maria gets there.
Cause otherwise he might, if like Maria takes him,
she might not have a chance to say something to him.
Like, Hey, I'm actually going to break you out of here.
Or he might think, or I think it'd be cool
if you're in the prison too.
Then Stuart says, "Okay."
And so Stuart
goes to the milkman and he says, "Look, I don't usually want to do this,
but I need to steal the milk from you so I can go to prison and save a good
wizard
so I can go through the Mariana Trench and get a gem."
And the milkman says, "That's fine with me. Just make sure, if you can, bring the milk back
when you're out of prison
or even before that, bring it back. Bring it back way before. Actually, can you
take the milk, I will call the cops on you and then in a panic you can give me the
milk back that can be the plan and Stuart's like okay it's a good idea
they do that cops come they're like we got your cat and they throw the cat in
prison he's got the uniform on he looks like a prisoner and the prisoners are
like who's this cat who's this guy and Stuart's like it's me I'm Stuart I was
called
is the wizard Balthazar. He is in here for things we don't even know.
Apparently it was so bad he sits all alone at lunch.
And Stuart says, "I'll sit with him." And they go, "Whoa, hold on. He's not very cool though."
And Stuart says, "Hey man, what's being cool when we're all in jail?"
And the guy said, "That's a good point, but okay, good luck, 'cause you're gonna be a
loser." And then so then
he goes over there, Stuart goes over there and says, "Hey, who are you, Balthazar?"
*laughs*
Balthazar says, "You just said..."
Balth...
Balthazar says, "You... I mean...
Come on...
I mean, you just said my name,
so I know you know who I am."
Oh man, I really...
Can I do that again?
Let me just do that again, right? Okay.
Hold on.
So Stuart saunters over to the lunch table where Balthazar is.
And he says...
Excuse me.
And he says, "Balthazar, I know who you are."
And his voice gets really quiet so nobody can hear.
He says, "I'm breaking you out of here."
I'm taking you out of the prison.
And Balthazar goes
Okay, that's awesome.
I have magic spells I can use
but they took away my magic powers
when they threw me in the prison.
So if you're going to take me out of here, that's fine.
But just know that I don't even have magic right now.
So we're going to need to get my magic back.
And then Stuart goes,
Okay, that's fine, but where's your magic?
do magic.
Balthazar says it's deep in Marianas Trench.
And then, um, nah that's stupid it can't be in the same place.
Hold on, let me, let me.
Balthazar says it's, it's behind.
No.
Oh, I got a good idea.
And Balthazar says, well, I left it in the parking lot.
No, that wasn't even the idea.
That just, I got nervous.
But what if Barthasar left it with his former lover and her name is...
Felicia.
Hey, so my bad, but I realized that I called her Felicia.
I think there's probably a lot of stuff that doesn't make sense, but this is something
I noticed when I was listening again for sure that I did change her name to I think Cassandra.
I'm pretty sure.
So I think it went from Felicia to Cassandra.
So that's the same character.
So I'm sorry.
Bye bye.
Felicia and Felicia took his magic in the divorce.
So now he's got to get his magic back.
legally it does belong to her so hmm
that's that's pretty tough
thing but but yeah I think it's fine
yeah so she's got it she took in divorce so
we have to talk to her her and she's really she's really only talking to me
through lawyers now so
I'm gonna have to talk to my lawyer
and Stuart said okay okay this is boring though so we gotta keep going
And so Maria meanwhile is swimming through the sewers
blub blub blub blub blub blub blub blub
and she gets to
the grate that's gonna let her into the prison
however it is locked
and so she's like oh no I'm not drowning
blub blub blub blub blub blub blub
she forgot to bring a scuba gear
so she brought a scuba gear
she's not drowning she's like oh no this is locked
but then behind her
is a shark, not a shark but like
some kind of sea
I know behind her is a magic sea monster a little guy and
You've got a symbol on his head and it says M for Matt
And so she knows it's oh, no, it's from Matt the dark wizard
He must know on his tail and so he has sent this sea monster. It's not that big
It's like it's big enough that I can fit in like the sewer thing that she's swimming through the like pipes
But it's certainly certainly big enough that it is a formidable foe
So she presses on her wrist communicator which she got from Luciano
Luciano we got trouble here
Well, not true. It's like it'll be fine. You don't have to worry
No, she doesn't say she says she said Luciano we got trouble here
There's a fish summoned by man and he's gonna attack me. Also, it's locked. So I'm a little worried and Luciano says
Okay, good. Thank you for telling me Rick and Rick goes
I'm on it. So Rick changes course on the computer where he was gonna hack a different thing. He says I got it
If I'm gonna hack this thing, it's gonna make hacking the door later difficult. Louisiana says doesn't matter
We got to get our friend out of there and Rick goes you got it boss. That makes sense to me
And so he's hacking the door. Meanwhile, she's fighting off the fish and then we go back now. We're going back
to Stewart and Balthazar and
Stewart's like
Okay, so how are we gonna get you out of here then?
Umm...
Oh, no, Stuart doesn't say that.
Balthazar says, "How are you gonna get me out of here then?"
Stuart says, "Well, I've got a friend who's gonna help get you out of here."
And then Balthazar says, "How are you gonna get out of here?"
And Stuart says...
Oh, man. Um...
I guess, uh, she's probably gonna get both of us out of here.
Otherwise, I'll probably get off in good behavior.
But she's probably gonna get both--
She's gonna get both of us out of here.
what she told me earlier so don't worry about it and so Balthazar is like
okay so what's going on and Sue says I'm not much
than Balthazar hold on sorry this is not they then go back to the prison cell and
we go back to the to the fight yeah and this hacking going on
Rick's trying to hack in and Luciano's like you gotta go faster man this not
to be good and then Rick goes I'm trying I'm trying but there's so many different
firewalls and attacks and so then Maria goes there's a lot of firewalls and
attacks out there and so she's trying to fight off the fish and and eventually she
gets a hand she puts a hand and slaps in the face just bops it and the fish goes
ah and it's really getting mad now so she's getting really worried and so
So the fish is coming to charge her and she's about to probably gonna bite him.
Probably gonna bite her.
But then the door opens and the hack has been completed.
And Luciana goes "Maria now!
Go!
Hurry!"
And so she swims up to the door and the door is closing as the fish is coming towards her.
And Luciana's like "Rick make the door close!"
And Rick's like "I'm trying but I have to do reverse coding combinations."
and then it happens and she's found in the doors closed so it's okay
and she now is in the prison okay
and um...
hmm
and now she gotta get the guard uniform
so she goes in and she's like she's a communicator
and she goes Luciano I'm here you have the blueprints of the whole place right?
and he goes of course I do
so you gotta have to go left right and then up and then left again
and she's like perfect and so she does that
she does that basically but then she gets stopped
and God sees her and she goes "hey who are you?"
"you're not in uniform for the prisoners"
and she's like "uh oh I'm being compromised"
and then at the same time
Stuart Balthazar walking by back from lunch
and Stuart goes "I've got an idea"
and he starts going "meow meow" to the cat
And so the guy's like, "Who let this cat in prison?"
And so then she slips away, and Stuart runs away, and the guard's chasing him now.
And then, Stuart leads the guard to a closet,
and Maria comes in and she knocks him out,
puts on his uniform, and she and Stuart come out of the closet now,
and she tells Stuart, "You have to go, 'cause you're a cat."
And now everyone knows you're a cat, which was...
so you gotta go and so it's like okay but the first things gotta happen
I guess I made him a cat again. I mean not that he wasn't a cat
just...
yeah and so he goes okay
I can't get out of here though because I am also in prison
so why don't I instead sit on your head
and act like a hairdo and she goes
That is crazy enough to work, right?
And so then he does that.
And now she's got cat hair, kind of like a cat hair.
Like it looks, it doesn't really look like anything good, but it looks fine enough.
And she's really smart at like being like, this is just my hair.
So don't worry about it.
You know, it's like, somebody tries to tell you, you better stop making fun of me.
She can go or like, or somebody goes like, I'm, I'm making fun of you.
That's what I meant.
Yeah.
Someone's going like, I'm making fun of you.
she goes like I know what you are but what am I right you know so it's done
deal done deal so now she's she's got the wizard now and Luciano's like okay you
now you know where to go you gotta go left right left and then you need to
tell the guard at the door that you've taken this prisoner out for a yard break
and then you got to make a run for it cuz Rick's gonna have the gates open but
only hold it open for a certain amount of time because of the way that the
computers and the technology involved are doing things with the codes and the
doors. She's like that makes sense yes and so she goes to do that
she's got Balthazar to it says to her that's Balthazar by the way he goes
hello and then they get to the garden the garden she says look here this is
you know she says the thing they're in the prison yard now right okay and so
So Luciano's like, "Okay, ready now!"
And Rick hits the button that starts the coding, or opens the door.
Through the code, through computers, and the door starts to open.
And the guards are like, "What's going on?"
And she's making a break for it with Balthazar.
And now she's like, "Balthazar, you gotta run too!"
And Balthazar, before she was like, kinda holding him like a prisoner,
but now she and him are both running.
And Stuart even hops off her head and is starting to dart around like a cat.
And now all three of them are going forward.
And then Stuart, um...
Uh, the door's closing, Stuart slips in very easily because he's a cat.
And then Balthazar and Maria are going, but Balthazar trips on his wizard robe.
I'm...
I know he's wearing a uniform, but he trips on his wiz- it's just like a...
It's like they knew he'd be comfortable in it.
'Cause if you think about it, like, you know, you're not trying to like hurt nobody.
I guess some people are really bad in prisons.
But I mean if I had it
If I, like, you're gonna, maybe it's
Maybe, well maybe they're just like, they wanted to make him comfortable
So he would get used to it so he wouldn't cause problems.
Yeah, that's kind of like a, that's kind of nasty.
That's kind of a mean reason.
To make him wear the robe.
But like still be like a thing that
So he's wearing the robe
But the robe also has the prison straps on it.
And so you know he's a wizard.
That's right, okay.
They did that so they want everyone to know, that guy's a wizard, be careful.
be careful but then he didn't have magic they didn't know that but they were like
that guy what that guy's a wizard so he's wearing the prisoner prisoner wizard
robe and so he trips on his robe and the doors about to close and Maria's all
the other side she's like no and then Stuart goes Balthazar you gotta hurry
And so then, um, Balthazar, uh, uses his robe as a lasso.
He like, he ropes it up and he tosses it, exposing his body, which is fine.
I don't know where I even fixated on that.
And then it's grabbed by the rest of the gang and they go "Pull!" and they yank him because
Because the robe is also tied to his...
Because it's a wizard robe, but...
It's got like a cloak part, and so then they grab it and they pull him in.
Okay, there we go, alright?
Okay, so then they got him and then they get away.
And so now it's...
They're back together, the gang, and they're like, "Okay."
"Balthazar, we gotta find your ex-wife so we can get your magic powers back."
And Balthazar says, "That's gonna be difficult."
"Because we're only talking to our lawyers."
And so Luciano says, "Okay, so probably then what we're gonna have to do is...
You guys are on really bad terms then, huh?"
And he's like, "Yes, very bad."
And he said, "Well, what do you know about... Where can we find her though? Maybe I can talk to her."
Said Stuart, the main guy, main character, Cat.
He's also a person. He says, "Maybe I can talk to her."
Balthasar says, "Okay, if you say so."
She works as a...
Um...
Hmm... Oh, she works as
a...
researcher at the...
um... the Institute for
magical studies we met when we were both going to school there
and they said oh the one the one on Main Street yes
and so you can go there Stuart but I wouldn't even bring me up because
it was really very acrimonious um you know we just it was
just at the end you know lots of sniping really just getting on each other's nerves
it was very difficult
I'm just glad we didn't have
kids because you know that could be very
challenging
and so it's and also glad you can have kids i mean that you put maybe would be
nice for you to have it so still goes to the any meets her
he says hello
uh...
both as i was wife
cassandra swan of that's an embarrassing so he does not say he says hello miss
cassandra
uses yes who who is it
didn't mean it my name is stewart i'm here to talk to you about magic
she said it will you have the right places into medical research in
"Stuart, girls, we need some help. Are you happen to be a wizard of some kind?"
And she said, "No, I'm simply a researcher. I never practiced the arts. I found them to be dangerous.
Far too dangerous, in fact. Though I studied them, not to better understand them, so that we can
stop them from hurting other people." I think, you know, and he said, and Stuart
thinks to himself, "I see now why this was difficult, because they had different philosophies on
on what should happen with magic and so Stuart says well
we need your help because there's a dark wizard who's trying to get a crystal
at the bottom of the Mariana's Trench
and we need somebody who understands
the dark wizard's magics so we can prevent him from doing stuff
and she said that's actually that's like a perfect marriage of my interests
and
the kind of like and um... my my skills and
up and still it makes a perfect marriage from
uh... and then she she comes to the loose luciano's hot he has a high now by
the way luciano it was just like is a been there was like a department i think
there was a secretary i said earlier but
but it's also like a hideout and sky gadgets and he's got like a little area
for the submarine
and he goes there
which and still it leads leads her there
and she says
all not this guy again to she sees both is our involves i goes to it i told you
don't this is very bad now. Stuart says you guys need to just be calm and be
friends for a minute because we have bigger things going on and Stuart he
gets up on the table and he says there's a lot of people who could be hurt if
Matt gets this crystal so I don't want to hear about you your petty differences I
mean I don't mean to minimize them you know I mean you know I look at marriage
is very difficult I hear I've never been in a relationship myself I saw a girl
Girl Cat once, but other than that, um, diving there, I guess that doesn't...
There are just more important things, and I need you guys to get along right now.
And Luciano looks at Stewie and thinks, "That could be my protege."
And they sort of nod in agreement.
They're all bigger things. That they always agreed on. It was magic always.
Just different feelings about it, right?
Oh, that's cooking. This is really cooking now. Okay.
And so then Luciano says, "Alright, well, we got the team here.
A magic knowing expert, a magic having expert."
And then we got a scuba diver, water expert, and espionage, and Maria, powers, and Rick.
Incredible technical abilities.
And, um, um, now, and Luciano goes to, uh, uh, uh, Cassandra and he says, "Look, I know
this might be difficult, but, but he's gonna need his powers to defeat Matt.
You know this.
You are a Magic Institute researcher."
And she says, "I, I will give him the powers back, even though I got it legally in the
divorce.
First I must see that he can fare in this adventure without them and then I will return them to him
at a time when I see that
And they're like that is crazy you're playing with a lot of fire then she says we can do this without magic
And he should know that there are things we can do in life without it and he goes
Oh here we go Balthazar goes like all man. Here we go and Stuart says that's enough
she reserves the right to withhold the powers and
He turns to Luciano and says, "We gotta just make this work, man!"
Luciano says, "You will rise beyond your years, young Stuart."
"Um, okay. Maria, how's the water?"
And she says, "It's good."
"Rick, submarine?" He said, "It's good to go."
"And I'm glad that Maria checked the water."
Okay, everybody, time to pile in.
We're heading to Mariana's Trench.
And they all get in the submarine.
They start to go down deep into the water.
And now there's all kinds of creatures around
and they're chomping at the submarine.
And they're like, "Uh-oh, this is really tough."
And Rick, who's piloting, obviously, is steering.
And Maria's identifying, "Those fish are really nice.
So we should swim in that direction.
That school of fish is not very nice.
We got to avoid them."
So that's part of what she does.
And as they're swimming down,
they see something they did not expect,
which is a barrier
as they get closer to the trench.
It's a magical barrier.
And Cassandra immediately recognizes it.
She goes, "That is a magical barrier.
We're going to need to use some sort of magics
to get rid of it. And Balthazar is like, "Well, I'm waiting." And Stuart says, "Hold on.
What makes this magical barrier happen? Is it just pure magic or is there some
kind of source?" And Luciano says, "That's good thinking, Stuart." And Cassandra says,
"Yes, indeed it is. This barrier is probably being held up by four pillars
that we need to destroy that hold up magical barriers of this size in ilk."
And sure enough as they continue to pilot the submarine around they identify them.
And Stuart says maybe we can destroy them without using magic but using our
intelligence and some of the other weapons. I think we have weapons on
board and Rick goes I'm also the weapons guy yes we have weapons so that's fine.
And Stuart goes okay so let's figure this out and then someone
And at a note it goes "Not so fast"
And um...
They see this um...
This man, the Supai
And it's Matt, the Darkwing
He heard them in the submarine
And he's swimming in the water but it's via magic
So he can breathe and talk normally and
Actually, he's uh...
He's talking to them through their minds
So he says "Not so fast" and they can all hear it in their minds
And Luciana goes "Did you say something young Stuart?"
And young Stuart says
I didn't say anything and Rick says I didn't say anything and then the other characters saying it as well, but then Matt
re-emphasizes I
See you have brought the failure that is Balthazar and his loser or ex-wife
so good job jerks and
Balthazar says dang you Matt and I heard about what you're doing and we're here to stop you and
Cassandra says "Yeah!" and they have like a moment of like, we know each other, you know.
That was like nice, that reminded us of something else.
And Luciano says "Matt, this is the last time I have to deal with you on my adventures, I swear it!"
And Matt goes "Hahaha, there's no way that's true."
I'm gonna come back again and again, but first I'm gonna get this crystal.
So I won't come back again and again, I'll get the crystal and it'll all be over.
But if you guys beat me, I'm not going anywhere unless you have to really beat me bad
To the point where I wouldn't
And Stuart says, "That might just happen today"
"Um, Rick, gun it!"
And Rick goes, "Right-o, Captain Stuart"
And uh, Luciano thinks, "Hmm, maybe he could be captain one day"
And then Rick zooms down with the submarine
And he's going towards the pillars
And uh, lo and behold, um, uh, Matt, Matt, who actually, you know what, and also going
back, Matt wasn't there, he was just talking through their minds.
I don't think they see him yet.
They just heard him through their minds.
I think that's better.
And so then they're zooming down the submarine to get to the first pillar.
And lo and behold, uh, the pillar has a big mouth.
He's going blah blah blah and he's shooting out beams.
And Rick is trying to swerve with the submarine.
They're like "Whoa!" and the beams are coming out.
And Stuart says "How do we stop that thing?"
And Maria looks around and she says "There!"
And she points at a fish that she recognizes.
And she says "That fish can plug up the mouth that's shooting out the beams if we time it
right.
And the best way to lure that fish throw is with cat."
And Stuart goes, "Uh-oh," he thinks, right?
And then he's now outside the submarine in a little...
He's got an outfit on to help him breathe in the water.
And Maria says, "Remember the things I taught you about being underwater?"
And Stuart goes, "Okay, you got it."
And so he starts to swim towards the totem pole.
Is it a totem pole?
It's just a pillar.
I keep imagining.
He swims towards the pillar while shooting beams and he's trying to get out of the way.
He finds a spot and he goes, "Here, here kitty kitty."
He's laughing.
That's a good joke, he thinks.
But it does work on getting that fish over there.
That fish, just like Maria said, just charges like a bull and just plugs up the mouth of
the beam.
The beam is shooting out.
The fish is still stuck in there.
Maria says, "That fish can handle any kind of beam.
You just gotta do that three more times.
And so they go up and go to the other pillars and they do that three more times and the
barrier dissipates.
And now they can finally enter into Mariana's Trench.
Which has very strange creatures.
And Maria's like, "I don't even know if I've seen many of these fish before we're about
to see so we gotta be careful."
Also, it will be incredibly dark.
And Rick says it'll be exactly 42,349 darkness.
Luciana says, "Okay, we got to be very careful. That's one of the
highest levels of darkness that are possible. Do we have any light that we
can use?" And Cassandra looks over to Balthazar and says, "I grant you back from
our divorce the light spell." And Balthazar says, "Thank you, Cassandra."
And it's very impactful. It's a very impactful moment.
And he shoots out his hand up and he goes light be bright and
It shoots up on top of the submarine now is glowing bright
And as they go and they go down Marianas trench and now they can see what's going on
They see all kinds of crazy as fish you can imagine
One that looks like a draft one that looks like a dog one that looks like a cat one that looks like a mouse
They look like other animals, but also fish and that's
And also some of them have the lights on their heads
Some of them have squiggly arms.
And it's very scary for a moment there, for sure.
But as they approach deeper, thanks to Maria's special intelligence and knowledge around the fish,
and not just fish, but other things that are down there, crazy plants, obviously, as well, that are shooting out stuff.
They are able to make it to the bottom of Mariana's Trench.
And then Luciano turns to everybody and goes, "Is everybody doing okay?"
And everyone says, "Yes, we're doing alright. Thank you, Luciano."
And he goes, "Okay." So now we're here at the bottom.
And look, it's a magic crystal.
And the crystal's there.
And we have to...
Did I say that they have to destroy it earlier?
Um...
What does it do again?
I don't want to cheat, you know, I don't want to cheat and go back to what I was recording
But they have to just
They have to destroy it
In this case, that's what the doctor said. I mean I did he didn't say that but he did say that earlier
He texted Stuart and said "Stuart, you have to destroy the crystal forgot to mention." So Stuart was like "okay."
So...
They go, they, uh, they're, they're approaching it and then
Swoosh! Out of nowhere.
It is I, Matt, the evil wizard. And I just, I feel like a jerk for picking that name, you know.
I should have come up with something more interesting.
Can I, I'll change his name now.
I mean, it could be short for Matthias.
That sounds, I mean, it's not evil, but it's more formal.
Alright, Matthias, the evil wizard.
And then maybe mockingly, you know.
They could be like, "Yeah, sure, Matt."
And he goes, "That's not my name!"
Yeah, that's pretty good.
But I don't know.
That's sort of like a whole... I should've...
You know, you're probably...
Are you asleep, by the way?
I forgot I was trying to make you go to sleep.
This is too exciting.
I mean, you guys gotta let me know.
Because then next time I'll make it boring.
I wanted it to be a good story.
Um, sorry, anyway.
And he says, "I have arrived. It is I, Mathias the Evil Wizard."
And in this moment, this is where Cassandra turns to her former lover, Baldasar, and says,
"By the power of my attorney, I grant you back, after our divorce, I grant you now,
through your wizarding powers and Balthazar says are you sure and she says
I now know that you have it in you to just to not use your magic and to calm
down you know what and what I should have done earlier is he should have come up
with a solution because it would have been more impactful maybe he could have
Oh, well I guess Maria...
Uh...
That's fine though, but she sees that he wasn't like, you know...
"I need the powers so bad!"
You know?
There's probably other things that help tell you that she sees something in him, right?
We just don't get to see it. You can't see everything in the story.
I wish you could though, sometimes.
I wish you could see all the bits.
But...
Anyway, she's giving him the powers.
He's like, "Raaah! I'm the strongest now!"
And so now it's him vs. Mathias.
He exits the submarine.
They're having a water wizard battle.
Shooting spells at each other.
Going back and forth.
And while that's going on, Stuart's like, "Let's go get the crystal while they're fighting!"
And they go to get it.
And as they're approaching it, it's glowing bright red, crimson.
Crimson, yeah, and like different colors too.
And they get the crystal.
And when Stuart has it, he's like,
"Whoa, this is a lot more powerful than I thought."
And Luciano's like, "Be careful, Stuart.
This crystal could change everything.
You must destroy it."
And so Stuart goes and he starts punching it.
And he's like, "I can't destroy it. I'm trying so hard."
And Matthias laughs while he's fighting Balthasar still.
And he says, "Ha ha. You can't destroy this crystal.
I'm going to use it for evil.
The only thing that can destroy it is the power of true love.
And in that moment, Balthazar remembers how much he loves Cassandra.
And how much their differences are not so different and that they should reconcile.
This became more about love and about divorce.
And I don't think... I think people can relate to that.
And he remembers this and he goes "I love my ex-wife"
And he shoots the crystal and Matthias is like "Noooooo!"
And the crystal explodes and then *pew pew pew*
All the still stars start shooting around.
And Luciano's like "We gotta get out of here, Rick!" And Rick's like
already on it and he just guns it.
And now the wizard fight continues.
But now it's like, "You're not getting away!" and he starts shooting wizard powers at Balthazar.
Balthazar's like, "I'll stay behind, you guys keep going!"
And Cassandra's like, "No, Balthazar, you can't!"
And he's like, "I must. If my wizard powers are to be used for good, this is what it looks like."
And that's the way it is, and he's shooting, and they're like, "No, Balthazar!"
But they escape from the thing, and they get out of Mariana's Trench, like *swoosh*
*Grrraaaaaaah*
and they destroy the crystal of evil and they submarine to get back to Luciano's
lair and they're all really like really tired but they're also really sad
because now Balthazar's gone or so they think because soon flying up from the
water it's Balthazar. Balthazar are you alive? and he's like yes I am I have paid a
terrible price though. I might never be able to use my wizarding powers again.
But, because I had to, I shot them all at him and that shot me up and also trapped
him dead and sealed him. And I did that, gave up my powers so I could be with you
all. And Cassandra's like, "We should get married again by the years." And Stuart's
like, "Wow, we did it! That was an amazing adventure, Luciano." Luciano says, "Stuart,
"You did such an incredible job, would you like to come with me on more adventures?"
And Stuart says, "I think so."
"Sounds like a good idea."
And Luciano says, "Then we shall continue to adventure together."
"Me and you."
Stuart and Luciano.
And Stuart said, "You put my name first, that's so nice."
And Luciano said, "Hey."
"Um, yeah."
And Maria went back to teaching scuba diving,
She also got a million dollars for discovering a new fish
while she was under the Mayan's trench.
And Rick got hired by NASA for making amazing ships
in submarines and technology.
And because of them destroying the crystal,
they're absolved of the prison break earlier.
And also 'cause Balthazar didn't actually do anything wrong.
I forgot to address that, but he didn't do anything wrong.
It was a mistaken identity or maybe his magic misfired.
That's kind of interesting.
But anyway, that actually would be--
that's a pretty nice way to tie it all together, actually.
He went to prison because magic misfired,
and that sparked the whole thing between him and Cassandra.
OK.
And she abandoned him in his time of need.
Yeah, I like that.
I think that's pretty good.
And so that is the story of Luciano and Stuart,
and Stuart and Luciano, the amazing adventurers.
Yeah.
And that's your bedtime story.
And I want to tell you guys that.
So hopefully you're asleep by now.
You know, I hope you guys like this.
This was sort of a, kind of an experiment.
We never, well, you know,
we didn't get to go on an adventure today
with me and the guys,
so had to kind of come up with something.
And I thought, oh, I'll make a sleepy tape.
And then I started to do that.
And then I was like, I should tell a story
'Cause that's a sleepy time story.
Matter of fact, well, very good story.
And then I was getting nervous about that too.
But I think it's pretty fun.
But yeah, if you like this, let me know.
If you don't like it, I don't know.
I mean, you can let me know too,
but don't be too mean.
I get it, but you know.
Anyway, well, I hope you guys have an amazing day.
And if you ever wanna hang out, let me know.
Okay, bye-bye.
(upbeat music)
♪
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC]
[ Music ]
[BLANK_AUDIO]