[MUSIC]
I've been the Holiday Sheriff of Brooklyn, Texas for 45 years.
Grandfather, father, son, grandson, great grandson, my zygote nephew,
Charles Ford, we're all Holiday Sheriffs.
Hardly knew what that was then now.
But you know, you just know you gotta look after the joy and the sensations of popular traditions, pastimes.
Make sure they all occur and go smoothly.
We all had a way of doing things.
Things we took special care of. Grandpa always cared for the Fourth of July, patriotic type.
My Pa always loved the Jew ones, no offense.
And my cousin Artie, he loved Christmas.
Loves the cookies and the milk.
presents and the way those bits of poop
dingleberries hang around the hairs of your ass
I try to tell him that that ain't a part of Christmas but
[laughter]
he don't want to listen to him
but he defends it all the same
and I'm sure Dallas is better for it
sometimes he'll grow a beard for Christmas
he'll put little bits of
little bits of poo poo in there and he'll say
I'm the Christmas Carol
he thinks the Christmas Carol's a guy who has a lot of dried shit hanging around his body
That just about confused everybody, but you know, I think he only lost three kids that
year.
I don't know where they went.
I'm getting sidetracked.
See, for me it's about Easter.
Rebirth, I like the eggs, hell I like peeps alright.
Springtime, something new, and you need something new because when you look down the barrel of
Good Friday, if you're not thinking that there's something on the other side, some kind of rebirth,
well, I don't know.
Maybe it ain't worth it. It's all we got.
We pan...
It's a good toffee.
It's perfect. Perfect Cormac McCarthy.
And we pan, along, thank you, to the desert.
The El Desierto, or the desert.
Where there are three eggs.
In Brooklyn, Texas.
Three of known repute who've made their mark.
Different forms.
They're hunters, and today they've tracked a herd of beagles into the desert.
For them, it's maybe just another day meant to pass the time beneath the unending fire
of the lone star's sun.
But little do they know, their lives are about to change forever.
Hmm?
Oh, they don't know that.
Little do they know.
Okay.
They know a little of it.
They know a little bit of it.
Who are these eggs on this fine, good Friday?
Remember me?
It's me, Yolkman, the memorable egg.
You probably used to watch my show when you were a kid.
Practically everybody did.
I'm Yolkman, the egg.
Come on, I know you remember me from Yolkman's world.
Remember my egg body?
Remember my cute little arms and legs
with the white gloves and the black platform boots?
Remember the floppy appendage between my legs
that the North American localization
desperately tried to claim was a tail?
I know you remember me, I'm Yolkman!
Remember my doorman, Mr. Loopy?
He's one of the funniest characters for sure.
Well, he's dead.
But remember him?
Remember my nemesis, the nefarious Dr. Mingala?
Remember the-
[laughter]
Remember the banned episode where he teamed up with Freddy Krueger?
Remember my toy line?
Remember Yolkman's surprise eggs?
Remember how many children were hospitalized for choking, lead poisoning, seizures, and suicidal ideation?
I do.
zero and remember me yoke man from my world. Remember your favorite episode of
yoke man's world. That was my favorite episode to unless yours is yoke man goes
to jail or the yoke man family court debacle or yoke man teams up with
doctor. It's not important. What's important is that you remember me the
memorable egg from yoke man's world yoke man
yoke man. The
from yorkman's world. You guys remember him yeah yorkens. I think I've seen
maybe thirty or forty episodes of you yeah, it's a lot of it's like two
hundred seasons somewhere between thirty or forty. I think I've seen a
lot of that world actually the more I think about this world. Yeah, I think
it's like one of the most viewed worlds for me of world. Yeah, yeah, so
you open a memorable egg. You have a tackle move.
I just thought that would be good
And then also I gave you yolk shot.
Mm-hmm.
From the show, yeah.
Yeah, from the show.
We all know yolk shot.
Yeah, from the world.
Right, sorry, yeah.
When you do that, it marks a target.
So it sort of does like a fairy fire kind of move.
Yeah, of course, yeah.
You get advantage, which in the show, Yolkman would always announce that he has advantage
on attacks.
It's like fairy fire.
Yeah, that's what he would say.
Yeah, he had to take the yolk button.
But yeah, we have another egg out hunting.
Who is this second egg?
[Squeaky laughter]
Oh no.
It's the century egg.
[Squeaky laughter]
What?
I needed to go to Rostress for less.
[Squeaky laughter]
I need to go today.
I need to go to Rostress for less right now.
now my shoes are hurting me I need to buy new orthopedics oh there surely is no
country for me anymore I'm dying I'm constantly sick they put a video of me
on tick-tock and my skin look like beef jerky. Oh I remember so many people in my
life but they don't remember me anymore.
Oh there were two Thebes here. I hurt all the time. And you really went with both of them.
which was old man I guess and eggs so you're the century egg one of the oldest
eggs in Brooklyn Texas you one of century egg there might be a millennial like saw
slavery happen and I did nothing so you have a few moves defender egg which you
you can you can protect your fellow eggs reducing damage you have five uses per
long rest of that and then urine because as we all know and even though Wikipedia
said it was it was just a popular myth well yeah it's bullshit century eggs are
marinated in horse urine for a hundred years you're thinking of a virgin boy egg
that's marinated in virgin boys urine. I've never thought of a virgin boy egg.
Maybe I should have been that character. Well I spend a lot of time thinking about
a virgin boy a virgin boy eggs I've never thought of this the other one's
combination of probably spent like that's I probably spent like 36 hours of
waking time thinking about virgin boy eggs good for you you know I'm not gonna
say if that's good or bad I feel like it's a trap for me um yeah so you have
an ability to sort of a let urine come out of your body and create sort of a
puddle that's an ability that's just a mistake I have that ability it is up to
15 feet around I'm using my ability and then you have egg foo old century egg
all right and then we have a third egg you're all by the way using the exact
same hunting rifle pointing it at the herd of beagles okay and what's this
third egg we have here um T Dumpty sat on a wall empty dumpty had a great fall
all. Umpty Dumpty wasn't so umpty. Wumpty? We've all heard the stories. I feel like 30
stories. It wasn't bloody gory, just yolks and whites are pouring. These days I live
in Texas, on the hunt for girls to have sex with. But this old washed up breakfast got
stood up in the desert. I was supposed to meet a slut named Amy. In the desert.
desert. Cool, we got Hupty Dupty. You have a few abilities. DIY! You've got Great Fall.
So when you use Great Fall, you can jump upwards of 30 feet high, but only so that you can
fall. So you can't just jump up 30 feet and land on something. You deal 1d10 damage plus
1d6 for every 10 feet from which you fall to an enemy. So it's a huge attack. Afterwards
you enter cracked mode. When you're cracked mode, you can, you have a ranged attack instead
where you can sling eggshell shards at people. If you do great fall again when you're in cracked
mode, that's when you actually take fall damage.
Okay, so I get one freebie.
You get one freebie and then you gotta wait for three rounds and then cracked mode will
reset. You'll put yourself together again.
Okay.
As the story goes.
Cool.
And then you have a regular melee attack called Whack.
Okay.
So, you guys are hunting a herd of beagles.
You see them sort of out in the desert, El Deserito.
And yeah, I mean, you guys want to try to take a shot?
Like what's your beagle hunting sort of strategy?
Shoot 'em in the brine!
Yeah, well I'm down with that.
Okay, cool.
Can you just put your mic further away when you do that?
A beagle is licking my head.
Beagle to herd. We should send the old one down as bait.
I kick this entry egg down the cliff and just watch him kind of roll.
Okay. Are you gonna let that happen or you really don't resist?
Got it. Okay.
Roll into the pile of beagles.
You roll into the herd of beagles. They sort of like cock their heads to the side.
They're just beagles. They start to like kind of lick you.
I don't care if I live or die.
yeah. One of them goes okay and starts to chomp at you a little
bit. There's a nibble at you. You guys have a clear shot.
Can we? We can understand beagles.
Do they scooby-doo type?
They start, this one of them is scooby-doo.
Can I aim directly at the doo himself?
Yeah, he goes rut-ro as you aim. Okay, roll just a d20 and we'll
add your decks.
And actually, both of you roll d20s.
all your old that you pack is your bait right now it is six anyway
and sixteen nine-year-old with the higher eleven-plus tax in fifteen
okay and what what's your decks
one so i guess it's seventeen two-year-old as a single okay so take
sixteen
yet you hit that scooby-doo and okay you get that's going to be doing i couldn't
add one clear between the eyes i think you can sorry
uh... in a it i totally can't
the
uh... plus like that episode
mhm you go to jail or else i want
yes i think i did world deception no man at the dog park
is
the
twelve
afforded to roll inside
six. Okay. Yeah, you believe you saw it.
Was that good one?
I'm like nodding.
My whole body is not a brains of the dog.
Just splatter on you.
Yokeman the other Beagle start to scatter.
Yoke as you do that.
I'll let you know.
I'm sorry century egg and the other Beagle start to scatter
and as they do you see them sort of heading in towards the
distance and you can get a clear view of what's going on
further past where the Beagles are.
There seems to be some sort of litany of abandoned trucks, or at least they're just sort of laying
in the middle of the field.
Actually you, Sentry A, because you're closer, roll...
Let's have you roll Perception, because you're probably going to get a better view of this.
Because you rolled down the hill.
I got a 12.
Okay.
All right, that's fine.
You can probably see it then.
So you see not just like the cars down there, but you see eggs look similar to
you guys and you see them in different states.
Oh my grandson.
In different states.
Yeah what is this fucking summer sunny.
So what is this the United States?
No they're all.
Those eggs are in Oklahoma.
You're all in Texas.
We're in North Texas and those eggs are in Oklahoma.
So what is it the border of Texas, Oklahoma and.
Mexico.
the four the egg corners. The egg corners yeah. What's up? Yep. All right and you see
the four cartons. Yeah there's a fist bump. So we're all we're doing this in person in the
office finally. Four fist bumps for every single joke. So it's gonna be a lot longer now.
Usually I have to deal with it. Yeah. Let's build our four cartons. So yeah you can see that
there are I'll fist bump you for that. You can see that the century you can
Century Egg, you can see that there are like, there's one egg that's scrambled on the ground,
one that's sunny side up on the hood of the car.
Um, it's pretty bad. It looks like a pretty bad scene.
I wish that was me!
Oh, God!
Hey, fellas!
What?
There's dead people!
People?
Well, I'm referring to people in the egg sense.
Here's an old egg. That's back when they were called eggs people.
They considered people eggs.
There's egg pools here.
There's dead egg pools.
Much better. Egg pool. Great movie.
I like egg pool too.
Egg pool was great.
Funny ass egg.
When he was an eggs man it was bad but then he was great at egg pool.
I love when the eggs men showed up.
Egg losses.
egg lobs
noite egg
stop that egg
stop that egg lobs
egg voreen
jean gray egg
jean greg
egg bully
professor egg
that's beast
Professor Egg Xavier, I knew where you were going.
Eggnito?
Eggpocalypse!
Okay, I'm going down to the cars.
Or the whatever it is.
Can I roll my eggs?
Yeah, you guys can try to roll your eggs.
I'm running on top of him, because I have arms and legs, by the way.
Okay, roll.
If I establish that.
Okay, fine.
I have arms and legs too, but I-
No, you didn't say that. You didn't say that at the beginning.
I said it in my character.
You don't have arms and legs?
Nope.
I don't have arms and legs, and I hold everything like a VeggieTales.
Just floating?
Yeah.
they're not called VeggieTales. They're called VeggieTales. They're not called like a VeggieTales.
Bob the Tomato is not a VeggieTale. He's a VeggieTale. A VeggieTale is one of the beautiful
stories that he fucking creates with his friends. So is he a tomato then? He's a yeah he's Bob is
what he is is in his name. You know they can't go to heaven? The tomatoes yeah because they're
vegetables. Yeah. Was that yeah well they could have some version. Like they that's why they
always say I love you or God loves you. And not them. Yeah. Because they're just food. Like God
does not God does not live in his fuel for believers yeah yeah I guess that's
true yeah okay I'm a forum yeah so yeah you guys you got roll roll acrobatics if
you're gonna try to run on him okay I'm rolling cuz it's the easiest way oh oh
baby I was a 19 19 yeah plus 420 yeah easy easy as shit you yolk man you used
to do this all the time in your show. Yeah, I mean, yeah, Yoakman at the Circus. Yeah, you're a professional.
Yoakman Live, I even did this a few times. I remember that episode too. I didn't say that in character. You're just saying that to yourself.
Just running on my body. Oh, I remember this episode. Yeah, see you guys arrive at the scene and
yeah, you see all that and you realize that it's they're scrambled, they're sunny
side up there's also inside there's there's a boiled egg inside the one of
the cars there's a full-ass omelet in one of the back of the pickup truck so it
looks like a pretty brutal scene looks delicious and I'm what unscrambled eggs
something's wrong with you what what do you mean it's food wait it's food it's
sunny side up eggs and scrambled eggs and omelets that's food right?
Wink!
(Laughter)
He's excited by the way he says what.
Wink!
(Laughter)
So, uh, I mean, you guys can try to
Touch my bones!
Try to investigate, figure out what happened here if you care
or you can like just, I'm gonna investigate
I'm gonna look for money
You're gonna look directly for money?
I'm gonna look for a bag of money
I'm gonna look for a bag of money and when I find it
I'm gonna dig through it and I'm gonna remove a transponder from it. No, there's no...
No, no. Hold on, I just need to edit something. Is there... Yeah, we will investigate. Yeah.
Is there an invisibility cloak? Can I roll an investigation for that? You can roll an
investigation to see if there's any sort of magical items here. Nope, don't care.
Invisibility cloak. Can I roll for that too? I want to find a magic item. Okay, yeah.
Do you want to roll for money? Yeah, money. Okay, I mean, what is that under?
I'm rolling for money.
This was an investigation and it was like, "Can we play CeeLo?"
Oh, I got a nat 20.
No way.
Oh man, he did get a nat 20.
That's pretty tight.
I got a 15.
That means I get a lot of money.
I got 15.
I got a 17.
Oh, wow.
Okay.
Great, I'm shit.
You two don't find any magic items here.
That doesn't mean that there aren't magic items in this session, by the way.
Keep looking, boys.
I'm sure you'll find something.
It is Easter, of course.
I'm gonna keep looking for magic items you with that 20 are able to perfectly trace a
Ketchup stain for the omelet or in the scrambled eggs, okay? Yeah, do we bleed ketchup as eggs?
I think we I think we bleed our yolks. Yeah, you guys bleed yolk, okay, but in this case. It's ketchup. Yeah
Yeah, and you can trace it all the way to a tree further in the back
like like way far from the scene like somebody who was trying to get away yeah
And you see there. It looks like a extremely dead frog
Let's go okay his mouth fully
Holy and self suck I put my nuts in his face. Yeah, it doesn't react you can feel in the cosmos
But yeah, it's fully dead hand
Gripping yeah a golden. Yeah Easter basket. Oh my god filled with tiny
Golden goose eggs. Holy shit. This is the mother
a
lot of golden babies
Remind me why are us three friends?
Bachi Club
For all ages just trying to remember yeah
It was a cruise ship in a sink
Yeah, how small are we you guys are regular sized things regular size regular for eggs or regular people?
Oh, so we're like huge egg monster. So in the modern world setting of
Our of the pal universe. There are also a race of egg people who are in, Texas
That is what I have had to decide. Hey, I mean so can we just start a new setting called Easter world
worlds that we can return to time and time again on different
holidays.
Well, there is I also established through this a an
idea of a holiday Sheriff and so there's sort of a litany of
sheriffs out there who oversee holidays.
Okay, cool.
So there's there's lots of there's lots of Lord potential.
I want all the autistic fans taking notes on this.
Yes, please do.
We love you guys.
I love nobody else does sorry.
I'm the I'm the nice one in the you are my slaves.
Yeah. That's facts. And so, as you guys get the eggs, roll a perception, all of you.
Okay, that's a seven. Fourteen. Thirteen. Pretty good. You're too enamored with the golden eggs, I would say,
Yoakamon. Century Egg and Humpty Dumpty, you have your wits about you. Somehow, Century Egg, you have your wits
about you a little bit more. I've been around the block.
That's cool. You changed up the accent a little bit.
How did I change the accent?
A little more slipping into Cosby here.
What do you mean I've not slipped up into anything?
Do you have any jello pudding pies?
It's very good.
You got the cadence down too. It's not just the voice.
Okay.
You guys get the sense I've got an episode with mr. Cosby
You guys sense the presence of
of what? Cosby Surprise Egg. Oh yeah, true. I should have written that in. God damn, I
had that on my desk. I could have just written the Cosby Surprise Egg. It was looking right
at you the entire time. The cartel. The white Cuban cartel has arrived. What? They're here?
Well, you could you two can sense that they're approaching can hear their car
Sounds like an Impala with a baby on board sticker
Think it might be the white Cubans Oh
Dear I can hear the rustling of motorcycle jeans
You get the sense that there's a a t-shirt with a daffy duck
Approaching at Mach speed
They're here
Yeah, you see them roll up and you would recognize this you know you guys you know you guys kind of wander into the scene
You're not too unfamiliar with the criminal world of the of the desert
And you would recognize
Domenico van Halen a lieutenant of the white Cubans and he says to you guys
Were you guys doing
What accent should I choose for this voice for this character? I didn't decide on the way here. You think that's good
No, I think you nailed it. You think I'm like sort of tattling like straddling line there
I I've been facing the other way and I hear that voice. I'm like what?
See you nailed it
What do you got there? It looks like it's ours. I'm sorry. Who is that behind you for hence? Oh
What?
Yeah, what do you want oh it's been ages oh
Seen you
Since I was a much younger man for NCO. Yeah, well you were a man
- This son is a man.
- I was a much younger man, egg.
- Well, you know.
- I met you at a bath house.
- That's right, that's right, I was 13.
- I'm running away with the eggs.
- Why did you say you were 13?
You weren't 13.
(laughing)
- For roll initiative, guys.
- We have to roll initiative?
God damn it, dude.
- Patrick's thing didn't work.
(laughing)
- God damn it.
- 15.
- Eight.
- Six.
- Okay, one.
- God.
Well, my life is basically fucking shit. Okay, my life just changed great great
My life just changed for the better and by better. I mean worse. Yeah, if it's only ones and zeros of my computer ass
Oh my god, then I feel like a binary robot
This is your own ones and zeros. I am my robot
I got a six. I
Love hearing those crazy board noises. I got a figure it
I want to it sounds great it's cool your money is pointed right at the keyboard
sounds great right yeah like the raw kind of hangout keyboard yeah computer feel
ambience he was gonna add in computer board sounds anyway yeah board yep my
board go ahead and type hey white boy type yeah type white boy show us what
you got. I think I can do this. Making the white kid play the typing game where you shoot
the spaceship. Alright cool. Alright that's enough. So Sentry A you're gonna go, why are
you so fast and smart? I've been around. Wait how's he going first? What'd you get? You
got a 15. No I got a 15. Oh you got the 15 I'm sorry. Oh my god. You can't even type.
I'm not dumb. What is DM stand for dumbest moron?
Oh yeah. What is what is patches stand for?
Pelo averaged intelligence. It's just
It might. It really might.
Scary. Alright you're up. It really might. So what do you want to do with these guys?
There's about four of them including Domenico Van Halen.
I'm gonna I'm gonna shoot my yolk shot at Domenico Van Halen right in his
is fat fucking face right role in fact role
there's a twenty three
that fucking it's
okay let's see here
use upon the star wars where it does six freaking fucking damage alright okay
yes it's the easter episode no more swearing on your own patches are reset
that said it the fuck up and we're fucking swear in the air fucking and
that's and that's piercing damage and shit
you know i don't denied denied and he's my and he's marked very fire style of
fucking shit I'm sick of this day I just said I do something like this fucking
bitch ass shitter just keep on fucking going a bitcher yeah I didn't even know
that I did that damn right so yeah fucking fucking you shoot him okay cool
you did you shit him you fucking shoot him yeah you shoot him with the oak is
He's like, "Ugh, fucking disgusting, I hate you egg people."
And uh...
Woah!
What the hell?
We're not people!
[Laughter]
We're eggs.
Why does everybody keep saying that?
Don't ever call me, I said egg people.
I have an arms and legs and a long flaccid penis doesn't make me a person.
It's legal to kill us.
We're not people.
You're pretty flaccid though.
I've never got it up in my life.
I'm an egg.
I'm not even born yet.
I don't even have a penis.
My penis fell off when I was born.
This is another thing inside me that might be something later.
This is a sperm's tail.
[Laughter]
My penis fell off when I rolled down a hill.
Domenico comes up to you.
I taped it there. I taped a penis to me.
With his shank.
And he stabs you four.
Me? Nah.
Yeah, who's four?
[Laughter]
Fucking genius.
For four damage.
My sides.
Oh my sides are in orbit right now.
Me for damage?
This reminds me of that episode
Yolkman takes 4 damage.
Oh I don't remember that one.
Maybe you saw Yolkman takes 5 damage.
That one was more popular.
AC?
My AC is 14.
Okay, your AC?
12. Okay.
You get hit, two others come after you
And they miss they miss you're able to sort of Humpty Dumpty them. I just fall
Yeah, you just fall over and they're like that was a great fall and they miss thanks you get shank old man
You have like three HP or you take three damage no he's alright
Whoa what is going on with your your brain in mind right now? I said three and then you said three yeah
No, I mean I had to I rolled it. Yeah mine fucking blown. You're up Humpty Dumpty
Um, I guess, I mean, let's start it off pretty cool. Let's start it off pretty cool by me
doing my Greatfall ability.
Alright, cool.
And I want to do the maximum damage.
Okay.
Yeah, I realize now that also that I like didn't create any incentive for you to not do the
maximum damage. I should have done something where it's like if you do the maximum height
it takes longer to come back together.
- You introduced the mechanic of it.
- But I didn't create any disincentives to that.
- You do more damage for the higher up you go,
but there's no downside.
- There's no downside.
- I could jump up one foot and I'm still proud.
- It doesn't take longer to recover
or do more damage going forward.
No, I realized that after the fact, yeah.
And that's on me.
And this is part of a learning podcast.
So yeah, go for it.
- Okay.
(high-pitched squeaking)
Crit one, failure.
- Really?
- Yep.
Or is it a DC?
CritFail.
No, it's not.
Wow, you got a CritFail.
So you jump up 30 feet and you just like go somewhere else?
You just keep going.
Through the skybox.
You just keep going in the area?
Yeah.
I'm just suspended in the sky.
You clip through the skybox and reload in this area when the system sort of realizes
that like, oh, the model is sort of out of frame and we got to reload it.
More reality is broken.
But you're also shattered too.
So you're still in, you're still in, uh, uh, crap mode.
Nate's sacked!
Okay.
Uh, SentryEgg, you're up.
How many people are around me?
Uh, well, uh, only one went after you.
Two went after him.
So there's only one right in front of you, but all of them are kind of around you-ish.
What'd you say there?
Did you say that they're, um, 15 feet around me?
Uh, yes.
Well, I'm, I just, I don't know what to do.
I'm an old man.
You start peeing.
I just, I'm sitting here and I'm just, "Oh no! Oh dear!"
And I just pee all over the ground.
That's right, your horse urine leaking out of your body.
I didn't mean to do this, I swear!
Okay.
Oh, heavens.
Play it as it lies.
That is a six.
Oh my god.
Domenico. Domenico got a crit. Okay.
everybody did very poorly except for the main guy so they all the three guys who
are around like as you're peeing your horse pees like leaks out of your body
they all go whoa wait is that an attack it's not it's a it's a it's a Domenico
is marked just saying oh no cuz it's a saving throw thing you know it's not
just saying but Domenico is marked so if you do an attack roll on him was it me
you get advantage which actually that's what i should have asked you
who are you targeting specifically dominico
don't say to me
say to medicare
you can see them
you'll say to me that it was a little while ago and i think i think i think i
can
noted that it was after him ago i'm gonna be real i was going after the guys
who are going to be
you know she could have can i appreciate that uh... but you
uh... just
uh... for fucked up some
some some some some some some guys some comments
some commas i was gonna say commas
uh...
and you did
you did five damage to both of them and they're knock prone
uh... all three of the guys are knock prone except for Domenico
uh... so that's pretty good
damn so you guys all have advantage on them
for melee attacks on your next turn
do i have another move after that?
no no no no do i get to roll or anything away?
can i roll away out of embarrassment
you know what i want you to be a reader of the first five dollars you'd be good
for you disengage action to roll away and embarrass them okay i do that
capital
well
there are about five hundred not the mountain all right i don't know what i
would think that there's an army here
i'm gonna go into this army and and try to clean my pants are the threat of
I've been wearing pants this whole time.
[Laughter]
Okay.
Why did you diss Aide away from the mic like that? It scared me.
[Mumbling]
I'm gonna tackle Domenico.
I'm gonna launch.
I'm gonna use my wiener like a spring
and spring up in the air and hit him in the face
with my egg-shaped, egg-shell
white body. And I have advantage, so...
Roll again.
Okay, that's 14.
On whom? Domenico.
hits him okay royal demolish that's nine damage nice okay yeah he's really not
looking good or wait no that's ten damage he's my bad but extra not looking
good um yeah you ram it to him oh man can my floppy wiener going is up his nose up
Not the floppy wiener in my nose!
[Laughter]
That's how Joakim laughs.
Is he laughing?
[Laughter]
This is like that one episode.
What's the one? I don't remember.
Oh, you saw the...
Oh...
I thought I scrubbed that one.
The collaboration with Vivid Media.
I poked my head out of the RV
RV and I see the penis and the nose and I go...
Here come your peas, boy.
As you're beating these guys down and it's their turn now and suddenly Domenico perks
up and he goes, "El Conejo."
And he looks around and all of his guys go, "El Conejo."
We'll be back. We'll be back. We'll fuck you guys up and they all start to run away
Sex with us there in mail
Up and down and all which ways there you know I think I'm gonna stay right here
There in melee range of you guys wait in various capacities, so you can
roll for an opportunity. I'm like I'm spinning around and using my I'm
slapping him in the face with my dick. Okay, yeah, Domenico is pretty low right
now and I have advantage, but that's a 22. I assume that roll. See if you get
crit. Okay, now it's not crit. Yeah, roll for damage
to
man. You didn't kill him. You slap him. But can you have a big dick shaped
like a punisher for the rear for the rest of the
do i get one 'cause i just wrote that net twenty
you do get a head on to guide one of the two guys is running away from you
okay i a
i take off my white glove and i slap him
as you guys don't have white gloves i have white glove have white rain
rayman rain man rayman gloves no you already said you have no arms and legs
legs you hold stuff like you guys are stealing my shit I have white gloves I
have black platform boots and I have a long flaccid penis and you guys can't
have any of those things those are my things you get I pull out my black
gloves okay that's fine I pull my black gloves out of my egg pocket and I slap
one of the guys and I say what I'm not even a pocket that's he can have an egg
pocket I have an egg pocket you didn't say you had an egg pocket yet though
should have ever says if you're famous for his pockets on the front of his
over rolls but hey whatever. I rolled a nat 6. Do I get to hit them? No. Okay. They run
away from you. They get away. As he's leaving Domenico. Do I do any damage to anybody? What
did you get? I got a nat 20. Oh yeah roll, what's your basic attack? It's a d10 I think.
Oh damn why'd I do that? Yeah roll that, roll that twice. This one? Where is this a d10?
- Isn't that a D10?
- That's your hit dice.
- Yeah, he's right.
No, he's right if it's a D10.
- For hit dice?
- Oh, for hit dice.
Oh no, sorry, let me look at my sheet.
I have this sheet up here.
- Is it a D4?
- But it is a D10, you should roll a D10.
- No, it's a D6.
- Roll a D10.
- So it was regular dice.
What was that?
It was a one, okay, and then what do you get?
- I got a two.
- So three plus three, six.
So you just extinguish one of them.
I mean, they just like take it in the face and keep running.
take in the face
no don't bridge so dominica
uh...
uh... which
you know but i don't know if he's running
rips i guess what i get for our to hear that he has and throws them on the
ground like
is a cure
date we surrender and he just keeps running he's running away
you guys see the localize
the gloves are read tonight yorkshire that and while he's was running away
still in rein sixty up to sixty feet
i've tried it and i definitely have to say because he's not gonna run
what's a soldier and it's been a great movie space so he's full action
so you can get up and i mean i even uses for me because i don't know if you're
right here and you're talking to attack and myself advantage
that is uh... eighteen i mean you hit him
okay uh... uh... will you have a little as far as
dominica there's a wild and yet he said
use fucking like
and uh...
the proper
good job hitting that cuban
I don't want him in the neighborhood anymore
specifically the white cubans
specifically only white cubans have a cuban man
you see
yeah
before he goes on his sort of vaguely like somehow not racist racist rant you
You guys have the golden basket, you have the golden eggs, you heard about some El Conejo
guy but um...
As a Cuban man I know that means rabbit.
You do know that.
Oh that's common knowledge.
What's a rabbit?
It chases the children.
The rabbit...
Has tricks.
Rabbit has, he has cereal and yogurt in the children.
You can roll wisdom saving throw as you're listening to this
13 yeah, all right you're able to sort of stave off madness
Anybody older than 70 trying to talk to you and there's also a leprechaun they chase him for his cereal, too
So what are we gonna do with these? Well, we're gonna lure up those hogs class. Yeah, you guys
I'll talk
Finally have grandkids. I'm young diamond full of cam. What's
diamond
I can't hear too. Well guys, excuse me. Who are you? I'm the egg Sino
Hey, we'm J
What's your name again shut up old man shut up old man, my name is century egg
I'm 50. Nope. I'm
hundred
and i would love to go to the eggcino in my final days
eggcino eggcino
i never got an episode of the eggcino
here we go
let me call my crew
yeah yeah yeah you guys can go to the eggcino
theres an eggcino in brooklyn texas
of course there is
is there an alamo draft house here
no
ok
I'll go to the egg-cino. I think I'd like to see... just to see what it's like. I don't know that I'm gonna gamble.
What else is in the golden Easter basket?
Just eggs?
Just golden goose eggs.
No candy?
Alright, we're at the egg-cino.
Yeah, it's the most valuable, you know, thing though.
So yeah, we're at the egg-cino, shaped like a giant egg.
Uhhh.
So the casino's not shaped like a guy.
[laughter]
Beats a little on the nose, huh?
- This is strange.
- Eggsy now.
- How come all of our buildings are shaped
like giant versions of us?
I just started thinking about that.
- Kind of obvious, yeah?
An egg building?
- I mean, I've seen human buildings.
- With the money you have is eggs,
so the buildings are also eggs, you're also eggs.
- Why couldn't it just be a building?
- Yeah, so the guitar--
- Madison was literally poking holes in this this morning.
She's like, "Why is the money eggs also?
"They're eggs."
- But guitar casino in Florida,
that's for guitars then, right?
That's what a guitar stick is, it's shaped like a guitar.
I know a guitar back in the day when I swam here from Ed Cuba.
I met a guitar.
You're Cuban?
I'm Cuban.
I'm Ed Cuban.
I come from a Cuban chicken.
One of those ones that they have all, walking around all the time.
One of the ones that runs around in a modern warfare level.
Yes!
So yeah, you guys are at the AXE, you know.
It was Slash's guitar!
What game do you guys want to play?
Slash.
Well, first we got, you know what we got to do first.
Give me the briefcase.
It's a basket!
It's a basket, I brought a briefcase.
Biscuit case.
I give him a briefcase that has nothing in it.
Now I get to pretend like I'm a businessman.
Hello, yeah, I'd like to have five million dollars in chips because I'm a businessman.
Sure, sir.
Would you, do you have?
I'm looking on reef case. I'm obviously a businessman. Right. Do you have
anything about chips? I'm doing I'm doing, but I mean, I've taken I've
taken my third of the basket and I'm doing all one spin on a on a slot
machine. I've up to the like credits, so it's however much money that is.
I'm doing like a billion dollars. You can't spend all the money because
then nobody's going to want to hunt us. I want to hunt. What are you
talking about we have money where the egg Sina all of my money.
Hey, that's not our fault. Yeah, I think all of my money is like I think they're
golden children that I can that I can make my grandkids.
Okay, so you're coming on your third. I have them all in a pupus.
I have all my money in a pupus. Yeah, where you get the pupus New York.
I have I spent an egg.
I traded an egg for it.
So and then what are you doing with your third?
I'm gonna bet it all on it egg
At the rule egg table the rule egg
Yes, I traded another egg for a big red egg dress and I'm my my the arm that doesn't exist is around his shoulder
Yeah, I have one arm around your waist
Yeah, we head
that roll that business man's wife.
You guys are going to end up with only one third of the loot.
So if I roll these two d twenties and I get two twenties, can I win this?
The spin? What do you mean? What do you mean? We're going to, you know,
the odds, have you fixing this against us? It's just based on, yeah, wait,
I don't even want to roll. I mean, he sounds like he's, yeah,
it's 50 50 odds on a roulette table. Okay. You got to give me 20,
20 50 odds on a roulette 20s or 19s. I get twenties.
i when i get nineteen cells the one
that's fine yeah
or what it's like a freezer for a small but fifteen to twenty
okay doubles of fifty are done i think this is very unfair mine's gotta be
anything over eleven i went
and i think i think that is your own point and i'm calling a lot of our
immediate to things over eleven
zero to win
i think that's fair on the slot
Mm-hmm two things do they have to be doubles so to win two things over 11 to
rolls over 11 before two rolls under 11. Yeah, you know
Nice track. That's good, though. No two rolls over a lot of like in one roll
Okay, so if I just go it's good though if I get two numbers
This is a gambler. What's up two numbers over 11? Yeah, sure two numbers over 11
Yeah, two numbers over a look. I'm rolling. I win the slut 14 14. Okay, that's over 11
That's over 11 by my count.
Alright, roll the dice.
And 12.
Okay, yeah, you win that one. That's okay.
So he doubles his eggs?
He doubles his golden eggs.
Okay, I'm spinning the slot.
Okay, so one of them.
You've lost all your golden eggs.
That's okay, I made up the losses.
He did make up the losses.
I'll spin it. I'm out of luck.
I'm through. I didn't win on this spin, so I'm going to win on the next one.
It's gonna juice!
It's a juicy magusa.
It's a juice or a mcgristle, come on.
You promise?
Yeah, come on, hand it over.
Alright.
I had him at half the ice.
I promise.
Sure.
Okay, I lost again.
Give me the other, come on.
Believe in him, he's gonna juice!
I mean, he lost toys in a red one until he loses three toys in a red.
I'm gonna win, come on.
You gotta believe in him!
Oh, here they are.
By the power of Christ!
Uh, I lost again.
Well, I'm all out of--
Come on, give me the rest, give me the rest.
The rest I think, and he's--
Alright, I believe in you!
I'm seriously due.
I'm gonna give you my eggs!
Okay, I'm spinning.
Okay, I lost a bet.
(Laughter)
Well, no money.
At least we got...
I guess we have to plan a robbery!
(Laughter)
I think we need to rob the casino now.
That'd be an amazing idea!
Let's rob the casino!
Let's build together a group.
a group. We need 11 eggs to rob this casino. With different oiconic abilities. I'm getting
a sudden desire to eat in every single scene. I think we should skip to our second house
cause then we'll have 12 eggs and it's a dozen. Yeah that's a good idea. That makes a lot
more sense. Good point. I hope there's never a baker's dozen. I just noticed at the bottom
of this basket there's a blinking transponder looking thing and I'm
hungry so I'm thinking I'm gonna swallow it just so whatever happens next happens
next I don't know there's a piece of paper here it says El Conejo will look
for you no matter what I'm so hungry I'm wrong
you have to remember that El Conejo has principles all right we don't know
that yeah well you will know that soon whoa that was on the intercom okay so
because we spent so much money this case because you know we already have to we
have to be have a comp room right yes you do have a comp I think that's totally
fair so I'm gonna go up listen that would be crazy if they didn't give you
yeah just give them so much fucking yeah I'm gonna go up to my to my room it's
all it's egg themed of course right and I'm gonna I'm gonna kick my shoes off
Well, I'm the only one who played.
Nuh-uh, I did roulette.
You did one of a third of a bunch of money.
They don't want you to win though.
We share a room. We're sharing a room.
I'm in my red dress.
I gave you all my money.
I'm in my red dress at the bar and I'm looking for the wealthiest looking man in the world.
Okay, where are you two at?
We're in our room watching TV.
Yeah, we have our shoes off.
I'm flipping through the channels.
Finding Yoakman.
I know they have it.
They have to have it.
You're at the bar.
I'm starting to think you never had a TV show.
Can I roll to see if they have Yoakman's World?
Uh, let's roll Investigation, yeah.
Okay.
Flipping the channels is Investigation.
I'm down with that.
Ooh, that's fun.
Five.
You don't, you can't find, you just find, like, this fucking place sucks.
Find QVC Chambers.
We gotta get the fuck out of here.
It's a free room.
It's the worst fucking casino I've ever been to.
Please, please, please.
I've ever been to. Place a fucking bulls- I dial the front desk. Hello?
Hi, how are you doing? Shut the fuck up!
I'm checking out now, and I want all my money back.
Okay, sir. Well, uh
Sure, I'll get right on that for you then. She said sure you get your money back. Oh, yeah
Oh, this is the best casino, the best casino ever. No, well no you're not gonna be able to get your money back
You already said sure
I'll speaker phone no I'm just loud and you have great here my is a layout to
your layout you in the casino I'm at the bar in the yeah you're looking for the
wealthiest man I'm I'm I have a martini in my hand I'm
swirling the olive back and forth I hope no rich people try to fuck me Oh
Oh heavens!
You're going to drive them away saying that.
You see a...
No, that's like the worst strategy ever.
I hope they do, yeah.
You're going to attract some guys like fucking no one...
You're attracting rich rapists.
Yeah.
That's a horrible technique.
I hope I don't get fucked.
I'm attracting them for the lawsuit money.
Oh, okay.
All right.
I'm not going to try to interrogate that.
Um, yeah, you see a, uh, uh...
"I hope nobody fucks me."
"Oh, I hope nobody takes me to dinner and then has sex with me!"
"A man can earn money!"
He's a man, but he looks...
He's got a peculiar haircut.
And he looks at you and he says,
"I don't want to fuck you."
"I don't want to fuck you either, you look like a mushroom."
*laughing*
Oh, is that so?
Look at you!
I have not looked at myself.
Dusty-ass old bitch!
I'm 100 years old!
Congratulations.
Whoa! You have a shiny pin on your lapel!
What is that?
It's something I got for being a good-
It's four lines!
intersecting
do you know
and it's red and black
with white on it
why do you have that pin on? let me look
holy crap
(laughing)
what the hell? why are you wearing that?
I guess this is Texas
and there's a lot of them here
do you know the story of Easter?
huh?
when Christ
rose from the dead
I'm so old.
100 years later.
And he hands you a D20.
Uh huh.
Whoa.
And he says.
Damn.
Nerd.
Why I heard that?
He says.
Did you bring this?
Oh I think it's a nerd game.
Did you bring this color D20 specifically for this?
Damn.
So sick dude.
Roll the dice.
Roll the dice?
You're gonna have to.
I don't have any more money to roll the.
Hold on.
Let me go get more chips.
No no you don't need the money.
I need to get more chips. You don't need money. You need to buy me chips before I roll this dice
You don't ask the bartender for chips. Come on now
We just can we just get some chips chips and salsa
Some chips I'm allergic to guacamole
Okay, and avocado if you don't onions you don't roll this dice
You're getting me chips!
I'm not rolling the dice until you get me chips and salsa!
I'll roll it for you.
I'll roll it then!
Please kill us.
Eleven.
Okay.
Do I add anything to that?
No. Hold on. One second.
He opens his Dungeon Master's Guide.
Yes.
Where's that little book you got there?
Okay, hold on. So...
I'm holding.
holding. Well you have 11, so we're going to divide that by 2. What is that 5.5? What's
your birthday? Uh, 1. 1, 1. What year is it? Oh, I don't want to say. I feel like I don't
want to date too much of the modern campaigns. What year is it? It's 2022. Okay, I guess
1922. Okay, hold on one second. New Year's Day. I was the New Year's baby one year. Do you know what time?
What time?
I'm turning it into Unix code. Hold on. It's 836, right?
What time I was born? Do you know how many seconds?
It's fine, don't worry about it. I was born at 56 10 o'clock
Okay, we're going to take that number and then we're going to
Hold on one second. I've got to call my friend Roger. Hold on
Roger he's gonna take that number and divide it by 5.5, but he's gonna call his friend Roger Roger
From American dad. No, it's Roger if Roger didn't have breakfast but did have his multivitamin
The target gets a head start of 30 seconds on him
If Roger did have breakfast and it was a grain and it was an odd number
There's a whole set of rules for this. This is your chance to get away.
He has to go through this entire rule set.
And you can get away right now.
I... Hold on, let me just...
Do I have... Did I...
Did I get my chips?
You did not get your chips.
I'm gonna wait for my chips.
He's going to call Roger.
Roger.
Where are the chips? Oh god!
I'm going back into this kitchen right now!
I walk into the kitchen.
Okay.
Wait, wait, hold on.
Okay, okay, yeah.
So that's the Easter Bunny.
He's coming after you now.
Is he look like a bunny?
Looks like a rabbit with a great haircut.
It's a normal question.
Is he look like a bunny?
Is he looks like a bunny?
I'm storming down to the front desk too, so I'm out of the room.
I'm checking out.
come in with a suitcase so I filled it's felt like a complimentary tote bag with
all the bed
Oh sir sir please you need to put some this is why I walk out of the kitchen
into the front lobby I walk out of the kitchen in the front lobby I see you
doing that and I walk up and I go "BRAH BRAH BRAH BRAH BRAH!"
"BRAH BRAH BRAH BRAH BRAH!"
"BUBBA BUBBA BUBBA!"
"NO CHIPS!"
What was that, the multivitamin or?
There's no chips in the kitchen!
Mkay.
"WOAH A BUNNY!"
There's no- Oh that guy would not buy me any chips!
I'm gonna talk to him.
You go talk to him and get me chips!
What are you up to?
What's he up to?
Are you with me?
on the other important in the market
i'm charging it all you have great
you know it's not
had by now
hold on had by what you want
while you're getting steps
i'm a woman right now
but later i'll change into something else and then after that i'll change in
the southern different later
roll a dice
what are the
basically i have no gender because i'm an ed
i wrote a three
I rolled a three.
Okay, what is your birthday?
I don't know.
You don't know your birthday?
Nope.
This is going to be hard.
Try January 1st, 1922.
[Laughter]
Well, that's not my birthday. I don't have, I don't think I have one.
You know, I think about it, an egg doesn't really have a birthday because it's not born yet.
So, I don't actually think...
I mean, a chicken's born from an egg.
What came first?
Well, the egg.
Huh?
The chicken comes after the egg.
What came first?
The egg.
Who?
Who's egg first?
He takes role initiative.
You just broke his brain.
You're watching porn?
I'm trying to, but actually right now I run down.
Yaukman, Yaukman, I fanned an episode of your show.
Really? Which one? Which one?
The one we were talking about earlier.
I didn't even know they showed that episode on TV.
I thought we just put that one on laser disk and then we threw them all on a fire.
I remember when they made laser disk!
Me too!
It was the worst day of my life!
*laughter*
Me too!
I'm...
Uh...
That's the con- that's the condejo!
I'm the Easter Bunny.
That's Mr. Nerdo!
His name is Comerculo!
You have something that belongs to me.
What?
My basket.
Oh, yeah, I'll take a hand. Yeah, we hand on the basket. You can have the biscuit. That's a bathroom
Where are the eggs?
What else where ads we lost all the eggs
You will need to get me back the eggs
Okay, well, what does she know? Yeah, we just have we'll have to read us have to go through that
Well, we'll figure that out.
Just give us a few minutes.
You've already ordered chips.
Roll deception.
Sit down and eat the chips.
All of us?
I got a 3. He got a nat 20.
I got a nat 20.
I got a 7.
I hate what I've done to it.
Gary Gygax hates me.
Look at that.
I have to put on my glasses to see.
a nat 20 on that. Yeah if it is what that is. Fuck. There's like no way for him to
believe you except that pretty much. I gave him like very high wisdom because I
was afraid of this. So just sit here you eat the chips. He has +6 on wisdom and +4 on proficiency.
We're gonna get this all sorted out. You just sit here and eat the chips.
is broken. That's on me. So he just goes, okay.
Can I have some of the chips before I go?
I slap him in the face with my dick before we walk out.
Just take advantage of the net toy.
Yeah. Roll, roll, attack roll with advantage.
You stupid floppy dick.
That is an 11.
is not good enough
you know i had a good idea of for the person sitting next to him
it's been a long time remember
all of your commitment to the president should you know one of my biggest fans
right
uh... well you know we have a little you want to do is have a very good and
short do you have a whole biscuit for like golden eggs
no
i have seen it next to you
uh... i don't
What?
Get out of my sight.
Okay, well, great to meet you, Yolkman.
*explosion*
Well, alright.
Wait, can I roll? Can I do a roll right now?
You can do whatever you want.
This is gonna...
You gotta restart the fight, though.
I will say.
No, we need to get out of here.
We need to leave.
I was gonna try and steal his wallet.
Wait, wait, oh, we should steal that guy's car keys, so...
Oh, that's it? Okay.
We gotta have a car.
We probably got here.
I've got an 18.
Do we have a car?
uh... let's take this guy's car
yeah i steal his car keys
you do it quick
you have an impala
you can take this guy's car though
can i use the fact that i'm in the red dress to seduce him with maybe a persuasion
with this roll instead of a slight of hand
so you already have the slight of hand
oh ok i see what you're doing
you already have a slight of hand roll so you can take it
i'll let you try to seduce him with this move though
tell me how it goes
so i've already already have his car keys
the
so you're just a warning i'm doing this because i'm doing this because
i can let this beautiful dress go to waste i traded an egg for it for god's
sakes
i walk up to my say hello
uh... while she had
this all down there
group in the world persuasion
Can I help him out?
I shaved all down there!
What do you do to help him out?
Not my legs though!
Please let me fuck you!
And I roll with it now.
You're the sexiest girl in the world!
Any man would be lucky to fuck you!
What? Why do you throw the dice like that?
It's like a two year old.
Well I got a 17.
Do it straight up in the air.
Wow you really shaved?
Why don't I say- everyone else in the campaign so far
sounded like they're from Texas except me.
Back off, she's mine.
I shaved everything!
Wraps!
Of my legs and my thighs!
I'm getting a phone call.
I shaved one square off my pussy.
Bring, bring, bring!
I pull the phone up.
I can't fuck you, my son has cancer.
Well, I guess I'm gonna go with him.
You owe me $70.
You got his car keys, right?
Yeah.
I would turn to him and be like...
I'm going to kill you.
I was thinking of featuring...
I saw you from across the bar and I was thinking of featuring you on an episode of Yolkman's Garage.
Could I ask you what color and make your car is, sir?
Oh, sure.
It's, uh, it's a Mazda...
Oh God, what's the model?
Mazda Miata?
Heavens! Is it lowered?
Let me just look up...
Do you have a lowered Mazda Miata?
Look up some models.
Does it have a straight pipe?
I'm looking at the Mazda website right now.
from high school.
I just, it's a simple question.
It's a Mazda CX9.
Okay, uh, what color is it?
It's gray.
Yeah, no chance.
Sorry, pal.
Well, we'll see ya.
Okay, well, I'll keep these and we're gonna go.
And while I'm leaving, I turn the alarm on in the car.
All of you roll dexterity saving throws because the Easter Bunny is shooting his Fortnite
egg launcher at you.
What?
I got a 16.
I got a crit 1.
I got a 19.
Oh, I got a 17, actually.
Okay, you two are gonna be okay.
You're gonna take some fucking damage damn
whoopsie
the Easter Bunny says
to you God damage
Excuse me fist bump on that one. It's good as hell. It's boom. It's actually fucking fire
Gotta make that sense of people know we're fist bumping my sides are in orbit
Trick Norbit
Norbit from Shrek yep
Come on, which rate take 12 plays tracking that 12 damage. Yeah, dude. I'm at four
We got to get out of here four inches. Yeah, no, no, dude. It's closer to seven
No on the egg on the egg. Oh, all right word you guys can use your full movements this turn to run. Hey, I'm running
I'm cartwheeling. I'm gonna shoot another egg launcher at you. I
Even I opened my legs at him
Why are you all said just like a fucking
Sexual bit like these are from like just sort of old man
We build Cosby to sort of whore like I like the trajectory here. I'll be right there
I'm a blank canvas true. You're right. It's like you'd be painted egg is nature's. Yeah. He's a true Easter egg
Yeah, yeah, all of you roll dexterity saving throws again
That doesn't count you didn't say roll. I did say roll. It doesn't I got a 7. Oh, I got a 23 this year, okay?
How am I not in the fucking car yet?
I got a four.
How am I not in the Mazda?
That one's bad.
Yeah?
It's very bad.
You're gonna take 15 damage.
I'm dead, brother!
I took 15?
Humpty Dumpty's dead?
Uh, yeah, you're at six.
Humpty Dumpty is dead. You can carry him.
I carry him.
Alright.
He's trying to shoot you further.
Oh, the egg launcher went straight into my cooter!
I'm gonna push it back out and try and hit him. It's a battle royale
Shoot can I shoot? I just wanna I want a shoot that lot rocket out of my my pussy at the
You're an egg I'm an egg I can have whatever I want
Curious no because it's where he's an hour in ten minutes. I know you need to lay down the law
I know it's one of these things where I'm like I want to play the game that Patrick is playing
because that sounds much more creative where it's like yeah now I have a pussy and I could
shoot egg eggs out of that. Don't let him do this to you. I know I can't let you do this.
You need to have some more more pride. It is an hour and 10 minutes. I've been doing this with
you guys for two years. You can't do it. Why did you look at your watch for two years? He's had a
timer going the entire time. It's a little joke. All right yeah so you guys are able to get to the
the car. You are knocked out, though. I tied my wiener around his leg to drag him
behind me while I run. So you get to the Mazda CX-9. Okay, okay, what part of your
body do you want me to tie my wiener around? Fucking my lips. Okay, your lips.
Okay, you have to get to the airport. The airport is in Universal Studios, Texas,
so it's two days journey. It's Good Friday. You can get there by Easter Sunday.
okay my nephew works at the airport what's this see we just got guys we just
got to be quiet it'll pass we just don't have to feed it okay curious person I
always ask the fall that's my problem you're right I won't say anything I'm
resuscitating Humpty Dumpty okay how are you doing that I guess I'm driving
The 100 year old egg is driving the car.
I'm bouncing up and down on him.
Like a trampoline.
Don't you fucking die!
You do that thing?
Say the fucking words!
Do I need a death saving roll or no?
Yeah, you do.
Okay.
Unless you guys are...
One of you guys has smells.
Hey, now I'm bouncing up and down.
One of you guys I think has healing.
Hey, I'm bouncing up and down on his damn...
You're the one with healing?
On his damn lower back like a trampstampoline.
Yeah, sure.
I think I gave...
I'll do it on the chive later.
You gave me defender egg.
I know I gave you defender egg. I thought I gave one egg.
That's what I was trying to do with my pussy.
I don't have any healing.
No yoke man I thought I gave you healing.
How do I do this death saving roll again?
You gave me a melee attack and a ranged attack and that's it.
Oh shit.
Oh well. Roll death saving throw.
I thought I was healing him. Wait hold on I can't stabilize him.
Oh you can stabilize him.
I'm sorry about that.
Rolled you 20.
Oh my god.
Uh, 20.
Not natural.
But that's fine.
He's stabilized.
You're stabilized so you only need to do death saving throws.
Beast mode.
Uh, we'll basically like-
It's gonna be my new catchphrase the rest of the campaign.
What was it?
Beast mode.
Are you saying beast mode or beast mode?
I guess beast mode would make sense because we're food.
Like a wild beast.
Like a-
Beast?
Are you saying beast mode?
Like a wild beast.
Are you saying base or beast?
I don't know what base or beast is.
Who is this?
Why did you turn this damn radio off?
There's so much going on in that damn car.
I can't focus while I'm driving.
I can never play.
So yeah, you guys are driving in the Mazda CX-9.
You're booking it.
Obviously, the Easter Bunny is after you.
You drive for hours and hours and hours. You're now resuscitated. Let's get you at roll a hit die
So let's figure out how much you get. I think your hit die is 8? D8, right?
Which one? It's the one that's like two triangles. This one?
One
Cool, but add your con
It's zero. So you got one back. Okay, it's not bad. You got one HP brother
So you guys, but here's the thing you guys have the opportunity to stop at a motel. Can I heal up too?
Um, yeah, you guys can all do short rests for this.
Okay.
Short rest is how much hit dice?
How many times are you rolling?
You guys all have two hit dice for this one.
Oh, okay.
I'm gonna roll technically level two for this one.
Okay, so I can roll another one?
Yes.
Okay, I got 10 back.
Oh, shit.
I'm at 14.
I'm up to seven.
Damn, playboy!
Look at me!
I'm 7 HP.
Okay.
I got 7 plus 6.
Cool.
What is that?
Thirteen.
You got it.
So you guys are at a motel.
If you guys- you guys can stay at a motel rather.
Sorry, I didn't mean you're at a motel.
You can either do a rest stop, you can stay at a motel.
Or you can just keep driving.
I'm driving this car to Chuck E. Cheese.
If you keep-
*snickers*
I don't know why that got me.
The only 24 hour Chuck E. Cheese in Texas and they know me.
They know me there.
If you guys drive-
It's like a casino but you pay more.
There's a chance that the Easter Bunny finds you.
Remember there was a whole system I developed for this but we don't have time.
But instead, here's what it is.
There's a chance that the Easter Bunny finds you.
If you keep driving, the Easter Bunny probably won't find you at the motel.
If you just drive through it.
He's not going to find you.
He won't find you at the motel.
He probably won't find you on the road.
It's very unlikely.
What's the disadvantage then?
If you stay at the motel, you can do a long rest.
If you keep driving though, you become cooked.
So you saw those eggs in the field?
There's two ways that that happens to eggs.
When they don't get proper rest or when they're just generally killed.
If you're cooked, you have half HP, disadvantage on ability checks, and saving throws until
you long rest.
I don't care, I'm getting cooked.
I'm in the car, I'm driving.
I'm ready to get cooked.
I could, I could.
Let's take a vote.
Alright, I'm ready.
I vote to go to the motel.
Sounds pretty beast mode to me.
I still don't know if you're saying "baste" or "beast."
I vote for "cucked."
Alright, well I guess we're at a stalemate.
No you are the one who could... there is no stalemate, there's three of you.
So I'm gonna just crash the car into oncoming traffic.
That's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna crash this car into oncoming traffic.
Please vote.
I'm gonna drive the car all the way into oncoming traffic and no one's gonna survive.
There's gonna be no survivors.
Everyone here is gonna die with me tonight.
Here's the thing.
And I pull into the motel.
I was gonna let you do that.
Oh shit, I missed all the traffic.
I pulled off of the off ramp and went into this motel.
So I'm going to roll for Easter Bunny and see if he finds you.
I'm not going to tell you the result.
He's got to tell.
Okay.
I saw it.
He found us.
It was a 100.
I looked at his eyes.
He did a little smile.
He found us.
What do you guys do at the motel?
What do you guys do?
I probably get fucking killed by Easter Bunny, obviously.
Flipping the channels.
I'm still in my red dress.
I'm standing out front.
(laughing)
- Welcome to the Acarolage, I'm the concierge.
- I thought you were working the streets.
- You can pay me for sex.
- Okay, just checking.
- That's what I thought, yeah.
- All right, cool.
What are you guys, you guys watching TV again?
- I'm flipping, yeah, I'm flipping.
- Can I roll? - Roll investigation.
- I'm kind of, I'm occupying sort of a henchman role
for him. - Okay, cool.
- Yeah.
- Dumpty Dumpty is the henchman for the more famous Yoakaman.
- That's a 12.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Everyone knows Yoakaman.
- I was a minor celebrity back in the day, you know?
You may be ahead of me, but--
- Oh yeah, no, you're honestly,
you're one of my biggest inspirations.
- Nah, you don't mean that.
- No, I'm serious.
- That's straight beast, man.
(laughing)
- I studied a lot of your work for my episode,
The Stupid Ant.
(laughing)
The Stupid Ant, that's the sequel
to The Stupidest Ant in the World.
I'm poking a guy in a machine and I'm asking you the highest compliments I've
ever had.
I inspired in episode of Yankman.
My God, you from my episode.
I also you're also inspired to be a fucker egg who poops himself.
Yokeman fucks a pig that one was based on me.
Yeah, that's one of my favorite episodes for obvious reasons.
*laughter*
I'm gonna find you a show on TV no matter what.
And I just started like punching in numbers on the microwave.
*laughter*
Don't think it's on this one.
You're all a hundred years old.
It's not on 1 minute 30.
It's not on popcorn.
*laughter*
Let's check defrost.
These channels suck!
Try a timer!
Basic cable. Cheap ass motel.
Um, yeah you guys get a good night's rest.
Easter Bunny isn't there. Woah. So I have 26
until he's not. No, I'm playing fair and square
in this. Okay. So, yeah. You guys can
now make it to Universal Studios Airport. Alright. I'm there.
You can take a flight out of this god forsaken state
With your money that you don't have
When we have our you know, we do have a wealth of experience. Yes friendship and memories
In that motel by a fat old guy older than me Thank You darling
I was too tired to drive. Thanks you
So grab you grant huge giant
You have I sucked and fucked you great. Well, my name is huge ass, but
What you told me you were Hugh Grant? Oh, no. Oh no one do I'm not getting paid
Famously doesn't pay his horse my mistake. I said grass gas or ass
You guys are at the airport
What do you guys want to do you guys
Know
Patrick and then
I'm standing I'm standing you let it flow. I couldn't do that
Where would be okay to be a terrorist? It's an Easter one. I'm standing in front of the airport
I'm doing jumping jacks. I'm saying
We got away from the Easter Bunny we did it he's gone. He's never gonna see me
He's never gonna pull up in a car.
He's never gonna know where we are.
We did it. We did it.
He's never gonna know that we're here.
He's not pulling up right now.
Now. Now.
3, 2, 1, now.
I have pre-checked, which line do I go in?
The Easter egg hunt.
If the Easter egg hunt led you here, what use was the hunt?
What?
What does that mean?
I read it in the fortune cookie.
Sounds like an oddly specific fortune cookie, some kind of Easter Chinese restaurant.
Do they serve egg old?
Egg food old?
Do they serve egg too old?
That's gonna be a fist bump with me.
Let's go!
It was base mode.
(Laughter)
At that Chinese restaurant, they serve egg foo old.
(Explosion)
I'm going to kill you all now.
I have TSA pre-check you can't kill me into that water.
TSA pre-check?
You can't kill me?
You have TSA pre-check?
TSA.
Okay.
You try getting a weird fucking egg cannon through TSA.
There's so many people here.
Are you going to kill us here?
here? I have a cold. Why didn't you kill us at the motel last night? You guys were at the motel?
Yeah. Where did you go to try and find us? I checked the waffle house. You checked the- oh
my god he checked the waffle house! The one connected to the hotel! One of you kept saying
that they were hungry. I thought- oh you stupid bitch! Why would we eat eggs in breakfast food?
We only eat dinner! Yeah we're eggs. I didn't think about that. You stupid bitch! Yeah I'm
Lock toward the security line. I'm gonna like you sir
Roll initiative oh
Owen oh
I'm Oh Nat 20. Oh
Nat 10 5
Nat 5 I already did that guys you're up first me awesome
I'm gonna I'm gonna yolk shot him. Oh really yeah, all right
That is a 10 does not hit
He's up. Oh, oh
He's gonna walk up to you and try to strangle you how you strangle an egg
Very try to crack me on step. Yeah, they try is the operative word here. Oh, yeah the operative word. All right. Oh
my god, I
Could give you a little Wow. He has a plus 10 on his attack roll for that and he got 12
because he got to oh okay. He's not able to strangle. Of course, I'm an egg.
All right, you're not bar. Yeah, I'm stupid ass. I mean shut up. I'm going to
do egg food. All right, remember earlier when I said egg food, that's a fist
That's what I was referring to!
Okay, I'm gonna fight you now!
I got an 11.
You are not gonna hit him. You guys are gonna have a very hard time hitting him.
I try to... I mean if I had arms and legs...
What? You're up.
If I had arms and legs, imagine me doing a cartwheel.
Okay. He didn't have better than... he didn't roll better than a 6 on initiative?
He got a 17.
Can I give you guys some...
some I'll give you guys a clue okay he has 500 HP and an AC of 22 okay that's
impossible for me to hit him because I have an initiative or ever you got a
crate you can hit him oh true it sounds easy enough you have to get an 18 or
higher for me so what are you okay then I guess what do you suggest we do I
suggest nothing as a dungeon master I just provide information well let's
think about the movie okay so in the nevermind I don't want to think about it
anymore I attack him I'm gonna do my great fall but I'm gonna go 10,000 feet
in the air and attack him for 1,000
- Hey, that's my sheet, he's assaulting me.
(laughing)
- Don't say that on mic.
- Let me see.
- Don't look at it, okay, he's going, come on.
- Go ahead, touch the sheet.
- Upwards of 30 feet high.
- Upwards, upwards, upwards of 30 feet.
That means anything above 30 feet.
- That's not what that means.
- Upwards of 30 feet, that is what that means.
- I'm looking up what upwards means now.
- Oh my God.
- Okay, it doesn't matter what upwards,
listen, it doesn't matter what upwards means in numbers,
first of all, that's true,
but also upwards is upwards, directionally,
- It has to be above 30 feet.
- 30 is the minimum.
- Minimum 30 feet.
- It does mean 30's the minimum.
- Yeah.
- Is it really?
Should I have wrote up to?
- It does, but if it doesn't--
- You should have said up to.
- No.
- Yes you, yeah.
- That's Patrick trying to trick me.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- If I know that, that's a problem.
- Listen to what I'm saying too.
It doesn't matter whether it means that or not,
because you go up for it.
- Okay, genuinely, I love when I get called out
on me not doing this.
I'm going to look it up right now. Upwards versus up to.
Guys, I think we win. Guys, I think we's going to win this.
Guys, I think we might actually win him.
This is the most, this is like, honestly,
the most tense I've ever felt in the DND session.
The most suspense ever.
Up to 10 feet tall means that, okay, here.
Up to 10 feet tall means that the tallest tree of that type is,
speak in the it's Google right.
Google with their trees right up words of ten feet tall implies that the tree
typically grows ten feet, but some or many examples may be taller than that.
Yes, all right, let's do
all right, so that I'm okay, so
wait, but I still have to hit him. Yeah, that's the thing I have to I have to
crit
that's one thing and i don't know can i
assist if i do that you're not even
gonna make me roll damage because
theoretically i can roll infinite die or
infinite guys can't wait wait even if
they were can you can you hold can you
hold can you hold this of us can you
pick both of us episode you'll never be
released
this will ruin my cred in the DM
community he's gonna hold on to both of
us as he goes up I have I mean like
basically doing my big jump
I can't wait to fly!
Yeah, we're both p- I'm piggybacking on you and he's piggybacking on me.
I'm gonna let you get advantage because you basically just called me a bitch in front of our
hundreds of millions of fans.
It's funny that I wasn't even thinking that. I was just gonna put my thumb over the rules
to hope that you didn't look and he actually got you with the whole word thing.
All right.
I'm very depressed.
That's 15, so that's 16.
Oh, come on, come on.
Oh, wait, what's my what do I add to my my AC is 22 so it's plus 5 what my I add 5
yes from what you see get a 17 or higher
it's okay you still mother I mean like look okay he's splats and if you don't
die from his attack right you can still kill him no idea yeah it is a deal this
worst day in my life okay this is genuinely so depressing that my like I
couldn't pick the right word you gotta know this by now patches nothing gets by
us I mean we're very clever oriented yeah yeah this is my nightmare okay uh all
right imagine getting called out by the three stupidest people the reason why
you guys pick me as your DM. I'm the fourth dumbest person. Okay, who's up though by the
way? I was top of the order. Right, he went and then you went, so you're up now, Century
Egg. Oh, no wait, you already went. No, I'm the top of the order. So you're up. Yeah,
I'm gonna yolk shot him again. Okay, that's a three. Yeah, it doesn't hit. Whoops! He's
He's up now, he's gonna try to do his egg move.
Okay.
Sure.
His egg, uh, oh yeah, so all you guys roll dexterity saving throws.
Uh oh.
Okay, that is an 11.
11.
No shit.
Alright.
20?
I got a nat 20.
Alright, so you're safe.
Fuck.
Play it as it lies.
Okay.
It's a 4, so.
It's a D4.
Nope.
Oh god.
What'd I say?
You take 14 damage.
1 HP.
Me too.
I'm at 6.
Great.
I take no damage?
You take none.
Cause I didn't do half damage shit with this one.
Why don't you give me some of your yolk?
You're up.
Me?
I'm up.
(whistling)
- Oh wait, no, no, you're up first.
- Sorry.
(whistling)
- I'm gonna use my urine.
- What is the DC?
- There's no real point to you guys attacking him, I guess.
- Actually, no, I'm gonna use Defender Egg.
- Yeah, that's a good idea.
- Well, no, that's a reaction.
- Well, I'm reacting to him being mean to me.
- All right, you could have done that earlier,
but I'll say that you used your reaction for him earlier.
So roll a D6.
- Yeah, 'cause I can use, I can reduce the damage
that any of my friends take.
- So roll a D6, roll a D6.
We'll retroactively do this. I mean, I got so fucking bitch made right now.
I got a three.
All right, so you are at four then, HP.
Okay.
But I have no, I can't do anything.
Get him. Get him.
I've been completely fucking, I am totally solid right now.
I need everyone to blow on this stuff.
This is the worst day, a worst day of my life.
Come on, get him.
Damn, fuck.
All right, then this time, don't blow on it.
Okay.
Actually, you blow on it.
Blow on it.
Go ahead.
Blow on it now.
I blow on it's going to get it.
Oh,
close okay, fifteen or twenty, I guess all right, you're up top of the order,
okay, I'm yoke shouting him.
That's a twelve nope, he's up running out of yoke, I'm looking very thin and
ring, he's going to try to strangle you.
Is that you trying to strangle me or is that you think it is me, what do you
I think that it's you personally. Can I jump in front of it?
What if the entire airport becomes like a world war Z mob and they're all
defending me like a giant human? I would like to jump in front of the
strangle.
You know, I mean, I don't know. I don't want to be like a poo poo guy.
You know, I'm saying no, he can't do that fine. All right, what is he?
He does strangle you, so all that is I roll a dex thing or no
Here's what's happening, when you're strangled,
what's your con modifier?
Okay, okay, this is tough.
You have one round or you're gonna be at zero.
The way that strangulation works
or suffocation works in 5E,
you can hold your breath for however many minutes,
there's a rule for that,
but for suffocation, it's your modifier,
your con modifier is how many rounds
you can be suffocating, quote, unquote.
So you're considered suffocating, yeah.
And you're zero, so I'm gonna give you one.
I think it's dumb to be like, he strangles you and you immediately pass out.
So this is your last chance at this.
Okay, well we gotta go through the border one more time.
Pat has a turn.
Okay.
And he's close to me?
I'm gonna pee on him.
If you do that he could slip, that could change things.
So hold on, he's gotta roll against that.
Okay.
He's got very high dex.
You're not rolling anything.
Alright.
Oh, man!
Fuck.
You got a two. You got a two. So he's gonna be knocked prone. Oh my god. So he drops you.
Oh shit. Oh I didn't, ow! You have to pay me for that. Oh my god. I get paid in the hundred
thousands to pee on man. Beast mode. Beast mode dude. A million feet in the air this time.
I'm gonna keep giving you advantage. You now legitimately have advantage. A billion feet in
in the air. Please prone. He's not prone. We also you're just
destroying this airport. Oh my God. Okay. This is the final
try. If you don't get this, we lose. We don't know that. What
if I survive the next attack?
So this probably isn't my final try. So I'm just gonna throw it
on you care.
Fuck.
All right, wait, but that's doubles. It's monopoly rules. I
get to roll again.
All right, back to the top of the order. Okay, I'm yo
The yolk shot comes out of my ween.
That's not a hit.
Nope.
He's up.
He's up?
Yeah, he's up.
Up from prone?
Well, yeah, he gets up.
That only takes half his movement.
Wait, do I get advantage or something if he's prone?
Well, no, because yolk shot's a ranged attack.
Okay.
So he's going to get up.
He's not prone from being not prone.
He's going to try to strangle you this time.
You got to pay me to do that!
you
though yeah you can't do anything besides try to get out of this right now I start
pissing you can do that I guess all right I didn't think about that that's pretty
dumb of me yeah I gotta let you fucking piss yourself oh fuck man he slips again
It's like the scene in the movie when the blood goes towards his shoe and he moves
his shoe but it's pee. He's just going like oh no. All right. Oh my god. Oh my god.
I can't believe you made him slip again. Come on. 15. Dude we are so close. How many 15s in 14?
Come on we got this. We got this. We got this. Drop on him. A trillion feet. A
A trillion feet in the air.
God damn it, dude.
Oh my god, dude.
Dude, I suck at this.
You're really bad. You should let me roll it next time.
You're out.
I'm Yolkshaw.
Why do you keep doing that?
I hit him this time, I think. That's 22.
That does hit him.
Okay.
Okay, now I know why you keep doing that.
I mean, the damage doesn't really matter, but now attacks on him have advantage.
That's true.
That's seven damage.
Okay, I was giving him advantage already.
The yolk's going in his mouth.
Alright.
I peed on him!
And now he's got a yoke in him!
Alright, he's gonna-
Lursell doesn't give up!
He's going to try to attack you again, Cam.
Fuck.
Music to my ears.
I hate this game.
Alright, you're up.
This is the longest fight we've ever been in.
So I'm gonna use-
I'm just waiting on one roll.
I'm gonna use Defender Egg on myself.
No, as a reaction to damage you take.
Oh, right, and I can only use it five per long rest.
Okay.
Well, I took damage because he was strangling me.
No, you didn't take any damage.
Oh, right, right, right.
And I'm still at full health.
There's things you can do.
So in 5e, if you want to tell me what you want to do to make it easier for him,
describe it to me, we can figure out what the checks are for that, and then it can work.
I mean, I'm an old century egg.
That's right.
They're very elastic.
Okay, what are you thinking?
I've heard that too.
Century eggs are very elastic and rubbery.
So I just lay down and I say, "Jump on me like a trampoline.
I'm going to turn into an egg trampoline."
I don't really need extra height.
You could go a billion feet.
I can already jump.
Are you going to jump a billion feet in the air for one billion dollars?
I lie down on the ground too.
Is that a mechanic in Dungeons and Dragons?
It's not.
And like again, I'm embarrassed.
I'm thinking I got triple advantage.
That means it's triple advantage.
Well, I already gave, I already yolk shot it, so you should have quadruple advantage.
No.
Yeah, he has quadruple advantage.
We cut it at triple, but.
Please, because then you ruin it for the audience at home.
Here I go.
This has got to be it, right?
This is going to be it.
I guess that's a six.
I knew it wasn't that one.
That's why I didn't go the whole way around.
Yeah, no, it's going to be the next.
What we meant when we said it's going to be it is it's important.
It's not going to be this one.
So don't even care about this one.
I mean, like, statistically, it has to be this one.
(ball bouncing)
Dis two.
(laughing)
All right, guys.
- Statistically.
- Oh my God.
- What is wrong about my technique right now?
- Can I just get on the plane?
- I mean, you guys can run away whenever you want.
- All right, if this one doesn't hit, I'm running away.
- Me too.
- Okay, can we call it at that?
- Yeah.
- All right.
- Jump on my vagina.
(laughing)
- I'm gonna jump on your vagina very shortly.
- That's what's gonna say, but.
My butt-gina.
God is real, God is real, God is real.
(laughter)
- There's an angel looking at me.
- Christ died for all my sins.
- All of mine, I'm talking all my damn sins.
- Wow.
(high pitched squeal)
- Yeah!
(cheering)
- And it's 'cause he said God is real,
and this is the Easter special.
- Uh huh.
- Oh my God.
- Only took 20 rolls, baby.
- What is that, what is that?
First try, what is that? The best moment in radio history? First try. First real
try. First try. Right, first try? Yeah, first try. Alright,
describe your kill.
Alright.
In the airport. Here's my kill. So, you guys jump with me, right? Yeah, yeah.
Well, I'm the trampoline, I'm the trampoline. So, I grab you. You jump on
my butt. I'm holding onto you, I'm holding onto you like a jet pack. I'm
gonna do something else. And I'm shooting my yoke downward to give you extra
Here's what we do. We-
You grab my butt, Gino.
I grab you, we jump, right?
Uh-huh.
We're going up.
We're going up. Wait, we're not stopping.
What?
We're going up.
And we can build this world together!
And up and up. No.
We're going up and up and up.
Shut up, dude. I already had a music cue for this and you fucked it up.
My bad.
Ducktales space theme starts playing.
[laughter]
As we just go higher and higher and higher.
and eventually we just we hit the Sun and guess what fried eggs
god damn we died yeah we still won cuz that bitch never got his money yep so
you guys fly up into the Sun and die
and if big camera sort of cuts away to back to that sheriff who hasn't done
anything like he does just a story they heard
well I've been having I'm having dreams lately first dream to to recently first
dream is me my father and we're fishing he's teaching me how to hook the bait
and I pricked my finger but I tried to hide it from him I didn't want him to
see me cry and then the second dream I've been having it's me my dad again
we're in the middle of town it was but it also was in the middle of town you
know and a Yeti came up to my father and the Yeti he started to suck off my
father like real slow and gentle one need and the other knee he slowly unzips
his pants and pulls out his thing and my father was moaning and then another Yeti
came around he started to take off his pants and the yeti had pants and he started sucking
me off too but he was also putting his wiener in my father's ass and I you know it was sort
of like the same time I know how seeing as we was I thought about 10 15 away from one
another but but then the third yeti came he was starting to poop his butthole was starting
to appearing out of my head was the third head of my his butthole was coming out of my head
a little man was coming out he was clapping and dancing my father and he came in the yeti
mouth and then that yeti started shitting out the cum that went in and it went into another
yeti I guess a fourth one showed up at some point you know how dreams are and he was spreading
his ass but he was bent so he has to swallow the poop from from from falling from the third
yeti and the little man on my head started to turn into the poop too and then I came or
the yeti behind my father's ass came but then my ass started to come too it had a discharge
and that was bright yellow and everyone in town was watching and they were watching the
Yeti and my father's face was on the town, he was also on my stomach.
And then we started to fish again, I pricked my finger but it was with the Yeti's penis
and that one was sucking me off, and then the bait was sucking me off, and then I was
sucking him off too.
And then the poop was sucking me off, so the poop had a mouth now.
And my father had my face.
And then I woke up.
And then, fate cuts the black.
Happy Halloween!
Happy Halloween everyone!
Bye!
[Music]