[Music]
What's happening guys? I'm Gunny Sack and you're watching PAL Kids TV.
me
What's happening guys, I'm GunnySack, and you're watching PALKIDS TV, the Saturday
morning cartoon block only on Logo.
So it's Scare-tober!
Ooooooh!
You know what that means, we got something spooky for you.
That's right, a classic episode of the Teenage Gumshoe Crew and their dog.
In this episode, the gang investigates a haunted castle where some creep is terrifying the
town.
Yikes!
I know I wouldn't want to be there, I love being safe inside your TV.
anyway, hold on to your diaper because this episode is scary.
And then we push into the TV.
We're inside the television now.
The teens of Weirdo, Pennsylvania, love to head down to Sully's Joint
when the gumshoe crew needs a break from solving mysteries.
It's just about the only dog friendly establishment in town that includes pizza,
an arcade and a roller rink that plays awesome disco music.
Does it get any better than that?
The proprietor of this joint is none other than Sullivan the Frog.
Proud manager and frog person, the only one still alive after the event.
Him and his chief, Fez from that 70s show, love serving pizzas to the kids and playing
the grooviest tunes.
There's even a couple competitions going on today.
The roller dance finals in the rink and the pinball warlock tournament happening in the
arcade over there.
Lots of things for the Gumshoe Crew to do if they want.
Hopefully no mysteries are afoot.
It sure be nice for there to be no mysteries afoot right now on October 31st, the anniversary
of Halloween.
So you guys are in right now.
You're chilling.
You've probably just solved a whole bunch of crimes.
You're the Gumshoe Crew.
Put your piece on the board wherever you guys want.
We have a board now.
Which one is my piece?
No one assigned me a piece.
Yeah, I never got a piece either, so it's already a disaster.
This is my piece, everybody.
This is yours.
Okay, well, now there's other people with no pieces.
So my character's black?
He has one.
I don't--yeah, it's up to you.
Why do you sound so mad about it?
Oh, my character's black?
Look, I don't want to do that voice. It'll sound offensive.
You don't have to do any voice.
Nobody would have even ever known that you had a black figurine until you just decided to get mad about it.
Well, I'm mad about it, but now I am because you're all making me sound racist. This is all right
So should I put that you said wherever wherever you want?
Where are you and this is where the warlock pinball tournament is happening for that time?
This is where the pizza is that's that so this is this is kind of where you would order. Yeah, so I'm back here though
You're back by worse. Look behind. I'm behind the counter. Yeah, okay cool. Yeah, cuz you're the dog right?
We'll get to that. That's word. That's us you guys on the roller rink roller rink now girls
I'll be in one of these beds over here.
Are we?
Sorry, that's...
The pinball is over there, that's just a regular arcade.
While I'm laying down on the pinball machine,
I'm taking a siesta.
Then I'm...
I'm just over here.
Nearby the arcade machines.
Patrick's thinking, "Oh, where would a black guy be?"
Okay.
So now that we know where you all are at Sully's Joy,
even where black guys are,
let's go around.
Who are your characters?
What's going on? Let's start with you, Jed.
- I'm Jed.
My name's Jed and I'm kind of the leader of the crew.
My name is Jed and I'm kind of the leader
of the whole crew.
I have blonde hair and blue eyes,
which some in the party seem to be jealous of.
(laughing)
I'm known for my, how good I am at fingering,
and women can tell just by my pheromones that I put out.
Well, I'm insinuating and inferring.
And basically I'm just gonna pass it on to the next one.
That's awesome.
So Jed is really good at traps, finding as well.
Oh, and traps and finding.
And finding.
As well.
Yeah, also.
But yeah, no, that's great.
You're right now, you're laying on top
of the pinball machine, right?
Yeah, yeah, I smoked too many cigarettes. I got sick. I accidentally smoked the red ones.
You did?
Yeah, I smoked two.
Okay.
I'm falling over on them.
You're falling over.
Yeah.
Okay, yeah, the tournament is happening. The tournament was...
What year is this again?
Sorry, this is 1975.
Was pinball even invented in 1975?
Yes, it was.
Pinball wizard.
Okay, and what about...
With Warlock in this case.
What about ice skating?
Roller rinks were around the 70s, yeah.
Roller rinks.
Alright.
And ice skating.
Okay, well...
Ice skating's been around for a really long time.
Alright, just get out of my face.
I'm gonna get out of you.
uh... and who's this fetching young
teenage girl
the
that is to just walk by the window you know
that is not part of this record
uh... no
i don't think
so
please talk
and
I'm a pretty girl!
Busy week for Alex.
I see.
Had no time to write that intro.
I'm Denise, I'm a girl.
I'm pretty.
I got a good, I'm good at,
I got a good heart.
I love my friends.
Oh my god.
And I'm, I'm here.
That's great.
(laughing)
- Good heart, loves her friends and she's here.
- So Denise is the--
- You're cute.
- Don't do this.
(laughing)
I was trying to make a joke and I became in trouble.
Denise has a lot of abilities around crying
and calling the police on people and using pepper spray.
And she's also governed by her,
She's got very, very high charisma stat.
- Oh yeah.
- She'll be using throughout this potentially mystery.
Who knows if there'll be a mystery though, right?
- Right, who knows?
- Shut up. - Right, okay.
- I love having sex.
- And then we're gonna go to Vera.
That's my fault too.
I can't really pretend I'm immune to that.
You're up, Vera.
- Vera.
Hi everyone, my name is Vera.
- Oh look at this, somebody did their homework.
- And I am a lesbian.
(laughing)
- I love the lesbian voice you're doing, Joe.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- It's close enough, I can,
I can haircut everything.
Wow, it feels so good to finally come out and say that.
But when I'm not giving brain to ladies,
I'm using my brain to imprison crazies.
(laughing)
When I'm not licking the stinky,
I'm solving a mystery saying jinkies.
And when I'm not looking for my glasses and clues,
I'm probably eating stinky muff and going,
and going absolutely dome crazy on other lesbians in the back of our crime-solving
mystery machine fuck palace of a van.
You're doing that in the van?
Do we know?
After dark.
I may be a smart whiz kid, but believe me when I say I have a crazy ass side.
You heard that right. I will eat your muff and your crazy ass side.
Vera's really good at investigating in addition to her muff diving.
Oh yeah, Denise, by the way, I apologize Vera.
Denise, where are you on the board right now?
What are you doing?
I'm in the roller rink.
So you're in the roller rink, you're skating around.
You see it's the roller rink competitions.
Have these two ever fucked each other?
Vera ever fucked him?
Is that the implication?
Let's just say I'm on the case.
I'm a virgin.
(laughing)
- I'm a virgin.
- I'm so excited for this episode.
(laughing)
- Yeah, I think we're gonna stay back at the--
- You're funny.
- So Vera's really good at investigating.
She has a lot of abilities around that.
She also has her magnifying glass to look for clues
and to use to do a lot of fire damage actually,
believe it or not, which is pretty nuts.
- That's fire.
- It is fire.
And now we have, let's pound that out, okay.
And then let's have, we have, who's this layabout?
- Oink zoinks, it's me, Shabby.
I'm the only 35 year old in the crew.
(laughing)
- Do you have the levels?
- They only hang out with me because I have a car
and Vietnam made me crazy.
(laughing)
I have to smoke cigarettes just to stop
the voices in my head.
I think the dog can talk.
- Oh boy!
- That's awesome.
- And I'm addicted to food completely!
(laughing)
Like, completely addicted to food!
- So we have Shabby Todgers here,
and he is 35, which I didn't know, but I'm open to it.
And he--
- He's a Vietnam vet.
- Right.
And he's a Vietnam vet.
- Does he have all of his limbs?
- Let's hope.
(laughing)
- Okay, we don't know.
- That's another mystery solved.
- Does he wear long sleeves all the time?
- His limbs are in a quantum state
of being there and not being there, I guess.
Which isn't an ability you have.
You have the ability--
- And I'm losing my hair!
(laughing)
- That's not, you don't have to even.
- Yeah, you don't have to say that.
- That's just like a world builder.
- I'm losing my hair from stress, man!
- Your abilities are, Shabby's abilities are--
- That's not what I saw!
- Prat falling and running through people
and losing his hair.
And he also, he's an animal lover,
so he can talk with animals and has ability around that.
So he'll get a little bonus for that.
Shabby, what are you doing?
You're at the arcade right now?
- I'm freaking out.
- You're freaking out.
(laughing)
- He's like looking at Galaga and having PTSD.
- Jesus Christ!
Johnson!
No!
- It's gonna sound awesome.
We're gonna love that.
- I remembered my friend.
John Johnson, you remember either your dick or your friend.
Did you fight in the Galaga wars?
Yeah.
I'm the veteran of the Galaga wars.
I saw Galaga.
In Vietnam?
You were in Vietnam playing a lot of arcade games.
Yeah, I was not in the U.S.A.
You were on a sex tour.
He was in San Diego.
And then of course we have, last but not least, everyone's favorite.
I'm Scooby-Doo! I'm the eponymous rarictor and protagonist of the Ranimated
Relovision franchise of the same name, created in 1969 by the American
Ranimation company, Ranomarera. I am a male Great Rain and a lifelong
companion of amateur detective Shabby Rock Dodger, with whom he shares many
personality traits. I feature a mix of both canine and human behaviors
reminiscent of other rocking ranimals in Ranomarera series, and is treated by my
My rents more or less as an equal.
(laughter)
I often speak in a rhotocised way,
substituting the first letters of many words
with the letter R.
My catchphrase is "Scooby-Dooby-Doo!"
So I don't know about
I don't know about all that, but
Scooby's really good at finding
uh, investigating and smelling stuff
he can, has a smell bank, he can
store smells in and use it to track
uh, things. Where are you at right now, Scooby-Doo?
I'm behind the
pizza counter and whoever's making the pizza I'm licking their leg like their
upper thigh.
Mike! Scoob! You gotta get in here!
Okay! I'm not doing what I was doing anymore.
I need my pills!
Oh is he like your companion service dog?
Oh that makes a lot more sense.
So yeah you guys are uh yeah you walk before you know you uh you know Sullivan
is a good friend of yours, you know, he's an older man frog who runs this joint. You can
see it's not as populated as it usually is and he had told you that recently.
With all the haunting going on up at...
Holy crap, a talking frog!
Shabby, we've known each other for a little while now.
Let's unmask him!
Oh no, please don't!
That sounds like a great idea, man!
Get that mask off that bastard right now!
Just add your strength to that.
What was that?
- Three.
- Okay, yeah.
You, yeah, Sullivan's able to sort of dodge out of the way.
Oh, stop, please!
He's like trying to duck around.
Duck around, you're trying to grab him.
Please, I know, I know how bad the Gallagher wars are,
but please, just.
- You don't know how bad they were, man!
- Oh no, I set him off now.
- I was in Vietnam, San Diego.
- I just, since the castle,
the castle cigarette has been so haunted lately
by the wacky tabacky, I feel like I don't have any customers.
- What?
(laughing)
- I'd be giving, I'd be giving a reward.
- What the hell are you on about, frog?
- That made complete sense to me.
- I'm trying to, I would give a reward to anyone
who could solve that mystery.
- Why are you acting like such a coy slut?
(laughing)
Either hire us to do the job, or fucking leave me alone.
I'm trying to sleep on this pinball machine.
- You would do the job?
- Oh, twirling your fucking frog tongues,
and oh, what if somebody fixes all this for me?
- I can't hear you if you twirl your tongue with your finger.
- I wasn't twirling my tongue.
It's a good idea.
I wish I did that, but I didn't.
- Let's go shopping.
(laughing)
- Denise, you are such a hot bitch.
- Thank you.
- Either me or Vera is going to fuck you today.
- It's gonna happen.
- Or me.
(laughing)
- Or the dog.
- I have a wife.
- I love having sex.
(laughing)
- Is there a window in this?
- Yeah, yeah, there's tons of windows.
- I take out my magnifying glass and use it on the frog.
- Oh, you're gonna just attack the frog?
- Yeah, sure.
- We're catching on quickly.
- Yeah, yeah, roll, just roll a D20.
- I think we've killed Sullivan
in half of the campaigns we've done.
Usually, that definitely hits him.
Roll two D6s.
Roll another one.
Okay, yeah, so, uh...
So where are you right now, just so I know where you are?
I'm in a Roman ring!
So what you're doing-
I was super far away from across the entire Roman ring!
From downtown!
That is- you are literally just in range.
Yeah!
So there's like- and so the line is just going across.
People are just dancing to music, like, rolling around to the music.
Just a line of fire just-
A laser beam.
Just fucking goes across the establishment, and Sullivan, who just got out of the way of Shabby,
He tried to grab it there. I can't even hear what he's saying
You guys want to do that you could take it to the kid
I'm already like violently licking the burn spot on you guys
takes all of them and you put up he can't resist at this point you put him in the
deep right here's your reward yeah me and shabby are standing and we're like we're
like we're like just dead twiddling our thumbs over the dead person we at least
eat his body yep he's what do you think I was doing we
we have big sandwiches and we eat them at the same time in one bite.
One half of his face is in each of the sandwiches.
So yeah, you guys giggle and he eats all of them in the product.
Yeah. Okay, so now your move.
My move is you roll a perception check.
Okay. Jed.
Use the dice tower.
Use the dice tower. Maybe I will.
I will use it
Nice that sounded so good. Yeah, that's gonna be an eight for me, okay, you
Don't get the sense of where it's coming from but you hear a hissing sound
You guys can't hear anything I think it's Vera's downstairs is like releasing air
So I just kind of chalk it up to that, but I do try to smell it
I would like to note the floor is wet underneath me
Can I see or as in the roller rinks we can go to the roller rink over here?
So are you guys participating in the competition or you just I'm kind of tracking. I'm looking at all the cute boys
So the main boy here who is is Jamee French foreign exchange student who is a
Very much very close to winning the very happy. How old is he? He is 13 years old
Oh, wow. I'd like to take out my trusty magnifying glass.
Of course, anything else you're gonna...
Anybody, anything that's happening here is 18.
But unless it's not. Except for Jemay.
Jemay is 18.
Oh. I'd like to take out my magnifying glass and hit Jemay too.
Okay.
Wait, wait, hit the disco ball with the light.
Oh, oh my.
Every show.
Oh, that's pretty funny.
I'm trying to think of the...
Oh my God, that's terrifying.
That's a hysterical implication. I do, I want that to happen.
Let's do that. Roll a, also a, slide a hand check to see if you could position your magnifying glass
and hit the, hit it in such a way that it will just spray fire down on the establishment.
D20 and then it will say that sidebar there, it says slide of hand, the number next to that.
Zero.
Yeah, so you add zero to whatever you get in your roll.
Fifteen.
Oh wow, okay.
You're able to angle the magnifying glass in such a way that it shoots out a ray of fire
Holy shit
Yeah, this is gonna. Just go here, and we'll have one you're gonna have to roll at me. Yeah
Can I use this guy's a human shield uh?
You don't really have time for that
He's in the way. It's the speed of light you look he breaks the line you drew yeah
It's a race. It's a red the idea is it goes through all of the I'm letting all right, okay fine roll
So you have to roll an attack roll so just roll d20 and we'll see how well you hit everything
15 okay, yeah, I mean that beats your AC for sure roll. I have a 15 AC so it's oh yeah
But if it if it matches the AC the he wins yeah, so you roll roll 2d 6 to see the damage you do
I guess you're just gonna melt this guy because that is just a kind of a person
that's eight you take eight damage Jed you're just lying on the pinball machine
the pinball tournament just gets interrupted by a ray of fire that's
going through like run it's the gumshoe crew they're fucking insane
why am I half dead all of a sudden yeah you're just we're just sleeping and now
you're nearly dead and that hissing sound that you thought you heard you did hear
it's getting a lot louder now and now all of a sudden this green like almost
viscous smoke is blasting blasting through the place
well look from where through from from what you can tell roll a perception
check to see if you can tell where it's coming from you couldn't quite tell
before 14 ok you can kind of you sense
that it's coming from something around
over here something behind the billiards
table over there
ok our arcade area yes and you have to
roll a dex check
roll it's fun yeah you might die I'm
getting I'm getting fucked
yeah nine ok you're gonna take all right
because I didn't write an intro that's
not why I get just a really bad place or
do a voice. You take three damage. Every round that you're in this smoke you will take more
damage. Everyone roll initiative while we figure out how to deal with this smoke. It's
going to keep expanding. D20 and then add the thing that says initiative in the top
middle. I got a six. I got a thirteen. Eight. Where's initiative? Right there, the square
next to speed it's right under intelligence I mean 13 for you so you
roll a d20 you take it straight so you'll have a 10 okay and then six for
you Jed eight for me for you so you roll out yeah what'd you get I got 18 oh
very good first you'll probably be first Denise got 18 we have an 8 for Denise's
18 this is all my children
- I got the eight.
- You got the shabby.
I mean, you got the six shabby.
And what did you get, Vera?
- 10.
- 10, okay, cool.
All right, so, the smoke is billowing out.
Denise, what do you wanna do first?
- What are my options?
- So you can move, you can do an action,
you could try to stop the smoke,
you could just try to leave the establishment.
- I'm gonna run right into the smoke.
- You're gonna run right into the smoke.
Okay, go for it.
So, use your movement.
So each of these squares on this is five feet, okay, then you have 30 feet of movement
So six squares is your full movement without using your - action. Why are you running into the smoke?
to investigate
Mm-hmm. Yeah, but the smoke does poison damage cool. So well, you can't do it. I'm gonna
From where you are. Yeah, so what I would you can roll roll a
You want as your action you can do like a perception check quickly because it's just like timing wise so just roll that d20 and add
Perception to it. Yeah. Yeah, that's the one
Eight plus or anything I think plus one right? Yeah plus one nine
So you can't quite tell what this smoke is
You definitely recognize you've definitely like smelt it before but you don't know exactly what it is
And you know, you know what its places but you don't you just don't have enough smelt it before and know that it's poisonous
Yeah, but like like not just now like she was she just came over and whiffed it like this is it
but you've smelt it before.
You don't know exactly what it is though.
But that you can do for your turn.
And now Scoob, you're up.
- Okay.
Well I'm all the way over here.
And I guess, did I notice that the smoke is coming in?
- Yeah.
- We're in the kitchen eating food.
Do we know it all?
- Eating frog.
- Yeah.
Food.
- Just food.
It is food now.
- I would say that you would hear the hissing pop
and probably hear the lasers being shot out
from the disco ball enough that you would be aware of it.
There's activity.
- Okay, I mean, yeah, I'll just run out.
- Put yourself here, like you can have yourself be there.
- Okay, and I'll just run out into the open
and just see what's up.
- Okay, cool.
- I'm just gonna stand on this table.
- I mean, what you can do, you can definitely
lock the smell of this now and add it to your smell bank.
- Okay, I add it to my smell bank.
- It's your smell bank.
You take a big whiff of this skunky smelling thing.
- Oh, it's skunky smelling.
- You can start to piece that together now.
And now--
- Okay, I'll write skunk smell into my smell bank.
- He's twice, for some reason.
- Vera.
- Yes.
I see what has happened to my friend Jed.
My Eskimo brother Jed.
And I want to--
- Wait, we haven't, we fucked, I don't think we've--
- You're not supposed to reveal that yet.
- I just think that-- - It's not a rule.
- I assume that we're kind of operating--
- You and me are like taking turns--
- But we fuck the same people and then fucking trade it.
But we never at the same time.
- And never together, never with each other.
- 'Cause that'd be gay.
- Yeah, well, yeah, it'd be gay to fuck with a lesbian.
(laughing)
- Yeah, hello, rainy day.
I see what has happened to Jed,
and I want to give him a sully snack.
- Okay, cool.
So what you can do--
- Do they do anything for me?
- Yes, they give you five HP.
So you can eat a sully snack on your turn, too.
- Shove it in my mouth like Narcan?
- Yeah, I assume he's lying
and kind of discombobulated a little bit,
so I'm gonna try to make him eat it down.
- Okay, cool.
So you have to, the thing is,
you're pretty far away from him.
- Yeah.
So what you can do is you can try to toss it over to him.
- Can I do a run and kind of like--
- Yeah, shot put it.
- Shot felt off the pinball machine onto the ground.
- That makes sense.
Yeah, you could do that.
Let's do either athletics.
Do athletics or acrobatics.
- Okay, minus one.
- Yeah.
- You're gonna try to hit it into my gullet?
- Yeah. - Okay.
- Yeah, let's do it.
- Yeah, I guess I'm knocked out.
My mouth is--
(dice clatters)
- Yeah, your mouth is-- - 20.
- You got an add 20? - Oh my God.
- Wow.
- Joe's really good at D&D.
(laughing)
You just, Velma, Chariots of Fire is playing,
you just like, for some reason it's a perfect launch.
You're just like, lying there, like,
and you just taste this delicious,
sully snack in your mouth.
You gain five HP back.
- Woo, do I wake up or not?
Or was I ever, I wasn't--
- You weren't knocked out, yeah, no.
Cool, that's great.
Now we're back to Jed.
So Jed, you're the only one who's near the source of this.
- Back to?
- Just 'cause stuff was happening.
- I'm near the source. - No, sorry, I didn't mean--
- Do I have, did you ever go?
No, he goes last. That was my bad.
I thought that I got... Oh no, he got an ace.
I said back, but I shouldn't have said back.
Oh.
Yeah.
So you're nearest to the source of this.
It's also by the back door, too.
So you can check to see, as a free action I would say,
you can see where it's leaking out of,
and you know that the back door...
The back door's open, or no?
The back door... Well, roll a perception check.
Throw it wide.
18 plus... So 20.
Okay, dirty 20.
You can tell that not only is it, it's not open,
but you can see that it's like,
even when you just open a door and it swings back to close
and a little bit of it is like--
- Yeah, okay, it's like that.
- It's like somebody had opened it kinda recently.
- I'm going to open it to see what's up in there.
- Okay, cool.
So you head out to the back and you don't see anybody around.
You do see just a dumpster to your left
and then just parking.
- He's in the dumpster.
- I don't see any greenness.
I don't see any greenness.
- You don't see any greenness.
I don't see the trail from where all the crap was coming from no not not here not like right outside
What does the ceiling look like just for my role my turn but but wait, but but it was coming from this door
No, no, I'm saying like you I
What I'm
Yes, but okay, you know actually I should have you do
Roll roll another perception check because I realize that like you should be able to see something, but I misspoke there
I got a fucking 20 last time this time. I get a four
I mean I'll say that like well you've said you forgot to do it, so I think I should get it
I think he just gets it. It's actually kind of true
You see a green smoke sort of from underneath the dumpster. I knew it's a dumpster dude. I said okay
So I walk outside and I do continue. Yes. Yes, you do okay, and I've superhuman strike no
You're strong. What did you want to do? I wanted to flip the dumpster?
I don't think you need superhuman strength to flip a dumpster.
You could certainly try.
Try flipping a dumpster, Patrick.
I could.
No, you could not.
I will stop right now and go.
Let's go.
Pause right now.
We're gonna go and see.
Pause for 20.
He did it.
Okay.
Holy shit.
Sure, he did it.
I mean, I wasn't sure.
It's now midnight, but like, you know.
We had to find a really small dumpster.
I am going to...
Okay.
You can use your action to investigate.
Well, first I'm gonna say.
I know you're under there, green-o.
Say it just like that.
Come on out of there, you bastard!
Get out of there!
Come on!
Get out from under the dumpster, you green bastard!
You don't hear any like, stirring or- Come on before I get angry with you, you green
nutcase.
Nothing, nothing, it's just- Alright, I'm gonna go back inside.
I go back inside. All right yeah and now your turn Shabby. You wanted to know what the
ceiling was like? Yeah. It's like regular, it's like kind of a mauve color for some
reason. So it's not like the 70s? No ceiling tiles. Yeah I was gonna ask that.
There are ceiling tiles in the bathroom. I thought it was being pumped in through the
ceiling but now. I came in so I could tell everybody. Yeah but now that he's already
figured that out are you leaving the door open I close the door close the door
stops coming in okay okay everybody I figured out the source of the green
smoke there's a stink of some stink guy and he lives under the trash okay and
there you go we'll end initiative it might just be trash so we can crash we
could end the initiative at this point if like someone opened the window all
the smoke's going out nobody's gonna keep taking damage there is that window that
yes yes yes yeah and so I think I think that somebody could have opened a window
you guys you guys can you guys can investigate the dumpster if you want to
or you could just I want to investigate but I just want the whole squad with me
because I think that I might be getting a green attack yeah yeah I think I need
the strength right spit up people I put up I'll investigate the refrigerator
the whole scooby-doo
i'll investigate the ice cream machine
ok scoob and shabby
you guys got your thing
i'll go with the two girls
i'll go lift the giant
heavy dumpster
as soon as you're out of the room
me and shabby start fucking
ok
can't stop that i guess
like oh man
That's you coming. How do you come, Shad?
Oh, God!
Yeah, that's okay.
Freaking normal as hell.
Okay, so me, Vera, and Denise.
We go from the roller rink and go to investigate it.
And I'll put my arm around her when we walk out.
So what do you guys want to do to investigate?
Do you want to just roll an investigation check?
Well, I kind of split between the two of them.
Because I know Vera has her arm around Denise.
I get between the two of them and put my arm on both of them.
Oh, yeah.
yeah okay ladies so basically we I need we got to pick this big thing up Denise
why don't you go give it a try first just get down there on your ball fours
okay before Denise does it I slide back I slide back around and get between two of
them so I also have Denise on my arm okay yeah I'm gonna go down and I'm gonna try
to start lifting the all of you guys roll
I'm actually gonna get to the fucking bottom all of you guys roll d20 and add your string
Yeah, me and shabby like sneak back outside like we've been with you guys
You're trying to lift the
You just turn, you just see we're just all so next to you.
Your hair is fucking out.
We're so scared.
My tongue is out of the side of my mouth.
I'm panting.
It's like cutting to the angle you had seen before.
You guys are just there now, panting.
I don't have, I just have a jacket on.
Shabby, your fly's unzipped.
Yeah, so is the rest of my pants.
And that sandwich you ate must have had a lot of mayonnaise on it.
(laughing)
- Oh man, it's A-O-L-E-O.
- Oh, mayonnaise.
(gurgling)
- Stupid dude licking.
(laughing)
Licks him clean.
- He's, oh my god.
- Just a ding, and he's so clean and shiny.
(laughing)
- I got a 16 on my strength, or, no wait, no, I--
- With all five of you there--
- I got a 19.
- I got a 17.
with all five of you there it's way easier. As you lift it you don't see
like anything underneath it but you do see a hole cut out and you see like a
little glass like top of like a glass tube sticking out of the hole and you
also see like a hole into the establishment from that so imagine
dumpster hole on the bottom of it and a little glass tube coming out of that
okay and that kind of sticking into so it's so the side of the dumpster yeah
Okay, so let's I'm gonna open the door you see what looks like
You don't know how to describe it. It's sort of like a glass tube and it has like a little like another smaller like
apparatus on it with some sort of like green material, and it looks lit and
Also, and and and it's just like shooting it out. It's like a like a bad bong. It doesn't make any sense
It's makeup
(laughing)
- It could be makeup, Denise.
That's a really good guess and you're really smart.
- You guys can roll.
- Thank you.
- One of you can roll a history check
to see if you know what this is.
- Wait, don't just, you should try to see.
- Who's the best intelligent?
- Oh, you're right.
- Definitely Vera does.
- This, well I got a 15, so.
- I got an eight plus three.
- 11?
Okay, so, I mean that's pretty good.
You would know that this is some kind of paraphernalia
that has been going around the school for a little bit.
- Okay.
- I don't know.
- Do we all go to the same school?
- I asked why I should not go to another school.
(laughing)
I don't know how.
- Shabby is a guidance counselor.
- Okay, I'd like to ask Shabby,
'cause I think he has something to do
with the spread around school.
(laughing)
- You guys have never,
you haven't seen anything like this before.
You don't really recognize what the green stuff is.
- Can I tell if this,
can I tell if the smell is leading anywhere?
- Good call.
- You can--
- It's in my smell bank.
It's in your smell bank.
So you can use a sniff to like try to track it.
- And I only get five sniffs.
- We only get five sniffs total.
- Are we gonna use one of these?
- Ever.
I don't know, what do you guys think?
- I feel like this--
- I feel like we just--
- It's almost done.
- I feel like we just metagame it,
we just go straight to the castle.
(laughing)
That the frog mentioned.
- Yeah.
- We don't, we stop investigating this.
We just go straight to the castle.
- You could go straight to the castle.
- But then he's gonna spend another 45 minutes
- Drawn. - No, I've got it drawn.
You got it drawn.
- Let's all run to the castle.
- No, come here.
- We all, we all like, we don't say anything.
We just look at that device, all look at each other
and then just run to the castle.
- Yeah, you guys run to the castle.
Let's do it.
So yeah, you guys, you have a mystery machine.
You run right by it.
You sprint to the castle.
And I'll talk about the castle in a second.
first I have to flip over some tiles.
Everyone take their guy. Or girl.
Or dog. Or dog.
Thank you. Or boy dog I think. Yeah but it's just different.
Boy dog. So as you guys are approaching...
Actually everybody flip these over while I read this.
Guys we're heading to the mysterious
castle that you heard about from Sullivan before you
Killed and ate him.
This looks weird this cigarette castle.
There's all manner of youths outside
protesting cigarettes. How peculiar a little peculiar. Why did I write that word? I can't say.
How peculiar...
How strange.
Some of them are dressed in their Halloween finest, of course, but they have eggs and TP ready also.
What gives? At the helm you see Mary Jane, a real goody two-shoes junior at Weird Al High School.
What she got against cigarettes? Everyone knows are just about the best. You also see a gatekeeper sitting guard in a guard shack
Alongside the iron barred gate trying his best to keep the protests under control
While also mostly reading a magazine. I wonder if these teens will let you in
The manor itself or the castle is incredible
It's four stories high at the very top rest the cigarette tower even now defunct. It's still always perpetually lit
Circle driveway out front beyond the gate none of that is drawn. That's all
Imagination this is the manor itself will get and then this is that the entrance yeah, you guys aren't there
Oh, that's right. Okay, right now. We're gonna do theater of the mind for this part. Oh
Like what we usually do
And right the circle driveway out front beyond the gate the center of which holds the famous statues of Sir Nigel cigarette
OBE the guy who invented the cigarette and cigar
Bumming the first cigarette ever off of his nephew Chris while they were outside of a funeral home during the wake of Chris's father
The entire place is made of white stone tipped with the custom customary yellow at the base of each stone
So it's kind of looks like a bunch of stones with a little bit of yellow on the bottom
As if the place were made of fat hard cigarettes
The door is a rich brown seemingly the same texture as a cigar it's a huge entrance
But yeah, you guys roll up there and you see there's like all these protests against the cigarettes
Oh, geez, it's just like Vietnam again.
Um, but yeah.
Protests?
I didn't go over there, I just got scared of it.
Because of the protests that were going on.
You guys see a crowd out front.
Looks like it might be hard to push your way through or get in.
You can try to talk to people in the crowd, investigate, you can try to go around.
What do you guys want to do?
My interest has been piqued by this Mary Jane character.
Might as well.
- I'd like to walk in tandem with Jed up to her.
And we both speak at the same time.
- So she has a megaphone and she's going,
"What do we want?"
And the crowd says, "No more cigarettes."
- And we speak at the same time and we say,
"When do we want it?"
And they say, "Right now!"
- I let them use my megaphone to talk back to her.
(laughing)
- Okay, we both go up to her and we say,
"Hello, slut."
What are we-- what are you losers doing here?
Trying to fuck you.
I put my hand on his head and push him away and go,
try to get to know you first.
And then I push my head back in, and then fuck you.
And then I push back and say, and fuck you.
All anyone can hear is just the two megaphones
are too close to each other.
Would you just--
We have it on alarm.
That noise is making me howl and freak out.
I'm going crazy. I'm biting people's legs in the crowd.
He's screaming so I'm going like, "Oh jeez! Oh man!"
Okay, so she doesn't hear any of that. She just hears the siren. Two sirens a little bit off sync.
She puts the megaphone away and she says,
"Everybody, take five! Weirdos are here!" And she goes, "What do you two want?"
"Who the hell are you and what are you doing outside of my damn house?" "I wanna take five!"
This is not your house. This is the cigarette castle
God you're dead. You're smart
Just can you guys get out of here unless you're a part of the movement? Yeah, you're right. Let's get out of here
I'm actually a part of the movement - and like I'd really be interested in taking more of more of a leadership
You can roll persuasion you have - 10 persuasion against any women. Yes. Yes. Oh, yeah
She's really nervous
She's like so nervous. Okay
15. So you have five. She's like, what are you? You just kind of to her, it sounds like
you're saying, that's happened before. Yeah. And so what you were saying and then just
what is coming out. I try to just get the word movement out. Yeah. Join movement. Yeah,
Yeah, sure. Do you want me to get you a sign-up sheet?
I'd like to join you in some kind of movement.
Yeah, I got it, Jed. And she goes to get a sign-up sheet for you and hands it to you.
I mean, you're endearing yourself to her, even if you don't make any sense.
When I get it back, I kind of scratch the back of my head and smile.
Because that's what I can muster that up.
Yeah, we have different playbooks.
like yeah one of us is gonna use the van at the end of the day. Well okay if you join the
movement that's great but I still really can't let you in I mean. Into the castle?
Is this your house? No it's I mean well. Well then how come you can't just let me
in then? Well we're planning to we're planning the storm at the castle later
tonight if you want to join. But if not whatever. Can I take a quick sidebar
with Jed? Yeah, you can do that. Jed, I feel like one of us should be talking to her and
joining this running in on the castle while the other one tries to sneak in
before it happens. So like making a distraction? Yeah, sort of a
distraction and one of us kind of gets to stick back with this girl. So you want
to talk to her and maybe I go we have a great idea for a distraction well go
ahead tell us okay so what are you guys gonna do to distract her?
well me and Bear will sneak in while you guys distract him. Perfect.
Or her. Him or her. Okay. Sounds great. Okay so let's go Ravi. Start the distraction in front of all these
teenagers are you guys doing some kind of cheerleader hey everybody I use the
megaphone now I have it on the right the right thing everybody these two are
about to do something you've never seen before everybody bring your attention to
the 35 year old man and the dog
Roll Persuasion with advantage.
Me?
Mega Pulse.
Okay.
Um, that's an 18.
Oh, baby.
Uh, and that's a 6.
So the 18 plus...
It's like a dirty 29.
It's a 19.
Nice.
Okay, cool. Yeah.
Uh, everybody turns to like...
They're like, "Oh! We're on a break! I'd love to see this!"
"I guess I gotta roll a performance."
Yeah!
You roll a performance.
Roll a performance.
What'd you get?
Uh, 16.
I got a 15.
Wow. Okay.
That's some solid...
fucking you know what you guys tell me what it's like now you say that
you guys yeah it's like really like what is like dirty it's brutal who's on what
side are you see what we switch every minute we're doing it for 20 minutes
It's like you can see a cloud
Transparent cloud
Fists popping I feel like a dick it said like yeah, yeah, it's like that
Okay, amazing
distracted. Everyone's distracted. Me and Vera. Including MJ. MJ's distracted too. And while MJ's looking the other way I pluck a piece of her hair out.
And we're gonna go into... and I'm gonna put that in my inventory. Yeah, add her hair. We're gonna sneak into one of the windows.
It'll be useful maybe. So really quickly, what's the... Sure. Can I find a point of entry here? So what you can do, you have a free like
investigation check to look around. I will say going through the front entrance because of the gatekeeper will still be hard to do.
This is where perhaps Denise, your feminine wiles could come into play and the gatekeepers penchant for fucking teens I guess also
How much time are they buying us?
It's really up to you guys. 20 minutes.
20 minutes.
I'm on all sorts of medication.
I can last a long time.
And I got that dog in me.
And everyone can't stop watching.
20 minutes there just transfixed.
It's like the Silencio scene.
So I'm it we're gonna bring so I guess we'll bring Denise - yeah, so we're gonna bring you up
Like you're our niece. I guess
Bring him to the gatekeeper and we go someone wants to talk to you to the gatekeeper and we push Denise
You have nice eyes I like your skin
We're gonna have you roll persuasion you guys are gonna do it you got all right well, so let's play out this scene
Then we'll do investigation check for you guys. Okay, so he goes a
Thank-you
Roll roll persuasion check you get plus three on that because he's the opposite
sex
No, you had like no introduction so he's kind of like
He is a I breached my arm in I just put lipstick all over her face
How about now, buddy
What if I take off all my clothes
Do I
I have a 75 feet of wire and I make like a Garrett and a Garrett whatever that's
called and I maybe just kill this guy yeah I didn't want our kid so you also
have you also have Denise the crying ability - you can use okay I'll do that
yeah yeah so you start crying what are you crying about um I'm sad no don't
Cry, start crying.
Oh, I'm sad.
Please let us in.
Give me a D20.
Here we go.
OK.
Yeah, that's not enough.
So he's-- he's like-- no, no, no.
What the fuck?
No, she did-- no, that's not enough on his part.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, nice.
So he's-- sorry, yeah, yeah.
Good job, Denise.
Keep crying.
So he's like, oh, I'm sorry.
I--
[CRYING]
OK, I guess I can--
I remember if that's not enough she will take her clothes off. I don't want to keep trying.
Somebody's telling me to not acknowledge her.
Alright.
Somewhere.
Okay, I'll look I'll let you in you can just come into the come to the front area just don't go anywhere else.
And so he he opens the gate.
I'm coming, right now.
We just want you to come into the front area.
Right now outside I'm also coming into the front area.
[Laughter]
So he just lets you in so you're behind the gate.
You two, you roll an investigation check, Vera.
- Two.
- That's bad.
You roll one now.
- Okay.
- Oh wait, that's five.
- Yeah, that's still not better.
- Yeah.
- I get, you said investigation?
- That's right.
- That's a 17.
- Okay.
- That's how it's done, lesbian.
(dramatic music)
- I stand down.
- Oh, while all this is happening--
- Cut back to you guys for a minute.
- Yeah, we're done, and I opened up a pack of cigarettes
to have a cigarette after this,
and I get a golden ticket to the cigarette banter.
(laughing)
- Does not happen.
Doesn't happen.
- Blake, I found a golden ticket!
I've got a golden ticket!
- I'm smoking a bully stick.
- You're smoking a what stick?
- One of those dog sticks.
(laughing)
- Dog owners know.
- They're raw.
- Wide bone.
- Yeah, that's actually, it's a cow's penis or something.
- Yeah, it's a bull's penis.
- Okay, yeah.
So you, with that 17, oh damn, yeah.
You see iron, you see like iron, like,
rungs on the side of the manor, on the back,
going all the way up to the second floor,
that look like they're meant to blend in,
but you can see them pretty clearly.
So you can use that to get in through a window up there
where you see these pretty curtains.
- I bring the girls and we go do that.
But I go up, I sag my pants a little bit
so that I show my butt crack to Denise.
- Okay, cool. - And I like it.
- Okay, looks good. - That's right.
- So are we going in with them?
- Yeah, we realize that they're leaving.
- I have a plan for you guys.
- And we just try to walk in.
- Okay, you say what? - I have a plan for you guys.
- The guard goes, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I can't I already let this little girl in I can't let you are you a little girl now. No, he's
My reception
I mean, I don't know. I don't how do I know that she's your daughter?
Okay, is she balding too?
She's also balding!
You can roll deception again with no penalty with your health.
I...
She's far away.
I- I-
She's just in the front yard.
Oh.
I stand up on my hind- I stand up on my hind legs,
and I'm face to face with him,
eyes to eyes, and I say,
"I left my dog to win there!"
*laughter*
Okay, he saves against psychic damage.
That was on saving against psychic damage, but now roll a Deceptor.
Okay, that's a 10.
Okay, yeah, he's like, "I don't know if I've ever seen you before."
Like, I left my dog toy in there too!
Do you know them?
Yeah, these guys are my best friends.
- Okay, yeah, with that he's like,
all right, just fine, come here,
I don't want these protestors to know.
Just take care of your kid, I guess, or whatever.
- He's like just looking at you, Scooby.
- I'm looking his face, and he's getting
an interesting taste.
- Roll perception, also.
- Okay.
That's a 19.
- Oh, wow, okay.
As you're looking his face, you get a look at his lapel,
And you see his name there and it says George Dewey.
That's just something you say.
George Dewey?
Good name.
So, you guys enter in.
I say, "Thank you, George Dewey."
[Laughter]
You guys get in there from the front.
You guys are going from the back.
So we're going to split this up a little bit in that case.
Because you three are going in from the front.
Or, yeah, and Velma,
Vera, whoops,
and Jed are going in from the back.
Whoa, now that's an awesome episode of television. I wonder what's gonna happen next
Whoa, I didn't see you there. Don't sneak up on me like that. It's Halloween
Anyway, I got an awesome message for you and your parents as you probably know our Saturday morning cartoon block is able to provide you
With high quality programming through our generous donor network
Your gifts help keep the PAL Kids TV system strong and provides revenue that makes outsized impact possible.
If you want to find out what happens next on
the Teenage Gumshoe Crew and Their Dog, you'll have to become a donor too.
For just $10 a month, you can listen to more of our ScareTober programming and also additional
Dungeons & Dragons programming and help keep cartoon characters like the ones you just heard off the streets and
and away from drugs like weed, which was alluded to in this episode of the show.
Head to swagpoop.com to find out how to subscribe to the Dungeons and Dragons tier, or go to
patreon.com/podcastaboutlist.
This is Gunnysack, signing off and saying cowabunga!
Thank you.
[music]