We're starting.
He showed me that.
I don't even know what this game is.
You guys know this Pokemon song?
Whoa, jukebox.
Mate, you playing Zelda.
No, it's one of the Pokemon songs.
What?
I got Squirtle?
You got Blue.
- What the fuck? - Your water, bro.
- We are in-- - You said your water.
- I never-- - You chose water.
- I never chose water.
- Then someone didn't check the group chat often enough
to respond in time and pick the two best types.
- So, here's-- - This is busy.
- First of all, water's way better than grass, but--
(Justin groans)
- Okay, girlish woman.
- Fine with me. - I actually like it.
So, we are in, we're doing a little test run.
I wanna try this out.
I sort of took some 5e stuff, re-skinned it with some Pokemon stuff.
I wanted to see what it would look like to have you guys play as Pokemons.
Can I change my sprite?
Yeah, if you want to. You're in control of that.
Oh, I can change that on my own?
I think so, yeah. I'm pretty sure I gave you controls of that.
I can't believe how slow my computer runs when I have Roll20 open.
Yeah, Roll20 is optimized for sure.
So you guys, the trainer Sullivan is on a mission
to become the greatest of them all, the very best,
and he got to have three starter Pokemon
because he's such a bad trainer.
So they're like, we're just gonna give you all three.
And he got you three Pokemon,
and you're now in the first gym,
and you're up against Dwight.
- We skipped all the town stuff?
That's the best part of the game.
- This is what I wanted to try out the fighting first.
I wanted to see how this worked.
- Oh, I thought maybe you prepared stuff.
- Oh, so we're playing out of order?
- Mm-mm, mm-mm.
We're starting in the gyms.
We'll go back to the towns.
- Then maybe eventually we can become trainers ourselves
instead of just little animals.
- Yes, that's what I mean, that's what I mean.
We're starting with this,
'cause I maybe would want you guys to just be trainers.
I wanna see what's up to have you be--
- I'm overprepared.
- Animals first.
No, tell me about your guide. - You're overprepared?
- You're overprepared.
- I wrote a character intro, man.
I thought that this was the beginning
of something amazing and new.
- It is a beginning. - And new and amazing.
- Well, we're gonna do that.
I do wanna do like a real Pokemon campaign,
but I didn't wanna just rush into it
'cause I had lots of other things to prep for that.
But I wanted to start with the battles at least.
So tell me about your character.
What are your starter Pokemon?
Who are you guys?
- I'll go last 'cause I actually have
something awesome to read. - Go, Caleb.
- And you guys are the Pokemon. - Go, go, go.
- Yeah, Caleb, go first. - I'm adding stuff to it
as we speak. - Oh, you're adding to it.
Yeah, so. That's awesome.
So you guys should go ahead and finish adding.
I'll probably be adding for a couple minutes, so you might as well just go.
Alright, well we can sit and wait. I don't mind waiting.
Okay, I'm gonna go.
Whatever.
Okay, go ahead.
I thought it was gonna be...
Okay, make sure to do the voice.
You gaze through the tree line in the dead night.
(laughing)
No sounds to be heard, no sights to be seen.
It's quiet.
Thank you.
Too quiet. - Perfect.
- That is, until you see two glowing red eyes
breaking through the dark.
At first, you may think it might be two leaves
or two red marbles or a red-eyed bear.
But as your eyes adjust to the darkness,
you realize it's something much, much more terrifying.
Me.
part dog, part ant, part monkey, part lava, part food,
part bird, and part fire ant.
My name strikes fear across almost all cultures,
and they all have some name for me.
Helios, Kagatsuchi, Chantico, Pele, Gira.
But please, just call me Flamer.
(laughing)
- The frog named me Flamer.
- Yeah, Flamer's my favorite, go Flamer!
- Okay, thank you.
- Patches, I tried to switch my character token
and it didn't work.
- So my Pokemon is known as Smoku.
I'll do a Pokedex.
Smoku, the smoking weed and watching TV Pokemon.
Able to watch over 100 episodes of Netflix in a single day.
and able to smoke weed and watch 100 movies in a single week.
- How much weed can he smoke according to the Pokedex?
- Over 100 joints of weed can be smoked
by this small but pint-sized Pokemon.
- But what does he look like?
- Small but pint-sized.
- He's the size of a pint. - This small but pound-sized
Pokemon packs a powerful punch with his special ability.
And he looks like a weed. - What is it?
- What does he look like, sorry?
- He looks like a weed leaf holding a TV remote,
or a Roku remote, more specifically.
And he has red eyes, like you, but in a different way,
if you know what I'm saying, if anyone at home
knows what I'm saying.
- Okay.
- Not fire eyes.
- Not fire, but-- - Not like a fire ability eyes.
- No, like maybe he was using fire,
and the eyes got red because of that.
- Later evolutions, you're gonna be grass poison,
That's what I'm hearing.
- Well, we'll split more grass psychic.
- No, definitely. - Oh.
- Yeah, I think poison.
- Or maybe it'll be three or four types by the end.
- You can't really do that, but that's fine.
- Yeah, I might, probably 10 to 12 types
by my second evolution.
- Helios is sort of like a-- - Because there's so many
different channels on TV that it's kind of--
- Well, it's Flamer. - Sorry, Flamer.
- I could be watching water channel or fire channel
or basically whatever.
- Flamer's sort of gonna be like dark fire
or something like that.
- Right. - Dark.
- Fire.
Just fire, pure fire you'll be the whole way through.
- Yeah, I don't need a second thing.
- Yeah.
Who is this then?
This blue one.
- Did you get my...
- Did you send it to me over Discord?
- Yeah.
I tried to change it on roll 20, but it didn't let me.
- All right, I'll do it.
You explain who your guy is while I do this.
- Why the photo has to show up first.
it's the only way for it to make sense
okay give me one second
is it a bowl of water?
no
or a cup i guess? why do i think it's going to be a sperm? why am i guessing right now that it's about to be a sperm?
why would that be a water animal? i'm the water pig
what? ok...
water's a stupid idea for a pokemon
damn
what are you even doing?
I'm a pig that lives in water instead of mud.
Like a swimming pig?
Yeah, it's a pig that swims.
I guess that's kinda cool.
And his ability is eating.
Any animal eats.
Not like a pig.
So you're some kind of water pig.
Yeah, I'm going ahead.
He is a water pig, not some kind of water pig.
I'm sending my guy's icon to you right now,
Pat, just real quick. Yeah, please do.
just so you can tell. - Oh, oh, oh.
And I live, I'm from the Bahamas.
- Okay, this is getting to something.
- Okay, but your name is still just Waterpig?
- Yes.
- Which region is the Bahamas?
In like, the Bahama region? - Alola.
- Is that Alola also?
Yeah, okay.
- I would like to change my image to this.
- Yeah, I changed it already.
Are you giving me another image?
- I gave you another one, and it's even better.
- So you're still a pig?
- Why'd you send a pig wearing a human suit?
- I was gonna be the human pig,
then remembered that it had to be water.
- So you went water pig.
- So you changed to the water pig.
- So this was the other one, I said water pig.
So this is--
- That's a good one.
- Okay.
- That looks almost like a Pokemon.
- Are you both the pig, it's like--
- That's part of my body, yeah.
It's like Klefki.
- It's like a snail shell.
You have a water fountain attached to your back.
- Okay guys, I'm gonna create--
- Oh, my name is LK.
- I'm gonna create my point of orders.
Like the water company, like the water bubbler company.
LK the water pig.
- You should just be Bubbler.
- I'm water pig.
No, I'm gonna continue to be water pig.
- Go Bubbler!
- 'Cause he named me or Cameron.
- You know he named you Bubbler.
- Pokemon.
All right, I'm Bubbler, the pig.
I'm Bubbler the pig.
- Bubbler the pig.
- Well I'm fucking, I'm a flamer.
- Flame animal? - Charmander.
You're just a regular Charmander?
- No, I'm a flamer and I'm a fucking,
some kind of crazy god.
- So, okay, cool.
So now I know who you guys are.
So you're facing off against Dwight, Dwight Trainer.
- And, Dwight Trainer?
- No, Dwight, Dwight-- - Oh, now I see him.
- He's really hard to say.
Dwight Trainer. - Truth.
- No, 'cause he's not, no, it's a different guy.
- Okay. - Looks like Dwight Schrute.
- Yeah, looks a lot like Dwight Schrute.
- And he says, "You're never gonna beat my Pokemon."
And then Sullivan says he's going to beat him.
- So let's-- - What kind of line is that?
- He says he's-- - You're never gonna
beat my Pokemon?
(laughing)
- That's what he said. - That's what he sucks.
- Sometimes some trainers be saying that
in the Pokemon games. - That's literally
what they say, that I thought maybe you'd have a--
- Well, no, usually they say something more like,
"The sky is so blue," or something.
- Okay, I'd like to-- - Or they'll say--
- I like swimming with rubber pants on.
- Get back here, Flamer.
- We're rolling for initiative?
- Don't clip that, by the way.
- Yeah, sure.
Everyone roll for initiative.
- Okay, I got a 15.
- Okay.
- Okay, I have a character sheet.
- Why am I getting the wrong character sheet?
Under Pokemon, I'm getting this one that says weird stuff.
- Oh, I've got mine.
I got mine, y'all.
- You should be getting yours.
- It just looks weird.
- Yeah, it is weird.
It's a simpler one.
- I keep finding better pictures of the 12s.
- Can you, sorry, can you re-roll, Pat,
but make sure you have your character clicked?
'Cause then it shows up in the turn orders.
- Okay.
- And I will edit it.
It'll be 15 still.
- Why is White Spy rolling rolls?
- 'Cause he's confused.
- What's White Spy doing here?
- Did you ever--
- Get out of here, White Spy.
- White Spy at the bottom.
- Pat, you gotta have your character clicked.
- I did.
So click on the little initiative.
- Just rolling D20s.
- You have to roll the initiative.
- Click on the character sheet
and then there's initiative is a little dice,
a little die between actions and your name.
There we go.
- Crit one. - That's awesome.
Okay, that's fine.
It'll be what you want it to be this time.
Cameron, you're gonna go first.
- What does that mean?
- No, 15. - Okay.
- It's gonna be 15. - Okay.
- I'm going to use Smoker Beam.
- So you don't have, I did not give you,
what does Smoker Beam do?
(laughing)
- Basically my guy takes out a blunt and he smokes it
and he gets high as fuck.
- Where's the beam come from though?
- The beam is the light shining out of the TV
onto his face and he smiles at it.
- Oh, he like turns around and clicks on the TV
and it like blasts like a,
like it's a shadow almost of his entire body.
- Exactly, that's what I was thinking all along.
So it's like-- - See,
why am I so good at this Pokemon shit?
- Who are you shooting that at?
Which one are you shooting at?
- The water pig.
(laughing)
- Don't shoot at the water pig.
- I'm super effective against the water pig,
so I might as well shoot at it.
- Stop, he's on your team, mate.
- I'm not gonna shoot at the water pig.
So who's here, are these just normal Pokemon?
Whoa!
- How are you doing that blast?
- What the hell is that?
- I have a blast ability now.
- That's so fucking cool.
- What, are these just normal Pokemon
that we're fighting against?
- Yeah.
- An Onix and a Jamaican?
- An Onix and an Executor.
(laughing)
Okay, I will shoot my beam at the Onix.
- Oh!
- That is a critical.
- Did you get a critical hit?
- Yeah, but it doesn't do anything for the first turn.
- For this turn, yeah.
So this first turn, you start charging up your,
what did you call it?
- Smoker's beam.
- Well here's what it says about solar beam,
which I think we can--
- Smoker's beam. - Smoker's beam.
The user gathers light on the first turn,
then blasts a bundled beam on the next turn.
- Okay, that is from--
- So next turn I think I'll be blasting a bundled beam.
- Okay, that's just, that's what it said.
So I tried to find descriptions.
- A bundled beam.
- And they called it a bundled beam.
- What does that mean?
- Okay, but yeah, I don't do anything this turn.
- Okay, so you're gathering your charge here.
- But maybe we can use that attack roll next turn.
- Oh yeah, we can use that.
You are up now, PatrickPokemon.
- Okay, so I'm effective against,
or is it water against, or no, no, no, no.
Is it water, these are both,
I'm effective against both of them, right?
- No, you're not.
- You're effective against rock.
- Water's good against rock, but water's bad against grass.
Right, okay, that's what it was.
Okay, then I'm gonna go for the onyx.
- Okay, cool.
So what are you gonna do?
- I blasted it with wet pig shit.
(laughing)
- So is that muddy water?
- I don't have that.
- I gave him muddy water.
- No, it's not muddy.
I didn't even change muddy water.
he just updated it before i can change them
he changed, he changed, yeah he changed
yeah you can change it, this is what
yeah you can change the name of your moves
yeah so he changed
he changed water gun to wet pig shit
*laughter*
cool, wait, describe to me how does he shoot wet pig shit
how does bubbler shoot, and what sound does bubbler make
can you just imagine how he would shoot
wet pig shit
ok, so sullivan goes
bubbler use water gun
then instead... *burp*
yeah
*laughter*
I do that, turn around
and then the bubbler on my butt
shoots
wet pig shit out at
Onyx. And that was a... did I get a
20 or...
It looks like you rolled it with advantage
Oh. So let's take the...
what was the first one?
17? The first one was a 17. That still hits
for sure. So yeah, so now
So now you're gonna roll for damage now.
So you'll see there on your sheet, it'll say what to do.
- I roll 1d6 plus three.
- And that's gonna be doing double because of the type.
- Four.
- So it's doing eight damage to this rock snake creature
that writhes in pain as it's showered in your pig shit.
(pig snorting)
- He's like the nastiest Pokemon.
Nobody usually chooses him.
- He's gross.
- Maybe someone felt bad for him.
- Sullivan was bullied into picking him.
He did feel bad for him,
but he didn't necessarily want him either.
But now it is that Onix's turn.
And so he's gonna go after spying a type differential
using his keen Dwight senses.
- Bastard.
- He's just gonna go after Flamer.
- Uh-oh.
- Wait, he's gonna go after him specifically?
He's targeting him?
- He's targeting me?
I don't know about that, man.
- He's targeting the character.
- He kinda looks like me.
Both of these kinda look like me.
- You have kind of a moment of recognition.
- Okay, so what do I do?
I dodge it?
Okay, I dodge.
- You will have to roll, actually.
- Okay, I'll roll.
- Roll a D20 against your decks,
'cause as the onyx rears its head up.
- 13 with my dex bonus.
- 13 with your dex bonus.
Okay, that is not enough to save.
- Oh shit.
- It rears its head up and starts knocking around
and rocks, smaller rocks fall out of the crevices
of its bigger rocks.
I have no idea how else it would do that, to be honest.
But you end up taking 16 damage in that case.
- 16, man, oh crap.
- So here's the thing. - That's a lot.
- How do I change my damage, my health on this new version?
- Go to your, if you click on your icon,
you'll see the number on the top.
- Oh yes, I see this. - Just subtract, yeah.
So that'll be 19 you'll have.
Also, so next for you guys,
you have five potions you can use that will fully heal you
for this whole fight.
There are a couple other Pokemon you'll have to fight.
Three revives you can use as well.
And then three of each status effect healing item.
- Mr. Patches?
- Yes, Maya Califf.
- My life won't change.
- I'll do it.
- I don't know what-- - Thank you.
- I'm sorry.
- There you go.
Okay.
So now it is your turn, Flamer.
- Well, I want to use fire blast on the egg.
- Okay.
- 16.
- That hits the egg.
- Yes.
Oh yeah.
- 24.
- Yeah, you-- - 24?
- Yeah, so times two. - You kill my kill?
- Yeah, describe your kill on the egg.
You have five uses of this, so you have four now left.
- I close my eyes and I rumble around, I clench my fist.
(growling)
And then I flame it all over him.
- Yeah, and Dwight goes, "No, Jamaican!"
And he takes him back, and then he throws him out.
- He's fucking dead.
- Yeah, but he puts him back in the ball.
- They put the dead ones in the ball when they're done.
- Yeah, okay, yeah.
- Can I jump into the Pokeball?
- Yeah, you jump, yeah.
- I jump into the Pokeball too?
- Roll a d20 and we'll add your decks.
What'd you get?
- 12.
- Okay, cool, yeah, you land in the Pokeball with--
- Come here!
- Nope, just you.
- You land the executor.
You're out of the match now.
- I wanna just--
- I'm just beating the shit out of him.
(laughing)
- You see--
- Last nobody tried this tactic before.
- Yeah, chase him into the Pokeball, man.
- Yeah, just go in there with him.
- Dwight, please, please, please tell him to stop.
and Sullivan joins, return, Flamer!
- No.
- Didn't, Sullivan kinda just shrugs.
- Okay, I'm individually choking out every single head
on the executor. - Please!
Yeah, you're just, you're--
- I'm taking both of my hands
and I'm putting them between two sets of heads each
and slapping them front hand, back hand,
front hand, back hand, over and over and over again.
- Okay, yeah.
- Dwight makes executor, Dwight, oh no, I shit.
- There's nothing he can do, man.
He can't get in this Pokeball.
- I was trying to figure out what he can do.
- Okay guys, the strat here, we're all gonna get
into the other guy's Pokeballs
before he can even send out the other Pokemon.
- This is a new strategy I came up with.
- This is the perfect strategy.
- This is a strategy that's gonna change the way
that the game is played forever.
You're going to have to address this
in the next Pokemon game. - They will.
Dwight starts to plead with Sullivan and says,
"I concede, I concede, please!"
And Sullivan goes, "Okay, okay."
- Who's conceding?
- Yeah, sure, all right.
- I would like to destroy one of the,
I would like to cut off one of the heads.
The other two can live.
- Roll a strength check.
Let's just see if you can saw through it with your claws.
- No, I can't.
- Okay, yeah.
It's worse though, almost,
'cause you just kinda mangle it.
- It's kinda hanging off a little bit.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Okay, I'm done.
- Dwight does give up.
Dwight gives up.
- What, I didn't even get to use Smoker's Beam yet.
- Okay, you wanna use Smoker's Beam?
Or you wanna save it for the next?
- Yeah, we gotta take out the Onix.
- No, he gave up.
- Oh, wait, yeah, that's true.
We could save it for the next.
- It's super effective, and it's 17 plus 25,
which is 42 times two.
- Yeah, it's 84. - You could save it
for the next, the first Pokemon that he throws out.
- So I've used it on the Onix and I did 84 damage.
- He wants to see.
- I also climbed inside the Onix's mouth
so that when he takes a back on the Pokeball,
I'm going into the Pokeball with it.
- Okay, cool.
So, you're gonna--
- 'Cause listen, turn order and concede,
I already was charging this up.
It's gonna happen whether or not he concedes.
I can't keep the bungled beam inside my body.
- Just shoot it at Dwight.
You can shoot it at Dwight.
- Okay, I shoot at Dwight,
but then I also am still going inside Onix's mouth.
- Oh yeah, you kill Dwight.
and uh... yeah
the next day i don't worry i get all of the white spooky was a sir cracking them
like exit from the uh... you guys
guys are not over flame is body
i've got sullivan in a book you bought the
but i don't know
you're an animal
or a little bit
you know that i like
you know that really have some fun
okay cool
- All right, now the other trainer and the gym leader
are both throwing out their Pokemon
'cause they're terrified of you guys.
- They should be.
- Yeah, so here they come.
- Better not be Tarakion.
- I don't know what that is.
- Is that called Ekis?
Or Ekis?
- Arbok. - Arbok.
- And that one's called My Arms?
- That's Machoke.
- Machoke. - God damn it.
- It's okay.
And then last but not least,
Raichu.
- Raichu.
Tell me why this old guy patch
is only using the first generation of Pokemon.
- Right?
- Come on, throw some Clefkies in there.
- I'm not gonna do that on the first,
this is like a trial run to see what I win.
- That's true.
- Can I put stuff on the map?
- Can I put an image on the map,
or is that only a DM thing?
- If you have the ability-- - I would like to throw
my Pokemon. - You might have the ability.
You wanna throw your, you can throw your own.
- I wanna throw my own Pokemon. - One of us needs to,
one of us needs to pretend to be the trainer
so they don't get wise. - I'll do it.
- We're stray Pokemon. - Yeah.
- You guys can-- - I got that sound.
- So I'm in the back, I mean I have a suit,
so I'm sitting in the back. - Yeah, sure.
- I'm pretending to be a normal--
- A pig? - Human, yeah.
Just a pig man. - What the fuck
is on the screen? - Big red block.
- Sorry y'all.
- What are you doing?
my b
does my son on your sorry about that
all right cool
we're back to the top of the order
uh...
array waits a long first okay you're pretending you're a guy
so i don't know
uh... and i think
i'm glad i did it
that i had a lot of these
i'm trying to be a a human i'm trying to speak so you can only say water pig
you know but what do you have a a a a a
you know you're going on your say your name
Oh my god!
So the trainer comes up to you, the gym leader.
He says, "Okay, I could have swore there was a frog here a little while ago."
I'm smelling his butt.
Are you getting rolled?
Roll to see how it smells.
What'd you get?
Six.
six
the case is that the
the
I know that Pokemon. Where's your train?
That's one of the original 153.
And I blast him with my udder.
Damn it.
Okay, I mean you still hit him, he's a normal guy.
Yeah. He's like, "Oh my god!"
And he starts to just blast him to the other side.
He just, yeah, he runs back there, he like sends out his Pokemon, he's like,
"Alright, I gotta take care of these rogue-ass Pokemon."
And, uh, yeah, uh, let's start from the top of the order again.
- You're up.
And then we'll see what happens after you beat him.
'Cause then you guys are gonna have the town
at your disposal, I guess.
- Is Grass effective against the strong guy?
- The strong?
Is Grass effective against the strong?
- I think so. - No.
Grass is not effective against fighting.
- What about the everything else that's on the screen?
- No, he's weak against poison.
- Weak against poison?
Okay, well, all you--
- These are guys,
These were supposed to be staggered out as you fought them,
but then you guys trapped your trainer in a pokeball.
- Well, we have new strategies where the effectiveness
barely even matters these days.
- Oh, okay.
- So first of all, I'm going to use my attack, Hulu,
which, I'll read this here,
Hulu shoots two to five seeds in a row to strike the foe.
- So roll one D6 to see how many seeds
when you do Hulu.
- Six.
Three.
- Okay, so you get three seeds, and so--
- One D4 each it looks like.
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay, so.
- And who are you shooting that at again?
- Now I'm shooting this directly at the gym leader.
So that's eight damage from my seeds.
And I'm aiming for his groin.
- He's--
- 'Cause I'm high, and when I'm high,
Honestly, I can't control myself.
- And how much damage did he get from Utter?
What did he get?
Oh, Christ.
- Dude, I don't even think he did any damage.
I think I was just blasting him away from me.
So you don't have to worry about that.
- So you weren't using, it says torn water.
- You were not using Hydro Pump then on this guy.
- No, no, I was using Utter, which is the foe is bla--
Oh, it is Hydro Pump, actually.
- Okay, so he's dead.
(laughing)
I was kinda like wondering how long it would take for you guys to attack traitors, but
this is immediate.
Alright you Arbok macho, macho Raichu, get it back in your balls.
Or join us and we will destroy all of the human civilization.
Stop Waterpig.
Stop copying me.
I thought that we were supposed to look menacing.
The snake is like...
I just got Deja vu, Waterpig.
I feel like I heard what you said before.
That's my character's voice and that's the first time he's talked to.
Arbok, Arbok says, "Uh, what's in it for us?"
Dude!
I will feed you this.
Snotilisp.
You sound gay.
Well, no, you're flamer.
What is that supposed to mean?
Whoa!
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
Okay, I'm going to attack him.
Arbok, I will feed you this.
I
Don't see it what I sent it to him I sent to him on this on discord
Oh, that's not a private message. You said this and private message. Yeah, I didn't think that through he sent me a hamtaro hamster
I have this in my back pocket. He's sent me one of the hamtaro
What's the deal with these guys?
- It's so small to hold a seed like that.
- Okay, here's what's in it for you, Arbok.
You don't have to live in a Pokeball anymore,
and you don't have to hide away and hide your true self.
You can be whoever you want.
- And you can eat this.
- You're calling me gay again, I think.
- I'm not, what is up with you being obsessed
with gay stuff, okay?
I'm just saying.
- You're playing the victim here, dude.
- Once we get rid of all the humans,
There's nobody to look down on you
for whatever kind of lifestyle you choose to live.
- Urgent as to whoever you want to spend your time with.
- And the snake goes over to the Raichu
and they start to confer.
And the Machoke goes over to you, Flamer,
and he says,
so,
me know
have to listen
to
puny humans.
(laughs)
- He's thinking about it.
And they go, okay.
They agree, all three of them agree
that that would be better. - Wow.
- The hamster-- - Okay, now we can launch
a surprise attack and kill them.
- Okay, I put the hamster back in my back pocket.
- Oh no, you guys are gonna attack them?
- Caleb said he's frozen, can we hear him?
- No, we can't hear him. - But he's not talking.
He's just looking around.
- Yeah, wait, is he actually frozen or is he lying?
- I think he's lying.
- It's a weird lie.
- He hasn't even tried to speak.
- He hasn't seen you, I haven't seen your mouth.
You're not moving at all.
You're not talking.
- He's gonna reload.
- He's just lying.
- Maybe we're frozen?
- Okay, so while he's doing this,
we should change his character token.
- Hello.
- Okay, he's back.
- We could see you, man,
when you weren't even trying to talk.
You were just looking around.
You guys were frozen.
I really just wanted to get your attention.
He said, "Can you hear me?"
I was trying to see if you guys were moving.
Can you hear me?
I don't know.
I knew you guys were frozen,
so I figured I was too.
Like a fucking baby.
What's that about?
What's that dig?
It's like a baby.
thinks how about your ball frozen patches so why would that it's not just on your
why would it just assumed what because I thought that my zinc castor crash that's
funny patches is call me a baby and I'm sorry man anyway what did you want to say
they agreed to - they're gonna say I think we should just kill them now though
So they have, now we know that we could basically have domination over them.
We might as well kill them.
Here's what we do.
Guys, guys, okay.
We're gonna do our plan.
We're gonna take over the human world.
But six Pokemon running around.
Listen, we don't have the numbers for this.
That's a whole team.
What are you talking about?
We don't have the numbers for this yet.
We don't have the numbers for this yet, okay?
They're gonna get wise.
We have no trainer.
We're gonna be running around.
We're gonna have to have you guys get into Pokeballs just for a little bit so that we
collect a bunch of Pokemon and then we'll let you all out
at the same time and we'll kill the mayor.
- Except for Machoke, we're gonna put you in human clothes
and we're also going to actually implant an explosive
into your body that we have a remote to,
but you don't have to worry about that.
- And a fake nose.
- But you're gonna be in human clothes
and a fake nose and a fake mustache.
- We're going to give you a disguise.
- And you will be our trainer.
- Mm, yay.
- So we have Sullivan in a Pokeball plus Raichu and--
- Put 'em all in the same one.
- Yeah.
- And we only have one ball.
- We'll see what they do to,
see what they do with Sullivan.
- You can just see a skeleton,
like, coming out the other side of that.
(laughing)
- Carrying around just a fat Pokeball,
a big, fat, bulging Pokeball.
- Yeah, so okay, so you put the snake away,
you put the mouse away,
You dress up the macho thing in this suit.
So you guys have your guys,
you guys are now done with this gym.
So you're in this town now.
Let's zoom out.
You're in the town.
What do you guys wanna go?
It's the first town, it's like the Pewter City town
kind of thing.
Is Pewter the first one in Kanto?
- I wanna go to Nurse Jackie's office.
- I think Pewter is the first one 'cause that's rock.
- Right, yeah, that's right.
Nurse Jock.
- Nurse Joe. - Nurse Jackie is the show.
- Nurse Jackie.
- All right, so you want, is that Carmella Soprano?
She's Nurse Jackie, right? - Yeah.
- Okay. - Oh my God.
Was that Carmella Soprano on the phone right now?
- Is this Carmella Soprano?
(laughing)
- All right, yeah, you wanna go to Nurse Jackie, okay.
You guys go to the-- - Yeah.
- The Poke, what's it, the Poke Center?
- Center. - Poke Center.
- Pokemon Center. - The Pokemon Center.
You guys go in with the Machoke.
The Machoke is still trying to figure out
like kind of how to do stuff.
So he kind of, he sort of, it's a push door.
He figures out that it's, he tries to pull it.
And you could feel the hinges coming off.
- The first thing he tries is pulling it.
- Does Nurse Jackie think, is she attracted to Machoke?
- Why don't you roll Insight?
- Okay.
- Probably girls would be.
- She should have to roll some kind of wisdom save
against those muscles.
I think she can't help herself.
- How do I roll insight?
- Oh, just roll intelligence.
I didn't give him skills.
- Why does Machoke have all these lines on his arms?
What's that supposed to represent?
I'm stupid.
- Tattoos.
- Self-harm, dude.
- Yeah, that's a nice thing.
- It's really sad.
- They made him have crazy hair as well.
- I'm stupid.
Inside is wisdom.
I just saw I and thought, yeah.
- Well, it's the same multiplier,
so I'll take my first one.
- Sure, yeah, that's fine with me.
What is the multiplier, plus one or something?
- Plus one, yeah.
- Okay, so 15, cool.
She's definitely looking him up and down,
like he looks, most of the trainers
that come in here are 10.
- Here's a question I have, I guess, real quick.
- You know, it's the first man trainer
she's seen in a while.
- Since you're kind of the master
of this Pokemon world right now,
you might be able to answer this for me, Patches.
- Yeah, I'll do my best.
- But is his underwear part of his body
or does he have a thing under it?
Is that the kind of thing I'm supposed to?
- You should know that.
- Well, I mean, right now,
you have power over everything, essentially.
- So this is your decision.
- So I'm gonna go ahead and pull down that--
I'm gonna go ahead and pull down that--
- Pants him.
- Speedo, real quick.
- And it's, yeah, 'cause they can breed, right?
- Can a Pokemon like Machoke breed with a human woman?
- Can they at least go on dates
if they're not gonna-- - Can we see--
- Whether or not they're gonna breed?
- Can they fall in love, at the very least?
- Yeah.
- At the very least.
- All these things are possible.
- Life partners.
- Okay, so what we need to do is try to have
Nurse Jackie to have sex with this animal.
- Right, then we create human Pokemon hybrids
and that's how we take over the world.
- Okay, so it's a long term plan.
- We need to breed Nurse Jackie with a giant lizard.
- From what I'm seeing on Google Images right now,
It seems like Machoke has sex with other men.
- Okay, so I tried to...
(laughing)
I tried to look up how long does breeding a Pokemon take
'cause I know it does it in game
and it says after every 256 steps.
- Okay, wait, this is, okay.
All right, so let's get these two rocketed and rolexed
and then we'll send her on a little, a brisk walk.
- Let's Google here, how long does it take to take 256?
- Yeah, so let's fight, can we find something
in between that and nine months?
Or is it like--
- No, it's 256 steps, dude, come on.
- Yeah. - Okay.
- Yeah, play it as it lies. - It's a dominant gene.
I guess I have been playing it as it lies.
- Come on.
- How long does Pokemon breeding take?
- 100 steps.
- You can get a new egg every couple minutes, smiley face.
- 100 steps a minute would be brisk walking.
- I can estimate it's roughly 1,000 steps,
spread about six eggs now and each time was on the spot.
- Yeah, people can see this, Patrick.
- What?
- The thing you just said.
(laughing)
- So?
- I guess you're right.
(laughing)
- Sucks.
Hey, for those listening, those just listening--
- Don't watch the video.
- Yeah.
- So Pokemon breed every two and a half minutes.
- Okay, that's, okay.
So, can we--
- But then, so would that make the--
- Well, all we have to do is--
- Can we do like a ratatouille?
Can we do a ratatouille thing first
where you guys take her on a date?
- Sure, but all we have to do is get them in the same room
for about five minutes and they're gonna have a red twice.
- They're definitely gonna fuck.
- Here's my question.
So, when the Pokemon puts the baby inside of her,
(laughing)
- So it takes 250, is that just to...
So she's gonna have a baby.
- That makes an egg.
I don't know how long it takes for the egg to hatch.
- But it takes like a full day.
It basically takes a full day to hatch a Pokemon egg.
- A whole day?
We don't have that kind of time.
- Hold on.
- Look up how long it takes for an egg to hatch.
So in the meantime, while you're looking that up,
What are you guys telling to the Machoke to get the nurse to get interested in him?
But it's also not gonna be an egg because this is a human woman and humans don't lay eggs.
So what would it be like a...
Hold on.
She might have to care for this child.
This will answer the question.
10,240 steps or if it's a...
The fastest...
The fastest Pokemon egg to hatch is 1,280.
So...
How long does it take for a Machop?
Look up how long it takes for a Machop egg to hatch then.
Guys, we're getting,
I think we're getting ahead of ourselves.
We don't even know if she like likes him.
We don't know.
I just Googled here what happens
when a Pokemon breeds with a human.
Okay, what does it say?
It says that there will never be a half-breed
from a female Pokemon.
Okay, but that's--
Yeah, but we have a male Pokemon.
Solved.
Okay.
DNA follows a different set of rules. It takes 10 minutes and 30 seconds.
So apparently guys, Pokemon DNA follows a different set of rules y'all. So it takes two minutes.
I would like to... Here's what it says. Human female and male Pokemon is a little more
tricky. The offspring is full human with minimal Pokemon traits. The human
would still give birth to a baby so the human offspring could gain some IV
traits from the father, maybe be stronger than normal humans, or faster, or etc.
- No, a human wouldn't be able to use Pokemon moves
unless there was some other mutation.
Maybe a human osprey could.
- Wait, who's writing this?
- So you're saying it would have hidden stat values.
- This is on GameFAQs.
- It would have hidden.
(laughing)
- Okay.
- So it would have hidden stat values,
but it can't use quick attack is what I'm getting at.
- Right.
- It would be a Pokemon in disguise.
- And it does say maybe if you breed with a male psychic type
that the Pokemon could have,
the human could have psychic moves.
- Okay, okay.
- Okay, this guy's a fighting type though.
- So he'll be able to fight.
- Yeah.
- So that's a good way to--
- And he'll be strong.
- That's sort of a good way to hide it too.
These are just, you're basically making
Master Chiefs right now, right?
Like you're just making super soldiers basically.
- Oh, somebody else said that they tried it
for a while with Gardevoir and they proved
that it can happen.
- Interesting.
- Oh, okay.
- Do you have any footage of that?
- Yeah, let me check their page.
- What does that mean, a while?
- I would like to set up a romantic spaghetti
and meatballs dinner by candlelight
in one of the checkup rooms.
- Okay.
- Yeah, that's a good idea.
- Are you guys gonna--
- Red tablecloth, all that.
- You guys are gonna have to coach Machoke
on how to talk to a woman.
Usually Pokemon just bang
when you put them in the house together.
You gotta help him here.
- Listen here, Machoke.
You need to just smile, nod your head.
Can you nod your head for me?
Can you say yes?
- Yeah.
(laughs)
- There we go.
- It's horrible.
- That's okay, yeah.
Yay, yeah, perfect.
All right, so I want you to go in there
and do that maybe four or five times
and then you'll pretty much make her move.
- Uh-huh.
- Yay.
- Machoke.
- Yeah, there we go.
- Hold on.
- Machoke, do you have five fingers
or are you a four fingered cartoon?
- Yeah, how many fingers do you have?
- He starts shaking his head at the thought of counting.
- I played this video on my pig phone.
- What video?
- How to use unspoken riz, okay.
- Tutorial.
- Oh, that could be useful for a Machoke.
- Yeah, that would work.
- Yeah, let's roll insight for Machoke
to see how he does reading that.
Or understanding that, rather.
I guess it's really just an intelligence check.
- I mean, he's an animal.
- All right, he got a solid 11.
- He's pretty good.
- He gets most of it.
He starts putting his hand in what he thinks is his pocket.
He's trying that out to see--
- His hand is down the front of his pants.
(laughing)
The front of his shorts.
- She'll like that, man.
Oh wait, wait, we need to give him a makeover.
Can we make him sag his pants?
- Yes. - Yes.
- Girls love that shit.
Okay, so we sag his pants.
- Sag his speedo.
- We sag his speedo so his butt cheeks are out
like the Johnson and Johnson logo.
And then we're going to,
what's the male version of makeup?
- Beard.
- We are going to,
there's gotta be some like biohazard,
like pube trimming somewhere in this hospital, right?
- Yes. - Yeah, there has to be.
Yeah, I mean like,
what kind of hospital would it be?
- So we will spray him with some kind of adhesive,
throw those on his face,
kind of just like blow him into his face.
- Yeah. - So there's just these
- Little Pokemon just running around the hospital,
like knocking shit over, grabbing pubes.
- Wait, the babies are already there?
- No, you're the little Pokemon.
- Sorry, I got excited, little Pokemon.
- We ain't that little, buddy.
- I guess I was 100 feet tall, did I mention that?
- So where are you guys telling him
how to do this and stuff?
You guys were like--
- We're telling him in the lobby.
- Oh, the lobby of the hospital.
- Yeah, and then we come in and we say,
nurse Jackie, nurse Jackie, this guy,
whose name is Darren, needs a checkup.
- Darren Chris.
- He needs a checkup very, very badly in room 21B.
- So his pants are all the way down.
He's going, "Yay!"
(laughing)
Staring directly at her.
We're gonna roll Riz for him.
- Okay. - Yes!
- Bovine eyes.
- Can we always rename Charisma to Riz?
As a meme for ourselves?
- As a meme-y?
He's gonna do it with advantage 'cause he's so fire.
- Oh.
- Okay, so that's 14.
So she sort of like looks him up and down and goes,
"Okay, I'll take him."
(laughing)
- Okay. - I'll take him.
- Okay. - I'll take him,
I'll check him up.
So she goes back in the room.
Do you guys follow?
- Yes.
- Yeah, but she does it in a way where nobody knows.
- Yeah, I use sneak. - Roll stealth.
Oh, I don't want to fuck this up actually. I kind of just want to, but we need one person who can coach him.
Who has the highest charisma?
I have plus one charisma.
Mine's plus two.
My, um, hold on.
Oh, 14.
So that's also plus two.
I got a 19.
Okay, well.
I'm a crazy buddy.
Okay, well you want to follow them and kind of coach him through it?
- Can you guys hear it?
'Cause it's gonna be harder if all three of us come.
- I put my pig suit back on.
- Yeah, there we go.
- My human suit.
And I'm walking behind them.
- And so she says,
"What kind of pain have you been feeling?"
- It's no different than a dog being in the room
when you're getting it on.
- Exactly.
(snorting)
(laughing)
Exactly.
- What kind of pain have you been feeling?
(grunting)
He's like trying to...
(laughing)
Don't mess it up, bro.
What are you saying to him?
Um...
Are you saying--
Groin pain.
Okay.
Tell him to just point.
Point to your groin.
Day.
[Laughter]
Pointing at his penis.
Yes!
Okay.
Alright.
[Laughter]
That means the pain scale is at a nine.
Yeah, you're saying that.
He can't even talk.
Yeah.
You're telling, you're this pig with a suit on, it's like leg to nurse though.
Like, that means he's really hurt.
I kicked him.
I'm sorry.
She takes him back to the room.
She says, "Do you want to come in or should I?"
To you, the pig.
Don't go in then.
Don't go in.
that means I'm gonna stand outside and listen.
- Okay, cool.
- Don't say that.
(laughing)
- I mean, I'm actually not listening.
I'm gonna not listen.
- Cool, all right.
So you're standing outside now and--
- And I have a glass up to the door like this.
- Do you have any words of encouragement
before Darren Chris goes in there?
- Any words of advice to-- - I hold him by the--
- I hold him by the hands. - Give him a speech.
Give him a Riz speech.
- Yeah. - Okay.
I hold him by the hands and I look at him and I go.
(slurping)
- Inhuman.
Inhuman, please.
- That means.
- That means fucker right in the pussy.
- Okay.
Yep, I really should have gone, man.
That's where I'm at.
This one's on me, guys.
We're not gonna get our baby.
- Remember that one?
Remember that one?
- I know, I remember that, yep.
- Pretty good.
- I remember that.
- Oh, I'm glad you remember that.
- Remember that.
- I'm glad you remember that.
- So meanwhile, a doctor comes into the lobby
and sees you two, Flamer and Smoker.
- Sounds like Thanksgiving.
- Yeah, my name's Smoku.
- Smoku.
- It's like a combination of Smoker and Roku.
- It's actually an anglicization of the Japanese name
of the Pokemon, which is Samoku.
How are you two fellas doing?
Where's your trainer?
- He's in-- - Smoku, Smoku.
- Smoku, Smoku. - Flamer, Flammy Flamer.
- You're adorable.
- Yeah, but-- - I'm a Flamer.
(laughing)
- Clip that.
- Flamer. - Roll, just charisma.
Roll Riz. - Riz.
- 14. - Nice.
- 15. - Cool, yeah.
Yeah, he's like, oh, you're adorable.
- Well if you guys don't mind just sitting over there
by where the other Pokemon are,
while we take a look at your trainer.
- You guys, you guys bite.
Bite right now, bite.
- No!
- Oh, oh, I'm rolling on my back as if I have an ache.
- Oh no!
- Flamer, flamer!
- What does that mean?
- I'm kind of, I'm like, help him!
- Okay, yeah.
- Flamer, flamer!
Flamer, flamer!
- Pokemon, the Pokemon doctor picks up Smoku and goes,
- Oh, you poor little thing.
And he goes to walk, he picks me up
and I fucking come into the palm of his hand.
(laughing)
'Cause I'm an animal and I don't know any better
and I'm just overstimulated.
(laughing)
I have jizz everywhere.
And I look into his eyes and I go,
smooch, and bat my eyes.
(laughing)
- The doctor, he goes, "Oh."
- I'm just trying to keep him out of work.
- Here, oh.
- He's going.
- Why don't you wait right here and I'll,
I'll be right back, I should just clean this up.
- Wait, wait, point to like a napkin or something.
Make him clean you up.
He puts you, he puts you, he puts you.
What did you say?
- I started licking it up out of his hand.
- And he maybe gets a little HP off that.
(laughing)
Uh-huh.
- He's like, "Oh."
- Definitely gets some HP.
- Does he try to stop me?
- No, he does, he puts you--
- He doesn't try to stop me.
- Well, he puts you on the--
- Okay, so Flamer is videoing this whole thing.
- Yeah, I have the whole thing on a flip camera.
This guy, and I'm talking over it,
oh no, y'all, this doctor just let this dog
eat his own jizz.
Y'all, this shit is disgusting.
- Flamer, Flamer.
- Flamer, Flamer, Flamer, Flamer, Flamer.
(laughing)
No, please, I just want to help this poor creature.
And meanwhile, you...
We just got to keep this guy occupied for two and a half minutes.
Pig, pig, pig, pig man.
Water bubbler.
Water pig.
Bubbler the water pig.
You hear...
Say the whole thing.
Bubbler the water pig.
You hear the nurse make sort of a surprise yelp.
(laughing)
- What do you mean a surprised Yelp?
- Like a ah.
- Yeah, like that.
- And then you hear some other noises
that you ain't never heard before.
- I'm sniffing the crack in the door.
(laughing)
I'm just going.
- Is he hitting it from the back?
- I can smell it 'cause it smells like wing stop.
- Roll to see if you can tell what he's doing.
- Roll the smell check.
- Roll insight, I guess.
Or roll, yeah sure, insight.
31, yeah.
You rolled a D100.
- Oh, I didn't mean to.
I thought I'd get a D20.
- Cool. - Oh, I got the reverse.
I got 13.
- He's doing something not very Christian,
but everyone seems to be enjoying themselves.
- Mommy don't know, dad is getting hot.
- Yep.
- I'm singing that in pig. - At the pokey stop.
- Oh my god.
- And meanwhile, the doctor now is bringing Yusmoku
to the healing station.
And he starts to hear loud noises going on
in one of the rooms where people get attended to.
- I shoot, I use my attack in a non-damaging way.
I use smoke shoot and I shoot smoke into his mouth
to get him high as fuck.
- Okay, cool.
- And then I turn on, I use my universal Roku remote
to change all of the heart monitors in the hospital
to be playing Planet Earth.
- Damn.
- You use the smoke shoot, it gets in his eyes,
Oh! Nurse, can someone get this creature in a Pokeball quickly?
I just need to...
You see a nurse walk over to try to get you in a Pokeball.
Meanwhile, you, Water Pig, see...
The nurse walks out, she's kind of in a daze.
Her hair is askew.
She's pulling down her nurse's...
Yeah, she's doing that.
And you see he see the machoke and he is uh he is a like on the ceiling like spider-man
And he falls he lands on his back and he's got a raging boner
Still yeah - man
Any I get I flick his boner till it goes away
Okay, it slowly goes down and he
He looks to you, and he goes do good
and
Just like that guys
We are going to have an empire over this planet
Yeah, well we need him to do it twice so so we can make them mate with each other
That's a good point to make sure they're both women - or both
Male and female or you need to get other Pokemon
So that there's less because otherwise you're gonna start getting inbreeding shit, and they're gonna be all fine
- They do in the Bible. - What's wrong with that?
- Yeah, but you're not gonna get a good army out of that.
- That's true, also.
- It's not about an army, it's just about
getting more people than the other people.
- Exodus 620, Amorim as his wife,
Jochebed his father's sister,
and she bore him Aaron and Moses.
You think Moses was fucking inbred?
- He was. - It sounds like
he literally was, yeah, just based on that.
- But you mean that he was like stupid type of inbred?
- I guess not, yeah.
- He built a boat.
- No, it's Noah.
- He opened all the exits.
- Ophosus did other stuff.
He ran around the desert.
- He parted the seas.
- He parted the Red Sea.
- So similar.
- Yeah.
- All right, I guess it's--
- But you gotta be a genius
to do something like that. - Maybe these guys
will have magic powers then.
(laughing)
- They can learn--
- Sorry, my fucking mic unplugged.
What were we exactly in the middle of?
- We were debating incest.
- Right. - Yeah.
- Yes.
- But, so okay.
So the nurse is now pregnant at the desk.
That just like happened in the last two minutes.
- So that happened.
- She's like, I have to go to the bathroom.
So she runs to go to the bathroom.
So here's the thing, it's gonna be an egg.
- Fine by me.
- You guys--
- It could be like children of men.
We could be like protecting the first Pokemon
human hybrid egg.
- Oh my God, that's such a good idea.
- I would just say, like you guys should be like,
- She's gonna be like, "Oh God, I fucked a Pokemon.
"That's why an egg came out."
You guys really cannot think of that?
- Somebody fucked up an egg.
- That would be, listen, if I was a girl
and I had sex with someone and I laid an egg,
my first thought wouldn't be that's a Pokemon
that I fucked, it would be that there's something
wrong with me, but like--
- I fucked a chicken. - Oh my God, I have an egg.
- Yeah, an egg came out of me for some weird reason.
- Yeah, she might think she is a Pokemon.
- Yeah.
- So instead of her realizing what happened,
You think and said she would...
- Well, she might just not just instantly think
that's what happened.
Maybe she got through a few other explanations.
- Maybe she thought that guy she just had sex with
used, put an egg in her.
- That's actually maybe true.
- 'Cause why would he be a Pokemon?
- Right, yeah, he was a pleasant, polite guy.
- Yeah, he's--
- With a strong command of the English language.
- Yeah, and his this hurt.
- Oh, he--
- His duh.
- His dog. - His dog.
(laughing)
- Cool, she runs to the bathroom, you hear a--
- Plop.
- Oh, no!
- Dude, she's shit.
- Don't, why are you such a shit?
Bro, this is like a TV show,
you're trying to show the characters
going to the bathroom, man.
- True. - You hear a plop,
and then you hear,
and when you hear like a second later,
she gets off the toilet and you hear an egg fall.
(laughter)
- You hear a plop.
- Yeah, you hear a plop, a flush, and then--
- The second it does--
- Oh my god, wait, an egg.
- Wait, I have to sit back down again.
- The second the egg plops out,
your friend, Darren, his eyes like
light up and he starts shaking,
and he fucking bum rushes to bathroom
and paternal instinct's kicking in.
- Okay. - I just let him go.
kicks down the door and you hear, wait, no, I don't let him go.
I don't let him go. Then I don't let him go. Actually.
I'm realizing the error of my ways. I stopped him. I stopped him and I go,
and that means
you have to make her think she pooped an egg.
Yeah. She's just a regular poop.
Maybe she ate an egg earlier and did she didn't digest it like a kernel of corn.
He's like sort of like looking around like, and then just like,
Like he kind of looks at you, kind of nods, and then like dashes for the door.
Uh-huh.
And he goes, "EH POOP!"
And like reaches into the toilet and pulls out the egg.
And you hear her scream.
Well, look, she probably is embarrassed by this whole situation.
She probably just wants to be rid of this egg, right?
And he's just like, sort of like, running to the bathroom and crapping his shit.
This guy that just fucked craps his own crap on the sheet.
And then he sits on it.
Am I the asshole?
That's funny.
Yeah.
Am I the asshole that craps the girl that I just hooked up with's poop out of the toilet?
it
She's like yelling.
He's holding the egg in front of her and says,
"Poop! You poop!"
And then like...
I grab the egg too.
I also, I grab the egg out of his hand and I go...
You're eating the poop, man?
I'm not helping at all.
Yeah, you...
I'm grabbing it.
I'm just like trying to make the whole situation seem normal.
So I pick up the poop and I'm just like...
(laughing)
- Put the egg in a Pokeball, man.
- Yeah.
- Oh, that's a good idea.
- Oh, I could do that.
- Or an incubator.
- Yeah.
- They have incubators at the Poke place.
- A Pokeball is safer though.
- A Pokeball is basically the incubator, so.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
- So you put the egg in the Pokeball,
and she sort of has an instinct of like,
trying to reach out for it.
- Putting her poop in the Pokeball.
- She's like.
(laughing)
- Filling all my friends Pokeballs with shit
- And then, Moriarty goes to his big gym battle.
(laughing)
- I do that.
- Yeah, and she's just sort of like rattled,
and he goes up to her and he puts his hand on her face
and like, like, touches it and then runs
and then crashes out the window of the bathroom.
(laughing)
- I'm a champ.
- So yeah, you guys might wanna go see what he's up to.
Or you guys can--
- No, he doesn't matter much anymore.
- He did his job, he did his job.
- Yeah. - Okay, yeah.
- And we're on the, what, 30th floor anyway?
He's probably dead.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- That's the sad truth.
- You guys now have this egg.
It is going to hatch in 1,000 steps, I think we calculated.
- Yeah, that's 10 minutes of walking,
according to my Google search. - Let's get our steps in, man.
- Yeah. - Risk walking.
- Yeah, you guys ready to see what happens
when this thing hatches? - Yeah, let's just take
really small steps really fast so that it goes quicker.
- Oh yeah, like ding ding ding ding ding ding.
- Oh my god, let's walk in a circle.
You guys, we will walk in a circle.
- And if we're all walking together,
it's three times the steps.
- People won't think it's weird.
- And wait, most of us have four legs.
- Oh my god, you guys, no no no no no.
We will put on a special presentation for the hospital
and we are all gonna do the game plan.
- We don't want them to see this, oh.
- No, they're gonna kill our baby if they see it.
- Oh no wait, the Machamp jumped out the window.
I was gonna say we could have him,
we could have him come say like,
and here I am with my traveling Pokemon.
- He can't say that, you know he can't say that shit.
- He would say, me duh duh.
- We could say it, I mean we could roll to see
if he says it and then--
- No, we're outside, we're walking in a circle.
- All right, well the can can was a good way
to get all the steps in, but I guess just F me, I guess.
- You can do the can can still, outside.
- I'm gonna do the can-can, okay.
- Away from the prime eyes of the humans
who wanna take away our new genetic anomaly
that we've developed. - Then I do it.
Then I do it.
I'm standing and I'm doing the can-can.
- Why don't you roll performance?
- Make him roll. - Roll Riz.
Make him roll, Patches.
- I roll Riz.
- 11.
- It's like a serviceable,
sometimes you miss a,
you're supposed to put up the knee, but you do the leg.
- It's like I'm doing the can-can on Lip Sync Battle.
Mm-hmm. No, you're gonna have to worry. It's just it's mostly it's like when Tom Holland did the
Umbrella dance and it was just like, you know, he's missing. He's fucking up the choreo, but he's mostly got it
Yeah, I haven't seen that. I hate to say it. Yeah, I mean so what you're saying is it's a bad dancing job is no
No, no, no, no it cuz it impressed service
It impressed
Zendaya somewhere, her heart's aflutter.
- Uh-huh, Zendaya is impressed.
- By this pig.
And you guys hatch.
(laughing)
- Somewhere Zendaya turned to Tom Holland and said,
"I just got impressed by a pig."
(laughing)
- All right, okay, actually I kinda want this to be
a collaborative thing.
What do we think this guy looks like, this baby?
- I think that he looks, he has no belly button,
like KyleXY. - So it's a guy.
- And he, it's definitely a guy,
'cause Machamp is a guy.
Oh wait, but his mom's a girl.
- I guess then it would mix together
and be something halfway.
- Okay, so it's half guy, half girl.
- Yeah. - Okay.
- So it's girl from the-- - Like a Pokemon.
- From the wheels up, the waist up.
- Wheels. - It has wheels.
- It has wheels. - It has wheels.
- It's a handicap kid.
- It's born and it does completely as wheels.
It's a robot.
(laughing)
- It's a woman for the wheel.
- It's like a two completely different species
of Pokemon breed and they make a third
completely different thing.
We've just, it's a car.
(laughing)
It's a car with a human head.
- It's the first ever car type Pokemon.
- Yeah.
- With a human head like an ornament,
like a hood ornament on the top.
- Looks sort of like a--
- It looks like a baby's head because it was just born.
- Yeah.
- It looks sort of like a,
what's the clown from Twisted Metal?
- Yeah, Sweet Tooth.
- Sweet Tooth, it looks like Sweet Tooth.
- It looks like Sweet Tooth's car.
- But a baby.
- Yeah.
- In the head.
And so it's a really tiny car right now,
so it's like a little Hot Wheel.
- It's like one of the, yeah, perfect.
Okay, he's going in the cookie bowl.
- But it's gonna grow fast.
No, come on, what does he actually look like?
Come on, what does he look like?
- That's what he looks like.
It's just a Machamp with boobs.
(laughter)
Boobs?
Patrick, that's a newborn baby.
No, it's a Pokemon.
Yeah, it's a Pokemon.
It doesn't matter what it looks like.
He's not saying he likes the boobs, man.
No, no, I don't like it.
It's just, yeah, I'm talking about genetics.
(laughter)
Yeah, it's got boobs.
I don't like boobs.
It's just sign us.
It's a blue Machamp with long blonde hair and white boobs.
Yeah.
Plain, plain white boobs.
There's nothing wrong with plain white boobs.
Cool. Alright. I think it's either that or a car.
Now the car is sounding pretty good to him, huh?
Now you like the car.
I just think that's the best Pokemon anyone came up with in a long time.
- Car with a head.
- All right, so this is the beginning of your guys' journey
to, I guess, destroy all humans with your sort of like
twisted metal Pokemon creations.
- That's cool. - Okay.
- Yeah, I think this is a good trial run.
I wanted to see what this would play like.
It kind of basically did exactly what I thought,
which was take whatever I had planned
and throw it in directly--
- I bet you didn't think three buttoned up nerds like us
would spend so much time breeding during a session
like this, did you?
And yet here we are.
- I thought you guys were gonna do a lot more math,
so that was really surprising.
- No math, man.
- But next time we do Pokemon though,
maybe we'll do something a little bit more interesting.
- Can we go to Poop Brown Town?
- We can go to Poop Brown Town, for example.
- Okay, I always wanted them to put that in the game.
- That's just somebody's house.
Poop Brown Town. - Yeah, it's your house.
- Mr. Poop Brown Town.
I was on your side and you went and you changed it.
- I'm just telling you what nationality you are.
- I'm not brown.
- You're poop.
- It's not a nationality anyway.
- Give me a nation of brown.
- Nation of brown.
- I thought it was.
- Now we can talk about, okay, bye guys.
- Bye. - Bye.
- Is it unattractive to women when you throw your back out?
- Yes.
Really? Man, if you hurt yourself, that sucks.
If you ever stub your toe, this is what you should do.
You say, "I didn't stub my toe."
Yeah.
"I didn't stub my toe."
Number two.
Wait, can I just ask your fans real quick?
Lady fans, what is more attractive?
When a man peels off his shirt like this and then kind of drops it?
And then, you know, he's shirtless?
Well, you just did that gayly.
Yeah.
Right.
Okay, well, if he did that straightly...
If someone did that straightly...
- When he peels off his shirt?
- Or if you just pop out of it.
(laughing)
- Do you mean rip out of it or do you mean
pop out of it as a different thing?
- Like if you kind of flex.
- Like you go like this, you go like this
and then you're next to all your clothes
falling in a pile next to you.
- Do you get raptured out of your clothes?
- Your nightcrawler bamps out of your clothes?
Oh, like you have clothes that are on you
with suction cups?
Like there's a tear on your e-flexor bicep and then your bicep pops out of that.
I don't think a single person has ever done that.
That necessitates having a very tiny shirt on for anybody.
Right, well that's what I mean.
What is it? More sexy when you peel off a tiny shirt?
If you're a woman, leave a comment down below.
Address it to Pierce. Say "Dear Pierce."
And then write what you think is sexy about a boy taking off his shirt or whatever.
Is it sexy? Because I think it's sexy when a boy pops out.
The question is, so your question is, women, do you think it's sexier when a man takes off his shirt or explodes his clothes?
Do you think it's sexier if a man explodes his clothes or takes his shirt off?
Women, do you like it when a man pops out?
Pops out or takes his clothes out?
Do you like it when a man pops out at you?
Or slides?
Slides or pops?
Do you like it when a man slides on you?