[music]
This land is your land, this land is my land.
I'm a Texas tiger, you're a liberal wiener.
I'm a great crusader, you're a Herman Munster.
This land will surely vote for me.
Okay, we're going. We're going.
Monday, September 5th, 1892.
It's 12.01am in Duluth, Brooklyn, right?
When the work day starts.
But nobody's working today.
You see, yesterday, the 100% illegal Barrel Workers Union staged a citywide strike, specifically
in protest against the more than fair working conditions found in the Solve in the Frog
Enterprise Barrel Suspenders and Clothes Burning Corporation, factory in the Busvich neighborhood
of Duluth, Brooklyn, where Barrel Suspenders and Clothes Burning takes place.
Hasan the Chapo, the dreaded Turk, friend to the common man and seriously clouded, has brought
his foreign ideas about labor laws to the uncorrupted mind of the good Duluthian worker,
organizing them against their benevolent employers.
Scandalous!
And now, he and his army of child laborers and a few awesome older laborers are attempting
storm the factory, take it over by force, and have it be the first worker-run, barrel-suspenders
and clothes-burning factory the world has ever seen.
Okay, this is fucked. This is seriously fucked. We can't stand for this shit, guys. It's fucking
garbage, dude. I'm honestly so sick of this shit. We don't get paid. We don't get time off. It's
fucking weak. And those chuds in there, they're not gonna fucking stop until, like, you know,
You know, like we step in there, and you hear the twitchy chattering of the union outside.
Today we're walking out of here, and like honestly bro, fuck it.
They're a bunch of fucking neoliberal fucking scumbags who think they know what's right,
and know what to do, but they don't.
They're fucking stupid.
Let's take them down.
Let's walk today, bro.
The strike had been building for some time, you see.
Sullivan the Frog, factory manager and frog person which the company is not named after,
has been working to make the Bustvich factory
the best and most profitable one in the company.
In doing so, he's innovated in a number of ways.
Installing feeding troughs throughout
to keep meals brief, efficient, and cost effective.
Is it troughs?
- Troughs. - Troughs.
- Troughs, how do we say that wrong?
- You drop in trough. - You've only read it.
- Yeah, you city boy.
(laughing)
- You never said trough?
- You've never seen a trough?
- I've never said trough.
- I am a city boy.
- Holy shit, the pig's trough.
- He never read Charlotte's Web in class.
- Well, he read it, but he said--
I never read it. He read it in the city class.
Oh yeah. The trow.
They were all using iPads and headphones probably.
That's right. I would read about it and go trow.
Like, because I didn't know how to say it.
Just keep going.
As well as enforcing a BYOD, or bring your own diaper policy.
To ensure there isn't too much overhead, he adjusted pay to $50 an hour
from the previous $20 an hour every employee was paying to work there.
While the results speak for themselves,
With enough barrels and suspenders to clothe the whole city. The workers felt like they got too many owies and boo-boos, and so they went on strike.
Sullivan, panicking, already really not suited for this kind of stuff, asked his assistant,
"Child Worker Superstar Jordy El Nino Polla"
*laughter*
Dude, that gets us.
Giggle Bear.
A+ for GiggleBerry.
To call the Pinky Toe Detective Agency, who sent their finest Pinky Toe agents to help.
However, not wanting to let this just be led by Sullivan, you three decided to step in
to assist.
Oh, Pinky Toe.
Like Pinkerton.
I get it.
And who are you?
Like Pinkerton?
I thought we were businessmen.
You are your businessmen.
Weeza.
So tell me, where's a Weeza this game?
what you know we kind of look we're kind of like Weezer ways
Weezer, Weezer, Pinkerton, Pinkerton, I'm a do the things and I wanna do pork and beans,
Weezer, Blue, the blue album, blue album, continue, so you guys, who are you guys, Weezer, Weezer,
Weezer, Weezer, Weezer, Weezer, Weezer, Weezer, Weezer, Weezer, Weezer, Weezer, Weezer, Weezer,
We can't.
So yeah, you guys are...
Good way!
I can totally be Weezer!
We might be Weezer!
Yeah baby, yeah we're Weezer!
I'm Weezer baby!
Yeah baby!
No.
Do Asian girls make me horny baby?
Yes!
I'm Weezer!
You are 18 year old girl!
You guys are the executives who run the barrel suspenders and clothes burning factory.
Yes.
You can be Weezer or you can tell me who you are.
I wrote a whole intro.
You can also be the guy you came here with.
I would say it's 49% of me is like I have to be Weezer, but 51% is like I already am.
I could be pushed over the edge.
We could turn into Weezer.
Weezer!
With these one-offs.
Here's what I'll say.
You never know.
Just start with your characters.
If you end up being Weezer.
Is it transforming into Weezer?
Let's see where it goes.
Weezer!
Hey!
Hey, what are you doing here? Can't you see I'm busy?
No, you didn't tell me to introduce yourself.
You wanna know about me?
Fuck you! I grew up rich!
I plan on staying rich.
Money is the only thing I know about.
In school, I never went to school. I paid poor people to go to school for me.
That's how rich I am.
Ultimately, I have the education of a second grader,
but I have the cash and cars of a man who is almost four times the age of a second grader. Got it?
No, you don't. I don't even get it. Do you have any gum? I made gum. No, I didn't.
I paid poor people to make gum for me. I just thought of the idea for gum.
There's a new style of gum.
It's called quadruple bubble.
Unfortunately, everyone in the factory died of a shark attack. Didn't see that coming, did ya?
No one sees me coming. Not even my own wife, our first kid.
I paid a poor person to bust his gunk in her slit
I have no immediate heirs
None that none that are related to me. You know why I'm gonna live forever who cares. I don't care look at me
I weigh 400 pounds. I'm 5 foot 2 and I'll dance with you got it. Look at this
Look at what I can do with my arm. What's his name?
Look what I can do with my arm
You want to see it? Give me a dollar
See I'm smart I have business savvy. I'm addicted to drowning people
small people
Richer people for my first wife. She was fat five foot nine 120 pounds. I couldn't stand to look at her
I've been married 100 times all drowned who cares the police. I'm the police I think I don't remember
Was I supposed to tell you that I drowned those women?
It doesn't matter. I'll pay for your silence
Look at you! Look at us! All my buddies rich as fuck! Watch this! Didn't see it too bad,
it'll cost you to see it again! See? I'm smart! That's why they pay me the big bucks! My name's
Johnny Knoxville and welcome to Jackass! What does that mean? I have no idea, who cares?
I'm Dan and Fudd, creator of the Ridge Wallet.
That's good.
This guy's on hinge.
So Dan and Fudd, yeah.
Dan is fully just unprompted, just starts introducing himself.
Yeah, you're sitting in the executive office that is carved out of all these factories.
I thought you told us to start doing intros.
No, I did.
I wasn't sure if I was going to know who exactly you were, but you're with them in the executive
office where Sullivan is there and he's beside himself and standing nearby is Jordy, who
is just the best child worker ever and has been like a loyal to Sullivan this whole
time. And who else is here too? Who are the other two executives who run this
company? Say! The name's Robert Downey Jr. and I didn't prepare anything for this
meeting here but I'm very excited to meet all of you. It's a great pleasure.
You see, I clawed my way to the top of this company. It was a hard
hard task you see I used to be completely addicted to something
whatever they do at this time time period sure a lot of them
diluted dirt opium opium I love opium still never got off that
stuff, but I got some right here. Thank you. You're welcome.
And then you hear like I'm hitting an opium bong. It's like
Yeah, exactly. But my main thing is I have a power suit. It's a, I call it that
because it's a suit that gives me powers, like the power to have a heavy
footstep, a very loud clanging footstep or a very slow but hard punch. And it's
it's powered by the some of the the greatest technologies that our time
period has to offer like steam and clocks, child labor, and it looks cool. It
does it, it burns me completely when I turn it on. It's filled with steam and I've been trying to make it fly.
So Robert Downey jr. but also classes. A bunch of pipes, a little hot steam on your body.
Dan and Fudd is a monk by the way, level 5, way of the drunken fist. I've never
had a sip of alcohol in my life. I'm 16 years old you see.
A child executive. And then Robert Downey Jr. obviously is an artificer, an artillerist.
obviously obviously and then we have one more
Hello! My name is Tuck and I'm a really really good business owner. I've owned tons and tons
of businesses that sell really really good stuff. During the Civil War I fought for the
Confederacy! But I was discharged for being too loud. Then I started my fourth business,
The West want we sold sandwiches. I opened more West once then I sold the West one and
now here I am one of the wittiest moguls in the country. I was born in America and I'll
die in America because I really really like it here.
cool tuck is a barbarian path of the beat you don't say yeah so you guys are in
right now in the executive office with Sullivan and Jordi who are there trying
to explain you guys a situation you know but the strike happened there's all these
issues and so we don't spend much time at the factory we're here to solve yeah
you're here to solve this problem okay basically like like you guys so we're
not familiar with this office. Yeah, you guys run a bunch of different factories. At every
factory there's an executive office that you guys are allowed into and so you guys just
are up here right now as outside the pinky toe agency men are lining up and the people
who are in the union workers are lining up as well. So this is the only time that we're
ever in this building is to go into our office. Not even, it's like you have a headquarters.
This is like a factory among your...
We don't have an office in here?
Yeah, you're in your office.
But you wouldn't go in.
It's like you wouldn't go into the office of a factory unless you were overseeing it that week or something.
But otherwise you would be at the corporate headquarters.
I'm going to investigate the office.
Yeah, you can definitely do that.
Roll investigation check.
What is that?
That is a 19.
That's good.
Plus my investigation, which is a zero, so that is a 19.
I mean, that's good.
Yeah, I mean, so, you know, it looks similar to your other corporate executive offices that
you've seen.
I'm looking for like a Matt Lauer button.
Yeah.
There isn't a Matt Lauer button here, but you do, so one of the things I can tell you
about is that there is a door to like this like...
Is there a painting on the wall?
Yes.
will take a hundred
you take a look at the off there is nothing behind the painting i will
there'd be a something not even a wall was a wall by
yeah i think i was almost out of the area not i will tell you that i will say
that with your best addition you actually do hear some rumbling from the
toilet
for a
the by
you got your keep that down if you're gonna do that in their my bad
i know what you're doing in their two and i can see it too and it's not good
Okay, I would like to now open the door.
I was in the bathroom.
I'm gonna open the door of the bathroom.
- Okay, yeah.
- The three of you are wumbling in there.
- Yeah, and I know what you're doing.
- Okay, go duck it out.
- I haven't used the toilet.
- You used it?
- No, I never used the executive toilet.
- Okay, hold on.
- Company policy.
- We're all gonna get to the bottom of this toilet.
- Say, you've never used a toilet before?
- One jaw.
- I grab Sullivan 'cause he's green.
I think he's a plunger.
And he looks like kind of plastic, rubbery.
And I start dunking him in and out of the toilet.
Wait, I think I can be of assistance with this. I have a piston on my arm.
Yeah.
(imitating piston)
Let me staple him, I mean the plunger, to your arm.
Oh, hold on. Let me flush it for a second.
Yeah.
I pull down like the, the cord or whatever.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, you pull down the cord breaks.
Yeah.
(laughing)
I don't know how that works.
So you use the piston.
Well, my piston is supposed to be going really fast like that, but it's, it's,
it's a really shitty power suit. So it's, uh, it's, um, it's really slow.
it's like a hydraulic press is just slowly pushing the toilet.
He's like yeah it's like he's just yeah it's like a Bond villain dropping
somebody in the law. It's exactly like a hydraulic press like a YouTube video of
green slime. And as you're pulling Sullivan out. Oh I didn't pull him out
yet. Okay it's just in there. Yeah the piston's stuck there's nothing you can do.
Yeah while Sullivan's stuck in there, Jordy comes up to you guys he says you know Sullivan's
not really good at running this place I have to say like I think I could
probably run this way better than all right you're in charge who the fuck is
Sullivan I thought you were Sullivan no I'm Jordi he's Jordi oh well where's
from Spain so I can do this voice you found it up perfect Spanish accent
thank you yeah you sound like a complete Spaniard thank you so where is
Sullivan you just dunked him in the toilet which is pretty funny
he's a plunger!
Sullivan starts to get pulled out he says there's there's a there's a there's
somebody down there there's what the hell is that supposed to mean?
wait just a minute there's someone in the toilet! there's somebody in the toilet it
was you you were in the toilet!
reflection god you are stupid!
no there's somebody besides me!
well he was in there he was in there masturbating
my common nuts in there oh my god oh my god you masturbated into the toilet and
created a baby out of the toilet didn't you I think I need to see my son we need
to find his son we need to find his baby oh pipe man do it put a pipe in there
okay let me I'll free your son from this toilet and I my fist goes and turns into
a big fist and I smash the toilet yeah okay I just completely smash this
smashed the toilet and you see dead on the ground one of the workers a spy.
Wait just a minute! Your son looks exactly like a spy! My beautiful son!
They grow up so fast. Your son was born with spy attire on!
Okay can you let me off this piston or unstable me? Well he pissed in the
toilet and I come in the toilet -
Jordy can you can you pull down the projector please so we can explain the
factory layout before they destroyed more than one devolves of Viking funeral
yeah we're gonna set the toilet on fire okay you guys want to do that you have
you have thrower one of you as you have I think I do have a flamethrower when I
I do the flamethrower to it just it fills the entire inside of the suit with fire.
So my entire body is completely but I'm going to say you don't take damage from
I'm going to say I take damage you do because it's the very beginning so I'll
have time to go to the hospital or whatever.
Yeah, sure.
Let's roll.
I'd like to burn my entire body.
Burn your body.
It's like the 20s.
All you just have to take for fire.
Yeah,
exactly that we all have for been in our inventory or some kind of like you
have you have a to each of you have to
greater potions of healing. Which is just bourbon. You can call it bourbon though, that's fine with me.
Yeah, so you guys can use that. I've already drank both of them. Yeah, this is not useful.
You are disgusting. I'm an alcoholic. But we haven't invented alcoholism yet, so I just have a
I just have a funny tinge to me. You burn up the worker, he's just ashes right? He's just ashes now.
uh... and uh... jordy pulls on a projector as he does the floor rotates in a mini
orchestra kinda comes up
as well as well as a man uh... play the entertainer wearing a tuxedo
uh...
and he begins to speak excuse me
he says uh... play the entertainer
they start playing i wanna hear that scott joplin tune they start playing upbeat uh... music
upbeat sort of orchestral music it's broadly free we can play the entertainer
and uh... and it's one of the first motion pictures uh... and so you hear the
the man in the tuxedo starts reading off of cue cards.
Sullivan the Frog--
- Holy crap, where'd this man come from?
- Enterprises is proud to present
the first major corporate motion picture
to you, the humble worker.
Scum, so you've been hired to work
at Sullivan the Frog Enterprises
in one of our state of the art factories.
You're gonna need to know the ins and outs
of those factories if you want to succeed here.
So let's go over some important information
around its layout.
And so then you see this map
that I drew for you guys over here.
- Oh my. - Wow, it's beautiful.
- I try to climb into the screen.
- Yeah, the train is coming and you're like,
I want to get on board.
(laughing)
The factory is split into two main sections,
and then there's smaller locales around it.
Okay, you see all that?
The main sections are the barrel section
and the suspender section.
Here's the barrel section, all right?
Here's the suspender section.
The barrels are assembled in the barrel section
by the workers and the machines aligning the bottom,
middle, and top parts of the barrel.
So the bottom gets loaded in here from the docking bay,
and then it goes around once,
and it gets the top part, goes around again,
gets the bottom part of the barrel and then it's dis- and then uh or rather
sorry the barrels are like brought in here the bottom parts goes around here
and it gets the middle part on it and then it comes around here and gets the
top part on it and then that completed barrel ends up in here. Okay. And then
it's carted out through here into the suspender section. Um, where the barrels
are funneled into the suspenders machine which is over here where hot glue is
applied, suspenders holders, and then the actual suspenders themselves and then
they are brought over here this is where the workers apply the suspenders and
then they're brought over here into the rather than this is the where things are
loaded the loading area this is the dispatch area so it's loaded onto one of
these 16 wheeler trucks that are pulled by oh so that's where we dispatch the
workers that's where we all sing the song the general by dispatch what the hell is
a twerk I think you're gonna say your name there's 16 as a worker you may be
assigned to to the clothes burning facility on the west end of the factory
free. This is over here. This is a closed burning facility.
How many employees real quick do we have? Sure, you have 200 at this factory.
Okay. They're all striking right now.
199 now. My son's dead. Yeah.
Yeah. True. Can we keep a running tally?
Yeah. I have a number. I am keeping track of numbers
of employees. Okay, nice. Awesome.
With a 10% survival rate, this is only for our most disposable workers. You funnel clothes.
What the hell is a workaholic? They couldn't edit that out of the video?
- Pause the video! - Pause the presentation!
He pauses the video, the guy's...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry folks, I misread the cue card.
I'm sorry.
They're capin' the bloopers in the movies now!
What the hell is going on?
Wait a minute, what's a movie?
I was confused by this earlier!
"Jordy, please press play!"
And Jordy presses play on the film.
Uh, the factory has, uh...
And so you will funnel clothes
gathered from none of your business
and burn them into one of the four industrial furnaces over here.
over here. This powers the factory and also keeps warm the floor manager and the
assistant's office. So that's where their offices are. So it's right behind us?
It's right over here. So you guys are in the executive area over here. This is the floor
manager's office and this is Jordi's office. Okay. Over here is, by the way, so
when it's loaded into here, the stuff, this is where the barrels are put and
this is where the suspenders are put. These are the storage areas. And these are
horse-drawn? These are horse-drawn trucks. 16-wheel trucks. Horse-drawn
16-wheeler trucks. The factory has three main entrances. This is probably the more
important part. So the front entrance, which opens into a lobby area for when
visitors come to the factory. You, as a worker, are never to use this. This is the
lobby area where you usually have a receptionist. Then you have the... where
am I going? Yeah, then we have the back entrance, which is the unloading area for
raw barrel and suspended materials, which is over here. So you have entrances that
go in here these are like the loading docks but you have entrances where you
walk in here and then you it moves into the rest of the factory then you have do
you have a third you have two other major entrance you have one other major
entrance which is the this is the unloading dock right so this is where
you store him and it sends it out off off to the fucking stores or whatever
and then you have an entrance into the burning facility as well to the closed
burning facility but it's only from the outside and it doesn't move into the
factory. Okay. So you can't like go from here out in there. And then there's one
other entrance, the worker entrance, which they take the outdoor toilets where they
go in them like Mario and they come out on the other side in the suspenders part
of the factory over here. So there's three outdoor toilets here. Mm-hmm. So
workers can use this to end up in here and they pop up a pop up here. And they
go through the toilet. Yes, through the toilet. Like Fortnite. So they're not
allowed to enter the barrels part until they have scrubbed themselves clean
because visitors enter through the barrels part of the factory. So best to get here early if you're
on barrel duty that day. Finally, there are stairs on the northeast end, this is where you guys are,
the facility. This office should be occupied by no one except when one of the three Sullivan
the Frog executives have arrived. Trespassers will be thrown into the furnace.
We have to throw all these people besides us who are in here into the furnace, right?
Yeah. Well, they're not. We gave them permission.
Yeah, you gave them permission. I didn't give them permission.
So we have to put Sullivan in the furnace. I guess you could kill them.
There is a platform you can walk on that wraps around the entire main two subsections of the
is a factory. So this is a platform where you can observe. Oh my God, I cannot wait to walk
around that with my hands behind my back. A platform! I walk out and I want to see what
it's like out there. Yeah, so you can see the full factory. I mean, nothing is working
right now. You know, there's no workers here. So you can hear the noises of industry because
clothes are still being burned, and the conveyor belts are going, but there's no barrels loaded
on them. There's no suspenders loaded. So there's no workers in here? Yeah, they're
all outside right now, about to storm. Oh, okay. The facility is trying to take it over.
I thought that they were in the factory. Bruh!
Say, bruh! Bruh!
Wha! Bruh!
And so this allows you to walk around the entire factory area, but you can't, it doesn't
allow you to walk in here. There are windows along here though, so you can see what's going
on outside from here too. And you can see what's going on in these other parts of
the factory. But you can't see like outside from like these two
walls because that's where that is. And then yeah, thank you for watching. You're
sure to not be a complete loser as a worker I'm sure. Solve in the Frog
Enterprises. There's the door. The movie was wrong. There's nobody in here. This
This place is as empty as a muh.
- A what? - A muh.
- You know, like a muh.
- Like damn, that was cool as a muh.
(laughing)
Like that.
It means like, where would you--
- Say, I think he's trying to say muh-fuh.
- Like muh, like damn.
- Oh, muh-fuh.
- That was cool as a muh. - A muh-fuh.
- That's the issue.
- Now it's just muh.
- It's just muh.
- Yeah.
- None of the words-- - Say, bruh.
- There is we.
- I hired the pinky toe agents,
but I'm hoping that you guys can help too.
- So, here's what you guys--
we were the pinky toe agent no you guys should run the company oh so you have
three you have two moves you can do mm-hmm I have four moves I can do watch
this this is called the Charleston actually but you can do I invented this
Start so I'm one of the greatest that is a cutting-edge dance
Never seen anything like it. It's gonna take the world by storm after all this check out this one. I invented it's called the renegade
Wow that's amazing PT's are when they invent small cameras
That's gonna look incredible pinky toe agents and W's are the workers, okay?
So these are you the forces okay there these guys are outside the map
But they're there on the two ways some of those who work forces are the same who burn bosses
Well, I just well because because I'm not gonna draw and redraw everything. There's gonna just be general movement of the mob
Okay, I wish I had more markers. I could have done this with but anyway, so
But yeah, I am lazy. I guess we need to get like a hologram thing like an endless game
Do you think you could do a Star Wars holodeck? I would love to yeah, I think I can make that or
Well, there's like ways you can get a D&D table that like has like a screen on it, but it's pretty expensive
Whoa?
TV basically and then plugging it in and yeah, I can't wait to put all my drinks and foods on it to my TV
Yeah, well, no you put like it does not not on mine. This is not people want to hear this
so
You have the three things you can do you have two moves you can do before the scene. I just like pretty imminent can I?
Can I propose a chant that the workers are saying?
Oh, well, I said it or I said a couple seconds ago and everyone was talking and no one heard it
And I thought it was pretty good
What was it some of those who some of those who work forces are the same that burn bosses?
Okay, that's good. So I'll add that good the other chant. They have they have a couple moves
I can do all right one of the chance they can do is they do that this other saying that outside
They do that this land is your land, but the jib jab one. Okay, George W Bush and John Kerry
I have all the lyrics for in case I need to use that.
Yeah, I remember that one.
Yeah, I do too. But so, you can either, you have three moves.
Are they doing okay, boomer?
Troops, they're doing that a lot. Traps and Trentel, just Intel, but I just like the TR
thing and I couldn't think of anything that was similar. So with troops...
Trespassing.
No, because, well, I guess if you're trespassing on your own property, I wouldn't say that.
Oh, wait.
gathering Intel so you either you either you know buff your troops so you give
them buffs on rolls because the way it's gonna work is each round they're gonna
like clash and then you can give them like a buff on the rolls that they do
you could set traps so that traps you can set at any part in the factory or outside
the factory before the siege and like just have that ready for the different
entrances if an Intel is you can pick one of the locations on the map and roll
investigation and each you can roll and then I'll tell you information that you
gather from that we can roleplay that out as well yeah what about troops traps try
to get Intel try to get Intel yeah let's do that's better that is way better yeah
try to get into try to get it teaching no it needs to be true tree try to get
reaching until yeah preaching try to get Intel fan ways ang ways a Rick no so yeah
We that those are three you can choose from and you have to you can do now traps you guys have stuff in your like
For your character like you is particularly have something. That's a very obvious trap is in
But I also have a list of home alone traps that you guys can set if you want to do as well
So you can either come up with a trap on your own or I can give you trap ideas or if you just want to like
Add the buff to your the troops
So cuz what's gonna happen is wanna indiscriminately slaughter all these workers
So you do that to each of these guys want to completely just destroy every single one of them basically be doing a d20
contest against each other and
After three wins on one side or the other side
Then that group is defeated so if crap so
Like you guys can add a buff to these guys or you can also go there and fight with them
With the pinky toes with the pinky toes and like you know try to help like wipe out one of the do we get a gun?
wipeout yeah wipeout oh my god we can set up a wipeout course you imagine if you
for the for the workers wipeout course and that's how we get that's the job
that's how we get them gone so smart and then also I will say though so like you
know you can plan for all these moves but like I have I have traps that the
workers have set up of their own for when we go outside and there for and the
the whole factory has not i know that it is a little so like you just have to be
ready for
anything but if you if you
preventing these guys from getting in will make whatever you have to deal
with in the factory easier i'm going to have a question about what are my
characters abilities yet so i can create a a canon early to return to think
do i have to do i have to man it there is a like automatic is like magical
automatic okay it doesn't say uh... doesn't say i don't agree i i i have not
really are can i haven't done like artificer
ever just goes it was a great if too
so like a roots but i think the i think the artist is a good for a mad at me see
uh... which keeps so i mean but i like to have to look at the engineer
is in a way when i say all valor
killed roger to kill the time to accuse johnson i didn't know that there was a
guy and and and and risk it's dwarfs
it is a dwarf can't adore or there's no dwarves in this incident is america
dwarf
it's not a we're not in middle earth or or is not it says it's a deal nor
moons
regard uh...
the land of isaac i actually cause the can to activate if you're within sixty
feet of it so they said it's a truth in sixty feet okay
because i think we could do a whole wipeout course and i could just put a
flamethrower at the end of it for a new and get you know you know you and
yes
yeah so what you can i could be like you sure are your hot stuff
that's right so yeah
we're not the spring of mistletoe
Oh, I know why.
Trying to kiss.
Jordy's right there.
He's got his lips puckered.
Oh, I'm not trying to kiss another man.
And he's a child.
What are you talking about?
He's also a boy.
You're telling me I have to kiss a boy?
So you have, if you guys want to do like a wipeout course.
That's my immediate idea.
I feel like that's a pretty good idea.
I think that's a really good idea.
Can we continue to be entertained?
And so that's the question.
And we can watch it from up on the catwalk.
I either put... here's what I'll say.
Yeah!
If you're gonna put a wipeout course...
Sounds bussin'!
You have to pick...
I like the sound of that.
What is that?
Bussin'?
It's a new word I came up with.
It's in my lexicon!
Completely in my lexicon!
You can choose one of the areas to put it in.
Now, if you put it outside, you know, then that...
Can we do, for a wipeout course, can we just do one obstacle in each room and have it be
one long course?
I would say that that will use both your moves if you do that.
I kind of just want to do it in one of these main factory areas because, you know, you
drive by when you're a kid, you drive by like treatment plants and like factories and stuff
and you're like, "God, I would love for there to be a water slide or some kind of
giant pooch."
I will also say that will be effective because like these two rooms especially are like massive
and like will probably, like they are going to go into either this room or like they're
they're going to end up in this room at some point because they're going to
storm the executive yeah okay I will say it the trap here that is like a like a
good way to start deterring them as they can we do can we do a wipeout course in
one room and then an evil haunted amusement park in the other one haunted
house that's a really good idea I think haunted house is more likely to be a
little like a roller coaster and they think it's really get in and they're
and then we're gonna be all our workers are out and then it scares them you want
to do a scary dark ride. Yeah, a ghost jumps out. I would say you could do something where
it's like, if you want to fool off, it's like a wisdom saving throw. People will still die
of fright. I want to do the white belt first, but I also want to be in a sniper nest. And
I want to be picking them off if they win. You can position yourself for, I think, you
don't have like a ranged weapon though. No, I have a sprig of mistletoe. You could throw
a missile. He has a ranged weapon. I have a lot of ranged weapons. Because he's the Iron
man I have three javelins you have three javelins I do have water skin I'm sorry
you do have three javelins as true I've been doing this for like and a skim tar
you have to talk into the mic patches um you say what tarred a skim tarred
scimitar scimitar skim tarred are you seriously calling it that so you can
also perch yourself like if you want to Pat I mean I knew the language of the
1890s was coarse and and rather uninclusive but seriously Pat you can
also like use your turns in this siege to like walk along the the you know yeah
find a gun well I don't know what I was trying to do in the office when I was
investigating trying to find a gun yeah yeah I feel like the exact trying to
find a sniper or something it have like I hit your elbow on this part of the
wall can I make can I make a cannon you can make a cannon you can use you'll be
able to control it if I give it to him I think you can make a range cannon I
think it just has to be I think he just has to just makes me the
the
an arcane firearm or I don't know what any of this means should you should make me
about it doesn't matter we'd also don't play by that or the or the Spartan laser
I will say that you can make him a can and would be cool
on laser okay blicky here's here the up here your options a flamethrower
mmm a force ballista which I think is what you want
that's a great go and then a protector
yeah probably want the middle one yeah you're going for a course ballista
yeah that shoots bolts of force okay well it was a bear fifty cal
Yeah, that's fine.
Okay, cool.
So you got a four, yeah, he makes you a Barrett .50 cal with his Tony Stark genius.
From Modern Warfare 2.
Who the hell is Tony Stark?
The name's Robert Downey Jr.
And he wants to attack with it.
And I'm Iron Man.
And I'm Dan and Fudd.
When he wants to attack with it, can you just...
And I just learned how to spell that.
Yeah, you do the roll for it.
Okay, cool.
And then, yeah, what individual actions do you guys...
I'm also 400 pounds and 5'2".
So the gun is, looks very small on me.
When you say, when you say whatever individual action, you've decided on the obstacle course
now?
I mean if you guys want to, I was just saying like just to, because we're in that, but if
you guys are down for the obstacle course and then either get intel, buff the troops,
or do one other thing, and then each of you can do an individual action.
I would like to do obstacle course I feel like, right?
Yeah I think we should do the obstacle course, and if we also have an individual action.
I'm 6'5" about 420 pounds and I would like to maybe do some intel gathering, see if I
can sneak through it.
Okay, cool.
So what you can do is you can pick.
You didn't need to say your height.
You can pick any of these, you can pick one of these rooms.
8'100".
You can pick any one of these rooms or regions.
So these are the four regions and then you can pick any one of these rooms.
You already like.
I'm east coast baby.
Yeah, you want to go to the east region like here?
Yeah, so the the East loading bay. Yes. Okay, cool. We'll we'll do that in a second Pat
What do you want to do and that's that's the Intel gathering I'm also you also can do an individual action after I'm gonna investigate the
lobby
Okay, you guys okay. All right, so that's
No, because that's like your Intel gathering. So he's doing that the wake what's an individual thing you want you to prepare?
So you can prepare like you can like put yourself on the like ledge and ready to snipe out. Yeah, I can do that
I just set up a gun yeah, you know that cool. Which which which where does the obstacle course end?
The obstacle course will end like right by the like entrance to the executive office
Okay, pick up this the whole suspenders, so I'm gonna what this is walkway right here is a walk
It's a walkway
But it only looks out into the suspenders part of the factory like the walk so this side on this side until the stairway
Where the executive office is right? Yeah, you can like perch yourself here. Yeah
I'm perching my gun towards the end so that they think that they are probably going to
go up there and that I'm just picking them off.
Got it, cool.
So you'll perch your cannon over here.
Yeah.
Okay, cool.
I'll put PC because that's Pat Cannon.
And then you, you want to investigate.
I want to investigate.
I want to see.
My guess is that there's some kind of.
And Danon Cannon.
Can we just take a moment to thank God that we're in 1890 and there's no SJWs at this
time of the century.
Oh, thank God.
Thank God.
like to thank God for that so let's go let's go straight to the east there are
SJWs in the 1800s. Will you let me sneak? Are you just slave jerkin workers?
That did nothing that was nothing so I'm gonna go here and I'm gonna check out this
slave Joe I'm gonna check out this he's ruining can you stop tell me yeah stop
I'm gonna check out this truck. That work? You should do that more often.
to
16-wheeler trucks. And I'm trying to think, I'm going to need a disguise. I'll be a bag
of laundry. And you're a bag of laundry. And I'm sliding like a worm. Yeah, it's Phantom
Chain. You're just sliding around. And you, yeah, you could see. Actually, I move more
like prop hunt. I just completely float around. You could see on the other side of the truck,
like the pinky toe forces sort of sizing up and some of the workers like getting rallied
up and you can hear inside the truck some shuffling.
What do you say sizing up? Are they like spinning their fists?
Yeah, they're all winding up. They're all getting ready. And you can hear some rustling
around in this truck. And when you peek inside, if you want to peek inside, I'd say roll stealth.
I'm rolling stealth.
Yeah.
You just peeked my, you peeked my fucking interest, I'll tell you that much.
I did.
stealth role was a complete 10 okay it's not that stealthy um but maybe it could
be it could you if I want me to win
okay cool um so yeah no no it's a good it's a good that you look in they are
they are all facing the wall but it is workers who is workers their workers are
hiding in there and they're all standing up and just they got a one on
perceptions of the wall of the truck and you are like a bag of flour just poking
your head or a bag of laundry and they're in there you hear one of them
say oh boy I hope they don't I hope they don't look in the other trucks - that's
good in Trento that's good Trento I'm going to really
That is some fire fucking trinto.
Speaking of fire, can I really quickly,
'cause I have a torch in my inventory,
can I light it, just throw it under this truck?
I've been looking at the other trucks too,
they like know you looked.
Sorry, just realizing how stupid what I said was.
Yeah, you can do that.
(laughing)
Sorry.
I hope they don't look at the other ones too,
they know you're looking.
There's nothing they can do about it.
(laughing)
Yeah, they're looking the other way.
So yeah, what do you wanna do?
Sorry.
I wanna light my torch, I have a torch in my inventory.
Yes, you do.
And I'd like to just kind of like,
like toss it under the truck and let me see and I also have rope. I'd like to really quickly
tie a knot on the door of the truck so that they're all trapped in there.
Yeah.
You basically like to boil these minimum wage workers alive.
Yeah, you can absolutely do that.
All right, I'm going to do that.
Yeah, cool. Okay. Yeah, you do that. You tie it up. You close it.
Let me remove my torch.
Yeah, and it is...
Oh, I have ten of them.
You don't hear anything yet, but they're about to get my inventory.
And that's, okay, so that's cool.
So that's...
Do I have enough time to prop hunt back into the executive office?
Yes, you do.
That's like your move.
I'll say that's your like individual move and your like intel.
So all right, let me...
Wait, where'd my pencil go?
You've dropped it.
I dropped me pencil.
It's right on the ground right there.
He dropped his pencil.
He dropped it.
That's cool.
So you guys took out that truck.
So that'll be good for you. Okay, cool. You have the obstacle course set up. You used Intel
and used your turn to take out some of the truck, one of the trucks. And now...
What are those circles you drew?
Those are just like obstacle course things. I remember that's what's...
Okay.
Wait, we don't get to see these people die? They're done?
Well, no. I haven't even got to take my turn yet.
Yeah, yeah. Don't worry.
ahead. I want to be just on the floor in the thick of it wherever I think wherever
it seems like they're about to start rushing I want to be waiting through
them and just machine gunning their heads off. I have a punch card that I've
punched out that's about the like holes in it like you know when you write a
word on your Scantron test yeah it says kill and I put it in my mouth and I chew it up
and I swallow it. So you guys don't want to but you so you guys are not
stationing outside. You know I'll station in the lobby maybe.
Yeah, okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, yeah, French
totally French cheese
We's a patches we sell
We say
We say F and F is for patches. Okay
Let's do this then
Let me make sure I have all my notes ready. So I know everything that's going on
Mm-hmm. Oh my god, Peter Griffin showed up to the factory
Whoa
Okay, you want talk to Sullivan weather in Peter Griffin?
It's an honor. I'm here. I'm here to shake hands with all of you because I think you're all perfect employees are perfect
Oh, well perfect business owners. Why thank you. I'll shake your hand. I have what the hell was that?
Sullivan comes up to you guys and he says is there anything you want me to do?
before there. I've got an idea how about you go down to the malt shop get us all
root beer floats. I before I grab him and I load him into an arm cannon. I just learned what that is.
He's in my he's in my arm cannon. He's shaped like a cylinder now. Yeah I'm just and I'm just
gonna wait. He's gonna be in there until it's time for me to use him. He said bruh.
Sullivan said bruh. This green frog's bussing bussing. Green frog said bruh. I don't think
I don't think I'll ever I'm never gonna say bruh the Sullivan voice. Hey Sullivan, I have a question for you
Can you smell my two fingers real quick?
They're bad, it's really bad. God it's not just me. I thought that I was losing my mind
And you see Geordi
Geordi goes I'm going to go to my office. Let me know if you need anything and you see he kind of walks down the stairs
Oh my god, he's bringing a MILF with him and heads over to it
He is bringing a milf with him. Holy crap. So Jordy and his milf are in here for now.
And okay. Holy crap she's an Amazon she's gonna pick him up. Yeah yeah so then you
hear from way back you hear Hasan go uh. I thought his name was Chapo. Hasan the
chapeau. Oh, Hassan the chapeau. Yeah. And he goes, "Charge!" Oh dear. And yeah, it begins.
The siege begins. This Turkish man in a sequined suit is running towards us. So everybody roll
initiative. Everybody roll initiative and we're going to follow this initiative order
for actions going forward. Okay. Do I get initiative bonus? Do I get a reroll if I don't like my
I got a 14. My initiative. I have an 18 initiative. Nice. I got five. Okay, so hold on a second.
Me. Me. He got four. I don't know what happened, but out of nowhere he just said 14. 14. 18.
I got a five. Charlie Brown reference. Yep. I got a five. I got a five. I got a 14. I got an 18.
I got a five. I got a five. I got a five. I got a five. I got a five. I got a five. I got a five.
You know what I would say? I'd say Charlie Brown. Rocks can actually be worth quite a
quite a lot if you if you get the right kind of rock and you sell it to a place such as a
of the Smithsonian. So maybe you could or you could flip that rock. Yep. You could.
Yeah. How about this? With enough pressure? Try carving it into a figurine. Yeah.
Do something beautiful with it. With enough pressure you could turn that rock into a diamond. Or artistic. Okay.
So let's go. I'm gonna start doing rolls to see what's gonna happen here. And I'm
doing the jelly roll. This is for the north end. It's a straight d20 contest right now
with no bonuses. South end I mean. And then we're gonna go west, north, east. So
So this is for the workers.
I didn't even roll.
19.
You dropped that.
You reroll that right now.
Don't roll that.
Don't roll it on paper.
That's bullshit.
Roll it on the...
You're a fucker.
Alright, so that's one win for the workers.
They got a win.
And one loss for them.
We'll go over here.
Oh my lord.
I take my shirt off.
Okay, 13 for the workers.
And oh man, shit.
The pinky toe.
I take my shirt off and a mouse falls out from unpointed.
I bet this fucking antifa piece of shit made the workers super mad.
supercharged I did not instead of our guys yeah because of his antifo
wait a second right and I knew that this shit would be happening cuz he you can't
see it but patches dyed his hair blue yeah blue hair and he made talking about
chop-chop oh I remember the chop-o-taco why does he know who these people are
the pinkie toes won this one this fight over here what the fuck he's that's
complete so she literally made my own in that socialists used to make people with
glasses get killed yeah he made my my my Iron Man suit bad he made it burn me I
do you know is your job he's an undercover fucking and he's making my
character bad he doesn't realize he made me roll for you can we get try to
initiative from complete fascism yeah okay so that's the first round now you
guys are up you can do things so you can see here in the south end south west and
and north. The workers are actually fighting back pretty good against the Pinky Toes right
now. On the east side where you burned this, they are winning right now. But is there anything
you guys want to do?
Oh, the Pinkertons are winning.
Yeah, the Pinky Toes are winning over here. Is there anything you guys want to do? Change
your positions? Move somewhere? Or do you guys want to stay as is right now?
I look upon the Pinkertons.
You can definitely see the losing here and the winning here.
I see the ones that are losing and I say, "Hey, everybody!
Look at this!"
As a morale boost and I do the Charleston.
Okay, I'm going to roll.
Do I roll performance?
Yeah, roll performance.
And do a real life performance.
I have to go pee real quick.
Go.
Go now.
That's a 15. Okay, 15. Yeah. And I need you to do a real performance of the Charleston too
to prove that you deserve that 15. Let's see it.
It's not even the Charleston, but that was pretty good.
Was that the-- that wasn't the Charleston?
You have to-- I don't want to do it, but it's--
Dude, I do want to do it.
Right now.
You can't correct somebody on the Charleston.
It's this.
Whoa, okay. He knows how to do the job.
All right, this whole, this whole, it's a city, it's a city, it was a sting operation.
We're done. Yeah, I've been, I've, that would honestly, yeah, that's fine. If that ended my
life. Um, so you got a plus, so I'll say that with that 15, that adds a plus one to their next role.
Nice. Um, so that's useful. Um, anything we do with a bonus action with my bonus action,
I do the truffle truffle.
You do the truffle truffle.
They're still looking at me.
Yeah.
So do I just roll again?
No, because you wouldn't be able to do that again as a bonus action.
Okay, then with my bonus action, are there any workers near me right now?
Well, with your... so I can tell you what you can do with your bonus action.
I look at one of the workers and I say, "I'm going to come down there and give you a knuckle sandwich, I tell you what!"
Shoot the cannon.
Well, the cannon is purged.
And the cannon would be an action at the other point.
Yeah, it would be his action right now was raising around.
I can control it with a bonus action.
Yeah, you can control it with a bonus action. He did the Charleston,
which did help give a bonus.
Um...
So, he could have attacked, but
he did the Charleston.
And then, yeah, anything...
Let's see, what's the... that was...
'cause you were first, so Tuck is next.
Tuck is in the bathroom.
Tuck is peeping.
Where the hell is Tuck?
There's Tuck.
I need to go to the bathroom now. Okay, copying. Tuck, you are up. I'm up? Yeah, so basically
I'm asking. I didn't really establish where I was after. So Pat moved over here. Okay.
And he did the Charleston for the for the for the pinky toes and they liked it and so
they get a plus one in their next role. You are, I mean, you kind of like went back to
the executive office. So I mean, you can go anywhere you want to go in the factory or you
can go outside and try to help one of the fights but this is your time to pick your move.
These guys already have a +1 right?
They just got a +1 to their next roll yes.
So it's basically just a straight up d20 check between these two.
I'm going to go give them another +.
Ok so what do you want to do?
Do you want to try to boost morale or do you want to go and fight with them or what?
I'd like to go to the front door and I have three javelins in my inventory.
like to I'd like to go to you're gonna go under the front door to let go.
Pssst! Pssst! Walk over here! Whoa! Wait can I hear am I in the same room? Pssst! Guys, pinky toes, walk over here!
Yeah they look over. I have a javelin for you. Oh thank you thank you sir
rightly. Okay I'm gonna slide it under. Okay so you slide the javelin.
a javelin I'll give them another plus one for that for you giving them the javelin
whisper the whisper one whisper one definitely didn't sound now you are
guys take the javelin and that's also not a character that should be whispering
tuck is now here white day is white you're white - I'm white tuck is now here
oh yeah second well back back in these times that the Irish weren't even
considered white yeah back in these times these times people are gonna look back
on these times and say what the hey talk say D's what tuck I will say crap while
you were going down the executive office and crossing the suspenders don't tell me
I had a trap bro no no you didn't trap you heard you heard a flush sound coming
from the the workers bathroom area over here on the other side of the wall okay
I immediately am like my son yeah yeah you'll have to do that in
your next turn, but you heard something over here.
- But first I have to go do a bunch of quads
and wait a little bit.
(laughing)
- Okay.
You, what do you want to do?
Are you in the lobby you said?
- Yeah, I'm in the lobby.
Nobody came into the lobby.
- No, you're there with Tuck right now.
No, the lobby is empty.
- Okay, and there's fighting right outside the lobby?
- Yeah, like, I mean, like a good like 50-ish feet outside.
- Okay, I mean, I guess I'll just shoot.
So here's the thing too, I have on my actions,
I have this thing that says fire bolt,
but I couldn't find it.
I don't know what--
- It's a cantrip.
- Okay.
it's just uh...
it's just a spell you can cast
it's just a spell, oh here it is
well i have a spell called catapult i didn't even see, i didn't look at my spell
holy crapping fuck
holy crapping fuck, you have stuff when you rage, use some stuff
my god i have thunder wave, i straight up have pokemon, i fuck up my voice
uh... i guess i'm gonna just try and shoot a firebolt, at the crowd? yeah
indiscriminately, yeah roll at the workers, just roll the attack for firebolt
So we're doing like kind of mob combat. So okay, like see here if it beats the AC it'll do like a certain amount damage
That is 19. Yeah
Can we get a worker count really quick?
Well, okay. Yeah sure. So right now there is
so there's
lost one here, so there's like
35 Pinkerton's here and
40 workers. I just want a total war. This seems like a crazy cantrip. There's like a hundred. There's 159 right?
This does 2d10 damage?
What?
And it's a cantrip?
That's 12 damage.
Um, yeah, I mean it's, it's, it's, you're, yeah you're strong.
Um...
Bruh!
Wait, this guy knows magic?
What the fuck?
It's not magic.
Oh wait, wow.
How much damage did you do?
Uh, it looks like 12.
12, yeah.
Nice, okay, yeah.
This is, this is, I, I, I...
I didn't know I was working with some kind of Satanist!
Alright, no, I opened up, I opened up a vent on my Iron Man suit,
and it shoots out just, there, there...
there has just been fire in the
it's nice in the whole so i will affect
and i guess i was in a trend attack i
just like say it feels a little hot in
here you open up the belt
both of my that's a lot better
yeah the workers are mostly children
like screaming they're going to take
minus two to their next role now against
us these guys have plus two these guys
minus two
ok so we're going to now run it run it
again.
I love having a siege.
Minus two, plus two, oh wow.
Okay, we're going to re-roll.
They tied.
Who tied?
These two tied.
We're going to re-roll.
Wait, and they got plus two?
Yeah, and then they got minus two and they tied.
Holy crap.
Okay, and then...
Alright, they won this one.
Which one of ours is worse?
Dude, hell yeah.
I knew that plus one would help.
How much did they win by?
I mean, it won by a lot.
We tied it with all that crap.
That's right.
Okay.
And then it did help, but not like the most ever, but it helped.
Bitch.
Okay.
And all right.
They won here too.
That's another win.
Oh no.
Not the workers.
Our guys won again.
You guys won, workers lost here.
This is so easy.
I feel like a war general workers. This is the coolest here. Unfortunately, we
should do a siege every time. I wish there was a video game where you could
do this, but I don't care for violence and maybe some kind of party item and
yeah, but pinky toes one here, okay,
So the piggy toes are doing very well on this side on the east side.
The workers look like they might break through on this side.
I'm not sure that will happen.
The north side and then the west side.
The west side it's tied.
This side it's also tied.
But they have advantages.
And there's that bathroom there?
Yeah, the bathroom had a noise right now.
I just start indiscriminately firing around.
I told you you don't know you didn't hear well. I'm already indiscriminately firing
Indiscriminately fire after the first thing just luckily you just throw up perfectly. I throw a perfect cannonball
Okay, at I'm just shooting. It's actually a horse bolt office a force bolt not a cannonball
Okay, so who goes first here? He goes first you're gonna start indiscriminately just shooting
Well, and maybe I hit the bathroom
And I yell like maybe we should check every toy with to see if I have any more heirs to my fortune
I'll let you fire indiscriminately roll a d20 to see if let's do like a luck roll. Let's have fun with this roll
Do you 20 if you get 15 or higher? I'll say you hit the bathroom
If you don't you might hit something else. What is that?
There's not a 13. We don't want to destroy the dam. So you're shooting indiscriminately
uh... just around and uh...
you hit this thing
and you see like
like a steam like ice cold steam come out and it cools the glue
no he really did that
and you see
not him breaking the machine away
it's giving recklessness
and one ton destruction
it's the indiscriminate firing for me
you see a nose poke out of the machine
uh... and it is indeed the snow miser
the
just
still mystery
this is the only way
the
what is he doing here
guys all the hell
the
well i i i was told you about that i saw his no-fly zeros is used to cool the
glue as it's attached to the
the hooks are attached and i do that dance with him to see the job this is
his job because he go only workers not yeah he's like spinning around you
what's going on here I don't remember what the snow miser sounds he's he's had
more like a
white Christmas mr. snow mr. icicle mr. ten below
I'm so clutch think about this we might want to go and throw Dan and into the
furnace. Why? I have a feeling if the Snow Miser is nearby there might be another
Miser in the building. Why would you throw me in the furnace? Why don't we put the
Snow Miser? Why don't we use the Snow Miser? Because you seem to be that you'd
be able to sniff this kind of thing out pretty well. No. I'm thinking you should
hop up in that. Well I know the Snow Miser. So far you are the Miser Fizer.
Fizer? Miser Finder. So the Snow Miser is saying, says, "Say what's going on here?" "Hey I wish I could tell you!"
attack the front building you guys now as a bonus action can command the snow
miser oh my god that is literally my dream we're gonna win okay cool you've
unlocked the snow miser okay so now we'll go to your turd you thought he was
a bad guy but turns out to be our our pawn he's good AF there's one snow miser in
every factory that helps I just found out I didn't really know about the
technology of the day yeah you are seriously giving ice I would like to go
to this bit part of the north side not the snow miser freezing all the north
side so you can go to the dock yeah and can I bring this no miser with me as a
a bonus action you can command him to come with you and so it could be just
both of you post on my door I'm mr. snow I know singing no I hate singing no the
calm miser lives in the bathroom
that's disgusting you got time I'm too much
You're stuck in the Snowmiser now, posted it at the loading dock.
At the loading dock you don't see anything going on, by the way.
There's activity going on outside, though, yes.
You used your...
I'm already kind of anticipating...
You just moved and used a bonus action, so you can attack if you have a ranged weapon.
Can I do any kind of... I was thinking of having the Snowmiser maybe build some kind of ice wall to kind of reinforce this part of it.
He has an ice wall spell you can use.
Because we're so close to losing it.
Yeah, I would say you can use the ice wall. You can command me uses ice wall spell as your action
Hey while he's doing that you have a make me a snow cone. I have type 2 diabetes. That's fine
So what this will do is bear I'm the first I'm patient zero for type 2 diabetes the doors
So even if they win this fight against the pinky toes, they still will have
One turn where they have to break this down so that you can delay them invading
okay put a bunch of your body stuff all over this yeah you say oh and one more
thing there's a another guy in the bathrooms that somebody should do that
on their turn yeah yeah and it is your turn okay you guys are both in the lobby
so you and RDJ so you probably you could have told him that anyway okay okay I
just wanted I'm right by the bathroom once I'd already been over here I just
kind of realized you're gonna head over to the bathroom over here I am okay are
you I know sure the bathroom is right here we got it there we have to go
around if there's two spies now that if I can other spies here if I can do if I
can do it in my turn then yeah I'll do it yeah you can move okay make that move
and I I have I have um I have like a buzzsaw in my stomach mm-hmm like Gigan
from Godzilla. Fuck you. Yeah, it's cool. And I have to, I have to, it doesn't spin on its own. I have to crank a thing inside of my suit to spin it.
And I'm cranking it and I'm spinning it and I just walk through the bathroom wall. Yeah, you see, you see a handful, a handful. It's also a music box.
You see a handful of child, of child laborers who are coming in to attack you. Um, so you can roll an attack roll against them.
I have a trash compactor of my stomach like Wally also
And I'm going to make a kid cube yeah, whatever this attack would be roll that
Well, it's a 19 plus something. I mean that's gonna hit whatever it is, but this is your it's gonna
Be like you're just regular this is me crushing all the children into a cube
I know, but I'm just and then you're gonna roll it like a die like yeah, I make that into a spell. It's my power source
True that's my battery as soon as that happens you could make that into hotter
You can make that into scorching ray or you can make that into fire bolting. I thought scorching ray lived in the furnace
Bruh, I mean all the fireball has more damage than scorching ray
Squirting ray well scorching ray you can you can hurl three of them. Oh, okay
I'll do I'll do cool. I'll solve any sense you Sullivan is inside you have him Sullivan is still in my cannon
I'm saving him. Yeah, he's he's important and I can breathe
Yeah, oh, sorry about that. Yeah, I close the compartment
Okay, so that's that's what 66 damage well you did 66 image D 6 6 D 6
So on it you make a range spell attack for each ray, so you would target oh three of them with this
Okay, it's mob. It's mob rules. So like there's should I roll two more time
I think you could just roll for full damage cuz mob rules. Okay. Hey, whatever you say, whatever you say
Okay, let's see here that's nine I don't want to make you roll for each race annoying
16 18 what's that? What's that's a six? Okay, that's 24 damage that up, but
Oh, it's a 2, so no, it's not 24 damage. It's 20 damage.
Okay, that's still enough. Yeah, you just like incinerate the spies that were in here.
The spy children.
I, no, I'd cubed them.
You cube these children. You have children cubes now ready for you.
It's plugged into my back.
Yeah, and so that's great. Okay, now we'll go back to what we were,
back to the siege stuff, okay?
and okay
pinky toes won this one yo
close to close to defeating the this is gonna be so for a king easy one
okay that
say this is an absolutely an epic win there was a lot of the other day
well i do want to my eyes not the workers and now that i have a little
over here that's an epic way and
k
you know i don't have that to fail bulletin
Check this out. Check this out. Check this out.
Leroy Jenkins!
That might come in handy. Wait us.
Alright, so, okay. There's still...
Alright. So still, there's no definitive win or loss yet on either side.
But, I will tell you.
Who's winning?
Winning, you're winning on the South.
You're winning in the East.
You said it's three wins before three losses?
Yeah, it's winning on the south and east you're still losing on the north and west
But you stopped you almost lost in the north completely, but you didn't this time
So it's one but it's one one more win for each of those people for the person who's winning
Okay, I feel like we should because the north side is barricaded a little bit
I feel like we should focus everything on giving buffs to this. Yes. Well, I was gonna take out those spies in the bathroom
He just did yeah, he did okay, then I'm gonna turn
Turn my cannon towards the barricade I
Guess what the barricade no not the barricade. Why you want to break the barrel? I'm gonna shoot over the barricade
No, we want to go west side. There's no barricade there, okay?
This is a serious west side story, so you're gonna go to that's a reference
I'm serving cunt. I'm serving cunt I say. Sir you just set my sides into orbit. Well I'm
completely serving cunt. That's completely based. I'll tell you. The workers are fake
and gay. So you're gonna go over to the west side here. Child I'm serving cunt. Okay. It's
Jimmy Stewart saying that is really funny.
So a miracle, so I go serving con we're all
sorry, we're here, but every time a every time a bell rings, an angel is
serving,
so you want to go to the west side here. I didn't say it in Jimmy Stewart's
voice. God damn it. He just was saying his idea for a tick tock or something.
It seems yeah every time an angel every time a bell rings an angel serving
It's over. It's done. Yeah. All right. So you're going to the West side here.
Okay. So I bring my cannon over there to the West side,
to the West Danon's cannon on the West side.
As you're walking along, this is actually very good timing. Um, you,
you on accident. Um,
but I had something set in motion after three rounds and they just failed a major
stealth check. Uh,
You hear Jordy and his MILF inside Jordy's office as you're walking along the outside.
I don't really want to hear what they're doing in there.
My guess is that he's a betrayer.
Make the noises.
I think he's a betrayer.
I hear the noises.
You hear him press what's... he got a wand.
You hear him say, "I've got to press my Matt Lauer button," and he presses it.
And the bathroom in his office starts to pop out.
You hear workers popping out.
I hear all the workers popping out and I'm like, "What in the blazes? I gotta do something
about this!"
That MILF's having babies at an incredible rate!
Holy crap!
And that MILF... Gianna Michaels.
And they're coming out...
No, shut up.
And I'm just right there with the...
I don't think they've ever done anything together.
I have the gun pointed at them, right?
That working relationship between Jordi and Gianna what?
I have the gun pointed at them already? I'm like right there?
You can't... I will let you... If you wanna like... Instead of like peering out on the
west side you want to stop what you're doing and like sort of post yourself
like above them and yes they're coming out the door yeah below you just like
start fucking like that that uh was it scarface one yes okay I'm reloading okay
I'm I'm reloading okay cool you haven't even shot yet you say that yeah yeah is
it okay yeah it is don't you dirty cockroaches I'm reloading roll it I'm
I'm sorry roll an attack. You just stood up and I would like turning his laptop
and I saw that.
Doing yes, so when I roll weird, you should roll the attack roll for the
cannon. You go, okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. He rolls attack. He's you give you
the cannon. Yeah, you're gonna or maybe Patrick should roll it. Okay, I'll
roll it.
I didn't but the cannon actually doesn't have I did notice is it doesn't
have an attack roll associated with it here on the force ballista. So I
got him. There's one for the flamethrower above but not for the force
ballista. It's a plus six to hit. So it says that where does it say that? Right here. Okay.
Well I got a 14. Oh yeah. I didn't know you could like zoom in on it like that. That hits.
Roll for damage. How much is it? What's the damage? Oh wait. Let me. How did you get to
that screen? No don't. You don't. Just hold on. Wait. Oh it's 2d8. Yeah 2d8. And it pushes
the target five feet. So roll 2d8 Pat. Is it add anything else or is it just 2d8? 2d8
says okay so go get the two d_a_ here's one d_-eight
here is is another one of the eight
that's my face
it's very addictive
role that shit for
no and that he needs a new era where enemies
seven
that's pretty sad to know okay i have to get you started spraying have been
forceful list uh...
it's like a ship as these workers are coming out
and uh... yeah a few of them get killed but you have a few of them have
are still around and they're still in this area but you killed a good amount
of them in your journey go
all sheet
and uh... he tries to let me know a little bit shitty we're running away
into the toilet writing is milk with him
uh...
and uh... so that was that was a good i mean that was good uh...
uh... only didn't hear that okay so
or my going now you're on to a that little guy was a uh...
uh... an imposter he was sus
And he was sus too. And he was completely among us.
He was. That imposter was among us. And he was sus.
I would like to go to the west side, right? West side, the best side, right? And I would
like to help out these. Do you want to take out those guys?
Yeah, I want to sing my song, actually. Because I actually think my song and my story is better.
Tuckmiser? Do you want the Snowmiser to come with you or do you want him to post up here
still? He can do all of the instrumental stuff and
I can do he made an ice keyboard and I can do you want the snow miser here or do
you want to come with you well compete then the West Side people will they be
able to hear the instruments or is it gonna sound like I'm doing a completely
acapella if he stays here oh I see what you're saying yeah hmm well we can roll
a performance check and okay well then he can stay there okay yeah what happened
and I'm gonna walk all the way to the West Side all right cool so time I'm
gonna start singing my song sure should I roll my performance check first before I
I perform it? Yeah, and I'll roll one for the Snow Mizer. All right, hold just on a moment.
Hold just on a moment? Seriously, you said that? Okay. He said hold just on a moment.
Hold just on a moment. Bruh really said that. Bruh really said hold just on a moment. All
right, I have a negative one performance, but let's see what I get. I got an 11. Okay,
and Snow Mizer got a 7. So it's a 7-11. That's a lucky number. Snake Eye is watching you.
guys play Motorhead? No. Okay, what do you guys play? I'm on the West Side, right? Sing your song.
Oh. Sometimes I feel like I don't have a partner. Sometimes I feel like my only
friend is the city I live in. The city of angels. Won't we as I am, together we cry.
and then you hear the Snowmiser in the back goes and he goes and then I do the
whole song. Yeah yeah. Well I got a baby named Dino. You gotta give it to your mama.
So you're gonna attack them? No I'm just I'm imbuing them with with West Coast
spirit. Oh these are your enemies? No you misunderstood what I was doing I'm
I'm coming over here to help these guys.
(mimics a baby crying)
So, wait, wait.
Why would I just walk up to them and sing at them?
Oh, I'm sorry, I got confused there.
Okay, so-- I know.
So you walked up over here yourself.
I don't even know about the toilet men.
I haven't even seen them.
Okay, so you walked out over here.
Can I inform him?
Can I just yell it?
Inform him. No, no, it's fine now.
Inform me. About the toilet men.
I need to know about the toilet guys right now.
That's good enough.
That's good enough that we'll give them
a plus one on their next roll.
Jor-E-N-G-O-R-E. Snow, Snow-Mizer.
Holy shit.
you are all my god. Why didn't you see that? I'm here. Yeah. Okay. Are we're
losing? Can I get to either the north or the west easily from where I am? I
don't I can't tell where the doors are in this. You know full movement, right?
The north the north you'd have to both of them. You probably have to use your
full movement. You're okay. What about these people coming out of the
bathroom? Also, do I know what do I know about them? I mean if you walk if
you're walking up, I guess I just killed a bunch of guys in a in a bathroom.
I'm coming out and you hear gunfire too from them.
- I guess I'll go towards them.
- Okay, cool.
So you're over here where Tuck was
or where I thought he was.
And so do you want to attack them?
- Yeah, I'll shoot all my, whatever the three one is.
- He's gonna shoot as well.
- Oh, the Scorching Ray.
- Yeah.
- The Scorching Ray.
- Yeah, that might be, check your spell slots
'cause I don't know how many spell slots you have.
- Oh shit, true.
I completely forgot it.
- Yeah.
- Fucking shit.
- I would do a cantrip probably.
I would do Firebolt maybe 'cause in,
or you can just use it. Oh yeah, because I'll do I'll do firebolt. I forgot about
spell slots. I just dnd beyond I pressed a spell slot. It's been loading the whole
time. Yeah, I'll just look at this. That's very it's this freaking app needs a
loading screen like this to make a check in a checkbox. What is technology come to
nowadays that makes me I look at that and I just say bro the way this iPhone is
functioning. I'm glad we're in the 1890s right now. It's completely fucked. All
all right that's a sixteen plus
six
ninety-two yamina had some
roper damage
merits except seven from you right
yes so it doesn't want to be a
was attend image okay cool yet there's only one worker left and he's injured
uh... and the fire come to
i say
i say say hello to my little friend and then i and then it's the little friend
is the child cube
in me and it has a face a child's face on it still on the fire yeah and the child
the fire comes out of the child's mouth yeah yeah yeah they're horrified they're
saying no jimmy they recognize the child's face that you're burning and uh
with yeah and they're gone um okay so jordy is in the toilet right now jordy
escaped somewhere he went into the toilet he might have
went somewhere let's see what happens now i hope he's not on the east side now
because if he goes to the east side that would probably be
pretty bad for us because he can sabotage because he knows the layout of the
workplace. Nobody even went in the obstacle course yet.
I know. I hope he got teleported to the obstacle course.
Oh. I just checked he wasn't there. Uh oh. What are you saying? Uh oh.
He's saying uh oh. It's tied again over here.
Oh no. And then. You tricked us. You made us go away from there and then you tied
it. He's working against us. I'm not working against you.
Color me fucking shocked. All right. He's got an I voted sticker. The workers won
here. I did not have an eye voted sticker. Even with my song they
won? Yeah, it wasn't enough. So the workers won over here. I
mean, they'll be less than them, but they're gonna start to
storm. I guess they're gonna have to go they're gonna have to
go through the south through the north entrance up here. Now the
north workers let's see how they do. Loose loose. They lose and
they are defeated. Yo. Oh wait, no, they're not sorry.
know my oh my god my bad me reading wrong not me reading wrong mm-hmm okay it's
the illiteracy for me yes no way we roll there was a tie that's completely the
illiteracy for me okay they won over here you guys okay so oh yeah lost tied
one yeah yeah so we won the east side yeah so east and west are we have East
East, West, Worker West, North and South are tied.
Worker West, East, East, East is the beastest.
And the Pinky Toes, being good contractors that they are, they go, "Well, my work here
is done."
And they brush their hands off and they walk out.
But you guys beat all the workers here.
And so now the workers are coming in over here and now we're back at the top of the
order.
So where am I right now?
You are up here.
There's one worker left.
You were shooting down there.
I'm you're still like on top and is there any sort of in the building is there any way that I could get a there's one
There's no piggy toes in the building
Is there any way I could get a bunch of people?
From like all those guys that are leaving is there any way I can tell them to come in here and like fortify
I mean, they're
Well, I can hire them again right yeah money you could oh, yeah, we're rich. Yeah, we're completely rich
You could use a turn to try to hire them back to help out and buff one of the forces up if you want to
I want to do that.
Alright, cool.
So you're gonna run over here.
So you're over here.
Hey!
Alright, listen!
You're yelling out the window now.
Hey!
What do you want, sir?
Same thing I wanted before!
I guess, I don't...
Say you'll give them an entire dawah if they with their lives.
I'll give you a dawah!
No!
A dawah!
No, it makes the world go wow!
I'll give you a world go round one of them one of the guys stands up it goes oh
yeah oh
so these guys now are gonna have they're gonna have plus five okay so and then
with my extra move my bonus action yeah I mean you don't have like much you
could do with your bonus action that would be relevant. I do the Charleston again.
Do you do the Charleston again? Okay. You should do it for the Northside. Actually I'm gonna do the
Charleston on the Northside. I mean you can't move all the way to the Northside.
I say hey! Hey Northside! I have to show you something beautiful! So how about all the soldiers from the Northside come over here?
And then go back! I got the Northside. I'll take care of the Northside.
North side, Canada, right? Canadian is the north side, right?
So you're right now the workers from the west side are coming around the corner towards you
because you went out here and you sang for them and then they all died and now the workers are
coming towards you. Okay, so I'm right completely away from them. You could fight them too,
you're a barbarian. Okay, well, then I, oh, can I beckon the Snowmizer to come help?
Yes, you can use that as a bonus action. So the thing is if your bonus action would be to rage,
So you won't have the rage if you do that, but you can still get the skill.
Okay, I want to rage. I want to rage.
Yeah, I think you should rage.
Wait.
Nobody wiped my thong!
[Laughter]
And so, how do I click rage?
Um, so, well, it's just like, it's just an ability, so what's just gonna happen is...
Hey, bitches.
Um, you, right now, you have advantage on any strength checks or saving throws, but not attacks.
You do +2 damage for any melee damage with strength weapons.
You have resistance to damage now.
And so you're just gonna do more damage now
and you're gonna be stronger.
But you also get some abilities from raging
with the path of the beast.
- The form of the beast stuff?
- Yeah.
So you also have, until your rage ends,
you can manifest a natural weapon.
It counts as a simple melee weapon for you
and add your strength modifier to the attack
and damage rolls when you attack with it as normal.
- Okay, I know what I'm gonna do.
I would like to, so they're all running at me.
Are they like in a line pretty much?
- Yeah, and you have like a tail too.
- Oh yeah, so that's what I'd like to do
is I'd like to I'd like to turn around and take my pants off and
shoot my tail at them to sweep under their legs. Roll an
attack roll. All right, let's see. Wait, I accidentally rolled
the damage. Hold on. Let me roll the attack roll instead.
And my god got and
14. Okay, that's enough. Now I roll for damage. And I got a
seven. Nice. Okay, cool. So the workers are coming towards you
and you pull down your pants and you just whip around and you go "HE'S GOT A TAIL!"
"PINCHED TAIL!"
"A MILLION EYES!"
And so they take some damage.
"What's that for?"
They take some damage, so that was good.
Oh wait, I think that was from the Simpsons talking.
You add another +2.
You actually did 9 damage.
I like Homer.
I like when Homer says "go."
I like Mr. Burns.
Cartoon Network. So that group is now, they're not doing too well. Did I knock them down?
You knocked down a bunch of them. I saw that talkie the other day, the secret life of pets.
Can I walk them down? And they change the name of the main character. What'd you say?
The main dog. They change his name. This is like a joke for a ten year old who knows what
that movie is? If a creature you see. I've never seen that movie. Louis C.K. is the voice
of the main character.
So now also if somebody tries to attack you when you have your tail out, you can use your
reaction to swipe your tail and roll a d8, applying bonus to your AC.
So basically like, if they try to attack you while you have your tail out, you can be like,
"Get away!"
And like, "Bang!"
Can I swing from the waftas like Nightclaw-la?
Swing from the waftas!
Not right now, but in a minute.
Nightclaw-la!
I'm like some kind of Nightclaw-la!
Doing good!
Claw-la!
Nightclaw-la!
You're up now.
up now. Okay, am I what's yeah? How many people are left? There's one. There's like one very
weak worker here. Okay, you I mean, I guess I'm just gonna well, let's see and mine literally
be more worth your time to like go like yeah, where where is where have we not want so we
won on the on the on the east west is lost and then Caleb you're doing stuff on the north
Well, I haven't done anything yet. I was just fighting the people who can I get to the north from where I am?
Yes, you cuz they got plus five down. Yeah, you can get to north where you are
I'm gonna go to the I'm gonna go to the north about the snow mine. I'm gonna try tromp up to the north
Okay, you're gonna go outside - yeah, and then I'm gonna stand right in the middle of all the all the workers
Okay, what's your role in?
What's your role in?
And I'm gonna cast Thunderwave. Oh, okay. Cool. Yeah, so they're gonna throw a constitution saving throw against that
that you just plug yourself into an outlet in the wall it's the 18 no
there's no freaking furthest of freaking outlets okay okay I'm struck by
lightning storm and it just yeah I just you can see my writing so the creatures
they did save so they are gonna take but they're gonna take half damage and
they're not pushed back but still roll 2d 8 okay under damage or are you up are
you upcasting it actually no no okay where's the that is ten so what have is
five cool so they will take minus two
there they are they're gonna take minus two in their next role and when and when
they come up to you they're gonna be they're gonna be less fewer of them yeah
also the lightning bolt brings the child cube back to life like Frank. It's
just horrible screaming all right cool. What we're back to the top so all
right South side South side
South side
the dirty South you won yeah, let's fucking go. Yeah, workers are going to
South side down. So let's fucking go
North side.
Uh-uh.
He flopped it again.
He just plopped it down.
He didn't roll up.
Here, I'll roll for it.
Do not flop it.
The DM is in his flop era.
Then they won.
That doesn't count because that would be a...
So the workers won over here.
What?
So we're two and two.
You're two and two.
You prevented them from coming over and helping them, but they still won.
Okay, great.
I'm glad I used my...
I'm glad I revealed my tale early in the story.
Whatever.
Well, no, it's helpful.
Wait, it's two and two?
I thought we...
So what happens now?
- Are all the fights over?
- We won Southeast, shout out North Carolina.
- No, they're still gonna charge.
The ones who lived are gonna still charge the factory.
- Oh, okay.
- So we're back to top of the order now.
You're up.
- I heard a beep.
- Me too.
- You are, so Pat, you are back here.
You got these workers to stay with you for one more fight.
- The workers?
- Oh, not the workers, sorry.
You got the pinky toes to stick with you.
So if you want to, you can try to send them up here to help
or have them storm the factory now and prepare for--
- I think probably storm the factory, right?
- I think that's probably your best move, I would say.
- Yeah, yeah, I'm gonna have them storm--
- Can I get a worker account really quickly?
- Sure, we are at, 'cause they're dead here,
so that's them there, and then they're dead here.
So you have now--
- How many pinker toes?
- Pinky toes I haven't been keeping track of.
- I hear an actual Jurassic Park footstep outside right now.
- I think that's just some kind of loud music.
- I think it's a serious Godzilla attack.
stop squeaking. I haven't even been paying attention to the sound outside.
Where's my counter? Report card. Sorry. Where's my counter? Oh, I'm in the wrong
document. I'm adding that as a section on your report card. There's a ghost in the
factory. You have 75 workers left. 75 workers left in you? Oh my god, yeah.
You're the longest D&D of all time. Yeah, I know. Alright, I'm doing a tactical nuke.
self-destruct and so now so you where did you go pat you went you brought them in
here yeah okay cool and then there is still this one worker that's like kind
of hanging out well there I'll just say obviously obviously they're gonna just
kill yeah like soon as they he was on the pinky toes walking nobody's even
though I want to point out again and I'm putting this out to Caleb and Patrick but
I want patches to like to listen in I'm complaining to you guys can you believe
no one's even done our obstacle course yet holy crap what do we even spend time
I'm doing that, but it's not like pointed. It's not directed at
anybody. It's just like a complaint. I'm making to my
friends and maybe so I might overhear it and somebody and
roll a dice and the bathroom they would have maybe done it
maybe. Yeah, that's true. I guess I totally missed my chance
Patrick to make three workers go on our obstacle course. Maybe
you should have a 75. Yeah, maybe we should walk out and
ask if anyone wants to volunteer. Okay, that's actually
not that bad of an idea. Hold on your it's almost like the DM
I've never heard of check offs wipe out. Well, maybe we will play with it at
maybe the end of ourselves.
I'm gonna actually I'm gonna go play with it right now. It was where we fun.
I'm gonna go do it yeah. You can use the rest of your movement to just go
over here and start playing. That's gonna give you some kind of buff. I
don't think it's gonna make you buff working out on that. Yeah, you are up
now
the top. I'm on the gladiator portion right now, and I don't have anyone to do
with. It looks like coway muffle.
So the workers are going to come and try to attack you soon. Um,
but you can still hold them at bay with your tail. Okay. Wait.
And I have more beast, uh, abilities. Yes.
So let's dive into those really quick.
Let's do a deep dive into my beast abilities.
So I would like to use a deep butt dive, my bite,
and I would like to go and how many people did I knock over with my tail?
Are you supposed to choose one weapon?
I think you should just have all of them.
I agree.
So I don't really care.
Keep going.
Sorry, yeah.
How many people did I knock down?
You knocked down like seven.
Okay, I would like to go and individually bite each and every one of them while they're
knocked down prone.
Yeah.
Just like.
Oh, you like eat them?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, go for it.
Roll and take.
Okay, I'm rolling.
Yeah, that's going to be a 21, bud.
Yeah, that hits.
Yeah, okay.
Oh, you should.
I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm
But yeah, that hits yeah, okay, no
Freaking damn roach these girls for damage, and I would like to completely hit them with five damage, okay?
Oh, yeah, you eat um I don't eat
I just bite yeah, you kill like four of them on the ground
Yeah, if you could go ahead and get bitten by me. Yeah, that'd be great
Yeah, that would be great. They are in yeah by you now factory are they're afraid of you
So they are gonna try to run away from you
Don't you come back cuz I'm will
And you are now up unless you want to come in the snow miser to do something
Oh true
You should make an ice sculpture he should oh my god get this snow miser to freeze up all the water and all the toilets
Are we doing this
We'll just think it's so somebody could come back. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I do that or specifically the one that Jordan went through
Yeah, I'm gonna send him to the entrance toilets that the workers go through and I'm gonna say
Start here and freeze the entire system
Right
And while you do you have to say no my you know, the W's on me I go blam like that
I don't know. You got a whack that freezer toilet down
Thank You
Like a domain, I mean I'm in a dorm and I'm gonna wake you boom boom down with you boom boom ba
He's doing that and he's freezing the toilet and you hear you hear
This Geordie is trapped now in the pipes and can't yeah, that's right. That's right. Yeah that
Yeah, he's pretty much whoa then
And you're up now
Okay, um people are running away from the north side. They're running away from the west peep side people are running
okay i want to walk to where i can get a good vantage point on them
man i want to use my my catapult spell
jay go for which i just looked at my kin
i can judge should i can shoot any object yes i'd jump in a couple
who's going to shoot the child cubicle catapult you yeah
do i'm big and i don't think a lot of damage if i can pull you
see look mean as in to do look at me look at you take three d eight damage to
you want to take three d eight damage do you think i give a fuck if i live or die
yes
no
put me in, load me in
load him in and roll it
okay, i'm loading
i'd like to pull, really quickly
i'd like to pull out the rest of my javelins
they all save
against it, a deck save
you're holding all of your javelins
they fail!
no i'm not holding them, i got them stuck in my belly button
roll for damage now
okay, it's 3d8 damage
and that's for both of them
i don't know if i roll separately or not
i guess it's the same for both
okay well it is 16
Wow, okay. Yeah, those workers are basically dead and they're running away.
So do you even need to shoot me in the catapult? I mean you launch in the air.
You already did? Oh, okay. So you take 16.
Tails flopping around and just crashes in. I have four javelins stuck in my belly button.
You hear the children scream, "Ahh!" and they go blast it away. You can see Hasan the Chapo now
is getting really worried. This might not be as poggers as I thought it was going to be.
He now that you were launched him far enough. He can spot him sort of in the
South don't draw on the table. Sorry.
What the hell are you doing?
Worked on me so bad.
How much how much damage do I take?
What you took?
What was it?
How much was that?
16 16 50 HP.
Yeah, you're fine.
Okay, and now let's do it again next turn.
No, not you now.
We're back to the top of the order of the workers and so they're gone.
So these workers are charging now and they're going to try to break in to
the you probably sorry you were can be
moved over here talk is now off the map
and the workers are now trying to break
down the ice wall but the ice was now in
the way so they can't break it down
right away and it's back to the top of
the order and you guys almost won this I
would say well we've almost won I think
the only thing that could make this I
know what you're about to say is not
finish the fight and win I think I'm
getting white that vibes from this one net well the little one wants to play
forget the other i think it's i think i'm i i think it's a 5050 here's either
a wipeout or charles you can ladies and gentlemen you can concert from the band
weiser
all right everybody where we
with the glacies from say somebody's hiney is
Sorry my icebox
Somebody's cold one is given me
Sweater pull on the strings from it. Here's what I'll say you can do you can you can try to
Negotiate now with us on the chapeau. I'm gonna know no no no
I'm negotiating good. Maybe we could solve all of these problems with a concert from Ouisa
Hey, I got a negotiation for you pal. Can I be there? Yeah, I'm point-blank Sullivan in the face
Roll an attack roll, okay, give him a kiss dude. No one Sullivan's gay ass
You remember Sullivan was in the toilet for a long time. No, we could get tight. This is a it's a poop. Oh
We need to get him tuberculosis
That's a 10 plus. I've assumed plus
better than right let me see I don't know what it if it's if it's the same as
firebolt it's plus six okay that's sixteen yeah that hits yes you launch
solvent at Hassan the chapeau he was no and he like it's like knocked all the
way back the other workers scattered does he do like a like Team Rocket like
glint in the yeah he's in the sky before he does that can he also do the thing
like in a fighting game when you get a chaos like
and he like flies back a little bit at a time. Yes, and then he
goes and then it speaks of it goes back and he gets the glint.
Yeah, he goes in the sky and I mean, I'm gone has gone off
line and then it let's have this. Let's have the rest of the
workers. You can force them to into the obstacle course while
you guys play after he tried to wait us while you guys play
Weezer. You guys gonna score the score the obstacle course and
we can have them what was the obstacle course made of what is it it's machinery
machine guns yeah like like it looks like it's like it's the wipeout course
it's all pure metal it looks like it looks like it's inflatable like things
that are going up and down like inflatable like tubes and shit but those
are all like you know lined with lead yeah it's like a Jeff Koons sculpture
yeah looks like it's a balloon yeah I'm gonna roll athletics and acrobatics for
for or acrobatics, I guess for each of them for like a four groups of workers
okay, one got a two and my own
a three oh my God, wow, oh my God and a ten, so I my iron man suit I'm turning
the crank on the other side, which powers a phonograph and it's playing like the
playlist that like a gym teacher would play when you're doing like the
parachute and Jim
So yeah, one of them slips on the ball and just bangs. You see the
wipeout logo pop up. It lands on the conveyor belt and just gets
like suspenders forcibly attached to his back, screaming and
bloody murder and it is attached to a barrel and put into this
this hot truck. Also we're doing the pre-wipeout
interviews too. Yeah. Yeah. Went through what Death Woko had to say.
Yeah. And he's like, I'm ready to do it. I was just hoping I would get...
Now here's Jimmy. Jimmy is a 10 year old boy. He lost three of
his fingers working working suck so this kid doesn't exactly have his head on
let's see how we did on the call his head gets completely twisted around
you're doing funny puns about the way they're dying yeah it's so that that
goes on and then and then as the Sun begins to rise as the last worker has
fallen, you can hear the echoes of the future, the sounds and sights of Labor Day celebrations.
You know what those are, right?
It's such an important holiday that means so much to the average person, that just saying
Labor Day conjures up so many memories of joy and camaraderie in the world that you
feel overwhelmed.
I mean, who doesn't remember their first Labor Day?
You know, like the first one you could remember.
I know I do.
It was the first Monday of September that year, and I remember my parents coming to my room
and saying, "Get up."
(laughing)
And as you stand over the dead bodies of these nobodies,
the sacrifices you made today
will reverberate throughout history.
The projector comes down in your office once again,
tuxedo man comes back up.
It's another glorious day here in Duluth, Brooklyn,
and you, the good worker, should know your rights.
One, you don't have them, two, you'll never get them,
and three, most importantly, burn your clothes
and buy some barrels and suspenders.
I'm Xander Corvis saying goodnight to all of you.
is no sander corvices no you can really quickly to the porn star
uh... uh... why it's okay that's a we could do here's what i'd like to i'd
like to really quickly addresses yet
you've met reference over the course is campaign
was the reference johnny sins to self
there were three male porn stars and one of the one who has not had a lot of
feeling just slipped in halfway through was in a really a mail for stars are are
i don't know a single and i don't know any other than a johnny sins 'cause it
He's got a cameo
Yes, it's true I wanted right this land was surely vote for me
You have more waffles than a house of pancakes
You offer flip-flops, I offer tax breaks, you're a UN pussy
And yes it's true that I kick ass, ha!
This land will surely vote for me
[MUSIC PLAYING]