You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[Laughter]
Okay.
Did you figure it out?
Did you figure out how to press the button?
I'm still not recording.
Countdown, you're gonna need a beatdown from me.
I'm still not recording right now.
I'm gonna beat you down.
Yeah.
Are you serious?
You're gonna have a body count when I'm done with you.
That's right.
you don't have one now that's right I'm gonna have body kind of going up by one
but by the yeah we're done fighting yeah that's right
I just closed audacity oh yeah you were the you were the foolish smile you're
lying you're lying yeah hey guys I actually the rascal I actually just
burned my house down I'm actually just wait right seriously yeah I'm serious no
I actually did I just burned my house down you're just you're you're just
jealous of me you're just jealous of my click I'm jealous what's your click ain't
nobody fucking with my click ain't nobody fucking with your clit you could don't
wash it yes thank you boy damn I'm like if you like it's like if you like rolled
a little sticky katamari ball down around you got all that dust on there
stuff yeah you got a Indiana Jones in there and he's like blowing on it and
waving hand around it and he's got like a brush yeah yeah it's like it's like a
fossil dig dude they have brushes and they got little picks and they're trying
to discover the structure like a dragon's pearl and it's hidden under a
bunch of gold yeah it's inside a treasure chest yeah you have to enter
the skeleton key into the lock to get it to open up hey buddy we warned you when
you were when you did all that prank shit talking all that mess we were gonna
body you and it happened yeah I bet you mad with our words dude being verbally
assaulted by the by the by that fucking suck twins I don't appreciate this you
suck you brought it on yourself twin you got to say the other part you saw in
twins twins that's who you're sucking yeah nasty ass clip anyway I'm back how
come you guys how come it all happened from the Capitol yeah we're back dude we
were in we were at the capital we're milf hunting yeah dude walking around a big
milf hunter van yeah we had milf hunter shirts on yeah yeah we were looking for
we were looking for women throwing them into unmarked vans. This is true. Attention DC there are unmarked vans
driving around throwing milfs into the back that's right made a milf disappear
yeah but like also not real like just like a 29 year old girl with like really
bad skin who they're just like she's a total milf we're grabbing her but yeah
we're back from there I should have drank some coffee before this I'm
drinking some cold coffee ice you're drinking you're drinking that out of
your little glove hand I have a goal I sustained an injury while whilst
golfing what was your injury his injury was he put his fist in his ass no no I
was reached for a ball in an alligator that'd be cooler that would actually be
cool if that is so sick I would not be like here right now I'd be like chubs I'd
be like Chuck from the show yeah you would wear it you'd be a secret agent who
wears Converse yeah not yeah that's the coolest thing yeah the Converse secret
agent kind of okay he kind of was just like they put Jim from the office and in
a CIA situation yeah but if they did that Jim or Chuck Taylor's oh yeah they did
that too yeah casual Jim yeah Chuck Jim is short for Chuck it is short Chuck
roast so what was your injury damn check I'm so bad at golfing or I have I guess
I have really poor depth perception. So every single time that I hit the ball, I
just hit the ground. Yeah. And like I hit the ground like a full eight inches
before the ball and my club would just get stuck and I would probably do that
four times before I ever hit the ball. So I just was putting it like... So like worse
than a divot like you were trying to like... Way... Yeah, no I was just like hitting
like it wasn't... the ball wasn't moving. Yeah. So I... and the way I swing because of
how strong I am. I'm probably putting like 500,000 pounds of power behind that and
all that is going directly into my right hand, my back swing hand is what I
call it. So yeah, my beautiful Swedish golf coach, she told me that
I shouldn't do that. And so she told you to put bandages on your hands?
What's your golf coach's name? Her name's Fiona. Fiona? Fiona.
mm-hmm you mean Fiona nope it's Fiona it's cuz she's Swedish yeah oh is that
like is that like the Swedish spelling of Fiona just say Fiona tell you what we
didn't just say in her didn't talk much we just got straight to the point yeah
what was the point my point the tip of your head like a knife you it's like
it's like the leveled up version of a widow's peak is when the widow's peak is
like your actual head it looks like Big Ben dude that's not true dude I don't
have a I don't have a clock for a face I'm a clock for a face and a point at
the top of my head you're singing we be our guest you guys do you guys do when
you wear your wait doesn't the candle sing that I think all the different
tools all right okay so then I'm right so then so Caleb's out here so it could
be our guest I don't know about girly little kid bullshit like that so I just
know about actually you're not really adult yeah actually Josh Gad was in the
live-action movie so you know would you call him would you call him a manchild
would you call him an adult kid no you'd call him a man man he's a man's man yeah
you call him savage yeah his boyfriends oh that's what yeah his character was
gay he danced with a man for a second in oh that's actually he played did he play
Gaston's little gay guy yeah okay that makes sense yeah and they made Gaston
dude they made him for that role do you remember that they made him gay by
having him dance with a man for exactly one second I did not see that movie or
anything about it I did I did see that of like oh he's gay cuz he danced with
him for one second if you watch the movie he's gay the whole movie yeah he
act super gay the entire time. That's just Josh Gad. Oh well yeah maybe you're right
maybe he was doing method acting though for that one moment where he touches that man. Patrick just broke his own neck.
Yeah I know. Damn doing fatalities to yourself that's so sick. Patrick just turned his head like a normal speed and just looked at like
look to the side and then went ah. Yeah he made a whip crack sound too. Dude it did make a sound.
it picked up because I'm looking at my audacity and there's a huge spike.
The spike is probably you going "Ahhhh".
No, it's not it.
Hold on, let's pause the episode so I can go back and listen to it.
Man, I went to the dentist this week.
Oh, did you get your shit ironed out?
I got an antibiotic put in my gums because I have the, I'm in some stage of periodontitis,
which is after gingivitis.
You have a period in your mouth?
Yes.
no they made my gums bleed so I did have a period on my period on Titus uh-huh
Christopher Titus a comedian yeah oh man why didn't bring that back Christopher
Titus mm-hmm bring back Titus on I think he's one of those guys who does a two
hour special every six weeks yeah yeah he made some just angry he used to be
like like a Dennis Leary like I want coffee flavored coffee guy and then at
some point he started making specials called like the Republicans are crazy
yeah today I went to Starbucks and I had to I had to order I don't get coffee
from Starbucks and I had to pull the Dennis Leary I had to say can I just get
a normal coffee what options are there and I felt like such an asshole but the
best part and all I like was ordering for my girlfriend too so she wrote down
her order like on my phone. I have to read this thing about like flavor pumps and
something and then after just be like yeah can I also just get a normal one?
yeah that's right girl get hands your order looks like a goddamn math equation
yeah what is this? This looks like the flavors that that Remy
imagines in Ratatouille. I don't want this. Give me something that looks like oil
that's a man's drink yeah give me black I want something crude I want your coffee
women order women be going to Starbucks ordering a four-dimensional shape yeah I
want to see you I want to see you I want to see you scrape the dirt off the
baseboard to put in this coffee yeah I want it pitch black I want it musty mm-hmm
I want I want you to throw dirt I want spiders in there yeah can you put cobwebs
in my shit just to make it I want I want a haunted coffee yeah I want to open the
lid to let it cool off in here go once I'm done with my order can you play the
organ mints coffee yeah can I have a man's coffee just hot barbecue sauce in
a cup that's all I fucking want don't caffeinate it and one sugar please yeah
I don't put any sugar in my coffee I put him and how did your teeth get so
fucked up then candy because guess who's winning he doesn't drink coffee oh yeah
- Yeah. - At least it not.
Now I do.
- You just drink like,
stuff called like battery surge or something.
- Yeah, you drink like the liquid metal
that they eventually press into like truck nuts.
- Yeah. - You drink the stuff
that's in the power plant in Fortnite.
- Yeah. - Yeah, the splurge.
- Yeah, the stuff that,
the gloop that like gives you shields when you break it.
That's what you drink, dude.
- Cam has converted to a humongous gamer.
- Oh, I know. - Out of nowhere.
- It's really funny. - I don't know,
I played a lot of games in high school.
- Cam is obsessed with Fortnite right now.
- You were too, Patrick, but then you abandoned me.
- Oh my God, being abandoned, that's fucked.
- I got too into Fallout 4, 'cause Will bought it for me.
- No, you abandoned me way before that, but nice try.
- That's true, yeah.
- Yeah, there's really no excuse for you.
- Well, I'm trying to, I might play it again.
- Yeah, right, okay, sure, sure, man.
- You guys can talk about that.
- Yeah.
- Wait, let's talk about the news, dude.
- We gotta--
- Well, hold on, I never--
- Wait, can I figure out--
- The news right now.
- Yeah, I feel like there's a lot of like--
- I told you about my dentist appointment.
- Oh yeah, well, okay, go ahead.
Say the rest of your dentist appointment stuff.
- I know there's some stuff going on in the news
or whatever, but I mean--
- No, go ahead, say the dentist appointment.
- I had a crazy experience at the dentist.
- We'll push that, we'll do that next episode.
Just talk about the dentist.
- Okay.
So they put an antibiotic in my gums
and I have to use a special toothpaste
that has calcium in it.
It has like milk,
Cassian or whatever it's called.
- Casein.
I have to put milk casein on my teeth
and I have to use this mouthwash.
And they told me I can't floss my back teeth for a week.
It's like, how do you think I got here?
Huh?
What do you think of that?
(laughing)
- Should I?
- It's pretty good, dude.
- You're just doing like,
like you didn't just stand up to us.
(laughing)
- What do you think?
Do you think some open mics in Brooklyn are open?
'Cause I wanna go to...
(laughing)
- No, let's just all do like,
kinda like stand up style spiels
about what we've been up to, right?
- So, like, 'cause I've been building a lot of furniture,
right? - Yeah, yeah, okay.
- 'Cause I've been moving,
and I'm building all these furniture kits, right?
And it turns out I really don't like building furniture,
and I'm really not good at it,
which, you know, it's, the thing about building furniture,
the thing about building furniture is that it's one
of the easiest things in the world,
because it's like, think about this, right?
- Okay. - You know Legos?
Legos is a kid's toy. It's a toy for kids and they have like 3,000 pieces.
And building furniture is like the same thing as Legos except instead of like thousands of pieces,
it only has like five pieces.
Yeah, so true. That's so true.
Do you guys think that would be good?
Yeah, we could do a show. Oh, what if you did a show in a restaurant?
And you could do that there.
- Yeah, okay. - Right?
- I could be like, I could say something,
I could be like,
every time I build a piece of furniture,
I always mess it up
'cause I don't look at the steps close enough.
Like I always put on a part backwards or something.
But the thing about building, the thing about it,
that's just like an aside,
that's a really good line to use
if you're trying to do standup.
- Definitely, yeah. - Yeah, it's the thing about--
- Take notes, hey, amateurs.
These are some professionals that work here.
- The thing about messing up when you're building furniture
is that the lesson you take away from it
isn't that you should look at the instructions closer it's that you just
shouldn't build furniture anymore you don't like yeah and everybody's gonna
laugh they'll they'll feel that you know yeah I everybody's had to do it here let
me do my turn okay Legos well that reminds me of Legos are from some
fucking blonde caveman country so that reminds me of my my golf instructor
Fiorna right and she's up there she's wearing a bikini and she's showing me how
to how to use at a stroke right and I'm like hey babe could you would you mind
demonstrating yeah on my penis okay see that that works because it has kind of
like this punch of like I'm gonna I'm gonna be sexually inappropriate with this
woman yeah yeah you know it has that like yeah like yeah I mean that's
classic stand-up being sexually inappropriate with a woman yeah exactly
that's what I mean and then yeah all right Pat now you can go yeah okay and I
mean see that you could actually use that for your dentist story if I had to give
like a punch-up advice yeah right you could be like should I should I sexually
inappropriate to my dentist wait you'd be like a dentist lady I assume it's a
woman you'd be like it's three women it's three women who have to work on my
teeth I think I think I just coat that's hot I think I have a I think I have like
a like a hole in my tooth I think it's the exact shape of your pussy and I think
that's the only way to fill it I think it was okay I think it would work better if
it was a boob your boob needs to be but boobs in their mouth babies a baby kid
that's good a baby who does stand up all right Wow
okay yeah um okay and the baby and if if we wanted to like tie it to the news or
politics or something here's a line here's a line here's a line for the
political baby okay he sees the he sees the the stuff going on at the capital
and he says so i he's saying in a baby voice these people need a nap he says he
says hey so i've seen the stuff that's going on at the capital lately the past
day or the past that happened yesterday um you know and speaking as a baby those
guys seriously are wearing diapers. Okay. And it's kind of like the... These guys are
acting like me when I don't get my diaper change. You know what else you can do? I know how I act when I don't get my
diaper change because I'm a baby. If it's a newborn, if it's a newborn who's
under two weeks old, right? Uh-huh. You could be, they could be like... It's a preemie.
Yeah, they could be like, "Hey, have you seen this crap on the news recently?"
yeah it's crazy my TV's everything's upside down his baby see upside down for
a couple weeks is that true someone told me that I don't think that's real I
think babies okay see upside down for a little bit
because they sit in your stomach upside down they get their head first oh yeah
this is a pre this is a fall I have to like come come back well I mean your
- Your eyes are like mirrors, so they reflect,
your vision is upside down, I think,
and you get used to it.
Like, if you put on glasses that reflect your vision,
it'd be upside down.
After like some length of time, you just get used to it.
And you just see normal.
- So maybe they're not used to it yet.
- Yeah.
- Oh, okay.
- So let's make a baby face,
so we can work it into material.
- Oh, that's why you never put glasses on a baby.
- Okay, so this-- - Exactly.
- Well, this would kill with like pediatricians, though.
- Yeah, okay, so we go, so here's the plan, all right?
we walk into the hospital. Yeah, we gotta find the funniest baby contest at the hospital.
And we say and we get a baby to say, "Hey listen, here's a fact about babies. We,
the first time we take a poop it's green and it's called meconium. And you know even that green poop
isn't as green as this newcomer to politics Alexia Alcacio-Cortesian." That's so true.
She's so green.
Well, okay, we gotta find...
We do have to hold the funniest...
Hospital's Funniest Baby Contest.
I forgot her first name for a minute there.
We can get Simon Cowell.
We can get Simon Cowell for the hospital's funniest baby.
And then we have the funniest baby...
You're a baby.
We have the funniest baby in the hospital tell these jokes.
Yes.
Well, let's just get the 2003 American Idol crew.
Let's get Randy Savage or whatever.
Randy Jackson.
Well, he was a savage though.
let's get it. Randy Rainbow. They call him Randy Savage. They call Randy Jackson Randy Savage
because he was so savage. Yeah and Paula Abdul Jabbar and we'll get both of them
and Simon Cowell and then a celebrity. We could also get like we could get like
like Alton Brown maybe. Yeah. Ryan Seacrest is busy now. He's on SiriusXM.
He could do the character that he does on Cutthroat Kitchen so like
they'll like be judging the baby normally and then he goes like I have a
deliciously evil challenge for you and he brings out like I like you know a big
bowl that the baby has to go inside of well I don't know there's something now
that you're saying Alton Brown on cutthroat kitchen I don't want to do
that because he uses actual S&M gear for the cutthroat kitchen challenges yeah and
he uses MSG in his food yeah which could damage Madison Square Garden he takes a
keep its cubes in this he also let just like he just like acts evil on that show
so you're kind of right you know we should get he kind of gives you get all the
brown and goodies because that's the scientist and let's get David Cho and
then also so it's a half comedy half cooking challenge yeah yeah we teach
these babies to cook yeah and we'll get David Cho and Arthur Chu and but
Arthur Chu CHEW okay like a baby would do yeah so and it's a different guy
it's not the other yeah yeah can we get you know that we're like Cesar Milan to
get the train the babies to say the jokes oh yeah that's a good idea and also food
name what do you think the budget is for this five million dollars trillion
dollars a trillion dollars an episode well if we can go higher let's go higher
right yeah we can get it as high well let's let's do let's plan it out per
season okay so first season we find the winner of the the winner yeah second
season we find a baby what it's a baby yeah yeah I mean it's still a winner
Actually, you know what, I mean, we could throw a ringer in.
We could throw a ringer into the contest.
A very talented baby?
I thought we were looking for the talented baby.
No, just like a guy that looks like a baby.
No, like a guy who's really funny,
like dressed as a baby.
Like we could have like John Mulaney
once he's out of his, you know,
whatever the hell he's doing right now.
Well, he's already in a hospital,
so we could just go to that hospital.
I realize what the end goal of this is.
What?
Okay, so, the first season,
we find a baby that's the funniest
and the best at cooking, right?
the most charismatic chef.
Then we spend the next like five years
giving them like Juilliard acting training, right?
So in six years, when they're six years old,
we do a sequel to Chef called Chef Junior
about a very funny baby who's married to a big bimbo
and loves Cuban food.
- Okay. - What do you think?
- Well, where's the standup comedy?
- 'Cause we're like kind of making, were you--
the stand-up comedy will come in with John Leguizamo.
Exactly, we're creating like he can play both John Leguizamo, he can play both
Johns, Favreau Leguizamo. Yeah right but he's playing John Leguizamo in the pest.
He's not playing... He's playing John Leguizamo in Ice Age. That's right.
Which one is he in Ice Age? Slid. He, that's, oh my god. He slides on the ice.
You don't realize that? No. That's like one of the most distinctive, that was like one of the first
voices I never knew that was John Leguizamo. I never knew that was John Leguizamo. I never knew that was John Leguizamo.
I never knew who a cartoon character was. When you were a kid you were like damn
that's John Leguizamo. That's the first like that that voice you'd hear him you'd hear
that voice you go oh I know that's Sid the Sloth. Like that's if I saw him in a
movie. Well that's just because. Well the first movie I saw him in was The Pest.
Yeah well the first movie I ever saw was The Pest. No. For me it was Mario Brothers. No no no. I thought Leguizamo was an Italian.
I thought that was an Italian last name for a really long time because I didn't see the best show last year
I've never seen I've only seen the shower scene from the page. Oh, that's what I mean. I've only seen that
Can we get back on track for our baby show? Yeah, so what's it gonna be called?
It's called the honest baby. Anyway, okay, which which one which babe?
What's this called? Which one tasty, baby?
Okay
No
funny baby
the world's
the comedy snore
adventure of what if it's called like what if it's okay what if it's called like
Adventure of the world and then like people can it can be like a surprise what the show's about. Yeah, that's not bad
Yeah, yeah, no cuz for a competition show you you want it to surprise like X Factor American Idol
You wanted to surprise in the most let's say let's call it like the oldest
cook ever hunt and it's not a contest and nobody and there's no winners and no
losers because it's not a good yeah oh what's this bull crap oh it actually
surprised I'm so reeled in yeah it's actually not every episode of this how
much did this cost yeah sixty trillion dollars we can call it the worst show
the worst show of all time and then people watch the bar is low exactly
that's a really good point yeah we could get the guy who played
floop to what if we may and then we could do a show called the best show of all
time and it's the worst one mm-hmm and that's where we put that that's when we
do our French New Wave stuff you want to do French New Wave TV show called the
worst show of all time uh-huh or the best show of all time I mean yeah we can
do like it's like a series of vignettes yeah yeah yeah keep going keep going to
director smoking people's criterion Patrick uh-huh Wow you get cigarettes on
the show and then you can't put cigarettes on TV because it's French
doing that we'll show cigarettes and wine oh what about absinthe what's your
problem okay Marilyn Manson freak I had a
shower last night before I did we did this I'm tripping right now I don't
think you are I am dude I'm see absence doesn't make you trip dude I'm seriously
sure absent oh my god I'm seeing colors doesn't doesn't absence just tastes like
black licorice I've never I would imagine that it tastes like stinky alcohol yeah
I would think it probably tastes like I've ever had after the moon shine
though I am me too I had moonshine one time cuz a guy does it really tastes
like the moon it tastes exactly like cheese yeah yeah
- Yeah. - Winsleydale.
I went and did a glass shower door install
for this old, he was like a civil rights leader,
this old black dude in my hometown
who lived in the nicest old house.
He was insanely rich and he walked in,
everything was gold and shit.
And as we were leaving, he was like,
I'm gonna tip you guys something better than,
instead of money, I'm gonna tip you guys
on something priceless.
And he gave us a bottle of moonshine
that I guess his friend makes.
- This here is a drawing, a little drawing I just made of you.
(laughing)
- I've been gluing the macaroni on
the whole time you were here.
- I'm gonna tip you guys with something priceless, a kiss.
(kissing)
- Come here, let me pinch those cheeks.
- I was like, oh swag, this is gonna be awesome.
'Cause usually you get paid, you get tipped like 20 bucks
maybe, but I got home and took one sip
and just poured it out, it was horrible.
It was like the worst thing I've ever had.
I like moonshine.
I was just like--
If it tastes like apple pie.
No, see that, you've had apple,
you've had those like moonshine in a can that they sell.
This was one of those like done in like a--
Like real.
Like done in the mountains by like a guy.
Oh right, yeah, you were in the south.
Yeah, like a cartoon shack that's like
on the side of a mountain, like horizontal.
Yeah, and it's made--
Or vertical.
The steel is made out of like car parts.
Yeah.
That's your problem, you didn't mix it with anything.
You just took a sip of it.
What am I supposed to mix it with?
Apple pie, is that what you're saying?
No, you're supposed to mix it with whiskey.
That would only make it worse.
You're just, you're inventing cocktails.
Okay, I've got a cocktail for you.
Okay.
Pat, you get one shot at this.
You got my cock in your tail, pal.
No, we're not doing that.
Okay, one, eight ounce.
You get one shot, one opportunity
to make a good cocktail.
All right, all right, all right, all right.
Two ounces.
Dr. McGillicuddy's root beer.
two ounces fireball okay two ounces dr mcgillicuddy's butterscotch schnapps
so this is the cocktail that you talk about like maybe once every two weeks
what is it called and you it's called patrick's delight that's and you bring it up every you
pretend you never brought it up before and then you tell this right okay how about this traitor
Trader Joy's soyaki marinade. Trader Joy's? Trader Joy's. No I'm sticking with it. Trader
Joy's soyaki marinade and then Trader Joy's cabernet sauvignon. Okay. Half and half. Okay.
I got another one. That'll get you twisted with an oriental twist. Okay. After you I
have another one that's important that we get over this. One, you could get some amount
of gin and another amount of tonic.
They call that the "My Dad."
That's called Caleb's Dad.
My Dad, can I get the My Dad?
When my dad visited Boston, he was here for, he was there for like three days.
First day, touchdown, bought the biggest thing of New Amsterdam gin they sold in the liquor
store for like $11 and four bottles of tonic water, polished him, dude.
left me with like a that's right just tonic water and I was like god one day
dude one day I'll have that that much power I had that much power really before
sober January how's that going by the way eight days eight days sober dude nice
you should get a chip for that yeah yeah lays yeah I have been eating a lot more
chips but alright so this is my new cocktail so it's two ounces moonshine
okay two ounces honey whiskey six ounces grenadine and it's called Patrick's
threat oh yeah that's really good that's what I get for it for being mean to you
about Patrick's delight mm-hmm yeah here's my cocktail it's it's a it's a
tab of rat poison we're like from dumb and dumber right yeah and then just a
a bunch of my pee and it's called Caleb's invisibility potion.
And it actually will make you invisible if you try it out. So I'm serious, go try that
out. You'll have to get some pee out of me by jerking me off. So there's a challenge
for the listener.
Okay, six ounces aromatic bitters.
Okay.
Two ounces gin.
Right.
12 ounces Mountain Dew Voltage.
And that's called the Patrick's Tahitian Treat.
How about 16 ounces of Coors Banquet and a smile?
(laughing)
That's a good cocktail.
That's a damn good cocktail.
- What about, whatever happened to water?
Come on, Cameron.
- Yeah, how about one part A, Cameron.
- Cameron, I'm-- - Two parts O.
- I'm being sober this month,
I have to think about alcohol.
- Really, do you just drink it in your brain
before you go to sleep?
- Mm-hmm. - Yeah?
I have two 9 ABV beers waiting for me on February 1st.
It would be funny to like go like knock on Pat's door.
We should you and me go surprise him and we open up the door and he has like a sim.
He has like a thought cloud above his head that just has a beer on it the entire time.
Do you want any beer Pat?
No, no I'm sober.
We go over to hang out with Patrick and he's just sitting there holding his hand in the
shape of a beer can just walking around and it's every once in a while just
moving his hand up to his mouth. Between every sip he goes "Kh!"
So it's a new beer every time.
I think one of the first times we ever hung out it was that
what was it after like the comedy special thing or whatever and I drank
We bought like a 30 of beer and I drank most of them.
And it was supposed to be for like 13 people.
Yeah, I mean this guy loves beer.
Make no mistake.
He this morning, Patrick Doren, beer he does enjoy.
It's normal to do that.
It's normal to drink at least 13 beers.
You would have been such a good like,
you know on a pirate ship,
everybody always, they all had like fat,
useless, drunk pirate.
Yeah.
that that way I mean in another yeah and he was stupid you know ugly and no one
liked him they would just take turns spitting on him remember that guy that's
the guy who was in charge of the map yeah you would I would have been like a
really I would be I would have been like a really good like like cursed skeleton
guy who like was who like lived inside of like an agent yourself you're giving
you're you're you're not giving your personally I would have been the captain
yeah the captain of the poop deck yeah the poop deck is the top likes me and
the captain you would have been put in you would have put in you would have
been putting your poop deck in your top deck now you're to the you both go into
the brig no break now no no I would live in the break cuz I'm like it I'm already
there I drank all the grog if you don't if you don't leave me a sip of grog yeah
did remember that time when I bought a 30 rack of grog and then we're supposed to split it with the whole crew
god that was so annoying. That cost like three pieces of eight too that's so fucked up. So many shillings
my shillings. Well once we find once we find that treasure I mean
yeah and what are you gonna do? It's all gonna be worth it. You're stuck in a brig drinking grog
What do you do?
What?
Are you doing no grog January?
Yeah.
Yeah?
I've been doing no grog this month.
Dude, the grogless samurai.
Do you remember that bar rescue episode?
It's the pirate themed bar and they make a drink called grog that is literally just like
- it's what - it's - I gotta look up the fucking recipe because it's one of the funniest - it's
like blue carousel - is that how you say it?
Caracal?
I don't fucking know.
I have no - I've never -
And just like -
I know what you're talking about but I don't know how to say it.
Vodka, that's what grog is dude. Let me look this a bar rescue grog is named after a guy named grog
Do you think we could make a movie where there's one samurai on a pirate ship?
I was thinking about that since you said the grog less samurai. Yeah and call it the grog less samurai
Yeah, that would be such a good Jackie Chan movie. Honestly
That would have been the fucking coolest Jackie Chan movie
Just like him like a like a karate master on a on a pirate ship like who goes back in time basically just Shanghai noon
But instead of the Western its pirates. Yeah, right and he would he could do karate to the Kraken
That would be a chop clean. That would be a cool. Oh, man, dude a karate pirate
Yeah, the karate pirate would be so fucking amazing or if they'd done Jackie Chan instead of
Jack Sparrow Jack Sparrow. Yeah. Yeah, Jackie Sparrow Jackie. Yeah. Yeah, exactly or captain Jack Chan
That's good
Captain Jack Chan would
Yeah, yeah, yeah they could go to like
They can visit like Taiwan, right?
Yeah, good and Jackie Chan could keep being like, oh, we're going to China right now. This is China
Yeah, yeah, yeah exactly everybody's like this is he's like it's China. I'm the president of the ship. We're going to China
Be some good shit, dude. I
Can't find that recipe for grog. Here's the recipe for you. How about you spend time with your two friends instead of studying drinks?
I was I wanted to drink this with you guys. We can't drink it for over three weeks
You're doing no wrong January planning
I'm playing it. But send me that recipe because I'm gonna send you a video of me drinking grog tonight.
All right, then I gotta find it.
Joyful grog. The only way for me to find it is to watch that bar rescue episode.
So maybe I could share my screen with you guys so we could just watch the episode. No, you're gonna be jealous of my grog tonight though.
Yeah? Yeah. Your penis?
Not my penis. Can we stop talking about penises? That doesn't even make any sense.
For just- Like with grog. You make everything so dirty all the time. You make everything about grog all the time.
You got grog, you're grog obsessed dude.
I hate hanging out with this fucking guy, he won't shut up about grog.
Complete grog hound.
He's not going out unless he gets his grog.
Just walking up to just a guy, a guy walking the party and just everyone going oh my god
just hide the grog.
Pat just walking down like the French Quarter in New Orleans, just walking to every bar,
do you have grog?
No.
And just going to the next one just over and over again.
That's the next Jollibee documentary.
We're gonna take you to that bar where they made Grog.
- Oh no, it's closed down.
They closed down because they wouldn't
accept John Taffer's help.
- We're gonna reopen it with the money
from all our shows and movies.
- That's true, yeah.
- True, all of our media empire.
- Oh, speaking of media empire,
started watching Succession, Caleb.
- Oh, pretty fucking cool.
- Yeah, you're gonna be in a succession with me.
- You already did that.
- Wait, what?
- You did that last time that I said that word
I haven't said it since. You said, Caleb, I remember you saying that we had to watch
Succession so we'd understand an impression that you could do. So I want
you to do the impression now. Well I haven't seen it yet. Well I want to see
it. I haven't seen it yet. I don't care if you haven't seen it in months. I don't even know who it was of.
Dad, Dad I um... Alright, what did he say? Is this the main guy you're trying to do?
Yeah, yeah. What's his name? It's pretty bad so far. It's been months! I told you it's been months!
It's not my fault. Hey dad. Um, I'm gonna can I play video games?
God damn it son. No
That's not that good. Hey dad. Can I can't look at the guy look at you?
I can't believe you told me to watch that show so you can do this impression for me
I can't remember an issue on it in months. I don't remember what they sound like even
If it's a good if it was a good impression, you wouldn't have to I don't that's not you
Okay, you do an impression of them then?
Hey, what's up? I never said I heard a good one. It was a month. I was did you not hear that it's what?
Then let me start over okay. Hey, what's up? It's Tweety bird
What's up, Tweety bird? It's me the it's me the cat
What's up, see Cameron just do something like this do that. It's easy
Give me a character then I think I saw a weird cat do a
Hmm Homer Simpson
Okay, well we discover give me another give me another talent Marge Simpson
Okay, but Lisa Simpson
Yep Bart Simpson
Apu Simpson Homer crazy Simpson
That's good. That's some good shit. Yeah. You might be an impressionist bastard, dude.
I mean, I always knew I was. He could be the man of 101 voices. Yeah. Yeah,
they basically were gonna cast me in Master of Disguise, but I didn't want to because
of some of the offensive things in that movie. Okay, do the Turtle Club, then. Am I a turtle?
Damn am I a turtle
What?
What just happened? I'm a damn turtle now
Turtle no god damn. I'm the freaky turtle my clothes are funny
Around a big round sure admit. I look like a turtle right now
I'm kind of like a tiny turtle
He's not tiny. He's a normal turtle. Yeah. He's pretty big when it comes to turtles
Do you remember the look in that movie where the bad bullshit bad the bad guy keeps a lot doing his evil laugh
But he has any farms. That's that's uh, that's Brent Spiner. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's
So many times to me too. This guy played dead. What if the life he's my dad
Yeah, have you ever heard the story about the turtle club scene? Oh, dude
Wait, did something happen in the middle of the turtle club scene that they had to have a moment of silence for yeah
Dana Carvey farted in the suit
And it killed one of the camera and they had to have a moment of silence and then he farted
Is the ultimate disrespect yeah, yeah, you know yeah that scene in the turtle club scene where he bites off the guy's nose
That actually happened and they had to stop filming
He's improvising good. Yeah, yeah, Dana Carvey classic improv. Yeah that motherfucker can do it
Yeah, he had it in him. He had the devil. Yeah, he actually improvised all those costumes and
them every every improv show is somebody being possessed by the devil mm-hmm
that's the funny one yeah mm-hmm the funny devil the fun yeah all of them are
the funny devil is the name of my blog where I review improv shows yeah yeah
yeah what do you give today the funny devil today's South Park episode was a
bit uninspired and a far cry from their former glory that's a first line of a
the funny devil post damn my teeth are looking whiter we should become comedy
journalists that is that's comedy journalist is one of the funniest jobs
in such a sick job did so it's just like one of like like it's like it's
impressive to find a way to be lamer than like a journalist you know what I
mean yeah and a comedian taking the worst of both and which are two yeah -
very very bad yeah and when I nestle myself in right there yeah like imagine
they're being like like a like there has to be like theater journalism it's like
it's like it's like it's like you know how you know how blade gets like the
good part of being a vampire and the good part of being a human yeah as I
being a comedy journalist it's like you get the bad part of both it's like an
inverse play all comedy journalists are like blade yeah like Wesley Snipes mm-hmm
cuz yeah their taxes they get like the like sensibility of a journalist and
like the sexual like paraphilia of being a comedian. Yeah exactly. Yeah. So they're just
like sitting. Yeah they get the they get the sense of humor of a journalist and then like
the the ability to to share information well of a comedian. Yeah. They just sit watching like
Talladega Nights and like this is overrated. I wish I was raping someone right now. If only.
Yeah, that's a bad job, dude.
[Laughter]
Yeah.
It's a very tough job.
Someone's going to cut that.
No!
And post it out of context.
A podcast about list clips is going to post that without context.
I'm not doing my own voice.
It says, "Caleb's a confession."
There you go. You got a clip right there for you.
I've got this.
There's two lies in there because, one,
Tally Day and I's rules, and two,
I've never even had sex.
Okay, what a long do you guys want to hear I have it do you guys want to hear mine another joke about comedy journalists?
Yeah, yes comedy journalists sit there. We're watching a stand-up stand-up special and they say
Yeah, I'm I'm not enjoying this it's way too funny
Dad's no true, dude. Yeah. Yeah, I wish this was about school
Yeah, I wish his dad was mentioned more. Yeah, can you talk about how your dad died?
There's not enough jokes about home. You talk about how my dad died. Yeah
Yeah, this is this says nothing about me, which is why I don't yeah, where's nothing to do with the timeouts I got as a child
What happened to everybody had those spankings they really liked
That's it that's them trying comedy and then later this is and then later they're writing about Freddy got fingered
Not once does someone get spanked and they enjoy it in this movie
one star yeah those people are fucking sick yeah actually I remember we all
remember being chained to the radiator as a child yeah and liking it a lot and now
we have tattoos where the scars and the chains left on our arms we love that we
all had that we all had that one girl in our class that we pushed down the stairs
in first grade yeah because we liked them everyone used to hide farts in their
desks and then open them up when they needed a smile right we all have that
one grog drinking ass friend that's real comedy that one grog drinking friend
He's a comedy journalist and a pirate the groggy journalist
The donkey journalist
I don't think we've ever talked about it, but Jeff Tiedrich's website is called the smirking chimp. Yeah, that's so sick dude it rocks
That's a really funny band name - one second. Let me look hit a band. Yeah, you didn't know that fuck
It is I probably did not you know with alligator. You know I probably did know that and then just forgot about it
the music alligator
Listen his band's name is alligator music band
That rocks he's the best
It sucks it sucks that he's just got no job come January 20 the name. Oh my god, okay
He's the lead guitarist and vocals for alligator music band. Do you want to hear the names of his other band members?
yeah yeah stumpy swag John Chazen Eric Lundberg Sam man and V Don Bogut the
third V Don Bogut the third he looks like Eric Clapton. Yeah dude I'm the third guy named V Don Bogut.
yeah well we've had three of us yeah keep it going right yeah my family
actually got got cursed by a Star Wars witch three generations ago we should
play some of the alligator music band no no you could play your songs rocket okay
all right play one of their songs dude play some magic wait that was him yeah
Oh my god, that's sick. You couldn't even tell right?
Jeff's daughter is the founder of awkward zombies an ongoing video game webcomic in a comedic fashion
Damn, I'm just looking at this at this uh
This website. We should get into doing webcomic nerdy webcomics. Dude, Jeff Tudor is 5'6"
Yes! Yo!
Welcome to the club. Birthplace Rockaway, New Jersey. God chose his profession dude. Rockstar
are. Exactly. Yeah, rock away young Teej Rich. Rock away indeed. Damn. Yeah, we should definitely
get into nerdy pop culture web comics. I think that would be next in our media empire maybe.
Yeah, web comics is a good place to expand. We could do like, it would be called like
um... Something that's in between XKCD and CTRL ALT DELETE. Yeah, something that's like
informative in a very kind of sly way. What was XKCD even? What was that?
XKCD is like a comic for like programmers and nerds and science.
Yeah, it's kind of a genius comic, right? So I'm sure you've seen comics like,
like you probably love Nightcrawler, Garfield and X-Men, Dilbert. Those are probably your kind of
things. For me and Cam growing up, it was all about like numbers, XKCD, like, you know.
And they're stick figures?
Um, yeah, because art isn't really that important.
It's more about the message.
Well, is it supposed to be like binary numbers?
Science and math is more important than art.
Yeah, so it's stickmen because the arms and legs are ones and then the head is a zero,
so it's kind of a binary joke.
So, so, I did understand that.
No, see, that's, no, you're definitely too stupid for something like XKCD.
You probably should read like Batman or like Super Hero Man or some bullshit like that.
- I've been doing that.
- I mean, yeah, me and Caleb would read like,
you know, stuff like Akewood,
that's like kind of hard to understand
and like intellectual, or like that one,
what's it, like, sad something pictures
about for something children, depressed,
something, the one that's about depression.
- Oh, we should make a webcomic about depression.
- Yeah, see, I'm into depression and stuff like that,
and like websites like the--
- Pictures for sad children.
- I like the Dictionary of Obscure Sorrows.
I kind of go on there and I press random
and I hit one and I say, yeah, I've felt that.
- Yeah. - You know?
I'm kinda that guy.
- Yeah, I basically, I have like this room in my house
that's filled with like various tinctures
that are kind of like different like mental instabilities
and like different like spirits that are trapped
in like jars and test tubes and I like open them up
and it like kind of puffs out and I can kind of like tell
what kind of sickness or like brain disease it is
and I've basically, I like recognize them.
- That's really scary and I appreciate it.
- Are you like me, like you're an empath?
- No, no, I'm not an empath, I'm a--
well I've become an empath recently I'm an empath as an eminent path and I'm on
the path to greatness yeah being the greatest rapper of all time
and Patrick's following an eminent path to the gates
let's fucking go that's good yeah that's pretty good yeah but I am an empath and
I feel your pain Patrick yeah and when we had funny I could feel I mean I'm a
reverse empath and that like I feel my own pain and I can like tell how I'm
feeling most yeah mm-hmm wouldn't win by hell I can't even do that hell Wow so
you're not even a path dude no you're not even on my path no no see I'm an
empath and of my path and a fem path and yeah because I understand when women are
bad I see where I can tell when a woman's been here yeah yeah it's funny
than what I said. I see a floating pink trail of like dust like I'm like I'm
following somebody in a Skyrim quest. Yeah when I see when I see a woman I
immediately go into VATS. A fempath is when you can... I'm identifying the percentage of every point of her body and the
likelihood that I could touch it. Yeah it's all zero. Zero zero zero and then I just
escape the vet system. Yeah scientists gave uh gave the first guy fem path powers
today the ability to detect women's emotions the second they installed the
chip into him he had a seizure because the nurse was in the room. Whoa. Or he
killed himself. Yeah or like it was kind of like an alternate punchline. Yeah or
if or wait let me if it's if we're doing punchlines let's go funny ready? All
right yeah that's what I usually say when I'm writing jokes. If we're doing
punchlines let's make it funny. Let's think of a funny one. Okay listen he's a
fempath right so there's this guy he's a fempath the scientist game of fempath
disease he's the number one guy in the world to have this thing. Standing on stage describing what a fempath is.
So there's this thing called a fempath that I invented with my friends when we were doing a
podcast so basically there's a guy who can feel all the different things that a
girl can feel and I think that he could see things that when he goes into a VAT
system he sees girls penises and then you keep press him but then he gets the
ability to feel a girl and then he has a any shits his pants you shits his damn
pants there's a girl in the room so a little something like that ladies and
gentlemen thank you right yeah that's and that's your five minutes and that's
my five minutes dude yeah I mean the tricks the trick and that's you know if
you're a really good comedian you don't need five minutes exactly just need one
one second for one facial tick.
Yeah, for one noise.
Yeah, just be like...
Just go upstairs, upstairs, upstairs, shriek.
Just go upstairs and shriek.
Well, it is upstairs.
It's up a couple of steps usually.
Yeah.
I mean, okay, here's an idea for a gimmick, a stage gimmick, right?
When it's your turn to perform, you go upstairs, you go to the floor above and they have to
listen to you perform like through the ceiling.
So it's really muffled.
And you know that nobody's on their phones because they have to be giving their full attention
to even hear what you're saying.
Yeah.
It'd be like a good alt comic kind of like thing.
That'd be a funny ass alt comedy bit, dude.
Yeah.
What about an alt comedy bit where you talk into your shoe like a phone?
Uh-huh.
Right?
Yeah, hey, hey, alt comedy?
No thanks.
I'm into salt comedy, which is what white people think is seasoning.
That's right.
I'm into gestalt comedy.
Yay!
That's right.
I can't wait till Stan Oaks back so I can try out all my new ideas. Yeah, all my new ideas
like what if a dick could fart. Yeah. I'm gonna go dress like a prince. Hey guys, you
might have heard of a little thing called alt comedy. It's kind of like when comedy
is weird if you haven't heard of it but you can just like look it up. But you might have
heard of a little thing called alt comedy and I think that stuff sucks so bad and listen
if you're in the audience and you did that before that's your fault comedy. That's right.
Yeah, I'm more of an intellectual comedian.
I'm kind of a, I like wordplay and puns.
I kind of, I'm like almost a poet,
so you might call me a thought comedian,
like you'll have a thought while you hear me do my set.
You might have a couple of thoughts.
I'm pretty thought-provoking, actually.
I'm kind of like the Jonas Salk of comedy.
Yeah.
'Cause I can't sit down.
Yeah, alt comedy.
I'm making sure people aren't sitting down.
Hey, yeah, alt comedy, when I listen to something like that,
it makes me want it it makes me want to yell help comedy that's right
that's like a moron comedian yeah mm-hmm you're like a ball comedian I'm a 50s
comedian that do a lot of Polish jokes that is true actually yeah yeah I have
to go pee pee see that'd be part of my bit yeah yeah I go up dress as a prince
and I'd say I have to go pee pee the prince of pee pee Prince of no pee well
they I would walk up and they'd say okay it's a prince of comedy he has to be
he's doing comedy and he's dressed as a prince. A prince wouldn't do something
that he's not the best at but then it would subvert the expectation by me
going "I have to go pee pee!" and they go "oh he's a prince of pee"
"oh wrong prince I had the wrong prince in my mental" yeah it's not a bad idea
pretty good. What do you guys think? I mean any of the things we mentioned in this episode
are fair game for anyone who's you know getting into stand-up. You can you could
just say like stuff from the show if you want. Yeah I don't care. People already do
that in real life. That's true. Yeah you know that people tomorrow at the office
gonna be like hey Jim you have a grog. It is funny like I know like there's people
are always like oh like people always repeat like Chapo bits or come town bits
to their friends to seem funny. It's so funny to imagine someone trying to do
that with this podcast. It's like going up to the friends be like, "Hey man, I just
ate a huge poop in line at McDonald's."
Yeah, I told them I'm gonna eat a dog's... Hey, hey, Bottoms Green Day, am I right?
Hey, going to the TGI Friday's later to eat a dog's pussy. What's up?
Yeah, what do you think about that?
Nobody ate my pitbull, it tastes like cheese.
Pitbull tastes like a bratty old pussy bitch.
Yeah, doing vats, I'm a girl,
I'm a pussy.
I break old man's hymen.
I break a hymen like nobody business.
I break in your hymen. Can I break your hymen?
Can you speak up please?
Can I break your hymen?
Yeah, have you been listening to that
podcast that is impossible
to google again?
Yeah, just be like oh, it's called podcast about list and they're like I'm googling it and getting zero results
I don't know. I don't think this exists. I think my son is
Doesn't make any damn sense I googled that I get top 10 podcasts and the top one is cereal. Yeah
You get a cereal. I don't think Sarah Koenig would say that
But imagine if she did it would sound a little like this
I ate a dog's pussy. I was eating a dog's pussy
Yeah, I have
ten father-in-laws
They got good music for that show cereal well they yeah
It's just like like a song that a kid invents when they sit at a piano for the first time
Mm-hmm. That's uh, it's the same succession is the same kind of thing really they stole they stole the they stole the theme song from it's
Just the epic Rick and Morty and Morty. It's just the music
It's just the one you know
the song and Rick and Morty when the evil guy comes and he goes like and it goes like and it's like the piano music
Starts playing. No that one the guy with the eye patch the evil Morty one dad
Yeah, dad. Yeah, dad. That's what I mean. Yeah, but they play like this epic music. I
I haven't heard that epic music.
Oh, you guys aren't really intellectual.
Yeah, it's like the Nathan For You theme song is used in car commercials all the time.
Or it was.
Yeah, and it's like the Dat 70s theme songs on my dad's iPod.
Yeah.
It's kind of like how they put Yoda in Soulcalibur.
Yeah, yeah. And they put Mario on the TV.
And Smash Brothers.
Did you know that that, I found out like two, three years ago,
that Dat 70s show theme song was an actual song?
yeah you couldn't tell no I don't here's the rule if they don't say the name of
the show yeah it's and it's just a song they picked not well yeah if they don't
say the theme song the taxi 70 show then that's a song the taxi wasn't I think it
was written for taxi but they said they say they say this that we were watching
taxi and it's true and they say let's go taxi with the piano with the electric
piano that's true yeah if you if you read all that because if they play the
t-note the a note the X note and the I note yeah yeah also it was it was written
in a taxi so there's a lot of ways that you're wrong here Patrick yeah we don't
have to go there's something is called Angela and Angela is Spanish for taxi I
don't think that's true Patrick I think Angela Spanish for angel then I'm
thinking of a different language what language is taxi there's Angela a taxi
it's Chinese maybe it's Chinese Mandarin speaking Chinese reacting in a Chinese
way just a very very different way to talk
Chinese is a different way to talk?
What's different about it?
Yeah, what's so different?
Can you pinpoint some of the key differences?
Well, I mean, come on, it's a different language.
They speak Chinese, and that's different.
And Chinese is a language.
It is.
Is it?
Yes.
Okay, wait.
What?
No, because I thought that like Chinese wasn't a language and it's Mandarin or Cantonese.
You thought they were just making noises?
No.
I didn't think Chinese people were just making noises.
Come on, dude.
I thought they weren't speaking a language.
I thought they were, I didn't think they were making noises, I thought they were making
words.
I think, actually, you might, I think Chinese, I think it's Mandarin, Chinese, and Cantonese,
right?
But it's, it's, the, the, both of them are technically Chinese language.
Yeah.
- If you said-- - That's what I meant.
That's what I meant, but I'm not smart enough
to fucking say that. - If you said someone
was speaking Chinese, somebody wouldn't be like,
"That's wrong, that's not true."
- Maybe a Chinese person. - It's just different types,
right, I mean, well, yeah, but they wouldn't,
they would say it in a way you couldn't understand anyway.
- One thing that is cool about China
is that there's so many different weird dialects
that sometimes-- - That are normal to them.
- People in China, well, no, 'cause if you're
from one part of China, you go to another part of China,
they're speaking a version of Chinese
that you just sometimes can't even understand.
So it's like if you went to--
I mean, it's like--
- If you went to California and they started talking
and you were like, "You might as well be speaking
"Chinese to me, brother."
- It's like if you go to the bayou.
I mean, not to get back to the Cajun stuff.
I think that's the closest thing.
- The closest thing we have to Chinese is Cajun.
(laughing)
- But you still know when you're in the bayou that they're,
I mean, you can just guess that they're asking for like
shrimp or to go to sleep.
Like it doesn't matter what they're saying,
you're like, "I get it."
- Those are the two things on end
either you're in shrimp, you're you're you're you want shrimp, you are in jail or you're
sleeping or you're casting a spell. It's one of those four things and I can tell based
on your facial features which one it is. Yeah I can tell I can tell based on whether you're
like wearing a skull over your head or not. Yeah exactly. All right boys it's been a lovely
It's been a lovely afternoon. Patrick's waking up right now. I am. I've been up
since like... I got up a couple hours ago but I'm still tired. It happens. Maybe you have
the coronavirus. Don't... don't do that to me. Don't say that. I think you have it dude.
You should go get checked. Don't say that to me. Don't say that to Patrick. I'm just saying.
That's like abuse. That's like friend abuse. All right. Pat, you're clear. No matter what
symptoms you may exhibit, you don't have it. Okay. That's better. You think that Patrick
being tired is a symptom you don't think it's because he stayed up till now
Wikipedia that's all his fault all right bye bye bye