come back and make a bet
and receive a bite
snow we're not doing that
for what maybe this is a new get are you a citizen of the day we are going to
that we would have had a this is not a this is how the sausage gets made a
kind of workshop as you know
between before a lot of these episodes you guys might
these these podcasters they have they have some they have some crazy bits and
riffs they're funny as fuck they're just endless that's what we do it for
bits and they and they and they riff endlessly yeah and you know it might
seem like we're doing it on the spot but a lot of these we develop beforehand and
we thought maybe we do a workshop episode today. So this one Patrick is one of those one of
those wheels that a child uses where they press a button and it lands on an
animal yeah and it makes a noise. So this is called animal wheels but... I thought it was fighting its cats.
you know what that's what that's actually one of the maybe that's one of the
symbols on the wheel of symbols. The kid turns it yeah like it's like what's
this and he turns it and it's a picture of us fighting as yeah yeah that's true
that could be.
The us fighting as cats says.
Get that cat out of here. Get that cat out of here. No i'm fighting the cat.
Yeah you're a cat. No you're a cat too.
Wow wow wow wow wow wow okay that one's good that's a good bit but it doesn't
have much riffing okay it's kind of too much on the bit side of that to two guys
two guys okay wait two guys they're both trying to play with the toy the cat toy
we're both trying to play the toy that does they're playing with a cat toy the
toy we were just talking or maybe they're playing with a cat toy do you
you guys ever think about the those cat towers that they scratch and that that
might actually be really nice to do that yeah yeah cuz I'd be on there like mm-hmm
and if that was on the wheel ago me scratching the cat pole
so I could go to sleep right now you can go to sleep I could it's so horrible in
here is I feel great and here we are you can wait better than us to to hear for an
extra hour okay so first of all I'd like to get one of those little AC you know I
know we need we don't we need a fan or you guys really think it's hot in here
it's not hot it's just so stuff muggy oh my god you got you I mean I'm in
Northeastern is sitting here for an out now get so fucking muggy in the northeast
I can sit here for forever this is a you're in your muggy in New York City oh
Oh yeah. Yeah, I got mugged last night.
Not a joke.
No, that's what you meant.
They stole my AirPods.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
That's, I'm actually joking.
That would have been so funny to wait until we're recording to tell us that you got mugged.
Also, if someone steals your AirPods, that's...
They have a geotag.
You deserve that.
Yeah, you deserve that.
No, they shouldn't have those in the first place.
They have a geotag.
They have a geocache.
Geocache yeah, you fall you go to the location on the map you give me my air pods back
I know you have my air pods the geotag. I have the tattle phone app. Yeah, that is true
Like what do you what the fuck give those back? Yeah? I got your pods. Yeah, I can't
Wired headphones for so long fucking way better. I bought air pods
The thing about like everyone I saw these articles like the day that I bought them all these articles came out where it's like our
AirPods out wired earphones are the new thing and it was just like
Lily Rose Depp is wearing wired headphones and you wish that you had
you had stayed with the new thing you're kind of mad that you know it's just
yeah I'm saying there was not a bunch of articles that said wire look it up on
the on the on the like stuff he looks like that probably true Google what's
cool today. FUD mag. What's the new cool thing today? Yeah. I'm gonna look up what's the cool
thing. How did you find lots of articles about- Because people were complaining about the things.
People like there's like people complain about this shit all the time. Like some 30 year old
complains that like oh like uh Gen Z is like wearing uh Gen Z is wearing stuff that I wore
in middle school and now looks stupid. This is skateboarder brain. I know yeah. Skateboarders
are truly the biggest posers in the world. I think I just am. I'll take that I guess.
I was expecting to say there was like an article that said like they fry your brain or something.
Well that's what I was expecting. Yeah that's what I was expecting.
Bluetooth radiation. Also I feel like you get something and then immediately it's just like
this thing sucks. This thing actually sucks and is bullshit.
But it's not like it was on CNN. It's not like it was breaking news.
I was always more bullshit and sucked those breaking that I don't think you
should need an air quality look really stupid look stupid and they are there
don't I'm not I like this I like the spatial audio when I see somebody Apple
music is so good what is spatial audio you don't know non-air pod use it's when
you can play it plays a sound only in the left side no you can you can hold
you can hold it down and it noise cancels and then you hear a threat so it
it sounds like it's in 360. What does that mean? It sounds like I just love
360. You hate technology. I love technology. You don't. I love new apps. You do like new
apps. You do, that's true. I love new apps and I love new games. Yeah. I just don't,
I do still mentally detract kind of points when I meet somebody for the first time and
they have AirPods on. Definitely. For me, yeah, I can't stand Bluetooth headphones in
general. I think that it is, I think it is the stupidest thing ever that people were
like like that that these companies are like oh we're making new headphones but
that you have to charge and people are like oh I want that I'll pay more money
for that well I think it's actually so the audio quality is actually pretty
good but that doesn't it doesn't matter you're still there's nice useless the
ones that are the what the ones that are no it's not useless you can walk away
from whatever it's connected to just have your phone in your pocket
somebody's not a runner now I am or I've run and I would just hold my phone or
put in my pocket. That's the one thing that I would think that is useful for.
But when I see like people like on the train with them or something or even just
like sitting at your computer with them. Also, you can be complete... Alright, here's honestly the
benefit of a Bluetooth headphones. You can sit, you can be completely naked and
that's true. And you do stuff with your hands in your house and still have headphones in.
That is true. Sometimes I wish I could have a pocket on my underwear. I could have a pocket on my underwear.
Well, I'm not gonna say that Bluetooth headphones are completely useless.
I used to do it. I think it's very stupid. I used to clench my phone between my butt
cheeks while I do the dishes. Yeah, that's pretty sick. And now I don't have to do
that anymore. Yeah, I mostly, I usually when I'm in that situation I just, I just
play, I just don't use headphones. I don't, I actually don't like wired
headphones at all. I'm thinking about every time that I've worn wired
headphones and I've been trying to do something and it's just like, like me
going on the train and then getting like stuck in that the wire gets stuck in the
turnstile.
I don't think that's ever happened to me.
No, it happens to me on doorknobs, but in the turnstile, what are you doing on the turnstile
that the wire gets caught?
Well, I'm trying to slide it.
I'm trying to go through.
You're trying to slide it into the space to the side of it.
And then...
Yeah, I just hate when it gets like, when I'm using wired headphones and the wire gets
get caught in the door handle of a taxi driving by and I get dragged along for
ten blocks. Yeah, when I get when I'm falling out of a window and my wireless
headphones, I actually catch a gargoyle on the corner like that, because I
survive. I don't like that.
Yeah, when the door or the turn style pulls that out of the headphone jack and
then your headphone jack doesn't work anymore. I do I can't bring out the
whole
subway station. They take
yeah it's annoying yeah yeah have you guys ever had the the i think that's as
embarrassing as having your pants pulled down is having your phone unplugged yeah
this and remember back when stuff would just keep playing yeah yeah touch when
stuff would just yeah what the worst part is when they don't pull when that
doesn't get pulled out and yeah your headphone jack is like partially broken
and it's every once in a while just play a snippet yeah just out loud and then go
back to the wire headphones do the it and you have to like twist it yeah but
but that doesn't do that anymore.
- What's the most embarrassing thing that you can,
besides like porn.
- Probably peeing my pants and pooping on the floor.
- As a, no, I mean a sound.
- Naked.
- Admitting to your crush. - Naked in court.
- Admitting that one time I peed and pooped.
- Admitting that you love your crush in court
while you pee your pants.
- Your headphones, your headphones,
they like come out and you just hear your voice
coming from under like,
later, earlier I peed on the floor
I pooped all over the floor in my into my pants and I hope my crush doesn't and my
crush is Veronica and I really want to eat pee and poop and I don't know why I
recorded this and I recorded it so loud so everyone could it in a super volume
oh no my bluetooth speaker accidentally connected to my phone yeah my headphones
came out and it defaulted to the giant boom box on my back all completely
pre-recorded I was hanging out with this these guys like we were all skating and
like what is it it was it this did or was it these guys get your story straight
huh you said I was hanging out with this duh like you were gonna say this dude
and then all the sudden the story was a bunch of guys well there's a guy it was
a bunch of areas a bunch of us were skating and then he like he saw on doodoo
mag that one guy to hang out with isn't cool anymore and he had to redo his whole
story there's actually a bunch of guys cuz I
Who hangs out with just one dude?
Can I speak? Didn't you see Fart Weekly said that one dude sucks?
Well, continue. The guy he had like music playing from his Bluetooth speaker, but he was going like
It was one guy. It was one guy in a group of guys, and he was going to the thing
He was going to like a spot so that he could like go and then skate this ledge
So he was playing this song and all you could hear like he would go away and all you'd hear is like
*imitates the music*
Yeah, like dance hall stuff. Whoa
Like see not no like why don't you just leave us his phones in his pocket? Why doesn't he just leave it there?
I really that he was cool. I think that people who play
Speaker music on the street are like crazier than the craziest like I know
I can't imagine like wanting to do that
Yeah, the worst thing now is like the music what the music was like bad
But now it's like you can like go somewhere and it's just somebody watching like tick tocks on full volume
And on the train and you hear like like yeah, this is my new car or like yeah
I'm like that tick-tock
I just it to me like like that that sucks
But I can least I can at least understand where it's like oh, I have my phone and I'm doing something
Yeah
like when I see so like there'll be like
Somebody like bikes by and they have like a blue tooth for my kids in their backpack like playing their their favorite music
music that everyone that's safer than having headphones in as a yeah bike in
that you kind of that makes I guess okay when you're biking I guess that makes
sense but it's still just the people walking to it just is weird to be all
completely alone I guess that the thing you're doing I guess the argument would
be like that's what like if you're like I guess I just wouldn't be listening I
wouldn't listen to music if it was between wearing head not a bike wearing
headphones and playing a speaker I would do that I need to listen to my music
every day you need your tunes I'm on I'm on a no I'm on a no music break really
music break. A no music break. Hell, I'm on a no music break. I'm having, I have
nothing playing in my headphones. I'll leave my headphones at home for the next
couple of days. Yeah. Yeah, I'm sick of just, just walking around. I'm just, all
I'm thinking about is these fucking Blondie songs I'm listening to. I just
don't like them. I love, I found all my Pet Shop Boys remixes. Nice. That I made.
Very cool. Yeah. I've been listening to those. It's such a drag to pick what
- I like listening to music to listen to.
I like listening to music while I'm walking around,
but that's the reason I would take it.
- There's walking around music
and then there's at home music.
- I don't think that's necessarily true.
- I never listen to music at home.
- I listen to music, yeah, I guess I don't,
I listen to music much more when I'm walking around,
but also I'll listen to music when I'm doing the dishes
or some really menial thing.
- Do you not just sit there and listen, what the hell?
- 'Cause I usually watch movies or like,
actually I listen to music when I read.
I do that's probably the most I have it on constantly. Yeah, I think I have to shower
with music on. I know it's very funny. Yeah, it is funny to be a grown man who showers with music.
I don't care. It's just funny every time because every time that we're all three of us are together
somewhere and you're like, I'm going to take a quick shower and then I just hear all the
I don't listen to Blink 182 in the shower. What do you listen to in the shower?
You need to listen to a song that's like, first you wash your hair,
then you wash your face.
Yeah, what? I'm just listening to my music.
This is my favorite song.
Time to turn the shower off.
And then you hear Patrick go, "I don't want to turn the shower off! I'm not done!"
You start the song.
Yeah, the song restarts and then I turn the shower off, and the song restarts.
You turn the shower on.
shower on. I don't have any clean you get shampoo. You put it on your hair.
Then you wash your hair. Then you don't check off in the shower that will take
too long and clog the drain. Patrick does a homer doe
unless you're the only one who uses the shower, but it's still kind of gross.
Whoa
yeah
Yeah, I don't know like I think that it's good to have music on in the shower. I don't think there's anything wrong with it
It's all funny. It's I
It's yeah, I think it's a normal thing to do. I think the thing that's funny
Was that you were doing it at someone else's house. That's what made me laugh to do it
It's like boring in there, but that's that's the good part of the shower. That's why people come up with good ideas in the show
Yeah, I do genuinely do come up with good ideas that it's crazy
That's true that I most of my good ideas. I feel because I just heard somebody talk about this the other day
It's like that's like the closest the waking person gets to being like
Like that the 30 minutes before you fall asleep where you're sitting in bed. That's a little bit of shower
I think it's also cuz like a constant state of that
I think that like when coming up with ideas is easier like if you do it regularly
I guess like it's like a they they do like creativity studies or whatever where it's like
oh if you like try to write at the same time every day yeah and you'll it'll get
better you'll get better at it and it'll be easier to come up with stuff and then
you just if you're always in the shower when the when you're in the shower you
know I have to think of ideas and they think like what if there's a crazy
invention that could change the world I'm trying to really most of my ideas I
just gotta leave my penis in my balls alone on the shower because I'll just sit
there no I'm speed bagging I'm yeah just smack them back and forth I'm just doing
different stuff in the shower of course I have come on you got that never have
sticky racing stripe down your leg.
(laughing)
- I don't think I have.
- It's really, it's definitely something that
I probably did as a teen and then realized,
oh, this is actually like so nasty.
- How cruel is God that he makes hot water
do a science experiment when it touches cum?
- Yeah, it's crazy.
- What the fuck is that?
- It's crazy what it does.
- What, like, it turns into--
- It's literally oobleck.
- It actually is, dude.
That is like the cruelest fact of nature,
is that when hot water touches come, it turns into super glue immediately.
That's how you know God didn't want us jacking off in the shower. Absolutely,
yeah. If you have somehow the like endurance, the like tenacity to jack off
in a cold shower, yeah, then you are to you. The first time I ever heard the
word gelatinous was on the bus when like a kid was, my friend was like talking
about jacking off in the shower and he's like, yeah, just make sure like you're
not facing the water or else it'll become gelatinous.
I was like what does that mean? I thought that no you have to do is you
have to you have to peek open the shower curtain a little and just come on to
the best
come on to your
doors cracked open to see a little like
and off to the floor bath, aiming into the toilet and then you get out of the
shower. Do you just step on it? You're a shag bath
oh damn that's just that bit was actually good though dude I'm that would be a
good bit the bits in the riffs today or just you know it's all do we think we
come up with any good bits or riffs so far that we could maybe use I think this
is the we're gonna delete this episode after we got it I gotta ask myself
delete this episode after I got it I doubted myself as a huge poser I'm a
huge poser it's cool to admit it now actually I really know poser is actually
it's like based these days. Yeah, it's actually based as fuck to be a poser.
That is based as fuck to be a shrub. That's a good bit. What was that?
Saying it's based to be a poser? Yeah. That's actually a good bit. Yeah,
that's a might be a good riff. I love this bit. If you take it to another
level, it could be a good riff. What the hell? No, it's not a riff. It's
more of a bit. No, riffing is what you do to a bit. Riffing is like...
What's the difference? Riffing is like the funny ass shit that follows a
good ass bit. Yeah. Shit. And it... Riffing, like...
bits are actually good, but riffing whip sack when it happens. Okay, I'm starting
to understand a little more. I think yeah, Dr Pepper whips asked Dr Pepper does
you and I fuckin what the thing about like brutalist architecture is it
actually whip sack to twenty eighteen is just like the worst time for language
and every white person. I would have said that whips ass bro. Oh, you're
worried about white people using language wrong. I would have personally
in the antebellum south but go ahead I would have said that was the worst time
for language do the horrific racial epithets that people were hurling what's
an epithet I'm gonna you may say what you put on your gravestone you say yeah
WAP. Wappy Wapper. That actually made me very sad. Okay that's actually a good bit.
Actually made me very sad to hear that yeah makes me sad too yeah I you know we
having fun. I think I've discovered an underground Polish mafia.
You know what I saw today? I've been getting these DMs from a crazy person.
He sends me like full-on, like I've showed you him, the German guy.
He sends a selfie and then he sends, like he's an older man, and then
he sends me a bunch of stuff about how his rights in Germany are being
stripped or something yeah and he sent me something today and he said like it said
like good evening blah blah blah per me and and then he tagged somebody and
their at was Polack hunter and I was like what and I clicked it and it was a guy
named hunter Polack holy shit it's crazy I was like that's like Kevin Pollak yeah
spelled like that okay that's hilarious dude it was the fuck cuz I thought that
like oh this guy must be involved with some like racist yeah yeah but no his
name is a guy hunter Pollock so fucking yeah that's a really bad I've shown you
that where yeah yeah he sends me photos of his passport that's cool I think it's
a passport I'm gonna use a German passport looks like but he sends me like
a full it's like I'm getting like a like a dossier on this guy every day or he
sends it like bi-monthly now but like it used to be every I kept sending him he
sent it to me and then I said like oh my stomach hurts and he just replied with
like a like a surprised emoji and then I continued to send me his dossiers cool
it's so cool to be like somebody that like a targeted individual is reaching
out to yeah I think you're the target individual I think the target I've
become targeted yeah from the targeted individual um maybe there's something he
sees in me maybe I can change this guy maybe I can save yeah I think you need
to change your life in your hands yeah yeah no question man I got it I gotta
save him yeah he needs help we should adopt him I think we should he's a 43
year old or Mary you can marry him let me show you a photo of him he could come to
United States. That's maybe what he's trying to do because it's a lot of
photos. He might think you're like yeah like an immigration person. Say I ain't no say I
ain't no I'm not Captain Save-A-Ho. I'm not Captain Save-A-Ho. I can't say okay let
me see. While you find this I'm gonna get a water. Look at how he sent so much. He sent so
much that it broke it broke the screen oh my god but then this is him he looks
great yeah he kind of looks like James Lipton can I see him again here's his
license yeah can you say at least his first name
Joaquim Joaquim okay him maybe oh yeah like oh that's a star of David emoji
in there. Noah an emoji. Dear journalists and my last Twitter I'm now taking action
and self-defense against the 26 years of discrimination according to BGB 227 for
that long civil servants have been active against me without empathy from
bullying to provoked accident in 1996 90% severely cured that's 26 years of
discrimination so far the thugs and criminals and then he tagged somebody
interest is I have to shit yeah he's cool dude this guy rocks I thought it would
stop when I kept saying I have a stomach ache yeah that usually any response
usually eggs those people on yeah here's him in his wife maybe whoa he's not 43
yeah he's way older that's his full life oh my this guy's a spy yeah look at his
fucking face he's trying to get sent back home they have been yeah they
abandoned I guess whatever country he was a spy for dissolved I guess he had an
accident in 1996 and he's 90% completely cured of what does it specify injury oh
well that's nice yeah how what percentage of the population is people
like this at this point I don't know and what is doing everybody doing this to
people everybody's been so MK altered into into living like this what does
does that mean I don't know
I was just making stuff up. I thought that I would just make it up and then
we we just move on.
I thought that we'd you know, it's been so in kale. I look you can just
throw words around your you're right. I mean that basically, but that's that's
that's passable yeah. I think that's a that's a that's a made up statement
that's worth moving past. I think that counts yeah, yeah, there's no reason a
lot of things. There's a lot of
basic. It's basically true. It's
blank. Sure, basically true. Yeah,
it's true enough to accept yeah
yeah. A lot of statements. I make
that could be passed on
that we think we just get a little
up on just drilling to
yeah. I'm willing to let this one
slide. Yeah, all right. If we have
you, it is crazy that people just
are mk altered
to live like this. You know that
this bit is going too far. Sorry,
that's a bad. Yeah, the bit is I
I tried to riff on the bit and it was yeah, you just can't do it. Yeah, I
wonder I it's already complete. I bet that like I feel like five percent of
the people who act like that actually there's actually is something going on.
Yeah, yeah, I know I just believe I would I would sooner believe him. I
think yeah, I mean that's that like people it doesn't have to be the
government. That's the thing people get like are mean and bully other people
and if everyone bullies you probably think that everyone's you know, you'd
probably break your brain pretty watch a lot of targeted individual videos. I
think you become one one day. Yeah, yeah, I think if you watch a bunch of them,
yeah, I think like that living like that. I think that's what you do is you
spend all day being like, oh, that's it's funny that people are like that and
then one of them make some amount of sense to you and you're done. Yeah,
exactly. You have to be really careful. It's the same. It's the same with
morgulans stuff. Yeah, there's you can't let that stuff get to you have to eat
like whether even if it is real, you can't believe that it's real or else it
happen to you yeah there was a guy I used to watch in middle school who was like a
targeted an individual who believed he was a reincarnation of Hitler really yeah
and he said that like Steven Spielberg and everybody were in the CIA and they
were watching it was just a skit wait he's reincarnated so what did he was he
like sorry yeah was it he was he happy I don't know he didn't really talk too
much see that would be my I would say the only there was a video of him
microwaving a steak though that's how I found out about him he microwaves a
steak and he says like it's the juiciest thing I've ever eaten. That's the best
part is that as when they those people also live normal lives like or like
semi normal lives. Oh he didn't live a normal life. He lived in a tent. Like just see like less than that but more just like
seeing what else they do like like when you go to their YouTube channel and they
have like you know like a hundred videos that are like the CIA is killing me with
rays and then in between you'll see a video that's like me singing my
favorite song and it's just them like like it's so that's the better fly. I
saw on the street. Yeah, what am I do you guys remember this the targeted
individual guy who said that the CIA stole his penis? No, that he used to
have like he used to have a twelve inch penis and the CIA actually the CIA
stole it and replaced it with like a four inch penis or something. Yeah,
that's the CIA stole it and they're using it to fuck people. Yeah, yeah,
And he didn't have like a bunch of shit taped on his walls or I think so.
Yeah. Yeah, and I think there was maybe some race stuff in there, too.
That was maybe a super awesome.
Yeah, but just the thing of like, yeah, they stole my penis.
You know why because they wanted to fuck people with yeah, it's so funny.
They don't want me to fuck people with it.
They wanted to fuck the also fuck people like screw them over is like a cooler way to fit like they need his penis.
so they need his penis to ruin someone's life.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- With that good dick. - That good dick
will ruin a bitch's life. - That good dick
will ruin a bitch. - True.
- Have you sitting up in the house
with your life ruined.
- Yup, yup. - Okay, that bit actually.
- The CIA, the CIA is using good dick
to ruin bad bitches' lives. - It's true.
(laughing)
- That is true, yeah.
- Some true shit.
- Yeah, that moment where you're like,
I'm not messing with his lazy ass anymore.
- Buh-ding. - Yup.
and then I check my phone like bro yeah, it's fucking true man.
It's like a it's like a Cia like it's like a guy and like a classic like spy
outfit with like a suit and like shades and so but it's with a giant
think about like a briefcase and stuff - yeah his briefcase is filled to the
brim with Magnum condoms yeah you ever think about how like like some of some
of the like weirdest people are blessed with the like biggest Pete like Ron
Jeremy got a big penis looks like he's definitely we think that good people
have little penis yes yeah I probably I think that's true yeah I think bad
people have big penises yeah I think having a big penis cause you to be a bad
person absolutely cuz you get to you get to confident you don't you don't build
your own kind of personality you know and and also you never learn how to how to
actually I know what there is some exceptions no there's no exceptions if
you have a big penis Tyler bad person I do have a friend I don't know anybody I
You have a friend who's brother has like a friend of mine his older brother has
like had just a scary big penis and we we see big penises are fucking terrifying
he's just see it he would like a shower and he would like go was like fall out
of the bottom of his fucking towel and she's we just be like we're terrified
yeah yeah yeah do you know scary I think he works as an engineer or something
Probably for the CIA.
Is it R. Crumb? Robert Crumb? I was watching that documentary.
Apparently he's like hung.
That's pretty funny.
He's hung like crazy but he only gets off if he gets a piggyback ride.
Yeah.
Which they say in the movie.
That's awesome.
That's the way you can be a... I mean I guess he probably wasn't that good of a person was he?
No. I mean look at how he drew black people. That's not good.
But maybe that's the key is that if you can shortcut being a bad person if you
have some horrible fetish that yeah that that humbles you like like he's into
like women who are like seven feet tall like he likes he likes Bigfoot - yeah
yeah yeah he likes to like there's that scene where he's like I was sexually
attracted to Bugs Bunny I like bought it I was like yeah I'm gonna watch this
multiple times. I have some fucked up sexual fetishes. Yeah. I actually, I like getting
head. I kind of, yeah, I honestly like getting head and I kind of like doggy style honestly.
Yeah. I like kissing a girl. I know it's kind of scary and fucked up but like. I like kissing
my girlfriend as a fetish. I like to see my wiener disappear inside someone's body. Yeah.
Just making it go away. Alright. You know what time it is? It's time to make my wiener
go away inside your body. Alright, I have to make my next trick. And every time I'm praying
that I go to pull it and there's nothing there. It sucks it up and it's gone. They should suck
up your penis, that should be sex. You should only have sex one time like a spider. Yeah,
like the tube at the bank. Yeah, exactly. Like the tube at the bank, which my dad used
one of those tubes so bad. The penis grows in. My dad used to talk about it all the time.
dad would talk he'd be like we need to get one of those tubes installed in our
house so that we can send beer to the living room from the kitchen that's sick
and it'd be like that'd be the most fucked up beer in the world when you opened it.
Yeah, it goes up, it goes up, it like goes around a bend immediately shatters and
that just shoots broken glass into the living room. It kills my mom.
You put a beer bottle in it and it just goes *swoosh*. Like Doc Ock's eye.
Just shards of glass directly in her eye. I'm thinking about that penis thing where it
like goes into like that's how it should work this thing where it goes in it goes
in and out thinking about that penis thing where it goes in and out although
like goes up like a vacuum tube so like the size of your penis will determine
the size of your child so if it goes in right here's here's here's my like the
raw material so it's like when you get those little dinosaurs yeah in the
capsule and it unfolds gonna get whatever multitude larger mm-hmm so
basically your penis becomes so in this scenario your penis is a little guy yeah
or girl okay depends but you only get to use it once is it like stone still or is
it like alive it's I mean dead until it's like it's like the capsule with the
dinosaur great so it's not real okay then so it's not real it's made of a
sponge. Okay. Maybe it's alive in there but it's a waxy coating. But it's showing you what
it's gonna look like. It still looks like a penis. I was thinking maybe you could see what
your son would look like. No, no it still looks like a penis. But there's like certain things
like you look at it and you're like oh the head's a little big I think he's gonna have
a big head. Oh, so it follows the characteristics of your penis. Yeah. And then it goes in and
and then it goes in and it grows in mommy
and then it comes out nine months later.
- Yeah.
- It goes into mommy?
- It goes into mommy.
- Okay.
All right, I'm starting to get it.
What if your penis had red skin and horns?
- Oh no.
- Chomp it off.
- What would you do?
- What if it looked like a Bulbasaur?
- Get that penis off of there.
- Yeah.
- Get that penis off my body.
- Since I broke my toe, I've been getting so,
back into Pokemon so hard.
- That makes no sense 'cause I feel like
you wouldn't wanna walk around very much
pokemon go no no no pokemon the pokemon normal oh yeah he mon i beat rcs or
arceus i don't know how you say it the arceus is a beat rcs main quest that's
done nice nice got a level up i'm starting i'm starting shining pearl
gaming patrick i became a gamer too i've been playing so much game well we've
been playing pokemon go speaking of hold on don't you dare i've been playing
I have to do my streak.
Sekiro Shadows Die Twice.
I've been off of video games.
Shadow?
Shadows Die Twice.
Sekiro Shadows Die Twice.
Oh, I thought you were talking about Shadow the Hedgehog.
That would be a cool game to play.
Yeah.
No, this one's about a ninja fighting Samurai.
Shadow's kind of a ninja if you think about it.
I'm doing a full dopamine fest.
Yeah.
No music, no movies, no video games, no TV show, no food, no water.
Team Rocket Gym.
Team Rocket Poke Stop.
I'm not going to.
Not right now.
now but I figure it out I think you got to catch a cat real quick yeah I gotta
catch this cat the spring what's its name this is what is this glam meow
glam mixing in normal animal yeah the glam meow fled so they don't have any
normal animals in Pokemon kind of there's some that are just birds and
cats and stuff I mean they're not but they're not called bird but yeah that's
what they don't have like there's not a bird or a dog there is a few dogs like
they don't you know what you know what there's one called there's one called
crabby that's a crab so does is our humans the only animals that had a
normal evolution are they the only animals yeah so yeah so is the god of
all Pokemon yeah but that's like before that what and like just one Pokemon like
came out or everyone they're making a show before they had this whole like
mythology thing and it it's really you can like look up you can they have like
you can read parts of the like style guide for the show and it's like yeah you
can never show an animal that's not a Pokemon because it will make the world
not make sense and like the really fun part that is like you can't ever show
like they can't ever eat anything with meat and the show you can't visibly see
them eating because because they would be eating yeah come on yeah that's why
they're always eating just the rice and stuff oh yeah and then the American
localization they say call it donuts yeah jelly doughnuts or what is it like
like hot dogs and stuff. - Rice balls, or jelly donuts.
- Yeah, it's pretty funny.
But yeah, I just, I love that they had to put that
in the thing, it's like the design document.
- Yeah, 'cause you can't eat a Pokemon.
- Yeah, you cannot.
'Cause imagine one guy slips up and has,
they eat a hamburger one time,
and it's like, yeah, one kid sees it,
and is like, oh my God.
Like one kid who's smart enough to realize what that means.
- Yeah, or they're eating something
that looks like fried chicken,
but it's clearly like, you see Pikachu's tail,
lightning thing yeah I guess it's good that they said didn't show that you
could eat a Pokemon you should I want to know exactly what I mean honestly I would
love to eat a match oak making them fight each other getting them to thin
fight and lean knock at each other out is is way worse than eating them I
absolutely yeah it's like what you can't battle dogs in the real world yeah but
you can eat them yeah you're making they're making the Pokemon fight so that
you can be the king of a building that has a pool in it.
- Yeah, wait, okay, so it's a freaking,
and they have balls.
- Yeah. - Balls, what the hell?
- Is a Pokeball on the Nintendo Switch today?
- And you wake up, and your mom wakes you up.
You're 10 years old and you go on an adventure.
Isn't that a little young?
- Makes no sense.
- Wait, and you can only--
- Isn't Professor Oak a little bit weird
for hanging out with a child?
- Yep. (laughing)
- Isn't he a little bit weird for hanging out with a child?
- Wait, and you only get one starter Pokemon?
Why can't you get all three?
- And hold on, this makes no sense.
He's making you take pictures of Pokemon in a little car.
Isn't that kind of dangerous for the dogs and stuff?
- And why can't you just get every Pokemon instantly
at the start of the game?
- It's actually true.
- It doesn't make any sense.
- How come I have to complete the Pokedex?
- What the hell did you just say?
- I have to look at Pokemon's dicks?
- No, that's not at all.
- Bruh, come on.
- Bruh.
- No, bruh.
- Come on, bruh.
- No, that can't be right.
- I thought the Pokedex was so cool when I was a kid.
- It is cool.
- That was one of the coolest things ever to me.
and that looks like that now I'd literally I would I would have like I
would have killed one of my parents to make my other parent by me a real life
Pokedex if there was one maybe there was one, but just like one where I can like
like in the in the show they like scan the Pokemon yeah, and it goes like yeah,
like the crab Pokemon and then like says that like if I had something like that
as a kid well, it would make that I was one that worked completely the same
perfectly, but because there's no Pokemon in the world you would just been
fucked yeah. Well, you first of all okay to branching pads here either they make
it for animals.
or they may do that with this you can do that on Google now you can like really
yeah and the Google voice well you can do that with plants and shit doesn't
important part lion enclosure huh I'm gonna drop myself in with the lions and
the bamboos and I'm gonna scan them with my Google app yeah and then they shreds
the second before the the lion eats you it's like could not recognize yeah you
die lion the human eater the human eater animal lion type its weakness is being
dropped off a building
What's the one animal that you would not want to be put into an animal enclosure
with? Squidward. Yeah, Squidward is this big. He'd be so rude to me. He is really small, I guess.
Yeah, he's really small. Yeah, okay. But he's got that plot armor. Oh, true. No, but I mean--
And I'd probably kill myself after being with him for five minutes. I think
alligators is-- they're not gonna attack you, honestly. I don't think alligators--
All you have to do is climb.
- Well, also, alligators in enclosures,
alligators only need to eat once a week,
and they're all pretty well-fed.
That's why they don't attack people who--
- Well, hungry alligator is the scenario.
- There's not-- - They're saying--
(laughing)
- That's the part of the scenario.
- You could assume the placard says--
- The hungriest alligator. - Hungry alligator.
American hungry alligator.
- Also, yeah, if an alligator bucks at you,
you can kind of, there's stuff,
if you hit it on the nose and stuff,
or that's a shark, there's something you can do where--
anything if you hear no it's like if you stand behind it and hold its mouth shut
that's what you do it's all pretty easy. I think alligators are just not that big
of a deal yeah they don't kill that I've been watching a bunch of alligator
movies they're the belly and lions I think you're not so good to be around
yeah I think a tiger would or lion any of any big cat that's not good and then I
think maybe oh you know what a grizzly bear yeah grizzly bear like an enclosure
with a grizzly bear you're fucked. You think so? Yeah, completely. You have no
chance because they're so big you can't climb away. I don't think it's gonna try, I don't
think it'll. Yes it will, they're aggressive. They are aggressive. That's the thing about
grizzly bears. Grizzly man? Literally the thing with grizzly bears is that they. No,
you're absolutely fucked. A grizzly bear is a brown bear? Yeah. It's an American brown
bear. I think I could soothe it. No. You could sue it? Have you ever seen the video of the
brown bear that walks up next to the guy always fishing that was fine. That was a
I think that's probably a Kodiak bear was it I don't know it was brown. I think I
know the video you're talking about the thing about girls. I guess the thing
about a grizzly bear is a grizzly bear. I think is the one that will chase you if
you run if you freak out at all like if you if you have any sense yeah like
like seen that that video that bear that gets stuck in the window no no trying to
get honey and his friends have to push him out. Oh my god that shit's scary as
fuck yeah and it's trying to get yeah it has and the scariest part of that bear
is on the back of it it is like another face yeah have you seen this it is like
fucking horns on the back I can't believe how much you just got me I can't even
believe it I was like no I haven't I can't believe how bad I just got owned
ground yeah. No, I think grizzly bear you're fucked yeah. I think that's it's
called a grizzly bear. Yeah, you know there's a scientific name is murderous
man literally is it's ersus arctos horribilis. That's sick. Yeah, it's so
cool. Yeah, the fucking like what because which came first grizzly bear or
grizzly murder because grizzly murder is spelled with an s. Yeah, it's different
words. Really? Yeah. I didn't know that. Yeah. Gris, so it's grisly? Grisly murder.
Grisly, yeah. So which game, like, I feel like Grisly Bear. Is that, is Grisly Bear
a scientific name? Like, is that like it's... That's, no, it's, so it's like, well, you
know, it's scientific name is Ursus Arctos Horribilis. You know what I mean? Like...
Yeah, but I think that... A subspecies or whatever? It's called an American Brown Bear,
also I think it's one of those things where neither of them like there's not
like enough necessarily an official name like you would know either way yeah I
don't think there's such thing as like an official name and that's like really
mean well so do you want to know a fun fact about bears yeah why they're called
bears is it called a grizzly bear because of that or is it like a like
oh there's like a little grizzled grizzled is like also like like they're
like I think is like a type of color texture type thing like I think that's
that's where it's okay, but so bear is originally bears were called there's
some words for bears and like like old like like
european or like maybe it was russian like like oh they had this word for bear,
but they never they would never call bear. It was arctos that's what it was
they would never call bear arctos because they believed that bears were
like demons, and if you said the word arctos, it would summon a bear to come
kill you. So they would they'd instead they called them like like brown haired
animals or like they would use like euphemisms to describe them and that's
where bear comes from is like brown or something whoa or they would call them
like honey eaters and stuff, but they were too afraid to say the word the word
for bear whoa yeah bears were out there fucking people up for quite yeah
they're they're crazy. That's sick before that we got houses and cars yeah
pre houses and cars. They were just fucking destroyers were just doing
crazy. I was reading this thing about
about bear attacks throughout history. I was going through the wikipedia page
yeah and it's like it goes from like the seventeen hundreds or whatever to
like just to the present day. It's funny because all the first ones are
like a man, a man put on his hunting had and today, like from the excerpt
from a newspaper, like a man put on his hunting hat today and and stated I'm
going out to kill a bear and he never returned
like the nineteen hundreds. They're like twenty in a row that are just
like a man was hitting a bear with a stick through the bars that a zoo and he
got pulled in and ripped apart.
Yeah, that's a bad. I think there's a bad way to go. I think any any lot of
just animal just tear you to bits alive. Yeah, probably got to be in my top two
worst ways of die there, so it's so far. So the original question is like which
animal would you would you least want to be in an enclosure with? I guess there's
lot yeah what's the most probably a mosquito you know that's the deadliest
animal I carry West Nile true and truly yeah Hitler yeah yeah I got Jack the
Ripper I jacked the rip do you guys think I feel like I'm not a I'm not a lady of
the night I would probably like a hundred and ten pounds yeah you know
yeah like he's probably such a pussy dude yeah well yeah he was a pussy
because of all that stuff he did to those women that's right that's right the
a coward. Yeah, you're a loser. Pick on someone your own size. Jack the Ripper?
You're a frigging bitch. Yeah, this is... That's it. You're done, Jack the Ripper.
You're done, man. You're not doing that shit anymore. So did he really... We're
putting an end to it. Did he really rip these women up? He did.
They get some crazy old serial...
There's the old joke, like, "Oh, stop giving them such cool names."
I feel like we've effectively done,
there hasn't been a cool serial killer name in a while.
- That's 'cause we don't have serial killers anymore,
we have mass shooters and now we just,
they just have their names.
- Most of their names are very stupid.
- True crime has just destroyed the brains of people.
- Zodiac is so cool.
- Zodiac Killer?
- Such a cool--
- Zodiac and Mr. Cruel was like some Australian.
Actually, he wasn't a killer, I don't think.
He was a serial rapist.
Yeah, BTK.
It's all just so cool.
Yeah.
But like, True Crime's just, it's eroded our brains into fucking shit.
You think so?
Yeah.
Our brains?
I don't think so.
People's brains, the collective conscious.
I'm not so much into True Crime.
I hate it.
I really liked the first season of Serial.
I think.
Because I thought, I really, I was hoping that the girl and the kid in jail were going to
fuck at the end, but they didn't.
I think the problem with True Crime is that it all has really boring endings.
because it's all real. You either go to jail. They should make up endings for it.
Yeah, the ending should be scary. You think the guy's dead and then he's
actually alive. Exactly, the ending to every true crime thing is either, "but we have
no idea and there's no way to solve this" or it's like, "and then they got him and
they put him in jail and that's that." Yeah, there's always, it's there's never
like a, like they always try to tell it like it's like a movie story.
In the end, there's just like, "was Robert Durst having a heart attack and then like you..."
and then a lightning strikes him. Yeah exactly. Or you see his body under a sheet at the morgue.
And the sheet's gone. Yeah exactly. There's this woman who like, because her mom got killed by her
mom's friend who took out a life insurance policy on her or some shit. Her friend? Yeah. I don't
know. I don't remember the exact details of the story. When someone kills somebody and one week
earlier they were at a life insurance office like, "I'd like to take out a life insurance policy on
my friend yeah but there is like some detail out there's some details I forget
but like because there was a Dateline episode that story of her mom's murder
is like being optioned off into a show it's like Jesus fucking Christ like
there's a real person like how the foot like this fucking stupid like she should
always get some money for that she yeah like you should get like a shit ton of
of money yeah yeah money money will bring the mommy back yeah money brings mommy
back money brings mommy back mm-hmm yeah yeah yeah I don't know I don't think it
matters that much I mean I think if you had your entire family killed I mean I
would I would be really mad I wouldn't like it I don't think it's like my like
here's the caveat you should be able to pick who plays you yeah yeah cuz you're
gonna be in the show exactly and you should either be able to play yourself or
or you should be able to pick just whoever you want yeah you get the choice
if I if I if I lose my parents to a murderer mm-hmm and then they are like
on the dateline reenactment is some like ugly motherfucker yeah just like totally
dishonor
they get Jonah Hill to play you in the true cry like they had like like 50
infidelity subplots between yeah yeah like Pamela Adlon both of your parents
have like like 50 side okay Pamela Adlon plays my dad and or my mom and Louie
plays my dad that's that's the only way I'll do it uh-huh
and I know like they they get some like they make my dad bald for no reason well
that's a that's okay no like ball like you know like bald like he's got like a
a cleft lip or something.
- Yeah, no, like, bald is not on the same level as cleft lip.
- No, what are you talking about?
- Like, the reenactor--
- They make my dad bald, he has one arm.
- In the reenactment, they make my dad a bald guy
with a cleft lip, it's like, you're not honoring my dad.
- They make my dad Immortan Joe from Mad Max Fury Road.
They give him like a gas mask.
- Yeah, they make my dad, like, if they did that shit,
if my, like, if the reenactors of my life
were fucking weird looking, I'd be so mad.
Yeah, it's like I already lost my mom and now you're making her like 600 pounds. Yeah, that's fucked up. You're adding insult
Yeah, they make my dad an alien
And he's totally from another world. Here's Brosnan and Pamela Anderson to be my mom and dad and you're if they get murdered
Yeah, yeah, the person who it's about should have some power over it, I guess but I don't think yeah, I don't I don't know
Whatever Idris Elba plays my dad
Please me. Did you sell what plays my dad? I play myself. Mm-hmm
Favorite son Caleb. Yeah, thank you dad
Thank you dad my favorite son. I've always thought murdered now. No, don't go get murdered. I've always loved how similar we are
People immediately know that I'm your show
You're amazing on a soccer field, I'm a footy player ball field. I'm a footy player. I really am
You're so amazing. I wish you were alive to solve your own blokes on your thank you. I really appreciate that age or a dad
That's so sweet of you
and my mom
my mom is
Kate Kate yeah, and then the the murderer Darth Vader
Okay, my mom is Kate Upton and a plot point is that I breastfed until I was
having like a like like you know what okay we are saying all these like true
crime stories and like like starting a true crime show and being like like
figuring out all the stories you're gonna do and just like every episode and
just being like now there aren't that many hints but I think we're being that
I think based on the clues here we can conclude that Darth Vader was the killer
who's more evil than possibly have it in them to do something so evil giving
like interviews with all the family were like dredging up this horrible stuff.
Everyone's crying and then they're like so did you ever see Darth Vader around
the house at any point during your childhood? I mean I've seen him a few
times. Not really. I mean I guess I guess I guess on the TV. Yeah, I saw I
saw Darth Vader. So after yes, so the family admits what is there a big bug?
Oh, it's just a spider. It's a big spider going down to you. That is a
crazy coming down to me. Shut up. You screamed last time. I was hoping you
it again. We were in the middle of doing an amazing riff slash bit. I'm sorry.
Darth Vader being the killer. Okay let's get back into the riff. I don't even have
an enemy anymore. You don't have the riff anymore dude. Okay here's a new bit.
Caleb would if he sees a spider. Okay that one's pretty good. Do you want to riff on
that Pat? Here's a sound Caleb would make if he saw like the if he was in stuck in
a spider enclosure. Yeah a spider enclosure would give fuck. Okay wait here's the sound that Caleb would make if he
was if he saw Darth Vader I would say his name Darth Vader I mean I would get
pretty excited so I get a photo of them that's probably one that you don't want
to see you see you into he's a scariest battle at the end of Kenobi no looks
like shit. Oh my god. But before I've had that battle at the end of my cannoli, all that cheese,
oh my god. Oh, the raccote. That battle in my body. It's so cool that people- My body battle.
Jersey Italians just make up that word, make up words. Raccote. Raccote. That's what my grandpa
does, he does that. Yeah. Yeah. Fucking piece of shit. Mm. Madone. He doesn't say madone. Oof,
madone. My girlfriend says that. That's just from the Sopranos. That's not it, no. She's never seen
it. She's never seen The Sopranos? Yeah. Unless she picked it up from somebody who
had seen it then. Probably. Yeah, it's only in Sopranos. It only exists in New Jersey. If you're from like
Bergen County or just you're in Sopranos all the time. Pretty much. Yeah. Yeah. It
is so cool that the that the... Did you guys see the thing where the the fucking
what's-his-name Tony Soprano, the actor, what is his name? Oh yeah. James Gannolfini.
He got a call in the middle of the night from some like unknown number and it was
just somebody they were like listen we really like what you're doing we think
you're doing a very good job but a Don would never wear shorts and then he hung
up that's crazy just called us a like no guy who's in the mafia would never be
caught dead where that's sick what a beast yeah I something I love about the
Sopranos that I think that needs to be more chose still is a leftism the left
leftism is huge. But I love how many how many jokes are just of a fat guy who's
like I'm gonna go eat some food. It's funny. It's not a no Bobby. No Bobby
Bacala Bobby Bacala. He's the best. What's the fucking this every time. Oh
Don Vito. Yeah. Don't say any spoilers though because I haven't finished the
Oh, yeah, oh, I know he's gay though. I found that out. Okay, I just watch that episode season 5
Second to last right there's like season 6 a and 6 beers. Oh, yeah, damn
New Hampshire makes an appearance for real. I will holy crap. Okay, I need a
TV show like that goes to New Hampshire not breaking bad. What the fuck are you talking about?
about I got to hold the license plate from Breaking Bad because in my in my
wait when did you know he goes to New Hampshire at the end of season or the
beginning of season 5 he's in New Hampshire oh I thought he's in fucking
Alaska no that's New Hampshire he's gonna be in are they say it's Alaska
though it may be oh no it's in you he has New Hampshire plates on his car I
guess Alaska they live in the show they say he's going to Alaska I'm like 90
he must have gotten New Hampshire plates and gone to Alaska it doesn't look like
like New Hampshire always. Yeah, it's Alaska. The first episode is called Live Free or Die.
Oh, you're right. Let me look it up. I also, I, that's crazy. I think I honestly just assumed
that it was Alaska. Because it was snowy and in a TV show that it was supposed to be Alaska.
I could have sworn he said something about Alaska. I'm like clearly I am right about
something but the both, there's a, the mob mentality of you two. Two versus one is always
right. Oh, it always wins. Dude, it is New Hampshire, what the fuck? You're such a genius.
- Dude, that was a huge thing.
- Was it huge for y'all?
- That was huge and everyone was like, "Holy shit."
And then, yeah, I got to some guy
who came to my class and held a license plate up.
- Fucking Jesse wants to go to Alaska.
- Oh, yeah.
- That's what I'm thinking of.
- You know, that's very cool about New Hampshire,
but they actually filmed "Under the Dome" in Wilmington.
- Was "Under the Dome."
- Okay, so somebody fucking hates prestige television.
"Under the Dome."
- They go "Under a Dome."
every show that somebody like like like Breaking Bad and like Sopranos maybe
it's just Breaking Bad and Sopranos do they go to I've never seen Mad Men do
they go to New Hampshire and Mad Men I don't think so I mean if we're talking
the wires TV Holly Flax moves to Nashua what the fuck is that it's Holly Flax
you can imagine the face I'm making at the camera right now I don't know what
what it is. He's at the office. Yeah. Oh, I'm doing a gym face at him not
knowing who Holly Flax is Holly Flax. Which one is that? Which one is
Holly Sweetheart? Michael's sweet my way. Michael has a sweetheart. Oh,
when they yeah, when I see screenshots of that stupid ass character in that
show, I'm like I pray that this this white guy never breeds true and he has
a fucking sweetheart. Thank God. She moves away. She moves away, but then
he moves to Nashua. Does he get her eggs before she moves? He goes and he
has six kids with her.
That is fucking disgusting.
They go to Nashville, but they did not film in Nashville.
I know.
I see some of the quotes.
I'll tell you what, I like the Stanley and Pam.
Some of the quotes from that fucking idiot moronic lunatic, I wish I could shake him
by the shoulders and say, "Sir, never reproduce."
We need a new plague.
Remove yourself from the gene pool.
Oh my God, Darwin award, please.
Please give yourself a Darwin award, my friend.
I shouldn't even call you my friend.
My moronic friend.
He's a fucking idiot.
You waste of crapping space.
You friggin' idiot, Michael Scott.
You don't even have 30 IQ points to rub together.
You are basically like a shit on a stick with a pooper brain.
Michael Scott, I hope you get AIDS.
How did you get to be boss?
See, I think that's where the comedy lies.
The boss should be everyone else.
I agree.
This guy has no business being a boss of a lunch, let alone a fucking entire company.
Oh my God, don't even get me started.
He'd be like, "Don't eat the sandwich."
Yeah.
Meanwhile, an effective boss, "Eat the sandwich at your own pace."
Yep.
Meanwhile, an effective boss.
We should do the office with, but like fixing the office where we get, we replace...
CinemaSins.
Michael is actually a really ineffective boss.
(laughing)
- He's inefficient and poor management technique.
- His team building is pitiful.
- Pris and Mike is actually quite offensive.
(laughing)
- No office would actually have a diversity day.
- Yep.
- Actually, they probably would these days.
- I think they would have a diversity day.
- Nowadays, probably.
- Nowadays, they'd love--
- Back when I was working at offices.
- When I worked in an office,
when I worked in an office, I was harassed every day.
- For being the only-- - For real?
- For wearing a skirt.
- Me too.
Well, not for wearing a skirt.
I did it for wearing pants because I was in a liberal office.
Oh yeah.
And I was the only-
Why aren't you wearing a dress?
I was the only white cracker in the whole office.
Yep.
And I was completely male.
Yeah.
I was completely a male cracker and they hated me for that.
And they hated me at my liberal office.
Can you believe it?
Oh my God, they hated you.
And I was straight.
Wow.
Yeah.
I mean nowadays at liberal offices they'll be like, "Oh, you're wearing pants?
Why aren't you wearing a dress?" And I'll be like, "Buddy, the only address I care
about is 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue."
That's right.
And then I do this.
"Why aren't you wearing a dress? The only address I care about..."
Holy shit.
I'm about to shit myself. I'm about to shit myself.
I thought that was the chair breaking.
It was the chair and it was a little bit my stomach and I have to go. And I hope
you guys have a great last 15 seconds of this episode. But I am going to leave.
How long is it gonna take you to shit in there?
Probably three minutes. Okay, or less. Okay, I'm just gonna be a shotgun blast. I'm gonna run
Wait bring the mic in with you
Just go in there the door and start pooping
I'm not gonna do it. I'm afraid I don't think we should record him pooping. Oh
He turned the sink on so we can't hear it. All right. It's what a fucking bitch
So we have learned merges up merges up. It's not we announced the last time but if you didn't go it's a pre-order
Don't use no promo code use promo code Buffy
Buffy for 100% added to the price of your order. We'd like to pay twice as much use Buffy
Swag poop comm slash shop. We have two beautiful shirts up
And if you'd rather if instead of a shirt, you'd rather wear our skin
you can come and kill us in Portland or Seattle.
- Portland, Oregon or Seattle, Washington.
- Pacific Northwest, that's August 18th and 19th.
Tickets are up at swagpoop.com/shows.
It's gonna be the last show of the tour.
- Last show of the tour.
And then go to swagpoop.com/patrickscorner.
- For a special surprise.
All right, bye everybody.
- Bye bye.