You're listening to Israel's number one pod.
This is premium content!
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately!
[Laughter]
[Explosion]
Welcome to cum.
[Groans]
Oh, God.
How do-
[Groans]
Oh, God.
How do Hawaiian people just fucking do that every morning?
What, eat- I don't think Hawaiian people eat what you made every morning.
Yeah, I don't think Hawaiian people are real, Caleb.
[Laughter]
Every day they eat four King's Hawaiian rolls, four eggs, and four pieces of spam.
Yeah.
Every day.
Did you give us each four eggs?
Yeah, I did.
That's probably why I shit so much.
Yeah, we've been just taking turns raw dogging my toilet.
Everybody in this apartment just shit one after another.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, dude, you know what sucks is I took the longest because for some reason
I was about to get up and then immediately felt it in my stomach that I needed to sit back down.
You had a crap attack.
I did. I did. Thankfully I have a whole thing of Pepto with me if you guys...
Now you're doing a cap attack.
If you want to check.
True.
I'm not lying.
Why do you cap someone?
You cap dude.
Are you the capper? Are you kidding me?
I... Are you kidding me?
He was capping this... You saw him. You heard him this morning. He was capping.
I was not capping.
You guys both cap all day.
No, no.
No, you know what? You're the capper.
No, I'm not.
You're the capper of the group.
What have I capped about? Everything. You capped about- See? You're capping dude. You capped about fucking loving me earlier. Yeah, that's true. I was not capping.
Oh wow. Real shit?
*laughter*
Real shit.
I think Cam is like- the thing about Cam is he sat in my doorway,
and he was such a like menacing large figure that I accidentally fell in love.
So now that's something you have to deal with dude. You have to fucking deal with that dude. What? Yeah.
I was just telling him I caught feelings for him.
He caught feelings for me. I caught feelings. I'm just trying to fall in love before this world ends you feel me yeah, I
Fall in love with everybody I fall in love too easily man
I fell in love with my breakfast this morning before I the rules of a gracious God
And he tells me to fucking love camera with all my heart. Yeah, that's what I've been doing
Yeah, this is why I don't eat breakfast this breakfast did damage dude that yeah, okay, but that's not like a normal breakfast
That's a normal breakfast. No you shouldn't be eating that regular like a month's worth of fucking chicken eggs
Yeah, yeah bunch of green onion and
Dessert I'm so glad you didn't make that yesterday. Why I'm glad we have more fucking time left in New York
And you made that it would have yeah, we had to ramp it up. Yeah, you know, yeah
Yeah, I mean, I think the next time I come here. I'm only eating salad. I
Do what?
No, yeah, you're gonna get like one of those like golden corral salads
It's all croutons and bacon bits. Doesn't matter. Blue cheese on it. It's still healthy. You're right. It's so healthy. If it says salad
It means it's healthy. Yeah
That's not macaroni salad. Those are all healthy. You're right salad. Yeah, mayonnaise and Polish salad
What's that a steak?
Yeah paper clips and twigs from the ground
Broken glass. Yeah, and you can't find it also. Yeah
You serve it on you serve it by a bowl upside down they serve it in a colander
And then they pour dressing all over a Polish soup bowl
Stupid fucking poles. Oh
I can't believe what they do those Polak pieces of shit Cameron and sex chair the only two Polish people I know I think
Yeah, pretty rare. Yeah, not that rare not rare enough if he asked me
They keep getting lost on their way.
Exactly.
To the states.
Yeah.
Not a lot of Polish people in America.
There's a lot of us.
There's not a lot of you.
There's a ton.
No.
More than anyone else.
I don't think so.
I think it's Cameron the Capper again.
Yeah, guess who's capping?
Look who's capping now.
Yeah, look who's capping now.
Yeah.
Look who's capping too.
Yeah, look who's--
Look who's capping the first one.
Yeah.
You're capping, obviously.
Come on, man.
Come on, man. I got feelings too, man.
Look who's talking now was the one with the dogs, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, because the kids could talk.
Yeah, it's like, okay, the kids talk, the dogs talk, now the food talks.
First the baby talks.
That was a hot dog party with Seth Rogen.
Yeah, sausage party.
Hot dog. Hot dog bash.
Did you guys see that movie?
No.
It was fucking terrible, dude.
I know that the animators were abused.
Really?
I think most animators are abused.
It's true.
Animators, because they're not like famous actors.
Yeah, they're allowed to get abused.
Nobody cares.
They'll work an 80 hour week.
There is an animators union,
but all the things in the animators union
are just things that let you get abused.
We get to have candy for breakfast.
The animators union is like
you cannot make me draw Spongebob as a circle.
That's it. That's all you get as an animator. And let me say, animators, it's a tough job.
The real American heroes.
Do you think it's easy?
Well, it's tough if you do it as a job, but if you do it as a hobby, it's the easiest thing in the world.
That's not true.
You okay?
Thank you.
Let's just sit here in silence.
debates it just tears us apart dude exactly I fucking hate it
I hate to see you guys like this I hate capping it's hard for me I hate people
who cap yeah no cap I hate cap that's cap brother I hate cap you're currently
capping it literally makes me cry you're not beautiful all right you capping I'm
I'm caff, I'm caff.
- No.
- You fucking know I'm caff.
- No, he was, no, he was camera, he was caff.
- You're so pretty when you cry.
(imitates crying)
- Damn.
- I hate to see you cry, but I love to watch you bawl.
(laughing)
Hate to see you cry, but I love when you lose your mind.
- Hair ties, sweatpants on, chilling with no makeup on.
That's when you're most beautiful, girl.
- That's when you fucking turn me on, baby.
(laughing)
Damn, girl, you look like shit and I'm horny.
- Damn.
Ooh, you look like fuckin' crap.
You look like fuckin' dog shit today.
Put some makeup on, stupid bitch! Fuck you, sexy!
Damn.
'Cause I know later you're gonna look good, but right now you look like shit.
Hair pants, sweats tied,
Chillin' with your face on the floor,
Chillin' with your tears out,
Chillin' crying.
Nice. You got fuckin' ketchup on your forehead.
You got the forehead the size of an ape.
You got a gorilla's head.
- Ooh.
- We about to get you some plastic surgery,
but for right now, damn, you're the most beautiful,
most sexy girl in the world.
- You look like Rocky Dennis Mask,
but you know what, girl?
You beautiful as hell.
- Damn, girl, you look like Lou Ferrigno.
(laughing)
And man, I'm turned on.
- You sound like him, too.
- God damn, you sound like Lou Ferrigno right now.
- You got those hooky hands.
- You sound just like him.
- You got them hands, too.
- Oh my God.
- Mama, real shit, you green as hell.
- You green?
- God damn, if it ain't sexy.
- You got them purple shorts on.
You got the-- man, you ripped out of your clothes!
You ripped out your damn shirt, bitch!
You ripped out your damn shirt thinking about me.
Fuck, you look bad.
You know what's crazy is, uh, they have the She-Hulk.
So they have Hulk, but then they have his cousin, Jessica Banner, I think her name is.
Why do they have to be cousins? Wasn't he an experiment?
I think she got a blood transfusion from him.
Real fucking smart idea, Bruce.
Yeah, great move, dude.
He was the only person who could do it or whatever.
but so she gets a blood transfusion she becomes she Hulk the only thing that
changes about her is that she just becomes like a beautiful green
Amazonian woman no Hulk stuff no what do you mean no Hulk's she's
really than shit yeah she's got super strength and shit so what do you mean no
Hulk stuff giant green and strong no no she like doesn't look like a Hulk she
just looks like a green lady and she has muscles yeah she has muscles but not Hulk
size muscles muscular and green and big she doesn't turn no she just looks like a
regular person who's green like a regular person in the superhero universe
who's green she's WNBA I'm going to see Hulk exactly no cuz if you think she
Hulk if I think look at this Patrick if it does not look like the fucking Hulk
no that's not big enough huge muscle needs to be bigger come on
I'd love for her to fucking snap my dong off in her snatch.
See, no, she just looks...
Yeah, exactly.
She just looks like normal.
Yeah, dude, she's got a fucking thick ass.
Right.
She's got a fucking horse ass on her.
Yeah, the whole point of the Hulk is that he's a Hulk.
Can you search She-Hulk ass?
No.
What the hell, man?
Can you look up She-Hulk cosplay ass?
Yeah.
She-Hulk Cosby.
Yeah, no, that's different.
See look how big she is.
That's for the cover.
She's like big.
She's literally fucking 12 feet tall.
No, she doesn't get that tall in the rest of it.
That's just because of the cover.
She Hulk is like at least like...
Hey Patrick.
Because she's a woman they make her like 6 feet tall.
Hold on.
You have something to say.
Hey Patrick.
What?
You capping?
No!
Yep, capping again dude.
I'm on the She Hulk Wikipedia page.
I'm going to command F muscles.
Okay?
she has a crush on hercules
because they're the same size. Yeah, she's herculean. Yeah, she probably
look her.
That's right.
Damn.
Look up there.
It's like the hercules.
She's like her.
I'm him.
Julie's dude.
Now she's fucking big and green big.
Turning green is enough already.
Yeah, that wouldn't yeah.
I wouldn't say I wouldn't see someone who turns green when they're angry and
like that guy's nothing like the Hulk. You're almost nothing like the Hulk.
She just becomes six foot seven. That's the only thing. She just becomes a WNBA
player. That I will say, that's not as tall as she should be. Right. Yeah. She should be at
least seven feet and way bigger. How tall is she? The Hulk is only 5'9".
That's not true. That's what it says. Not when he's Hulked out. Okay, this is as Bruce Banner. I
searched Hulk height and it says approximately 5'9". He's got to be alright.
Oh seven and eight between seven and eight feet tall. That's not that tall though. Eight feet tall
Well, no between seven and eight feet if he's seven feet tall. He's like shorter than Yao Ming
Yeah, Yao Ming's a fucking Chinese. Okay, but she Hulk goes from five one to six seven. Yeah
Well, that's just do and then when she she Hulk she weighs 650 pounds
That's a big bitch. No, that's what it says right here. Okay. Well, maybe that's fucking a baby
Yeah, that's a hundo doesn't look like she weighs 600 pounds. You want to be fat?
Yeah, muscle weighs more than fat brother. I want I want a hulk she has a fucking 18 pack
And I want to step on my balls. Yeah
When I crush my balls like a fucking car. Mm-hmm. Yeah, bitch
She Hulk I want you to fucking I want you to tear me
Listening to this you split me in half. Yeah, I want you to shoot me in the head with a rifle
I would start committing crimes to see if she could stop me. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, no
difference from the Hulk unlike Bruce Jennifer Walters retains control over
her Hulk form and emotional intelligence making she Hulk stories even more
captivating
intelligent storyline people are so she's like a lawyer she Hulk and then
she'll do like all she's hulk yeah really
yeah I think we have to throw this case out she's intimidating the jury I think
I'm falling in love with this green lawyer bitch mm-hmm yeah damn I think
she my new wife yeah I wish it they were still trying to just turn every every
a superhero into a girl version. When I hear She-Hulk, I'm just... They still are. What
are you talking about? They're not adding new ones are they? What do you mean adding
new ones? There's not like a girl version of Shazam. I think there probably was in the
70s. There is, yeah. Shazam? Aw, shit! Captain Marvel is a girl version of Captain Marvel.
I think Captain Marvel likes girls. They just made a girl Thor. They made a girl Thor. They're
doing that more than ever dude. They changed Thor into a girl in the comics. Yeah, well
that's a while ago. My bad. But I mean still recently. I'm gonna get ahead, I'm gonna get
in front of this I was capping so that's well yeah they're getting the 70s they
would just be like I guess literally just them sitting around like oh what if
Thor was a girl those broads are up to 20 cents on the dollar we got a start
appealing to them no but the thing the complaint I have about she Hulk is it
would be way cooler if it was just Hulk in like a girl wig what when you hear
She-Hulk that's what you think right like not like not really I mean I don't I
think about the She-Hulk that I know a girl a girl who turns green and muscular
and big you want to you want her to be like wide you want to be like lunch lady
you want her to just wear shorts it should be it should be like an ugly
woman who turns into the Hulk is like a big ugly woman with like a giant mole
mm-hmm right and the mole turns purple into a second face look I'm just trying
spread body positivity yeah yeah I know that's like your project yeah yeah yeah
yeah for all my what was that fucking DM we good for much I'm trying to spread
positivity for my child acting workshops oh yeah I forgot we got that yeah yeah
some guy trying to get us this post about a workshop that he's putting about
a workshop so he'll promote us to his six thousand six hundred thousand followers
Yes, we'll do it. Yes. Oh my god. Yes. We will suck you sir
Sir, we will suck you sir. Yes, sir. I make you feel the best pain you ever felt
With all due respect
That's the damn sorry is blowjob I ever had got
You're cappin major that was fun. I gave you that fire throw. Yeah, I gave you sloppy top commander
That's a dryus mouth I ever got we're in the desert sir
No water, please
Only I get the water I'll make water into you. Oh you thirsty, huh?
Oh no, we're going to get in so much trouble with the army.
Oh no, not again.
Caleb's going to get in trouble with the army again.
Whatever, I'll fight for the army.
I'm saying it right now.
I waive all of my rights to deny service.
It would be funny if I joined the army.
Would you think that would be funny?
What would be funny about that?
It would be funny if I got jacked.
That would be really funny.
If you had to get jacked for your job, you should go completely Kumail.
You should get an acting gig where you have to play a fucking, I don't know.
You should be She-Hulk, dude.
Oh my God.
That'd be huge.
That'd be amazing.
You'd be huge.
In green.
Yeah.
I'm thinking about it.
You could finally play the character the way you want to see it.
Or you could get hired to do a Wario biopic movie.
And then you have to get ripped for the young Wario scenes.
Before he eats all the garlic.
Before he somehow got fat off garlic, which as far as I know has zero calories.
But he ate so much of it.
You know why he is fat, right?
Does he have a thyroid issue?
Oh, that's so sad.
Yeah, that's why he's called Wario.
Why?
I don't fucking know.
I had a teacher in elementary school, she was a very big lady, I think she did have
a thyroid problem named Mrs. Wario. But she had a U in her name. Maybe she lived in a food
dessert. Food dessert? Don't mind if I fucking do. Sounds delicious, dude. What's that, flan?
So we're mad about giving poor people food desserts? No way. So we're mad that people
are getting birthday cake and fucking crunchy candies? You know, I'll say it. You cap it.
I would love to live in a food desert.
Me too.
I'd love to live in Gourmet Race.
From Gertie.
I would live in a castle made out of Jell-O that never got destroyed.
Kim, do you still have those tums?
Jell-O.
It would look beautiful.
I mean just think about- A Jell-O castle.
I don't think it would be very convenient to live-
It would be like a Jell-O castle.
To walk around inside Jell-O, but imagine how it would look.
Like a- That's a good point.
It would just look cool.
And also, if you're going to live in a food house, you want it to be something that you
can really eat.
Like, fuck a gingerbread house.
I'm gonna live in a beef jerky apartment.
The beef jerky with no studio.
Yeah.
The beef jerky is just a square.
There's no...
All the furniture is normal.
It's just that the walls, floors and ceiling.
I don't need a kitchen. Guess what I'm fucking eating? Beef jerky.
Yeah.
Off my wall.
Yeah, it regenerates.
Man, I'm gonna live in the soup yurt.
Yeah, that's right.
It's not convenient at all.
Isn't it so fucked up that Jell-O's made out of like...
Horses?
Yeah, horses and bones.
Bones and furs.
Not really.
Would you rather them just throw the bones in the ocean?
No, it's just like...
You cap it.
It's weird that like jello is like fruit flavored.
Whenever in the store, me and Jana will walk by like the meat section and there's like
chicken hearts in like a big bucket, she'll be like, "Oh, it's so sad."
And it's like, "What else? You want them to fucking... They're either going in you or your
dog." Like that's the rule with all the weird parts of a chicken.
I'll eat any part of a chicken. I don't care. Yeah. Yeah, I've been thinking I've never had liver. Would you eat brain?
If somebody put it in front of me, maybe I think I would I feel like it's too tender
I feel like it had to be like I
Worried that I would acquire a taste for it and I could only brain the rest. Yeah, you get Kuru because you eat tongue
Yeah
Do you've eaten tongue? Yeah, I've been looking at a lot of beef tongue like it's fucking good
Like yeah, you've been looking in the mirror. Yeah, your beef tongue shredded be like a like a beef tongue
sandwich is really good. Yeah I've been looking at like those like you know
those chefs that wear like the black gloves like the pitmasters and shit on
Instagram and they've been cooking I've seen a guy cook beef tongue and I was
like like as a kid I you know what it was it was the Goonies that scared me
away from tongue. That scene where Mama Fratelli's like oh you got new food
and she goes like oh yeah we've got tongue and she pulls out the knife and
puts up the Corey Feldman's tongue. So I thought tongue every anytime you saw
tongue. You thought it was Corey Feldman's tongue. I thought it was Corey Feldman's tongue.
I don't want which is I don't want to eat anything
Yeah
right
What a sad story though, yeah, yeah, yeah, I feel so bad for that guy. Yeah, he lost his tongue just for being in a movie
They take off your tongue if you're too good of a child actor mm-hmm
What's the weirdest meat you've ever eaten come on man Michael J. Let the dead fucking rest in peace fucking yeah
Let them fucking fuck kids in hell.
Just fucking leave them alone.
Come on, dude.
Weirdest meat I've ever eaten is probably, I mean, it's probably gator.
Yeah, gator's good though.
Gator is good.
It's like chicken.
Yeah.
It's like basically exactly like chicken.
Fried gator is so good.
I think I had fried gator too.
We've talked about it before, but every like weird meat just tastes like chicken.
Yeah.
I've never had any sort of gamey meat.
I've never had like elk or anything.
You've never had venison?
You've never had wild boar?
No.
Have you?
Yeah.
- Big pig, right?
- My cousin--
- Yeah, it's like, I don't know if it was just
the preparation of it, but it was very salty.
Very like--
- There's like a ranch in California
that my cousin went to to hunt wild boar,
and they caught like one of the biggest ones
they'd ever had, and it was worth like all this
fucking money, and they could have like sold it
to the place and made a bunch of money,
but instead they were like, no, we want all this meat.
And so for like four years, he's had frozen,
it's like an entire frozen boar in his fucking freezer.
- Dude, that's fucking sick.
And he doesn't even really like it. He was just like, "Yeah, dude, it's just if somebody
comes over, I tell him the story about killing the boar and then we eat him for lunch."
Yeah.
I mean, that's not that bad.
No, there's nothing bad about it. It's not a bad story.
It's like keeping your wedding cake.
I would turn the tusk into a pencil.
Oh, okay.
That's a good idea.
You wouldn't turn it into a shofar?
I would turn it into a shofar, convert to Judaism. And I'd be like--
That was my question for him.
And he'd be like, "Here's your--"
It's good that you've answered it.
They'd be like, "Here's your shofar," and I'd be like, "Hey, buddy, brought my own."
What's a shofar?
Sorry.
A shofar is a thing that-- it's a horn.
I think it's a ram's horn that they blow in the middle of the fucking service.
So you're saying that Jews have horns?
In a way.
In a way, they do.
Yeah.
Shofars, yeah.
It's not on their head, yeah.
That thing's sick, though.
But in the middle of the service, like, the rabbi will be, like, speaking some fucking
gibberish and then you'll just hear like "BRAAAA" like the loudest thing you've ever
fucking heard and you'll look back.
That's the interrupting cow.
And it's yeah.
Exactly.
The interrupting antisemitism cow.
Yeah.
Come on man.
What?
What about that?
So it's the antisemitism cow from Twitter.
What's Twitter?
It's the interrupting cow.
I don't give a fuck about that guy.
Yeah.
We should start one of those accounts.
the way the cat boy boy the cap and white boy let's do it accounts of like two
followers that's yeah that just say like I just ate the most delicious dinner no
no cap detected yeah my son is so beautiful cap that's cap cap cap you
just got you just got attacked by the cap and white boy you capping right now
Melissa it just feels so good to hold them in my arms for one last time I'll
never love anything as much as I loved you Robert
Cap!
Why are you capping right now?
It's been four years and I miss you so much.
But it's all voice memos that we screen record and post.
You capping!
It was undead.
Like the animojis.
Yeah, exactly.
It's like the squid animoji.
Capping!
You capping.
You made me ink cap.
No cap.
No cap, I'm your cousin.
Why would we say that?
If it was to my cousin.
Do you guys have any family members who use Twitter?
I think yeah.
Yeah.
I don't, thank God.
They do, they follow me but they don't understand anything I do.
All my cousins are nerds and they fucking do math.
Yeah.
Yeah, because there are no nerds on Twitter.
That's not a nerd thing.
That's right.
I'm cool.
Cap.
Ask me a question.
Test me.
I'm cool.
Okay.
Ask him a skateboard question.
Uh, what, okay, uh...
Come on, it's not that hard to think of one.
No, it's hard.
You gotta, no, it's hard.
Come on, it's dead air right now, just ask a question.
No, he's looking at me too.
Jesus Christ!
He's doing the face again, he's doing the...
Ask him a question!
Oh my god, who's the guy that ollied over the, for the audio ad, ollied over the water
tower?
Tony Hawk.
No.
Wow.
He was cappin'.
- Caleb's a nerd. - Eric Costin.
- Eric Clapton. - No.
- Monkey Jr. - No.
- Prince Philip. - No.
- President Breasts. - President Breasts?
- Elbow at earnest.
- Well, we never had President Breasts
because of 2016 Russian interference.
(all laughing)
- Yeah, dude, now we got Vice President Breasts.
- Oh, fuck! - Yeah.
- Yeah, I think we'll have a woman president soon,
but I think it's either because Joe Biden dies of old age
or we'll have like a Nazi woman for president.
- You think we'll have a Nazi woman next?
You think that'll be, it is funny,
people are already like scared about who runs in 2024.
- Yeah, it's gonna be like,
the Republicans are gonna run like
the scariest woman of all time.
They're gonna run Ms. Trunchable.
(laughing)
- Don't even fucking say that, dude.
- The Republicans are gonna run Ms. Trunchable.
- Don't speak that into existence, okay?
God hears your thoughts and he makes them real.
don't fucking do that. She's gonna put she's gonna put Democrats in the chokie.
No. That's gonna be her slogan. I want her to put me in the fucking chokie. Hillary for chokie. She's
gonna swing AOC around by the hair and throw her out the window. Throw AOC's pigtails. I'd like to
be in I'd like to get up in Kamala Harris's chokie. I think that now that Kamala Harris is a girl as
vice president it should change it to be called nice president. That's right because she's gonna
nice nice yeah change it to female in office what the hell yeah sensitive ass
female boss ass bitch yeah the bus has bitch yeah and then they don't change it
back so then the next guy has to be called a bus you think she could do a
split what he's asking what's a split no yeah what do you mean what would she
split me and you oh enough for both of us did she has a pretty funny voice sounds
like a porn star I don't think I've ever heard her voice because she's from
California really yeah well that makes sense I guess it's just a valley accent
I love her she's got a Silicon Valley accent she's like excuse me can I be the
vice president. TJ stop. That's a Silicon Valley accent is whatever Alexa sounds like.
You think people there sound like robots? Mm-hmm. Fuck you man. What about E-40?
He's got a robot name. Okay, okay you think a rapper can be that fast without being a
robot? Oh my god dude he's a rap bot. Mm-hmm. And what do you rap god? What do you
- What do you think the E stands for?
- Electronic.
- E-mail.
(laughing)
- Electronic mail 40.
- E-mail 40?
- Yeah, and you know who 40 is?
- Who?
- A robot inventor.
- No!
Joseph 40.
He's named after his creator.
- Yeah.
Oh my God, that's terrifying.
- He was a robot.
- One, zero.
One, one.
- He's a robot programmed to make women shake their ass.
- That's right.
You and that monkey?
What a song.
Yeah.
about me and my monkey. No, he has a song where he's like, "I'm trying to see that monkey,
eww." And I was like, "She got a pet monkey in the club. God damn." She brought a capuchin
in here. They let you bring a monkey in the club now. San Francisco wild. I can't wait
to be 18. What's that, have you ever heard that E40 Cali Swag District song, "She's Getting
no what it go like it's like how'd that go the intro is like e4 to go like you
guys cookie monster yeah he just straight-up sounds like a devils he
sounds like the at the beginning it was exactly like when you throw Bowser in
Mario 64 I love him dude he's one of my favorite rappers ever most Bay Area
rappers are great yeah that song choices is so good
is Andre Andre Nicotine is a Bay Area rapper right Andre Nicotine Nila Kena is
a basketball player that's that's not that's you think you're thinking of a
different guy yeah his name's something Nila Kena Andre Nicotine is the guy
Andre the giant he's the guy that fuck was huge get that song on the last last
rap that I write do you think maybe that guy they just gave him like tiny beers
yeah it was trick photography yeah yeah they gave him the beers really far away
from the oh yeah they didn't have coronitas back then but could you
imagine Andre the Giant holding a coronita drink with his pinky yeah it's a
thimble for him yeah yeah you need the bottle he would he could eat that glass
he would think it was a wax bottle candy yeah that's right I would have loved to
be a humongous guy I yeah it's funny that there was like that was a time you
have to shit in the bathtub. I just remembered that. Andre the Giant used to have to shit
in his bathtub.
I think, okay, so the thing is, Andre the Giant--
The toilets were too small.
I think he was only like 6'8" or 6'9", but that was back when there was no like, he didn't
have a verified height and--
He was seven feet tall.
No, I don't think he was seven feet tall. But they said that he was seven foot eight
and people just believed him. But he was, I think he was closer to like 6'10", 6'11".
He was just very wide.
because people didn't know how big somebody was. He was just 6'3". Yeah. Yeah, he was 6 foot even.
Yeah. Yeah, I think, no, because they have to have his height as in his autopsy.
It says he was 7'4". Yeah. It's fake. No. Okay. I mean, there's a documentary on him that's really
good. Why wouldn't they just put that in all this information? Yeah, they're not going to not
measure. Now this one says 6'11". Yeah, I don't think he had a... See, I fucking told you. I
I don't think he had a verified height.
No, this one says 7 foot 0.
Yeah.
That guy dead is the only time you can measure him.
Because he's too big, first of all.
Well, but the thing is 6'11" is like not, I mean that's tall, of course, but it's not
like the biggest guy in the world.
The biggest guy in the world was, who is this, Dave?
A thousand feet tall.
Starts with a W.
Joe.
Charles W.
Joey Humongous.
The Hulk.
Charles Whitting?
Charles wedding that's not Charles's wedding what's the tallest man long John
silver tallest long mont long mont silver
it's they don't get it calling you fucking long Patrick John Robert Wadlow
oh yeah that's the guy that all the all the Ripley's believe it or not
yeah I'm you go they have a wax figurine of him yeah and you get to imagine his
penis Joe Rogan was the second tallest guy John Rogan oh okay there's a bit
pretty pretty big the Rogans really run the spectrum there yeah as far as height
how tall is Joe Rogan he's like five five five six you know what he's four feet one
yeah yeah he could be shorter he has no confirmed height actually yeah he's much
like the Andre yeah he knows what fucking size yeah I thought that the okay so the
tallest woman is 8 4 that's the tallest woman that's a big bitch dude current
tallest woman no she's dead oh the current tallest woman is dead or her
height is disputed but that so that the undisputed tallest woman is Zeng Jin
Lian from China. Really? Is that where she's from? You don't say. She could have been from she
could have had that name and been from San Francisco or like. Why San Francisco?
I said San Francisco or Oregon. Why San Francisco or Oregon? West Coast I don't know why I
pick those two. But, uh, say the height. She's eight foot one and three-fourths. Not that
tall. That's a man. That's not that tall. That's a huge, that's a man. Once you're over
six feet, you're a boy. No. Yeah. Anna Hanning Bates, niece one from Canada is the second
tallest woman. Whoa. She was 7'11". That's a funny height. She was 7'11"? I am 7'11".
They named all the stores after her because the guy who made 7'11" was in love with her
and he had a giant-ish fetish. I would love to have just like a humongous girlfriend.
Yeah. That'd be pretty cool, right? No, like two or three feet taller. Yeah. You know,
pick you up, put you on her back. Yeah. Carry you around like Yoda in a backpack. Yeah.
I think I want to be a baby.
Yeah.
You're almost there.
What do you mean almost there?
The head down.
You guys have the brains of babies.
You need a bonnet and a rattle.
Yeah.
Should I dress up like a baby?
Is that my next move?
Get a diaper and a rattle and a giant safety pin?
A crop top shirt.
Do I get a onesie?
No.
A baby.
You should get a pacifier.
No, because you have to look.
It's funny if you look like a Victorian baby, but if you're like an adult and you're dressing
up like a 90s baby, that's a problem. What do you mean a 90s baby? Like wearing like a Rugrats
onesie as an adult and you're and you got a binky too. Is this? That's weird but a Victorian baby,
always funny to look like. I was saying I'm gonna dress up like the New Year baby. Okay. Yeah. Okay.
And I'll also have, I'll have implanted into my head one extremely thick hair. Yeah one curly.
See that's funny. You think so? But if you're like wearing like little Pokemon footie pajamas
When did I say Pokemon? I feel like this is just something that's in your head.
I'm thinking of a specific guy. I'm thinking of Pamperchew. I don't know him.
Pamperchew was one of the most famous adult babies.
I mean the fans are gonna know. Fans are gonna go wild for this reference.
The kind of information that you have in your brain is just, it's amazing.
Yeah, I have no math knowledge but I know about an adult baby from 2008.
Yeah, I mean really. He would microwave his diapers. That's why. He was famous.
better. Well I think he had pee in the diapers. Probably smell better. Yeah.
Yeah. Probably sit there huff that fucking... I see the one, what's that video where they like
microwave the... there's like little... there's like gel inside a diaper. No that was Kipke.
That was a hack video. What was that one again? Oh was that to make snow? No, oh that was... that's
part of the video but it was a... it was Kipke's diaper pranks. Oh yeah and he melts like chocolate.
- He melts a baby Ruth into it and eats it on the camera.
- Yeah.
- That's normal.
I mean, he's eating candy.
- Exactly.
- It looks like a baby poop.
- It doesn't matter what you use for a plate.
- Also, it's not what baby poop looks like, dude.
Baby poop looks like fucking mustard.
- Green.
- Yeah.
It's horrible.
What are these kids eating?
- Yeah.
- That's why I think I'm gonna adopt.
I wanna skip the first couple years.
- You're gonna adopt?
- Yeah.
- Just solo?
You walking into an adoption agency?
- Yeah.
- I wanna get a baby.
- I'm so bored.
I need a kid.
that one yeah pointing to one of the workers yeah that's better that's Diane
she she's beautiful I want her she's my could treat her right as a father I put
it through college come here Diane she's 65 years old and you're most beautiful
baby I've ever seen I get on my shoulders come on just come to Pepe
Get on my shoulders so you can see the fair better, Diane.
Well, okay.
Diane, they'll throw the candy to you.
I love you, my daughter, Diane.
Yeah, I might adopt, but I don't want one of those, like,
one of those kids who, like, you fucking, you get the kid,
you raise it until it's like five, and then you realize
that his dad was, like, Osama Bin Laden or something.
Yeah, his dad was Darth Vader.
Well, that would kind of be a cash cow.
No.
Okay.
That's not because when Darth Vader comes back looking for his droids, you're either
getting set on fire.
I won't care.
Yeah?
I'll just kind of sit there and smile Riley.
And just be like.
Smile at Riley?
Uncle Owen.
I don't care.
Uncle Owen and Aunt Beru got their shit cooked.
Aunt Peru?
Aunt Beru.
Oh.
Yeah.
I just don't want something like that to happen so I think I'm going to make my wife shoot
a baby out of her thingy.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Adoption, we'll just say it. It's kind of lame.
I don't think it's lame.
I think it's bad.
I think it's cooler that you get to choose.
Hey, you know what I think should be adopted?
Better environmental policies by the US government.
I say just put the kids in jail.
Yeah, the adopted.
In the orphanage.
Yeah.
Like, instead of adopting them.
Orphanage is a jail.
Just put them straight to jail. That's where they're headed anyway.
[laughter]
Just fucking, just throw them in there.
You know?
Okay.
Alright.
Yeah.
(laughing)
- Right?
- Yeah.
- You're saving a lot of heartbreak here
by just throwing those kids in jail.
You know?
It's like the fucking, they don't fuck, you know,
when they're hatching chicken eggs,
they throw the male ones at a fucking grinder.
- They do?
- Yeah.
- Oh, I didn't know that.
- They grind them up into dust.
- Yeah, 'cause they'll fight.
- That's true.
- We can make the kids fight.
- Okay.
- You guys ever see those Brahman chicken?
- No.
- Nope.
- The chicken that are like five feet tall?
- Oh yes, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Oh shit, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. - Three ass legs.
- Yeah. - Yeah, they don't look
as big as they look, or they aren't as big
as they look in those videos.
- Yeah, they are pretty big. - But they are pretty big.
- Those things. - They're like two feet tall,
which is huge for a chicken.
- Right, that's still fucking terrifying.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- You would hate turkeys.
Actually, you would hate ostriches.
- No. - Now that's a big bird.
- You know what you would hate--
- When I was younger, I did. - Is a 1,000 foot tall bird.
- Yeah. - That honestly was
my biggest fear when I was younger.
Thousand foot tall bird. I was scared of birds because of Wind Waker when I was a young kid.
Did you ever see the birds Alfred Hitchcock? No, no. I saw that when I was older and I was like this is pretty lame.
Yeah, he's he's they're afraid of birds. What the hell? Most of those Hitchcock movies are pretty shitty.
Yeah, I'm not a big fan. Yeah, I like Hitchcock.
You would.
You're capping. Yeah, if it's one of those things that you're supposed to like it like it's one of it's like I understand it
I understand the merits of it, but I'm not gonna like like I'm not gonna fucking sit down and watch Citizen Kane
Yeah, I'm not gonna sit here and watch
Citizen Kane isn't
Hitchcock I know that it's not Hitchcock it is I'm just saying like like you don't need to see you can see you can see
Citizen Kane one time and I mean the truth is you don't have to watch any movies. Yeah, true. Yes. I don't it's not yeah
Yeah, I I definitely
There's so many class you do not yet. I've seen and I'll just never see yeah, I don't trust anybody
is like oh you haven't seen this bro this is you have this is the best movie ever
you have to watch this is not true the best movie ever is the movie that you
watch and you go that was cool yeah and then you watch it again a year later
i'm trying to think what movie i've probably seen more than any movie
wet hot american summer for me it could be that for me too i've probably seen that movie 10 times
i've seen that movie 15 more actually i think i've seen cars like over 100 times i've seen
reddit too yeah shit ton of times because i took french in high school and they would always be
like, "Well, we don't know what to do in class today. We're going to put on Ratatouille for
you guys." My younger brother, when he was like four, the only movie he would watch was Cars.
Yeah. So he'd watch it every single day. Yeah. Oh, that's true. Oh, dude, that's the fucking
worst thing in the world about kids. Babysitting. That's why I should adopt at like 16. Adopt a kid
at age 16. Yeah, because at least they'll have taste. Yeah, they have taste. They have their
own shit that they like, you know. But like a five-year-old, like a four-year-old or a
five-year-old, they're watching the same movie over and over.
Yeah, don't you get bored?
I think streaming has definitely solved that, but I remember my cousin's niece going over
to their house. We had to go over for like Christmas or something. It was like one of
their birthdays and my cousin was having like their party at their house, and they watched
chip-wrecked six times in a row.
Like, left them--
- Yeah, yeah.
- Fucking left it running.
They weren't in the room.
- Yeah, it was because--
- Shut it off, they freak out.
- It's because, yeah, you would just have
only so many DVDs.
- Right.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, there was a time in, like,
elementary school-- - They had more DVDs.
- I would just come home and I'd just watch
Holy Grail every day.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah, I just loved it.
Couldn't get enough of it.
- Yeah, I think the movie I've seen the most times,
if it's not Ratatouille, it might be
Between Two Ferns, the movie.
Oh yeah. That's a bummer. Yeah, no dude, against my will. I've not watched that movie once.
Watching a movie against your will is like the worst feeling. Yeah, that's bad. I'm sure
there's more bad feelings than that. No, that's the worst one. Yeah, that's the worst one
in the whole world. Yeah, when it comes to things against your will, that's definitely
the worst one. That's number one, absolutely, uncontested. Just like watching like, having
watch like Clerks or something. Fuck that movie dude. Yeah. Why do people like that shit? I liked it like it's a good movie for like a
14 year old.
I've never seen it. If a 14 year old had made it, it would be a good movie. Yeah, no it's made by a mental 14 year old.
Yeah. For 14 year olds. Yeah. But I think I had a friend who uh
in high school when he was like 16
He like forced a bunch of people to watch clerks at a party and everyone got mad at him
That's the worst kind of guys like yeah. Hey, we should watch this when I in
College I was hanging out a friend's house and this this kid came home
It was one of their one of my friends roommates and they were like, hey
I just finished the like final cut of my my like thesis film. Let's put it on and my friends just like no
We're not gonna do that. Yeah. Yeah, why the fuck you just saved us so much fucking
I would never watch somebody's thesis film or you can I mean I mean fuck terrible
I would it would be fun to
Go to watch something mean to it. Yeah. Yeah, well the person in the room. No while they're in the room
Oh, yeah, I guess you're right. Yeah, maybe on who it is. Yeah, this this person would have killed themselves. Yeah
Almost did just being denied the the right to show it against our will so yeah, yeah
Yeah, cuz it sucks. I guess it must it must
Yeah
nobody wants to watch a thesis it must suck to like spend all your time in college and like make end up making like a
45-minute film about mental illness coming to life and not a single person in the world wants to watch it
Yeah, it's like your parents. Yeah, sir watches 20 minutes of it and yeah, you did a great job. Yeah, and like I'm
Brother I'm rewatching succession for the third time. I don't have fucking time to watch this bullshit. Yeah, you know
Oh, the worst is uh, I don't know you guys probably didn't take film class
but like like the actual like like film the bolexes and shit I took that and I
why had like an idea for a project and then I couldn't do it because
Of like timing and like I couldn't get people to be in it
So then I was like, I guess I have to just shoot this over a weekend.
And it was just like a video.
It's it was a video of just like this skeleton that I had in my apartment.
And I just kind of like threw it in different places.
And I was like, yeah, this looks weird.
And then I like cut it together with like found footage.
You did a scary thing?
No, no.
And then I it wasn't even scary.
It was very, it was very stupid.
It was just like me, like figuring out how to use the camera.
So that was my final project.
I got an A for dude nice or I got like an A or a B or something and I just remember just being like that
Didn't deserve that like that phony shit in and getting a grade. You don't deserve. It's like the best feeling
Straight up. I'm sure I've said it before but in high school
I was such a bad student that like I would make my just teachers feel sorry for me and it got to the point where
One of my classes I didn't turn in my final project like at all and my teacher just gave me an a-plus
Yeah, my fucking--
Just like so I could graduate.
My film class, I got like-- that whole thing is like you can barely see anything because
I shot it indoors and I had no lighting and it's on film and I don't know how to expose
film.
Yeah.
I do not know how to use a camera at all.
Me neither.
It's all-- all of it was set to a swinging--
You just press record.
--record by--
Oh, that's what that button's for?
Yeah.
Oh, never mind.
I know how to use one perfectly.
Yeah.
I'm amazing at it.
Yeah, I can do it all day.
films. That was always the worst thing. Watching it in a classroom.
Yeah. And also having that thought of like, I know how I feel when I
have to watch your bullshit. Right. And like me being in this class and showing
you fucking whatever I made and knowing that it sucks dog dick. Yeah, because I did
it for a grade. Yeah, because like also I always felt like I had that excuse of
like, well I don't actually want to do this so I don't really care. Yeah. You
know but it was bad I put some pretty bad shit out in college oh yeah me too yeah
yeah every like group project everybody like I I was always the person who
didn't do any of the work that's the best feeling in the world yeah getting
an a on a project that you did nothing on yeah when I I took it I took a game
design class like a board game design class in college and what a fucking
stupid such a stupid school but that my my group project I I mean I literally
really did nothing yeah and we I think that those guys are like trying to make
that a real board game now and like a cell and I just did absolutely nothing
and they're like my favorite so if they so I could sue them yeah I think I
probably will yeah I mean why my favorite group project shit to do is if
there was one person who wasn't doing anything just like make a slide with
nothing but like bullet points with no like with no like tag and just be like
all right you take this slide it's like it's just a bullet point that says like
like the effects of the effects of yeah cuz I'm also like all right go ahead
read the slide I'm doing nothing in the project I'm also just completely tuning
out yeah yeah every no it's so funny to just yeah to like till if I know what
I'm talking about I'm always gonna do that to someone who doesn't because it's
funny the worst worst class I had that happen in was that sex and comedy
seminar thing I took where we had to do sexy comedies yeah we do a project on a
movie that is only available on a DVD that the teacher has. I looked up the
movie because I was like, "Ah, maybe I could like stream this so I can miss the
class that day." It's like a $35 DVD on Amazon that like a Goodwill in
like Fresno has. Sometimes you got to bite the bullet, dude. I almost bought it, dude.
I almost bought it, but I knew it wouldn't have come in time. So I like watched the
movie in class, had to go that day, didn't take any notes, and then had to do like
a presentation on it with this kid named Wade and he fucking carried that project.
Wait, Wade Wilson? Yeah, Wade Wilson. Deadpool? Yes. Dude, he put the team on his
back for that one. Deadpool put the team on his back. I did fucking nothing and then
the whole time I was like, "Hey man, I had a pretty weird weekend. I've been working
so much." Which I was working at the time. Yeah, you don't understand how bad I've been
eating. You don't understand. I had to do a bunch of... I had to do a bunch of shit.
Sorry dude, I'm experiencing like a bunch of weird brain fog recently.
So, I just can't do anything right now.
My bad.
I saw a DVD online that was too much money.
I've been spiraling.
The idea of a movie being that much was too much on my brain.
It actually put me in a really, really dark mental spot and place.
You know what it was though?
I also had to do...
I have a migraine because it's raining.
I had to do the readings for that class and all the readings.
I think I posted one of the things before.
is probably taken down now, but it was like a thing about like the normal and the abnormal,
and it's just the sentence is just repeating the words like normal and abnormal, abnormality.
It's just academia is the stupidest fucking thing.
My, there are, there are, I think, 12 professors at that school who think that I had a grandma die
during their class.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because I was like, sorry, either I had to leave class earlier or didn't come to class
because my grandma just died. Yeah. And actually I'm not gonna be there next
week either because that's when the funeral is. Yeah. Oh and I won't be there
the week after that because... Because I'll be crying. Because then I'm gonna be
crying so hard, seriously. Yeah. Oh and then I have to take over her ranch. Yeah.
That's gonna be the next week. Oh and then after that they're doing a TV show
about me running the ranch by myself. It's gonna be on A&E, tune in. And then
I'm gonna be at the Golden Globes after that. Yeah. Which I know the Golden
Globes aren't that weak, but they pre tape it. Don't tell anyone. I might write a
paper on that or something and that could I could work as a as a thing show you my
Golden Globe. Mm-hmm. I did win it. I could get I could get Homer Simpson to come
speak to the class. Yeah, so in the end this is gonna be really good for you. As
long as it's this could make your career. This could make your career. You could no
longer be a fucking 35 year old failed filmmaker teaching. I'm gonna get Homer
Simpson in your indie movie yeah I'm Homer Simpson he's gonna play the lead
he's gonna be in it just make sure you have doughnuts on set god damn you dude
there is it did you guys ever have like one of those kids at school who just
like yes I did have a kid at school me too let's move on now what I told you
guys about that I like one kid showed a film that he made and randomly Matt
Damon was in it and then at the end it was like executive producer Chris Damon
and it was like his nephew or something and he was like hey uncle Matt come be in
my right in my vidi yeah so stupid yeah that's so crazy dude it's like you're
you're hacking right you're like no clipping through college I put Matt
Damon and all your projects yeah cuz if I'm a professor I'm gonna be like
beast mode I feel like if I was a professor I would be like I would be
like I would create it worse. Yeah. If I saw that Matt Damon's nephew was
putting Matt Damon in his projects I'd be like all right you're failing.
Zero. I hate Matt Damon. Yeah I hate him after what he did to me. That's right. And
then don't elaborate even though he did nothing to me. Yeah. So you're gonna have a hard time in this
class. Mm-hmm. Yeah. I just want to let you know if any of you guys know Matt Damon
you're gonna want to drop the class. Finding out that he's his nephew pretty
early on and then just like just shitting on Good Will Hunting for the rest of the
semester. And Matt Damon, and now let's talk about some of the worst actors in
history for example Matt Damon. You know what else about Matt Damon? All his
family members are ugly. I mean what a fucking what an untalented fucking family
Jesus Christ. It makes sense I mean go to school in Boston. How many fucking lemons can you fit in one name?
Going to Boston and being related. Why are you talking so quiet today?
makes sense that he was at that school in Boston and met Damon's nephew that is so
true I feel like you just like reversed the order of that sentence yes I did
yeah I feel like in I'm feeling like you there I'm like that Damon's nephew right
now I feel like Matt Damon right and I'm feeling like Matt damn damn I got born
I'm born again I'm born again Christian Matt Damon is he born again Christian no
born like B-O-U-R-N-E. B-J-O-N. Yeah born, born, my born identity is Catholic.
What's up? That's right. That's fucking right. I was baptized. My born identity was baby.
Yep. Yeah. I bathe in the blood of Christ. I'd like to bathe in the blood of Christ.
Dude you cap. The blood of the Buddha. All cholesterol. Dude was Buddha, Buddha was a
real guy right? Yeah Buddha was a real guy. Dude imagine. Is he funny? He was fat so he's
funny. Okay I don't think he actually was fat. No he was. Oh. His name was Siddhartha
right? His name was Kevin. His name was Kevin Buddha. Yeah. And he was just a
regular guy. Until one day he got fat. He got really fat. And people came to rub
his belly. Did they rub his belly like a like a dog? Yeah. Dude. He sat under a tree
eating his curds and whey and then a spider came. Spider came and scared the crap out of him.
He must have been rich dude. It's pretty hard to get fat back then. Yeah. Rich of mind and spirit.
He was pregnant with knowledge. Oh my god. He was pregnant with the truth. He was pregnant with
Questlove. Yeah. Uh-huh. Mm-hmm. And Questlove played on his drum, belly like a drum. Mm-hmm.
Like he does. That cat, that cat is jazzy on those drums. That's some real shit, dude.
No cap detective. No cap detective. That Questlove fool, he goes stupid on those hams. Imagine Donald
Trump quote tweeting someone and just saying "cap" in all capitals with a bunch of exclamation points.
cap baron actives
you can't
and it's going to be a very great that's kept him to nobody's got more than me
nobody's going to do it
n_b_c_ news all you do is get by and i don't remember
and made on the ground and i don't drop in a new s_i_a_ acting
dark camping i'm here to suck you what do you think is next move is which a l
prison
Wait, jail and prison?
Yeah, they're gonna cut him in half but half in jail, I haven't proven.
God, I'm so fucking scared right now for Randy Rainbow.
Why?
What's he gonna do?
He's gonna go to jail too.
What's Randy Rainbow gonna do now?
What about that other bitch who lives in...
Sarah Cooper?
Yeah, what are they gonna do? They're screwed.
See, Donald Trump again taking away jobs from people of color and queers.
Yeah, queers.
(laughter)
Whoa!
What?
People of color and queers!
(laughter)
I forgot the word for LQBT, I forgot the whole phrase.
Queers!
(laughter)
You can't say that.
Why?
Taking away jobs from BIPOC, fucking queers!
I realize now that's what it sounded like. That's not what it sounded like, it's what you said. That's not how I meant it.
That's funny. I meant the LGBTQ community. So you think there are a bunch of queers?
No. Okay, I think the last letter is. Is it queer? The Q is queer.
What did you think it stood for?
Quasi.
Questlove.
Questlove!
[laughter]
Yeah, he's got something going on.
Yeah.
Questlove has a sandwich at that restaurant near Canal Street.
Oh!
What the fuck are you talking about?
He has Questlove--
That restaurant near Canal Street?
You didn't-- it was when we first came-- or the first time I was ever in New York,
I saw Questlove had a sandwich at some place.
I don't remember that.
It was a Questlove steak and cheese.
Okay.
Let me look up the questions.
You don't have to.
We don't have to do this, Pat.
Well, now I want to go eat it.
No.
What are we going to do for our last meal in New York City?
I can't eat another meal.
Yeah, dude, I can't.
We're going to go to Harvey's in Boston.
We're going to go to what we're fucking talking about.
Yes.
Yeah.
Are you guys going to miss the Big Apple?
Yeah, I want to come back soon.
You will be back soon.
Questlove launches cheesesteak sandwich made with plant-based impossible meat.
That ain't fucking steak.
No.
you clapping you clap you clapping you clapping right now quest love quest love
clapping all right I have to get some water yeah you guys don't don't move in
this four minutes left oh you can just okay fine I'll do the best I don't give
a fuck in Harvey Fierstein great voice yeah yeah I think I think if I had the
one of those ways should hit him up mmm this is a business idea I should have
kept to myself and you're gonna steal it ways yeah he's is gonna steal your idea
for ways they are ways is a that's an Israel company yeah yeah they're gonna
do fucking brain robbery on you dude they're gonna send some fucking
inception ninjas come hack your brain you know Patrick Stinnean that's me
Patrick Stein. Patrick Stein? This is what we're going with? Israel versus
Patrick Stein. This is how we're capping off the episode? Patrick Stein? Yep. Okay.
Free Patrick Stein. No, no, no, let's keep it going. Yeah. Okay, Patrick Stein.
Where's that? It's in Israel. It's in? Okay, so that's interesting. Kind of
making a weird insinuation there about where Palestine is. I know where
Palestine is. Yeah like you just said you think it's in Israel? No. Yeah. Again I
forgot a word. Inside of Israel. No I think Israel's inside of Palestine and they
they should they should be fair about it. Okay. I think maybe if we went over there
and showed them Barney's sharing song. Showed them a couple fucking. That's right. If we
played the sharing song from Barney over there in Israel and Palestine I think
shit would have got solved in five minutes.
- Yeah, knock it off guys.
- Yeah. - Guys, sharing is caring.
- Can you guys just take a break?
Here, take five.
You're not you when you're hungry.
(laughing)
And they both turn into Israelis.
Oh shit, nevermind.
Give me that back.
- What did I do?
- Oh fuck.
Nevermind.
(laughing)
- Oops, oops, oops.
- I take all that, nevermind.
- Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
- I thought this would go a different way.
Shit, ah, fuck.
no no no no no no no see you see tonight's top story a big oopsie in
Israel another in a series of Israel oopsies
Mohammed Al Dura video every fucking like every story that comes out of like
the West Bank is just described as an oopsie on CNN looks like is Reezy made
another oopsie-zee fo-shee-zee another Israeli oopsie another big ouchie yeah
another big ouchie for Palestine yeah Israel made an oopsie which caused an
ouchie in Palestine one death on the Israeli side 900 ouchies on the
the palestinian side. That rocks listen. I think Gigi might be ready for her baba.
That's a notification I got from my mom. Not from your mom, from your amazon echo.
My mom's amazon echo. It's crazy that you have one of those in your house dude. My mom
does. That's psycho. I would put tape over it like a webcam. Yeah, just tape over the
microphone. Tape over the entire thing. The guy in the amazon surveillance office just
was like my mouth is on the Alexa play Kesha playing guess up there's a hole in
the wall it's a dirty free-for-all I wish it I wish Alexa sung the songs then
I think I might buy one. Yeah. Yeah, it's kind of like a gag. You can make Alexa sing things.
I can make her do whatever I want. I'm gonna make her sing like a canary. You know she can tell you
a joke. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I knew that. Isn't that awesome? It's so good. You know what, I guess I
will buy one. She can tell you a joke. She can help me work on my stand-up. She can work on my
material with me. She'll love it, dude. I think that joke has problems in the third act structure.
You don't put an act in a joke.
The third act structure?
That movie is a movie.
I'm gonna kill myself.
What happens if you say that to Alexa?
Does she say no?
They give you the suicide hotline.
They play that song by Logic.
Here is the number for the suicide hotline.
I've been on the road.
I just wanna die today.
Imagine that song saving your fucking life.
Who can relate, dude?
that's it really it saved a few people's lives I think yeah no no yeah it had to
have right yeah I didn't like fucking a couple people who were like I'm not
gonna do it yeah and then probably like high schoolers or middle schoolers yeah
probably like some seven-year-old we should just every song every song should
be about not killing yourself yep we how many lives could we save then oh my god
I think we found the next angle for the thanks to sensitive gangster album I
think we're making a suicide is a joke suicide makes you go to hell yeah that'll
be one of them suicide kills the you inside oh and the you outside yeah you
die when you do and the kills the you inside and the you outside I'm outside
suicide and then you look out the window Caleb's outside what about this what
about a song called I'm killing me smalls right yeah I could be a better baseball
player and we could get Patrick ready to do it we should do the sensitive me
smalls all the songs about suicide yeah definitely because only anti-sew is that
fucking dude this is an epidemic fuck the coronavirus a cab a demic this is a
cabinet these people cap into themselves and they're ugly they're worthless they
deserve to live. Everybody deserves to live. You're all beautiful. You're all beautiful.
Inside and probably just inside if you're killing yourself. Yeah. Probably pretty ugly
outside. Yeah. But I'm not gonna let you. I'm not gonna let you kill yourself. You know
why? Because you can't make your own decisions. Because you're too stupid. This album is dedicated
to Jonathan Brandes. Yeah. Don't do it kids. I only know one. That's like the one teen
actor who killed himself that I know. There's that girl who drank bleach. Oh yeah, well
that's then we're taking the Uncle Adams. Yeah. We're just stealing from
Uncle Adams, we can't do that. Yeah, we've stolen enough from him. His swag. His swag,
his G kind of feel. Yeah, his different level of thinking. His pimp walk.
Oh my god, he showed us how to do it and he started the show. He kind of was like
the architect of the game. Uh-huh. You know. He really is. He's the game's architect.
Yeah. So true. And we're carrying on the torch. We're carrying on the legacy. What'd you say?
You're Karen. I said Cameron. Karen Fedder. All right, I gotta get these boys home.
Bye. Don't kill yourself.