you're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
We can talk about the houses real quick, actually.
We can talk about our Harry Potter houses.
Patrick would be Hufflepuff.
Patrick is Hufflepuff, apparently.
I did take the test.
Which test? Is there an official one?
an official sorted hat thing. Does it have a proctor? No. It's just some fat guy. It's
a fat nerd in a rope. It's a fat guy in a witch hat. In a rope. Yeah, you're in some
middle school. At 730 taking the placement test. Like the ACT. Yeah. He walks up and
down the aisles and he smells you. It's just like British school. Yeah. But I did take
- Because that's their standardized test they take.
- Their standardized test in England
is they have to take the Harry Potter house.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- But I did take it on the Harry Potter website.
- Pottermore.
- Pottermore, yeah.
My Hogwarts house is Hufflepuff
and the United States one is like Ilvermorny or something.
- There's a United States Harry Potter.
- They have US different houses?
One second, I have to look up this.
I have to look up this.
You know what, that's what we're doing today is you guys are going to take your Pottermore
quizzes.
I'll take a Pottermore quiz.
Yeah.
Pottermore.
Let's go.
This is so fucking stupid.
Alright.
Googling Pottermore quiz.
Let me see.
Yeah.
Oh, you also get, if you, I think if you take another test on there, you can get what wand
type you have.
I have to log in with my wizarding passport?
Okay, I do not have a wizarding passport.
You do have to log in with your wizarding passport.
So you created an account for this?
i did two years ago
that's awesome did you can sign in with google
i'm okay
yeah i'm not going to go yet that we are doing in the room
we have to confirm that caleb is a slither in the caleb slither and i'm
ravenclaw i'm obviously slid it does i don't have to take the test
i'm what's the united states school called i want to find the four houses
uh...
fuck
potter more on the so i found it i found out that they're called
it's called a little more knee
the houses are still use such a british and the houses are waiting for serpent
puck what i was gonna ask you what uh...
the
the schools
the harry potter u_s_ school was
it's over morning
here's how i didn't get over more yet you already said that
uh... the four options you can get our horned serpent serpents puck wedgie
thunderbird and wampus
paragraph g that's the one i got a couple of what i got like an ablation like a
cryptid it's like a little man
i'm not going to put what g_m_i_ i'm a hufflepuff and i'm a puck would be
uh... i'm i'm getting those are
here's what they did one test we don't know if you know that's really unfair
listen
these are the descriptions of the four houses for a gap for the u_s_ school
horned serpent
a great horned river serpent with a jewel set into its forehead i guess it's just
just the description of what the creatures are yeah but it's a little
unbalanced puck wedgie a short gray face large eared creature Thunderbird a
creature that can create storms as it flies and whampus a magical panther like
a magical panther like creature that is fast strong and almost impossible to
kill yeah it's pretty one of those the boys yeah yeah you want to be a mortal or
Do you want to be a puck wedgie?
Yeah, do you want to be a short, gray-faced creature?
I'm a fucking puck wedgie, dude.
I'm a puck wedgie.
Yeah, the trade-off is you have to, it's called a wampus.
You have to say, "I'm a wampus."
Still better than puck wedgie.
Yeah.
They had an announcement video for it.
Whoa.
Yeah.
It's huge.
Big news.
More big news, separately.
The UCB is gone.
Oh yeah.
Oh my God.
This is our first post-UCB episode.
- Oh my gosh, finally.
- Never been to the building.
I've never stepped foot in a, I've never taken a class.
I've never taken an improv class,
but this really affected me deep.
- Yeah, me too.
You guys know I have a history with UCB.
And so I actually wrote a little,
I wrote a little memorial for them.
- Whoa.
- Do you guys wanna hear it?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
What was the Upright Citizens Brigade?
A name that will forever echo through the hallowed halls of comedy alongside other titans of
improv like Greg Proops and Big L. It was also a place, much like Cambodian death camps
or the murderous castle of H.H. Holmes were both places.
It was a school, a school that marketed itself as accredited even after it lost its accreditation
in 2017 due to a lack of handicap accessibility, which is actually something they told me when
I worked there.
That is true.
But the UCB was more than a name, more than a place, more than a school.
It was a family.
A family of weirdos, freaks, rapists, CIA agents, cannibals, and very funny women.
They say improv theatres die twice.
Once when its blatant mismanagement leads to declining ticket sales, empty classes, and
the eventual closure of the theatre, and the second time when somebody speaks its name
one final time while describing where exactly they were sexually assaulted.
UCB, the place that, when asked whether or not they are in fact a cabal of satanic pedophiles,
they responded with a hearty "Yes, and."
You are already so missed.
And as a former employee of the UCB, Caleb knows more than anyone.
That is true.
As someone who was let into their little satanic pedo cabal.
I was.
I got to see behind the curtain.
It was awesome, man.
It was perfect.
It was like, every day was that scene in Broad City when Hillary Clinton walks in.
Yeah, because she was walking in every day to pick up a new baby.
Yeah, yeah, dude. It fucking rocked, man. This one's for you, UCB. We miss you, boys.
We're pouring one out for the UCB. We're re-watching that sketch where Amy Poehler
does Chinese Face. Yeah, dude.
The sickest thing ever is to make every single improv scene just about how everyone is retarded
in gay until 2014 and then be like,
"If you ever talked like that, you're a piece of shit."
- Yeah.
- So we miss them, man.
I'm pouring out this bottle of Adrenochrome for you guys.
Seriously, I mean it.
- Yeah.
Wow.
- We should start our own improv theater.
- We're gonna watch, we're watching that,
the live episode of the UCB show season one
and we're looking for Nick Kroll and Paul Shearer
in the crowd.
- Oh my God, I'm so excited.
I love being a fan.
we're looking for a new cruel and his highness college years with his little
glasses
he had little glasses
yeah
the a_f_ little cubes at the end of the pieces of flaws you put it at his head
you know i just feel awful for you know like the next generation of
underage girls will never get to know the magic
of
of chris get their asking them to do is not this
all my god
there is a doubt that this is leaves a huge void
it's true it's such a it's such a hole in the comedy community you know i mean a
whole the normal you see the way to aggressively try to talk about
the
we miss him yet we're starting our own improv theater it's called the
it's called the citizens
down down right down right down right down right down right down right
players club
the p_c_
that's right
and everybody's everybody's invited everybody and we change the rules you
can say no and now
yeah that's right much whatever you want
you honestly had said it's exactly said bastion for free speech and improv
you the improv doesn't have to be funny
i'm like a doesn't seem to be a
i'm not going to be so funny or it had to be super funny and it didn't have to
be like uh... why did your character make that choice and it's like
my characters peter griffin
(laughing)
- We should do those shows where we,
all of our shows are those awesome improv shows
where you actually get involved as the audience
and we go and we grab your phone.
- Yeah.
- And we actually do improv from your phone.
- We do Tinder live.
- We do, we actually look at Tinder live.
- Yeah.
- And we make you fuck the person.
- We do live Tinder.
- I'm serious.
- And we.
- We grab your phone and we write down the phone number
of every contact with a female name.
yeah
that's all those shows were
they would be like
"oh and you ma'am, can I see your phone?" and they're just air dropping all the photos to themselves
"it's improv you cunt"
man it's so crazy how like
he's got it
I've got it
it's so crazy how that uh...
how it didn't survive
Who would have thought?
Yeah, who would have thought?
That would have been unsustainable.
20 years of not paying comedians.
And Amy Poehler opening up a winery.
Yeah, who would have fucking thought?
And Besser and fucking Wong.
And Besser leaving his credit card all over the office for random interns to take photos
of.
It just makes no sense.
It's like how'd you lose that?
They're making a pot themed stand up show partnered with Lyft.
Yeah, Besser's spending all that money.
That didn't pull them out the hole?
Spending all that money on research
on how to shrink a man's arms.
God damn dude, it will be missed, you know?
Truly.
I think I swallowed something wrong.
Yeah, I bet you did.
You know what I got?
Swallowed a germ, dude.
Yeah, I swallowed a big bug.
You remember, remember townhouse flip sides?
What?
The flip side crackers, they're half cracker, half pretzel.
Sounds like me.
That's true, because you're half white, half German.
That's why you shaved your head.
No.
Yeah, that's why you shaved your head.
Take it back.
No, I shaved my head because I'm in Slytherin.
Yeah.
I got recruited by Slytherin in prison.
yeah I have all these Slytherin tattoos from prison and they made me shave my
head and now we're gonna go beat the shit out of some hufflepuffs for speaking Spanish at lunch
you're standing there with like the Deathly Hallows tattoo on your chest and
you're pointing at your stepdad you're going see this that means not welcome
fuck no I don't remember those those pretzels that you eat oh yeah they're
half pretzel half cracker.
And I haven't had them since I was-
The thin pretzels?
The pretzel crisps?
Yeah, the thin pretzel crackers.
No, no, not pretzel crisps.
They're called townhouse flip sides.
That's- they're called pretzel crisps.
I haven't had them, I haven't eaten them since I was like 13 and they were at my friend's
house and his mom got mad at me because I ate the whole box.
You know, in the past I've made jokes about like Patrick has an encyclopedic memory of
the last time he ate every single food but yeah really does things he has a
Okay, okay. Of anything...
Of anything...
Other than like...
Yeah, I'm actually a genius.
No, no.
I have a good memory when it comes to...
I have a good memory when it comes to
things like stupid shit like
that.
Food. That's what we're saying.
Food and skateboard stuff.
You have a Sherlock Holmes Mind Palace that you go into
that is a
version of Disney's Magic Kingdom
made out of cotton candy and gumballs and you walk through the halls looking at the paintings
of all the food and they all have plaques that say your coordinates of where you last
ate them.
Well yeah, I know that one, I remember that one because my friend's mom got mad at me.
I have an encyclopedic knowledge of every time someone's been mad at me.
Yeah?
When was the last time I was mad at you?
in New York when I didn't know how to put the cups away at the pit where I was I
was too high and I didn't know we were standing behind what's her fucking
Rachel's Senate and I was like Caleb I don't know where to put my cup yeah
Patrick didn't he never it was a bar and he didn't think to put the cup back on
the bar well okay I was very sick I was very sick that trip he was very sick and
and he had he had taken a whisper of weed yeah yeah I was also actively having an
allergic reaction to Prilosec OTC isn't that an is that an allergy medicine that
- That is a heartburn medication.
- Oh, yeah, so yeah, I forgot about that.
- Mm-hmm, I gotta add that.
- You were probably fucked up, man.
- Yeah, I had that rash, I drank a bunch of Monster Energy.
- We were in New York for like--
- Drank a bunch of gin and tonics.
- We were in New York for like 36 hours,
and eight hours in, Patrick was like,
"Man, I miss home so bad."
(laughing)
And he kept talking about how bad he wanted to go home.
- Patrick is a hobbit.
- He is, too.
I got absolutely a hobbit. Caleb's an orc. I don't care. I'm not an orc. Yeah you are an orc and I'm a wizard.
No you're Cameron you're a fucking wood elf. I'm a wizard. They don't have wood elves. If anyone is a legolas it's Cameron.
Legolas is not a wood elf. There's elves. Okay that's you. No. Yeah you're a legolas. No I'm Aragorn.
He's uh, you are not Aragorn.
I'm Aragorn.
He's Smeagol.
I'm the Witch King of Angmar.
Caleb's Gimli because he's short.
I'm Mario and Luigi.
You guys are both Gimli.
I am taller than you, Patrick.
Now that you've shaved your head, you're definitely not taller than him.
Yeah, you're not going to be taller than me now because you don't have the height of your hair.
Listen to me, I will pay to have a doctor measure us.
Okay.
I'm serious.
pay a doctor to measure us.
Fine, you're not gonna like the answer you gave.
I am gonna like it.
No.
You're gonna like being short?
That's a big step.
No, I'm taller than you.
You're gonna like being short.
You're gonna like being short because then you can go...
I'm so much taller.
Then you can do...
Maybe at one time you were taller than me, but the weight of your body has compressed
your bones.
It's not true.
It's pulling him down to the ground.
You are five feet, if that.
You shaved your head and you lost six inches of height.
That's not true.
Yeah, you did.
You lost six inches.
You had a kid in play.
You had a thinning kid in play haircut.
No.
And you would do the kid in play dance.
To by yourself and no one would join in.
That's not true.
'Cause no one wanted to joke with you.
I always measure to the top of my head
and not the top of my hair.
No, you measure to your hair.
You on the other hand, you're also a liar.
No.
Yeah, you're a compulsive liar.
You're lying right now.
I mean, well think about this.
Hufflepuff versus Slytherin.
Slytherin's more likely to lie.
Yes, exactly.
No, Slytherin is more likely to be evil.
exactly and the line is lying no line here are not knowing that i'm not even
like the same thing okay not slither is more likely to lie but who's more likely
to fib
it's what you're saying i'll tell you awful pop
how about this full of favors now pop up with the off is full of favors not true
it is whether in your city or is it your you realize you're defending your harry
potter house right now yeah
So are you. And you're short. So are you. No I'm not.
Okay then say Slytherin's are liars.
Slytherin's are liars but I'm not a Slytherin. You're a Slytherin. See he's lying.
He's lying right now. He's lying right now because it supports his evil agenda.
I don't have an evil agenda. You do. You Dr. Evil looking motherfucker. I don't have an evil agenda.
If anything I look like a mix between Dr. Evil and many people. And Kevin Spacey.
and can you look like a of mixed between doctor even kevin spacey
no you look like the end of gold member
that's not true
here you do
uh... you look like boom buff from the line king
you look like tomorrow and cuz you were your shorts i can't imagine or determine
tomorrow's a smart one doesn't matter is still small
did the actor played a minute ahead one of the most amazing broadway careers you
can have
though so now he's gay to he was gay but and that's fine to be gay
See dude, you can't beat me.
Yes I can.
No you can't.
I've already beaten you
because you're shorter than me.
I already beat you in the height race.
I'm not sure I'm way, I'm taller than you.
I'm probably an inch and a half taller than you.
No, we've already measured this.
We're the same height.
(laughing)
No.
Yeah, well now you're shorter than me.
Because you cut your hair.
Can we talk about something else?
Yeah, let's talk about something else.
What do you want to talk about?
Let's talk about the NFL draft.
- No.
- Who was that guy that, what was his name?
Something Headley or something or Heidley.
The guy who was obsessed with fucking Big Bird.
Did you see him?
- Oh yeah, that was awesome.
- Dude, that guy rules.
- He had all the tweets like,
what if Big Bird did a drive-by?
- Yeah, the best one was,
what if Big Bird walked up to you and said,
"Hey, where's Sesame Street at?"
(laughing)
- I mean, what if, what would you do?
- Yeah, what would you guys do?
- Honestly, those are great questions.
- I would say--
Let's look them up and let's answer each one.
I would probably be pretty sarcastic, like Todd Berry.
And I'd be like, I don't know.
You look like Todd Berry because you're bald.
Shut up.
I would be like, I don't know.
I don't know.
I would probably be like, I don't know, ask yourself.
I would pull out Google Maps and I would send him on a journey.
I'd put him on a wild big bird chase just for my own amusement.
I'd pull out my cannon and I'd say to him, "I would do..."
Yeah.
Pull out my bird cannon.
And shoot him with a sesame seed.
Load him in with a plunger.
Yeah, I'd be like, "Yeah, it's due north.
Hop in."
Yeah.
I'd say, "Hey."
It would suck though, 'cause he would obviously be followed by a fried chicken salesman who
wants to use his meat.
Yeah, he really is the golden goose of the fried chicken industry.
What kind of bird is he? Is he a chicken?
He's chicken.
Cheese, bird, poultry.
You should call him Big Chicken.
Yeah.
No, they already have a big chicken in Muppets.
Mm-hmm.
Well, Gonzo fucks chickens.
What?
Yeah, Gonzo fucks chickens.
I don't think you're allowed to say that, man.
No, that's true.
No.
Gonzo has a wife that's a chicken, and her name's Camilla.
- Yeah, but we don't know what they do.
- Nobody fucks in Muppets, dude.
There's--
- Then explain Muppets Christmas Carol
when the boys are frogs and the girls are pigs.
- It's called love.
- Yeah. - It's called frog-pig love.
- Yeah, that's just nature.
- That's just what nature happens, dudes.
- That's just when nature calls, buddy.
- That's just what nature does.
- Yeah, so relax.
- Yeah, just relax for a second.
Lay back and let it happen.
- You're freaking out.
Patrick's on air freaking out about Muppets having sex dude.
I'm not freaking out.
I'm just saying.
You sound like OJ dude.
Right before he killed his wife.
That's probably what he sounded like.
He probably was like, "I'm not freaking out!"
And then he killed her so you should tell Dom to watch out.
I'm saying that if Big Bird's name was...
Dude you're off the rails right now dude.
If Big Bird's name was Big Chicken, Gonzo would try to fuck Big Bird.
They wouldn't.
It doesn't make sense.
doesn't make no name doesn't matter if you were named Pamela Anderson I
wouldn't try to that's not true well no cuz then it would specify what kind of
bird he is not if it's just his name but we are you know what is it already
chicken no matter what he's not a chicken he's a big bird he's a single
he's a one-of-a-kind he's one of God's limited edition he's a special he's a
legendary. He's a very special bird. He's a legendary drop. Can you buy a
Big Bird outfit or is that like... I mean you can't. It's illegal. You can but it's like off.
It's illegal to impersonate Big Bird because you could go around giving
advice to people and they would take it because they think you're Big Bird.
I think you probably would get in trouble if you if you made a perfectly
accurate Big Bird. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's why you gotta make the legs like green or
something. Yeah. Or add a beauty mark. Yeah. Or a bikini. Add a penis. Put a bikini on it.
Big Bird with big jugs. Yeah. Big Bird, where'd you get those big
humongous jugs? Nowhere. I don't know. I've always had them. That's what he says.
Yeah. I've always had them. I just got my feathers cut. Yeah. They CGI them out for
show but I've always had humongous juicy tits that are you can't even hide them in a shirt dude just
big succulent big burp I would love I would love to do a wet t-shirt contest with all the
muppets and see who comes out on top I got a strong feeling miss piggy yeah yeah miss piggy had the
hams dude that's true what about um good I bet the muppets would smell really bad if you got them all
wet yeah yeah you're right hands the wet dirty hands in them for they make them
out of dog hair so yeah they make them out of dead dog skin yeah yeah that's
what I'm like the meat is still attached on the inside instead of telling my kids
that we brought the family dog to a farm I'm gonna say we shipped him off to Jim
henson and he turned him into a muppet yeah so don't worry he's dead you don't have to tell your
kids that well they turned jim henson to a muppet too and they did they scalped him yeah yeah they
just turned his scalp it's a muppet but just with a human scalp like the scalp is the mouth
yeah kind of pull it with the string so it's like doing that yeah and they use jim henson's dick as
the nose. That's the only part that's used. Did you know Gonzo's nose was modeled after
Jim Henson's penis? The puppeteer had to put the penis into the puppet in the nose to control
the nose. To move it, yeah. Like that jackass thing where he puts his penis in the puppet
and the snake bites it. Or is it a tarantula? It's a scorpion. No, no, no, it's a snake.
Is it?
Because the scorpion was when he's upside down his chin is like.
Oh yeah, when he's doing the pops thing.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, that was fucking Corn Pop's mascot for a long time.
That was big for a while.
Doing the upside down chin thing.
Fuck.
They didn't even come up with that.
You guys are talking about Corn Pop?
We're talking about Corn Pop with a chain.
Yeah, yeah.
From TV.
He used to touch Joe Biden's blonde leg hair.
And he used to have a mask on?
They used to put their heads upside down and then pretend that it was a child.
And then they would put googly eyes on their chin and then sit upside down and then lick
Joe Biden's leg hair.
That's foul.
That's just foul, dude.
I'm not going to say anything.
I'm going to not say anything just in case Weezer's lawyers get mad at me.
It's a bad move.
That was in foul taste, Patrick.
That was downright vile to hear from you.
Coming out of your little pink mouth.
That was disgusting.
(Laughter)
Oh my god, no, dude.
What?
I just grabbed a stress ball
from... I'm recording
in my little brother's room, so I'm at this like
very tiny table.
It's like a stress ball with beads
in it, and I guess he poked a hole
in it because I squeezed it, and all the
paint is all over me now. Damn. This fucking sucks. Oh fuck. What color is it? It's white
dude. Oh yeah. I know what he's been doing. You know what he's been using that hole for.
Uh huh. Come on man. That's what he got in it. That's what he got in it. Oh. What the?
That's what he put in the stress ball. What in the? He's a kid. This is my kid brother
man. What is Patrick? This is your worst episode yet dude. Patrick you gotta shut your silky
little lips. Yeah, before I fuck him. Stop saying my mouth is nice. You have a nice mouth,
dude. There's nothing weird about it. I would love to see Patrick without teeth. Just see
what it looks like. We can make that happen. Probably. Get us to 10,000 a month on the
Patreon and we'll remove all of Patrick's teeth. 10,000 a month, I will get one of my
teeth removed. You should get um... Can we agree to that? You'll get one tooth pulled.
If we get 2,000 a month, I will go to the dentist.
If we get 10,000 a month, you will get a tooth pulled.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, and if we get a month--
I'll go every day, I'll spray this tooth with germs.
Okay, what kind of germs?
At 20,000 a month, Pat's gonna get plastic surgery, so he's gonna be one of those alligator
toys where you push down the tooth, and you push it down into his gums.
And he bites every time, though.
Yeah.
But it's okay, because every time you push a tooth down, it's a little gummier and a
little sweeter.
That's true.
It's fine.
It's Patrick's sweet, gummy mouth.
That's such a terrifying game, dude.
What, the alligator game?
Yeah, dude.
Scary if you're a bitch.
No.
No, I have one that's Godzilla.
The problem is, you guys never saw alligators.
We had alligators in my backyard.
I've seen one in a book.
I saw alligators.
They brought alligators to my school.
Alligators in my backyard, dude.
What?
They brought baby-
Who's we?
Or they?
- Who's us?
(laughing)
- The guys, the alligator guys.
- Who are the alligator guys?
- Do they never bring an animal?
I guess you were homeschooled, whatever.
Pat, did they ever bring animals to your school?
Do like animal presentations?
- Yeah, they brought owls to our school once.
- There was a guy who would bring reptiles
and he brought a baby alligator.
- I never saw reptiles.
- You never seen a reptile before?
- I've seen reptiles. - Brother, just look down.
- They didn't bring reptiles to my school,
they brought owls, but--
- Owls are reptiles.
- My neighbor had a pet-- - Owls are reptiles.
neighbor had a pet alligator. Is Caleb frozen or just sitting like that? I just
I like sitting like that. I've developed a time ability. Yeah. Really? Yeah. Ready?
Watch this. Yeah. For the listeners, Caleb's sitting still. Mm-hmm. He's
learned the skill of sitting still. His eyes merge. He's sitting still because he
he looks like if you crossed Mr. Clean with a chimp.
He looks like if the Tang mascot and Mr. Clean got together and had a kid.
Yeah.
He's American History X.
He's American History XXL.
Dunstan checks into American History X.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Alright, stop sitting still, Caleb.
American history 2x chromosomes.
[laughter]
And I'm a girl.
That's pretty...
That's just Farouk's character in that movie.
[laughter]
Exactly.
Dude, I wish you were still fat, because I could say
American history double XL.
I fucking said that!
It didn't make any sense though, because I'm not fat anymore.
You wanna see a really funny
fat Caleb picture?
one of you is my cup is it the one of you right now? You keep your pictures in a cup? No,
my in-laws got me and Jana a cup with a picture of us on it a couple years ago. Look at him
dude. Oh my god. You're very fat. Wow. Yeah. Jana looks pretty stupid too. Or do you put
picture what do you look like I think I weigh I weighed like 215 pounds in that
photo damn yeah man it was awesome dude I miss being fat no it's awesome dude
who's sick yeah he's like I don't have to run the mile anymore exactly yeah you
get to walk it because if they have you run, recess will be over three times.
I fuckin, in the eighth grade, I, uh, me and my friend tried to like see how long we could
do the mile so we like walked super slow.
I think at one point we just like sat down but like we got like, we did the mile in like
an hour.
That's great pace man.
And the gym teacher was so fucking mad at me.
Of course.
Like, she...
Yeah, the class...
I feel like a mile and an hour is impressive.
It's impressive that you could stretch a mile that long.
Yeah.
The class is only 30 minutes long and everyone was just waiting for you for half an hour.
No, I think it was like an hour long.
I don't remember.
That, um, there's that King of the Hill episode where Bobby, Bobby has to run the mile and
And just every time he has to run out like every week or something and every time he
just goes to this restaurant and like he's wearing like a it has a dress code.
He's wearing like a suit under his gym shorts and he like just goes and hangs out with like
old ladies and eats appetizers.
I would that'd be so cool to just go to like McDonald's during the mile.
Oh yeah I wish the the closest thing to my school growing up was the skate park.
So the only thing like I couldn't go like skating during the mile.
Yeah I would go.
- I got back three hours later.
- Yeah, I went, I think I've said it before,
but I like set up my schedule sophomore year
of high school where I like took lunch and then a study.
So then I would leave during lunch at like 12
in the afternoon, like 1230, I would leave the building
and then stay there till like five.
- Yeah.
Yeah, that was the dream to have enough free periods
to
I could have left. You messed up dude. I messed that shit up. Yeah. Fucking stupid
bitch idiot. Don't care. Fucking dumbass. So stupid. Don't care I learned I learned a
nose grind. So. How good were you? I learned shit they wouldn't tell. I learned shit that they
wouldn't tell you in school. Yeah they're afraid to tell you. Like how to do a nose grind. Yeah.
Yeah exactly the the imperialist school system wouldn't tell you how to do a nose
grind yeah I you could I capitalism with the when I was in high school I got I got
pretty good like I got not like good good but I got like okay junior year and
then senior year I fucked up my ankle and then I was out for like a couple of
like coincided like I fucked up my ankle and then the winter happened but then
like it hasn't been the same since like sometimes I like didn't you say like
Your ankle hurts when it's cold?
Sometimes, yeah.
That's such an old man problem.
There was one day, I went to the skate park before Corona, when it was like 60 in February,
and I was skating and then just out of nowhere, my ankle, I just couldn't walk on it.
So I had to limp to the bus and then go home.
Hey, would you guys rather hunt or heal?
Would I rather hunt?
That's a really good question.
That's one of the best questions I've had this week.
Would you rather hunt or heal?
Well, there's 27 more, so...
I would rather hunt.
Hunt?
Yeah.
Okay, what's your preference?
Plot or explore?
I'm a bit of a plotter.
All right.
I'll say it.
I like to sit back.
I like to have a big map in front of me and making X's.
This is the Ilvermorny Sorting Quiz.
These questions are crazy.
Do you prefer to remember or experience?
Definitely experience.
You can rescue a baby or the only bottle of a potion that could save 1000 lives.
Which one?
But the bottle only might save 1000 lives.
The potion.
So?
Get the potion.
Why?
Well, Caleb's answered all the quiz.
This is Caleb's quiz.
Is it a mite?
Wait, the baby.
I don't know.
The baby?
If it's a mite, like, I mean, I don't know, my fucking, my boot might say, "Fixing lives."
Which is the better motto?
It is nobler to be deceived than to be mistrustful, or friends should not determine or demand blind
faith.
Which one's better, man?
Come on.
I'm going to say...
Which one's closer to Live Free Die Hard?
The Die Hard movie.
The title of that.
Probably the second one.
Yeah, go for that.
- No curse can work without the victim's secret consent.
True or false?
- False.
(laughing)
Definitely false.
- What a crazy question.
- Definitely false.
- I most value freedom, individuality,
service, or ambition.
- Money.
That sounds like service to me.
No, that's ambition.
Ambition?
Yeah.
I would most like to discover a powerful magical creature loyal only to me, an all magical
city hidden from the nomad's world, a spell more powerful than any other, or a magical
plant that will cure any illness.
A magical plant that will cure any illness, because I got a pretty good idea what that
is, baby.
Digunja!
Fasten it to achieve the dollar fine side!
I challenge authority other people's patience. Oops. I picked one by accident. All right,
you challenge. No, my greatest weaknesses. Nobody's business, but mine. What makes me
me the source of my greatest strength or something I must change. What makes me me baby? Yeah,
your baldness. My bat, my baldness. If I could, I would never feel pain, fear, regret or shame.
Shame.
A soulmate is, out there somewhere, an illusion, a psychic twin, or strong where I'm weak, weak
where I'm strong.
Easily psychic twin, no question.
My beliefs are hard one, who I am, constantly evolving, or few but strong.
Hard one.
This is taking so long, I'm just gonna pick random ones.
No, dude, I wanna know what I am, dude.
We have to figure out Caleb's...
Fine, my best idea is...
See, men hate astrology.
My best idea is "get me in trouble, aren't appreciated enough, have changed my life, or have gone to waste."
They get me in trouble.
That's true.
I had a shirt that said that in elementary school.
Why?
My best idea is "get me in trouble."
Why? Why not? Because I want to. Stupid question, or we may never know.
We may never know, baby.
Yeah, all I need is an opportunity, a little more time, some help already inside me.
Already inside me?
You are already inside me.
It's all my shits and my piss.
I often think, why did I do that?
Why can't I do that?
I wish I had done that, or I wonder whether I should do that.
Hurry up, come on.
Which one?
Yeah, WTF BBQ, the first one.
Alright.
What would you exchange for your heart's desire?
Anything.
How many fucking questions is this?
I'm just gonna pick the first one for all the rest of them.
That's fine, that's what I was planning on.
My magic is inborn.
What would you least like to lose?
Reputation.
Nobody's judgment.
A jinx that meant nothing was funny.
The power to change one day in your future.
Imprisoned alone in a silent dungeon.
a shadow of a doubt if you come with me not for many years.
Alright it's calculating results Caleb.
You are Thunderbird.
Yeah you fucking bet I am.
Named by Chadwick Boot after his favorite magical beast.
Chadwick Boot sounds like an alt-light kind of guy.
Yeah.
Oh and Pat I have a quiz for you too.
"Are you normal or weird?"
Okay.
I think I know the answer to this one, but we don't know.
Choose a flavor of drink.
Peach or strawberry?
Uh, peach.
Um, choose a marsupial.
Sugar glider or wombat?
Oh, sugar glider. I've seen those in person.
Choose an alternative baby name.
Baltazar or Oakland?
What the fuck?
Probably Balduzar because it's not the name of a place.
Who would you be in Dungeons and Dragons? Dungeons and what?
Or the Dungeon Master? Dungeons and
the Master. That's... which... what do I pick? Click both.
Click both of them. Choose a traditional candy.
Marzipan or peanut butter toffee? Marzipan.
There's only two... The fuck is marzipan?
Choose a color. It's like a almond thing. Rocky Horror Picture Show or The Room?
Ugh.
Dude, you don't- you know the answer here. You know what you need. Yeah, it's probably Rocky Horror.
And it's probably Rocky Horror. Halloween or Thanksgiving?
Thanksgiving. That's a lie. Yeah, that's ridiculous. You have it- your bathroom is blood themed.
Crazy by- No, it's psycho themed, you idiot. You stupid, fucking, bald idiot. Crazy by Narls Barkley
or I believe in a thing called love by the dark crazy by Narls Barkley is a better song and
your result is calculated you're fat you are weird and fat that didn't even that's not
even the end it says you also like mayonnaise on your fries no no I tell you it said you're
weird and fat dude no it says that at the end in in you know so if you you got thunderbird
'cause a bird snatched up your toupee.
- No.
- Yeah.
- No, I got Thunderbird, 'cause I'm like a thunder,
'cause I'm like a thunder cat that can fly.
- A huge bird, a huge bird flew in and took away all your hair.
- No, it's like a car, dude.
It's literally a muscle car.
- You're a bird, 'cause you lay eggs.
- But you wouldn't know anything about that
'cause you're a girl.
- Caleb lays eggs.
- You drove a muscle car and you put the top down
and all of your hair flew out the window.
- That's fine, yeah, and then you were in the car behind me
and you thought that it was spaghetti and you ate all of it.
- No, I didn't think it was spaghetti.
No you did.
I thought it was hair.
And you ate all of it.
You thought it was hair and then you ate all of it anyway.
You ate all of it.
Yeah.
Because you were like, "Oh, that's something I can eat."
No, I would probably...
Because you were about to turn on your steering wheel and eat that.
No, I took all the hair and I turned it into a wig for women with cancer.
No, you didn't.
You don't work at Locks of Love and you never have.
I work at Locks of Love.
No, you don't.
By the way, that is what I...
I brought it to my high school.
That is what I donated my hair to.
My high school had the biggest Locks of Love...
I donate all my hair to Locks of Love and now there's some woman...
walking around with some super fucked up hair.
Patrick, you uh, you work for Lotkas of Love,
'cause you like food and you're Jewish.
Yeah.
Yeah, you work for lots of-
you work for lots of food,
which is a charity where you just eat.
And that's it.
Caleb, you work for Nazi Love?
Not- he can't even say it.
He's afraid.
It's so messed up.
He's afraid of the power of those words.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
I don't wanna- I don't wanna say you're a Nazi.
Why?
I don't know I feel like that's too mean. No with the way that you look if someone
tried to accuse you. Oh dude it would be over yeah. No I look like a huge Nazi yeah.
And you're from North Carolina, you're from the south. We can't even make jokes about
that because it's like too far. It's too far. It's too soon.
It sucks because New Hampshire is so much more racist than North Carolina.
Oh, absolutely.
And also, isn't, aren't like nowadays
the like real like skinhead Nazis are mostly--
Isn't, yeah, one of the people from the Vice documentary
was from Keen and then they like,
they sat outside of his house and they bullied him.
They, Vice bullied a Nazi?
No, the people--
Okay, I like Vice now.
Yeah, no, I don't like--
Okay, Vice is officially awesome, dude.
No, people in Keen bullied the guy.
I remember watching, I used to watch like the Vice,
like Chirac documentary series.
- Yeah. - Have you guys seen that?
- No, the only thing I watched from Vice in high school
was Epically Latered.
- The Chirac, they basically send just like,
they send like the nerdiest little bitch
into like the South Side of Chicago,
like drill scene. - It's Nerd in the Hood, dude.
- It is Nerd in the Hood a million percent, dude.
And he's just walking around and he's like,
So are these firearms purchased legally?
[laughter]
It's fucking awesome, dude.
It's...
It's good shit. I love 'em.
Ah, man.
I gotta fuckin'...
My leg hurts.
My leg hurt.
You should get a wooden leg.
You should get two wooden legs.
If we get to $15,000, he'll take all his teeth out
and get a wooden leg.
I've been playing Sea of Thieves
We're placing them with wood.
That pirate game.
Yeah.
I've basically just been gaming all day for the last like three weeks.
Don't open CSGO or TF2.
I already did.
You're so stupid dude.
I didn't know about it until Cameron put it in the gaming discord.
You guys are lucky.
Did I-
Should I uninstall it?
No, just don't launch it.
I mean it's too late now.
If anything was going to happen, it's already happened.
Yeah, I think we were on like the casual.
I mean, that doesn't matter.
It's the thing itself.
So like, if you--
I think I'm, I think I, I think,
I think you're lying.
Yeah, I'm lying.
No, the source code, the source code got leaked.
It's funny that it's the source code.
Yeah, more like the horse--
You remember that movie?
More like the horse code,
'cause I say, "Nay, thank you to that."
(laughing)
I'm working on our improv theater.
I figured we should sprinkle a few little stuff like that.
Some more puns in improv.
Let's do a scene, let's do a scene, okay.
I'm a-
Okay.
What about improv but game?
Let's do a scene where we're all inside of Counter-Strike.
Okay.
Terrorists win.
Okay, scene.
Perfect.
[Laughter]
Perfect scene.
Okay.
Yeah, that's-
Now let's do a scene.
That is how the game ends, so...
So, Cam, you seem to be working on this horse character.
Let's explore that more.
Alright.
Okay.
Yeah.
So we're gonna do an exercise right now, where you're a horse, right?
No, I'm a guy who, I like, I make j- I'm a horse.
You're a guy who thinks he's a horse.
Okay.
And you're on a game show.
Oh, shit.
And that game show is hosted.
And the game show is called Guess That Horse.
All right, let's do it.
Guess That Guy's Nationality.
Okay, you take it and start it.
Let's go.
Start the scene.
Okay, all right.
Welcome back to Guess That Horse.
It's me, I'm the horse.
Welcome back to Guess That Guy's Nationality.
Okay, no, we changed the game show
because you won too fast.
Welcome back to Guess That Guy's Nationality.
Here's a picture of the guy who,
that one guy who played that actor who go was in iron man three and
uh... and he played gandhi that one time ben kingsley ben kingsley ok ready
guess
that
nationality horse
well i mean
he uh... uh... he's
i think he's british
british horse
I was right, that's the correct answer.
He's not a horse, dude, he's a guy.
What are you talking-- his name is Ben Hoofsley.
[laughter]
Right?
Yeah, you're right.
His name is actually
Krishna Pandit Banji.
His name is Ashley Madison.
[laughter]
Ashley Madison the actor.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, I'm Ashley Madison.
Next.
You know, this whole time I thought Ben Kingsley was doing brownface by playing Gandhi, but
turns out he's just an Indian guy.
I think he's, yeah, he's like half Indian or something.
Yeah.
People were still mad about it though.
Yeah, that's weird.
It's like that, do you guys watch Cutthroat Kitchen?
No.
Oh.
They have that.
That's the one where Alton Brown.
Alton Brown, yeah.
Yeah.
But they have a judge who's Indian, but he just looks like, he has a British accent and
just looks like a white guy.
Yeah.
And it just weirds me out.
not right. Christ. Yeah. I don't watch any cooking shows anymore. Yeah, Cutthroat Kitchen. I
watched that because Anna likes it. They, Cutthroat Kitchen gets a bunch of their like,
you know, like the stuff that they use to be like, oh, you have to chop onions. You
have to chop onions using these claws or whatever. You mean the challenges? Yes, the challenges,
- The sabotages are all BDSM like stuff
that Alton Brown buys.
- What?
- What the hell?
- That's not true.
- Yeah, it is.
- No, a bunch of them are like,
you have to cook using no salt.
- You have to, yeah, but there's some of them
where it's like--
- BDSM stuff.
- There's some of them, some of them,
they're like--
- That is BDSM to Alton Brown.
He's so into food.
- BDSM to him is--
- Yeah.
- No, but he uses--
- He's cooking with no salt.
Like it's like oh you have to cook your meal using these shackles
They've never done that. Yes. They have dude. Yes, maybe once or twice
Most of them are like you have to ride around this bike from station to station. I don't think they stop doing it because they got hot
Yeah
Into the new podcast where Cameron and Patrick talk about a TV show that Caleb has never
Seen okay
Fuckers talk about it's I've never seen jackass. I have to listen to you guys. What about it? It's called. Yeah stupid
No
What the fuck? Yeah, that's right
What is fun, yeah, I have to listen to it every
Talking about that exactly
And I don't complain because I like listening to it
It's been fucking just, it's so easy to watch it.
- It's an hour and a half.
- I haven't gotten around to it yet.
- Oh, you haven't gotten around to it?
- No.
- He's watched, he's watched every--
- I think it's funny not to watch it
'cause it makes you angry.
- He's watched every monster movie about--
- It doesn't make me angry, I just don't understand.
- Kitchen appliances that become very big
and fight Japan, fight the Japanese jackass.
- Cameron watches stuff called like,
The Lovely Nephew.
- He'll watch a 15 hour, The Lovely Nephew.
Yeah, that's the American translation.
That's actually a very beautiful film.
It has a very strong emotional core and the actors are brilliant.
It's the same cinematographer as Mandy.
Yeah.
It looks exactly the same as Mandy.
How many times have you seen one half A press video and you haven't watched Jackass?
Probably like five.
That video is like 20 minutes long.
What is Jackass on?
You've seen Godzilla one million times.
Jackass is on Patrick's computer.
Probably.
Yeah.
Listen, I don't...
We gotta watch Jackass, man.
Jackass 3 is on Amazon Prime.
It's imperative for you to know what we're doing here.
Yeah.
Like the goal of this podcast is to eventually reach a...
Eventually to become Jackass 4.
I know what Jackass is.
I know I can do it.
Oh, that's not enough, dude.
Here's a test. What is it?
It's about a donkey, right?
NOOOOOO!
Oh my god.
No!
I just don't get it.
It's about six donkeys if you know what I mean.
It's about four-
We're all best friends.
It's about four high school friends who play pranks on each other.
And at the end of the episode-
Much to the chagrin of their parents.
At the end of each of the episodes, one of them is awarded that night's biggest loser.
It's about sucking farts in fucking Boston.
So they copied it from the biggest loser?
Yeah, it's about 12 people who are placed on an island and they have to survive, right?
And so they, each week they vote each other off the island with tiki torches.
Some of them might actually be having sex, but you're not allowed to show that on TV.
Yeah, that was Jackass 1.
Jackass 2 is when it's 12 beautiful women and Preston Lacey, and each night Preston Lacey
decides which woman he's going to give his rock and roll VIP pass to.
And there's a lot of fighting between the women.
Yeah, and also it's simultaneously a weight loss show.
They should do a version of The Bachelor that's also the biggest loser.
He's like, "You gotta be under 120 to fuck me."
twelve personal trainers and one fat billionaire.
And one really fat bitch.
Yeah.
That he has an idea might be hot once he loses weight.
And that's the whole show.
And also you have to do it with shackles on.
Uh huh.
Like.
And you don't get to eat salt.
And.
I like the idea that Alton Brown watched like the Amistad and then the next day he walked
And he was like, "Yeah, what if we chain them all together and we start beating the shit out of them while they make the food?"
I had to watch... I had to fuckin'... I don't know why, but I had to watch Amistad in my music class in 8th grade.
My mom showed me that movie when I was like 8 years old and she was like...
I don't know what it is.
It's a movie about the slave trade.
It's kinda like Jackass.
It's why you haven't seen it, it's cause it's like that.
I'm never gonna watch Jackass. I don't care.
I don't know.
The Amistad is a movie about...
That's why I'm not going to watch it because I think it's funny to you.
It's about a slave ship.
It's about a Supreme Court case that was like, it was like basically like people, like slaves
from the, who were on the ship called the Amistad.
They were like sentenced to death for like revolting or something and killing the captain
and then they, it was this like court case.
But most of it is just like, just black people getting the shit kicked out of them.
It's a horrible movie.
There is no fun music in that movie.
We watched Little Shop of Horrors.
I forgot you said that you watched it at music class and I thought you were just saying.
There's no fun music in that movie.
It's crazy.
Dude, we had to watch Little Shop of Horrors with Rick Moranis and then the week after we
we watched Amistad for some reason.
- Damn dude, yeah that's a big downgrade.
- That makes no fucking sense.
- And your professor thought it was the musical Amistad,
he got the wrong DVD.
He thought it was the musical adaptation of that story.
- Did they make a musical adaptation?
- No.
- Yeah dude, yeah they did.
The same people who, it was Trey Parker and--
- Trey Parker.
(laughing)
- Oh no.
- I don't think they did do that.
- Yeah, it's like--
- I think they did.
- They made--
- I think they're working on it right now.
- Yeah.
- And I got insider information
that I wasn't supposed to--
- 'Cause your uncle, your uncle Trey Parker.
- The lovely uncle.
- I got inside her information.
Did you know that there's a hole,
there's two holes down there?
There's three.
There's three holes down there.
And also, you know they have a weird penis down there?
A weird little peeny head that you gotta click?
Fucked up.
That's called inside her information, baby.
Yeah.
Inside her, I'm inside her trading.
Trading Pokemon to myself.
I just traded myself a Gengar.
(laughing)
- My headphones are messed up again, hold on.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, you guys talk about something awesome.
- Okay.
- Wow, fixed 'em.
See, you guys didn't even have an awesome topic
to talk about.
Me, on the other hand, I have tons.
- All right, go ahead.
List a ton.
Don't talk about them, but just list them.
- I was thinking about Dr. Robotnik.
- Doctor who?
- Dr. Robotnik.
- Is that what you were saying?
- Dr. Who?
- No, Dr. Robotnik.
Do you think Dr. Robotnik has a perfectly flushed penis to his fupa?
Like it doesn't come outside of it at all?
And also like there's no like, you know that flap that big fat people have from their stomach
that sometimes covers their balls and their penis?
Do you think he has one of those?
I wouldn't, I'm not familiar with that flap.
Yeah you are.
No I'm not, I think that's a you problem.
No you're very, you're oh so familiar with it.
- You're familiar with it 'cause you have one.
- You hide cheeseburgers underneath it.
- Yeah, yeah, you hide-- - You do.
It's a satchel.
You use it as a laptop case.
- You have a little GPS that you keep under there.
- You have a little.
You are little, dude.
You're the littlest one.
What is it like to be the littlest podcast host?
- The littlest podcast, that's my favorite.
- The most adorable and smallest podcast host.
Littlest podcast host, it's a movie about Patrick.
sequel to the lovely nephew the lovely trying to trying to open a normal-sized
book no but it's so big and heavy that I can open up a book I'll do it right now
that's a miniature book that's a book for a Barbie doll why do you own that
book of oh what the fun comp yeah and what are you I don't think you should
own that dude I think that's it's sure it's Sherlock Holmes it's not bad it is
bad. Because you hate, you hate clues. I, no I actually, you hate looking for clues. No,
I actually love clues. No, you hate clues and you hate looking for clues. Sherlock Holmes
doesn't matter to me because it's so below my intellect. I'm working on tons of clue
based projects right now. I mean personally, I hate clues because I don't even need them
to solve a mystery. I just know the answer when I look at the crime. I have, I have a,
You guys can't see it, but on the other side of my webcam I have a wall covered in clues.
Yeah, covered in blues clues.
Yeah, you have blue pop raps all over your walls.
Blue blues clues wallpaper.
That's a clue.
That's a kind of clue.
Just because it's a blue clue doesn't mean it's not a clue.
Nah, I beg to differ.
What, an idiot?
Yeah?
Well, tell me, give me a clue.
What kind of clue do you have for me?
Here's a clue.
Where'd your hair go?
It's in the toilet, dude.
That's where I put it, in the toilet.
Yeah?
you fucking idiot dude where's you where'd you where is you skinny you go
the computer they can see him on the computer yeah no to the compute mm-hmm
no put a picture of him how come you have a blue paw print on your head yeah
how come you have a how do you come you have a series of blue paw prints leading
because I don't know it's normal it's called a psoriasis they lead into into
your ass and then out again and down your leg yeah yeah again it's fine it's
just a skin condition good text from patches got a text from patches you want
to just end the episode here and then call him oh we have 58 we have two
minutes left. We can do two more minutes. I love it dude. I love this every single time.
Yeah, Patrick, you're never gonna get all your teeth taken out and become the perfect
sex machine without it. I can get my teeth taken out whenever! I didn't do it, coward.
Patrick, the fans are starting to hate you, dude. Yeah, you're becoming the... The backlash
is coming. Yeah. It's not coming. Dude, they hate... I'm getting texts right now from all
the fans. Oh my god. The fans are mad at you. You're the least favorite now. You're becoming
- I'm the Draco Malfoy.
- Yeah, dude, Penis Reptar just texted me on Discord
and he says Patrick sucks.
- Nah.
- He does, dude, he did.
- They said they're mad at you for your video.
- No, they're mad at you for your video.
- What video?
- Who knows, 'cause you suck at videos.
- Oh!
- The videos are so bad,
you can't even tell which one is which.
- I don't even, yeah, the video, yeah, exactly.
I can't even tell these videos apart.
- Yeah, they're all the same.
- Patrick, yeah, Patrick has TikTok on his phone.
And that's all I need to say on the subject
of why Patrick should be in jail.
- We have to get you off of that app, dude.
- Yeah. - No, it's funny.
- It's not good for you.
- You can't be on that app.
- Nah, dude. - Why?
- It's just not. - 'Cause that's just one--
- Yeah, no exceptions.
Over 21, you can't use that app.
That's like--
- There are older people than me on there.
- You got that mom too.
- And you liked him?
- Yeah.
- Did you see that guy I sent you?
- I don't.
- No.
- The flat earth guy?
- I never watch any of them.
- You don't watch any of them?
- I only watch the ones of old people.
- You're so upset.
- You really don't watch those TikToks?
- You don't watch the ones I send you?
- Are you serious?
- No, I don't.
- But yeah, I don't think there's a single exception
to that rule.
If you're an adult and you're on that app,
I don't respect you.
- Yeah.
and i think you should be uh... put into a whole and you stay there
down i think i'm not think i'm the exception
i think we should reopen guantanamo and said i was the exception because he's a
he's childlike enough that
that uh... the other is the other all you say one little child yet the other
people can groom him so it's okay
to get a good idea of the other category he's he's in a he's in danger he's not a
dead danger
exactly a
so it's fine like that guy i sent you
who uh...
what he say he was like
who's like you have a you know it's like i it's like i always had a healthy
is the guy that said uh... he love he loves bob marley
and he loves bob marley because a stand up for your right
and that's why cove it is fake
what well
it's a good video
see this is a promise and you're digging yourself a dug
grief
you're doing is that the great with a headstone says which you was pedophile
fucking on all right let's go patches yet but