You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[Laughter]
Okay, alright, okay, alright.
Okay, alright, okay.
Okay, alright, alright.
[Laughter]
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Yeah!
I keep on reaching for greatness because I hear from it.
Mm-Hmm
Yeah, I like a 17 uh-huh yeah
Somebody like I saw somebody posted like a picture of the like the screenshot of like that guy's Spotify page and made that and he
Just makes rap songs for like trailers
Yeah
Need that and it's all I mean he's probably only making him for like movies like that and like
Pacific movies and shit like it was only yeah just making that song hoping that
they find it yeah he made all the songs for speculative movies it's not a
Godzilla versus Donkey Kong yeah the song that they used for the Godzilla
Kong trailer is just his trolls theme but they cut out all the references to
trolls and kept all the perfect movie yeah yeah he hopes that he puts his
wish list into a rap song that they will actually put it in Mario a dream come
true Robin Williams is the genie he's there too
Philip Seymour Hoffman stepping back in
his top two songs on Spotify are the first one is here we go by Chris classic
That's his name. His name's Chris Classic? Yup.
Oh that's great. His second song is Witch Doctor from Alvin and the Chipmunks.
Yo, he did a hip hop witch doctor? A more hip hop witch doctor?
Oh he did something for, he did work, Wrestlemania mix too.
Damn. Oh damn. Chris Classic. Chris Classic's making money.
He also did Ain't No Party from Alvin and the Chipmunks.
Ain't No Party Like a Chipmunk Party. Like a Chipmunk Party.
party don't stop it does not mm-hmm Pierce is back everybody music for planes
for play yeah back to you know a dang cook mm-hmm
is the star of that movie yeah he's the main plane is he the main point main
plane day and did plain cook whoo yeah Pierce is back Pierce is back I was I
I was going to look up planes to confirm that
and I just looked up plane cook.
(laughing)
- Did it come up?
- No, TikTok user cooks steak in plane lavatory.
- Ugh.
- That should have-- - On what?
- On the plane.
- Is the toilets hot?
What is he, how do you cook it?
- Wait, but in what vehicle?
- The plane, he cooked--
- And in what room in the plane?
- The lavatory.
- Well, how do you get a steak--
- And what did he cook?
- How do you get a steak on a plane, though?
- Hold on, I have to disable it.
I've had it with these motherfucking steaks.
Steaks on a plane.
I have to disable ad block.
Here we go!
Steaks on a plane!
I got a sous vide in the bathroom!
You think you did sous vide?
Yeah, you sous vide in the toilet.
But then you didn't...
That blue water.
He put a steak in the toilet water.
He didn't do that. That's so imprecise.
Yeah.
steak that just walked out of the toilet that's how fresh I want it yeah I can
still smell the shit on this steak yeah I want that thing to bleed blue yeah I
want to 65 I want to hear it poo that's right I want a dark brown crust on the
inside I want this cow to be shitting on the table so I can eat it where's my
Did you guys have to go take the shit out of the cow
Farm you get the cow pie for me leave the cow
We're doing we're doing diaper talk three dude most anticipated episode. I think this is like Super Mario 3
It can only get better from here, then we're gonna have diaper talk world
We have a diaper talk generations diaper talk worldwide
We could go to like the we could go to different type or diaper hot front around the world. Yeah paper diaper
Paper diaper might be good. Yeah, yeah diaper versus talk
Diaper and sonic at the Olympic games. Yeah, say diaper versus talking at the Olympic Games might be good
Now we can't do any of those because we spoiled. Yeah. Yep. So this is the last one wait
We have one there's one more in the pocket
Diaper talk for I need me some more
Here we go here we go
We got a contact Chris classic before tomorrow and get him to write a song for the diaper talk
Yeah
We got our diapers on so yeah, I guess if anybody it's been a while since the last diaper talk
If your diaper talk we're on this web service. I don't think it's been two years. I don't think two years old
Yeah, I think that's not even on the podcast two years ago Patrick. It's two years old. I don't think so
I think you are two years old two years. We're going to this. It's an adult. It's an adult baby diaper lover
Forum and we're gonna read we're reading stuff from it. That's it's pretty simple and this time when you left your
You left your D&D
intro at the bottom
Yeah, this is the document. I just use whenever I have to prep for an episode
I mean, I guess you guys don't do anything like that because you don't put any effort
You don't like the fans, but if you want to make you on me for like caring, that's fine. Okay
What do you want me to read this it's been read it's already been read did you he blew it on it?
Well, we could do an episode. No, those you have to pay ten dollars to hear it
We could have it in a different voice. You cannot review it would make any sense
I want to read you this this first post that I found from the diaper
talk the forums are called diaper talk by the way for anyone who doesn't know that
this is a post this is a post from user baby toodler five which they misspelled
toddler
baby type word yeah what is it the baby like I probably knew what that word
meant when I was a baby. I must have forgotten what toodler meant. Yeah,
toodler sort of gave me a deja vu back to my baby days. And baby
toodlers like little they have like every people have like little like
info under their names and baby toodler says I love being in my
diaper. This thread is titled diaper accident. And here's the
post. I read some thread on the topic of accident in diaper that
made no sense how do you consider it a accident in your diaper when diaper are
made to keep all messy inside your diaper what your opinion on this topic
accident in your diaper this might be an actual toodler this could be a real-life
toodler that well there it says baby to their five so there's just got to be
other baby - they were born in the year five okay that's no toodler is a
five-year-old a toddler no no it's a young adult five is old dude yeah that
baby can start reading Teen Titans you're in school there's there's one like
on this post from Christian diaper lover I mean this is like a serious question
This is like a this is like a if if you shit your pants in the woods and there's no one around to hear it type
Question. Yeah, there's a there's a kind of a philosophical slant to this
I'm like, is it even an accident if the diaper is meant to to catch all the poo poo in the peepee?
Yeah, well, so all the messy even an accident if you if you hijacked the car in the first place. Yeah, exactly
You but somebody does have an answer a good answer to it. The user pees a lot
lot. Who says, wait, wait, wait, their bio is I love wearing lingerie. Yeah, and I
guess their class makeup is diaper lover and other. And yeah, Pizzolat says,
never had an accident in my diapers. I try to have quite a few on purposes in
every day you bad a lingerie diaper yeah an Italian lace diaper you just kind of
like seep out in a pattern yeah it's like those like a play-doh like you
push it like a stress ball in the mesh it would just look like lace coming out
this is another this adds more complexity to it because she says I try
to have a few on purpose how can you fail to have well then well if you fail to
have an on purpose would it be an accident well that no well since you're
trying to do it made yeah you're trying hard you're failing you're not
shitting your pants yeah is being backed up I do like calling it an on-purpose
yeah yeah I think I'm making I have to go make an on-purpose in the toilet I've
said accident a few times here such as when I wear a diaper to bed and drink
700 milliliters of water to make sure I have an accident yeah I wanted to start
out with that post because of baby toodler baby toodler is such a good name
yes I wear diapers I like to roleplay scenarios in which someone would have a
real accident I like waiting until my bladder is full and then wetting my
nappy before I could get to the toilet what are the role like my shoelaces
together I set up a bunch of bear traps on the way to the bathroom they catch me
before I can make it to do it on purpose.
I basically like to rig my apartment with claymores and wire traps so I can't get anywhere in the place.
I have that puzzle floor from Spy Kids that falls down.
I have the Resident Evil laser hallway installed in my house.
And the cube laser hallway.
And the ghost ship big invisible wire.
Yeah.
If I fuck up, I'm getting lattice cut.
My hand is suspended while I'm sleeping with a string and a candle that slowly burns the string
so that my hand will fall into a pot of warm water and I'll piss my pants.
But then the thing is if you're tricking yourself into doing an accident it's an on purpose.
Right. Or is it?
I don't mean to bring that back to you know a larger question.
If you're successfully tricking yourself though.
If you but you're but that's still...
It's like tickling yourself and making yourself laugh.
Yeah that's on purpose.
Yeah.
Right, but it's impossible. You can't. An accident has to be kind of, it has to come from like a pure place of like I'm not in any way
Trying to shit or piss my pants. Right.
Yeah, you have to create some sort of duality of man in order to make this. You have to have, it's like Dr.
Strangelove is conspiring to make himself shit his pants. Yeah, you have to do a Jekyll and Hyde.
You have to kind of segment your personality into one that sets up
Accidents all throughout your life and one who is only trying to do it on purpose. It's a it's a fight club thing. Exactly
Yeah, it's a dike club
It basically is died. Yeah, yeah Tyler Durden is just constantly eating x-flags and
Yeah, just drinking is leaders and leaders of water Tyler Tyler Turden
Yeah, diaper
And instead of the narrator yeah, I
Yeah, we're all growing up and we're realizing we're not gonna shit our pants
We're not gonna piss our pants and we're very very pissed off
We're the little babies of history man
All right the next one this next post is from Fox 34
And it's how did you find out that you like nappies speak for myself?
I can't exactly remember how I remember stealing nappies at the age of three or four
for
red panda dl says well mine is not typical of what you will hear about i
just started wearing a little over a year ago at age 43 i have an underwear
fetish and like padded bicycle shorts i also like softer squishy padding of any
kind i vaguely recall stuffing things like socks in my underwear as a kid and
later in life too. I finally got the idea to put one of my daughter's diapers in my
underwear and loved it. Then I bought adult diapers from CVS to try and was hooked. I
wet them at first but decided I'd really just like being padded. I now wear mostly super
undies, rears, and baby pants training pants.
You just gotta have like a really small waist if you can fit into baby training pants.
Yeah, it's just a guy with like a Johnny Bravo figure.
It's fun to imagine like I need to know when you knew you liked diapers.
So like you're a baby and the first time you smile is like because you recognize yourself
in the mirror or you see a dog or like you see your father and you smile and like the
baby is checking in with itself.
Like why do I why am I smiling?
What's making me so happy?
Oh, it's my diaper.
I
Think like your dad sneezes or he tickles you
That is so fucked it like you're wearing a diaper as a kid and your aunt walks into the room and points at you and goes
Look at your look at your little diaper and then you're something in your brain snaps
And that's the only way you can ever be happy yeah, it's like yeah that combination
You don't realize that it's it's that a woman is pointing at you. It's
What yeah because the woman isn't touching your penis and the diaper is so there is that connection?
It's keeping that stranger from touching your penis is the diaper
Yeah, you don't realize that the the diapers actually the barrier for sexual pleasure in that moment
You think it wasn't a diaper you're on yeah
yeah the father stands between the baby and his mother and diaper stands between
the baby and his aunt blue bear says my subconscious mind knew before I did
when I was five or six I had this dream where I was put in a diaper I remember
feeling embarrassed but at the same time I thought the diaper felt amazing when I
woke up I was depressed that I wasn't really wearing one that was when I
realized I liked nappies my fascination with diapers did fade when I was 10 or so
but it resurfaced when I was 15. I remember having some spending money and my brain just went,
"Psst, you can buy diapers with that."
(laughter)
Yeah, you're a baby, or even you're a child, and you just, you learn the value of money,
and you're like, "Finally, I don't have to be finance dominated by my parents.
Emancipate myself by buying my own goddamn diapers
That's so funny like to be able to dream to take a break from diapers from the age of 10 to 15
Break did yeah
It hits harder when you put it on
Yeah, I
Remember one night I was in Walmart while on vacation in Idaho
And I remember seeing a baby girl pushed in a stroller and the mother buying diapers for the baby
And I thought to myself I wonder how it feels to wear diapers
That's a pretty simple like yeah, that's respectable you know I don't think that's jealousy of a baby
There's nothing there was nothing like sexual about it. His aunt isn't in the Walmart. Yeah, it's just like I wonder what it's like to wear diapers
Yeah
Wait, what is it's the baby costume? It's like it's like it's the only way to roleplay as a baby is to put on a diaper
You can't change your size. You can't be helpless again. Mm-hmm
Yeah
Imagine if your your your diaper awakening is fucking baby new year
True damn. I wonder what it's like to wear diapers man. I would be
To be in charge diet chamber pot says
I wet my pants on purpose my whole life got to where I could wet just enough to
have my underwear wet but not really show my outside pants being wet I would stay
damp all the time I just loved being wet the naughtiness of my pants about age 45
I tried out depends heaven in my pants I could wet more and show less did not
start wearing all the time until about four years ago imagine when I was
suspended you know you spend your entire life wetting your pants and it doesn't
your mind until age 45 to wish my underwear could collect this for later
yeah it sucks when you convince yourself that the naughtiness is what you like
and you realize the naughtyness is just because I forgot about this is a this is
really good one-two punch one from killerpanda3 who said I would have
dreams or I was wearing and using them sometimes even in cartoons like the rug
rats and then their icon is Timmy Turner in a big full diaper and then the next
comment is having to wear them due to being incontinent yeah I feel like
that's two opposite ends of the diaper spectrum yeah people who wear them
because they imagine cartoon babies wearing them and that being cool and
than people who can't stop shitting themselves.
- When I was in kindergarten,
there were like five kids in my class
who had trouble pissing themselves.
So their parents would pack them an extra pair of pants
and then like midday through the day,
they'd have to change.
And I just got jealous of the attention
that they were getting.
So I just brought, I didn't tell my parents,
I brought a spare change of pants
and I just pissed my pants on purpose
so that I could leave the room and change.
And everyone knew that I wasn't a pants pisser.
So they knew that I had just done it on purpose.
It's hard to piss your pants on purpose.
I know.
That was the only time I was ever able to do it on purpose.
Every other time has been an accident?
Yeah.
Damn, you poser.
I broke a seal.
You're a poser.
Nah, man.
I just reversed it.
I flipped the script.
User Twiley links a YouTube video called 1937 Mickey Modern Inventions and says, "This Donald
Duck cartoon might be the reason I got curious about diapers and the man nail
is a picture of Donald Duck in a baby body
this will be as real as I'm probably going to get tonight I am incontinent
and have been my entire life but as I hit puberty I started to love the thickness
and pressure it put on that area and started to love the feeling of when I
feel the warmth of a wet diaper touching my inner thigh and I really started to
I like the feeling of the lump when I realized I had a power movement. I
love my lump. I never noticed the warmth on my thigh from a wet diaper
before I hit puberty before puberty. It was like a whatever thing to me
puberty changed my sensory sensitivities in general. So diapers are
awesome to me. That's from Draco. Nym diapered little boy looking for
friends.
Listen listen to this one from Brie 89. I have little to no idea how to
go on the potty.
(laughter)
Just dunking your head in the toilet.
I learned from Ned's Declassified
that this is how you use the toilet.
It's little to no idea. It's not no idea.
I have a little bit of an idea.
I'm almost clueless about going potty.
I know to sit on it, but I don't
know how to take my pants off.
Just do like a family guy prat
fall into the toilet every time you try to get on. Here's a post from
Laughing Elf Man. I think I was age 7. I think I was age 7 my sister and I were
playing in the grass area in the center of the condo complex we live in. A nice
woman with a baby boy looked about one years old came out to the grass and
started playing with the baby she was so sweet and motherly I started to feel
envious of the baby I do think it's interesting how it spans that like
sexual to having a lump in my pants it can be anything between those some
people have like yes I'm kind of like naughty like like voyeuristic sexual
pleasure and some people are just like I love I just want everyone to know I'm
helpless so that they can take care of me and I also love brown stinky shitty doo-doo
I love doodoos and dookies in my little nap I love when my ass swells and I also
hate parting with my diarrhea I wanted I want to carry it around me all day that
is I think that's also a big part of it is just wanting to leash your shit to
you so it doesn't vanish into the toilet yeah but you can't like a hoarder
mentality you can't just like hold it forever because at some point you become
like like over encumbered like oblivion
so hard to walk around but you have like five or six days of shit in your pants
you just completely frozen yeah you just need you need to get to the
garbage cans you can save takes you all day to walk there. I want to move I want
to move to the next I'm just going to read this one through because this one's
kind of like a story like I'll go back and forth. I hope you guys know this is
from user ready wet for us one and is just an old guy which might be him and
the post is why do people this is the title of it. Why do people think it's
strange to wear it's our natural way from early on I wear every day and I would
never change my idea it's okay to wear and then the the extra details are it's
okay to pee when you want and then see bear responds and says I always think
that as well it's just another method of toileting just because toilets are the
most used method doesn't wait make wearing nappies strange they both have
pros and cons and are both better for some than others if nappies had been
around before toilets were common they would have become the norm I always hope
one day nappies will be accepted imagine saying to your boss excuse me I'm just
I'm just going to change my nappy and then and then wet for us one
responds and says are you female? I would I mean if I was wet for us one
even if I was turned on but yeah of a female employee asking her boss if she
could change her nappy. I would say what a salient point I agree completely are
female and then he gets scolded and they say we are not a relationship site yeah i
just i do agree that i do agree that it could have gone either way in history we
could have gone the nappy route yeah it does seem kind of insane that like you
need a whole fucking sewer system to make it work yeah especially like a whole
room takes up your floor plan yeah gallons of water every single fucking
movement you have it's able it is a because we had like holes before we had a
super absorbent gel I mean like if we had come up with super like strike a
balance like maybe we can fill the toilets with the gel or something what
about like I think that's a porta potty what about like a tube what about it
what about a tube bet what about it - I think like you just vacuum suction oh
- Oh, just like a Futurama tube hooked up to your ass
that shoots doo-doo into the kitchen.
- When you're in your house,
you walk around with a tube in your butt.
- But it's like a tail,
and then when you have to shit,
you plug it into the wall.
- Like a central bag.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Yeah, there's like little holes all over.
You move into a new apartment,
you're like, this one only has four ports,
our last one had six.
I gotta get out of bed and walk into the living room
just to port in.
All right, I mean it's pretty good.
From user, here's a new post from user Cambridge1.
Oh, oh.
Yeah.
Anyone else enjoy a stranger seeing your nappy?
Not sure if it is just me, but I think the biggest part of me being a diaper lover is
being seen or caught out by others.
Obviously this excludes anybody I know or would see again.
Being a diaper lover is the biggest secret I have, but for anyone else that doesn't know
me or I'll never see again, it really is a bit of a turn on to know someone has seen my
nappy.
go about hiding that pull-up from my waistline when out shopping etc.
Just sagging.
No this is the right way to be.
Just a guy wearing like Levi's silver tats just sagging them with like a big elbow diaper.
No you do like a, you become like a Britney Spears like slut and just every time you get
out of a limo.
Yeah, polarized jeans.
Just like, just fucking sharing.
Yeah a whale tail.
Yeah doing whale tail with like booty shorts and there's clearly a diaper underneath.
And you're like oh sorry did you see that?
this uh this response is really evil from sally an it's not something we should do
but i do get how you feel over the years decades really being occasionally seen
in a nappy has been exciting but i do have to remember that i should always be
very discreet and responsible a wet bed left on a hotel bed is also a bit naughty
and exciting being like no you shouldn't let anybody else see your nappy that's
very disrespectful but if I if I was a diaper where every time I was going to
get coffee and it's time for me to tip I would you know lift up my shirt my
dollar bills right out of my diaper just keeping like money and like a
screwdriver in it like Tommy Pickles dog boy responds I don't see a problem if
someone sees part of your diaper sticking up out of your pants etc it's
not gonna bother them unless they're the most fragile snowflake in the world
did my lump trigger you fragile snowflake in the world oh you need it you
You need to be in another room because I smell so much like pee and poop.
Oh, sorry, does my smell offend you because my fucking pants are full of shit?
Oh, you want me to go to a safe space called a bathroom?
Suck my dick.
It's covered in my own poop and piss.
I personally like the whole idea behind public embarrassment.
Now, I don't in any way condone to flaunting personal choices upon others,
But I don't either go out of my way to
Overly stress upon hiding my diapers if I know I am around people that I won't see again
I wouldn't mind being spotted wearing. I like the sentence. I personally like the whole idea behind public embarrassment
That's it to me that I need I needed to elaborate. I don't know. Yeah, I don't know what the whole idea
I don't want to be publicly and also I don't condone flaunting personal choices
So, you know that they like think gay marriage is wrong
People see their diapers. Yeah, I don't try and like it if gays were still publicly embarrassed by it
They would yeah, I would turn them on and make them fucking piss and poo
I don't try and advertise that I'm diapered usually but if my diaper waistband shows and people see it. I'm not bothered
I'm incontinent. So I'd rather people see me wearing a diaper than having accidents breathe deep seek peace dinotopia in 2002
I wish they had more signatures on here like that
So good
I'm not go out and about wearing only a t-shirt and a diaper
But I don't mind if I'm out someplace where I'm not likely to see anyone
I know and the top of my type is visible above the waistband of my it's always about just the hint the inkling
Yeah, diaper is also like just just seeing a little bit of the above the waistband
You could convince yourself that that's just like underwear, right? Yeah, but for them they're like they know it's a diaper
yeah oh yeah paper underwear that's a paper underwear I think that's a diaper
no no not like not like a diaper but like you know like disposable under
underwear paper okay yes says I've gone to the beach and nothing but diaper no
one really said much one person walking by said nice diaper and I just laughed
I would like to see like a diaper a diaper style bikini top to go yeah - you
know oh yeah diaper vault diapered volleyball game oh I'm gonna get turned
on I get hard every time I wear I like to masturbate in my diaper I'm sorry you and
I must have different ideas about how we relate to this sort of I'm seeing like a
civil war brewing on this on this page between people who want to fuck a diaper
and people want to shit in it yeah don't you don't worry cuz we will be getting
to the people who want to fuck a diaper a lot more I got some really disgusting
stuff lined up. Here's one that says a cute Scottish accent. It's not a skirt, it's a
kilt. Okay. That's in response to something. Yeah, that makes more sense. Yeah, this is
why I often wish it was acceptable for a man to wear a dress. Oh, so you can Marilyn Monroe
style like stand over a Stuart Gray. Yeah, oops. Oops, my diaper's showing. Honestly,
I just wish it were more acceptable to wear a diaper and long shirt out in public not because I am an exhibitionist
But because I really dislike pants. I don't get off from it desire to push it on people, etc
Just really dislike pants just wearing like a soldier boy. Yeah, just a giant white tea. Yeah
This person is like they're getting so frustrated by people thinking that incontinent people who identify as diaper likers
Shouldn't be lumped in with the kink people. It's like to get off the forum
No one's talking about people who constantly shit their pants and appreciate the invention of a diaper.
I happen to like the idea that I can shit my pants.
That is true. You definitely-- there's less of a need for a forum of people who just wear a diaper.
Yeah. I have a broken leg. I'm going to join a forum for people who like getting fucked in the ass by a cane.
[laughter]
Like doesn't work so I'm gonna join a forum of people who put the talk in a cast. Yeah, I'll put a wheelchair in their ass
Yeah, that makes perfect sense. I'm sure I have common ground with these people
Yeah, they spend every day trying to put distance between them and the people in the forum. Yeah, I
Enjoy a lot going out in public wearing a bulky diaper under my jeans as I can remember
It's just a few persons
I have seen reaction from and they have just giving me a warm smile probably they have been into a BDL themselves
There's something wrong
Yeah, here's a really good comment for Mandy bears responding to the skirt comment
They said do you want to know why it's called a kilt because we killed everyone who called it a skirt LMAO
That is nice to know diaper fans have a good sense of humor - yeah, yeah
I guess you have to.
I'm a diaper fan of Loz Monty Python too.
Next post is from Shy Tweeny, moderated for not wearing a diaper it says under their name.
Favorite activity while diapered?
What is your favorite thing to do while diapered?
For me, I simply like to watch kids movies while wearing goodnights.
Baby Link 9 says, video games.
It's pretty fun and convenient, but hard to relax so I can let go.
A big part of it is usually my diaper ends up leaking anyways.
Yeah, a big part of it.
the finale is usually German DL imagine I'm five years old hate potty training
and watching Disney movies also waddle around in my space with the diaper also
do you think they really waddle by my space do you think it means like an
adult playpen I hope so yeah maybe my favorite one that we've seen a diaper
It's from Tundra 1975 and it says I am
diapered 24/7 due to total bladder and
incontinence so everything I do I am
diapered I would say my favorite
activity is riding my quad through the
wilderness near my house. It's so relaxing to go out and explore the wilderness.
So he has a cheat code for this where he can just say anything that he likes doing most.
always has to wear a diaper yeah after a long stressful day of sitting around and
shitting my diaper I like to go out yeah
imagining a completely naked except for the diaper just like doing a wheelie just
in his backyard. No shirt, no pants. 119.75 too, what a good name. He's cold. He lives
somewhere so cold that all he wears is a diaper. He lives in Antarctica. They don't have bathrooms
in Antarctica. That's true, that's a good point. Oh my god, uh. I don't want to read
this whole thing but this username is really good, Fudgedinloves. Somebody's got to read
this Jim 100 one do you see this no Jim 100 you might hate me for this so here
goes I like to reload ammunition because it is relaxing but demanding then I like
to do fine woodwork making cabinet pens and pens you name it it costs a bit at
least for the woodwork the reloading is very cheap considering what it would
cost to buy new or already put together and then it's just like technical stuff
And then at the end it says of course TV and movies
I
Want to drive diapered and go to a store one day
But I drive stick and I don't know if the shifting would cause any clumping of pulp
Most of the time I wear it
Occasional health issues, but when I have the house to myself
I wear to watch long movie slash binge sessions building with Lego sets or if I'm having a cigar outside
I like Churchill sizes, which I can take a long enough time to get through
I don't want to have to read light because I have to empty my bladder other than that
I'll wear a diaper simply to wear a diaper
So he's saying the constant shift in gear it because I assume he's not very good at driving a stick shift
It would be so sudden that the momentum would create giant like clumps of pulp
all through his diaper
Pulp?
What the fuck is pulp?
He's got a sawdust diaper.
He's a man's man.
I'm hoping that pulp is like some, like the material of the diaper is called pulp or something.
Cause otherwise he has like,
fully, he eats a lot of like hay and corn.
He has a completely separate...
(laughter)
And it just completely separates.
After he shits.
Cause of that centrifugal force.
He's chewing food with his ass cheeks and making a cut in his diaper.
Two people in a row said running their chainsaw.
All these people are so outdoorsy.
What the fuck?
Both of them said they got really sweaty from running their chainsaw in the woods and then...
Just running it?
Just not cutting anything down?
This first one said, "I spent the day today not diapered.
My skin started to feel a little clammy and I knew the best practice would be to let it
air out.
run the chainsaw all day cutting up firewood logs.
Oh, then the second person says,
I just got done running my chainsaw
and cleaning up a section of the woods.
They're both running their chainsaws.
- Yeah, I can't believe it.
Yeah, they're all outdoorsy,
like driving their quads,
smoking Churchill cigarettes,
driving their stick shift vehicles
and worrying about getting home in time
to change their diapers.
- Going on the tilt a whirl with my diaper.
Even more worried that the pulp will separate.
- When I get the chance,
I love to go to the movies in double diapers,
drink all the soda and consume a tub of popcorn.
Also, I'm a pretty good bowler.
I've been bowling in diapers
and have had some accidental diaper exposure in public,
non-ABDL diapers.
People try to copy my form
and watch every aspect of my technique,
so I know they've seen the waddle effect
of double diapers beneath my basketball shorts.
(laughing)
- Oh my God.
It's so clear, two diapers underneath and ones.
That is sick.
Like you know the people who wear like the basketball shorts under the jeans, yeah
I could take off my jeans if I need to hoop and I take off my shorts if I need to poop
He's got such a strong they try to copy my swagger
I'm on that next channel.
I got that boom boom password.
What's your secret?
How do you move like that?
How do you move so fluidly?
Your fundamentals are so perfect.
Your bowling stroke.
Somebody else said they also love riding their quad but in the mountains.
Yeah.
I also do that in the mountains.
I like the fucking diaper loaves on quads and chainsaws.
It's so fucking sick.
I like to throw dynamite at black bears.
*laughter*
I like to...
I like to hunt wabbits in my diaper.
*laughter*
Holy shit.
Oh, I left a stinky little wabbit hole.
*laughter*
You ready to get really gross?
It smells like Elmer Fudd and more like Yosemite Sam.
*laughter*
Yeah, I want to get really nasty this is only one one one one. Oh, yes diaper masturbation. Oh
For all those that find diapers a turn on how do you play with yourself and then in parentheses?
Masturbate in diapers do you use toys? Well boy? I'm Detroit. Well cuz play
Yeah
Playing with yourself on this forum could mean
As a baby role player you use toys yeah, I use alphabet blocks
Yeah, I got Burt and Ernie.
Rubbing the front, best with a wet diaper, was the approach I've used the longest.
I've had a vibrating wand for a while, and after a bit of a training curve, I get good
results.
Doing it by hand gets more consistent results, but the wand has surprises, and that winds
up being pretty compelling.
Wouldn't it, wouldn't it, if it's a wet diaper and it's got like the pulp in it, like they
said, wouldn't the vibration move the, uh, uh, uh.
It's not great for the diaper, so this is typically done before a change.
This guy's got it down to a fucking science.
Sometimes by rubbing the front by hand, sometimes by humping a few pillows stacked on top of
each other, sometimes wet, sometimes dry, but preferably wet.
Wet makes sense because you create like a groove in the pulp that your penis goes into.
You know what I mean?
And then you get like more friction on it, on every part of it.
I just don't want to get my pillows wet with my piss.
Well, guess what buddy?
You have a diaper on.
Yeah, those are the special pillows.
Yeah, true, maybe they are those like...
Those are the pillows that have Bob the Builder on them.
Yeah, and they're like water resistant.
Yeah.
Cool.
Just in case you spill water on them.
[Laughter]
Oh, here's a comment from Zoran that says,
"I sometimes vibe, but I love to hump inflatables and especially while wet."
[Laughter]
Here's a... this guy's... this guy's scolding.
Um, littles really shouldn't play with anything that is in their diaper because that's their big's job.
If my little has been a good boy and gone to bed nicely, he may choose to make a sticky in his diaper.
*laughter*
Oh, fuck, dude.
I do this by rubbing the front of his diaper while making up a story of how his stuffie saved the day,
or how good he has been for me, and what he has been up to.
Not before long...
I love making up a story about how good a boy he's been.
He's not before long, he has become aroused within his diaper. I can do two things at this point
Soundly think of something that he did that was naughty and say but that was a naughty thing and stop so he doesn't climax
From that I will get a frosted little that I may
From that I will get a frosted little that may find a pillow the hump
This will give me a reason for a spanking or I go fasted with the rubbing until he climaxes
I then tell him to tell me that he is a little baby
Tell me you are a little baby
It's like a flowchart - it's very logical always end with cuddles and snuggles for when we are not together
He then does his own rubbing. I've tried to put him into a chastity cage to stop that but he won't wear one long-term
We have also used a wand.
Wow.
Not like a sex wand, just like a magician's wand.
I bet this is the two half people who have the wand from Fairly OddParents.
It's like a wand that turns into a bouquet of flowers.
I prefer to put a ton of lotion on my penis than a bit of powder and tape up into a thick diaper.
Then after wetting a fair bit, the pee and lotion mingle and make things delightfully squishy.
squish around on the floor, and eventually, laying on my back, penis pointing down,
I just keep opening and closing my legs.
That movement, plus the squishy interior, does the work for me.
*laughter*
This one says, "I can just rub myself, but I discovered I can orgasm without being hard!"
Listen to this one, "I'm weird and can point downwards in a dike with my heart!"
*laughter*
Wait, I'm weird what?
I'm weird and can point downwards in a diaper while hard.
So my favorite thing is to cut my hand over the front with my fingers massaging the bottom.
Works especially well when slightly wet and having rubbed in some baby lotion the night before.
The thing about me is I'm weird.
My gear is weird.
This may be the most disgusting post you've ever seen, dude.
seen this really bad this one so this one's so bad it's a landing x-ray it
says someone once mentioned that they nursed milk from their wife's breasts and
spontaneously or chasmed in their time fuck
dinosaur walk I do not use toys I simply go to town without the use of toys I
I either show my hand in my time you rip my diaper to shreds or I
Can out of the side or top of my diaper however?
I do usually soak a second and sometimes a third or fourth diaper that I'm not wearing with water and
Squeeze all the gel out either into the diaper
I am wearing or on my crotch area and rub it all over on occasion
I also use the aid of putting other items in my diaper after I urinate in it to turn me on that aids in the
masturbatory
masturbatory experience
cream mud dirt butter oatmeal very ripe bananas etc. Either way I love
masturbating in diapers and while cookie monster said it's nice to do it in a
diaper because there is no mess for me there is always a mess. I rarely throw a
diaper away that isn't a colossal mess of gel shredded diaper bits and possibly
other things when I am done but that is part of the fun for me as I was not a
messy child and getting messy while I'm doing this makes me feel little even
though I am doing a more adult thing. Go figure.
Ripping my diaper to shreds. I can't believe they tear their diaper to shreds.
Yeah, that's crazy. Just waking up from cumming just like the Hulk with just a ripped diaper.
Ugh. Yeah. The violent sort of the hate fuck side of diaper fantasies.
Yeah. That list of materials is so ganging. Just struggle fucking my diaper until it's ripped to shreds.
Whipped cream, mud, dirt, butter, oatmeal, very ripe bananas.
It's all food except for mud!
Butter dude. Mud is food to a baby.
Putting a stick of butter in there.
Yeah, cold butter from the fridge.
Here's a post from Chamber Pot.
I have some age-related ED problems but still enjoy rubbing the front of my wet and sometimes messy diaper.
And like someone else said I have found that I can still achieve orgasm even though I'm not hard
I don't like just the same at the end. I
Don't like that. That just means that like your whole life is now a series of secretions
That's the last thing that was supposed to be like the result of labor, but now everything just leaks out of your body
I like waiting until it's as wet as possible and rubbing or using a vibrator
But then also adding either a large batch of oatmeal or pudding in the front
And playing in it until I explode.
The sensations, yo!
*laughter*
I've never talked about this before.
Blushes and looks at floor.
Back before I had to wear 24/7,
I'd unfold a nice thick diaper out in front of me,
and while playing with myself,
softly whisper "my diaper"
over and over again.
*laughter*
While playing with myself,
*whispers* "my diaper, my diaper"
That is so fucking weird.
Just saying it, just saying it like, uh,
the 13th like feeling the front of a wet diaper while playing with myself insert
a very by the way this is bullet-pointed feeling the very front of a wet diaper
while playing with myself insert a very large toy in my bum bum put my diaper on
and play with myself smelling a wet diaper while playing with myself and
then playing with myself while varying while wearing a very wet and messy
while whispering, "Please, I need changed"
to myself over and over again.
And then it ends with, "I'm very embarrassed now.
It still feels very weird to do these things.
Seriously, what is wrong in my head?"
(laughing)
- This is from Bobby Sue Ellen.
"I wait until my diaper is very wet,
squirt Johnson's baby lotion on my fingertips,
reach in and tickle away until I go number three."
(laughing)
I mean it's like if you're coming without getting hard you're going number three
in your diaper. I like to take my diaper off spread it out and then just rub on it.
I just have nocturnal emissions after 30 days of no orgasm. Somebody okay so
somebody asked Chamber Pot how they bust soft they said what how does that work I
I kind of wished I could do that and they just said just get old
someone says
Leo Codal says I rub the front till I reach climax or point
upwards and rub my diaper against it until I reach climax
either way is a ton of fun wet or dry and then Albert diaper
boy responds. That sounds like great fun. My peepee is hard
thinking of that
puppy boy 97 says just go on the floor.
Get off! Get off of this fucking forum!
That's wrong!
Just go on the floor.
Oh man.
I don't know what this is in response to, but somebody named Daboze just said,
"That is really bad advice. I can't emphasize enough how badly that could end."
And it's not in response to anything.
I'm gonna--
No, no, no, no, wait.
No, okay.
So it's in response to this post from LittleFellow
that says, "For extra squishiness, mix a little water with just one drop of bleach
and pour it into a fresh diaper.
Wet it and enjoy.
Attention, pure bleach will hurt skin fast if exposed for too long.
Do not use pure bleach.
One drop with a little water is enough to make your diaper become really squishy after you wet.
Bleach chemically reacts with urine."
just try just try putting a little sprinkle of hydrochloric acid into your diaper
it actually reacts with urine
i usually lie on my belly in the bed moving my hips so my diaper rubs
once i'm done i just stay in it until i pee or i need to change and revert to my
adult life
back to my damn adult life
it's back to work for me
back to the rat race
Back to my Zoom meeting.
I mean that is what I say after I jerk off.
Just walking around the house after.
Yeah, just looking at your watch
until your next diaper appointment.
Erm, this is gonna sound weird,
but when I'm diapered up, I make love to my bed.
Erm.
Holy shit.
I'm gonna move to this, to some other posts here.
Yeah.
There's just a few more that I think are really good.
This one's from Neophyte.
and it's I don't want to read this whole post, but it's basically it's an alert
post to everyone else on the forum letting them know that they that this
company foresight now has a diaper that has pictures of weed leaves on it and
they have an ad that says who said adult diapers couldn't be fun and people are
arguing over whether this is good or bad Kimba Fox Natsume says I thought Mary
Jane was going to be some girly print. I guess the internet hasn't completely
ruined me.
And then it's...
I hate fucked diapers.
And then...
Yeah, what would being completely ruined look like?
Bambino Baby comments, "A drug leaf on diapers?
No thanks."
I honestly think this is going to be a big flop.
Holy fuck.
Cuddle Woozle says, "It's for when you've smoked so much weed that you can't figure out how
how to move and go pee, XD.
Not a fan really, LOL.
But then that's probably because I'm not
into the whole marijuana scene.
Yeah, I'm Cuddle Woozle, I'm an adult baby.
I'm not really into the whole marijuana thing.
- Padded Brony says, "Ah yes, the diaper for the burnout
with weed leaves all over the rest of their things."
I mean, it kind of feels like a gag to me.
Like seriously, weed printed diapers?
Bet it'd be good for Halloween though.
going as a diaper Bob Marley this will be perfect dog boy says I don't know we
rolled joints for our children when they were babies all the time they grabbed
the joint with one little baby hand and with the other baby hand light their
BIC hold it up to the joint and suck in typically they'd say oh man da da Wow
- Wow.
- Are they saying they made their case for me?
- I forced my case to smoke weed.
(laughing)
- I think it's just a deranged joke.
Like these are the, it's like a guy walks into a bar joke
from these people.
- Oh, gotcha.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- Everyone is absolutely entitled to their opinion
on this one.
However, I will definitely be buying these
for my little guy.
- Buying them for your baby?
- No.
- Oh, no, no, no.
(laughing)
- No, little guy is not your baby.
- Little guy is nothing Patrick.
- Yeah.
I don't know pot leaves are so drug leaf LMFAO. It's not like it's heroin
Some of us use it medicinal and medicinally, you know, I have severe PTSD and besides it's 100% legal in Canada
Where foresight health is based? Yeah
stinky diaper
I'm wet and high right now. Wish I had a weed friend
Dude a wet-ass diaper and a blunt
Seal the blunt shut with the diaper
We got oh
There was one more. I wanted to read let me figure out which one it was you guys can keep going
I'm just trying to what is this
Peeing while driving no
Let's look at that's got to be illegal
Yeah, are any of y'all able to pee and drive? I'm having a hard time sitting down and going any advice
That's illegal in the same way the driving barefoot is illegal. Yeah
Gossamer 77 whose picture is on the monster gossamer from Looney Tunes, but in a diaper
Says what I find helps me is setting the cruise control so that my right leg can relax that helps me a lot
Then I can also use both legs to lift myself off the seat just enough to relieve some pressure off your muscles as he Horton
mentioned above I do know exactly what he's talking about because I've had to
I've had to piss in a bottle and oh yeah you can't just sit down you do have to
like lean over you have to get up yeah I mean and even then when it's time to
like you shake your dick I'm still just pissing my pants just a little bit when
I put it back in my pants yeah I can't do the shake down that's a casualty of
pissing in the car I think you're always gonna have a little bit of piss well any
of a giant piss bottle in your car also that right says earn up says practice
while the car is parked and then work your way up from there just hang just
hang a diaper over your shoulder like football pads I've done it before but I
had to go in little dribbles that's from the padded turtle which is a picture of
squirtle winking wearing a diaper lift you bum when you need to pee it takes the
pressure off. Lifty bum. Lifty bum. The D seat is the only is the one and only place situation
where my body refuses to pee. Oh the driver's seat. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. I was like what is
the D seat? The diaper seat. Your car doesn't have a diaper seat. No. You gotta get one
of those installed. Which diaper do these last two? Diaper days yeah diaper days is
the one I want to end with. So let's just let's check out Soaking a Diaper by
Nikki93. Does anyone intentionally soak their diaper? I have noticed that as I
have gotten more comfortable with being diapered and better at sneaking wearing
them at night sort of that I really enjoy the feeling of a very wet diaper. I've
been wearing these adult depends type diapers I can't remember the name but
they're great and so far are my favorite. Anywho I am getting distracted. I can
either have two big peas in them before they overflow or a few little peas. When
they start to overflow I feel more of a sense of excitement. I've gotten to the
point where I will be completely soaked around that part of my body and I love
it I really wet the bed as a child so I don't think it is a regression thing I
just genuinely enjoy the feeling of it I like the squish the wetness the fact
that I've wet the bed I suppose this is what initially drew me to diapers but I
know one I never let myself indulge in it as much as I have been I lay a large
disposable pad down which has kept my mates dry so everything is working out
well for now so I like that their profile photo is like a galaxy brain DMT
it's sick did yeah a lot of people enjoy it it's not sexual for me but I love the
squish and he responds it's several things for me that's from Jason the
regressor from a Wabax with an American flag profile picture just as it feels
nice don't it and that was posted on September 11 Chris Chris Chris says
there is nothing better than chilling out in a wet diaper in the morning when
you don't have to go out so true to what the fuck Christian type look at
Christian diaper Luffer's profile picture where is it oh my god not very yeah
that's not Chris must be their name oh dude they made a log in love Christian
diapers yeah I mean it's you have to log in of you people's profiles now - this is
seasoned seasoned citizen whose profile picture says one person can make a
difference and everyone should try.
Um, comments, one of the few pleasures in my very dull life.
[Laughter]
This one's from Frungi.
I love a very, very wet diaper, and I like to keep a wet diaper on until it reaches capacity
and is about to leak.
I am pretty good at judging when I reach the saturation point.
[Laughter]
But nothing is to perfection, and of course I have misjudged a few times, resulting in
the tell-tale crescent-shaped wetness on the back of my pants.
I like to get the maximum use for my diaper. Changing when the diaper is only
slightly wet seems like a waste of both the diaper and the great feeling of a
soaked diaper.
Bratty Princess Sophie says, "Dry diaper is nice. Wet is better.
Soaked is a nirvana feeling that can't be beat."
I too enjoy the feel of diapers when they are wet. I might not flood,
but I do enjoy the feel and bludge when they start to soak.
the bloods. I did my kids laundry yesterday somehow an unused love size 5 diaper my
grandson uses made it into the wash when I opened up the washer I found the diaper
between two towels surprisingly open intact and flat it swelled to two inches
thick all over and was holding it all without any dripping doubled over and
taped it was four inches thick and quite weighty how come our diapers don't get
like that I really don't want to think about these people having like kids let
alone grandkids you know just so bad I guess if you mean filled to full
capacity I'm not crazy about my butt getting wet I love soaking the front so
it swells against my front side I like my junk to feel warm and padded but my
junk in the trunk I like the soft dry comfortable fabric against my butt feel
safe in the back arousing in the front someone just commented mine is which I
totally assume means that their diapers currently so wait what is why is this
guy on this website he says I don't wear them but if I did I'd echo pretty much
everybody here is a great feeling the way they start out and then swell up
when used they're much more fun to wear when they're soaking wet but again I do
not wear them. I would never oh no. I'm drawing on my very limited experience
from my first two years of life. Yeah I wore diapers back in the day but not too
much anymore. Yeah I used to be into that bullcrap but not anymore. Boy do I like to take a
trip down memory lane and visit these forums. It's just like I remember. I enjoy
any time that I can soak a diaper. I would rather wear a diaper than my clothes and
that's from partier22. Going to a party wearing only a diaper. Wet until I can't hold it anymore,
then enjoy the happy lovely feeling of a dry diaper in its place. I don't know
what that means. Is it dry or wet? Who knows?
Here's one from seasoned citizen that says one of the few pleasures in my very dull life.
I said that already, Patrick. Oh, you said that?
We read that one. Yeah, we read that one already. Patrick exposed.
Oh my God, Pat's exposed. Patrick just ruined the entire episode.
I did. You're going to do diaper days to bring it
back? Yeah, this is the last one. This is how we're
going to close it out. All right, I'm excited.
days da ze I would like
it's such a good phrase
but CDDL Jess the cross-dressing diaper lover and the picture is their avatar is
Teen Titans Robin and it looks like it's missing no in the background oh and
Robins wearing a diaper and Robins wearing a diaper of course I would like
to appreciate my piece I have found this weekend last week had a family weekend
gathering so no diaper time. Work has been hectic to say the least, working 70+ hours
for the last 3 or 4 weeks. Worked a short day yesterday and hit my favorite thrift store
where I have an agreement with the owner on if she gets any diapers in my size she holds
them for me. It's kind of right to first refusal arrangement. I have made many big
donations so I get a good deal. I also volunteer when time allows. So anyways, she gave me
a case of a 10s pull ups, a brand I haven't tried yet, and while they are thin and comfortable
they don't hold much. Even though I will be donating three packs back, I feel was a
great find. But I have been diapered since 4 p.m. yesterday and in such a better
mood. My wife commented, "I must be in my diaper days" before she left for work as she
patted my front to confirm. And then a smiley face and the last line is, "Have a
padded day." No replies, dude. That is such love, dude. That is the most true love I've ever read about.
my wife must be in your diaper days and patted my front.
Oh you must be in your diaper days. I would kill for that.
That would be the last line in a diaper movie. Just a 1940s return to tradition wife
just telling you that you're in your diaper... you must be in your diaper days.
I'm so i'm so trad I went all the way back. I went back to my baby
shit. Yeah. I went too far into my diaper days and cheated on my wife.
Yeah, I was on a three or four day diaper date.
Don't let me get in my zone!
Oh, fuck. All right, uh, thanks for coming on, my beautiful friend. Yeah, we love you.
I love you guys.
Is there anything that you want people to know?
Uh, no. Well, just keep your eyes posted on for the Adult Swim thing that I worked on.
Okay, keep your eyes posted.
Keep your eyes posted.
Keep your eyes posted on that.
all right happy Patty