you're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[laughter]
Okay, I'm recording right now.
Okay, I'm recording too.
- I just did it in a chat. - Have you done a mic test with that new microphone?
Yeah, no, fuck my fucking...
- I don't care about your sandwich at all. - ...fucking thing that goes on my sandwich.
- I really don't give a fuck. - Yeah, no, it doesn't matter.
No, no, no, seriously, it doesn't matter that the Capicolo
was like the greatest I've ever had.
That's great man. Hey Pat, did you do a mic test with that new mic?
I did record me singing "Don't You" by Simple Minds.
Just like Dan Ninen does on his SoundCloud.
That song is by you, dude.
That's also the only thing that is confirmed to sound good.
There you go.
Don't you...
My favorite part of that song is the lyrics that Pat knows.
My favorite part of the song is the lyrics.
Yeah.
When it comes to songs, one of my favorite parts is lyrics.
I do remember having, you know...
I got this skate wax that looks like weed.
Because it's green?
That doesn't look like weed.
No, look, it's got a stem.
It's got a stem.
Get your, your, wait, Pat, this is going to be a disaster with Pat holding the mic.
He needs that arm.
Yeah, I know, I need to get that arm.
So the fans...
We need to hire somebody to hold the mic in front of us.
The fans need to buy it for me.
Yeah, we all got new mics, except for Cameron.
Mine is coming in the mail.
Mine's coming in the mail. My mic goes to a different school.
Yeah. You don't have a mic.
You guys are just jealous because I've had a better mic than you this whole time.
Not anymore.
I think my mic would be good on the table.
I think it would not.
Absolutely not.
It would not at all.
I think it would sound good.
You're the stupidest guy I've ever met in my life.
I'm not stupid. I'm not actually stupid.
You're really stupid.
I just act stupid to make myself smart.
You just act stupid.
I'm like Jar Jar Binks in that I act stupid and I'm secretly a Sith Lord
lord
Oh, cuz he just sits all the time. Yeah. Got him. Yeah. You think that you, oh, that's
funny? That's funny to you? Yeah. That's funny to you? Yes. Alright. Yes. Say it again if
you think it's so funny. He's a sit lord cuz he's always sitting down. You're
sitting down right now. I'm not sitting down, I'm standing up. You're not. You're sitting up.
You're spitting up like a baby.
I'm standing up right now.
No I'm standing up.
I'm actually duct taped to the ceiling.
You're a baby and you're spitting up.
Patrick why are you obsessed with babies?
You're obsessed with babies.
Oh really am I?
Who's the one who keeps talking about them pal?
You keep talking about a diaper.
No I don't.
That you're wearing.
Can we just get back to my sandwich please?
Never.
Oh my god.
Why do I even do this anymore?
Alright fine.
I need water.
I need a drink, it's 80 degrees in this apartment.
Why didn't you get water before we started recording?
Because you guys didn't let me.
No we did, we said you could go to the store and get an energy drink if you wanted.
And then Cameron said don't do that.
I don't care, you can go. I'm the boss, you can go.
I just made myself the boss.
Yeah, I could, I could, if you guys record...
Well let's do a Patrick man on the street thing right now.
If you record my zoom call because I'm on my phone I could go to 7-eleven in the middle of this
I'll do the extra editing for this. It's worth it. Yeah, wait. No, this is gonna be tough. I know
We should do that at one point
Let's do it right now.
Come on.
Okay, wait.
Yeah, I can make it work.
I can make it work.
The audio quality for this episode is going to get worse.
Unmute your phone and mute that.
I'm literally, all I'm going to do is go to 7-Eleven.
I'm not going to talk to anyone.
Oh no, you're going to talk.
No, you have to talk.
You're going to talk to us or else you're not allowed to go.
Then no, then I don't want to do it.
No, come on dude.
Are you afraid to talk into your phone?
I'm not afraid to talk into my phone.
Look at me.
Fucking look at me.
You see somebody like me, that looks like me, walking down the street.
What is that supposed to mean?
People are going to call the police on you?
What are you talking about?
I was called, dude, I look fucking crazy.
Oh my god, it's a fat guy on the phone.
No you don't look...
They're going to call the police on a fat guy on the phone.
No dude, this fat guy is video chatting with his friends.
He's talking about skateboard.
Can you guys send the SWAT team?
They would do that.
We need to put this guy in jail immediately.
He looks too crazy.
Just go dude, you're going to get caught.
You're going to get caught.
Can you guys send the SWAT team?
They would like to SWAT us.
We need to put this guy in jail immediately. He looks too crazy.
Just go dude. You're such a baby.
No, I don't want to go anymore.
This guy's wearing his hat backwards.
Thanks for ruining the episode, Pat.
I didn't ruin the episode.
You literally just ruined the episode.
We're four minutes in.
Now what are we going to call the episode?
I can't.
Everybody listen to wear a mask.
You wouldn't hear me.
- You can hear people through the mask.
- Yeah, are you so quiet that you can't talk through a mask?
Patrick's mask is made of steel.
- I have like a neoprene one.
- You have a what?
A neal-breen?
- I have a neal-breen one.
- Neo what now?
- Neoprene.
- Go to 7-Eleven.
- Nah.
- You are the worst.
- You should be fun, dude.
- Yeah, you would've done this--
- You should come to my house and drink 50 beers
and sit on my head.
And now you won't even go to the store.
- Yeah, now you're afraid. - It's a scary time.
- What happened to you, dude?
- You go to the store every day.
- He goes to the store every,
you threatened to go to the store before we started.
- Yeah, that's true.
- Just go, oh, okay.
This is how you slowly convince Patrick or something.
He says, no, no, no, no, no.
And then at some point it clicks and he goes,
yeah, that's true.
And then it turns into, yeah, I guess.
And then he's doing it.
So we just have to push him over.
(laughing)
have to push him a little bit and then he'll do it.
Yeah.
And then he'll bring up, and the reason why he doesn't want to do it is because like his
mom did something at one point that taught him a lesson.
Yeah.
I don't know, it's just my mom went to the store recently.
My mom actually gave me a moral about that recently.
I was reading a fable.
I was reading Ace of Fables with my mom.
My mom and my dad actually recently went to the store on a podcast and it didn't go well.
I had a friend in middle school who actually played video games all the time, so I don't
know if I should do that.
My older brother, my older brother, Beatle, he went to the store one time.
My older brother, Beatle?
Who is he calling Beatle?
I don't know his name.
No, you have 15 brothers.
I have two brothers.
The oldest one is Beatle.
You think you have two brothers?
The oldest one is Beatle, he's a black lab.
He's a dog.
You have a dog brother?
I have a dog brother.
I have a dog. Yeah, my dog brother went to the store and they sent him to jail
because of how crazy he looked.
So I can't go to the store.
I walked, I walked, I walked to Whole Foods and I got sushi and I came back so
sweaty that I had to like take my shirt off and eat sushi without a shirt on.
Whoa. I was just sitting here.
I am, I am getting out of here soon.
To where exactly?
to
'cause I know it's above a restaurant.
He's typing in.
It is, hold up.
I'm not gonna cut it out, so just so you know,
I'm not doing any extra editing.
All right, it is 137 Rockingham Road.
Rockingham, dude, rock and roll.
That is my new address, send all the mail you want to it.
Yeah, go for it.
Oh, that's that same pizza place, isn't it?
No.
No, it's not a pizza place.
It is, it's your pizza place.
Once Patrick moves in there, it's going to be a pizza place.
It's a pizza place, as he called it.
It's a, it's not, it's going to be a pizza place at the Crossroads Mall.
It's going to be at a Comet, it's going to be a Comet style pizza place.
Once Pat gets in there.
Yeah, true.
Once Pat moves in, it basically, immediately it is listed on Google Maps as a ping pong pizza restaurant.
They flip the, like, sold sign into Comet ping pong.
- It just, yeah, just big.
(laughing)
- Just turn it over.
- Oh, fuck.
Yesterday, somebody asked, I was in the park,
we were walking around the park.
I went to Bushwick yesterday for the first time.
- Oh yeah, Caleb's in New York.
This is the first Caleb in New York.
- Oh yeah, this is the first, yeah, I guess you're right.
- I'm gonna be living in New Hampshire,
Caleb lives in New York,
and Cameron lives in New York City.
- And I'm living in a new state of mind.
- Whoa.
- New baby penis.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause that's what he has.
- You wish I had that too.
- Cameron, you do have sort of a,
like you cast the same shadow as Chris D'Elia.
- Yeah, similar outline.
- Yeah, he had like the same paper cutout.
- Dude, Chris D'Elia fucking, he laughs like.
- He does.
- He's so, oh my God.
- Dude, he laughs.
- There's something about that guy.
- No, but he does not like close his eyes.
His eyes widen when he laughs.
it's fucking scary
*laughter*
is worse his laugh or his penis than what it does? What it craves.
Ooh well because he might be laughing while... You think he jokers? I think he might be jokers.
He's a joker? What does a joker's cum face look like? He frowns. He is. The only time he ever frowns.
Yeah. How's his face? With teeth. Stop making that face dude. That's like a 2009 vine face.
Yeah, like it's like a will will Sasso face
Yeah, you look good
I went to Bushwick yesterday and it's an it's a entire not a neighbor. It's an entire city of people who look like us great
Every single person looks exactly like us. Like I thought I saw both of like us like us like to me and Pat. Oh
Yeah, that's pretty cool. I can't and I'll have everyone has a dog Jana asked what some of the issues like
what is that dog? Like, what is your dog made out of? And the
lady was like, well, we recently had the 23andMe done. And it's
basically like 1% this, 1% Chinese, 1% monster and 1%
black lab.
That's a small dog. It's only 5% of a dog.
4% of a dog. Wow.
It's sick, man.
Is that one of those like, genetic GMO dogs?
Yeah.
- Yeah. - It was like created in a lab dogs that has just like a shit ton of health problems.
- Yeah, it's a dog that's a cat. - Yeah.
- If you fuck up a dog enough, it's just a cat. - That's true.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- If you didn't breed it enough. - And vice versa.
- And Vice Magazine. - And Vice Magazine.
- That's where Caleb lives. - That's true. I moved here so that I could do...
- You can get a job at Vice. - I moved to Queens so I can do a
documentary here where I walk around talking to different rappers
and uh was being scared. Yeah. Have you seen those all those vice documents? The Chi-Rac one? Yeah.
They send a guy with Warby Parker glasses. They literally, I mean they send like like uh like
he looks like white Donald Glover and they send him to the fucking to like the south side of Chicago
and he's like I'm here with um a rapper named uh Murder 1 Million. Murder. Uh can you tell me about
What is it like being an artist?
Yeah, he's like man. I love to kill people
Yeah, I would love to kill you right now and the guy's like hugs on his collar and looks into the camera
Here you're seeing the long-lasting effects of the Rama manual administration here in Chicago I
Love it dude
We did go to the vice office when we visited. That's true. It was right next to the
Geico Gecko. Yeah. Yeah. The Brooklyn Geico Gecko. Yeah. Well, there, no, I remember
there's two. There was the Geico Gecko. Oh yeah. And then the Brooklyn Geico Gecko. Yeah.
That was right next to him. That is completely fucked up. Yeah. Yeah, that one was awesome.
It was like an off-brand mural. Yeah. Yeah. Of the Geico Gecko. Do you think, um, the,
Brooklyn Geico Gecko came first and then Geico came in and then like put through
up their tag and was like nah this one's better. Yeah like what the Redskins did
with Indian people. Yeah that's exactly what. They were like I think we can do a better version of this.
And then they came up with yeah the perfect you know the pinnacle. Me and um me and Pat and
Will last night found we're playing. We found this browser game called called
Crunker. Yeah, it's just like a Call of Duty knockoff, but like in the browser
and it's got like Minecraft style graphic. Yeah, dude, it's so fun. So
fun, but
for so long we played it for like we played it. We started playing it like
12 and stopped it to. Yeah, my God, at the end of we just like couldn't stop
just me like you just got crunked just over and over and by the end of it I had a horrible
headache and then I went to bed and I dreamed about crunker.
No, no dude it's too powerful.
They placed the crunk's curse on me.
We need to DDOS this game dude.
Crunker is so fun.
No we gotta play it.
We can't DDOS it.
It literally is just call of duty with minecraft style graphics.
We have to destroy it.
It's minecraft graphics and you can control like the gravity and shit so we were playing
like these games where we would only play crossbows and then like jump super high and snipe each
other.
It was fucking dope.
Oh my god, dude.
Yeah.
Dude, it was so sick.
It was crunked as hell.
It was crunked.
We're trying to buy Cameron a gaming PC.
Oh yeah, so everyone bump up your pledges.
Bump up.
100 bucks a month, let's go.
100,000 a month.
If we get everybody to do 100 bucks a month, we could each get a new game.
I could get two gaming PCs.
We'd have like 30.
How much money would that be?
We would be beating pod damn America.
We'd have $30.
the
I know I know nothing about it. Yeah, it started unnecessary beef so we can get Cameron a gaming PC
That's probably that's probably how we do it. Yeah, and you support us in this in this battle
Yeah, this battle in this clash of the Titans between pot about list and goddamn America
Yeah, that's up that sub. They stole the first word of their name
You're so dude, that's why I can't over see that's my camera needs a piece
I know, I should just get to take one of their PCs.
That's his thing!
I'm the fat one, Caleb's the skinhead looking one, and Cameron's the smart one, and we can
only make fun of Cameron for being too smart.
Yeah, your brain is so powerful that it's actually, it's dumb.
I fucking hate it when Cameron does his telekinesis on me.
I fucking hate it.
It's so annoying, dude.
I don't do that.
When he can learn every pattern of the railway.
Dude, it's so annoying when we're watching a movie and he just guesses the entire plot. Yeah before we get it
They believe press play on the DVD, right?
So that's fucking annoying you can extrapolate it if you read the back of the box. It's pretty simple annoying
It's so annoying when he hears look at the shiny the rainbow part of the DVD. You can just see what happens
It's so annoying you have to unfocus your eyes like a magic guy and you can just watch the movie in the back of the DVD
and
And then it's a lot harder with a double-layer disc.
You have to cut it in half down the middle.
Exactly.
Because then one eye sees in widescreen and the other sees in fullscreen.
I put the DVD on my finger and I spin it around and then I put a long fingernail down onto
the grooves in the DVD and it projects it onto the wall out of my eyes.
It's so hard for him to do that with laser discs too because the hole is bigger.
Last night, all he has is one big finger.
That's true.
You forget about my big finger.
That's his smart finger.
That's his RFID smart finger.
You couldn't fit enough brain in your head, so you had to put an extra finger.
You know what's a good place for an extra brain?
Definitely the finger.
The finger.
Just getting it closed in a car door.
Just getting an aneurysm.
Last night, I was in the bathroom, and I was like, "I'm going to go to the bathroom."
I was like, "I'm going to go to the bathroom."
Just getting it closed in a car door.
Just getting an aneurysm.
Getting a concussion from typing on the computer.
I've been smoking weed again.
It sucks.
You got that NYC kush dude.
Yeah, the famous New York City weed that Nas talks about.
Yeah, it's more like a thin crust.
[Laughter]
In Chicago.
Here we call it chopped grass.
Chopped weed.
Yeah, it's chopped...
Chopped chiba.
We just call it chopped cheese.
Chopped chib.
I smoked weed and I was imagining,
you know that conversation of like,
desert island movies, like what's the movie
you take me to, go to desert island?
I couldn't stop imagining like,
somebody asking that question,
and then me showing them that I own a DVD,
like a special edition of some DVD that comes,
it's packaged in a life raft.
(laughing)
And it's just like, I just could not,
I was like, well yeah, the special edition
Castaway to come to the work of a life raft and a month's supply of food.
You got this special edition of Without a Paddle and it comes with...
It comes with a paddle.
It comes with, yeah, it comes with the paddle and the raft.
And Seth Green.
Yeah.
Yeah, Seth Green.
Keep your hopes up.
He's so small.
Mm-hmm.
You guys want to play action figures?
But yeah, that's just, you know, the only...
That's the only thing that happened this week besides packing things up.
Yeah, I'm buying boxes after this. I'm packing my shit up this week.
Dude, boxes. So expensive, man.
Oh, I know, dude.
You should try making your own, like out of dirt and rocks.
You get like six boxes, it's like 20 bucks.
I know.
It's fucked up.
If you want to buy like a pallet.
Go out to the side of the street, go to the like, the grass.
Go into their dumpster.
Go to the dumpster, okay?
Find glass bottles, melt them down, and make glass boxes.
And then you can see what's inside the boxes.
That's true.
Good idea.
I should have saved the box that my PC came in.
That's true.
Yeah, that was a big box.
That's a good way to move it, too.
Yeah.
If you put all of your clothes in glass boxes, and then you put them in the moving truck when you arrive,
you open up the back, and they're all shattered, and your clothes are just filled with glass jars.
And then the mover just says to you, "People in glass boxes shouldn't store clothes."
In glass houses.
That's right.
Yeah.
Yeah, and you're moving to a glass house also.
He says, "I'm glass," and then he breaks it open and he increases.
I'm made of glass.
By the way, yeah, and I'm glass too.
One time when I was moving, when I worked installing shower doors.
- That was your job?
- Yeah, I used to work as a glass shower door installer
for like rich people.
- Damn.
- And yeah, it was awesome.
And one time I was installing--
- One time the stepmom was stuck in the washing machine?
(laughing)
- And then I passed a contract
into the washing machine in a pen.
And I said, "Read this and then sign."
But I was installing a shower door for basically one of the aunts from The Simpsons, Aunt Selma,
just exactly that lady.
And she was yelling at me, and I fucked her.
Yeah, and I fucked her.
"Caleb, I need you to have sex with me."
And then I was bringing the... she was yelling at me the whole time, like, "Don't hit the cat!"
She had a cat that was running around, she was like, "Don't hit the cat! Don't hit the cat!"
And then, um, I, I, because I was so distracted, I was like walking up a brick staircase and
the corner of the glass shower door, it's tempered glass, but the corner of it hit the
stairs and then the entire thing just exploded into a million pieces, like an $800 glass
shower door, and all of the glass landed on her cat.
And so, uh, I just, I was just like, we'll, we'll get you another one.
Sorry, bye.
and just left her just picking,
picking glass out of the cat's fucking eyes too.
It was awesome.
I miss that job.
It was such, it was so sick.
'Cause it's like, you truly do,
like, everybody who gets a glass shower door is rich,
but some of them will like,
tell you like when you show up, like,
"By the way, I will not give you any water.
You cannot use my bathroom."
Like, "I have kids, don't look at them.
Don't play with their toys."
And it's just like, what do you want me to do then?
Yeah, I'm here to use your house.
Not giving you water? That's so fucking weird.
And again, not letting me play with, you know, the pretend kitchen set and stuff.
Yeah.
Yeah, that sucks.
I just don't get it.
That really sucks. You don't even get to play with the toys?
You don't even get to play with the reek?
They have a reek action thing?
This one bitch, she put a lock on the trampoline.
What?
I wouldn't jump on it.
And then I had to crack the code to jump on the trampoline.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Well, if you just if you just rocket jump, you'd be able to get into it.
That's how I didn't have a rocket launcher.
It's not glass safe.
That's how Caleb's mom used to trick him into stop playing video games.
She would just put a put a padlock on top of the just on top of the PlayStation.
Not connected to anything.
And be like, Oh, no, I need to figure out the code.
Mom locked it.
I guess I'll go outside.
Yeah, it's just you sitting with the lock off of...
You're sitting away on the couch just trying to unlock it.
[laughter]
Yeah.
You try to go outside and you see the lock on your door.
Oh my god, I'm locked inside.
I'm locked inside forever.
What's the code?
You just have to turn the lock.
No, what's the code?
Did you have locks in your house that were like...
Like the door locks where there's no key to them.
The key is just you put a hole...
Like there's a hole and that's how you unlock it.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- I used to-- - You put a hole in the door
to unlock it? - I'm sorry,
I told you I've been smoking weed, my brain is a box.
There's like a, there's doorknobs where you have like the,
I give up.
(laughing)
I don't know what I'm even saying.
I don't know where I was going with this.
- You have to put a hole into the doorknob?
- No, there's a hole in the thing and then you put a--
- A key, you mean a keyhole?
- Not a key. - And then you put a key
into it? - A key.
Oh, like the door, like the doorknob has a hole, like a small hole in it.
YES!
Yeah, I had those, but we never had the lock thing.
See, I would lock it and then my mom would just unlock the door.
Fucking bitch, dude.
I still don't know what you're talking about.
I didn't have like a lock on my door or anything.
Anytime, I think, because my bedroom in high school, like my parents just kind of like built,
the
and
I'd go to diners, smoke cigarettes inside.
I had sex with old, old women as a child.
That's what you did as a latchkey kid.
I was a latchkey kid.
Yeah, I was pretty much a latchkey kid.
Me and my teacher had sex.
Yeah.
It was pretty much a latchkey.
It's pretty much what latchkey kids do all the time.
Yeah, I used to have to make my own PB&Js and sometimes I'd even have to beat my own
video games.
I was pretty much a latchkey kid.
My parents weren't around much when I was a kid.
They were always working.
- Yeah, they were always in the kitchen and the dining room
and I would just be in the living room.
So I had a really kind of isolated childhood.
- I had to have a job when I was a kid.
I actually had to do this.
I had to unload the silverware.
- I actually had to play with my friends every few days.
- Yeah, every couple of days I had to play with my friends.
One time I cleaned the bathroom, the downstairs bathroom,
and which was always the dirty one
because my dad would have his stinky friends over.
And so, yeah, I pretty much had the worst childhood ever.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
I basically, on Christmas, instead of gifts,
instead of one gift, I would get multiple gifts
and it was terrible.
I would get-- - Yeah, it was really bad.
- Yeah, I had a really tough childhood,
but it's really helped my career.
- Yeah, it helped my standup career.
- A standup comedian.
- I had a really difficult childhood.
You know, my dad, he would drink like a glass of wine
and then go to bed.
- Yeah, it was pretty tough.
- Without even saying goodnight to my mom or me.
- Yeah, sometimes when there was a big storm,
the power would actually go out of the house.
- Sometimes there would be thunder
and I would have to go under the bed.
- Yeah, sometimes we would get the mail
and there would be bills.
- Yeah, I pretty much went to public school,
and I actually stopped believing in Santa Claus
when I was in seventh grade, so that's pretty early.
- Yeah.
- It kind of like destroyed my life.
- One time when I was playing--
- My parents are actually divorced.
time I when I was playing tag it started to rain mm-hmm yeah well I had I had the
worst worst childhood one time I played in the mud and they made me take a
shower yeah also I got AIDS when I was a kid I got childhood AIDS and I still
the
Let's wake you up, dude.
Go to the store.
No, if I go outside, I'm gonna just start chafing.
I don't want to like...
Let's do it.
That's Patrick's dance move.
Yeah, he's gonna get too excited and start chafing.
I'm gonna start chafing.
I'm gonna start doing the chafe.
So when you put one leg behind your head and the other behind that leg, and you roll around
like a ball all the way to the store, and he goes with the chafe.
Yeah, I do a Lincoln chafe.
You do a LinkedIn chafe.
the
Jim Webb.
Which is like as soon as he didn't win he was like Trump's the guy.
Was it Jim Webb?
Yeah I think it was Jim Webb.
Yeah it was Jim Webb yeah.
As soon as like he did not, as soon as he had to drop out he was like I'm dropping out
and I'm endorsing Donald Trump.
So awesome.
It's so funny dude.
He's the man.
That Trump video with the white kid chasing the black kid is the most embarrassing.
Oh my god yeah that too.
It's been on my mind.
I think the funniest part is like, I'm sure people have talked about this,
but it's like, what is the message?
Is the message here that like the cops were playing with the protesters and
that's why the protesters are running away? Like what's going on here?
I don't think there's any, I think it's literally just like, I mean,
anything that he posts is just like, Oh, that's kind of funny. Like that's,
that is the only thing he thinks of before he posts it.
And most of the time he's very right. You know, I wouldn't post those, uh,
the
Obama with the big boobs.
Yeah, or one of the millions of ones that it's like Obama wearing like a headscarf.
I want him to post one of those and just be like, "Is this real?
Hard to say."
Hard to say either way if this is a real photo.
Can't tell.
There were these guys back during the Obama election, I think 2012, there were these guys
who would sit at a table outside the post office and they had a big banner with a picture of
Obama with a Hitler mustache and it said "Obama is Hitler".
(laughing)
- Would you go back in time--
- I'm just yelling at people.
- Would you go back in time to kill baby Obama?
Well, you'd have to go back in time
and take a plane to Kenya,
but would you do it and kill Obama?
- Would you go back in time and make Obama Hitler?
- Would you go back in time--
- Patrick, stop playing with a blob.
- I'm not.
- He's eating a blob.
- The only playing you're allowed to do
is going to the store.
- Okay.
I'm gonna keep harping on that this whole episode.
'Cause you, we--
- I might do it, I can do it at the--
- Yeah, I'll bring my gun.
- Yeah.
- Then I have to get all my stuff together.
I don't wanna--
- What kind of stuff?
- He has a store outfit.
- What are you talking about?
- He dresses up in a suit.
- He goes full hiking gear.
He has a big, tall backpack with a tent in it.
He has a compass, a map.
- He has a full Death Stranding outfit.
- Yeah, just in case I get lost.
- Yeah.
Yeah, look how mad he is. He's so mad. I'm not mad. He's so fucking mad. I'm not mad.
I'm making fun of him for being too much of a baby to go to the store.
Hey Patrick, there's a sandwich at the store. It's literally a block away.
People, sometimes you got to work for this fucking, you gotta work for that
patreon money you're not getting your cut next month yeah let me see let me see
what my phone's at all right I can probably go oh you can plug headphones
directly into the microphone yeah yeah that's a monitor it just monitors oh
yeah we're still figuring out these new mics but they're sick here he goes all
- All right, he's--
- Oh my God, wait, he's putting on a beautiful heading gown.
- Is one of you recording the Zoom call?
'Cause I can't-- - Yeah, I am, I am.
- Cam is.
He's making excuses already. - Then I can't go.
Then I can't go. - Cam, no, you can't go.
- I have been recording the Zoom call the whole time.
- Unmute your phone.
- Okay.
- And then mute your laptop or your computer.
- Am I unmuted now? - Yeah.
- Okay. - Mute your computer.
- Mute your computer. - Okay, I've muted my computer.
Can you hear me? - Oh my God, yes.
Dude, this is so...
Dude!
I'm so excited.
Alright, what are you gonna...
Are you recording the call?
I can't...
Yes!
I've said it like five times.
I am.
Yeah, but I never hit any of the consent buttons.
I'm recording it on...
I record everyone, one of them.
I have the audio.
Just go.
Just go!
Oh wait, I don't have my keys.
See, this is why I keep making up excuses.
No, no, I do.
I do have my keys.
They're in my back pocket.
I actually...
Wait, wait, I don't have any of my keys.
I don't have any of my keys.
I don't have any legs or feet actually.
Wait I forgot my brain in my eyes.
He's outside. Oh no he froze.
He already froze.
(Laughter)
Oh there he is.
He's back.
Did it work?
How is it so far?
I had to shut off my wifi.
How's it going?
It's fine.
Is it scary out there?
Yeah it's very scary out here.
Can you give somebody a hearty boo?
A boo?
Boo!
Can you yell at somebody on the street?
No, I'm not going to boo. I'm not going to scare anyone.
Sounds like someone is afraid.
Yeah, you're booing yourself right now.
I'm not afraid.
You are.
You're afraid.
He's very afraid to talk in normal volume.
I'm not.
You should yell.
Can you just give us one QGL?
Can you give us a play by play at least of where you are?
We don't want to see you we want to see you're going to see what you see, okay, there you go
Okay, I'm crossing the street. Okay. It's got this
You're okay
No, all right, he's safe you're fine again
He's crossing jaywalking
His video for the gun, I didn't give you enough credit you're a total badass dude. Yeah, this is a pretty cool
I'm with the gosh
You almost got what you must got what he's chasing a pigeon he's chasing he's going into 7-11
Magic happens. This is it. Show us show us some Doritos. You have 10 you have 10 seconds to find Doritos one
Four five six seven. Oh, we found a okay. All right now loudly say success
success loudly
success
They got one that doesn't have like
Whoa?
The top of that monster energy. Yeah monster. Is that do you think that's like a that one?
No, that's rare dude. You can sell it's not rare. This one's probably more rare. No
I don't know. What?
(laughter)
This one's probably more...
Hey, how's it going?
Hey. Wait, unplug him.
Let me talk to him.
Oh my god. I want to talk to him.
Yeah, let's get a conversation going.
I just hear beeping.
At least show us the guy.
Actually, I know the guy who works at that.
Yeah.
Thank you.
He'll recognize me. Show me.
them hold the door open for you. Say you like to open it yourself. Say you like to open it yourself.
Don't you dare fucking hold the door open for me. Say what do you think I'm an old man.
What do you say who do you think I am? I'm not doing that. Pat you used to be fun dude.
So I don't care. He turned his video off. He cares dude. He turned his video off.
Why did I turn it off? Oh whoops. Yeah it's okay we know we didn't miss anything because you're
so boring. Yeah do something run at somebody. I literally I literally told you. Just get on
the train and go somewhere. Just get on the green line and just see where it takes you.
This is awesome. This is the most innovative podcast experience.
Nobody is doing this right now.
Nobody is doing anything like this.
Goddamn America isn't doing this, dude. They don't know how to do this.
This is a...
Did I bring my keys? I don't remember.
You said you had your keys before you left.
That'd be really funny if I got locked out.
I hope you're locked out.
Oh my god.
What the fuck?
Woah a construction thing just went by.
You just, okay.
I have bad news.
What?
My audio on Audacity stopped recording.
Alright we'll just use the zoom call for this one.
You're just gonna have to use the zoom call.
This is gonna be a bad audio quality episode.
This is gonna be the worst.
It's all right. It means I don't have to sync anything. That's true.
Probably have to sync the first half. I'm sure my cats are fucking destroyed like
walked all over the goddamn keyboard. Yeah, they walked on the keyboard.
You almost said destroyed my entire apartment. They probably walked on the keyboard.
They, dude last, so I left my, I left my computer open last night and um, I fucking, I made that video.
Push that guy! Yeah, knock him over.
Push him! Come on, turn around, go back. Come on dude!
No! Remember when we used to play the knockout game? Yeah, that was fun. Remember when we used
to play knockout? We would just, we would just knock out, we would knock out Neil over and over.
the
Oh my god.
Get back on the audacity audio, unmute that shit.
You there?
Hello?
Come on, unmute something baby.
Oh no.
There we go.
Woo!
Successful trip to the store.
Give us a review, what do you think?
I go there every day
Yeah, pretty good that doesn't have
You just got a blue monster, yeah
What's the flavor called fee is that Fiesta flavor is Fiesta? I just I just crushed a white monster
I'm the white house now. Everyone's gonna now someone's gonna triangulate the location of my apartment. Yeah, everybody. Yeah
He always thinks somebody's hacking his location so funny. Yeah, what are they?
I've never met like a more paranoid young person than that. I don't think yeah, I like the correct for the craziest
Yeah, they're gonna they're gonna find my house and they're gonna look at my trash
They're gonna see you they're gonna see what I put in my tissue
We're worst-case scenario where you're putting like what would it take for you to be put in like a take-in?
Situation. Yeah, I put in a take-away. What would they need to take from your apartment?
for you is it your cats yeah are you worried about the cats probably the
cats I don't yeah maybe the cats probably my PC just go full taken you're calling
them yeah threatening messages yeah but now you're giving them ideas now you're
giving them ideas so yeah let's listen go hey maybe I should kidnap it we should
go steal his cats and you know wait I didn't even know he had a PC yeah let's
Yeah, that's what we're there.
Oh, you guys ruined my life.
You're done for dude.
You guys ruined my life.
They know what it is.
They heard Green Line.
They heard 7-Eleven.
You're going to, you're done for.
Yeah, you're going to jail.
Yeah, you're going to have a, you're going to have an Eminem stand situation on your hands.
Yeah.
This sucks.
Yo Pat, I wrote you, but you still ain't calling.
It could happen.
It couldn't.
It would not happen.
How do you know?
How do you know it wouldn't happen?
What if Eminem is a huge fan?
Exactly, that's what I'm fucking saying.
He's like, "Fuck, I wish there was a way to be crazy about this guy.
Oh wait, I wrote an entire song."
Yeah, I have an idea.
Let me get my hot daughter.
Are you re-wrapping a stick of gum? What are you doing?
Yeah, I just decided against it because we're recording something.
Would you rather date Eminem's daughter or have one million dollars?
I would rather date her and then have her and then sell her back to her dad for two years.
Would you rather date Eminem's daughter and get to be friends with him on PS3?
When?
Or be friends with Eminem on PS3 and you don't have to date his daughter?
Would you rather date Eminem or date his daughter?
Hayley.
Um.
I don't know, I think I would choose, that's a tough one.
That is a tough one.
Who would you rather finger?
Eminem or his daughter.
Who would you rather have sit on you?
Who would you rather want to watch Parasite with on a stormy day?
Just cuddle up.
Probably Eminem.
You know Eminem could probably do some fun accents or something.
True, in Parasite especially.
Parasite would kill it, dude.
He would kill it with the accents on that.
Yeah, I think he can only do like an Indian accent.
Well, doesn't he only do he goes like
"doing doing doing"
Yeah, he's
That's all he does. Yeah, you're right. I think he also raps but I might be mistaken. No, he didn't no
No
Eminem is famous for saying the "doing doing doing"
Yeah, he does say it
That's it. No that you guys don't understand the doing doing doing is his like rap alter ego
Normally is marshall matters, but then he he turns into the doing doing doing. Oh, okay. Marshall doing doing doing
Marshall doing doing doing yeah
M&M does that sound familiar are you talking about marshall going from detroit?
yet what are you looking at more agency you just completely he's chipping out
you have a child's face what i want to get you look like a kid watching a
picture
now it's a video uh... where you watching a video
i'm watching a video of a guy we should never ever i'm never selling weed in
juliet no more
and it's a group of white i saw that i said i like it
what we should never let that go to the story and i think you do whatever he
he
I should be able to walk away. You got a monster energy. You love monster energy.
You love the store. You love it. And you didn't even do anything funny like look at the trash while you were out.
You guys made me do...
Go back out and look at the trash and show us if there's anything cool. Yeah, go to the store again.
I don't want to look at the trash. Go outside,
look at the trash and see if you can find some food and if you do, you're gonna eat it.
I'm not gonna do that. You do. Oh my god. I'm not doing that. Unlock the door, go outside,
Look at the trash, make it your own.
[burp]
Put one of your cats in the toilet.
Yeah, put a cat in the toilet.
Put a cat in the toilet.
No!
Get a swirly.
Okay, two cats.
Can we go back to a normal episode?
No.
We're playing virtual buddy with Patrick.
Yeah, I know you are because this is torture.
Yeah, put sand on you.
Put a bunch of dynamite sticks around you and then float across the room.
And also detach your arms and your legs and your head from the body.
No.
Give me 1000 coins.
Be Greg.
No!
Wait, have a George Bush skin on.
Ugh.
Can I, I'm paying 200 coins for a George Bush skin right now.
I did not have sexual relations with that woman.
That's right.
That's George Bush.
Yeah, with any woman, coming from you.
Yeah, oh.
Ugh.
Now say, I had sexual relations with him.
We never make Cameron go outside.
I can't go outside.
Cameron is allergic to the outside, look at him.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's true.
If I go outside, I turn into dust.
He burns up in his skin.
He turned into a dusty baby.
If he goes outside, he turns into a girl.
Yeah.
And I've never been outside.
It'd kind of be the ideal situation.
A girl when you're out, a girl on the streets, boy in the sheets.
Yes!
Girl outside, boy inside.
Yeah.
Like beautiful, amazing.
Like a vampire.
It's just like a vampire.
Yeah, vampires are girls when they're outside.
But when they're inside, the freakish boy comes out.
You invite them to be a boy.
Yes.
Yeah, they can't turn into a boy unless you invite them.
I'm gonna defeat a vampire here in New York.
People keep getting shot in the head in my neighborhood.
Patrick, get off Twitter.
No.
Oh my god, we made Patrick too mad at us and now he won't talk anymore and he's just browsing Twitter.
No, I'm trying to, yeah.
Patrick is giving us the silent treatment.
I have sucked the last couple episodes, I will admit.
- Dude, you're such trash, dude.
Me, on the other hand, I'm gonna chew some gum now.
- Do not chew the gum.
- I can only be the second worst guy on the episode.
- Don't chew gum.
- So I'm gonna chew this gum.
- Do not chew gum.
- I can't wait until the fans call me fat and gay and,
and stuff.
- It's really getting to his head.
- They call me a fat gay guy all the time.
- Who calls you fat and gay?
Let's talk about this.
people who call me fat and gay.
- Give us some names, we'll go after it.
- Give us some names, yeah.
- We'll call them out.
We're gonna call them out on the podcast.
- Yeah, I don't wanna give out any names.
- Okay, so you like being called fat and gay then?
- I don't like being called fat and gay.
- Okay, so no, call them fat and gay some more.
- You know who calls you fat and gay, buddy?
The mirror.
And you gotta get your confidence right
before you try and comment in podcasts.
- Mm-mm.
- You know?
- Mm.
- Pat, if anybody calls you fat and gay,
we'll beat them up online style.
- You cannot do that.
- I won't do nothing.
- You can't beat anyone up.
uh...
pat if anyway cause you think they will beat them up on online style
you cannot not only know i didn't know
i'm gonna beat up patrick
you probably try it and i think anyone else insults him to beat you up
and i think that there's a big normal people who've been there
he's completely clocked out
look at the use of his watching a movie
is what i'm not watching is watching a video of toy trains going around a track
You can see his eyes following the he's watching a video of bugs
Mm-hmm. Yeah, and he's getting hungry walking sticking it. He's like it's like one
It's like a frog watching a video of an eye on an iPhone of flies
He's trying to look at the screen. Yeah, he's like that video of the monkey with the iPad who just keeps clicking a penis up here
Yeah, you know the peanuts. Oh, you know a penis appears. Oh, we got him. We got him. Yes
Venus appears what else do you have to say about that?
that
yeah
in red dead redemption
uh...
that you can go to the story and money
no i don't want to go to the university of what what what you want to do that
the
again in K2 and it's gonna...
You can't overdose on Kratom, it's from the earth.
Well, I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna figure out how.
Telling my mom K2 is from the earth.
Mom, it's good for me.
Mom, it's from the earth.
You want me to get a C in biology?
Let me smoke it.
Mom, seriously, seriously.
It's called a performance enhancing drug.
The reason it's banned is because it makes you better.
It's banned because the paper industry...
It's banned because the white man
doesn't want me to get a C in biology.
So think about that.
And maybe try some yourself, mom.
Mom, I just wanna smoke K2
and I wanna listen to Uncle Adams in the basement.
Is that too much to ask?
Is that too much?
I have a playlist, it's all uncles.
Uncle Cracker, Uncle Adams, and my uncle Matt's band,
the Matt DeVita Project.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, the Matt DeVita Project.
And I just want to listen to those three.
I want to play PlayStation 2.
I want to play Crash Bandicoot.
And I want to smoke K2.
So if you can't abide by that, Mom, guess what?
I'm moving to Dad's house.
You're going to have to move out.
Yeah, you're going to have to move in with Dad.
Just--
Mom, if you keep acting like such a bitch,
and you're going to move in with Dad,
I'm going to live in your bed with your husband.
And he's going to eat my pussy.
So you might want to let me do what I want.
That's what happens.
Yeah, that's what happened with my dad.
Your dad ate your pussy?
My dad ate my pussy too.
Damn. Damn.
Damn.
Caleb got ate up.
Yeah, my dad.
My dad is my dad is Alf.
What?
My dad is Alf.
Who?
He ate my pussy.
Your pussy cat?
My pussy cat.
Alf.
My dad is Alf.
It sounded like you were saying Alf.
Yeah, I was like, "Who the fuck is Alf?"
My dad is Alf.
Caleb thinks that's what Alf is named.
Yeah.
Owlf?
Owlf.
Yeah, 'cause he's an owl.
Yeah, I'm Owlf.
Yeah.
You guys like Oofle?
Oofle?
I love Oofle.
That's what Caleb thinks Alf is called.
Do you mean Ooby?
Ooby!
I think we're talking about Ooby.
Bro, Ooby's like my favorite guy on TV, man.
the
and
(laughing)
- Yeah, I don't know if we ever talked about this.
Me and Tim, this guy who sounded like that,
who came to our, he worked with us,
and he would just come in,
and he would just be like,
yo, Day of the Dead, dude?
Fire, bro.
And then every once in a while, I'd be like,
Tim and Eric is like the funniest shit
I've ever seen in my life, bro.
It's like kinda weird sometimes,
but sometimes I'm like, oh, you guys are cool.
- Yeah, he-- - He's so awesome.
He's the best.
- He was sick, too. - Yeah, dude, he ruled.
We watched all those Hollywood...
We didn't start air control.
Oh you did?
That was sick.
We watched that fucking...
When I came to work with you guys
we watched all those Hollywood High...
Oh yeah and we watched the video of the guy
shooting really fast.
Oh my god dude.
That video was fucking awesome.
I'm gonna retweet that right now.
It's so fucking funny.
He's just like a...
stoner like skater guy. He's old. He was in like he's like almost 50.
Yeah, he was in his 40s. He was telling us about like a skater owned bar in LA and we were
talking about Hollywood High. Then we saw Hollywood High the next day and I'd
never realized it was like the stair set was that big. I think we literally talked
about this the last time we recorded Pat. I think we talked about this with the
the
Oh skateboarding, they just, oh dude, skate four.
- Now it's all about inline skating.
Yeah, I brought this up at the beginning of the episode.
- You did?
- Yes, and you didn't even,
I couldn't even bait you then.
- Oh, I didn't hear it.
- What do you think of skate four?
- Dude, I'm excited, but also,
I'm excited, but like not, I'm skeptical.
- Yeah. - 'Cause it's EA.
- He's skeptical, 'cause he can't count higher than three,
So he's skeptical about whether they picked the right number.
He thinks they invented a number.
See, I think they're just going to call it skate again.
I think it's going to be S-K-4-T-E.
Oh!
I think it's going to be 5K 4+3-B-O-O-B-S.
Skate boobs.
Yeah.
That would be the greatest video game of all time.
That's an $80 game new again. Yeah
Rated AO
Why
It comes with a Donkey Kong Bongo style set of boobs that you play with yeah
You play it with it with a race car steering wheel to play skate boobs. Mm-hmm. Yeah, and you have to turn
Yeah
Yeah, and you play this awesome skater named Dale Earnhardt Jr.
Dale Earnhardt Sr. and he's like, "Just remember to turn left, that's all."
That was one thing that people don't acknowledge about Dale Earnhardt is that he just got confused,
left and right.
Sometimes he'd get confused in the kitchen and he just forgot.
No, he went to the bathroom.
He went to the bathroom.
He just forgot.
No, he went camera left. That's the problem.
Yeah, he was also, he had recently starred in a local theater production as Seymour in Little Shop of Horrors.
And so he learned the term stage left and stage right.
Yeah, and somebody said left and he was like, oh, stage left.
Yeah, he's a performer at heart.
Yeah, and he, yeah, and the boy was at a finale.
Yeah, he went out with a finale.
He went out with an ending.
Yeah, just the worst news anchorman ever.
Yeah. And Dale Earnhardt, he went out with an finale.
Yeah.
And the tragic story of Dale Earnhardt,
the tragic story of Dale Earnhardt unfortunately ended with the end.
Yeah. My name is Pussy Impossible.
This is Channel 5 News.
Good night, ladies and gentlemen.
Yeah, it's the morning news and he
says good night.
That's right.
And then they're just like, oh, I
guess we have to turn off the I
guess that I guess he said good
night. We have to turn the channel.
Pack everything up, I guess.
Yeah. And then he says he says
San Diego means
a whale's vagina.
And I'm Todd Burgundy.
Yeah, I'm red Burgundy
and I'm the freaking worst newsman
ever.
I just suck.
Hey, today on the morning news...
Balls.
I'm Red Burgundy.
I'm making my balls.
Yeah, hey, oh crap, I'm sitting on my balls.
This is the news now.
Hey, fuck you.
Yeah, suck me off.
This is my personal news.
Suck my dick, bitch.
I like wieners.
I'm...
(laughing)
Back to you with the weather, idiot.
Stupid bitch.
You stupid sucker.
Good morning, Arizona.
You're gay and I'm your dad.
You're gay, I'm your dad, and you're the news today.
And you're the news, hey,
how 'bout you tell me some news, you pussy?
Here's a piece of news, shut the fuck up.
Here's my news, ready?
(high pitched squealing)
And now I'm gonna reenact an entire episode from the second season of Workaholics.
Alright, and go.
Hi, what's up?
I'm Topher!
The real Topher Grace.
The real, no, he turned out to be real Topher.
Yeah.
The real Topher.
Topher da Toker.
No, Chris D'Elia played Topher on Workaholics and he was a pedophile.
A pedophile.
Ah, ah, turns out Crystal Lee is a pedophile.
Can't have that.
No.
We can't have that.
Oh no, Crystal Lee is a pedophile.
Crystal Lee is kind of like the white male of pedophiles.
The straight white male of pedophiles.
Norse.
Yeah, and everyone in the audience claps and like, I guess that's correct.
Yeah!
*laughter*
That's a good point.
That's a good point, Nanette.
Yeah.
You've done it again, Nanette?
*laughter*
Nanette?
Good one.
Ah, crikey Nanette, you've done it again!
Another amazing fuckin' stand-up special, Nanette!
I can't believe you're dunked from half-court like that!
You're beautiful on the inside, love.
*laughter*
I'm Nanette.
Outside, you fatter shit.
the
Yeah, I watched that in 5th grade.
It scared the shit out of me.
there's a point where they're like,
the document is like,
and they had a CIA handler whose name was Maxwell.
As we see in this song, when we play it backwards,
they have a strong message to send to him.
And it's like yellow submarine or something.
If you play it backwards, it goes like,
fuck you, Maxwell.
(laughing)
And they're like,
obviously this means the CIA handler's name was Maxwell.
(laughing)
And not even,
fuck you, Maxwell.
Not even like considering like the Maxwell silver hammer. Yeah. Yeah
Q Maxwell fuck you Maxwell
All right, yeah, we're done see where yeah
Habit Pat's happy I could do another two hours. I could all right second. I'm gonna stop recording
Back out a second win cuz he farted two times
*laughter*
(laughing)