You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[Laughter]
[Distorted sound]
Okay, so what were you saying before?
Pat doesn't like diners because, this is what he said,
he can make the food at home.
[Laughter]
That's why he doesn't like them.
I don't like diners where it's clear.
You can make any food at home, Pat.
You can't.
You go to a restaurant so you don't have to make any food.
You are waiting on it.
I got chicken and waffles and the wings were frozen.
Patrick, how many days a week do you buy a sandwich?
Probably every other day.
I mean, there you go.
That just proves that your opinion is completely...
It's different.
It's completely different.
Why is that different?
Also, if you go to the diner...
A sandwich is literally the easiest food to make in the world.
That's the first thing you teach a child how to make.
Not true.
First thing you teach a child how to make is a birthday cake.
You don't teach a kid how to make a birthday cake.
Birthday cake is a multi-step process.
You let your child put the frosting on and you let them lick the spoon.
That's not making a birthday cake.
That's part of the process.
That's frosting something.
Speaking of, did I ever tell you guys about...
He does not want to talk about the diner opinion.
He's embarrassed.
You're scared of what's going to come out.
- Someone's gonna get mad at me for that opinion.
It's gonna be annoying.
- An old Greek lady is gonna get so mad at you
about the diners.
- There's some diners where it's like,
if they have a special menu item,
it's like you gotta go to this diner to get this thing.
- Diners have 200 things on the menu.
You need to be discerning about what you order.
You can't go into a diner and order spaghetti
or chicken and waffles.
Get a fucking Reuben.
- The waffle was good, but the wings weren't good.
get a Reuben or get a BLT.
- Yeah.
- That's what you get at a diner,
and you get fries, and it's six bucks.
That is why you go to a diner.
You don't get a fucking
gazpacho at a diner.
- Why not?
- 'Cause it's gonna be hot.
- Yeah, that's true.
I don't know, I think a lot of
diners need to step their game up.
- Yeah.
- Talking big shit on diners, man.
My mom worked at a diner for like most of my middle school.
My dad was in the military.
Fuck you dude.
My dad wasn't in the military.
You're talking like you was.
No.
About these damn diners you fucking pussy.
My dad works at...
Just say the whole name.
I've definitely said my mom's place of employment on this show and that is a huge...
Probably when we had like zero listeners.
I was just like, like when it was just a conversation between us and we recorded it.
She works at a jail pressing license plates.
Yeah, my mom's a jailbird, my dad is the warden.
And I was...
It's a beautiful romance.
Oh, it's so gorgeous, dude.
Oh, yeah.
Did I ever tell you about our first date?
I probably shouldn't.
It's like every, every like romance novel before like Twilight existed was something like that.
Yeah.
every like romance novel from like the 30s. The Warden's Mistress. Yeah, or like this guy and his slave fell in so much love.
I found a, I found like old, I went to like an antique store with my mom when I was in New Hampshire last week,
and I found, my dad actually found it. My dad showed me it. We found like old
erotic novels there, and one of them was called Humpers Wild.
Is that the author's name or is that the no no that was the title of the book it was called humpers wild
It was a big yellow
Book did you literally figure out what did you read it?
Did you my dad started my dad started reading it to me in the middle of the store is pretty fun
You're here it is. Yeah, they got it on Amazon. You can order. It's currently unavailable
Picture for it either damn. It was published in 1968. Yeah, I should have picked up
Dyke yeah, my favorite thing is like look going to like an antique store, and they'll have like a porno mag section
and you look through them and it's like,
like they were showing like butthole in the 70s,
you know, in print.
They don't have the guts to do that anymore, dude.
- They do, they still do that.
- No, they don't do that shit, no.
- They do it on the computer.
- Yeah, not in print though.
Print is beautiful, beautiful,
Maxim, gorgeous, gorgeous Maxim bikini model.
You can't see a butthole for 90 cents anymore.
- That's so funny, I mean, it's so funny,
Maxim magazine was like such a middle school thing,
like, "Yo, my brother got Maxim."
You know, like something like that.
I remember when I was like nine years old,
my uncle Kevin was like, we had like this pool,
like this public pool in our condo complex,
and my uncle Kevin was down there reading Maxim's
and he was showing my brother and my cousin Brian,
but he wouldn't let me look at them
'cause he thought I would snitch to my mom.
It's just like, looking back at that,
it's so funny 'cause it's just like,
wait, it's fucking Maxim.
There's like articles about like,
oh, what's the best like--
- Cigar. - Drone I can buy?
What's the best legs to guard?
- There was a friend of mine in middle school,
his dad collected Sports Illustrated.
Of course he had the swimsuit edition,
but he hid the swimsuit edition from my friend.
So my friend collected, he stole all the body issues
from his dad, which are the ones that are focused
on athletes' bodies, and he's like,
"This is the hottest shit ever."
And he showed it to me, but it's all--
- Like half of it's guys, yeah.
- It's all pole vaulters, the ugliest athletic women
the world who are like insanely uh uh they're just like ripped and scary and i was like this sucks
dude i want i want maxim i found i found humpers wild oh yeah let's read it on triple x books.com
let's read humpers wild on here and it's a triple and the cover yeah it's part of the triple x series
it's starring vin diesel oh my god yellow cover it has the uh the eiffel tower on the cover yeah
Yeah, you found the exact yeah. Yeah. Yeah, it's an e-book here. I don't feel come well ordering from this website
But is it written by Cyril van Dyke?
Yeah
It is and here's it how they have the first lines of the book the first paragraph here as a sample if you guys want to
Hear it. Yeah
This is how the book opens Bob's success with Josie had rekindled his tired flame for hump activities
His taste of fucking with someone other than his wife had opened new fields of development to him
Given him a new outlook a new awareness and a new interest in physical charms of female bodies
He now found himself turning to let his eyes follow the progress of slender legs his hands sweating slightly
When firmly rounded breasts were near and his mind was wandering into daydreams when he caught a whiff of perfume or saw a nicely molded
Pair of ass cheeks. Oh my god, dude. What?
Yeah, people use words his hands sweating slightly when firmly
breasts or near
Erotica is the the grossest shit of all time. It's horrible like it's definitely a visual medium
Like I don't think like being it being really good at describing sex. It's just disgusting
I need to get off the top
They have a sidebar on this website for the bestsellers the top bestseller is a book called sex secrets of a children's doctor
what yeah I feel like I like them like I would never think to add all these
adjectives to describing sex right you know my shit would be like yay a fucked
her butt. It was crazy. There's multiple chapters where it's like big buildup and then it's like
a huge buildup like they went upstairs blah blah blah and then he fucked her butt. Chapter two.
The mailman's devilish grin was so enticing to Samantha so she invited him in
and then he fucked her butt. You know what? You know what? We should actually
totally right. We should do one like just like the whole pay every chapter is just
build up and then it just ends the same and then he fucked her butt.
Yeah and then he fucked her damn butt. It's called back towards secret.
Yeah that's how it should be right? I mean like nobody's jacking off to the parts where you're like
like yeah her mound there could be land you know like it's all there could be
one part two words like and you'll never guess what happened next turn book
upside down to see I think he fucks your butt again yeah yeah you have to guess
it could be an activity book - oh yeah yeah they could be yeah yes the word
search to find out what he fucked that's our next big book it's the pot about
list erotic novel yeah I think it's a not a bad idea on us yeah yeah we need a
scenario though like what's the most sexual sit alright so mailman I like
mailman mailman and probably on it's all mailman mailman is probably like you
know like first chapter to like you know kind of develop that like our
protagonist is horny as hell I believe she's an antagonist okay yeah because
she's horny as hell yeah okay so our antagonist is horny as hell an antihero
really all porn stars are antiheroes in the room in the room maybe instead of a
mailman it's like a delivery driver like okay I don't like it like ice cream man
yeah could be the ice cream man maybe it can't be the milk man that's overdone
Yeah, yeah, but mailman what's another guy that goes to your house uber driver guy make the guy who came to read the gas meter
Fucked by the guy who came to read the gas that could be the title of the book by national national grid
Grind his name's grud
Grud
Grud from national grid grid learn. It's ground on by grid grid Ler. Yeah, I did on god. That's so good
Oh, yeah, they don't have sex they just great. Yeah. Yeah. Oh wait. Yeah, we can make Mormon erotic novels
No
Cuz I don't want to do anything for them. No, I don't they don't they don't need our help, dude
They have a pretty good thing going on. I don't have have you seen the Mormon
It's like the BYU sketch troupe and they have like money as they have they have like an SNL style show that they film it
like I think it's BYU, but it's like a Mormon like SNL and
and I only saw one thing from it,
'cause it was called,
like it showed up in my YouTube recommended,
and it was a white guy with like a sideways baseball cap,
and it said, "Urban Spelling Bee."
(laughing)
- It's just exactly like the Derek comedy sketch.
- Yeah, it's the same thing.
Well, that's what I'm thinking.
Maybe they saw that and they were like,
"Okay, I feel bad for laughing at this.
Maybe there's a way we could feel good
I'm seriously going to heck for this one for laughing at this crap. Well Mormons love racism. Yeah, that's a good
Yeah, they didn't let black people into the church. They had there's a thing in their book
I think that says that black people are were reincarnated after being bad. Yeah, I've we talked about Mormons on here already
I think we probably yeah, cuz I think there was there's like Mormon
fucking
Like like there was a video I saw of like a Mormon like PSA thing where it was like a video like an old like slide
Projector thing and then like a white or black person turns white
Yeah, oh fuck just getting baptized and coming up white
Do you know we fucking totally talked about this but there's like
the more... ah fuck I don't want to just like talk about this if we've already
talked about it but like Mormons like baptize like people living people now
for like people who weren't able to be baptized for the church. Oh yeah I've heard about that.
Yeah and they got in trouble because they like baptized somebody for Anne
Frank. It's insane. Just baptizing you against your will. I like the idea that Anne Frank was like in
heaven and then they baptized you and you go straight to hell.
What am I doing on this planet?
Where the fuck am I dude?
I'm on fucking mercury.
If you think about it dude, I mean you can sin as much as you want if you just say the
sin is for somebody that's already dead.
I mean.
Yeah that's true.
You know, you stay pure, you drag them down to hell and then when you die you're still
pure you go to heaven, all the people you wronged are in hell so you don't even have
to like see them, they won't be mad at you or anything.
It's true.
go to heaven so bad. Yeah, well that's the thing. It's probably fun as hell up there. The thing about
like you know repenting for your sins, becoming born again, if you go to heaven
and like somebody died before you that you just like fucked over really bad
don't you think they'd be pissed off that you were there? You know? Yeah.
You're like, "Oh, they let this fucker in? That guy owes me like $600!" I think pissed
off is probably not many people in heaven are getting pissed off. Yeah.
Yeah, you're getting that fucking double blowjob.
But what if you see, you get into heaven, you get into heaven you see somebody you just fucking hate.
Just somebody you just like, you can't hang with.
I mean that's not really heaven then is it?
Yeah, true.
I think you're describing just a different thing.
Well, they get into heaven too, cause they fucking, I mean you follow, you follow Christ's word your whole life.
I think you need to read the bible buddy.
Yeah, I think you're doing the thing where people are like, oh you know, dog heaven is cat hell, you know that type of thing.
I mean it's, I think it's.
I'm not doing that.
I'm trying to use science to explain away the love of Christ.
Yeah, something that's more about blessings and grace.
I don't much care for that.
Yeah, I prefer we kind of take it at the Lord's word.
Yeah, like I'm gonna take it at face value because I know that it came from above.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
It came from my favorite book, so.
My favorite book is the Bible.
Don't get me wrong, I love the Bible.
I mean, I don't go in for all that Christianity crap, but the Bible's a great read.
I will say, people do say that like, anytime like Penn Jillette is interviewed and somebody's
like so what's your favorite book he'll be like the Bible the Bible a favorite
book the atheists love to say that they're like it's actually a fascinating
little piece of work these are scumbags just fucking just chill out yeah yeah
just relax man and just not even and also save yourself what are you doing
don't be don't be a fucking idiot free to go to heaven you realize that right
you don't have to pay anything well you do have to like you know you got to pay
the Piper. What Piper? You still haven't read the Bible. There's no Piper in the Bible.
I thought there was a Pied Piper. There's no Pied Piper. Yeah I thought he's one of like the bad
guys in the in the Bible. Literally, here's how you get into heaven. You can do anything you want. You can
fucking murder, you can have sex with your dog, but at the end you just have to be like "I'm sorry"
and you get to go into heaven and it's the easiest thing in the world. Yeah. I don't know why nobody
would do it you know I don't think hell exists yeah okay want to talk about that
why do you not think hell exists what get into this yeah I'm gonna talk about
about the I think I think hell probably exists so why do you say you thought it
did it cuz that's that's like one of those stupid like you know like like guys
say that like like oh Christ died for my sins so hell doesn't exist or whatever
like that's like a right people's I think the Bible doesn't exist I believe in
heaven and hell and God and all that shit books not real never seen I never
seen one my what I open it up and there's always a gun in there I can't
read it some I think some fucking potheads turn this into a stash book
god yeah I need to find a book that I can do that with yeah I need to do that
shit do you should make a stash book out of if you give a mouse a cookie yeah and
you can that'd be so small well I could I could only hide like a little crumbs in
there that you like to carry around over your head that's a very good point I
could keep my crumbs or a tortilla maybe yeah just keep one tortilla I found this
on the side of the road what is it give it to you to make a stash book I think it
it might be a little bit too thin.
Woodworking school.
- You know, I was thinking of making a stash book
out of this, I think this could work pretty well.
- I mean, I have an, oh, that'd be pretty good.
- I think of Altoids, I think, yeah, I think I could maybe,
I mean, I could hollow it out, get rid of these in here.
- I don't think I can give this up, I mean, look at this.
- So my dad always had this tin of Altoids
on his like wardrobe when I was growing up,
like on his drawers, and I would always be like,
"Hey, can I have an Altoid?"
And he'd say, "No."
He'd be like, "No, I never touch those.
"Those are mine, don't touch it."
So I got it in my head, I was like,
he has to be hiding something in there, right?
It makes no sense for him to just like,
not let me have these Altoids.
I've never seen him take one out and eat one in front of me.
Like, there's gotta be something in it.
So one time when he was at work,
I went into his room and I opened it up
and it was just Altoids.
(laughing)
He's just like being a dick about giving me an Altoid.
Which made way more sense.
And then under that he had like a drawer full of money.
(laughing)
Yeah, I got fucking owned.
Just let your boy take a damn mint, you fucker.
Got roasted by your dad.
Dude, Altoids are so strong.
I always forget.
They're great.
I take an Altoid whenever I feel nauseous.
I take an Altoid.
It's like medicine for me.
It is a medicinal.
It's that border between medicine and candy.
- Yeah, I would never take one.
I would just chew, if my breath smells bad
or my mouth tastes weird, I would just chew gum.
- Or you can brush your teeth, dude.
- They gotta bring back the-- - Yeah, that's true.
Yeah, well, I mean, like if I'm on the go.
- You don't bring a Wisp with you?
- A what? - A Colgate Wisp?
- A Colgate Wisp?
- I don't know what that is. - Yeah, you don't
bring the Wisp?
- It's that little toothbrush with a clip in the middle
that tastes like Listerine.
- I've never, I don't know what that is.
- Oh, you remember, Caleb, I still have those,
the Listerine dissolve tablets.
- Those things are awful, bro.
Yeah, those are the worst.
Yeah, the ones that you take like a tab of acid.
Yeah, those are crazy.
No, no, not those.
The ones that when we were staying for the live show, I had them because I was like,
"Well, I'm not going to be able to brush my teeth here."
Oh, those things that you chew and then spit out.
Yeah, you chew, you let it pour into mouthwash.
It just turns into mouthwash.
It's powdered mouthwash, basically.
And then you have to just rinse it.
It's horrible.
It makes no sense.
Oh, yeah.
Those are the worst.
Why not just bring a toothbrush?
I did.
was
And you brought the Listerine mouthwash.
You guys can't fucking question how I operate, alright?
I don't understand it either.
I'm sorry, buddy.
Those Listerine tabs, though, those things will send you to fucking hell.
Oh yeah.
I remember there was a kid in high school who had them and everyone would always ask him
for one, not because they wanted it, but just because, yeah, it hurts.
Yeah, it was funny. Yeah, yeah, yeah, no those things will fucking like like have that and then like eat some ice cream
Yeah, that's a
Chocolate chip ice cream. I mean, yeah, I'm a big bowl of ice eat a banana split
I mean, I never been right tried using one of those not eating like a bunch of needles. I mean, that's yeah
It's not gonna feel good. No, no, not at all. Yeah, I kind of want to invest in like some
I haven't been to the dentist in probably like 10 years.
I kind of want to get some like high-end numbing cream and just like have my mouth beaten up
most of the day.
And just suck a dick.
Yeah, no, I want to get some like Novocaine, some numbing cream and I just want to go to
town on some random guy.
Just go to town on some random guy.
Maybe go to like a glory hole or something.
It's like it doesn't even happen if I can't feel it in my mouth.
Oh man, I would love to, I mean I would love to just get a dental dam too.
(laughing)
- That'd be so awesome.
- Just to teach my dentist a thing or two.
- Yeah.
- Teach him a lesson.
- I just think it'd be funny to walk around
with a numb mouth all day. - I just don't want you
in my mouth, pal.
That would be funny, yeah.
- Yeah, I numb my mouth with Novocaine
and suck someone else's dick,
so it feels like someone's sucking mine.
(laughing)
- Yeah, you know if you suck another person's penis,
it feels like your own penis is getting sucked.
- Yeah.
- Pretty awesome.
Kind of a life hack for you.
- Yeah.
You guys wanna suck my dick?
(laughing)
- Nah, dude, I don't like getting my dick sucked.
I don't like having a wet penis.
I like to, I want it as dry as possible.
- Yeah, I go, I have like a--
- I don't wanna have like swamp dick.
- You know those like fans that they have
at the baseball game with like the squirt thing?
I have one of those and I leave it under my penis.
- Yeah, I have the two-- - And I let it dry out.
- The two dentist tools where you like squirt water
and then you suck it up so it gets extra dry.
- I think I just wanna become a dentist
'cause I want that too.
I want the big light and I want an x-ray machine.
- I want the big chair.
- How much is a full thing of dental equipment?
- How much is a whole dental kit?
- Yeah, I mean, you could just buy,
if money's no object, you could just buy dental equipment
and then just teach yourself on YouTube.
- Okay, so a dentist chair is like $2,000.
- That's not gonna make it.
- That's not bad.
- Actually, no, that's the most expensive one.
There's some cheaper ones here.
They're only like 400. - Oh, sick.
- This one's like 4,000.
How much is the sucker though? I want a sucker system in my entire house so that any room I'm in I can suck and squirt myself.
Dentist sucker for sale.
Let's see.
Dent...uh...heavy duty suction machine, $165.50.
What the fuck are we doing here?
Yeah, and you can just get these on Amazon too.
This is on vitalitymedical.com.
I need to order one as soon as humanly possible.
And it's got a 30 day return policy.
East dental portable mini turbine unit.
You just you order all the fucking dentist tools off this like medical supply site you you give yourself like a dental checkup
And you just return them you have to pay for the dentist anymore. Yeah, you suck all the fucking
Spit come and poop out of your body and then send it back to them. Yeah, here's we
Like we have to change the filter when I searched when I search for dental sucker for sale
I got a notification that google.com wants to know my location
- Do not allow, dude.
- I'm looking at this website here,
Isolite Systems Dental Professionals blog,
and it says, "How Dental Saliva Ejectors
"Put Your Health at Risks."
Whoa.
- They said at risks? - Yo, dude, check this,
hold up, check this one out.
Look at this link.
This is a, this is, this like,
this is a set of dental equipment
that comes in like a suitcase,
like a wheelie suitcase.
Like it's like built in. - Whoa.
- Wait, one second.
There, look at this, it's on eBay for 700 bucks.
- Dude, we'll never have to go to the dentist again.
can bring this wherever you go.
- What the fuck?
- Imagine like bringing this on a plane.
Just like carrying that around the airport.
- No, you don't understand, it's a bomb.
No, I mean, don't you get this crap.
- Listen, this is what it has in it.
Built-in air compressor, saliva ejector,
three-way air water syringe,
high-speed air turbine handpiece tube,
low-speed air turbine handpiece tube,
a foot pedal, clean water bottle,
syringe bottle, and a waste water bottle.
Dude, it's like you don't even need to go to the dentist.
This is making me think.
I wouldn't need to go ever again.
Dude, we should buy this.
This is a pink package and I was thinking that the easiest way to sneak a bomb onto a plane
is put it in something pink.
Because no self-respecting man is going to want to touch that little thing.
I don't think you can talk about that.
I can talk about it.
I'm not going to.
I mean, I'm not going to do it.
Because I don't know what bombs are made out of.
Yeah, let's not talk about that.
What's in bombs?
Is it...
Let's figure this out.
No.
- Are there wires or is there a gun involved?
- There, no.
- Do you put an old gun in there and it shoots the wire?
- It's like a crafting system, it's like--
- It's like Minecraft.
- Yeah.
- So it's redstone and gunpowder.
- Mm-hmm.
(ball bouncing)
- Yeah.
- And a bowling ball.
- Okay, so here's a, what is this?
Some kind of x-ray on Amazon that costs $100,000?
- I'll buy it.
What is this?
Pax I 3D.
Somebody, one of our dentist fans can message us and tell us what a VAT Pax I 3D.
I want the drill.
True.
Oh yeah.
Wouldn't that be cool?
I just fucking walk around with Swiss, fucking Swiss cheese teeth all the time.
Big holes in it.
Yo, wait, check out what you can buy.
This is like, you can buy one of those, you know those things in like a movie when they're
like inspecting radioactive stuff and they have like the gloves in a chamber?
You can buy that on Amazon for $58,000.
Check this thing out.
This is so cool.
58,000 bucks?
Really?
We have to get this.
It has a shield against...
It's pressurized.
Let's see here.
Oh, it's out of stock.
Come on, man.
It's...
Fuck.
Temporarily, though, but free delivery.
Yeah.
So, I mean, when you're spending like, oh, close to 60,000 bucks, I mean, you're not making
me pay for fucking shipping.
Yeah, you might make the money back on the shipping.
Wouldn't it be funny if there was like one review on it, it was like three stars, and
was like it was okay I felt kind of protected I'm looking at I'm looking at
lab equipment on Amazon now you can I didn't realize you could buy this kind of
shit yeah I found I used it what I used to do is I would just type in a random
word on Amazon and then search price high to low they have so much insane
stuff there was one you could buy like biblical scrolls for like $100,000
one point I just want a coke freestyle machine yeah wait a second coke freestyle
I've actually looked into this you have to you have to make a request to coca-cola
And then they have to come install it so you have to be like like I would need to pretend that my apartment was some kind
Of business or restaurant yeah me to get away with it. Yeah, I mean
We could rent office space disguise it like a restaurant. Yeah
Comes we like serve them we we try way too hard we make it like a fancy French restaurant
- Yeah.
- The Coke Freestyle Machine.
(laughing)
- We're all wearing suits.
We're all wearing suits, there's a HMD.
- You can put the Coke Freestyle Machine in my truck.
- Yeah.
- We hire an entire staff.
Yeah, we give them an egg.
And then we're like, thank you for the Coke Freestyle Machine
they still charge you thousands of dollars.
Also they have to keep,
they are the only people who can install the syrup.
- What?
- So they have to come restock it.
So.
- That sucks ass.
It's fucked up, man.
Well, I just searched--
Dude, it sucks so bad that having a Coke Freestyle machine would be way more of a hassle.
I know.
Yeah.
It's almost not even worth it.
I'm on Amazon right now, and I searched "poop" and sorted by highest price just to see what's
up.
It's mostly TV shows, not much interesting stuff.
But here's the thing is that related searches at the bottom, here are the related searches.
Poop emoji.
Butt.
Real poop.
poop from butt. We'll search real poop from butt. Let's see what's going on here. The top
result are socks that say "I'm gaming, do not disturb." Alright, we'll take 'em. Oh,
we got prank poop here, a rubber chicken. This is the highest priced items that we search
for poop from butt? Highest priced item is Bio Bidet Prodigy Advanced Toilet with Auto
open lid dual smart flush, tankless design and luxury bidet features, elongated white.
Nah dude, a bidet is a little bit sussy.
$2,399.
I don't care.
I don't give a shit.
You're going to care when you walk around with that wet butt all day.
No, no, no.
Jeez, look at my wet butt.
I know the bidet, I know the system.
I know what you do.
I've used it before.
You want to squirt emulator?
I do.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm trying to get squirt in my butt.
to
else in my family. That's a little sussy. I don't care dude. I'll fucking, I'll sit on
that thing. You're telling me you let a robot fucking squirt orange juice into your ass?
I'm sitting on there going yo-de-lay-hee-hoo. You are not saying yo-de-lay-hee-hoo. Oh, I'm
singing into the Alps when that thing's... Can you make it, can you fill it with different
liquids? Bidet? No. You can't make it squirt? It's a hassle because you gotta like hook
it up to your sink. At least the one my brother has. Oh. But like, you know what like Diet
coke does to a penny. Yeah. Imagine you could get your asshole that clean. Yeah. Right?
Oh man. Just squirt some diet coke up there. It's like dude. Great. I'm fucking, I'm ready
to go. I'm ready to take on the day. Because I mean an asshole, an asshole and a penny,
not, not too far off. Smell the same. Yeah. Both smell very metal-y. Uh huh. I, I searched,
I just searched machine and sorted Price Hidalgo. Some really good machines on Amazon. If you
guys I mean if you guys want to just what is it a draw money for like a year so
just buy a bunch of machines top machine most expensive machine is the V type
powder mixture mixer pharmaceutical machine powder mixing machine make
powder for tablets if you want that that's $30,000 see what we should do is
we should use the we should we should get these big machines and then we should
live in them yeah now okay now here's there's another machine that's called
njp 400 auto machine for joined capsules need machine price with shipping fee
please contact me and then has a phone number in the name of the item. How much
is that one? Let's see how much this is. This is $24,999.
$24,999. So $24,999. That's easy, dude. We could do that. We can make that work.
Filling material without viscous wet powder, small grains. Okay. So these are all
for filling pills or something? Those two were. Here's the next one that's really
getting me is the odor dock portable odor machine for $17,000 what odor I think
honey is it any odor look at this machine it looks like the it looks again
like a suitcase but it's green and it has a tube on the top that shoots out an
odor check out what this thing looks like this is a super villains thing yeah
what's the fuck is this is $7,000 a portable odor machine odor I need didn't
And
like it's like a freestyle yeah it's like a freestyle machine for it for odors you
can like mix and match odors I was so confident that that like was the thing
at amusement parks like the eat that makes like the ET ride smell like that
or something oh yeah no although we should invest in one of those for the
next live show here's one that looks exactly like a copy right yeah no we
We should put out the ET smell.
Yeah.
Oh, dude, it smells so good.
I love the ET ride.
I think we should get this and bring this to the next live show and let everyone use it.
This is another machine that looks exactly like a copy machine, and it's called the California
Microneedle Diode Laser Hair Remover Pernanent Hair Reduce Beauty Machine.
I don't need a hair reduction, dude.
For only $15,000.
And imagine if we could sell tickets to a live show and say every ticket comes with free
laser hair removal.
That's pretty good.
Yeah, and the tickets are a thousand dollars each.
We might actually make a profit.
People might want that.
Do it yourself laser hair removal.
And we could learn how to do it too.
We could also just use the laser for something more nefarious.
Oh wait, check this out.
Check this out.
Oh fuck, we could totally buy this.
If we pool our money together.
What is it?
Hold on, let me do the math here.
Type again.
10 plus 10 plus 10 plus 10.
10 plus 10 plus 10.
Okay, okay, okay.
Shut up, shut up, shut up.
30 dollars, we can afford it.
Okay, would you guys be willing to shell out 466 dollars and 66 cents?
For what?
For, you gotta tell me what it is, dude.
- Pick a portable, full digital laptop, ultrasound machine.
- I do not have a baby, so for that reason I'm out.
- Not yet.
Not yet, but now you can check whenever
and we can share this.
- Okay, but here's an ultrasound 4D machine for $25,000.
- 4D?
You can like, does it like shoot?
- Four dimensional.
- It shoots cold air at your feet
in the middle of the ultrasound?
- Yo, yo, wait, wait.
- So do you guys want to,
would you guys be willing to go in for $8,333
instead for the four dimensional one?
- Way less money, way less money,
probably a lot more fun, probably a better investment altogether.
Aquasonic ultrasound gel, 5 liters, 26 bucks.
I want to talk about the 4D ultrasound machine.
Like they show you a picture of the baby and it like, you know, it makes, it squirts red
juice in your face.
Yeah, the baby sneezes, there's a big comical sneeze, you get hit with it, you know?
Or you hear bats and you get killed on the back of your neck.
It's also 3D, so if the baby reaches, it goes towards your face.
Yeah, that might be the most incredible invention of all time.
The coolest ultrasound machine.
All right, wait, hold here.
So, Mr. and Mrs. Johnson, I'm going to need you to put on these sunglasses.
Yeah.
And make sure to stay in the seats the entirety of the ultrasound.
Yeah, the person, the receptionist, asking if you want to spend an extra $1,000 to see
your baby's ultrasound in 4D.
Are either of you or do either of you have any allergies, heart conditions, or are you pregnant?
Well, I guess you are pregnant. Okay, can't be a part of this ride.
Yeah, they put amps under your seat so when the baby like, like it goes like,
oh, it like shakes your seat.
Yeah, it's just, I really thank you for the 4D experience. It's amazing.
I really feel like our baby's in the room.
Yeah, it's so crazy. You can just buy medical supplies on here. You can buy
Frequently bought together ultrasound gel germicidal cleaner wipes, okay
Dealing with like some sort of cartel that yeah shift them all their medical supply
Companies I thought that they bought it like direct from a company. What about
528 diodes cold lipo laser professional lipo laser machine lipo laser 4d for super lose weight skin tightening body shape weight loss slimming
Reduce fat don't tell me we got another 4d machine on our hand
- All you had to-- - 4D, 4D lipo,
so it takes years off your life too.
- Oh my god, that's amazing.
- It reduces the time of your body.
- All you had to tell me that there was diodes in that.
I mean, I heard diode, I was immediately--
- I go stupid for diodes.
- 528 diodes.
- 528, that's the most amount of diodes
I've ever seen in my life.
- Dude, we might have to go stand in like
a Supreme style drop line to wait for one of these machines.
- Oh my god.
- We're waiting for the 4D diode machine actually.
- Yeah. - We camped out.
- How about muscle sculpt high intensity focused
Electromagnetic muscle EMS sculpting slimming machine weight loss skin tightening cellulite reduction
Remember muscle training a little eating line for an iPhone. Yeah, that was sick, dude
I feel like people still do that. Do they not I'm just think I miss drops like that
I never sat in any lines or anything like that
But I miss just seeing all like the I sat in a line for
Transformers 3 and I was like I'd hate lines and I have not done it since yeah
It's so funny
The last time I sat in a line was to see a bunch of baby animals at a farm
And then I pretended to shoot them with my finger, and I made my girlfriend angry
The girlfriend you gotta be worried about these animals now
They might have taken that as an actionable threat. They were a little you they were asleep
Oh, they were pretending to be asleep, dude
They're always vigilant one of them had a bad dream and was kicking around and I was like look at that
Stupid could have been a good dream could have been a karate dream. Yeah, maybe I wanted to die
I don't think a pig could have a good dream. I feel like in the world a pig is living
And I think pretty much anything that could happen to its bad. Do you have it pretty bad cuz they have a human brain?
They're like a pig
They're like a dog really it's like smarter than way smarter than dog. They're like really yeah
They're like as smart as like a five-year-old human
Amazon fuck what is it? You guys both need to just click on this link for me. Okay, this new one
I just sent you're really gonna like this penis stimulation stroker blowjob sex machine adult male master
Bader's cup automatic 30 frequency vibration modes for men rechargeable men oral six toys for men's sexy underwear for men
Why is it 11,000 bucks?
My god the pictures of a big shop like galaxies
I mean like tornadoes.
Sexy girl voice! It has sexy girl voice!
There's no way.
This isn't better than actually having sex.
There's a galaxy in it.
Look at the last picture.
It's sexy girl voice can make a sound.
Wow.
In your reviews, somebody has to have been buying this.
Look at the brand name here.
Shumanfungsi.
Here's the legal disclaimer for this.
"Statements regarding dietary supplements have not been evaluated by the FDA or are not intended to diagnose, treat, cure, or prevent any disease or health condition."
"This body safe silicone and whisper quiet made from medical grade silicone,
non-toxic, odorless, and skin friendly, smooth to touch and feel, giving you a skin like feeling as it imitates the real skin of human body,
and the noise is less than 50 decibels, almost negligible. You can enjoy its thrills at home or office without any worries."
*laughter*
The office, pulling that thing out at the office?
Is that the copy machine?
Yeah, but you could also pretend this is an office tool because it looks so discreet.
Yeah, this is my paper moaner. It moans when it touches my papers.
Fuck, dude. I mean, seriously, this thing has to be way better than pussy, right?
They have to have invented the perfect thing for penis to go into.
Look at the seller here.
What else are they selling?
They have the automatic blowjob sex toy for male masturbation with powerful vibrating modes.
modes adult men's penis massage sucking oral sex cup underwear he was a guy
sweater realistic tight masturbating stimulation masturbator for men's
pleasure Japan fully auto vacuum pocket cup read fleshlight toy flesh light sex
for men toy cup sleeve wait dude they have one that looks like a bottle of
beer and it has what the fuck in there also I should say every almost every
word and these in these names has like an accent over it to like avoid detection by
Amazon yeah. Make stroker hands-free waterproof electric penis massager and
then a bunch of fans and this one looks like c-3po. Exquisite workmanship
electric blowjob USB charging multiple modes sucking massage cup vibrating
aircraft cup man toy hands-free underwear for man masturbators cup and
And it's shaped like a toy car.
Psycho electric vibrating masturbator cup, silicone masturabator, detachable sleeve stroker men's adult toys,
masturbator massage cup toys for male, intelligent penis stroker underwear machine for men.
Dude, please scroll to the bottom of the first page.
Baby playpen, extra large play yard, kids activity center with anti-slip base, sturdy safety play yard.
No!
Alright, this is an evil company.
What the fuck dude?
USB charging automatic piston cup rechargeable men oral six toys for men sexy underwear vibrating sucking for men sexy underwear for vibrating and modes
I'm looking for vibrating underwear for a sexy man
Psycho blowjob sex toy adult male hands free master baiter cup electric stroker oral sex machine pinching sucking for men throat sucking oral cup underwear six toys for male aircraft cup black t-shirt
Wait, I gotta go to this last page.
Yeah.
I gotta see what there is on this final page.
Here's the final item.
The brand is called "Psycho" spelled C-Y-A-S-Q-O.
Is this it?
More baby play pens.
This is on the same page.
D-P-M-S, full auto, S-B-R, C-O-2 powered, BB air rifle with dual action.
Full auto, dude.
Dude I'm getting the Psycho Master Baiter, the baby play pen, and the rifle.
Those are the three things you need from Amazon.
- Snapdragon Singapore style laksa curry.
All right, this might just be like
the greatest brand of all time.
They have so much--
- This one looks like a toy car.
- Oh yeah, I was just looking at that one.
- There's one that also looks like a future car,
which is even cooler and it's $100.
- This one looks like a podcast, Mike.
- Yeah, they all, this one--
- Simulation please, toys for men, male masturbators,
electric blowjob men, deep throat sucking,
pocket pussy for men provide real experience, sexy underwear t-shirt.
Whatever happened in just your damn hand?
Yeah.
Right?
Your damn right hand or maybe a really...
What if this thing explodes on your thing?
Maybe a blanket and some rubber bands.
This one looks like a bluetooth speaker.
It has like volume knob on it or like volume buttons.
Yeah dude, so you can blast the weekend while you fuck the car.
Yeah you can play I Hear the Secrets that you Keep, that song.
Nah, dude, you playing fucking, fucking Wicked games super, super loud.
Oh, yeah.
As you're going to town on this fucking vibrating six toy.
Fuck.
Fuck, man.
I want to see-
Angelica Wig.
No.
That's a toast to London name.
Yeah, it is a toast to London name.
This is crazy.
Every page they have like a new insane way that one of these can look
that I didn't think would be possible.
They have a lot of beer shaped ones.
I have to say.
Yeah, well, because that's like every man, that's like the male fantasy, right?
That's like a...
Yeah, you can fuck a bottle of beer.
Dude, I've always wanted to fuck beer so bad, dude.
Not the opening either, from the bottom of it.
From the back.
I'm trying to hit this stuff from the back, dude.
That's just what it is, man.
I can't control it.
I mean, who wouldn't want to fucking be six deep in a bottle of beer?
Yeah.
Fuck.
- Is that an official like?
- No, the beer says--
- Is that a real beer company?
- No, it says premium quality and then under that
it says realistic product.
- Yeah, this is the most realistic beer.
This one has like a picture of like an insanely
veiny thing going into it.
Ugh, this is fucked up.
That is like a mutant thingy in the side of the crop.
You can't put that on Amazon.
- What is up with people having so many veins
in their penises?
got a penis pump for men enlargement here.
Ooh, they got several of them.
I think I probably have one vein in my penis and it's probably like the size of a pencil
lead.
Yeah, mine looks like a vein.
Yeah, I think my penis is a vein.
How do these guys have multiple veins on their penises?
It's fucking incredible.
Also, how do you get a vascular penis?
Are you just like, do you have to like curl with it?
Just you know, do push-ups.
This picture- I don't think that works.
This picture of one has a, it looks, the hole looks like a mouth and it has black slime dripping
out of the mouth.
Do you guys know anybody who's ever had like a fleshlight or something like that?
Not to my knowledge.
That they've admitted to?
No.
I just don't get it man.
Like just, I mean you could fuck like, like there's so many fruits that I've fucked before
I've fucked a thing that was plastic.
You know, there was a kid that my brother,
like one of my younger brother's friends,
who told me he made a fleshlight
out of two sponges and a rubber glove.
- Well, that's different, 'cause yeah, like kids--
- But these are like expensive, though.
That's the--
- Every kid who made a waterfall bong in high school
also made a fleshlight.
- The thing is, like, people will buy a fleshlight,
but then also be like, oh, I don't wanna use
a gas station charger on my phone, it could mess it up.
know what I mean? Like, I don't think you should be putting any machine...
Well, how much is an original fleshlight?
Probably like ten thousand dollars for something that incredible.
Original, like one of the old, like an old mahogany fleshlight.
It still has a, it's like a dusty bust in it.
That's what you want? Some, some fucking...
It's seventy dollars.
That's more expensive than I would have thought.
That is less expensive than psycho lifelike masturbation, stroke or electric blowjob,
men deep throat oral vibrate masturbate or cup masturbators cup man also let's
top it I will say they nailed one thing that is the best about having sex with a
woman which is the vibration yeah they just nailed difference the different
settings it's always been my problem with a fleshlight is that it doesn't
vibrate like a real woman and I can't play music from her either yeah yeah so I
I guess it is better.
Yeah, I wish she looked like a blue yeti.
That's my only thing.
Oh, fuck, only dude.
Um...
I'm just still scrolling through these.
There's so many.
I'm just looking at them all.
I'm gonna buy all of them.
This one looks like Boba Fett's mask.
[laughs]
It's for the nerds in the audience, dude.
Yeah.
Uh, I've just been thinking, like, we talked last night about Marina Abramovich.
Oh yeah.
We talked about her.
Yeah, with Sridhar.
Shout out to Sridhar.
Yeah, and I was just, I remembered this thing that my grandpa said, which I already told
Patrick but it's just been making me laugh every time I think about it.
Cam, you know who that is, right?
Marina Abramovic.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
She did spirit cooking.
Yeah, so like, so she did that, when she was doing that like the artist is present thing,
it was like on Fox News and I was like watching it with my grandpa when I was a kid and they
say like yeah artist Marina Abramovich you know this whole thing where you can do
whatever you want in the room with her and she just like can't move or whatever
and my grandpa goes huh world's oldest profession a just completely like just a
genius misread of that situation he's like he was just like yeah dude you
fucking pay so fucking funny we should do we should do an exhibit like that our
Our next live show should be--
We should just have an art exhibit in general, I think.
Yes, dude, we need to be--
We would do a really good art exhibit.
Yeah, I mean, we'd be, I mean, we have to be
some of the, secretly, some of the best artists
in the world, right?
No, no secret for me.
Everybody knows how good my art is.
Here's what I would do.
I make beautiful art in my mind.
We would need to make, I'm into making statements,
you know, 'cause I'm a very political and smart person.
So I would need to do something insane,
like an upside-down American flag,
or maybe like a, maybe like a Cheeto bag.
here and it says it says fat fat so here's a here's an idea or it's like an
American flag yeah instead of stars it's all upside down crosses that's been done
now that's been done okay what about this done what about out what about I put
it right side up cross whoa fuck well we need to like what about it what about
what about a bald eagle with a girl what about it's a plus sign you walk it you
look at it from a different angle it's a multiplication sign oh it's kind of a
commentary on mathematics yeah well that's the other thing is that a lot of
these artists they make the mistake of making commentary about like gender or
race or politics how about make commentary about like video games or
something yeah what about it's like like it's a french fry but you look at it
from the other side it's a potato makes you realize they were just a sign like a
neon sign that says French fries should be free what that's a statement is
everybody's gonna be everybody's gonna see I'd be like yeah they should be free
yeah or what about this like you it's a Banksy style like vandalism horrible
horrible horrible thing he does vandalism yeah you you make neon signs
you learn how to build neon signs,
and you go up to restaurants, maybe like McDonald's,
or maybe like Burger King, something like that,
and you put that sign that says,
"Free French fries" in the window.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- And then you fuck up. - And then you fuck up.
- You fuck up McDonald's, 'cause they don't know how to say no.
- You fuck up some cashier's day.
- Yeah, that'd be awesome. - Yeah.
You stick it to who really fucking runs the show,
these cashiers. - We could do,
we could make a lot of different statements about fast food.
- Okay, wait, here's another Banksy one, right?
Okay. So this would be like, you know, we would, we would be doing like our kind of
like Banksy imitation thing. Everybody would walk up to this piece would think
it's Banksy at first. Okay. Cause they'd see, they go up, it's a $100 bill. Yeah.
But instead of, um, you know, Mr. President in the middle, it's Ronald McDonald. Okay.
And everyone looks at that and think, oh, this is Banksy. But then you look closer,
there's a speech bubble. It says, you shouldn't have to pay this much money for fries.
That is so genius.
Wait, how about this, okay.
So, you know, there's been like exhibits
where somebody will like stack a million dollars, right?
A million dollars in a room
so that people can see what a million dollars is like.
So I was thinking about, what if you walk in
and there's a million dollars stacked up in a square, right?
And there's a tiny sign, like really, really small print,
like on a business card in front of it.
And it says, almost feels like this is
how much fries cost these days.
(laughing)
- What do you think?
- What about, okay.
- Yeah, that's pretty good.
- I got an idea.
So it's like a, so this is like a piece
that you do in some kind of store.
- Oh, yeah, these are all pieces, by the way.
- Yeah.
- They're nuts, yeah.
- This is a piece that you put in,
maybe you rent out a bodega for a day, right?
And you put all these Lay's bags,
like bags of Lay's chips,
and then when somebody opens the bag,
there's two potatoes in it,
and there's a note that says, "Make it yourself."
- Wow. - Wow.
- Uh-huh.
- What about one of those piracy ads,
but it says, "You would eat a free fry."
(laughing)
- This one's kind of a thinker, okay?
It's one of those things where it's like a commentary--
- I mean, these are all thinkers, let's be clear.
- Of course, yeah, this one's a thinker, thinker, okay?
It's like one of those things where it's commentary
on like, "Make America Great Again," okay?
And then it's, and they show, it's like,
so it says, "Make America Great Again,"
and it shows an old picture of the dollar menu,
where fries only cost $1.
- Yes. - Okay.
But then, but then, there's a thing under it,
or you walk into the next room,
and there's a part two of the painting,
or the piece, I mean, sorry.
- Yeah, come on.
- Say, you have to say piece.
- Yeah, the piece, the work, I should say, actually.
- The body of work.
- The body, yeah, well, it's all a body of work,
but, and it says, "But was it ever really great?"
They show the receipt of the $1 fries, 109 tax.
- Whoa. - Oh my God, dude.
- Holy shit.
What about Lady Gaga in a french fry dress?
*laughter*
And she wears it to the free Grammys.
For free stuff.
Right?
Yeah, okay. That could be good.
She says, yeah it's about free french fries.
Okay, what about this? So it's like an American flag.
It's got a picture of french fries and at the bottom it says,
"Freedom fries, yeah I wish they were free."
Oh shit.
aren't free. Yeah, free. That's perfect dude. Yeah. And how about a picture of a bunch
of french fries and it says bring our boys home. But we don't, we're talking
about fries and they should be free. Because this is how it used to work. You
should be able to buy a hamburger, alright? And listen, I'm not a maniac. You
should have to pay for a hamburger. Yeah. But you should get fries for free because
that's how it used to be you could pay for a sody pop tell you what you should
cost 49 cents so and there's only one size extra extra extra large till
Bloomberg came in and turned everything in Bloomberg in this fucking Morgan
Spurlock yeah it's more exactly it's Morgan Spurlock yeah we could do a piece
where it's Morgan Spurlock with a Hitler mustache and the mustache is made of
fries that we should do the Kathy Griffin thing that she did with Trump's
head with Morgan Spurlock uh-huh and have a decapitated thing and yeah and it
says this guy ruined fries this guy ruined fries yeah you should be able to
get a what was it called a super-sized fry mm-hmm yeah we could do like kind of
like a we could do a whole exhibit that's kind of just like smear attacks
on Morgan Spurlock we could have the cover we could have the poster for
super-sized me but it's his but it's his um it's his his face and it says
circumcised me and there's a pair of scissors and then also we could end up
you know this is gonna be big I think this exhibit so we end up doing a tour
for it right but we get into the UK stuff's different around there all the
sudden Chris make it make chips free chips yeah and over there they call over
there they call him Morgan Sherlock - yeah exactly so we'd have to change up a
lot of stuff. And they call circumcising "circle sizing." Yeah. Yeah, there's an extra "u"
in there. Yeah. In circumcision. Yeah. I know we moved on from this, but when I was clicking
through this Amazon store, I got to the section that starts to be "sex toys for women," and
I just want to read like... I'm gonna... No, I want to read three of these in a row because
they gradually forget how to spell the word "vibrator." How do they spell it? It starts
off G spot vibrator couple sex toy couples toys for adults G spot
vibrator clitoral vibrator partner toys for vaginal toy female clitorial
sucking stimulator. Okay, okay, then the next one thrusting rabbit toy for
women pleasure. G spot rabbit vibrator for women powerful thrusting toys for
women realistic anal for rabbit vibe raptors for vibrator triple vibe
brartoring. And then this one is rabbit, rabbit vibrobrater for
women, g-spot vibrobrater for women, vibroretratoring for
women, frequency vibrator women toys, clitoral clitoris
vibrator women spot.
Star Wars vibroblade.
True.
Yeah, dude. Yeah.
I've got okay.
Rose flower clot sucker toy for women.
I've hold on. I got another fry piece.
we can do. Yeah, okay, back to the fries, sorry. So it's a picture, alright, so it's a picture
of Darth Vader, Darth Vader's helmet. Yeah. And it says, "May the fries be free for you."
Oh, and then you can have a bunch of different pictures of Darth Vader, and it would be fries
of Vader, he got some free fries. Yeah. Emotions of Fry-Vader. Okay, wait, wait, then it's
like a picture of a hoth and the picture of the wampa and it says the Empire
fries back free and get this the lightsabers are fries uh-huh
okay fry saber yeah and oh and we could do one where we put a french fry in a
bunch of piss yeah that could be good piss fry yeah we could have we could do
like an Andy Warhol style thing where you know it's a bunch of pictures of
Campbell's soup but the soup says free fries on it. True and we could do a
Jackson Pollock thing where we throw a bunch of fries at something. Yeah and but it cut
the cut the price of that painting the piece zero dollars zero dollars aka
free for those of you who. Free yeah fries should be free we know that they
or easy to make.
Anything that is easy to make should be free.
- Maybe like a t-shirt, maybe like,
I remember when Lil Wayne went to jail, free fries.
And it's a picture of Lil Wayne eating french fries.
- Free fries 'til it's backwards.
- Uh-huh.
- Yeah, 'til it's fries free.
- Yep.
- I think that we need to,
I think this is getting bigger than art.
I think we're stepping into the world of politics again.
- Yeah, well I think--
- I think I might need to run for New York City Mayor.
- Yeah.
Free is a political statement in itself I think. Yeah we could have like we could
also I mean if we're gonna go political we could take out we could we could draw
a cartoon for the New Yorker okay. Where it's two old men on a bench.
They they look like fucking shit horrible art I mean the artist didn't even bother
to finish drawing. They don't even try. Gaps everywhere in the lines no detail no
color just absolutely appalling you know this artist should be fired and mulched
immediately. It's like shit. Just utter shit. The thing is it's not even, it's not the magazine's
fault either. It's definitely, it's the artist. You know, I don't think they should be receiving
any compensation for this type of thing. How many bad artists in a row can these fuckers at
the New Yorker hire? It's disgusting. It's really disgusting. Anyway, the caption says,
"I heard fries are free now." Wow. Because you know, they like that. Wait, wait, wait. They
like dry type of humor. No, no, no. It has to be even drier. One guy says, "I hear fries are free
now the other guy says no they're not and that's kind of a statement okay there's
not any free what okay it's two guys you know they might as well be stick figures
look like they look like a one-year-old drew them after getting his hands
mangled it's just like what the fuck is this New Yorker shit about dude this is yeah I mean it's like
it's appalling. I want to see pointillism. I want to see like a very realistic picture of a person.
What happened to the Mona Lisa?
It's like if you... yeah.
It's like a blind man holding a pencil with his foot.
Is like what this looks like.
And it's one guy holding a lot of fries.
A lot of fries.
And it says "Guess the price."
And it says...
Okay, that's good.
It's a caption contest.
And here are the three best captions they've selected.
Number one, "Guess the price."
Number two, "I guess that explains those free fries signs I saw."
Pretty good, right?
- Uh-huh. - Yeah.
- Caption number three,
"And I don't even have any money."
- Wow.
- All right, so what about-- - That's a big,
'cause we need to convince McDonald's,
like, you guys don't realize,
do you know how many more fries you'd be selling
if they were completely free?
- That's true, that's a really good point.
- You guys would be selling millions of fries.
- Lines out of the doors.
- People would be lining up day and night
for these fries. - I mean, remember how much
fun your cashiers had with the Rick and Morty sauce?
We could be doubling this every single day.
- Exactly. - So you know,
You know, you're familiar with the price is right.
So what if it's the price is right, Loger,
and it says the price is fries
and there's a big zero next to it.
Yeah. Wow, the fries are free.
Yeah. Yeah.
That's good.
How about, instead of Jeopardy, it's fries are free.
And they go, yep, I'll take fries for $0, Alex.
I guess not Alex anymore.
He fucked up.
What are $0, Alex?
says fries for zero dollars yeah they have luckily they record before he you know
wasted away and shriveled up or whatever they saw which way the winds were blowing
and they actually record a bunch of recorded episodes yeah where he burst
into flame where they have all the they have like Arthur Chu on there and all
the other classic guy they got the IBM Watson well no they just they recorded
Alex just saying like that's correct or no I'm sorry correct free their answer
was what is fries and then they just play those you know every episode is you know
that's the thing that guy what don't try to look for a new host man just make a
fucking soundboard yeah yeah just make a voice synthesize him yeah Watson on bring
him back if they get if they can have a website that anyone can use where you
can make spongebob say stuff you can make Alex Trebek say stuff with your
jeopardy money yeah and then he could also be we could make him you know curse
and say funny to make him say funny stuff yeah or like make it make it public
you know whatever tool they create to mummify him just you know to reanimate
him just just make it public around I ever saw was there's a new metal band
whose singers died and they did like a reunion and they played like old vocals
of his over a speaker that was on an animatronic skeleton oh yeah yes that
again it's so fucking cool I hope when I die you guys do that with me yeah and
get get this is named the singer of static X was named Wayne static yeah
Fuck cool
And he died and turned to a skeleton, you know how he died
He put his finger in an outlet
No, that's not true. Wow. No, he was an addict drugs
With a guy named static I made that joke you should work it
No, you should look at what his hair looks like though, cuz you know that he does look like you got electrocuted. He absolutely did
That was his style
Let's see. It's not no static isn't Rob zombies brother. That's power me. No power man 5,000 is Rob zombies brother
Yeah, I mean this guy looks like he did a spell looks like Wayne static, right and it blew up in his face
All right, I have to go peepee. All right, you're welcome for the art. Yeah, bye. Bye
Bye.