you're listening to Israel's number one podcast
this is premium content
if you are not a premium subscriber
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately
*laughter*
we're on our scooby shit tonight
yeah
scooby shit no cooby shit
mhm
no cooby shit again
yeah
Caleb is not here
still being punished
Caleb is still punished
yeah
We need everybody to sign our petition.
- I forget where I found that video.
- It's a really funny--
- Or that picture.
- It's so funny, just people holding up signs that say,
"Please shorten Caleb's punishment."
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Yeah, I'm really curious.
I wonder, 'cause I feel like if it was about something serious
they wouldn't say, like, "Shorten his punishment."
They would say, like, "Get him out of jail."
- Yeah.
- Or like, "Shorter sentence."
- I think it was something like,
oh, it was like, oh, my brother got grounded,
my grandparents are standing outside
protesting his punishment.
(laughing)
- Dude, what awful grandparents.
Can you imagine if your grandparents protested
to your parents when you got grounded?
- Right, every time.
- Yeah, they cut off contact.
if i tried to punish my son in my parents stood outside my house with signs
i would not talk to my fucking parents ever again yeah i would vote for
tried to
i'd vote for death panels
yeah
yeah i just saw a video i'm looking at uh...
looking at the youtube home page right now
and recommended for me is a video called uh...
the who's pete townsend
answers his most googled questions
and uh...
buddy i think the most googled question about him
his generally who
yeah who would know the uh...
the thing about his how they found child porn on his computer in two thousand one
well they did and in a year
he said he was researching it for a documentary
yeah
yeah i need to reset something
andy terry
it the exact words were that he looked up
russian orphan child in a billion results came up
yet he did
he's doing a reenactment and he's again all the details right
shop for shot
yeah i'm doing a remake doing a reboot of
of russian orphan porn
and uh...
yeah i need to make sure everything is just so
because people can tell if i'm using a
uh... a slavic child not a russian one
i need to take note of the facial structure
and
uh... the rest of it
uh...
i was just watching uh... have you ever seen the
the music video for the Limp Bizkit song "Eat You Alive"
it's maybe one of like the funniest music videos it's ever been made it's a
the song is is um...
boy
i don't know why i'm fucking yawning i slept until one o'clock today should
drink some energy dude
yeah i i just didn't leave the house all day yeah i didn't either actually i did
i left the house to get a sandwich but
sandwich place was closed so i got chinese food instead
oh that's good
i got uh... we had
shit hold up let me
let me sit up so I'm not laying down and all he can hear is me breathing again.
This is good, alright.
Everybody, I'm really sorry for all the thumps and bumps of Patrick's ass you just heard.
It's not that bad.
Patrick's ass be bumpin'.
My ass not be bumpin'.
Pat's butt be bumpin'.
My ass does not be bumpin'.
Pat has a bumpin' butt.
Ah, that is not true.
That's completely true.
Um.
False.
Yeah, I just took like a long nap before this, so now I'm drinking a Red Bull.
Yeah I wish I'd had something.
Well we had $20 in Grubhub credit because they fucked up an order.
Oh nice.
For Black Friday.
So I got, yeah, yeah, for Black Friday baby, we got a, yeah we just paid for the order
that we got today for lunch.
We didn't pay, like, we paid $3 for the delivery.
Nice.
So that was good.
What'd you get?
and I did not tip them.
- Yeah, I tipped them on the $3.
I gave them six cents.
Or no, 60 cents.
- I think they made enough today.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- On Black Friday.
- Yeah, come on.
- Right, you're already making way too much.
- Yeah, an Uber Eats driver should be making
maximum $10 a day.
After that, they just get greedy.
They try to take on too many orders
And it's like you're wearing yourself out.
Go home and go to sleep.
You should be doing one ride a day.
Yeah, you shouldn't do any rides at all.
Yeah, because you're making too much money.
Yeah.
You're taking away all the money from me.
I write articles for Vice.
And everybody knows that if one person makes money, the other person can't make money.
That's true.
And this situation just happens to be Uber Eats and Vice.
They're linked somehow.
I don't know.
They have the same, they both use Employee Co.
Yeah, well I stopped doing that with the microphone.
I'm trying to figure out the most comfortable position.
I can hear it getting louder and quieter when you do that.
Is this the perfect volume right here?
This is fine, yeah.
I mean, it depends, I guess it's really on your end that it matters, I suppose.
Yeah, that's true.
I don't know, I can't wait until we're done with the fucking internet recording.
Yeah, dude, it fucking blows.
this
a
Absolutely.
That's a good idea.
That's what we should do and it wouldn't backfire at all.
It would not backfire and no one would complain about...
And they would all be good quality.
Yeah, no one would complain about like the audio quality, no one would complain about
episode quality.
I don't know that anyone's ever complained about any of those things just because we
don't have...
Yeah, I don't think anyone has but like I don't know...
I know it's not good.
Yeah, oh I know it's not good.
Yeah.
I know that like the past like whole like the whole time I've been recording from this microphone
I know that my audio has sounded like shit and I'm taking this time to apologize to the
fans.
Yeah and I'm taking this time to uh revert Pat's apology and say fuck you instead.
Don't oh my don't revert my apology.
I just reversed it I flipped it on its head and now instead of I'm sorry you're saying
sorry I'm and that doesn't even make any sense.
Oh my god.
Okay but back to the eat you alive music video.
oh yeah uh...
this song is about
fred durst being super horny
and he's like
girl you're so beautiful let me sniff on them panties please and he says stuff
like that
and the chorus is him screaming
i'd eat you alive over and over again and the music video is the band is
playing in the woods
and they have
thora birch uh... tied to a chair
and they're they're playing to her and during the chorus fred durst just takes
out a megaphone
and screams directly into her face
like how hot she is and it's like the funniest thing ever is the image of
how old was she then
uh... i don't know what's the video it said the video is uploaded in two
thousand nine but i think it's for the song is from two thousand three i'm
pretty sure
okay so somewhere in between those two
those two times she was born in ninety two
okay
just like such a such a funny concept they're like what if we yelled directly
into a woman's face
yeah he's already screaming like he's doing is his his certified fred durst
growl
uh... reduce the certified classic exactly okay all right yet she looks
as you said limp it for a burgeon a limp biscuit music video and i just
assumed like
she was way too young to be in it
now that uh... i wouldn't watch the video for the if that were the case
yeah i don't want anything with young girls in it
only young boys fishes camera
well you know it's a uh... nothing suspicious about that i only want good
boys
the movie good boys and i laugh my freaking ass off i say this is like the
lego movie boat
but it's what the real boys in this way
this is like a little bit of a good causes in it
this is like the adult like a movie for adults
that'd be cool this is like a twenty one jump street
was for a babies
but it was for adults
twenty one jump street for kids now that's a damn movie yeah we call it
nine jump street
because that's the age you have to be to watch the movie
damn they made it she was in a dungeons and dragons movie yeah
they made a dungeons and dragons movie in two thousand yeah you didn't know about that
no
dude how do you not know about that
no i haven't seen it i've seen it multiple dungeons yeah me and caleb
watched one of the
the sequels we watched um... wrath of the dragon god and it was so fucking funny
i have it on dvd if you want to watch it when we get back to boston
yeah oh god damn dude
dungeons and dragons the movie
was it made it was a thirty five million budget
and it made 33.8 million they were like almost
damn
yeah dude
they almost cleared it dude
almost
by like
two million marlin wayans was in it
really he played a guy named snails
jeremy irons
wow damn
this is uh...
yeah i want to watch the original it looks like it shouldn't have failed
hit one with one worst picture at the stinkers bad movie or it's swept the
unknown it was nominated
well it sounds like it was leading to our bad movies
sounds like uh...
was the other one the golden raspberries yeah
so they're going to have a bad movie there's the golden turkey
there's the uh... the but that's a no that's a
there's the pattern to have a record or book
is the patrick award
that they were not a war in the movie with the of the latest
that is not in a war
come on
that's fucked up uh... yeah we should watch dungeon and dragons
that's a good idea
if we ever do watch alongs that's the type of movie i want to watch along for
i feel like
uh... you yet
you can do that on twitch rate we could do
yet it was a little less discuss content
yeah on this episode okay let's make hats and then i'll be in let's make hats
that have a t_v_ and set into the
the hat like a telltale the stomach
now do and people can wear 'em and will play a video on them
i'm i'm pushing forward the merchandise industry unlike on your west combined
with
uh... old checklists michael checklists
combined with
michael sarah combined with michael check this again
yeah yeah
uh...
yeah what you do for thanksgiving you a fun thanksgiving
yeah i just kinda hung out with uh... we got uh...
my nephew to do the high hopes dance that was funny that's good
well no not really we just put it on he really like the song
so he just danced
he did his own thing that's an endorsement right there and uh... buddy i had to tell him
some things
i had to tell my three-year-old nephew some things about uh...
who he was endorsing there
yet don't do you think
are you aware of this man's sexual orientation
it
how old is he?
he's three he like just turned three
yeah, stopping a three-year-old and being like
you should not be dancing to this song
yeah this is the favorite song of a famous gay man
and that's why none of like the none of the actual bad things about pete buta
judge what bad things
i don't know i did a little bit of a
a trick on you there
yeah you've done a trick flipping it around you know it's super funny
seeing like
actual pete buta judge supporters because they look exactly like
you'd fucking think they would yeah it's great
it's it's crazy i don't understand uh...
like it's all like but they all look like theater people
they all look like
i feel like that sounded homophobic
no it didn't until you said it was homophobic
it's like straight theater guys and then like... yeah we all know what you mean
by by
quote straight theater guys
straight theater guys means bi guys
straight theater guys means by guys
yeah
i think it's weird about this already but i had a couple come in both wearing
buddha judge like one of them is in a buddha judge shirt in the other one is
in the hat
and uh... they just
ticket got like a
like a fifty dollar order something i think i might have been eighty
i just know they didn't tip they bought a lot of food and then just did not tip
that's awesome
that's a shit
yeah and when people judges is president nobody will tip
nobody will tip ever again because we'll have such a good living wages
yeah when he's president exactly right podcast about list we are now pro
buddha judge
uh... i was looking up what
his last name what nationality it was it's uh...
it's like malty's yeah i was looking up his nationality i was i was curious
I'm curious, because what the fuck is Buttigieg? I can't remember now.
I think it might be Maltese.
Um, I don't know anything about Malta.
Hmm.
Yeah, that's my-
My mom just shared this picture.
It's a picture of baby Yoda.
And it says, "10 year old me looking at all the Lego sets I can't afford."
and then it's a picture of old Yoda and it says "25 year old me looking at the
Lego sets I still can't afford." Oh, so your mom's a Lego fan. No, she has never
played with Legos once. I don't know why she posted that. Yeah, Baby Yoda is pretty
ingenious like marketing. Like, yeah, my girlfriend who doesn't, who isn't
into Star Wars, loves Baby Yoda.
And I just, yeah, like, it's a very,
it's a good way to grab the girl base for Star Wars.
Make some, get some girls into the mix.
- Into the Star Wars.
- Into Star Wars, yeah.
Boys like Darth Vader and Luke Skying, Skye, Skywalker.
- Skye and Walker.
And girls like Baby Yoda and Princess Peach.
That's some true shit right there.
What if it turned out that Mario and Princess Peach were siblings?
That would be fucked up.
And then it turns out Bowser was the good guy all along trying to prevent incest.
I'm looking at my Facebook suggested pages right now.
It's just all omelette, chicken gizzards,
This is a good one.
Chicken gizzards and hot sauce.
I got recommended, I got suggested a page.
Scrambled egg.
This is awesome.
I got suggested a page this morning that was called like P-Bay and it was a website for
auctioning off racing pigeons.
Oh, okay.
So it's for Pigeon Bay.
like ebay but they sell pigeons.
Pigeon bay?
It's like the pirate bay?
You get illegal pigeons?
Yeah.
You can torrent pigeons.
So the way torrenting pigeons works is everyone has one tiny piece of a pigeon and they all
come together and put it together and it's not alive but it looks kind of like a pigeon.
Yeah.
That's some good shit.
like the marvel the marvel action figures they used to have where they would sell you like
you get like nightcrawler and then nightcrawler has like the arm of the blob yeah that's kind
of like pbay they did that was that on purpose or uh yeah yeah so you'd have to buy all of
them to make oh i get it that's cool that's a cool idea good page ham and cheese and tomato
croissant. Do you just only like food pages on Facebook? I think so. I guess I do now.
Tootsie Roll? There we go. The Rick Moranis Fan Club? Okay. Yeah, this all checks out so
far. Dill Pickle Chips. Yeah. When are you going to make Chips App? Oh, Chips App, god
What are you going to get down to?
That would be really funny if I did get really into making chips app.
That would be really funny.
I think you should do it.
I think when you graduate...
Instead of doing like...
Anything.
Yeah, anything close to what my major is.
Just develop an app.
Called chips app.
to
this group is for pro-smoking only.
Though most of our society frowns on smoking, it's still legal, plus it's our birthright
to light up if we choose to.
From research I've learned is smoking is that not nearly as deadly as our social media tells
us it is.
There are other toxins that are deliberately added to our environment that are much worse.
So let's vent, share, and light up.
And be happy.
Please note, this group is for tobacco smokers only.
No fetish or sex or pot.
Inappropriate comments will be deleted and you may be blocked.
thank you for smoking
that's sick
and this guy posted this picture just now says how old are you when you first
started smoking
here's me at the age of thirteen and it's
as a thirteen-year-old lighting up a cigarette
that's awesome
how what's that what are other people
uh... or other people
uh... i don't know
there's a bunch of uh...
i get i keep getting like people trying to add me
from the group because of it
you should know that i had a page
yeah i should add them back
uh... i really like this page
cooked meat
is this pictures of cooked meat
with like a various captions
like there's a really good picture you know what is it
well as a guy
and i got a cigarette in his mouth
and he's staring at a candle. He's staring directly into a candle and it's captioned "mood".
He's gonna go blind.
He's gonna go blind for sure.
Yeah, you should not be staring directly into a candle.
That is a big mistake that will damage your retinas irreparably.
Yeah.
Pro smokers... oh, damn.
Someone wrote something on their cigarette and is smoking it.
Yeah, they wrote "unemployment".
God damn dude.
What?
It's so weird because you know smoking is bad for you.
No you don't.
I don't.
Oh.
Well, I know it's good for me.
If you don't know it's bad for you, it should be bad for you.
No, it should be good for me.
Just because you say it's bad for me doesn't...
It's all about my mental power and the way I choose to view the world.
I mean you see it as like getting a tumor on your lung or whatever.
I see it as, you know, a bigger lung.
- Yeah.
- More cool, more cool bumps in my chest.
- That's pretty cool. - And my organs.
Yeah, it's cool shaped organs.
Unique, it's unique.
- You know what, I think smoking's good for you.
- Yeah, see, that's what I'm saying.
It's all about mindset.
It's a mindset thing.
- Somebody posted a link to Mosala Secondary School
and said is celebrating friendship
that's nice
that's sweet
yeah
yeah age called boy smoke
i don't think you should like that page
i'm a like it don't like that page or any input on a lot of us
boy smoke
patrick loves boy smoke
dennis leary on smoking
Did he, what did he say?
Is it a video?
Yeah.
Oh, then nevermind.
It's a stand up clip. Here's a good...
Woah.
[Laughing]
So this is just four pictures
of a guy smoking in his bathroom.
[Laughing]
That's pretty awesome.
This is bad content.
Um... No, this is good.
No, because nobody can see the pictures.
I'm gonna post this one to the patreon because this one is fucking cool. All right
Is it this yeah
Whoa
That's awesome. Yeah, definitely post that one
Yeah, I'm gonna post it right now
Yeah, I uh, I wonder in the description now, it's like no no fetish or sex stuff
Do people have like a smoking fetish?
I think so.
Is that like, is that even considered a fetish?
Or do you think smoking is attractive?
Or what is it?
Or do you want someone to like smoke into your pussy or something?
See, I think these are...
I think both of those are probably the thing.
Put a cigarette into your dick hole?
Yeah.
Smoking a cigarette with my dick.
That'd be cool.
That'd be awesome.
That'd be some really cool shit.
That would probably blow up viral.
That'd probably blow up viral online.
Blow up, blow up, blow up viral on them.
Yeah that'd probably blow up viral online and get straight to Ellen.
Yeah if you were smoking a cigarette out of your dick hole.
Ellen's like hey you need, everybody on the internet needs to check this video out today.
It's a guy.
It's a smoking cigarette out of the penis.
Yeah.
That's the title of the video, Smoking Cigarette from Penis.
And uh, the guy, and then the guy can't figure out how to get the cigarette out so it burns
down and burns his penis sets on fire.
That'd be cool.
And Ellen loves it.
Ellen loves to see a penis get mutilated.
That's one of her hobbies, I hear.
Yeah, that's one of the things on the show all the time.
like she comes down she starts dancing and then she immediately is like all
right now it's time for my favorite part of the show and she doesn't say what
it's called and then everyone starts clapping and then she just like shoots a
penis yeah she she plays she says let's play let's play happy or sad and she
plays videos of genital mutilation and on all the on all the female genital
mutilation the audience all boos and it awes and is sad yeah and then the male
genital mutilation everyone claps and cheers and then they all go out and and
perpetuate circumcision a little known fact is that is that the the audience at
the Ellen show are all all doctors are all the every doctor that's how dr. Oz
got a show he just kept showing up in to Ellen and eventually developed a
friendship with Ellen. Yeah, and yeah they're all doctors who practice
circumcision. So I would advise you to turn on the Ellen Show, pause on every
shot of the audience, take a good look, and don't let any of those faces near
your kid. Because God knows what they're gonna do to your kid's penis. That's true.
God and God knows. God only knows by the Beach Boys. That's what
they're talking about. Yeah, they're gonna sing God only knows by the Beach Boys
into your son's penis like a microphone.
(laughter)
What are you doing?
What is this? What is going on?
I'm circumcising your son. Shut up. Shut up.
(laughter)
Makes the foreskin fall off.
Shut up. I'm the doctor.
I am the doctor. I was on Ellen.
In the audience. You need
to trust me. I was on Ellen.
Now.
Yeah, I was an audience member of Ellen,
smoking a cigarette and telling you...
Yeah.
That would be crazy.
That totally didn't happen to me.
Yeah, that didn't happen to me either.
That totally didn't happen to every man who circumcised.
Yeah.
Here's another page.
eggs and soldiers
the reason they're called the beach boys
is it's short for nude beach boys
uh... because the beach boys used to love to go nude beaches and circumcised boys
and that's why it's gotta they sing god only knows
god only knows my
penis is
yeah
that's it
uh...
carlton windows my penis is right to you
but that
his right to use his right to you
they can shoot a thunderbolt
yeah
the i can shoot it evolved
and it on
he would've like uh... let me got the right to penis
to contain people
that's a cool shit
yet he's a thunderstone on your penis
it evolves into a...
or if you don't have a thunderstone you can just stick it into one of those
cigarette outlet things
in the car
cigarette lighter outlet whatever
you know the weird outlets
in a car?
uh huh
i stuck my... when i was a little kid i stuck my finger in there
and i like burned the shit
out of my finger
damn you're a dumb kid
i was a dumb kid
that's uh... yeah that's fine
it's so funny how
kids like you have to tell them not to do things but if you tell them not to do
things they also want to do it
like uh... if you tell a kid not to stick a fork in the outlet like
there's gonna be a serious
so the only thing to do is to tell them to do it
and it's not abuse well no then if they do it then you can just be like look
i was trying to teach you a lesson
yeah i was that yeah
yet to learn on your own
you're not gonna learn i'd
yet
listen you talking to a few like listen if we tell them not to put
this fork in the outlet he's not going to use can it be doing have to tell me
every day until he's twenty five
you know we have to let him learn on his own
so we go hey someone you stick a fork in the outlet for your fifth birthday
and then he's gonna like
not even just a fork just like you could tell mistake i feel like i know he's
He's gonna douse himself in water and wrap himself in aluminum foil and then crawl into
the outlet.
That'd be cool.
That'd be awesome.
That's what I would do.
That's what I would do if I was five years old.
I'd become so small I could fit into an electrical outlet.
I would shrink myself down and then like the borrowers, the movie the borrowers, I would
around and I would go down under the electrical outlet if you get my pun there.
I pour some water on it.
Yeah, absolutely.
That's one of the coolest things you can do.
Everybody listening out there, try the podcast about list challenge.
Become very small and pour water onto an outlet and jump inside.
That's our new challenge for the week.
Yeah, we're gonna have deeply challenges.
If you don't do that challenge, I can't talk to you.
Yeah, I mean either.
If you don't do that challenge,
I won't be able to talk ever again.
I'll be so upset.
I'll stop talking.
I'll revert back to 12 years old when I couldn't talk.
Yep.
I'll revert back to 19,
and I'll start crawling around
and drinking from a baby bottle.
Like you did at 19?
Yeah.
Or over...
You drank from a baby bottle?
Yeah.
And I crawled around and wore a onesie.
And I cried.
And played with alphabet blocks.
That's cool.
Man why do babies like alphabet blocks?
They can't even read.
Right.
Freaking idiots.
Man.
Why don't you give them picture blocks instead?
Yeah.
Why not just put a picture of you on the thing?
- Oh, why are babies playing at all?
- And then you can teach your kid your face.
- Yeah, that's true.
Yeah, 'cause kids shouldn't be playing,
they should be learning.
And the alphabet, you shouldn't be learning the alphabet
as a baby, it's just too tough.
- Yep.
- Wonder what Caleb's doing right now
in his punishment chamber.
- He's probably, he's doing God knows what.
- Yeah, he's singing the God only knows by the Beach Boys.
yet he's down at the beach
he's down in god only knows he's at the ellen show
uh... getting his penis mutilated on stage
yeah you know you already know
you already know what it is
uh...
and then his penis gets cut off
and baked like a hot dog in the microwave
what blows up
here's a page i just found
blues brothers colorado
you know whose brothers impersonators
sounds to me like a lot of
blues brothers colorado you are three dot the initials so that page for real quick
bbc's it
uh... wow yeah i think you might have a little bit of a euphemism on your
hit
for british broadcasting
i think i get it now
yet now i think i understand what this page is really about
yeah now i'm freaked out and i'm s_s_d_ message the pages it please don't fuck
me
yet
please please don't let us know
uh... like what you don't work blues brothers impersonators
this is a very very psychology
yet
please please john belushi
uh... dead
damn he's really had to really do be dead though
porridge that's a good page
porridge
what is more rich is oatmeal porridge
or is it a catch-up or is for ages
so don't like the page until you know
well i'm gonna find out
you're not gonna find out
spicy tender crisp
as a page i just liked
is this is basically as you telling me the names of foods
save all soda
isn't that from under a lot of comedy
tony soprano quotes yet
uh...
hicks and rednecks yet
that's cool you should like that one cash as you have a little wrongs
you belong in the hicks and red no i don't know i don't shut up by like too
to
like
You're not missing anything.
I'm missing cool Kevin Smith.
Oh, that's true, yeah.
I got called Silent Bob by one of the chefs at work.
Is Silent Bob Kevin Smith?
Yeah.
And the other J is?
The British chef was like,
hey, anyone ever called you Silent Bob?
'Cause you don't talk?
Yeah.
Do you not talk at work?
I don't talk at work,
unless I'm talking to customers or something.
I don't wanna like--
Well, there's your problem.
That's why you're not getting tips from the Buttigieg people.
They can tell that you're being too quiet.
- I think they should tip me regardless.
No, I try to talk to people, I try to get tips.
- Buttigieg people love to be talked to.
- That's true.
- They love a good talking to.
- Yeah, well, I mean, I can't reprimand them.
That'd be funny.
(laughing)
Just like, oh, you think you can order that here?
- Well, you can.
- Yeah.
- Thank you for, thank you.
Thank you, thank you for coming here.
- Yeah, for Thanksgiving I went to,
Caleb had a Thanksgiving,
Caleb's family had a Thanksgiving.
I became part of Caleb's family.
Yeah, so we're married now.
- And what's the address?
- It's 123, 123 Street.
I couldn't think of a street name, so I just said 123 again.
- Okay, well that exists in LA,
so you just doxed somebody.
So great job. - 123 Street.
- Great job, Cameron, you just doxed Caleb's family.
- Yeah, everybody go kill the people
who live at 123, 123 Street.
And that's an official threat.
- Yeah.
- But they live in Bakersfield, which is where Corn is from.
And so, apparently they, and Bakersfield is just like
the flattest city and it's just dust and stores.
It's very understandable that corn came from there.
It's, Caleb described it to me, he was like,
yeah, this is the only place in California
where people have southern accents.
Like that's the type of, yeah.
But yeah, so they have a street
that's named after corn there.
and they have a have it's called court corn row it's a street sign that as the
corn logo on it
and uh...
yet but it's not even a street just like on train tracks
it's uh... it's it's like this is in the middle of of of nowhere so funny
and it's all i guess baker's field
uh... i don't know
a hundred of them look too big for these are on the a hundred and
one hundred big
one hundred cities size
it's basically think of a really big city
nothing really small now really think of a really small city
uh...
and now combined
no don't combine them
do divide them
okay that's
bakersfield california is known for do you want music dating back to the early
mid
fifties to late eight sixties they made you up there
you like to walk that's sick
you guys like to do up
i guess so
that's the that's why jonathan davis always be like
don't doubt that the problem i'm not sure
yet these do you want to have to have to do
yeah
uh...
when those corn streets i was on like a twelve foot tall poll they're really
worried so in a baker's fields can a steel
still a corn street sign
uh... someone would are you kidding me of course they would i would only have a
camera next to that street yeah
they definitely do uh... it's just it was a whole areas we call poll
later literally twelve feet tall maybe a little taller
really is really something yeah
uh... made a hard to take a picture with
there's a tall
now is like what the f
what the f_ david blaine remember that remember what the f_ david blaine no
remembered what the f_ mark with mark maron
that's kind of what the uh... it's kind of what we're emulating right now
yes and we're guys
my guys are uh... jonathan davis
feel the
monkey and head
yeah and david so vera
those are those are some guys you know had you remember when head
uh... became a born-again christian left corn
and he made his own album of of christian new metal
didn't he he performed with mike huckabee yeah he did
and he has the lines of shit neatly that's why i did like i could be
many rejoined rejoined corn
i used to love that that album that heads christian new metal album
used to die mike relist knew it after this
as i'm sure it does not hold up
but i'm really not
i have been surprised by how much new metal does hold up though
i've been listening to so much limp bizkit lately
uh...
and uh... it's good
you know because he's like he's gets kinda like it's like what if a guy with
a rock and roll star
could rap
and kinda drop the rhymes with the best of the hip hop hip hoppers
i think he's one of the best rappers out there right now yeah i mean he's dropping
insane bars like he's like let me sniff on them panties miss and he's also like
he's like he's like bum right now I'm dangerous yeah right now I'm dangerous
though that now I'm dangerous that's one part of the blimp is good I can't defend
is that exact line I think that's maybe the lamest line in any song ever the
coolest line in all of their songs no no Jonathan Davis has a as an EDM band yeah
J devil that is so that is the best name yeah he could have had for that yeah
dude it's awesome cuz remember they did that album corn did a dubstep album
called the path of totality with like Skrillex and and yeah noisier and stuff
because Jonathan Davis has always been to like EDM on like the back burner but
then he's like you know what you're gonna do this with the whole band and
everyone hated it
and uh...
i wanna hike in in l_a_ a month or two ago and um... somebody was playing
adult one of the songs from that album one of the skrillex corn songs on like a
speaker in their backpack well they're hiking
as just the funniest choice of the song the hike to and to be a everyone else to
be like yelling yeah everybody i'm listening to this
this is what i like
yeah and i'm gonna admitted
blasted on my backpack so everyone can hear
medical
study would be ready
i would not do that
i'll do that personally
no that shut up you know to you know i would not know that i would play
outplayed in order to learn song
i play a i played i played you know
i'm going over
you play the limp biscuit behind blue eyes cover
it's funny they did that
Yeah.
It's cause Brent Durst, huge supporter of Pete Townshend in all of his endeavors.
Yeah, huge supporter of research.
Yeah, I'm a big investor in research.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm super into scientific progress.
And developing intelligent solutions.
Wink, wink.
It's so funny how many like, businesses there are now that are just called like,
something something career solutions or like something solutions.
Like what are you solving?
Yeah. How about I solve your ass with my boot?
Business solutions.
Yeah, what does that even mean?
Tyler and Rochelle business solutions.
Tyler and Rochelle?
Mm-hmm.
Who are those that?
Someone I went to high school with.
Oh, alright.
Okay.
Nice.
We're doing business solutions.
I think that's what we need to do.
We need to start an LLC called Podcast About List Business Solutions.
If we ever get big and have to start an LLC for tech stuff, we will absolutely call it
it
and a business name.
Well, hold on.
Let's look up create an LLC.
Let's do one right now.
Yeah.
Because that would probably be the best company name of all time.
If they let us do it, we would be on fire.
Google, can you name a business Suckafucka?
Sucka Fucka.
Whoa, wait, that says bushiness.
I spelled business wrong.
Damn, my man Pat trying to get the bushiness.
Sucka Fucka Bushiness Solutions?
That's awesome.
Alright, I'm looking right now.
What state would you like to form Sucka Fucka Business Solutions?
Whoa, I searched can you name a business Sucka Fucka and the like 10th result is Limp Bizkit
living it up lyrics. Hell yeah.
That's the song at the beginning when he goes
"dedicated to you Ben Stiller
you are my favorite motherfucker
I told you didn't I?"
Hell yeah.
It's the best intro to a song ever.
Great news
Suckafuckabusinessablutions appears to be available.
Now they're gonna... This is based on an initial search, a more comprehensive search
will be formed during your l_o_c_ filing process
uh... you're not allowed to use swear words
in a business name
why not
uh... it says
it says state and federal laws generally prohibit companies from using legally or
morally offensive terms
suck a fucker is a legally offensive term suck a fucker is illegal
you know the goal suck a fucker
they're making it illegal to suck a fucker
that's true
right now the congresspeople and so i had a dad dream
last night
that you came to
came to l_a_ like today
uh... and then
we were like what no we have said we can't we have to go do stuff you can we
can you know we're ready for you and you're like
i'll just hang out in the in the airport and skateboarding airport for a week
but sounds like it's time yeah
was pretty funny
as like that crazy that crazy guy patrick
always doing crazy stuff in my dreams if you know what i'm saying
world worldwide
what do i do
who wouldn't you like to know and what do i do wouldn't you like to know home
god these words are allowed in your business name
alabama
one
no wait wait wait is by state okay
uh...
has really can't be fixed for a second
r_l_ scroll in a massachusetts
here the prohibited words
army
navy marine corps coast guard
p_x_ g_i_
fire
police
states
or federal police in the name yet there
let's try to talk about the police police department
suck a book a police department l_l_c_
yes i could talk to army navy marine corps coast guard government p_x_g_i_
fire police state federal
business solutions
that'd be cool
they'll be awesome and the last name we'd ever have in new hampshire the only
prohibited word is farmers market
really a half
we can start the l_l_c_ we can start suck a fuck a l_l_c_ in new hampshire
but none of these list though have swear words on them i wonder if you are
actually
allowed
that's something to think about
that's that's a little something to think about
and uh... from something to talk about
you can't that
you can't use the word night in like it
you like that i don't like it
In Alaska it says vulgar names are not allowed, but it doesn't say that for anywhere else.
So I have to assume it's only Alaska that you can't.
Maybe.
Who knows?
In Hawaii you can't use the word Olympic.
Really?
Yeah.
Hawaii they have a lot of prohibited words.
Interesting.
Yeah, very interesting.
I'm learning a lot.
- Yeah.
This is how we solve our shit.
- This is on a website called Small Business Trends.
We should become small business owners.
I think that would be the next step in our...
- Yeah.
- In something.
Be some kind of step.
- That's how we get our shit.
- How to solve your hiring problem.
This is a good website.
They have 15 ways for service businesses
to tap into the holiday sales season.
i'm gonna read this entire website six acts throwing franchise ideas to toss
around was that in the
yeah what the fuck
just acts throwing
is this a bit
what's twenty five christmas gifts for co-workers this is this really uh...
so good list
the typing game makes entrepreneurs faster and more accurate at the mobile
keyboard
entrepreneurs have deployed typing games to learn how to use phones
yeah i got to use may this be can be a half for your phone
what is typing game today is it a specific game
i don't know
we see
uh...
well they have it's it's uh... it's got good st all it is it's a
it's a game called the typing game it's available on google play
uh... okay
it will teach you how to be an entrepreneur
i was literally a type words yeah well
that's some shit i'm trying to do
that's been a long time to pertain
i would like to be an entrepreneur
i'd love that shit
yet my first idea
water bottles made out of water you can drink the whole bottle are
second idea
uh...
a website
for my first idea
uh... third idea a website for my second idea
so on and so forth
and so is keep doing that and forthwith except in that i mean i want to
pranar
i'm making cia
uh... entrepreneur
could progressively nested websites
uh... i love what a website is nested
yeah i love ones that i would say he's an i'd frame html element
but i guess you would know about that
no i'm not an entrepreneur yeah and meanwhile i am
that's true you're the only entrepreneur i know
that's right
yeah that's true
yup
it's funny how ugly stephen king is
he's like really
really ugly and his son is very ugly too
and what's his son's name it's like uh... joe joe
Joe Hill. Joe King. Joe King or Joe Hill. He went under a pseudonym because he was afraid
his dad was too famous. Did your uncles ever tell you while you were watching SNL that
Andy Samberg was Adam Sandler's son? No. My uncle told me that and apparently enough people
I know have been also told that by their uncles. That's pretty funny. That Andy
Sandberg is Adam Sandler's son and he changed his name so that he could get
famous on his own without having to use his dad. Which is the stupidest. That's so
funny. Wow. Why why would he need... Also most of it just sounds like it's because
his name is like Andy Sandberg and that sounds similar enough to Adam Sandler.
Yeah, that's how it works when you have a son. You name them something that's
vaguely similar to your own name. Right. This is my son Andrew Sandler. Yeah. This
is my son Ang- Anchor Sandals. Anchor Sandals? Yeah. That's gonna be Andy Sandberg's son's
name yeah after that Al Qaeda. Al Qaeda Sandler. Nice to meet you I'm Al Qaeda
Sandler. Al Qaeda Andy Sandler how you doing? Nice to meet you my name is
Al but I go by my middle name, Kaida.
Al and Kaida.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I was thinking about why that
Stephen King and his son are both ugly because they're both in this docu-series
about the history of horror that's hosted by Eli Roth
and Greg Nicotero.
Oh, I watched that.
You watched that?
Yeah.
Didn't like it very much.
You didn't like it?
No, I just saw it.
It was just kind of like surface level.
I don't know.
Yeah.
It was very much.
Yeah, I mean it was surface level.
I mean, they got into some things.
There was some stuff that was cool.
I guess, I don't know, it was fun to just kind of watch.
Yeah, definitely a good time waster.
I did enjoy watching it.
I just don't, but yeah, it was nice.
It was, and it was like, yeah, Rob Zombie.
Nice to hear him say like three words every episode.
Oh, did you know he went to Parsons School of Design?
really
yeah that's cool that's how he met his girlfriend
who then they've been originally girlfriend yeah
his wife's on the girlfriend yeah i knew that news from a frill hair
so funny that the ice
that two guys from a parole
ended up being like
making lame music
lame yeah theatrical music
from the same family house and yet as they're both brothers yes of why they
both had careers doing that. Yeah. It'd be great if Power Man 5000 starts making movies.
Yeah. They'd be like robot movies or something? Yeah, robot movies. My favorite genre. But
that docuseries, I think my favorite part of that docuseries is how they had, every
once in a while they would have a clip of Jack Black just talking. And it was like,
Why are you here? What what cuz you just be like and then the demon was like
Yeah, and he's like though he had one story that he showed Rosemary's baby to his pregnant wife and she got mad at him
Which is so funny to show to show Rosemary's baby to your pregnant wife
That's such a always show my wife Rosemary's baby before she has a kid. Yeah, and I say I would never do this to you
Rest assured this will not happen. Oh my god is this I thought this was a movie about a good pregnancy
My bad, I didn't mean to show you this I
Thought this is gonna be fun. Yeah, I thought this was gonna be about a cute, baby
But no, but no it turns out. It's about Jack's black wife
Jack's blacks Jackson Blackson
That's his full name. That's his wife's name. Oh his wife's name is Jackson black. Oh in black. Oh in
in
that's why he married her
because they're like
our names are so similar
I guess we have to get married
we gotta go through with this, yeah
I don't even like you
I just like that your name is
Jacqueline Blackwell
and their vows were just like
I will not change my name, thus ruining our marriage.
I will not do anything.
I promise I will show you Rosemary's baby while you are pregnant.
Our child will be named Black Jack Black- Black- Black-lyn.
It's hyphenated.
Jack-o-Black-o-Black-lyn.
Yeah, it's our child's name, if it's a boy, will be Black Jack Black-Black-lyn.
it's a girl it'll be it'll be blacklin jacqueline black blacklin that's what
we're gonna name our baby everyone that everyone at the wedding is like you
don't have to say that in the vows you can save that for your own private
we really we don't care right now yeah I why did you even invite us you if you
We thought you loved each other.
This is kind of weird.
This isn't even...
Why are you telling us your wedding vows?
And I promised I will always skadoosh.
Yeah I vow I will not take over your career as a substitute teacher.
And I will not have a rock band of children.
That movie, yeah Jack Blas kind of sucks in that one huh?
Yeah, you know with kids all day
You know now that I think of it now that I think of it being a teacher is kind of fucked up
Just you in a room with a bunch of kids
I would never I think we might need to get rid of teachers
Yeah
Hey, you're saying it. I'm just
repeating this
I'm just repeating that shit
I'm still on this website small biz trends comm and they have trending topics at the top and
And here are the trending topics for small business.
Do they have business solutions?
Here are their trending topics.
Holidays. Small business growth.
Small business Saturday.
It's not even Saturday.
That's the shit right there.
And then the top trending topic is in quotes
"What is..."
[laughter]
I'm gonna see what this is.
Yeah, what is "what is"?
What is ghosting and how can small tech companies avoid it?
This is just a joke.
avoid it.
Small tech companies are getting ghosted?
I don't think they are.
I think they're the ones doing the ghosting.
But ghosting is about dating though.
Woah, what?
Ghosting is when you're dating someone and you don't text them for an hour.
No.
Yeah.
Nuh uh.
Yes.
Ghosting is a huge problem for some people apparently.
Ghosting is when you get scared by a ghost.
Yeah.
I think is when you wear a white sheet and you go to someone's house and you go
I wonder what the first piece of media to have ghosts go just like singing like that is it was a
Movie called
fucking
suck a shit suck a shit
Movie called the suck and fuck of shit suck a fuck of shit the movie of a go the movie of a ghost movie of a ghost
Just gonna fucking a shit is a movie of a ghost
That is that's just a lame sound for a monster to be making it's going like yeah
This sounds like it's supposed to be the moaning and crying
Yeah, but it isn't that it's them singing
That's true. You know maybe in the books it says they're moaning, but when it comes to the screen. They're all going oh
Ghosts always be doing that mm-hmm. Yeah, yeah
What's up? Yes? What's the deal with ghosts?
What's the deal with this ghost you keep singing?
in
looking
I'm looking at bushings.
What's that?
Is that like a...
That's the thing in the truck that... the soft things that help you turn.
Oh, okay.
Nice.
Yeah.
Seriously nice.
Seriously a nice thing.
Seriously cool.
Alright, um... let me pull up the Patreon and do Patreon shoutouts because I know we have
at least one new...
Yeah, we got one new...
I think it's Brian Tunneler.
I think it's Brian Regan.
Thank you Brian Regan.
We're a few small podcast hosts and we want to crawl up inside your asshole and just explore
what it's like up there.
What were you asking before?
Sorry.
Do you think I should stream me playing games?
Yeah.
I just got this new game called Session and I've been playing it and it's just me learning
how to play the game.
Yeah that would be fun.
I have 4 hours logged and I'm still not very good at the game.
You should stream it.
You think people would be into that?
I'd watch it.
And that's all that matters.
I'll try and start.
If people.
You should become a sexy streamer.
I'll become a, I'll sell my bath water.
I'll do. Yeah. Yeah. Um, all right.
So thank you to our new patron biz, biz, Judy. I don't know.
Is that how you pronounce it? Ass idiot. Yeah.
The ass idiot himself. Yeah. Uh, praise,
praise me to a lot. The ass idiot. Peace be upon him.
Yeah. Um,
and Caleb should be back for the normal episode on Monday.
We should be done with this punishment.
If you don't like how the show has been going, you're gonna love our episode on Sunday.
We record on Sunday, but then it comes out on Monday.
And then the week after that, Pat's in LA.
And then we're gonna have the best episodes we've ever done.
We're gonna have a Jollibee party, so if you're in the LA area, keep next weekend open.
You're invited to come eat Jollibee.
Yeah, because something's gonna happen.
Yeah, if you know what we're saying.
Something's going to happen.
Something big is gonna blow up in a, kind of like in an online sense though.
I mean like we're gonna blow up viral.
Not like we're gonna blow up the Bank of America that's on the corner of-
We're gonna go viral with our new Jollibee challenge.
Yeah.
We're gonna put viruses in the Jollibee food.
We're gonna go in, we're gonna say, "Can I have one chickenjoy?"
And we're gonna go viral.
Yeah.
That's gonna be viral.
Cause everyone's gonna be like, "A chickenjoy?
What?"
And then we say, "No, it's a Jollibee thing."
And then Jollibee will hire us to make commercials for them.
Yeah.
We're gonna get sponsored.
Alright, um...
Yeah.
Everybody wish me a safe trip on my flight or I will fucking die.
Yeah, Patrick's afraid of planes.
He doesn't mind the heights, he's just really afraid of seat trays.
I'm flying on Malaysian Air flight 93.
Malaysian Air United 93 is what I'm flying on.
So I'm a little nervous.
Alright, bye.
Goodbye everybody.
[BLANK_AUDIO]