Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
- Premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
(laughing)
- Okay.
Jinx, you owe me a soda is completely ruined now
because now, instead of having to actually physically
go to a vending machine,
you can just do a one-stop, one-click buy
on Amazon.com of soda.
- Oh, you owe me a soda.
- Okay, so for example, here I go.
- Here I go.
- I'm going to Amazon.com.
- Jinx, you owe me another soda.
- Wait, you should order a bunch of soda.
- Amazon soda.
I hope I don't get some soda made in the Amazon.
I feel like that's--
- Is this gonna be an Amazon,
can we do an Amazon episode today?
- Yeah, I'd be so down.
- Can we do a full episode?
- I'd be so down.
- Coca-Cola.
- I'm searching soda on Amazon.
Let me see if I can--
I can just sit here and I can buy 12,
say you jinx me 12 times in a row.
- Okay.
- I can buy that, I can buy 12 cans of soda for $8.99
with one click.
- Well, so here I'm looking on amazon.com,
I search soda and I'm seeing dry sparkling soda
in a glass bottle, 12 ounce lavender, four pack of 24
for $717.60.
- See, I'm looking right here,
10 pound bulk bag of baking soda.
- How much is that?
24.99.
- That's pretty cheap.
And that could handle a lot of jinxes probably.
- Yeah.
- I mean, yeah, I guess it's smart to just have soda on you.
- We should just have a billion sodas at the apartment.
- Just--
- Or at the office.
- At least you should--
- We should send it to my apartment.
We should send it to my apartment
so that I can bring it to the office.
- So that we can, just in case one of us jinxes the other one.
- Here's a--
- You know they have new Baja Blasas?
- Blasas?
- I got so excited that I--
- Baja Blasses?
I don't even really like soda these days.
- I don't either, I don't either,
'cause I went to the doctor finally
for the first time in like five years
'cause my health insurance is gone next year.
- Nice, okay, you're gonna finish your story?
- I'm gonna say the cool thing that I see,
which is that I'm on Amazon here
and I'm looking at, you can buy a soda button
like for a drink thing, for a soda fountain,
soda button and I scrolled down to see what, you know, customers also bought this product.
So the people who buy the soda button for a soda fountain also buy a Happy Buy Black Reptile
Incubator 25 liters. Scientific lab incubator, digital incubator, cooling and heating.
Wow. That's pretty fucking dope.
I think that does make sense to me that the kind of person who would have a soda fountain
in their house would also have a bunch of lizards in an incubator. I think that tracks.
Yeah. I would too, honestly.
Yeah.
If I had a bunch of soda, I would also have a bunch of lizards.
That's my fun demographic fact of the day.
I'm going to be doing that on every episode now.
Just a little bit of demographic information.
About one person who likes one thing also likes another thing, usually.
I think that's, honestly, I think that's a fucking terrible gimmick.
What do you, it's not a gimmick, first of all, it's a segment.
It's an awful segment.
I just think that's not a good segment at all.
I think that, I'll do a different one.
Most people over 12 years old are anciently old.
I think I might have to do Caleb Unleashed if you're doing that.
Well that's fine we can each do a segment. I mean my segment.
No, no. You don't want to see Caleb Unleashed live, okay?
You don't want to be there for that.
All right.
Yeah, because you might catch a couple strays, all right?
Because my targets are getting hit by me when I'm completely unleashed.
I have a segment.
What?
I want to try.
Let's go it.
Get those fangs out you mouth.
Get those fangs right out you mouth.
You put it, you put them back in.
Don't tell me you glued them back on right now.
Stop.
Patrick was gluing on fangs before we started recording.
Do you like my segment?
That's a terrible segment.
It was the worst segment ever.
Yeah, why does it make your voice an octave higher for some reason?
It makes you, you do a bit, you replace L's and R's with W's.
You do a baby voice.
- You really lean into the kind of nerd voice.
- Do you like my fangs?
- I have fangs on right now.
- I have fangs on.
- Look at my fangs.
- Oh, I have fangs on.
- If we were in the same room.
- The same room.
- You can't even sit.
Stop talking like that.
- You'd be scared.
You'd be scared as hell.
- I would not be scared.
They're plastic fangs, you bought them from the store.
You look so ugly when you do that.
Stop making that face.
Stop.
- If we had this recorded on video,
people would like this.
(laughing)
People would like this.
- If we had this recorded on video.
Can we record this on video?
- We should have recorded this segment
so that people could see my fangs.
- But nobody wants to see your fangs.
- Mom, can you record me on video with my fangs?
I'm playing with my fangs, Mom.
Can you record a video?
- I'm gonna sing with my fangs now.
- No.
- Yeah.
- Please don't sing with your fangs.
- They did the mash.
They did the months so match.
I thought you were gonna say kiss from a rose.
How did that sound like kiss from a woes at all?
I just thought that you were gonna do a...
Cause I thought that maybe hitting the rose would have done you as funny.
There's no way that those fangs make you say woes.
That's not possible.
What are you talking about?
It's just my fangs that are doing this.
Now you're kinda, you just added kinda like a...
You kinda like added an old Jewish guy thing there.
My fangs are making me do this!
Okay, are you saying that old Jewish guys have fangs?
See, now you're getting defensive on their behalf for some reason.
No, I don't think that.
That is completely ridiculous.
That is completely ridiculous!
That is completely ridiculous to say that old Jewish people have fangs.
I didn't say that!
I said that you sound like you're making kind of an impression of an old Jewish guy.
I'm doing an impression of somebody with fangs.
I'm doing an impression.
Stop.
Alright, fine.
I'll take the fangs out.
Have you ever tried putting them on the bottom teeth?
God damn it.
Did your tooth fall out?
Yeah, he hurt his tooth.
No the glue.
The glue.
See?
Lesson learned.
That's why you don't play with your toys.
You just look at them.
If I take the back in.
Take those out of your mouth.
Get those fangs out of your mouth.
- Okay.
That was a bad segment.
That was maybe the worst segment we've ever done.
- Patrick's Fangs is completely canceled.
- It's a banned segment.
- We're never doing Patrick's Fangs again.
- Okay.
- We're shutting it down.
It's over.
- What about Patrick's Two Front Teeth?
- Well, you already got a segment.
- You can't do a double segment.
- Well, I had to change the other segment.
You didn't have to change it, you did Patrick's Fangs.
You did a full segment, you did a full five minute segment.
This isn't Patrick's Fangs, this is Patrick's New 2 Frontiers.
That's not to say you don't get a second segment.
Well hang on, the other one was Candle.
The ratings were so low.
The ratings were never on the network again.
I'm looking at the live viewer count, or listener count.
We're down to four.
It's plummeted.
I've read that it plummeted.
I'd rather have four fans.
The release of...
You have two fangs.
- You have two fangs.
- Hold on, I'd rather have four fang fans than 400.
- Why'd you say fangs twice?
Take 'em out.
- Ow, ow, ow.
- Why are you gluing, every two minutes
you're gluing something to your front teeth
and you have bad teeth.
We've talked about this, you have bad teeth.
You are going to pull your tooth.
- I'd rather have four fang fans than 400 fake fans.
Well you have neither, because we're at zero now.
(laughing)
Nobody wants to listen to your fangs.
- The Patrick's 2 front teeth segment has been a disaster.
- It's been even worse than--
- For the podcast about this network.
- Even worse than the Patrick's fangs.
- We really need a network.
- Yeah.
I think if we started taking some of these podcasts--
- I've been saying this for a while.
- Under our wing, then maybe they'll blow up.
- I've been saying we need to do a bunch of spin-offs.
We're doing, I wanna do beers we drank,
I wanna do a Caleb, Caleb unleashed,
which would be like every day.
- Maybe I could do like my demographical facts cast.
- Yeah, you could do your demo, yeah, you could do that.
Patrick could do anything not fang related.
Anything that has nothing to do with fangs.
Caleb and Lee should be like,
every day I do like a little 10 minute,
they call it a mini-sode.
And it'd be 10 minutes of me just like,
I'm basically looking at the news,
like here I'll do an example.
What's the news website?
So I basically I'd go to CNN.
Both parties push Ukrainian born GOP lawmaker to tone it down.
That one's kind of hard
'cause there's some stuff in there I don't understand,
but I'll try another one.
But okay, so like just an example like that one.
- I'm looking at the ratings right now.
They're wavering.
- Okay, okay, wait, hold on.
Workers in these two industries
are the only ones coming out ahead right now.
Yeah, what?
Only fans and probably Photoshop.
yeah
uh... hey and i was if i was on there to have i was like a second i'd be like
what do you mean that's that those are the same industries
all
home
you know see that i will get it and it's like almost like you're the unleashed
one and i don't know if it's a little bit better so just kind of like a
uh... there's a bit of a completely like to get to injured by lightning near
white house
uh... yeah that's uh...
that's i i was hoping for that happen yeah and we have a a biden skin is
lightning from Trump skin which was dark orange. Okay you can't you can't come on
you can't come on to Caleb Unleashed and actually do like one like one upping of
me like you kind of. Trump looked more like lightning because he was like an orange bolt from the blue.
I'm gonna throw a news story at you guys and we'll see who comes up with a better punchline.
Okay it's not really about punchlines it's more about like kind of being the
most unleashed so maybe Cameron has better punchlines and puns and stuff but
and is that what is it will she is the most unleashed i mean okay all right jennifer coolidge
says iconic film role helped her have sex with 200 people i just i want uh we should chop
her in half
we should chop her in uh quarters see that's a copycat and you basically owe me a soda
that is a copycat yeah that's exactly which copying copycatting is not a way to okay 200
people what is that what is that a colony of ants because it's so many people
that's not that many people I think there's a lot to people what is that
like a whole colony of ants and there's way more what was she in an ant was she
a queen ant it do you think ants is the worst bestiality animal here's another
here's another headline here okay Kate Bush was singing about anal sex and
Vaseline in the 70s? Kate Bush, I say great Bush, stick to the pussy, leave the
butthole out of this sex. Okay that's pretty good. Cameron, yeah your unleashed
moment? Vaseline, well my opinion on Kate Bush
vacillates. I can't decide if I like her or not. I think Caleb wins that one.
- That's right.
- That was not unleashed at all.
- Mine was clever.
- That was not anywhere near unleashed.
- Mine was really clever.
- Yours was not clever.
- Mine was extremely clever.
- Okay, also the listenership of Caleb Unleashed
is not gonna know the word vacillate.
- Well that's why, yeah, I mean this is,
okay, I'll do Cameron Leashed.
- You're more like a Bill Maher type, okay?
Like I'm more of a, kinda like, I'm a man's man,
and I'm doing, you're on the truck,
you're on a ham radio.
I only broadcast Caleb Unleashed on ham radio.
- Yeah, going ham radio.
See that's some Bill Maher joke, because nobody knows, none of my listeners have ever listened to Watch the Throne.
Okay.
Okay, here's one.
Israel was unleashing a wave of airstrikes in Gaza. It said it targeted the Islamic Jihad militant group.
The Palestinian Health Ministry says its strikes killed seven people and wounded another 40.
I got this.
Go ahead.
Wave.
Surf's up!
(laughing)
- Okay.
- Serves up!
- Yeah, uh, uh, strike, yeah, they, strikes,
they striked out.
- Struck out.
- They strikest out.
- Now, okay.
- I'm seeing here.
- Patrick, who are you gonna give that one to?
- Are they, I'm going on strike from this long ass headline.
It's like, it's, that's a freaking 12 hour day
of a headline. - That one's a little better.
That one's a little better.
But mine was so mine was perfect because it also it kind of made the point that it was a little too long by just
Focusing on a single word in the thing. That's true. You know what? I think this one's a tie wave
I'm waving goodbye to this long-ass headlines like a 12-hour day of work and I'm going on strike
Go how long the headline is I'm looking here. It says mark bar is real
Huh mark bar?
Mark bar, I'd rather have a Mars bar. I'd like to put a bar in
Mark Simpson's house and drink there
Mark Barr sounds like the name of a troll and I think a troll is writing these headlines
because of how ridiculous they are.
I don't think that you're doing a good job with headlines.
You don't think I'm doing a good job?
Yeah.
Hey, CNN speaks to doctor who performed abortion on 10 year old and here's Caleb's on leash
thing.
10 years old?
That's a pretty old baby!
(laughing)
- To be killing.
- That's pretty good.
- Yeah, that's a pretty good one.
- That one's gonna get him.
- Yeah.
Okay, here, Caleb, I'll throw one at you, okay?
See if you can get this one.
Watch Tubbs the Staffordshire Bull Terrier
love all her neighbors in these utterly adorable TikToks.
Alright, let's hear it.
What was it?
I'll give you another one if that one's not going to work.
Wait, this one's good.
Israeli airstrikes in Gaza kill nine, including senior Islamic Jihad leader.
Yeah, this guy's got senioritis and he's actually about to graduate from Islamic Jihad leader high school.
Because he's a senior.
Pretty good.
And the summer's coming up and he's basically got the worst grades.
grades. Watch this clever TikTok dog force his lawn mowing human
into games of fetch.
Well, the human sounds smarter because he knows how to work a
lawnmower.
Caleb is unleashed today. Sunbathing pitties, Mayo and Olive
are the unquestioned champions of summer relaxation. Olive
- Olive Pit, yeah, somebody likes Popeye.
- Yeah, Olive Pits, what's that, Caleb's girl name?
- Yeah, that is Caleb's girl name.
It does suck having a name, a last name,
where when I name my kids,
10% of all names make it something funny.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Like Hamilton.
- What?
- If you call your kid Ham.
- Ham Pits?
What's a Ham Pit?
What are you talking about?
Hamilton pits?
What?
Why are you laughing like that?
You know, like a ham pit.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Like I can never name my kid like...
Yeah, you can never name your kid gravel.
Or deep dark endless.
Oh my god.
I could name my kid...
I could name my kid bottomless, but you couldn't.
but you couldn't.
- Bottomless Fetter?
- Yeah, that's a normal name.
- That sounds too much like Bottomless Feeder.
- Okay, Bottomless Doran, that's okay.
- Yeah, that would be fine,
but I could name my kid Orange.
- Orange Doran, oh wow.
I can't name my kid Orange Pits either.
See, anything that's like,
and like could be possibly used to describe a pit,
I can't do.
- Yeah, Patrick couldn't name his kid, I am not a.
I'm not adoring.
Because your kid would be adoring, see?
Oh, true.
Yeah.
Tell you what, I'm not adoring your kid because you're going to have an ugly child.
I'm not going to have an ugly child.
I think you were cursed to have an ugly child.
Me?
Yeah, I do think that.
No.
Yep.
I think I'd have a cute kid and an ugly adult.
What?
I think you're going to have a kid.
I think you would grow up to be ugly.
I think your kid is going to look like a far side kid.
Me?
Definitely.
Yeah, it just looks like a torpedo.
Why?
What about me?
I think all the energy drinks that you drink, I think your sperm has a life-in-hell face.
Okay, that's a good point.
I think your sperms are eating their own tails and just rolling around.
Caleb's kid would look like if Alfred E. Newman had a Mountain Dew mouth.
Caleb's kid is going to look exactly like a jib jab.
No, because I'm marrying...
Okay, what if I
What if I impregnated what if I
Caleb's kids gonna have damn satellites on the side of its head. That's not true. Yeah, I have big ears, but that's just okay
I'm gonna get like radio
No, he's not gonna get radio transmitted to it
Yeah, okay, if I have a daughter, I feel bad for her. But if I have a son he's gonna be a basketball player
player. Yeah. I think I listen I'm gonna be the ball. Hey, I'm gonna be the ball.
He's not gonna be the ball either. He's gonna be the listen. Listen, I've chosen
my mate well, okay? My father-in-law, full head of hair, okay? Yeah. And everyone in
that family is like over 6'2", all the men. So my son is gonna be, he's gonna
probably be like 6'4" or 6'5" honestly. Full head of hair, but I do think everyone in
her family dies when they're like 60. So we're just making a little bit of a
trade there. But it will be well worth it when I finally see, when I see pits hung
in the rafters of the of a triple or a double, he's got a triple double in the NBA.
Your kid is gonna get is gonna get frustrated and when he's like six
years old and he's going to eat you. I'm giving myself a big, I'm having a big scary son and
I'm going to teach him how to weight lift.
Dude, my kids are going to look crazy.
Your kids are going to get, are going to be like 5'4".
Yeah.
And there's going to be like 10 of them and they only ever stand in a line.
I got, I got every.
They stand in a line with their hands behind their backs.
I got every like recessive gene in my family.
and my two brothers have full heads of hair.
My dad has full head of hair.
His dad, no hair.
His dad's got the horseshoe.
So I got that shit from that fucker.
And that guy's also five seven, so whatever.
So I think I'm maybe the generation skip.
Where it's like, oh yeah, you're normal until this fucker.
- No, your kids are gonna be born with no arms.
- I'm like, yeah, I'm the worst one on the Punnett Square.
I'm like my kids are gonna my kids are gonna look exactly like a combination of me and Megan Fox. You're I won't explain why
I'm afraid of what Cameron's kids are gonna be like
What do you mean Cameron's kids are gonna be born wearing trench coats and sunglasses
They're gonna walk up to you and they're gonna say something like there's a darkness in me, yeah
They're gonna get sent home from school for being too dark
work. Yeah, that might happen. Yeah. Cameron's going to have to homeschool his kids because
his kids are already going to try to like, they get caught casting spells in the bathroom
or some shit. Yeah. Oh, he levitating. Dude, speaking of casting spells, do you guys remember
the spells that I was casting on tour? No. Barely. There was a spell that I was casting
in San Francisco. Do you remember what just happened in San Francisco?
No. I was casting a monkeypox spell in San Francisco
the entire time we were there. Oh yeah, I do remember that.
And that was the first city to declare a state of emergency for monkeypox.
Oh right! You declared spells on every city. You declared disease spells on every city.
I forgot about that. I caused this monkeypox thing.
Dude. How many fucking people actually have this?
I've been just completely out of the loop.
I know, I just keep seeing, I just keep, I think it's fine.
I've been terrified of it because of my lifestyle.
You only get, yeah, you only get if you're weak, I heard.
Oh, that's an interesting way to say it.
That's what I heard.
I mean, I hate to repeat stuff like that, but you know I'm honor bound to repeat everything
I hear word for word.
Oh, that's interesting.
Check this out, look up...
There's only 7,000 fucking people with monkey pox.
Suck my dick.
If you're honor bound to repeat everything you heard, there's a little thing called Chris
Rock the difference.
I've never heard of this.
The difference between me and you is...
It's that song.
Remember the Minions trailer where it's like, what's the difference between you and me?
it's like the minions and grew yeah remember the bill Cosby show where they
sang that song I was about Pokemon bill Cosby show it's yeah it's a bill Cosby
program it was on the Cosby shows a little intermission remember you
remember that episode of bill Cosby show where the kids are trying to make it's
like Rudy and her friend are trying to make jelly in the kitchen mm-hmm and
they break bill Cosby's juicer no I don't remember that I would hate to be in
that situation listen yeah I would I would hate to have to find out what
Bill Cosby does to someone who breaks yeah I would hate to have wronged Bill
Cosby yeah yeah I mean if he does no one about the stuff he does to people who
who he well there is that there's that episode where Bill Cosby he's like oh I
put Spanish fly in the barbecue oh yeah yeah it's it's like he's on like the
Tonight Show or something and he's talking about how he used to he's like
yeah back in my day there used to be a little something called Spanish Fly and
like Johnny Carson's like oh yeah really there was something called Spanish
Fly he's like yeah and we used to we used to just put it in everyone's drinks.
Hey back at Bill Cosby's so damn old back in his day I think there's something
called a love potion. That's true. Yeah that's called Spanish Fly.
I think it's called Spanish Fly. Have you ever heard that, you know that song?
*sings* I love that song. That's what I call it.
That song is called Spanish Fly. Really? I mean it has the same
effect. It has the exact same effect. It gets me bothered.
Like fuckin, what is it, Herb Alpert, it's Herb Alpert and the Tijuana Brass and that
album cover is a woman covered in whipped cream and
all the songs sound like that. Wow. So do you think he's fucking to these songs?
I think people were listening to that song in like bone and heart.
I think they were just covering each other in whipped cream.
I feel like that song could make me beat it up.
I feel like I could be hitting it.
I could be fucking.
Well, because that's like, I mean, you'd have the same effect if you played the Jeopardy
song while you were boning.
sure all right well I got a lot of time maybe you do it you put that on to eat
pussy kind of catch a rhythm yeah to the Jeopardy song that's nasty though that's
like that's like one of those things that like when you have like an old
co-worker he comes up to me he's like what you got to do is like write the
alphabet with your tongue when you're eating pussy. Yeah my co-worker's George Cardwin.
What you have to do. There's seven dirty words you can't say in the office so you
have to spell them in her pussy. Yeah what do you do do you are you supposed
to just do alphabet A to Z or could you maybe write a story? Dude it sucks here every time that I sell out.
between it between every letter you're supposed to go. What letter was that
guess? What letter that was it's actually I keep writing out the Arabic
alphabet. I did I keep it out the Arabic alphabet. She doesn't know what the
fuck I'm doing.
She knows she knows
you know I'd be in there like Jackson Pollock.
I'm in I'm going in there like Rothko. I'm drawing broad strokes
I
Try to eat
I bet J. R. R. Tolkien was writing was writing Elvish and shit in there
JRR
He's trying to teach her Cinder in
Now that's the Elvish word for friends
That's where he had the idea this is gonna be in my book that spells billbo
It's so funny to imagine and off he's a wizard
She starts getting really scared during all the parts in Mordor
door. Yeah, during the murder. She's like no Frodo don't put on the ring.
He just keeps going. At the end she's like tearing up. She's like oh my God
this is so beautiful. You have to write this down. It's the greatest book ever.
And he's like okay. And he comes up and he's like yeah it's about Christianity.
Yep here I'm gonna put ink on your pussy sit on this piece of paper.
(laughing)
- Oh, that's funny, man.
Do you know JRR Tolkien nowadays,
we got JRE and he's toking on that.
- Ooh, ooh. - Holy shit.
- I don't even wanna think about that.
- He's got Elon Musk and he's toking on it.
- Yeah, see, JRR Tolkien nowadays,
CNN is also toking on that shit
with some of the news they're putting out.
- Yeah, like for instance,
how to make the tastiest fried chicken.
Yeah, here's how to make the tastiest fried chicken.
and you had to KFC, pay 33 bucks for a 12 piece,
you put it in a bucket, and then you get home,
you put it on a plate, and you pretend you made it.
Yeah, Caleb Unleashed.
- Yep.
Now, JR, I told you. - Discovery in
a paleontologist's backyard reveals evidence
of North America's early humans.
Yeah, Adam and Eve.
- Okay, wait, I got one, guys.
I got one.
In a year that had no shortage of heartbreak and bad news,
some of the most uplifting moments came from animals.
Some of the most uplifting moments came from animals.
Uplifting Animals, what is this, a giant bird
that's back you ride on?
- Okay. - Holy shit.
Uplifting, no, that makes sense.
- Uplifting Animals, what is this,
frickin' Operation Dumbo Drop?
That's what we're spending our military money on?
- Yeah. - Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, Dumbo Drop, which was when we put an elephant
in Iraq.
- Yup.
Uplifting Animals, what is this,
holding a rat by the leg I found. Okay. A photographer's radical vision of a black
lesbian beauty pageant. Yeah here's my radical vision they're all making out.
Caleb Unleashed. Airlines cancel another 1,000 US flights on Friday. Yeah here's a
cancellation. Louis CK. Damn that's pretty good. A sloth met some dolphins at a Texas
aquarium and a dog befriended some monarch butterflies in California. A monarch in California?
Can we not talk about the politics?
Yep.
Supermodel Ashley Graham shares her 14 summer fashion staples. Yeah, I'd rather her share
her favorite butt. Her favorite butt on my face.
most valuable baseball card sells for over 7 million yeah and the players name
was money let me read that gold golderton let me read that again
okay actually Graham shares her favorite trendy summer fashion pieces I'd rather
share her stinky ass pieces yep all right I got one I got one visit insiders
homepage for more stories no thanks I've had enough that's right
Jill Biden summer is not gone exactly as planned yes she's stuck inside with
covid instead of getting railed in malibu fucking old slut
yep
oh yeah yeah man oh my god oh my fucking god wait anthony bourdain's
dead
what yeah and who's been making all this food
What the fuck?
Senator Christian Sinema announces deal on inflation reduction act.
Oh, we're talking about Senator Christian Sinema.
I'd rather see her inflation increasing.
I want to see her big and blown up.
That's right.
Also, Christian Sinema, what's she, fucking flywheel?
Left behind?
Oh my god.
Oh my fucking god, dude.
What the fuck is actually going on in K-Lub, at least these days?
Russia's ready to discuss prisoner swap with US after Greiner conviction.
Um, yeah, they can have the villain from Iron Man 2.
Pregnant woman who died in Windsor Hills car crash identified.
Yeah, identified to be dead.
Holy shit.
Chrissy Teigen announces she and John Legend are expecting another baby.
Yeah, what, baby back ribs?
Fat ass?
*laughter*
Oh...
That's funny.
Chrissy Teigen, more like Christian Demon, the way she's been...
Oh, I shouldn't say that about her babies.
NO!
What?
Oh my god, sometimes the news is scary.
Drake says he's tested positive for COVID at Big Bones Young Money Reunion show.
Holy fuck, that sucks ass, dude.
Hey, Drake test says he tested positive for COVID-19,
but actually he preferred to have COVID-17.
- Don't ever make fun of him.
- But actually I prefer to have COVID-17.
- Don't ever make fun of him again.
- How can you say that about the goat, man?
- How can you ever fucking shut the fuck up?
- Drake tested negative for COVID-19
because his opinion of 19 is negative.
- I have my Young Money shirt on right now.
- You were silently supporting.
- I might be too strong out on compliments,
overdose on compliments.
I started just to give a fucking stop
around my compliments see it's just like I don't know it's just like automatic for
me because Drake is like low-key a part of my entire worldview and one of the
very few stepping stones for my entire model of my life DC League of Super Pets
goes to the dogs in more ways than one yeah pitbull fighting they have a scene
of pitbull fighting in the yeah Christina Ricci says Johnny Depp taught
about homosexuality as a child that's we are that's oh so I guess that's okay
these days you're much on Johnny West behalf White House summoned Chinese
ambassador to condemn provocations after Pelosi's Taiwan visit summons what is
this Yu-Gi-Oh if so I'd like China have zero life points the kid marrow explains
split with Deezus how about you uh explain your split to Jesus? Yeah. Return to the
faith. How about you spit on Deez Nuts? Yep. Yep that's pretty good.
They/them underlines the risks of combining horror and social commentary
hey how about they/them shut the damn movie off turn on the game. Yeah and
they/them underlines the the risk of of atheist Democrats being in the
charge of the whole thing. Exactly. Yeah. And that's what we've been talking about.
Yep and so basically the atheistic, democratic types are basically just
fucking stupid as fuck. For example, one miscalculation away from a nuclear
holocaust. Yeah it was called Y2K. Oh my god. Yep I called out Lizzo and Beyonce
they actually heard me. How's that possible because of all the fat around
that well just Lizzo's just Lizzo's ears I guess. She's got small ears compared to
big head.
Cheap grills that won't burn a hole in your wallet.
What to know before ordering abortion pills.
Yeah, here's what to know.
Abortion is killing a child.
Rubber coating for garage floors.
Your search is over.
Fifteen vegan snacks perfect for road trips, lunch boxes, and more.
Yeah, what's that?
Sticks and twigs?
Yeah, what lunch box?
The trash can?
Yeah, that's right.
Cookout classics for Labor Day weekend.
This better just be hot dogs and hamburgers and not some of this bullshit impossible fucking
bullshit.
Dubai restaurants awarded first ever Michelin stars for the Middle East.
Yeah, where was it at Toby Keys?
I love this bar and grill.
They have that in Dubai.
It's one of the only that's one of the last places we need to do a live.
We need to do a live on leash there.
Got and call the pros with over 120 years of experience.
We're the best in pests.
120 years of experience.
How freaking old are these guys?
good. 130? They have to be at least, you can get a job at this. Yeah you can't.
Yeah. The world's second highest mountain just had its busiest climbing season
ever. Here's my guess, there was probably an open iPhone charger at the top of the
mountain. Yep. Hong Kong bids farewell to Jumbo Kingdom, the world's largest
floating restaurant. Hey back in my day Jumbo Kingdom was Hooters. That's right.
The best men's walking shoes for walking and standing all day. How about no shoes?
All right, you know what? I'd rather not wear shoes. I want to check out Fox News
now because I do want to see just kind of like what... Let's switch it over. I'm kind
of sick of just all the fake bullshit, you know? And so I just want some real
news. We're gonna allow ads. I'm actually gonna... we're gonna do... yeah, we're
allowing ads on this site. Yeah, we'll allow ads. We need to allow ads on Fox News.
not working. Pentagon rejects Bowser request for National Guard help with
migrant crisis. Yeah who the fuck wants to help fucking Bowser? Yep. Facts. He's got a
shell on his back and red hair he's a villain. Biden test positive for COVID-19
again doctor gives symptoms update. Yeah the symptom is that he's stuttering
and confused and old. He's losing his battle. He's losing his battle. Ten lesser known facts
about Julia Child. Hey, what about Julia Foxchild? She better go home and watch that damn kid.
She's out wearing weird outfits too much. Fourteen hundred pound great white shark. I
was just about to literally spot it near Myrtle Beach. Yeah, who was it? Henry McMaster? Okay.
Whoever you gonna say freaking Joe Biden's mom
Okay, oh shit. Oh, but it's fat white mom
Invented to stop your burrito from falling apart. Hey, how about you put some edible tape on my wife's burritos?
Like that thing will taste good. Finally have McDonald's worker
Reportedly shot over cold french fries has died. Police say I guess you should have warmed up those fries
Yeah
Sorry fry machine warming machine is broke
Probably what they said you should send that to the news go ahead and read that one
You're about to read have monkeypox CDC advises no sex, but says masturbation six feet apart or virtual sex reduces risk
So these people are fucking sickos what the fuck
Yeah, I don't think I want to masturbate within six feet of someone with
funny it's so funny that's like don't just you like you have monkey pox but
you of course you can't just masturbate by yourself you have to go and be six
feet away from somebody. Masturbating six feet apart is so funny. Because I don't know because sometimes that shoots long. I mean
yeah I've had times that have shoot. Six feet apart I think you could still hit someone. That's still in the
splash zone. But I don't think nut has monkey pox in it. I think it's nut has monkey pox.
No the nut doesn't have monkey pox. Yeah so you could get technically you could
get nutted in your mouth. But I also don't I I guess if I was the one with monkey
pox and someone nutted six feet on to I would not want that to hit my rash or
lesions maybe. If you had monkey oh so you're kind of worried about it. I would not if I had I feel like maybe if I mean
'cause you can't spread it through,
but I would not want someone else's
kind of nut to shoot into my open wound.
- You're thinking of it like getting water on an open cut.
- Yeah, I might not like that.
- Gotcha, see I'm, yeah, I guess you're thinking of it
from the monkey pox perspective.
- I'm kind of trying to have an open mind here.
- Also, like how excited would you be if anybody,
if you didn't have monkey pox
and someone nutted on your chest?
if i i really have not monkey parks and somebody noted on my chest
i guess i would like that much either
probably
now so if you you i guess virtual sex maybe is a good option here because you
can use that thing on zoom where you can smooth out your face
and you will look like a jujitsu monster
when you join the sex call true true yeah you know you could be a good
- Photoshop elements. - Get a virtual background
to put yourself in a meadow.
- Yeah, that's a good idea.
- And a filter to give yourself like lipstick
and eyebrows and stuff, that could actually be really nice.
- Are you guys, do you guys ever think sometimes
that you're gonna get hit by a foul ball
from a baseball field that just maybe somebody hit it
so hard that it comes out of the stadium and might hit you?
- No, I can't say I'm worried about that.
but I am worried about like an icicle attack.
- I don't like somebody attacking you with an icicle
or it's just falls.
- It falls on me.
- You know what I'm scared of is--
- If that happened, it would be God's will.
- I'm scared of air conditioners
falling out of people's windows.
- Oh, that's scary.
- That's definitely scary.
- That's a new one you just put in me.
- Especially walking around like downtown.
- I feel like my main thing is cars.
I feel like I'm afraid a car is gonna go
onto the sidewalk and get me.
I'm afraid of getting behind the wheel of a car.
'Cause I feel like when I'm walking on the sidewalk,
I'm like, oh, this is a safe zone.
You can't get me.
But it's not like there's a wall or anything.
Yeah, true. They could just go
wherever they want.
Yeah.
When I lived in that basement level apartment,
I was worried that one day a car would crash
through the window somehow.
Wait, I just found a video of a firefighter
getting hit by
what the air conditioner
only there are
i'm sending it right now
did you guys see the video of the guy of the that way i think it was a k_-pop
group and all my god all this
best video i've ever seen so that is the only that is the greatest video ever
i've been so i think i've been watching it every single day and you know he's a
lot it's so he's completely fine he literally only his arm got bruised
it literally looks like he is entirely dead
he shouldn't have a head after that it's not that if you search chinese screen
crash it doesn't come up
yet it's just the website screen crash
yeah
cheap uh... i think some hong kong i think i texted it to you guys on call
no man he got the in green
oh yeah i think the firefighter all man's lead on that helmet on
feel like he's fine
yet he got back up
yeah i'm pretty amazing somebody takes a hit like that gets back up
Yeah.
Because like this, also what are the odds that the Chinese government just, this guy
actually did die and they were just like, nah, he lived.
What do you think?
Um, no, I think because it's more impressive that he survived.
That's what I mean.
I think that they're probably, yeah, it's probably some propaganda thing where they're
like, yeah, it's, he lived actually.
He survived an 8,000 pound screen crushing his head.
I think it was, well I mean, in China,
some of the technology they have over there is like,
I mean, it's mind boggling,
and I think maybe they could have a screen
that weighs one pound.
That's a really good point.
That screen could have been, you know,
that could actually have been a health screen
that actually heals you when it hits you.
They might have that over there.
That's a good point.
Have you ever seen the Carlsbad,
Carlsbad Gap credit card.
- I never understood that name, Carlsbad.
- It's in Carlsbad, California.
- Yeah, but why are you naming, who the fuck is Carl?
And why are you fucking shitting on him right now?
- Carl...
- Come on, you got this.
Come on, you got something here.
You have something here. - Carl Holtz.
- What?
- Carl Holtz was a German Nazi party politician.
What the hell are you even fucking talking about?
That's who the bad Carl is.
Wait, Herman Cain's dead?
Yeah.
God fucking damn it!
You've got Cain died from COVID, right?
Credit card to Scorpion.
Yeah, I just watched it.
Looks painful.
It's, uh, looks painful.
Have you guys ever been stung by a bee?
I'd never have been stung by a bee in my life.
Yeah, I got stung by a- no, I got bit by a wasp.
- I feel like stung by a bee is a bit of a,
you can get, they don't bite, they sting, right?
- All right, then I got stung by a wasp.
- You thought, do they bite?
- I think, I don't know. - Wasps bite,
but I know that you're not gonna say that.
- Bite?
- I just wanna see. - I know that you're not
gonna say that.
- I know that you're not gonna say that's right.
- No, they sting.
- All right. - I think something,
I think maybe some types of wasps bite,
'cause I've heard that before.
I think that, I think they can bite.
Do you guys have hornets in like Massachusetts and stuff?
Oh maybe it was a hornet.
Do hornets bite?
I don't know but hornets are the really big ones.
They look super super scary.
I saw one at the bodega the other day.
Nice.
Did you try to chase it?
No it made me a chopped cheese.
I was driving down the street while I was on vacation.
Me and my brother we were driving and a bee, we noticed that a bee was in the car and then
the bee tried to attack me and I swatted it away but I swatted it towards my
brother and then we couldn't find it again so and then he was mad at me all
day he was like oh you swatted the bee at me you swatted the bee at me and I was
like first of all the bee was gone after I swatted it so he flew out of the
window probably most likely second of all if I if I have a bee on me I'm not
worried about anybody else I'm just trying to get the bee off of my body
that's right that's what you should be doing I should be like oh I have to I
have to swat it in a way where it doesn't like fight that's like a fighter
every man for himself oh yeah like be in a room I'm not concerned about it's the
same wife yeah it's the same like it's the same thing is like it's like
collateral damage it's like the same as like like you know if like a drone hits
like a wedding it's like yeah we got the target and I'm not so worried about how
many other people if there was a caterer there if the DJ was there or whatever
and that's how I feel about bees it's just like I fucking hate bees I hate all
bugs I hate every single bug I'm not a fan of bees are there some bugs that I
think are fine. See that's weird that's so weird to like bugs I feel like bugs
I mean I don't I think there I like looking at pictures of them but I
wouldn't like being I wouldn't like like touching them or anything I feel like
that's weird. It's clear to me that that God in seven days made every part of the earth
he made every animal every lovely beautiful vista on this on this green
earth and then he gave he said told the devil he was like you can make one you
You can make a single thing.
There's a few things that I think the devil has made.
Besides bugs?
Yeah.
I think he made every bug.
I think I hate every single bug.
I honestly hate butterflies.
I fucking hate butterflies.
That's a little...
It's a bug.
That's a little too much.
It's a bit strange of you.
I don't want any bug anywhere near me.
What else do you think the devil made?
What about yourself?
basically a bald head is like the shiny back of a beetle. Wow. What the fuck are you even
talking about? You said that about your own friend. Bald head is a shiny back of a beetle.
You said that about your own ass friend. My ass friend? Uh, paws. Bugs don't have paws. Sorry
guys, I'm free associating. I can't stop. Cats have paws. You're one cool cat. I'm sorry I said that.
Now he's rapping. Holy shit. Holy fuck. Wow. Splat is what a bug should do.
Bug on a window. Yep. Mm-hmm. Skunk in the barnyard. But instead, many bugs will flew
into your window, into your house. They are more annoying than a mouse.
Yep. Keep going. Keep going. Yes. Oh my god, Cameron. A mouse likes cheese,
but a bug likes these. And I'm pointing to a picture of a guy being stung.
Damn, God damn.
These activities.
Holy shit, fuck, oh my God.
Like stinging freaks.
Oh.
And normal guys, and so do flies also sting.
They say flies can't sting, but I know the true thing.
Flies have a stinger, it's right under their dinger.
Yes, that's where it is.
Yep.
That's dead ass facts.
And flies like to buzz.
Light year.
That one of you guys should say light year.
Wait, I'll do it.
Light year.
Flies like to buzz.
I like my cuz. Light beer! Because your cousin likes light beer. Yeah we drink light beer.
Before Thanksgiving, it's giving cousin time. It's giving cousin time. That's good. It's
Thanksgiving long walks with my cousin at Thanksgiving.
Thanksgiving cousin time.
Dude, I had some serious cousin time
this past couple weeks.
It was fucking, it was awesome.
It's so funny to be like hanging out with your cousins
as like a completely grown man.
Yeah.
It's so dope, dude.
I love my cousins.
Damn.
It's honestly dope as hell to have an extended family.
Okay, we got 10 minutes.
Oh my god dude.
I was going to buy a new backpack.
It's so funny.
You can see him literally because he has two monitors.
So you see him going like this and his eyes are just going back and forth as he's scanning
every item on the page.
You ain't slick.
See I make it.
You're literally like a human barcode reader.
I was going to get a new backpack.
I make a specific effort to show you guys.
I have two hands on my fucking microphone right now.
I'll do this, okay?
Yeah, there we go.
You know what it was? You know what it was? I looked up that Carlsbad Scorpion video.
And then you just didn't say anything for ten full minutes and looked at backpacks.
And I had to rap.
And you didn't have to rap. The rapping was pretty dope.
I don't know what about watching that video was like, "Oh, the straps on my duffel bag
just broke. I should just get something easier to carry my skateboard around."
I need a new backpack. I wear a backpack almost every day.
I can give you my old one.
Mine is yellow and it looks suspiciously like a Fjallraven backpack.
Yeah, your backpack's really funny.
Yeah, my backpack is so si- I've had this same backpack since like the beginning of high school.
It's like a hiking backpack.
I might have to take you up on that offer because I low-key need a backpack.
But I'd have to buy this backpack here.
But not right now while we're recording the show.
Yeah.
I don't think that you need to do that.
Okay.
I feel like you're ripe for like maybe a like-
I tried to, I literally like this week,
because I'm getting kicked off
my parents insurance next year,
I have been trying to get back on Adderall so bad.
Just trying to get, like trying to go to the doctor?
I tried to set up an appointment to get put back on it,
but like--
You have to get a psychiatrist.
Yeah, yeah, TikTok has convinced so many people
that they have like fucking ADHD
and they've been writing so many like Adderall prescriptions.
- I think there's some kind of limit on them now.
They made it really hard to get an Adderall prescription.
- Well, it was already like that before TikTok.
I mean, it's just been a controlled substance for forever.
And it was already over-prescribed
before it's even more over-prescribed now.
- When I was on it in like high school and shit,
I had to like go to my doctor,
wait for him to write the prescription,
have him write it, go to Walgreens,
wait another hour to get that filled.
- Yeah, you have to get a new prescription
every single time you fill it.
Like you can't just auto refill.
- Yeah.
- It's crazy.
- Did you start getting on Kratom?
- I did, I started doing that.
- You tried Kratom?
- Shai sent me those, like the Adol and the Relaxaid.
(laughing)
And so I took the Adol, and I didn't like the Adol,
but the Relaxaid, Relaxaid's tight.
- Does it have Kratom in it?
- It's like Kratom and like melatonin.
(laughing)
- I give that's a glowing endorsement of a relax aid.
I had a crazy ass, very vivid dream the other night.
And I don't get those often.
- Dude, I need to go pick up some Kratom.
- Dude, I have a bunch of relax aid.
- 'Cause there's different kinds of Kratom.
That's why Kratom's so scary.
There's Kratom that you can take that just makes you like,
like it like hypes you up.
And then there's Kratom, if you take too much,
it feels like you like did, you took like an oxy.
So maybe I'll have to do that.
I wanna take like 500 kratoms and see if I survive.
- Dude, RelaxAid, glowing endorsement.
Well, I'll say that now.
- Yeah.
- Perfect.
- What else did-- - Perfect pill.
- What else did the doctor,
did you try to do that thing where you go to the doctor
and you have like a specific thing
that you wanna get out of the doctor?
So you say like--
- I went to the doctor-- - Oh, you're like
a dialogue tree?
- Yeah, yeah, you're like-- - I went to the doctor
because I was trying to get Adderall--
- I'm too sleepy. - And he said,
he said, "Oh, you have to go to a psychiatrist."
- But did he refer you to anything?
- No, I tried to, I looked through my insurance thing.
- That means you did a really bad job with the doctor.
He didn't refer you.
- Yeah.
- Wait, did you tell the doctor
I want to get an Adderall prescription?
- Yeah, I was like, I'm trying to get back on.
I was like, I have ADHD and I'm trying to get back on
Adderall, and the guy was like,
oh, you have to go to a psychiatrist.
Just look in your network.
If you say I'm trying to get a drug,
the doctor's not gonna help you at all.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- That's so funny.
Basically I'm addicted to this drug and I need to get it.
- The last doctor I ever saw was my pediatrician
five years ago and he used to write my prescription
so I thought that I would just have to say
the same thing that I say to him.
Yeah, I who's know that my old psychiatrist was like that.
I could I would just be like, oh, I want I can you raise my dosage of Adderall and also
can you do that?
Like I would just tell him what I wanted and he would just write it.
It's pretty swaggy and his name was I like my doctor's name on this podcast before in
my eyes the prescription of the best prescription is probably waking up at 6 a.m.
Go and surfing.
Oh my God.
Don't even just enjoying so many dolphins on the beach.
Oh, yeah, I don't think I've ever seen a dolphin. Did you have a guy do a romantic contact with them? No, no
I think I saw a guy do a backflip on a surfboard and like keep surfing. That's sick
He was riding a wave and he did a backflip. I think that's a different name
I could probably fall in love with a dolphin. What do you mean? It's not a backflip. He flipped over backwards. I
Think that's a that's a it's a way. That's called a wind to go flip
I think that I could non-sexually fall in love with a dolphin in like a before
sunrise kind of way. Yeah, they don't have sex before sunrise, right?
But I could just sit there, yeah, I don't know I've never seen it I just know they
talk a lot so I just sit there and I just yeah so I just sit there and I just talk
to the dolphin all day and just like fall in love. I don't know I feel like
that's definitely possible. You can see all the water. Yeah but I would always I'd
probably be in like a kind of a tank that I designed to fall in love with the
dolphin that'd be up to my up to my waist. So you'd like to pick out the
dolphin beforehand? Would you know which dolphin you are trying to fall in love with?
Pick the hottest one. And what's your criteria for that? Because you
haven't fallen in love with it yet right? You don't fall in love with it till you
spend some time in the tank. Well kind of picking one that you would like to fall
in love with and then kind of like falling in love with it. Let's think about that. That's actually that's a good point. How do you choose the hottest of an
animal. I would say, so if I say you're an alien right? Or aliens are coming or
whatever there's there's an alien species and we're making you know one of those
one of those toys where you spin the button and it hits an animal and it
makes the animal sound like the cow goes "moo" like those toys. But we're
adding but we're adding humans to it okay? So I think that the one that you
would choose, the human you would choose would just be like the hottest human
right? Because you want to represent the best. You want the best for
something like that. Sure. So I would probably take one of those toys or
whichever one has a dolphin on it and I would kind of compare every dolphin to
the picture that's on the toy. But dolphins didn't make that toy. A person made that toy.
So that's whatever dolphin the person who made the toy thought was hottest.
So I'm just trusting that person to have pretty good taste. You're trusting them slowly.
I mean even though they've picked the hottest dolphin, cow, pig, cat, they've said that they'd...
I mean...
Dolphins are like the rapist animal.
Yeah.
So I think that's humans for the most part.
Yeah, I would say humans are probably...
I don't think it'd be hard for you to fuck a dolphin if that's what you said.
I didn't... I already said I don't want to fuck a dolphin. I just...
I got distracted. I saw another headline.
There he goes. I think that I can have a mental connection with a dolphin...
- Addison Rae advertising for Adidas
in a Holy Trinity bikini,
all I'm going to say is these people
are just going to learn the hard way not to play with God.
- That's a headline?
- That is not a headline,
that's just something somebody said about a headline.
- Oh, okay, so you're not actually looking at a headline,
you're looking at some kind of comment.
- No, I'm looking at a picture of Addison Rae.
- Okay, cool.
But so I think that maybe what you should do
is you should find the guy who made the spinning wheel toy
and like talk to him and like see what's up.
- Well I would also I guess, I would wanna find--
- Caleb would you wear this praying bikini?
- We're having a really important discussion Patrick.
- I'm having, I have a very important question.
Can Caleb wear the praying bikini?
- I would wear any bikini at any time.
- Yeah. - Okay.
- Anything-- - Then you're
disrespecting God.
- Anything, no I'm not first of all.
- Yeah you are because it says--
disrespect to God. Because it says father on one boob son on the other one and then
says Holy Spirit on the vagina. I remember my first time in God I remember my first
time cussing in church. Damn. In a church yeah my my friend Jordan who became a he
went into juggalo the juggalo world shortly after. So did Cameron. He said he said yeah I
would never cuss in church and I said who gives a shit. No way. I swear to God I
I said that. I said that. It was Sunday morning too. I think I said that. And here's what I
was, here's the worst part because I was, I was a vegan and I couldn't have the, I
couldn't have the, the like donuts and stuff they would bring for church on
Sundays. I would take those those coffee creamers, those non-dairy coffee creamers
and I would just drink them. So I probably, probably shortly after that I did a shot
of some kind of coffee creamer. That's what the weird kid always does. I remember
people doing that. Yeah but I was cool. I was really cool. I was, I could, there was a
tree on the side of the church that I set the record for highest. That's not cool.
That's just disrespectful and strange. You're literally have it, you have a shirt
on right now that says the H word on it. No it doesn't. It actually says, I see that it says
H-E-L-L. H-E double hockey sticks right there. No it says he. No it doesn't. He.
It clearly says "he" right here. What about "full of heat" because that's what hell's full of and
that's where Cameron's going for wearing a shirt that promotes it. I'm not going there.
You're wearing a shirt that promotes hell. I'm not going there! You will be going to hell.
God will grab you by your ear and drag you down to hell. I don't want to go there. You will go to hell.
God can't touch my ear because I wear headphones. See the fact that you're
already missing... Over a ear. You're underestimating God. It's like that's a clear...
- I don't want to go to hell.
- No, you're going.
- I don't wanna go.
I don't wanna go, I'm not gonna go.
- I don't think it would work.
- You can't make me go, I'll run away.
(laughing)
- I'll scream.
If you make me go to hell, I'll scream.
- I'm gonna tell everyone you kidnapped me
and brought me here.
I'll be pissed off.
- I need to start doing that more.
There was a scary guy,
I took Phil to the park the other night
and I ate an edible and I was like way too high
to get into a combat scenario
And there was like a scary guy that was like hiding behind
like the bleachers at the park that I took him to.
This is at like midnight or one in the morning.
And I was like, I think if he came up to me,
I would be like, if you don't get any closer
or I'm gonna scream.
(laughing)
I really considered that.
I was like, I think that might be my first
course of action there.
- I had a scary encounter last night too.
- What happened? - What happened?
- I heard rock and roll music playing
outside my house at 1145.
- No fucking way, really?
- Yeah.
- Did you--
- And only moments before that I heard
the noise of a glass bottle.
- Wow.
- What the hell, somebody's doing
some kind of demonic bullshit.
- Yeah.
- I woke up to a jackhammer this morning.
- Yeah, I was jackhammering your ass.
(laughing)
- And you woke up to it.
- What the hell?
What the hell, no!
- Yeah, it's too easy.
- Yeah.
- All right, come to Portland in Seattle.
- Portland in Seattle, please go to--
- Whatland.
- It's the last live show we're ever doing ever.
- Go to swagpoop.com/shows and check this out.
- And tonight we are at Life World.
- Life World!
- All Brooklyn, New York.
So yeah, go check that out.
- If it's not already sold out.
- That's also our last live show ever.
- The day that we're recording this,
it's already sold out.
We sold out a show in Brooklyn.
- Awesome.
- The Saturday one I don't think is sold out yet.
- No, the Friday show is sold out.
- I know, but when this comes out,
that's in the past, doesn't matter.
Go buy a ticket.
Patrick is trying to confuse you into not buying a ticket.
- In the past, we sold out a show.
- Okay, I'm stopping recording now.