You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
I pressed it.
I'm about to go kooky for kooky crisp on you.
Kooky crisp?
Yeah.
The thing about learning how to pop and lock.
Mm-hmm.
Ready?
[POPPING NOISES]
Wow.
That was pretty good.
[POPPING NOISES]
(Blooper)
(imitating a fart)
- That's my bit for the episode,
is I woke up from a nightmare.
- Still in a nightmare, look at this fucking pop and lock.
(imitating a fart)
- Yeah, wait, let me try, let me try.
- Oh, what are you, oh, your bones.
Your bones are gone.
(gagging)
It's so hard.
- How'd you get that thing that hard?
- Popping and locking it.
Oh, oh.
So he pops the boner.
You put, yeah, and you lock it into place.
Locks in the freshness.
Yeah, okay, that makes sense to me.
It's like a ziplock for boners.
See, to me, poppin' lockin' is a beautiful synthesis of hip-hop and robotics.
Poppin' lockin' is less of a dance and more of a lifestyle.
I went to Boston Dynamics, they taught me how to pop and lock.
Yeah, I went to Boston Dynamics.
Better than anybody.
I went to Bossed Up Dynamics.
Yeah.
Yeah, and I learned how to pop and lock.
And they made me to a robot dog.
Yeah, dog.
Yeah, we have the robot dog, and then we have the robot dog.
The C in C-3PO now stands for Caleb.
God damn it, you guys.
I had a rough week.
I'm sorry.
You have hurt your knee.
Me too.
I had a rough week too.
I had the most amazing week of my life, but you don't see me complaining.
I found a treasure chest.
It's true.
I have all sorts of rubies.
Can we restart this episode?
No!
You say that every time.
Yeah, just...
Ugh.
No one's gonna make fun of me.
If they are, you say that.
For what?
No one's gonna make fun of me.
Oh, Pat.
Pat fucked up another thing on the show.
What do you think you fucked up this time?
(sigh)
Hey, you know what I was thinking about something?
What?
So like, C-3PO, but now the C stands for Caleb.
The 3 could be your middle name and P's Pitts.
See, it was actually a great idea, Pat!
And the O is for awesome!
It was actually such a good idea. Come on, bud.
Come on, buddy. Come on, get yourself out of that there junk you're in.
Just wait back up.
Just pop one arm and lock it.
- Hey, hey, partner, let me see you pop and lock some.
- Come on, come on.
- Come on, you know you wanna pop and lock some.
- Please.
- Come on, just pop one thing for me
and lock that sucker in.
- Don't make me tickle you.
- Don't make me pop and lock for you.
- Just I haven't been able to break dance since the injury.
- 'Cause your knee?
- 'Cause of my knee.
- That's really, and also you hurt the top of your head
so you can't spin anymore.
really tough yeah the dreidel tip I had
man it sucks so much dude just everything about me that was so good at break
dancing just fucking went out the went in the fucking toilet
With a season-ending injury trying to spin on the wet cardboard and it just you just stay completely still
break dance regularly. Why don't you just buy a new cardboard? You have to break it in.
What do you mean buy a new cardboard? Tell me where would you buy cardboard? You get
cardboard. You fucking moron. You earn it. Idiot. You earn the cardboard. Yeah. I think go out to the
cardboard store. I don't think so. I think the supreme way to break dance now, the newest most
supremest way. The supreme supreme ex breakdancing. I think is to be on the subway and to use
all of the different poles to spin. Yeah that's pretty good. Yeah what's that called? Subway
spinning. No like the actual like the guys show up. Splinway. No the name of the it's
not called. Acrobatics? No there's a name for it. Jabberwockies. No it's not the Jabberwockies.
crazy ass dancers. I respect the Jabberwockys so much. Me too. Um... Me too. What's the
fucking thing called? Showtime. Is that what it's called? They get on the train
they say it's like oh it's showtime and they like start like dancing. Really? Yeah.
Usually they say we have a... We're trying to save... We have a ball! And if we don't get to break dance!
Sometimes they'll say like we have a basketball team we're trying to save or
some shit. And I'm like, "Just fucking shut up and dance."
Just ask me for the money. Remember last night, last night Cameron and I were going home and
this like homeless guy gets on the train and like he like clearly, like clearly he's like
very mentally unwell and he was asking, we were the only guys on the train, he was asking
me for like a dollar and I gave him like a dollar. He saw like another dollar fall out
of my wallet and he was like, "Man, come on, I know you can give me a little bit more."
I was like yeah, he played Patrick. Yeah. Yeah, he didn't say he wasn't he didn't say that he just Patrick gave him a dollar
He's like, okay now another dollar. Yeah, they say no, I was like
You shouldn't have tied up all your dollars and kept him in your sleeve, yeah
You're the most generous man in the world
God damn it. Yeah, but then he like explained
Yeah, I don't ask for money on the train to us. He was also yeah, I paid for some street knowledge. Yeah
We did I did pay you very unstable on his feet and he crossed through the train cars while I was running and I was like
Oh, we're gonna see this guy die. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I haven't done that yet. I always want to oh, yeah
I'm sorry do an excuse. Well, that's the thing anytime you see those train doors open
and it's like, "Oh, this is either going to be the greatest breakdancer in the world or
Davy Jones."
Yeah, just a pirate.
I've never had a good subway door opening interaction.
Not yet.
No?
Well, maybe I have and I wasn't paying attention.
You mean like one of those doors that was never opened and it wasn't like your dad coming
back from war that you hadn't seen?
door oh my god yeah I'd be pretty funny to do yeah don't steal this bit Eric
Andre Eric Andre I know you listen I know you already stole all of our being weird
stuff that we do took all of our ideas about how to be fucking weird yeah and
you stole our Hannibal Buress character yeah we came up with that guy yeah we
came up with the evil landlord what?
Whoa!
Come on.
What the fuck?
Just kidding, just kidding Hannibal.
Haha, if you ever want to join us, come on the show.
If you ever want to join us as the fourth guy.
Join us as the fourth microphone on the show.
If you ever want to join us for dinner.
Tea and crumpets.
One of our properties.
One of our favorite things.
Hannibal.
Oh, Hannibal.
Hannibal bless.
Hannibal.
Come here, Hannibal.
You cheeky, you cheeky little man.
cheeky little man he's not a little he's like five seven why do you know it's
like he's shorter than Eric Andre on the show you fucking sitting there googling
comedians height I saw a picture of him sitting down next to Eric on no you you
you have everybody's height memorized every media you have it's like how I
remember I knew every rappers religion well it's cuz you should only be laughing
you should only yeah you should only be laughing at a comedian if they're like
Six feet or above. I mean you can't, you don't want to guess up a shortcut.
Yeah, you don't want to make them feel good about it.
You're just gonna let that...
I know every rapper's religion because I was worried that they would go to hell.
So I would Google and I would, I remember crying when I found out T-Pain was a Muslim.
[Laughter]
Because I was like, "Noooo, dude! T-Pain! He won't be with me in paradise for eternity! Fuuuuck!"
It's true. That's so fucking weird.
That was like the only, and that's like why I got into like using Wikipedia
a bunch as a kid. That was like probably my first interaction.
That's how you got into Wikipedia?
It's like the first time I like knew what Wikipedia was.
Alright, alright, speed round. Jay Z.
Jay Z is Nation of Islam, but he says he's a Christian.
Eminem.
Eminem is atheist.
Tupac.
Tupac was Muslim.
Okay, Biggie.
Biggie was Christian.
Iceberg Slim.
Iceberg Slim was a pimp, he wasn't a rapper.
Well, what's his religion?
Yeah, uh, the game.
Yeah?
Women's pussies and money.
Ronald McDonald.
Ronald McDonald is burgers.
Uh, Michael Mann.
Michael Mann is big, uh, big.
Little Peep.
You know, that was after my time.
As far as the era.
He doesn't know, he doesn't know.
Ron Jeremy.
Ron Jeremy?
What was Ron Jeremy's religion?
I mean he's gotta be Catholic, right?
Yeah, with all that...
Weird Al.
We all thought Weird Al was Jewish.
We talked about this before.
That motherfucker Polish.
No, no, no, no. He's...
No, he's Yugoslavian.
He's Sokovian.
So...
He's one of them Star Wars guys.
Exactly. But yeah, man, because I was, you know...
Raised religious. I was super
afraid of the rapture and I was like dull. The rapture? You wore so many of them.
You're doing it again. Yeah. Yeah you are. And you're not even upset about it this time.
Because this time I was doing it on purpose. You fucker. Yeah. I was scared of the rapture
because I watched those movies left behind. The raptors? Okay all right. Yes I was scared of,
yeah I was scared of raptors as well I guess but the rapture because. You're scared of raptors and
and you yet you love Drake hmm what if I just disappeared right now my clothes
were left right as you guys had this conversation with me because I wasn't
able to stop you because that means you're in heaven I you know I'd be
unhappy with naked in heaven which got to see my penis rapture movie you're
talking about left behind dude oh yeah you left behind was the you guys did you
get scared in 2011 when there's that like May whatever rapture thing I got
scared every time anybody said it was gonna be the rapture yeah I remember I
I remember there was one rapture thing where my dad, who's like super big into eBay, was
like showing me that people were, yeah, that's his thing, was showing me like listings on
eBay where people were selling like, like selling a thing, like a, the service that
when these, when people got raptured, they would like take care of their pets.
Oh yeah.
And I was like, holy shit, dude.
Like, oh no.
I mean, that's.
I thought it was going to happen when I was 13.
It's so fucking funny that like the like main thing of the Rapture that when you
like mention the Rapture everyone knows is yeah you leave your clothes on the
ground. Yeah dude that's to be that's because of left behind yeah cuz it left
behind everybody's clothes are left. What if you go with your clothes? Can I just bring one shirt?
What kind of? It ain't heaven if I can't bring my like best fit 2019 Raptors NBA
championship. I need that. Put me put me up there fucking head to toe.
Yeah.
It would suck if you got raptured but it left your liver or something.
That'd be rough.
It would suck if you were walking around town and you saw a green one-piece shoestring bikini
and you were like, "Oh my god, dude.
Borat got raptured and I got left behind.
Fuck, dude."
You're just seeing like a mascot suit.
like a boat with a ton of like pirate hats on it. Seriously, is he a ghost sheep?
Wait, that doesn't make sense. It's already dead. The fuck? Like one of those like out in
front of like the Verizon store that Android costume is just like on the
ground. Yeah like, oh the fucking Android robot? Come on dude.
Oh yeah, passed out there for a little bit. Hot day. Yeah. It's pretty hot in this
here suit. There used to be when I there when I lived in like Revere there was
There's one near like Malden Center and there's a guy that just always had to like stand in
that suit just like point to a Verizon store.
That's hard work.
Yeah, no one's going to go, no one is going there for that.
Yeah, that's one job that should be outlawed I think.
I don't think, I think it's completely, I think it's outdated and I think it's torture.
That's like, that's legal torture.
That is straight up torture.
There's a guy on my block who has to dress up like the Statue of Liberty and go, "Yo!"
like it's gonna drive first of all it's gonna drive people away from the store
because nobody wants to have to interact with like a giant fuzzy monster in order
to like go in because you can just scream whatever you want in that suit
when nobody's around I saw a lady yelling at the Statue of Liberty guy and
she was like there's because I guess he got too close to her she was like I have
to go see my family later today and you could have possibly given me the
COVID-19 virus do that guy is not getting paid you probably get fucked
with by teens too yeah yeah dude you're dressed up first of all that guy's
dressed like a woman yeah just like a famous woman yeah you know you know a
woman screaming at a symbol of one of the most beautiful women of all time - I
mean one of the most gorgeous sex symbols this country's ever had yeah I
mean think about that that those spikes on her head oh how come women don't have
enough like spikes anymore I know dude yeah what's up with that in the 1800s
Just because it was such a Puritan time, they used to booby trap women.
They really did, I'm serious.
They would put little like, kinda invisible like, like wires that if you hit various,
various points, maybe a, maybe a scythe would hit you.
Yeah.
It would fall down, chop your head off.
Exactly.
You know?
Yeah.
That's what you would do to your daughter as a gift when she turned 18.
It's like the trap in Temple of Doom where you have to like bow a certain way.
Yeah, exactly.
Exactly.
Or her head would fall off and roll at you like a boulder.
Yeah.
Towards you.
I don't remember Temple of Doom that well.
Is that Temple of Doom or is that the Last Crusade?
Temple of Doom, she eats that weird soup.
Yeah.
And she says, "Um..."
It's like a monkey's brain.
Which is the one...
It might be the Last Crusade.
I don't remember.
I don't think she says that.
She says, "Check, please."
I don't think she says...
Yeah, I think she does.
It is funny that the female character in Temple of Doom,
her only purpose was to be annoying.
Yeah.
It's kind of like you.
I mean I feel like that's also like every character except for Indiana Jones in those movies.
I bet that you're so jealous of my poppin' lockin' skills after I fuckin' owned you.
You just got nothing to say now, do you?
Yeah.
You know why?
Because you just got poppin' lockin' dominated.
Yep.
Go ahead and cry.
Shut up.
Wait, Pat, can you say something real quick?
Patrick, are you okay?
Shut up.
Pat, are you okay?
Patrick?
Patrick.
Pat, Cam, call 911.
Beep boop boop!
*Bzzzzt*
Here, I just called them with my body.
With my robot body.
I turned my hands into defibrillators.
*Muffled* Hello, this is Dino Lord.
Hey, my friend Patrick's being a bitch. Can you come shoot him in the head?
Can you come put your fire hose in his mouth?
*Muffled* Hello, this is Dino Lord.
Press on, blow him up like a big balloon,
and then use a single needle to pop him
so that the whole city gets wet?
*Muffled* Yep.
Oh, what was that thing we were talking about earlier?
say bye. We saw the guy with the hose. Oh yeah, there's a guy with the hose, like a guy hosing
off the sidewalk, going up to a guy who's hosing off the sidewalk going, "STOP! YOU'RE GONNA
FLOOD THE WHOLE NEIGHBORHOOD! YOU CAN'T MAKE A RIVER IN THE CITY! IT'S TOO WET! STOP! YOU'RE
SCARING ME!" Yeah, 'cause why, like, the guy was just like, "I'M GONNA SLIP!" Yeah, just
Like, there's like, the guy was just hosing off the sidewalk.
Probably, probably somebody fucking yarfed or barfed or ralfed over there.
Oh, that makes sense.
Yeah, popped or locked.
I just thought he was just washing the sidewalk.
Yeah.
I don't know why that was like what I thought was happening, but...
No.
Stop!
Now!
You're gonna make our...
Why, why would you build a river here?
This is no place for a river!
Go to the forest!
Forest
Cars need to go by god
These look like boats to you you fucker
Did you like what happened in Katrina oh
I bet you loved Katrina
That was your favorite hurricane, huh?
Dude, I forgot I forgot how like bad Hurricane Sandy was here Hurricane Sandy. Yeah, remember that shit
Yeah, dude, they made a whole Louis episode about it. Yeah, it was
Yeah, I once it reaches Louis. That's a that might be the only
That was ever on Louis
So that's got a like pretty bad great like no one really taught like somebody probably died in Hurricane Sandy, right?
Yeah, not the spirit of the new year the people of New York though that will never die will never they are too brave
People who live in New York, they're so brave just for believing here for some reason absolutely you know you know if you want to become brave
Move to New York City. Yeah
Because two bad things happened here in the last a hundred years three three was a third the
defamation of Anthony Weiner
True that was actually a huge blow to the to the psyche. Yep. Yeah, I watched that documentary recently the wiener one
I've seen a lot of wiener documentaries, but I think this one was my favorite. Yeah
That way it's so fucking good, dude. I mean he's awesome. He it's so like he should have fucking stopped
so early into that and just not that he should have stopped because he's a he is like a
Egomaniac. He has no ability to stop.
Yeah, yeah. Oh, he was- he's a complete egomaniac.
He should have been stopped by some check along the way.
Uh-huh.
But he just didn't. And he just-
Yeah. It's crazy.
So fucking funny. Just like the-
He's the man, dude.
The scene of him
showing his wife,
him arguing with a guy on TV.
Yeah.
And he's like, "Isn't this great?"
what's her name Huma isn't she like yeah basically Hillary's top Hillary's top
exactly yeah she yeah there was like a like the like towards the end of the
movie it's like Hillary's like basically tells her through a magazine like you
have a choice either me or your husband what yeah she's like through a magazine
like a like a it shows like a picture it shows like a picture of a magazine that
says like I guess Hillary in an interview was like you know I love Huma or
whatever I really don't remember but it's like it was basically the movie
presented it as like Hillary giving Huma an ultimatum like you work on my
campaign or you work on your husband's campaign and then they like I don't
know I think she leaves him at the I don't remember honestly I watched it
like two weeks ago Wow she did leave Anthony Weiner in 2018
yeah I do remember looking at I see it you think he's in jail right now right
yeah he's in jail for showing his wiener to goddamn much I think he should I think
you sex it off like a 17 year old or something yeah I think that's why I
ended up no he did it Carlos Danger did who's Carlos Danger you don't know about
that no that was like his is like name that he would like is like Carlos Danger
he would say his name was Carlos Danger that's like sounds even more like a
pedophile yeah I mean I guess when your name is wiener you there's only one way
to go and it's up yeah so Carlos is a little no don't call me don't call me
by my real name call me Carlos danger are you Anthony wiener no I'm Carlos
also danger have you seen the wiener documentary oh my god you got to see it
just for the scene of him at like, he's at some like parade. And I think it's like a like,
I don't know, but he it's him on a float, like singing and dancing to reggaeton.
It's one of the funniest things I've ever seen. Just him like, like, go go is getting hard, dude.
He can see nearest. Yeah, he's like having the time of his goddamn life at this parade. And
everyone's like walking up to him because like it's after the allegations are
already out and everyone's walking up to him like I don't believe a man for him
that was like him it felt it probably felt like him coming out he was like I
can finally be myself yeah I'm sex addict yeah did yeah New York has a
pretty bad track record with with politicians having odd penises at this
point I would say. The Cuomo stuff that just came out? Yeah. Andrew Cuomo pulled his thing
out in a coronavirus town hall. He coronavirus pulled his thing out and he pulled his thing
out and he said "this is what's gonna cure you New York City, my gross penis, it looks
like ground beef yeah and I had it and I had a gauge earring in the hole yeah
yeah big thick one you can you can put your penis in this one yeah and I won't
be wearing a mask over this he's built exactly like the Dana Carvey show sketch
where Bill Clinton has a bunch of nipples that's like that is like that is
his body that's what he's gonna do for New York he's a bunch of weird little
flaps on an old man. And he's got a hen's ass too, just like the Bill Clinton message.
Yep, he does a big ass fucking hen's ass. I think we should take over politically this
city, maybe. Yeah, I think we could do a Cynthia Nixon-style campaign. I kind of want to run
for... As you both know, I took the quiz, I am a Miranda. Oh, that's huge! Yeah, that's
That's a great start.
If we do take over New York City governor race, I am the Miranda of the group.
I will have to be the Cynthia Nixon type figure.
I took the quiz and it said that I was Hitler, so I don't think I should work in politics.
I think you took the wrong quiz.
No, it was the Sex and the City quiz, but I just...
It was a very specific question.
- There's only one exact order of questions
you have to answer.
- Yeah, and then you get, fuck dude, Hitler again?
Took the office quiz, took the Buzzfeed food quiz,
took the, I'm gonna Hitler every time, dude.
- You know, they say New York City is the fifth character
in Sex and the City, but the sixth character is Adolf Hitler.
(laughing)
I just need to Cosmos so bad right now.
(laughter)
- I just need to get fucked.
- He's just like horribly green screened in.
- Sex, the city, and Hitler.
- Screw him, let's go downtown.
- Samantha, what are you doing on Staten Island?
- You're dating a bartender?
No honey.
Or Samantha, what are you doing in the firehouse? You cannot go in the firehouse, Samantha.
I should probably watch Sex and the City.
I've been watching it with my roommates.
Yeah?
Yeah, you guys jack off together to it?
No, we don't jack off. We watch it for the story.
There's got to be some nudity in that damn show.
Yeah, there is.
Really? Male or female?
Both.
You see a guy's butt go into a girl's butt.
Are you serious?
That's got to be a first of its kind.
Is it real or is it CG?
Who's to say?
You know they use like different camera angles.
It's practical effects and animatronics enhance with CG like Jurassic Park.
Okay.
Yeah.
All right.
I get it.
So they have butts that are made of metal and they CG the texture onto it.
So the butts in the foreground are animatronic but the butts in the background are CG.
Yeah.
As they run.
It's a John Williams score too.
beautiful it's the new it's the new force awakens one so it sucks so it's
like yeah and there's lightsabers in it too yeah this is all we're still talking
about section the city this is still sex they did it they did a crossover Wow
they did a crossover with Star Wars and also um but but versus but I mean you
You would think like a sequel to Kramer vs. Kramer would be.
Yeah.
You know.
I love that they went the route of setting it in the same universe but completely new
story.
Yeah.
Kramer vs. Kramer, Kenny vs. Spinney and now Butt vs. Butt.
Kramer vs. Kramer I've never seen but what is it?
It's like about a divorce or something?
I had to guess.
It's about two puppets who are fighting.
It's about a divorce but it's like one of those 70s movies where it's like women are
the most evil people on earth yeah yeah like a graduate yeah yeah that's like a
divorce but it's like fucking like Meryl Streep is just like being just insanely
evil sick I think unless she's unless she's a good guy at the end we just say
it's about two Muppets in a boxing match what about two Kramers and they're one
upping each other this has probably been done before they're one upping each
other one up and one upping each other at the laugh factory okay all right well I
think they're one of them already won yeah I would say I don't know how much
better you know about Kramer versus Kessler whoo what about that's how we get
it to work Raymond versus Kramer and great great creation
Cray-Sean versus Kramer and they both are trying to say the N-word as fast as possible.
That might be the worst movie ever that we just came up with.
Rain Man versus Raymond.
Oh no.
Yeah.
How am I supposed to know? He's winning so much at the casino.
1, 2, 3. That's him counting the cards.
Oh god.
Rainman versus Raymond versus Kramer versus
Debra I need you to pick me up at the casino this autistic guy's too good at math
versus Rayman
who has no neck or arms
versus Rabbids
versus Mario Kingdom Battle
that's actually that might be a great game
yeah
oh man why haven't the Rabbids collabed with Seinfeld yet?
it just makes sense
these Rabbids are raving
let me see hold on
not today. Not today. Not today. You say you're speaking Spanish.
No, I'm Jerry Seinfeld.
It just makes that so
don't they start
He would never say that. He would never say that. He would never say Spanish. He doesn't
know Spanish. It just makes sense. No.
K is the deal with El Fudo. No I, Torea. No, he would not say any of this crap.
These are like the three Spanish phrases I remember from Spanish class.
Well yeah there's only one guy in the audience who speaks Spanish so you don't need all the
words and most people understand English.
You're right.
So you've got to pepper them in.
Yeah.
I should learn Spanish pretty soon I think.
I'm planning to learn it tomorrow.
I think about learning Spanish but then I get stressed and I'm like if I learn Spanish
do I start when I speak Spanish do I have to do an accent or do I just talk normal?
Yeah.
Like if I know perfect Spanish will I go into like the bodega and be like "Hola" or will
I say like Ola yeah no that's a big dilemma for a for a it is yeah Feliz
cumpleaños a tea somebody cuz I'm like what you would say Feliz Festivus I am
100% saying all of those phrases wrong yeah well again well that's the third
option I either go Spanish accent my accent or Seinfeld accent. Is it what is
it it's años yeah if you say what if you don't say años and you say anos is
anus. I don't know I know that I know that bitch is punta and then point is
punto and that gets pretty confusing in my volleyball games yeah yeah that I
play yeah with with with Latina Latin Americans. I didn't the thing I didn't
about that because when I go to the skate park there's like a huge they can have
like the like a huge volleyball game there oh they go stupid on that yeah
every weekend yeah and tell you what I accidentally like I don't want to be a
bit of a stickler about the rules but in volleyball you cannot hold the ball for
a full three seconds I would just like to pass that on to the volleyball
community at the Maria Hernandez Park in Bushwick you guys listen I get it it's a
It's a tough game.
Not a lot of tall people playing that over there.
Come on man.
Not a lot of spiking going on.
So you can't just sit there holding the ball man.
I mean I get so heated when I walk by thinking about them just carrying that ball.
Stop!
You're supposed to slap the ball.
Not just.
These are not regulation size.
This is not regulation.
I'm going to take down your net.
That net's coming with me.
You guys are disrespecting this sport.
I'm actually a I'm a volleyball. It's like a bikini. I'm a volleyball
professional. I'll have you know it's like chess where like one of the rules
of chess like the chess foundation or whatever is that you can't disrespect
chess or they'll kick you out. That's how I would bring disrepute upon the
game of chess. I'd go to Union Square to one of those like hustler guys who
plays chess with Taurus, try to get them to disrespect the game and take their
money. Yeah, so that is like the funniest rule. I think dude is a chess
fucking stupid yeah yeah I guess it's kind of stupid you fucker I got your
money I I'm Bobby Fisher yeah you've disrespected my game and now I must kill
you and I and I will be destroying you in hand and I will be I will be playing
you we're sending you to chest how he comes out on like a big like nightpiece
hello Bobby Fisher I have to kill you he walks towards you and then he turns left
and walks like 10 feet to the side.
(laughter)
No, he's over here!
And then he's like, "Wait a second."
And then he turns and walks again, and then he just
is making L-shapes all over the place trying to get to you.
Can we go to him?
This sucks.
And then he gets up to you and he goes, "My dick, your mouth."
"My dick to your mouth, right now."
And you're trying to walk to him, but you can only move--
Just get off the fucking horse, Bobby!
You can only move diagonally.
Just get off of it!
thing and it makes me worse than a lot of other crap I have to do I'm sorry what
did he do Bobby Fischer is like a psycho right like the chess master yeah yeah
yeah you got to be psycho you got it I mean you have to be cut there it's like
Michael Jordan yeah yeah but you're like what did he like would like mentally
fuck with like his opponents yeah like he wouldn't show like apparently he would
apparently he was so psycho when he would get nervous you'd imagine them naked
it yeah you know chess is a psycho game because it's for nerds but it's also
it's for the kind of nerds that don't like games with like dragons and yeah
it's for nerds like it's like our yeah exactly it's a yeah it's like killing
people in D&D but I hate my imagination yeah yeah I wish it was just a bunch of
like horses and yeah exactly white guys I wish I could slay pawns yeah yeah the
scariest thing about chess to me probably like is that I don't know how to play
yeah I don't know probably man while you were slaying pawns I was out slaying
poon I'll tell you what. Damn dude if Bobby was here right now he would kill me
he would kill you for disrespecting the game of chess. I'll never join a chess tournament.
You know we if any of us ever enter a chess tournament somebody could just clip that
last couple of minutes yeah and just play it on a I mean that's that's how that's
how people should be playing like high-level chess is just like yeah do
like hire a private investigator record everything they say like wait for them
to say like I don't want to play chess tomorrow I'm too tired I don't mean I
can't it that'll be the evolution of chess is that eventually in a hundred
years it was a game of intelligence yeah like like intelligence gathering where
you'll have to get. I like that you do that there's like there's like a referee. Yeah.
You could show that too. You have to get opposition research on your opponent.
The games are never played. It's just about who can argue better than the
person disrespecting you. This would be like the XFL for chess I think. The XFL for
chess would be sick. Yeah. Like the pieces like the cooler pieces like instead
like instead of the pawn it's the soldier. Yeah. Right. Yeah. So. Oh. Pacific soldiers.
Yeah, instead of the king, the emperor.
Mm-hmm.
The dark emperor.
George W. Bush is the king.
Maybe the XFL for chess is you get to like, you own different, like, novelty chess games.
And then like, you have like the Star Wars one, you have like the Harry Potter one, you
have like all the fucking ones.
And then you just like mix.
You can mix and match.
You can build your team.
Mix and match, yeah.
Build a team.
It's like Warhammer.
Yeah.
Out of the chess pieces from other chess games.
That's the thing, there's no regulation on the size of those chess boards, I think.
Yeah, there's no rule that says I can't bring my 3,000 foot by 3,000 foot chess board to the tournament.
Exactly. Still has the standard square size, too.
When I unfold it, nobody else can fit in the room and I win the tournament by default.
True, yeah. Ah, it appears we're at a bit of an impasse here.
Well, I mean, I'm down to play. I know this board like the back of my hand.
Yeah, I'm bringing my maze board.
board yeah but you might be but you might be lost so your pawn is clipping through
the chessboard you turned on no clip here's what you're making as many moves
as you you're making another way to metagame it is you you put you coat each
piece in poison right and then you you you train in a new one just like poison
damage true yeah yeah get some DOT on there no you train an immunity to the
poison. Yeah, you took me out but you also took poison damage. You use like an Amazon
frog with a poison coating. You take that off and put it on each and every piece
and then you train an immunity by taking a little bit by touching a little bit on
your penis every day. The first time you try to train immunity you just die. Yeah
and then you lose the game so that's that maybe is the future of chess. Chess
mate. Chess mate. They really fucked up by not calling it chess mate when you win.
That's a very good point. Yeah and then right before Chessmate, chess.
You're in chess you better do something. You might be in Chessmate pretty soon.
Yeah. Checkmate. It was originally chess played. Yeah. Because that's what you say when you
finish the game. And then well before that it was a guy who wasn't friendly enough. He had just
invented chess and he called it Chessmate. Yeah. And before that it was probably nothing
because the game didn't exist before that. Yeah it was checkers before that. Yeah.
- Yeah, checkers mate.
- Checkers mate.
- There's a lot of, there was like a pizza place
in my hometown called Checkmate Pizza.
- Really, was it kind of the intellectual
hot spot of New Hampshire?
- Why would you name your pizza place after chess?
- You wanna become smart and you wanna
attract a smart clientele, you know?
- Yeah.
- You want people who can read the menu.
Know how to read the menu.
- Yeah, I guess it's a good name for a pizza place,
but like, you know what's a better name for a chess store?
- Yeah. - That's true.
- Checkmate Pizza. - You could never call
a chess store-- - What's a better name
for a chess store? (laughs)
- You could never call a chess store Domino's.
- It's a chess supply store called Checkmate Pizza.
- Maybe it was a knockoff of Domino's.
- Oh. - Oh shit.
That's exactly what it was.
- That's actually pretty smart.
- God damn it. - Those guys do play chess.
They're playing chess with Domino's.
Domino's.
They're playing fucking 3D chess with Domino's.
Oh my god, dude.
They're in Domino's fucking head right now.
Holy shit, well they're out of business now.
I guess no one else fucking picked up on that.
ChessMate.
Yeah, I think maybe Checkmate is a little too far from Domino's for that one.
Yeah.
Call it like...
Mahjong Pizza.
Yeah.
Chinese Checkers Pizza.
It might be good too.
Is that what it's...
Chinese Checkers, is that what it's still called?
Chinese Checkers?
Yeah.
You think they maybe changed it?
I think there is another name for it, but I don't remember what it...
I think, yeah.
I think check.
I thought Chinese food was so cool.
Did they change Chinese food to something more PC maybe?
What? Yeah, wait. I know there's another name for...
It is not Mancala. That's a different game.
No, that's a completely different game.
Mancala is fun though.
Yeah.
It's one of the only games with holes in it.
Sternholme.
Oh, that's a cooler name.
Sternholme, commonly known as Chinese Checkers, US and Canadian spelling,
or Chinese CheckWars, UK spelling.
Is it strategy board game of German origin?
Oh, so that's probably why they're
That's probably why it's called Chinese checkers. They just made it up so
they could sell it. Yeah, those German bastards. Those fucking Nazis. I hate them.
Yeah.
They knew, they jumped on the Chinese bandwagon. They made their checkers
non-German. It should have been German checkers, dude.
What are these guys doing? Well, then it would be confusing. It is funny, yeah, German people made it
And it's shaped like a Star of David. Yeah, just just was mixing a lot of stuff here. Uh-huh. Yeah, what was it?
What's the year of origin? Let's see. It's a scary question
1892 okay dodge don't blow. Yeah, I mean we I don't know why I feel like we would have been in trouble for figuring that out
Honestly, I feel like we would have gotten in a little bit of trouble for that, huh? Yeah, so that's a relief I
I don't even remember how to play Chinese. I don't think I ever knew how to play it. I
just thought the board and like little marble things were really cool. I was like, it's
like one of those things where it's like, damn, this is like, this is probably the coolest
game ever because of how many colors and designs there are. Yeah. Like it's like when you get
one of those like, like fancy nerd board games as a kid, but you never like actually learn
how to play it. And you're just like, like, damn, this game has three decks of cards.
You know what was always the game that I never ever played right was a mousetrap.
Yeah, of course.
Yeah.
When you buy a mousetrap you just do the mousetrap.
Why would you ever...
I'm trying to catch a real mouse over here.
I want to move a piece around the board too.
Dude.
Yeah, I never understood mousetrap.
I want to wait for 30 minutes before I get to use the mousetrap.
Yeah, what the fuck?
How stupid is that, dude?
I remember I bought mousetrap at a yard sale and they had the board but not the trap stuff
in it.
that sucks. You're just playing sorry. You ever play, you guys ever play like rummy? Yeah,
I love gin rummy. I had a gin rummy phase for a while. Oh yeah, my family, we had a huge,
I forget how to play it every time, so I have to relearn how to play rummy. But then when
I get into it, I'm like, "Duh, fuck you. I'm the best rummy player there's ever been."
You guys ever play pitch? No. That's a fun one. What is that? It's a card game. Explain
I don't remember how to play it. Okay. It's a trick taking game. You guys ever play NERTS?
No. You guys ever play tag?
There was Rummy Cube too, which was like a yeah. Yeah, I I had a
We had these like things I think they were called electives
They were either called electives or some other bullshit in fourth and fifth grade
and I never got to pick mine because of I
Just knew I didn't if you didn't do your homework or if you had like a below a C or something
you would not get your first pick in those.
And I got like, I had to do board game club in fourth grade.
- I did board game club.
- But it was like different things,
where it was like for a couple weeks,
it was like, oh, you could go learn this.
So I had to do board game club,
and then fifth grade I wanted to be in the AV club thing.
But they got rid of that,
so then I had to pick like three,
you would pick three,
and then depending on how your grades were
or if the class got filled up.
- Yeah.
We never had an AV club at my school,
which was so fucked up.
Got robbed of so much nostalgia, so much stranger things.
- So many cool cameras and shit.
- Fourth grade I played Rummikub.
- So many fun projectors to look at.
- And then fifth grade, because my grades were bad,
I put design your room club,
which was like, it was like a thing,
like a that was like my third choice but I got it and I was like this is actually
kind of sick. My first choice. And it just taught me how to do interior design and
then I made like we had to make a shoebox diorama of what we wanted our
room to look like. Is that why you have such a beautiful room right now? Mm-hmm.
It's so gorgeous when I walk in there. Yeah, because I learned how to do
interior design in fifth grade and I've never left a fifth graders interior design.
We had that activity in like math class where it was like a geometry thing where
like you have to like measure the area like we did it so yeah yeah the area was
too yeah but it's everyone's just like yep and here's the bedroom here's the
bathroom and then here's the 5,000 foot by 5,000 foot amusement park room like
literally every person in the class was like I have an idea that nobody else is
gonna have which is I'm gonna make the biggest room ever and it's gonna have a
roller coaster dude I need I need to make enough money that I can build a house I
remember there was I need to build some kind of fucked up there was one weird
kid who wanted to put a secret window into the bathroom.
(laughter)
- And he just told everybody?
He was like, when I built this house.
- He was like, sixth grade, yeah.
I just remembered that he wanted to have a room
that was like, it was like all glass
that you could see out of but couldn't see into.
- It was a qu--
- That's early for that, too.
- Yeah, it's real early, dude.
- Sixth grade, that's trouble.
- Dude, there's a record store in my hometown
where the owner got in trouble for putting cameras in the bathroom.
Chuck Berry's record store.
But his excuse was he was like, "Yeah, what if somebody goes in there and steals and puts
a record in their shirt?
What if someone puts a record in their ass or their vagina?"
"Hey, what if my toilet gets clogged?
Do you ever think about that, judge?"
"We want to put up a sign for the wanted man who clogged my damn toilet."
"That'd be bad news, dude."
"All right, fine.
We'll compromise.
the cameras in but I'll put cameras in my office and monitors in the bathroom so
we can see each other we know yeah yeah there's a connection yeah create a Skype
call between a computer in the bathroom this is a big TV screen that's just his
face just not blinking I hope you're not trying to steal anything in here and I
a normal shit or piss I hope you don't overuse the toilet paper because we would
we do take inventory it's one where one lie one ply no folding oh no folding
yeah that's a dude one ply toilet paper and if you use the if you use the the
hand dryers you have to blow some air back into the they're like an air
mattress you have to you don't get free air yeah I put a straw in them you have
to fill them back up no I was just thinking about maybe this is like very
stupid where's that air coming from intake it intakes the air and blows it
out you know like a vacuum opposite of a vacuum okay really angry guy behind it
well the older the older the older looking ones I don't know why I got this
into my head but I thought that maybe they had to like put like a you know
like how it's like a house will have like a vacuum sometimes built into the house
uh central back yeah central back i thought it was like one of those
situations where they would put like a central air maybe i mean i don't know i'm
i assume it just says like a vent on the bottom but i've never like
really put my face up close to a public bathroom
hand dryer really you've never put your mouth on it no i did that once
i've never done that i made your mouth blow blow blow my face back guys look
I can make my tongue is licking the inside of the one you say that I did
used to play that game.
Did you yeah?
I would draw I would I would pad my tongue down with my shirt dry if I
get it really really dry.
It is funny because then you can get it to like stick to your face.
Yeah, yeah, and I'm like damn.
I got damn a lizard in my house.
Fuck look how dehydrated I can get you know, I can make rocks in my
wiener.
My body can make rocks.
What can you do?
You rocking with me?
I thought that a hand dryer would blow my face back like a leaf blower.
Yeah, if a good one can.
Yeah, and I put my face up to that thing and just got hot air on my mouth.
Yeah, doesn't feel good.
His walkout looking like Freddy Krueger.
Yeah.
It's gross.
It was probably the grossest thing I've ever done.
Because immediately it was at a place.
You fingered my wall.
That's fine.
I'm making love to your house, baby.
That's not love dude, nothing lovely about a finger.
I mean that's part of living in New York, is it's like you know.
You can't, you can never, fingering is never romantic.
Fingering is always just like necessity.
Nothing lovely about a finger.
It's like eating a hot dog.
Yeah, yeah.
What do you mean eating a hot dog is romantic?
Eating like a hot dog out of a cart.
It's like yeah, I have two dollars, like I don't have time for something more involved
in this, I can't sit down at a restaurant.
That's basically what fingering is, you realize that?
Fingering is hot dogs.
is at 100% hot dogs yeah but but normal sex is hamburger that's hamburger that's
a sit-down hamburger that's five guys and and then the back door that's got to be
some dessert because it's just too damn sweet chocolate pudding that's gotta be
like poop pudding yeah almost yeah you know and then oral sex that's brushing
your teeth that's like yeah that's probably like brushing your teeth and
To me, sex is all filing your taxes.
Really?
You might have some sort of mental issue then.
Yeah?
Yeah.
You might be allergic to sex like a Weezer song.
That's true, I might be.
I think I'm working on a kidney stone right now.
Maybe even a kidney geode is being created in my body right now due to all the red thunder
I'm drinking.
I would love to make a kidney coin.
Yeah.
Did you say a kidney bitcoin?
A kidney coin.
Kidney corn? Coin?
Kidney corn.
Sounds pretty damn good actually.
[Burps]
Can we pause and pee real quick?
Yeah. Nice.
Ready to fall in love.
Okay, I just got powered up by a shit that I took.
Oh, I'm ready to fall in love all over again.
Dana just texted me, apparently on her way to work
a bird pooped on her head and she started crying.
Aww.
You guys are supposed to laugh at her.
That sucks. And then she tripped and she broke all her teeth.
teeth that's right that's right yeah yep she got hit back and forth by buses
going opposite directions on the street and just got like ping-pong like a
similar like in Sin City yeah exactly she's got hit back and forth for like a
couple hours and then Elijah would came out with these long sharp fingernails and
he yeah he's wearing shiny anime glasses and he kidnapped her and then city hey
buddy you tell my damn wife right now I'm talking about Elijah would oh cool
That's actually pretty cool. Yeah I'd be honored if Elijah Wood would kidnap my
wife. You guys remember Elijah Woods character in Sin City right? Yeah. He's
like the serial killer who was like a pet wolf and like I was like I was
arguing with people online because I was like I thought that he was supposed to
be like a wolf man because he has like claws and he has like a pet wolf and he
eats people. Yeah. Everyone's like no he's just like a serial killer and I was
like no he's clearly supposed to be like something because he also like move he
like dashes super fast and she runs like a dog and then I looked up and it was
like Frank Miller has said that everyone in Sin City is human except for Kevin
who is a demon. Just demon? Yeah he was a demon. Frank Miller's a he's a he's a guy
huh? He's a freak. He's quite the freak. I don't know much about him but I do know that he
like cast magic on women or something right? Yeah. He wanted to make
Batman fight the Taliban and they wouldn't let him. Was that him? That's
hilarious. That's sick. He wanted to make a comic called...
I want to double check. It's called Batman vs. Taliban. It was
called Holy Terror Batman. Sick. And then they wouldn't let him make it so
he just made a book. Yeah he just made something that doesn't have...
has a Batman ripoff in it called Holy Terror. They didn't want Batman to get
involved. They didn't want Batman to get political. They didn't want a Batman Jihad.
Batman likes terrorism. That was one thing in the DC Universe.
He probably does like terrorism, doesn't he?
Yeah, because he gets to fight it.
True.
I mean, you know, when your whole industry is fighting crime, you start to love it.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Terror is what made him into Batman, his terror of bats.
You know, Batman is a terrorist.
Yeah, in a way, I would say.
Terrorists.
Terror rich.
Wow.
Can we just let-
You know we watched that freestyle video and now I'm just trying to spit bars off my dome.
We need to have a freestyle workshop.
I'm trying to get spit on my dome.
Patrick, ball sack.
My ball sack, I just took a crap.
I got shit on my sack.
Wipe back on my ass.
shit on my crack. Broke my back. Trying to wipe. I tried to bend over and wipe. Broke
my back. Bend over back. With my sack. Stuck up my ass. Yeah. I broke my back. Smoking crack.
Straight drop from the top.
Nope, you just, you just,
hop on, pop.
- Give me one.
- Christmas.
- I just celebrated my favorite holiday, Christmas.
Buying presents is of my family business.
- Yes.
- Blib, blib, blib, blib, blib, blib, blib, blib, blib.
- That works?
- And I just, I opened my stocking on Christmas.
My wish list for Christmas was my family business.
My family business was writing my wish list.
Buying presents.
Presents for my...
Uh huh.
(farting noises)
Fuck.
Sorry, I couldn't resist.
Your rhymes are so fire you made Caleb pop and lock.
Damn.
Dude, I think I got...
Wait, guys.
I think I got locked in one position.
I can't pop anymore.
I think I ran out of hydraulic juice.
Hit the reset button.
it's on the back of my head. Did you guys play Animal Crossing on GameCube?
Do you have a paper clip? Animal Crossing? No, I was a boy growing up.
You can be a boy in that game. Oh really? Yeah. Yeah, I wouldn't know.
I made my town, my first town name, because you have to use like a whole memory card for
that. I remember I made a town called, because I thought, my neighbor said Gonads, and in
my head I misheard him. I thought he said Gones. And he's like, Gones means nuts. So
I named my town Gones and my mom was like what why did you name it that I was like
don't worry I I named my my hit Mon Lee on my Pokemon
whatever fire red I named him kick-ass when I was eight and because I guess
fucking yeah cuz he kicks ass and then my mom was like hey you should show me
your Pokemon game and I deleted my save file it was like I ain't fucking I don't
want that smoke.
But um, the reason I brought up Animal Crossing, you guys ever fucked up in like Reset and then
that Resetti guy shows up?
I never played Animal Crossing.
How many times do I have to tell you, we were raised boys.
Yeah.
Well, I don't know.
I wasn't raised as some fucking girl, okay?
I was raised as a boy.
I ate ground beef every meal.
That was a good, the Resetti song?
I was allowed to piss in the sink.
You know what I'm saying?
You understand?
I love interior design and catching bugs!
Yeah, wait, you did take an interior design class and then you played Animal Crossing?
It's true.
Nice, dude.
Hey, did you guys ever play Barbie Dress-Up growing up?
I did.
Yeah, I bet you did, girl.
Yeah, on Game Boy.
And as an adult, you sit with all your roommates watching Sex and the City?
Uh-huh.
I'm putting the puzzle pieces together right now.
I think you could have, in fact, been a woman this whole time.
Which is fine, you know?
I've had a bad attitude all day because I've been PMSing.
So maybe.
Patrick mood sour.
Yeah, that's right.
That's right.
Dude, I feel like there has to be, the scientists have to discover.
A pill that makes it so your period doesn't happen?
No, they have to discover like a male PMS thing that goes on.
Men have mixed PMS.
Yeah, there's times of the month where I'm like, I'm just a nasty little bitch right now.
You know? I need an excuse, but it can't be like, my ass hurts.
Yeah.
You know? I need a chemical excuse.
I lost my video game.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I need something where I can every month, I have like a week.
Well, for men, what that is, is withdrawal.
From Will Ferrell movies.
Yeah.
Sorry, it's a time of the month where I haven't been able to see a Will Ferrell movie
recently so i old-school dvd got scratched yeah have really spent watching
talladega nights at often recently been missing my weekly talladega nights
rewatch so
yeah i might be a little sorry might be a little mad right now
you know what they call it though
p_n_ messing
like your penis
yeah messing to call it will they'll call it will ferrell
f_e_r_a_l_
okay i'll tell you that i don't know if they're ok will be will be feral
Will Ferrell, yeah.
That's pretty good actually.
I'm starting to like that more.
Yeah, sorry.
That's what happens when a group of guys don't watch a goddamn Will Ferrell comedy from 2004.
Sorry, I didn't even really get a chance to watch the blooper reels either, so I'm not
feeling very good.
I've been in such a bad mood.
I haven't laughed my ass off in Stranger than Fiction in a minute, so, you know.
I'm in such a bad mood.
it's been a second since I watched everything must go and get to see the unrated anchor man
everything must go bewitched I mean these are the movies that keep me alive you know yeah
you guys see anchored man too no oh yeah saw it in the theaters with my cousin I saw it in theaters
too yeah I thought I saw it in theaters like the day after saw it in theaters but it was like my
first time hanging out with this guy who uh we ended up being very close friends his name was
was Will Ferrell but he like he like talked a lot during the movie and I got
so mad during Anchorman 2 yeah because he was like look he's singing about a
shark. He's like you fucking I'm gonna kill you. He was my best friend for years.
Yeah. Yeah. Noah? No. You don't know this guy? Being a movie talker is awesome. I
love being a movie talker. Yeah. I like pissing people off. Yeah I know it's also
It's a funny thing for people to get mad at cuz yeah, especially if they've seen the movie before yeah
It's like who gives a fuck. I'm a really bad movie talker, but I also get mad when people talk
Yeah, the worst the worst guy. I forget what movie it was
It was some like weird action movie that I think James McAvoy was in or it was just I don't remember
I have to fucking wanted what movie it was wanted might have been no definitely wasn't wanted
It was some PG-13 action movie from like 2008. I'll have to look that up.
But it was like me and like a group of my friends. The McAvoy ultimatum.
That's a really good one. Like it was a bunch of kids at the movie theater
and then we found there's like a group of like
high schoolers in front of us and then we thought it would be funny to just piss them off the whole time.
So we were just like like like literally just like making it just the worst movie experience.
Yeah. Yeah. For these high schoolers. Yeah. And like I was singing at one point.
(laughing)
♪ McAvoy, oh McAvoy ♪
- I was singing Green Day, I was singing
♪ Dearly beloved ♪
(humming)
- Jesus of Suburbia part four.
- And the guy turned around and was like,
"Were you just singing?"
And I was like, "No, I have no idea what you're talking about."
- No, dude.
- They must have got the rights for that song for the movie.
- 'Cause that was in the movie right then.
- It's part of the movie, dude.
- I remember when I saw Hereditary in the theater
for the first time, there were a bunch of high schoolers
in the theater, and you know how the trailer
for that movie. Like it was like they may look like the little girl was creepy
and like it had a bunch of like yeah, that was the thing in the trailer. So
like the entire movie they were sitting in like the front and just like going
like to each other and like laughing like and then they were like doing that
literally just for like the whole movie and then the like the this the scene in
the car don't spoil it. This the beheading scene came on and they're just
dead. So for the rest of the movie
That was a weird movie. That was the first time I went to see like a horror movie in
theaters and everybody just laughed the entire time. It was so bizarre.
Yeah, you went to the twisted theater. Yeah, I must have gone to an evil theater
because people thought that crap was funny. That was maybe one of the
most fun movies to see in theaters because you could
tell which people were seeing it for the first time. Yeah.
Yeah, it's so fun to just hear it like here an entire crowd just go like oh
Rewind that and change it yeah
Yeah, I think I've talked about this before but like a like just an activity that we would do in middle school was
Try to get kicked out of the movies. Yeah, like it's fun. Yeah. Yeah, so we would go see bad
We go jack each other up you go see bad
Blow each other is fuck each other in the movies me and my friends as a joke and then like yeah
You get kicked out and then you wait in the lobby for your friends to come back. Yeah, so we got kicked out of like
the last song
Starring Miley Cyrus. Yeah, you go there you spend like ten dollars that your parents give you
For did you know the movie is like, okay, you're gonna go have like a you're gonna go see the movie
I miss when they were fucking ten dollars. Yeah shit, dude. Well, it wasn't even $10. It was $8
Yeah, $2 is for snacks. Yeah
So your mom drops you off and she's like, oh this is like, you know, your movie night with your friends like no mom
I'm going to get kicked out of the movie. Little. Do you know you simple? You know, I'm gonna be so funny
They kicked me out
I'm gonna do the funniest Lenny Bruce shit in the world in the movie theater
I'm gonna go stand up and I'm gonna kick out of the movie in front of the projector and would be like
How many y'all like sex and they're gonna fucking throw me they're gonna pick me up on my collar
and they're gonna get a big guy I'm gonna get up there airbrush suit with my face
on it uh-huh I'm gonna say my friend brought his drum set damn dude I need to
do something like that now this thing that's happening again dude I gotta get
I got I gotta fucking start doing that kind of shit you get a real chance to
reinvent yourself as a comedian now mm-hmm it's like you haven't done it in
while I could do some Bernie Mac shit. Did you see that Tony Hinchcliffe video? No, did
he do Bernie Mac? Did he steal me? He just said he was racist to an Asian guy. Oh yeah,
see that? I would probably not do that. That would probably be the last thing I would do.
That's what he's doing now. I'd probably do something really not racist like pretend to
be Bernie Mac. Yeah. Alright, peace. Peace. Bye.