You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[Loud explosion]
Welcome to the podcast about Caleb's peeing penis.
Oh, fuck.
They fucked up, man. They really fucked up this time.
They gave me a regular coke.
Pat, stop.
Stop what?
Pat keeps trying to call on Skype from his phone to interrupt the podcast and sabotage...
Sabotage my Coke moment.
I'm not trying to sabotage anything.
I'm trying to make the show better.
Yeah?
By including an extra Skype source.
Including another guest, which is also me.
Saying the exact same thing at the exact same time.
Pat, does it look like, when I hold this little Coke can, does it look like I'm the biggest
guy on earth?
No.
That looks like a regular Coke can and your hand is small.
(laughing)
- Take it, okay.
Can we stop the podcast?
- No.
- Okay, can you take that back on air then?
- Huh?
- Can you reverse what you said?
- I can't hear you anymore, I think.
- You think what?
- I can hear Cameron, but I can't hear you.
- What?
That's impossible.
- Yeah, I can't hear you either, Caleb.
- Oh.
This Coke is making me too strong.
- The Coke is making Caleb invisible.
- It's giving me ESP powers.
Yeah, ESP powers. That's what you get when nobody can hear you.
This is the most amazing thing. I've been drinking only strictly, I've been on a strict
diet Coke diet for about a month now and now I'm, this is my first real Coke in a long
time.
I don't know if I've ever drank Coke.
Do it.
No.
Come on.
You expect me to just drink, to ruin a streak of over 20 years just right now because you
want me to?
No, I'm not gonna drink the coke.
Just try it.
I want my first time to be special.
This is special.
It's recorded.
You'll always remember it.
Yeah, yeah.
No.
Come on.
This is Cameron's first time drinking.
I don't wanna drink it.
Why?
It'll kill me.
I hope so.
Come on.
A little sip of coke.
Drink it right now.
Or I'll...
Oh my God.
He's gonna light himself on fire.
Patrick's gonna light himself on fire.
Come on.
I'm gonna light myself on fire.
Alright.
We're doing a first time ever coke review.
I'll drink it really close to the...
I'm gonna spill it all over the microphone.
Okay.
- Oh, it smells bad.
- It just tastes, I promise it tastes good.
- I accidentally smelled it.
It smells gross.
- Don't worry about the smell.
Okay, so the smell review is taken care of.
Now move on to taste.
- Wait, should we get him a glass?
- No, 'cause I still want the Coke.
- I'm gonna pour it out on the ground if I don't like it.
- Can we get him his own?
- I don't think so, unless he really likes it.
- He's drinking too much of it.
- No, yeah, I don't like that at all.
- What do you think?
- Actually, I think I have had Coke,
I think I've had it mixed with like with some kind of adult drink. Now that I think
about it, I drink coke every day. By adult drink I mean cum. The ultimate adult drink.
The ultimate adult beverage. What age do you have to turn before you can drink cum?
18. 12. 18? You're a little backwards. You think 18 year olds should drink cum? Huh?
Okay, so in Patrick's words, 18 year olds should be chugging cum daily?
That's kind of fucked up, Pat.
Yeah, man.
That's not that fucked up.
That's of legal age.
That's actually barely legal age.
Yeah, that's of barely legal age.
Nice.
Yeah, I don't like regular coke.
It's too sweet and also-
Because you're drinking it out of the can.
What do you mean?
It tastes different.
God, you're a human fucking crack.com article.
I'm not a human crack.com article.
You absolutely are.
You take that back.
Yeah.
Tell me about ten times Einstein really wasn't that smart.
God damn it, dude.
That's a really mean thing to say to him.
Coke tastes different in a can than it does in a glass bottle.
That's true.
How would you know?
You're so owned.
You eat it.
Tell me how you would know.
Tell me.
Yeah, how could you possibly figure that out?
It tastes different.
Yeah, oh and you've tried it?
No.
No, didn't think so.
I'm sorry.
The sugar is making me lash out a bit.
I haven't had sugar in so long.
You have sugar rage.
I'm getting a sugar rage.
I feel a sugar rage coming on.
I do, sugar does, it does get me.
Yeah, I've noticed.
I don't like hanging out with you right after you drink coke.
Yeah, it's not fun.
I do get a little weird.
You just go, "Oh yeah, is that true?
And you're gay?
And that's it?
Huh?
Yeah?
Yeah?"
It's tapping a button on the podcast.
You're actually doing an impression of yourself.
Fuck.
See, sugar makes me a genius.
I have sugar brain.
I have sugar genius.
- Today, I texted you guys this, but I thought it was so funny that today I had a 1-800 flowers
order that is coming in for my girlfriend's birthday and they called me today from a number
- Is that what you just said?
- No, I did not say boyfriend, I said girlfriend.
- You said girlfriend's boyfriend?
- Yeah, my girlfriend's boyfriend.
- You ordered flowers for yourself?
- You got your girlfriend's boyfriend a bunch of flowers?
- Yeah, I did.
Yeah, he's gonna be pumped.
a bunch of flowers but it's a it's or it's orange flowers inside of a small
bonsai tree that has been cut to look like Master Chief's helmet. Damn that
sounds sick. Dude I would love I don't understand bonsai trees at all I don't
know why they stay small. They're trees? But why are they so small? Well they it's
probably in the DNA of the tree. If I had to make a scientific guess. I'm no expert but if I had to
guess it's DNA it's probably a psychological thing it was a big tree
got bit by a small by a bug and it split the difference it became a small tree a
bug had sex with the tree oh so what yeah tell it to the tell it to the fans
cuz Cameron I already heard oh yeah yeah yeah so the 1-800 flowers called me from
a number that was listed as potential spam which is when I should have started
recording my screen, but I just didn't even think about it. And I answered it
and it was a woman and I didn't-- she had a very heavy Indian accent. I hate that
all my stories have accents I can't do. It sucks! But it was-- and then she was
like, "Hey, do you have an order coming in?" And I was like, "Yeah." And she's like,
"There's a card attached to it that you wrote, correct?" And I was like,
"Yeah." And she's like, "Okay, I just want to confirm that this is what you meant to
write on the card and then she proceeded to read the first like two lines of I
Miss You by Blink-182. She was like, "Hello there, the angel from my nightmare, the
shadow in the background of the morgue." And she was like, "Did you mean to write
this?" And I was like, "Huh, I was like, 'Can you keep going? Because I want to make
sure it's correct.'" And she was like, "Yes, of course, sir. The unsuspecting victim of
darkness in the valley we can live like Jack and Sally if you want and you can
always find me and we'll have Hallowreen on Christmas. That's how she said it.
Hallowreen on Christmas. And she just sang the entire thing.
No, she didn't sing it. That'd be cool. That'd be funnier.
She hands the phone to Mark Hoppus. Yes. Dude, what the F is he doing nowadays?
fucking aliens he's having a cool haircut which is it Tom DeLonge or Mark
Hoppus? Tom DeLonge. Who's into it? Tom? Yeah. Dude I love Blink-182. I never got
into them. That's crazy. Never listened to them. I got into them because they had all those
songs that were like... I loved to skateboard. What's that song? Mother's Day? Mother's Day?
Is that the I want to fuck a dog in the ass one? No no I want to fuck a dog in
the ass is called I want to fuck a dog. You're right. You're right. That's my yeah
they also have one that is Mother's Day the one that's uh... Mother's Day the one
that's like it goes sucking and fucking and touching sucking and fucking and
touching yeah it's Mother's Day yeah that's pretty cool the Mark Tom and
Travis show album is that what that's called the one that's the live album?
The Griffin, Justin and Travis album? Yeah Travis McElroy the drummer. Yeah I'm thinking it's Mother's Day.
Yeah, they did one song sucking and fucking and sucking and fucking I wanna fuck a dog in the ass
they
Doggo in the ass
The my brother my brother and me
special
They did a Blake when I - did one song that was just it was like all it was like Carlin's words
You can't say on TV. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's a good one
Yeah, it's a good one. Let's play it over this. Let's listen to it. If you have never listened
to... yeah, we can play it. We've never played Blink-182 on the podcast. They can't get us
on Patreon. Yeah, we're safe. They have no control. We're not making money off of this.
Exactly. Yeah. This is the one part of it we don't make money off of. Gotcha, bitch. Yeah.
We find out that all along Black Cool Man was Tom Delonge who's been monitoring.
He subscribes to every single Patreon just in case somebody uses one of the songs.
Yeah, just in case someone plays "I Wanna Fuck a Dog in the Ass."
I wanna fuck a dog in the ass, I wanna fuck a dog.
Is that how it goes?
Yeah.
It seems kind of boring, there's no guitars or anything.
Yeah, it sounds exactly like that.
I wanna fuck a...
(Suck a mother fucker, teeth spark, turn into twat)
Shit, piss, fuck, cum, cock, sucker, motherfucker.
That was it.
And then that video, that video starts out with this picture.
What is it?
So sick.
I can't see it.
Okay, so...
Oh, it's like a cool haircut?
Yeah, it's a cool haircut.
It's a picture of a cool haircut.
Damn, I love when they put cool haircuts in music videos.
Did you guys have Myspaces?
MySpace is no I did yeah yeah I can't I found my brother my brother's old one the
other day or the other day I mean like two months ago that's the other day dude
it's I'm yeah it's it's a bummer that just like every two years growing up I
would like scrub basically my entire existence on the internet because like
my myspace isn't around anymore I had it so that when you went to my page on
myspace it would play that like ringtone rap song that was like I got your my
space put me on your top eight and it would play that over and over and over
again and there's no option to turn it off I wish we're still like that yeah
yeah just play music yeah just terrible design my cousin my cousin had like a
meatloaf song he had paradise by the dashboard light and you couldn't shut
that off his page that's pretty cool Pat you're having fun imagining that your
head your headphone strings are like really thin rat tails like two rat
tails coming off your head yeah that'd be a really cool look that would be cool
and they join you should get dude you should grow it a rat tail my god and
then I grow in your phone there's a guy at work the other day who came in like
an old guy and he just had like a fucking Padawan tail but he had like
really curly hair pimp so he just had one braided bead on the back of his head
yeah I went on a cruise when I was a kid and I came back with some
braids nice dude yeah I want to grow I want to people at school went nuts for
that shit dude they were mad at you no they loved it dude no they got mad this
was before all that bullshit this mayo ass white boy yeah coming back from
Jamaica and yeah and I'd explain no no I paid a slave for dollars for these well
that's not a slave you're right yeah yeah I paid your mom I paid my mom four
dollars and she paid the slave you got me that was that that cruise was the
first time I ever saw stand-up comedy immediately when it got brave to be a
comedian is what I have to do it was this like terrible cruise comic and I
remember he had a he had like a like a regular show and then my dad was like
yeah I'm I'm busy tonight which like nobody's busy on a cruise ever but what
are you doing he's like oh I'm going to see the the late night show from that
comedian we saw earlier and then I asked him later I was like what did he was
like the difference he was like he just like said the f-word like three times
just instead of like saying stinking he was like fucking yeah he had one bit
that I thought was awesome when I was a kid about how he didn't realize you're
supposed to let the conditioner sit in your hair for a little bit before you
wash it out mm-hmm and I think that's the bit that's the whole bit man I didn't
realize yeah well I think it was like and here I am washing the conditioner
out of my hair probably something like that yeah you know any he did a lot of
act outs I bet yeah he did had a big bottle of conditioner yeah it was a prop
yeah yeah and that's the thing about comedy if you don't act it out I don't
know what you're doing exactly if you don't if you have a joke about if you
don't play all of the characters gun if you don't pick up the mic stand and
pretend it's a gun yeah I don't know what the fuck you're doing dude I don't know
what you're doing I don't know yeah yeah if you don't use the chair and pretend
that it's your car and you're driving with the sitting in the stool yeah
pretending to drive so I'm driving no and you sit down you go look I'm in a
car look I'm going around the state room room not even telling a story just
pretending it's a car that's a real comedy if you're talking about a time you
fucked and you don't fuck the stool mmm that's why I have a special hole
installed in the stool I bring a stool with me that is a pussy in it there's a
fleshlight and I fuck it on stage that's a good that's like a good idea for like
Kevin Hart in the middle of an unrelated bit so I was washing my car yeah I know
supposed to leave the conditioner in your hair. You're fucking a pocket pussy
duct-taped to a stool. Yeah this is the late night show get used to it. And this
is my wife. Yeah. Stool. Take my wife please. She's a stool with a pussy
installed. Have you guys ever been on cruises? No. Oh. Because I'm not rich like you dude.
Yeah at the time I was a millionaire. Yeah it was shortly after my parents got
divorced and it was when cruises started getting really cool yeah so they had
like you know water slides and shit on the cruises but this was like a
gambling cruise for like old people and me and my brothers were like the only
kids on the cruise and my dad just watched some naughty comedy and I got
sick and that was the whole... but I did get braids again. Again? Again I got
braids again I kept getting braids every day until I had a full head of it I
looked like Hurricane Chris and then I came out to the States and people said
are you Hurricane Chris said yeah and I said yeah man absolutely and clap um
yeah I don't think I would like a cruise I don't like boats not a boat guy I'm
scared I'm scared yeah I'm scared of the boat I'm scared of my penis fall off
into the water get away from a boat you're gonna fall in you're gonna fall
out of the water oh god I cannot believe how much water there is around the boat
it goes all the way around the boat
we hit a iceberg now
oh no we hit a iceberg
oh god it's so cold
me so gonna die
oh no
I fell off my penis and it fell off the boat.
Oh God!
We've hit an iceberg.
Oh no, have you seen my penis?
Have you seen my penis anywhere?
I think I lost it somewhere on the poopy deck.
I think my penis is on the poopy deck.
Oh Jesus Christ!
My penis fell off.
It fell on the gas pedal for the boat
and it goes straight into the iceberg.
Oh God!
My penis fell off into the chef's...
Whose penis is this?
into the chef's pot and it go into the stew and now everybody's getting sick from my penis.
It is terrible. Have you guys seen Ghost Ship? No. Is that the movie where they get cut in
half? Yes. What is this? Ghost Ship is a movie I've never seen the movie. I've seen the opening
scene a million times and it's just like I guess somebody installed a wire that will cut
in half everybody on this like cruise ship except for one kid who is too short
doesn't reach the height limit for the wire yeah and so everybody just like
falls in to two pieces and it's really cool there I yeah it's it's like cube
cube or like Resident Evil or there's a there that also happens in this movie
tag not the one no no it's the one with Hannibal Burrus yeah yeah there's a
Japanese movie called tag and it's a bunch of like Japanese school girls on a
bus and they and I like you know yeah it like it's like something some like
mysterious wind cuts the bus and I'm just makes no sense one girl like one girl
bends down to like look at something and she sits up and just everyone is just
cut in half it's sick yeah I'll spraying blood everywhere and I'm like damn this
is movies yeah Japanese school girls rules yeah it's a it's like battle royale
and imagine games I'm at a movies imagine if a childhood game of tag extended to
adulthood oh my god yeah and then a bunch of Japanese schoolgirls get cut in
half in the middle for no reason bunch of beautiful Japanese schoolgirls I
didn't understand that scene in tag that intro makes no sense the rest of the
movie I mean yes it was it was sexy yeah what did you I used to play I played tag
or hide-and-seek rather pretty pretty far into pretty close to adulthood yeah
because me and my dad would go camping with you play tag with your dad I play
tag with my MC I found him yet I've been playing for years he we would go camping
with him and his friend and his friend's kids who were like,
one was like a couple years older than me.
And we would play hide and seek
every time we would go camping.
And it was always really fun,
but this kid who was, he was like two years older than me,
until he was like 18, if he lost at tag, he would cry.
- Oh, nice. - Yeah.
- That's sad.
- No, it's not.
- Yeah, it's sad.
I mean, to be that guy, that would be sad.
Yeah, I know, it's sad to be a loser.
- I guess so, yeah.
i wouldn't know
yeah and you know you would know
but i would know
all right i'm opening up on the part of the team and loser okay
you're not sure if you don't touch me
don't touch me and i didn't can't i didn't
consent to playing tags so doesn't count i think you're it right now actually now
and you have to touch and get this you have to touch the president united
states so it's the attitude did not be it that's not the rule that is the
the president. I just touched Patrick. No you didn't. Patrick's the president now.
Yeah Patrick president. Whoever gets tagged is the president. President Patrick.
But Patrick what would you be your first policy? My first policy is I'm not it.
Yeah I'm not it. What is your first policy as president United States? First
policy no tag backs. Fuck. So you can't tag Cameron back then. Yeah that's actually
good for me. Well yeah but if someone tries to tag me. But you're it right now.
Yeah but if I tag Caleb. Then Caleb's president. Like I just did. You didn't tag me.
You didn't tag me. And your policy goes away. Your policy's gone so you're still the president.
What? Fuck you, you're the president still. You idiot. You fucking loser.
Were you, did you sign an executive order that I'm still the president? Yeah.
It's right here. Yeah I just signed it. Ah!
Curses! Ah! Confound it all.
God, there was a guy in my in my high school who legitimately said curses when
he was upset. That's cool. He had something wrong with his brain, though. I
knew this kid in my like high school co-op that I went to in like 2014, I guess,
who told me all the time he was like, "Buy Bitcoin. You have to buy Bitcoin as soon
as possible. Please buy Bitcoin." When it was like $60 and I remember being like,
I don't have fucking $60.
Yeah.
And now he has to be...
Either really rich or very poor.
Yeah, probably really poor.
Did you guys see this video?
No, I didn't see it. I don't see any videos anymore.
That's kind of my thing.
Is it a guy looking at like an Ant-Man costume?
Oh no.
No, he puts a...
It's a fuck doll.
It's a woman going in a hole.
No, it's a real lady.
That's not a real lady.
It's a real lady.
Yeah, it is.
seen thousands of real women in my life I think I would you see now you've seen it
most - yeah you and Patrick check this part out god I'm so good oh my god dude
she's getting lowered into a hole what the fuck is this how is there still a
a full minute left in this video does he jack off it gets no no he doesn't do
anything I actually just goes away today huh I accidentally opened this at work
today we should just do this with all women one by one until we have a giant
and then we sell the tube yeah to the highest bidder yeah I put the top on
going for five dollars is she like okay oh I get it she's like David Blaine and
she's gonna escape. Yeah she's an illusionist. You mean an escape artist?
No she's an illusionist because she never was in any danger in the first place.
Right. So what is the is this a fetish thing?
How much is this a gay thing? Well it is that too. To get rid of the women so you can fuck men.
Yeah. Wow and it perfectly matches up on the carpet. That's kind of scary.
Yeah. Anybody you know could have one of these. Ready? This is the best part.
He puts the... He's putting an ottoman over the hole. And then just sits down on the couch and drinks a glass of water and goes to sleep.
That's sick dude. Yeah. Wow. Oh yeah but speaking of the tag thing. Yeah. I just
this
it
join in the boat sleepover and we'd only known him like one hour so we my brother
like explained to him like oh yeah we're we're like sleeping on the boat tonight
and like something like that and then he his mom like eventually found my uncle
and was like cornering him at this thing is like come on just just just let my
That kid sleep on your boat.
Did he?
No, he didn't sleep on the boat.
Why not?
I don't know.
Who is he?
You are a really bad friend to Mickey.
That's kind of fucked up.
No I'm not.
You should have let him sleep on the boat dude.
I don't think so.
What if he was going in there to steal my shit?
He would be on the boat.
He's going to swim away with your shit?
No, the boat was docked.
Oh, you weren't even oh, so you were so it doesn't even count as a boat. Yeah, I didn't
No, this is just the lamest thing ever. I slept on a boat one time. I was
going to a family member's wedding and
For some and with like my parents and for some reason they decided they get to got Airbnb and they decided to an Airbnb
That was a boat. That's what my fucking mom did when it was in the boss horrible sucks
So why would you choose to do that?
Well, when we, when my mom did it was because she found a boat in Charlestown that was $30 a night.
Yeah, I guess that's like, yeah.
And she, okay, and we-
And that probably was part of it, yeah.
Yeah, I mean, it made sense, but it, it also took, it was like in the biggest dock,
maybe of all time, and it took like 45 minutes to take our stuff from the car to the boat.
If I remember correctly, it was like storming too.
Nice.
Yeah, it was not that cool.
And there was a giant octopus.
And there's a giant octopus and King Kong was fighting it.
And he was attacking the boat.
Oh yeah, it's all coming back to me now.
We had to fight it with spears.
Yeah.
Yeah, and I had a beautiful woman in a ripped dress.
Me and Caleb watched, and Pierce watched
the beginning of King Kong versus Godzilla,
so Caleb's got that on the brain.
Yeah, it's so funny hearing you and Pierce
talk about like kaiju movies,
'cause it just sounds like you're making them up.
Yeah.
You guys are just like,
You guys had one that was like, "Oh, have you seen Japan Man?"
Big Man Japan?
Yeah.
And I was like, "That's not a movie."
That one's like a mockumentary.
Ah, that's cool.
About a guy who gets big.
Like a scary movie.
A bunch of cops outside.
Yeah?
Uh-oh, Patrick's getting arrested for what he said about 18-year-olds drinking cum.
Yeah.
That's the response time, 20 minutes.
Were you aware that the women who were the subject of that joke were barely legal?
Your Honor.
Your Honor, she was barely legal.
Calling a cop your honor.
May I approach the bench?
Your Honor, may I approach this bench?
May I reach for your service weapon, your honor?
Your Honor, permission to take your gun.
No, no, you have to say overruled.
Permission to honor you, your honor.
You have to object.
There's no nose in the courtroom.
Permission to take your gun.
Permission to honor you, your honor.
nosed in the courtroom. This is the battleground of logic and reason. Yeah I'm
gonna become a lawyer. Yeah? Yeah I'm gonna. What's your lawyer name gonna be? Yeah
everybody has to choose their lawyer name I forget. When you get confirmed as a
lawyer. No. Can you can you hear us? Yes you can hear us. Right as Caleb's talking about his
lawyer name my fucking video we lost him oh yeah nice and we're back we're still
recording I'm still recording nice yeah the cops came in and the pack got
swatted Pat got swallowed by the cops yeah yeah yeah said your honor it would
be an honor for you to swallow me honor may I come in your mouth your honor may
you suck and swallow me yes may I honor you may I approach your your asshole
may I approach your asshole completely naked with a rock-hard thingy rock-hard
thingy in the honor your honor look at my thingy your honor may you look mate
your honor may you observe my thing yes you may yes I'm awesome right your honor
rate my thingy out of four four is bad four is bad now you said you said one
good because one is the best yeah four is bad zero is also bad one is great two
and three are okay but wait I'll explain the ratings but first give me a rating
I'll work backwards from that. What do you guys check this out? I love
The account that that was posted on was called loco freak
Did you guys see that video that account that just pees on shit?
That guy's just like peas in public and he like peas under the table and like a burger king
Just like he takes his day. I just peas on the floor
He's on an airport moving sidewalk. They're so funny. And then I saw one where he pees in a ball pit
No, he's like, oh god. No, I've been thinking
Video where I just pee on but I just walk down the like all the stars on like Hollywood Boulevard and just pee
Like on a bunch of them
Yeah, and Bill Cosby's that's right. Yeah, and Donald Trump's I
When we first got to LA you were doing that thing you were walking down we were walking down the walk
They just spit on every single star and I was laughing so hard cuz they're just like families taking pictures with stars
I said on one that somebody was taking a photo with
Yeah, just spitting on all the stars. What's Patrick doing? Patrick is such an such an online freak
We got frozen again
Dude the cops hate us
Well you're back it happened again, yeah, I don't know what the fuck's going on I
Think you're the glitch dude. I think you're the you're the glitch and you're glitching every piece of technology
They're the glitch you're the glitch you're Jack black and be kind rewind and you got electrocuted so badly that you're
demagnetizing the tape inside of your computer
We're gonna have to remake the internet.
What was going on?
I didn't hear any of that Hollywood story.
Well the listeners did.
Yes.
So you just have to pretend you heard it.
React.
React to it.
Yes.
Cool.
The people are gonna go nuts for that one.
Yeah.
Alright, moving on.
Beatcon Rewind is such a good movie.
Yeah.
I saw that for the first time like last year.
So good.
So fun.
I saw that.
Because my mom and I thought the commercial for it with the Ghostbusters
theme was really funny. That's the only reason I saw that. I got that movie from Redbox
two different times and forgot to bring it back so I had two Redbox copies of
Be Kind Rewind. Yeah. Don't know where they went. I should steal all the movies
out of a Redbox. That'd be fun to do. You steal all the movies? Just when I have a lot of money.
Yeah, you have to take the entire row not so just like borrow them all and just pay a lot of money
But just keep them all
Just like when I'm yeah, there's no I mean in red box. There's no real like you don't have an account
No, but you did you have your credit card? Yeah, exactly. So when I'm rich, I'll have 1,000 credit card
Oh, that's just go to a different red box
Or can you use cash? I don't think so
thousand credit that'd be terrible business did you guys ever go like just
to the grocery store with your parents and just look at red box while they're
checking out I always looked at the games and I'd be like how about this dad
how about this how about you let me have this game and I get to play it I yeah I
looked at the games and I was like damn imagine playing a video game yeah I
would love to do that someday bucks a day they're way more expensive than the
fucking movies I mean yeah yeah it makes it they can make bank cuz they know like
parents that will let their kids buy a video game from a red box will pay a lot
of money I feel like you like this by the game at that you will never remember to
return a video game from a from a red box yeah I used to live really close to
a movie gallery and which is like a just a DVD rental place yeah and that was
like honestly that was like the best time of my life yeah there was like a
video store like a video rental place like right walking distance from my
house I used to go there all the time. It's the best. I used to look at Jurassic
Park 3 and never get it just like look at the case I was like damn if the claw
marks are like a 3. This is the coolest movie ever. I used to go there and rent Turok for
GameCube. Yeah dude Turok. Turok fucking rocked. I never played it but I watched so
many YouTube videos of that game. It was so good. Anything with dinosaurs man. Also Turok
was the it was like dinosaurs, guns, yeah and also like people when you shot people
the
miles away from my house. I don't know why I used to do this.
But I used to move to this video store
and then I would bring my friends with me and we would try to go into the
adult video section in the back. And all jack off on each other?
Yeah. No, just because it was a game to see
how long we could stay in the back or if we could even get in.
Yeah. It's like jackass.
there's a there's like a triple X. I want to try that now with you guys.
Let's see if they let us in. He's giggling.
Just walking around, "Oh my god, they're gonna kick us out!"
Similarly, there was a, all through high school, there was me and my friend
John would drive by this like triple X movie store and we would like it had in
big flashing red X's like a sign with big red X's on the front we are there was
never anybody there and we just thought it was a funny place and on his 18th
birthday he we made him a ghost outfit out of a like a big sheet and he just
ran into them into the store and just like ran around and like knocked over a
bunch of DVDs and then ran out and then realized somehow he dropped his wallet
while he was in there and so then he had to just go back in and be like hey man
have you seen like a wallet anywhere and he didn't even take the ghost thing off.
It's so stupid. There was a I think it's in Hudson but there's an adult bookstore.
Nice. Whoa. But I don't know if they have I've never been in it but they have. Why do
you have a Lolita section? Yeah. That's weird. It's just one copy of Lolita.
just all the different editions of lolita but um there's that one and then I know
there's one in Manchester that's it that's it
Manchester Manchester by the sea yeah that's where Gislaine is baby really
she went well it was reported that she was in Manchester by the sea now she's
She's in my room. How do you pronounce her name?
Gislaine
Ma'am, isn't it? Like I know jerk
British people like to like jizz pronounce it with it. Yeah, they like jizz and they like the song Penny Lane
Yeah, so they combined that's how they got her into the perfect woman. Yeah, I
Like you know what say what she will about just laying Maxwell, but she stood by her man. Yeah, that's a girl boss
Mm-hmm. Yeah, she didn't really stand by her man. She kind of
- Yeah, she kind of killed him, honestly.
- Hey, that's cool too.
- That's true.
(laughing)
- It's also, also fine.
- Yeah, that's cool.
- It's better, those are the two,
better than any other alternative.
It's either standby or kill.
That's the other.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, and if you have, I mean,
yeah, Jeffrey Epstein, that's a tough one
'cause, you know, he was bad.
- What?
- He was like a bad, he was the bad guy.
I'm the bad guy.
- It's funny that like at some point,
there was a switch with him where it was like,
oh my God, he's like the worst guy ever.
It's like, how could you possibly?
He was so close to taking them all down.
He was almost a hero.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
I don't think.
- I didn't look at him as a hero like Caleb did.
- I did.
Me personally, I thought of him as a hero.
I thought of him as a-- - It doesn't use a--
- I didn't think of him as a hero.
I thought of him more as a main character
that I could play. - I thought of him as a hero
everything I thought he was a hero because he had 1 billion dollars. But he
was a pussy for getting arrested. Yeah. Yeah. I think that's when I lost respect
for him. That makes him a loser. Mm-hmm. Yeah. That's kind of fucked up guys. Hey
hey hey you want to hear something really fucked up? Yeah. Jeffrey Epstein
was good. What? Yeah he was the good guy man. Oh my god I don't think I can handle
this. Jeffrey. I think it's comments like this that caused Jeffrey Epstein to self
harm. That's true. Yeah. There's a... me and Cam have been doing something every time, for
some reason only when we're in my car where... It's state-dependent memory. Dude, it's the
car. I guess you're right. You remember it whenever we get into the car. Anytime we're
just like driving by people and we pretend a cat called them by going like, "Hey mama,
damn you looking good. Yo, come here and let me give you some.
[Honking]
[Laughter]
And just go like, "Hey, let me holler at you."
[Honking]
Damn. Shit.
[Laughter]
It's kind of, it's endless fun.
It's so much fun.
It's like the greatest car game you can have.
It's a good road trip game.
Yeah.
Who you gonna [Honking] that?
[Laughter]
It's a good one.
Yeah, you're gonna make me...
Yeah, I'm about to...
Oh man, I'm about to...
Now you're getting into it, yeah!
Yeah!
Do it again, man!
Oh, I'm about to...
See, we all have a different technique, you know what I mean?
That's what makes it special.
Yeah.
That one, when I do it, it really hurts.
It really hurts to hear. It's so bright.
Bright.
Bright? Yeah.
It's bright? It's bright. It's a bright noise.
How is that a bright noise? Loud.
Okay. You're the stupidest man on earth.
Damn, I'm about to... See, that's dark.
Damn, you're looking like a whole ass...
It's funny to me every time. It's so funny.
It's such a crazy noise.
Screaming into my own stomach.
Damn girl let me.
It's really slow and loud.
Hey girl.
Hey bitch.
Hey what's up bitch.
It's not even cat calling, just running up to women on the street.
"HELLO!"
"UGH!"
*laughter*
"HELLO BITCH!"
"AHHHHH!"
"YOU'RE A BITCH!"
"UGH!"
*laughter*
It would be terrible to listen to.
*snorting*
I'm not screaming at you, I'm screaming at myself.
I'm screaming with you.
Hmm.
Because you're screaming because I ran up to you holding a knife.
No, no, I'm screaming at you because I know you're an alien.
Yeah.
I can sense it.
I'm screaming at you because I love you.
I can smell it.
You're a different species.
[Laughter]
You're from Jupiter.
That's where you got more stupider.
This is how Jupiter people talk.
Yeah.
You went there and you got stupider.
Boys are from Mars.
I went to college to get more knowledge.
Boys are from Mars, drive fast cars.
Girls are from stupider and you're...
[Laughter]
(laughing)
- The other day I was,
I thought it was really funny to pretend to be Lenny Bruce
and say, Lenny Bruce on stage saying,
"Yeah, and here's something they won't tell you.
"Milk, milk, lemonade, round the corner fudges me."
(laughing)
And he gets arrested.
You know, he was a free speech hero.
He really, he put his life on the line.
(laughing)
You know, he really, he just told it like it is.
He told it like it is.
(laughing)
Yeah, yeah, and here's something they're not talking about.
Up your butt and around the corner.
(laughing)
That's the way to California.
Hey, listen, and listen here and listen real closely.
Mama mia, papa pia, baby got a diarrhea.
(laughing)
Sir, get off the stage.
I'm speaking truth to power, thank you very much.
I'm munching up.
I'm munching up at Mamma Mia and Papa Pia.
Their diarrhea baby.
Dude, it would suck if you had a baby and it was a diarrhea baby.
Am I right?
It would suck if you were Mamma Mia and Papa Pia.
It would suck if you were both Mamma Mia and Papa Pia and your baby had the diarrhea.
Yeah.
dirty knees so what are these?
Why were so many of those like like middle school rhymes about being Chinese?
I don't know. Like half of the ones I know. I was thinking about that the other day. What is it? Yeah cuz I got that I got that
fucking Mr. Show joke wrong I've talked about that. That is yeah. The one where it
was like I thought it was me Chinese me play joke me put poison in your coke
find out tonight at 10. What was that? It was actually just it was just David Cross
offhandedly saying oh the Chinese have found a new way to put pee in coke.
Definitely a worse joke honestly. Yeah. Dude you should write for Mr. Show. Yeah
that's what I'm saying. You could be Mrs. Show. Yeah. Nowadays it would be called
Mrs. Show. Nowadays it would be called Mr. / Mrs. in parentheses they/them.
They/Them gender fluid show. They/Them, Starbucks, sponsored by Starbucks,
mochaccino, the unicorn flavor. I think every Patreon episode we've made some joke about trans
Starbucks. Trans Starbucks? Trans Starbucks. We'll go to trans Starbucks. Instead of David Cross,
he'd be David the Quran. Am I right? It'd be David Sharia Law. Yeah, and Bob Al Odenkirk.
didn't they yeah like bob obama that's what it'd be nowadays yeah bob obama kirk bob obama kirk yeah
better call osama oh shit there we go wow breaking bag daddy
just kind of like departing from the formula here but um what else all
Breaking Bad Daddy is about a guy, a chemistry teacher who gets cancer so he decides to join
ISIS. He starts to fight but he starts ISIS. Breaking Bad Daddy. That's pretty good, I like
that. Say that again. Yeah and he's, yeah, um, I am the one who and then yeah. I'm the one who is in
ISIS. Yeah. Did you guys watch Breaking Bad? I watched like the first few episodes and I was
like this is too long my grandfather got me into it when I was 11 yeah yeah I
told him I had watched an episode and he was like yeah it's pretty good right and
I was like yeah and then I just continued watching it and then I stopped
I I didn't watch like the fifth season at all I watched the final episode did
you watch il Camino il Camino al Camino in the movie though it slowly over the
course of the five seasons he transitions to talking like an old Cuban man yeah
yeah JC JC yes see you see yeah I don't know what I'm trying to do so I Brian
(mimicking Spanish)
- Spanish 101.
- Yeah.
(mimicking Spanish)
- Yeah, I've been doing lingo.
- I was laughing about this at work.
Just a guy who has to talk to his Spanish speaking coworkers,
so then he just starts saying English words in an accent.
That's just what my dad does anytime he goes to a Mexican restaurant.
My dad will be like, "Oh yeah, let's go to La Costa."
And then walk in and be like, "I'll have a burrito,
y... y... uno enchilada."
"Kids, what do you want?"
"Ah, two aguas."
[laughter]
And they're like, "Sir, sir, this is Taco Bell. Please stop."
"My name is... my name is Jeremy."
Yeah, there's no Mexicans in North Carolina.
That's like, nevermind.
Tell me what it's like.
No, I forgot.
Yeah, I forgot my thought instantly.
Yeah, I forgot.
I'm actually so stupid, I forget things
as soon as I think them.
I'm Patrick.
I'm smart.
Yeah, prove it.
For my age.
Yeah, I'm smart.
I actually read on a 10th grade reading level, so.
I was me and Alex were talking about if there was there's a show it's like queer
I but it's Joker I for the straight guy and just like you should try doing this
crazy laugh wearing a cool colored suit yeah I'll just end up like the Joker
doesn't put on Joker makeup imagine imagine if he did like laugh like that in
movie he does dude where he's like oh he laughs like yeah that's one thing that
was really missing from the dark night he doesn't laugh much in the dark night
joker I'm playing a trick on you that's Sherry Sherry moon zombie Joker you know
how she laughs and like devil's rejects oh yeah that's his wife yeah Rob zombie
if you're listening let me just tell you something. Rob Zombie is a real dope.
He puts his wife's ass in every fucking movie. Yeah, thank God. I read this
angry comment where someone thought that it was his daughter. That would be so funny
if he's putting his daughter naked in every movie he makes. Didn't Kevin Smith do that?
Kevin Smith? I think so, maybe. Is it Kevin Smith's daughter named like Star Wars Jedi
or something? Kylo Ren, he changed her name when she was 15. This is my daughter
What's her actual name? It's something, something. It's Harley Quinn.
Yeah. Her name is Girl Jar Jar Binks. Jar Jar Binks with boobs. Yeah. Jar Jar boobs. And she's
really lives up to the name. Jar Jar Boo Binks. Did Jar Jar Binks get kicked off of
Dagoba or Naboo for being too stupid? Yeah he got kicked out of Oda Gunga. Yeah he
got kicked out of bubble bubble bubble bubble yeah me and Pat talking about
Star Wars is like you and Pierce talking about Godzilla no yeah hey Pat do you
remember computer man from Star Wars my favorite episode of Star Wars was in
episode 5 he was Lando's best friend yeah yeah yeah and were the remember
Lando's girlfriend Shakira in Godzilla though you're a doll wookie yeah we're
talking about kaiju though it's it's only just like oh did you see bubble be bill
and it's like yeah the monster looked cool and that's as far as it goes when
you guys talk about Star Wars it's like oh yeah and then bubble oh bubble went
to see both so so so and then so but but but but but but said the same thing 50
times now buddy yeah no I was saying actual Star Wars
even go to Zabu Bobo yeah that's not in that movie yeah see that's what I'm
talking about see the Godzilla stuff it's just it's it's the template is
Godzilla vs. and then just make something up it seems to be the yeah
Godzilla vs. they should make Godzilla vs. Godzilla I'm just realizing right now
they should do Godzilla vs. what if they had a robot Godzilla and they and then he
fights him she have you ever heard of terror of
mecha Godzilla you fucking idiot no no I haven't and now I'm suing them for
stealing my IP you guys stole my IP I'm suing them for stealing my PP you guys did a brain
robbery to me and you stole it yeah you guys did you guys went you you - you held
up my brain you had a gun opposite inception to me at the guns point
inception is such a good movie I incension is insane tension is mind
blowing tension tension is like if you were dreaming and you're in your dream
had one yeah faith in humanity yeah gone faith in humanity inception how about
this? Faith in Humanityception. How about this? What about you watch Inception, you
go, "Wow, I just lost my freaking faith in reality." And then your friends would all
go like, "Whoa." What if, okay, so what if you're taking a picture of somebody who
was taking a picture of somebody who's taking a picture?
Christopher Nolan one time, he was visiting Rome and he took a photo
that he later realized was a photo of somebody taking a photo and he said well
it's like freaking Inception and then he wrote the movie. Why Rome?
Rome because he was in Rome. Oh yeah that makes a lot of sense. You fucking idiot.
Yeah and then he also said he said when in Rome yeah he said I should write this
one. When in Rome write Inception. Yeah. Yeah. What if what if you were taking a
photo and somebody jumped into the photo? That's Inception. And and they made a
crazy face yeah much anything is inception yeah if you what if a cat
fought a dog what if a rattlesnake fought a mongoose and it was video of it
wouldn't that be inception wouldn't that be super inception what if my mom took
away all my video games is that inception yeah that's fucking bitch
my action that's bad inception that's conception as if as in I was never
conceived or born yeah yeah I wish my dad is never inception do you with his penis
to create me into my mom's dream my mom's dream me mom not to be weird can
I just tell you your pussy looks so dreamy
well I see nothing wrong with that exquisite ma'am your pussy is a total
dreamboat you got one hunky you got a chunky pussy. A heartthrob pussy.
(laughter)
- Oh my god.
See, you do it too, some.
Some.
- Oh, fuck.
That's just 'cause the diet, the regular Coke.
- Just 'cause of the Coke, yeah.
- I think the sugar has blocked my pineal gland.
- Yeah, your penile gland.
- My penile glands have been blocked by sugar,
and I'm unable to have penile thoughts now.
We should do IQ tests for the Patreon. Absolutely. Do you remember when we used
to we were at work and we do IQ tests all day? I'd score one point more than you.
Like three different IQ tests, Cameron just scored one point higher.
I know I'm getting the lowest score already. Yeah, what would if you had to
- What's ballpark your IQ?
- Me? - Yeah.
- I'm probably a 96.
- 96?
- That's me being modest.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Mine's probably like, I don't know, like one 2,004.
- 1,004. - 1,004.
- And 1,3006.
- Yeah, it sounds like it's actually zero.
- I have two separate IQs for my two different minds.
I actually have a dual mind system
that makes me twice as smart.
- You get 100 IQ points just for writing your name
on the test.
- Yeah. (laughs)
- Yeah, did you know if your IQ score is 15,
you're allowed to leave?
- Yeah, my son's been super busy recently
studying for his IQ test.
- Yeah.
That's stupid, you can't do that.
- Yeah, that's why I said it, dude.
Fucking idiot.
- I'm already having a hard time.
- Did you know that if--
- Are you taking, can we see?
- No, don't do it now, we should do an episode.
- No, let's do it, we have time, let's do it.
- All right, yeah, fine.
- I'm not, I have nowhere to go.
- Boy.
- Which number logically follows the series?
Yeah, this one's hard.
No, this is easy.
Three, three, six, okay, let me remember.
Three, six, nine, damn you fine.
Okay, oh, ah, shit.
Figure series, which of the figures in the bottom row
should logically be in the spot
of the question mark in the top row?
I'm not gonna give you any hints.
Yeah, but I know the answer for sure.
But the answer--
It's this one.
The answer is yo mama.
Which conclusion follows from the statements
with absolute certainty?
One, none of the stamp collectors is an architect.
Two, all the drones are stamp collectors.
Architects are not drones.
That's true.
I guess that's true.
Yeah.
What does--
If you were to fold this cube together,
it would probably look like--
Probably like a little something like this.
Hit it, boys.
(laughing)
I don't know the answer.
- I just know it'd look really cool
'cause cubes are one of the top 10 coolest shapes.
- Top one coolest shape for me.
- All right, all right.
- Cubes?
- I think cubes are the coolest.
- Tom has a new set of golf clubs.
- Not a shape.
- Using a club eight,
the ball travels an average distance of 100 meters.
Using a club seven,
the ball travels an average distance of 108 meters.
Using a club six,
the ball travels an average distance of 114 meters.
How far will the ball go if Tom uses a club five?
pretty damn far.
It's probably the most.
Yeah, so it's probably the, I'll just pick the highest number.
Because you're trying to get a high score on your IQ test.
Yeah, exactly.
Alright, what's the opposite of tough?
I think it's masculine.
Yeah, I think it's probably starch.
Water is to pipe as...
Blank is to a wire.
...cold water is to wire.
Patrick's so smart.
He's answering me so quickly.
That's because I've already taken the test.
Oh, alright.
You know all the answers.
So what's the best meaning of displeasure?
Oh, come on.
Did it just freeze?
Oh, we're back.
Okay.
Alright.
That was fast.
So I just finished the test.
Yeah.
No, you're in college.
Put college.
Too late.
You're a 22-year-old high school student.
You got 4 out of 10.
Under or up to 100?
This is pretty good.
That's a lame, that's a bad ballpark, that's stupid.
I think, uh, you guys froze again.
No, we didn't.
You guys are frozen again.
Well, this is probably a good place to end this episode when he gets back.
A perfect natural stopping point.
Let's just hang up and call him back.
No, don't do that.
Why?
Because it's about to reconnect.
I'm going to edit this out anyway, so.
to
I think you're embarrassed.
I'm upset that my internet keeps shutting off.
I think you're embarrassed by the number.
I think you're embarrassed that you're 30 IQ.
I think it said that you have a baby's IQ.
I don't even care about the IQ test.
I think you're more upset that the fans
are gonna be upset about this.
About the internet?
Yeah.
How will he connect?
That's my impression of the fans.
How is he gonna connect and get online now?
What if he has an ailment pop up?
Oh, and he just hung up on us.
Wait.
resume call
uh... so fuck is going this i don't want to have to edit this uh...
but and that
what don't
spun up again welcome
just don't uh... alright this is the end of the episode not gonna have any more
than a shit
uh... sucks dude alright
uh... but her patrick
await we do it did not have a subscriber new people i mean i don't think so
okay well then we're gonna shout out
- Okay, we each get to shout out one person.
- We shout out Xfinity from Comcast.
- All right, can I go first?
Yeah, you can go first.
- For having great wifi.
- Okay, you shout out Xfinity.
- For great service.
And then they tell you that they're shutting off your bill
because they forgot to set up an auto pay thing.
- Owned.
- Yeah.
- Xfinity's gonna flip their shit when they hear this.
- When they hear this, they're gonna get mad.
- So you shout out Xfinity, you shout it out.
- Patrick's mom.
Okay, I'd like to shout out the brave men and women
who make up the first responders of this great nation.
- Yeah, so Patrick's mom.
- So Patrick's mom, 'cause anytime I call 911 and I say,
"I need somebody to come suck my penis right now,"
she's over in a jiffy.
- Yeah.
All right.
- Gotcha.
- Yeah.
- I haven't talked about fucking your mom in a long time.
- I know.
- It's okay to do behind a paywall.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, she's gonna have to pay.
Won't be the first time I got five bucks from your mom
if you know what I'm talking about.
- God damn it.
- Yeah.
*Screaming*