Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
(laughing)
- If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
(laughing)
(explosion)
♪ Can you let a white dog hit it one time ♪
♪ Do it from the back in the sunshine ♪
♪ Pussies on the ground 'cause it's online ♪
- It should be pussies on the ground 'cause it's all mine.
- 'Cause it's all mine?
- Yeah.
- And then online?
♪ Looking at pictures online ♪
♪ They're online ♪
- Yeah, that's better.
♪ Can you let a white thug hit it one time ♪
♪ Hit it from the back in the sunshine ♪
- Yep.
♪ Pussy on the ground 'cause it's all mine ♪
- Yeah.
♪ Boobies online ♪
- What is it?
- The white thug needs sunshine, that's the thing.
- The white thug needs sunshine and he needs vitamin D.
- Boobies on my phone and they're online.
- Yeah.
Online boobies on my phone.
on the phone cuz they're online. I'm black thug the boobs on my phone.
mm-hmm white thug and black thug on the song together. Turn that down.
White thug and black thug. Sharing an office has its quirks. It seriously has its quirks.
it's a lot like The Office. Yep. Basically it's like it's like The Office and
Jim and Homer there. Yeah. Oh my god. Jim Homer from The Office. Jim Tomy from The Phillies.
Next level. Oh my god. When he grabs Bart Pam. Bart Pam. Oh my god. Don't even get me started.
She bad. Don't even get me started on how bad I want to see Bart Pam's boobies. I will say
Pam Pam with a Bart style like short haircut like a pixie cut oh my god Jamie
Lee Curtis with the Bart cut she does look like a Simpson yeah I saw they did
Trudeau and he's unsimpsonable. That's Trudeau. Yeah, he's unsimpsonable.
What he does is unconscionable. That's right. What's up? Yep, about those truckers.
He won't let them... What is it? Is that still happening? Yeah, it's still happening.
Really? He won't let them do loop-de-loops. Yeah, they want to do loop-de-loops like a
Hot Wheels track. Dude, they want to make burritos in the parking lot. They want to do burnouts.
They won't let them do it. He won't let them get microwaves in their car.
Burnritos. He said you can't have PlayStation in the cab of your truck.
Yeah. Yeah. We're gonna do this again. I'm just kidding. That's not true. But you did
say you're not allowed to use CDs. Yeah. Yeah. You have to use that the tape adapter thing.
He said he thinks it's distracting to put a CD in the car while you drive. Yeah. He
says he says, Well, how about you be a car driver instead of a truck driver? Yeah. He
also said, I want to see D so bad. How about you car drive? I bet you see these nuts? What?
He also said that truckers aren't allowed to put anything in their trucks. The trucks have
have to be empty. Is the trucker thing still happening?
We just said.
They just actually, there was a big movement in it where now they're allowed to put one thing in the back of the truck.
They move the trucks. Yeah, they're allowed to move the truck with one thing.
They move the trucks one inch.
But they still have to hold their breath the whole time they're driving.
Yeah, because it's like driving a truck is like swimming, so you should be holding your breath.
That's one of those things. That's the thing, this guy's an idiot.
He doesn't even understand anything.
He said you should be able to drown while driving a truck.
Yeah, well he said the truck has to be full of water.
That's just not okay.
Yeah, he said anything that you,
he said you can only bring fish.
Yeah, he also said, he said trucks can go forward,
back and turn left or right, but they can't go up or down.
Nope.
No, that just can't be true.
So if there's a single--
That's not right.
That just can't be true though.
If there's a single inch of elevation on the route,
they can't do it.
This just in, that can't be true though.
That's right.
Mm-hmm.
If I was a newsman, I'd be making all sorts of puns.
And apparently he called the truckers the motherfuckers.
Oh my God.
That doesn't even rhyme.
That's just insulting.
Oh yeah, wait, it does rhyme.
Oh wow, that's actually kind of cool.
I'm not opposed to that.
Okay, now that I found out that it rhymed.
Now that I found out that he's cool.
Hold on, let me look at my rhyming dictionary to double check if that rhymes.
And apparently I also heard that he called bikers "motherfucker likers."
Hmm, well that, does that rhyme?
Bikers for truckers is a big group now.
I'm going to be a biker.
I'm a motherfucker liker.
Yeah, it does.
Yeah, it does rhyme.
And he also said that mailmen are--
- Snailmen, 'cause his mail goes so slow.
- Yeah, he did say that.
- He said, no, he said--
- He was the guy who came up with snail mail.
- How come mail isn't faster now?
- He said that they're crailmen.
Crail is an insult he came up with, though.
- Yeah? - Yeah.
- Like a crail tap?
- Nope, he just said one day, he was like, "You crail."
And everyone was like, "Oh."
- That's an 80-word. - Yeah, something.
- How come the mail isn't faster now?
You'd think the mail would be faster now.
- Well, that's why you use email, extremely fast mail.
- If you're still using normal mail,
you kind of deserve it, I think,
'cause everyone else has moved on to email, texting,
airdrop, SMS.
- They don't call it snail mail for nothing, brother.
They don't call it snail mail for nothing.
- Packages go pretty fast, too.
- And here's the thing, though,
if a snail was as fast as mail is,
that would be, you got a serious movie called Turbo on you.
(laughing)
You have an actual Turbo-style movie.
- I guess mail is, it's as fast as a car.
- Dude, they made a TV show.
They made a series out of Turbo.
- Dude, there was an iPhone game for that.
- Really?
- Or maybe it was at that point,
it was probably an iPod Touch game.
- We gotta get Turbo merch.
I think that's our next move.
- Turbo is swag.
- I bet there's the coolest Turbo shirt in the world.
Would that be sick if they tried to,
they probably made it look like old,
oh, that would be tight.
It made to look like old NASCAR stuff from the '90s,
but it's the Turbo snail.
- Oh, that would be cool as fuck.
- That would be so dope.
- Yeah, it looks like a Dale Earnhardt judgy.
- You ever hear what happened to Snail Earnhardt?
- Double sides.
- Snail Earnhardt.
- Yeah, he turned left too slow.
- Turbo two, the fall of Snail Earnhardt.
- He just, his shell just explodes.
He's stuck inside the shell.
- Oh my God.
- Dale Earnhardt.
- Yeah, you know what happened?
He became a slug.
- My mom was at the NASCAR cafe
in Myrtle Beach, South Carolina when he died.
Pretty cool.
I bet they put the checkered flag at half mast.
They did.
Yeah.
And people got confused.
They didn't know if that meant go or...
That's why everyone in the restaurant ran out.
Everyone was running in a circle.
Yeah.
They all ran out of the restaurant because they thought that meant 9/11 too.
NASCAR is cool as fuck.
Yeah.
NASCAR is awesome, dude.
NASCAR is sick.
I want to get some NASCAR information in my brain.
My favorite NASCAR driver would be Bobby.
Yeah, for me it would have to be the gay guy from that movie instead.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
John C. Reilly?
No.
he's in it and he's like yeah, I like people be a
pelia. I'm going to suck dc my boyfriend and everyone in two
thousand six is like what the fuck's going on. His boyfriend
is Andy Richter, most believable part of the whole movie. Yep,
yep,
that's true. It's very it's believable for Andy Richter to
be someone's boyfriend, but he can't be the guy who has a
but yeah, he doesn't have a specifically. He doesn't have
enough initiative or like yeah, he's the sidekick boyfriend
Exactly even in even in his relationships. He can't be like, oh, this is my boyfriend. He has to say I'm this guy's boy. Yeah
They're my boyfriend. Yeah, this guy I'm his boyfriend
Mom dad, I'd like to meet you. I like
Yep, yeah
Yeah, that's a woman just saw Borat for the first time yeah
Great, it's a great thing to show somebody Borat for the first time. I'd rather see a snoring rat. Yeah, no
I love Borat do you this is lying to you? We're at it's so good. It's the best. It's the best movie of all time
It's so crazy. I feel like it comes back to us every I mean like no every like six months
I watch it we watch it again, and we just talk about it for like a week when he's saying
Yeah, that's the funniest that's so many good moments
Oh my god, every every part every inch every nook and cranny of that movie. Oh my god, so good. Yeah
Said that uh, we will the national anthem. Yeah, so when he says we will drink the blood of every man woman and child
Yeah
even a lizard. Yeah, remember, we're just literally just repeating jokes from 4Head now. They're
good jokes. Oh dude. The part where he's interviewing the old guy and the old guy's just like, "Yeah,
we need to hang all the gay people." Oh yeah. It's so crazy dude. That guy, I hope he's doing
well. When he starts unpacking his suitcase in the elevator. Yep, that shit's funny. That
you should start to bore at three mm-hmm come on hit us up hit us up to do what
hit us up to be borat's three kids well now that they did already more at three
sons yeah what do poor at three sons why not yeah we can go around like yeah
winding up our fists like this yeah see the punch people and you know that we're
seriously gonna be interviewing Joseph Paul F Watson yeah yeah we're gonna be
interviewing Paul F Watson and we're gonna be like we're gonna be like now
what did the five fingers say to the face slap bitch that's right yeah we'll be
Like the Three Stooges were gonna be like, "Get in there, dog! Get in there, dog! I'm up in there, dog!"
We're gonna end like the Three Stooges.
"I'm Rich Biatch!"
"Nah, see? I'm Rich Biatch!"
That's what the Three Stooges did.
That's what, when they got the, when the Three Stooges found the Jawbreakers,
they said, "I'm Rich Biatch."
Did you see the new Three Stooges movie with Will Sasso?
Yes, I half of it and I shut it off.
I refuse to watch it.
I'm a big Will Sasso fan. Oh dude, Will Sasso's the best. I bet it's a good movie. Oh no,
the Three Stooges are the best. Will Sasso's so, dude, remember he did-
What are your comedy influences? Probably the Three Stooges. I watched so much Three
Stooges growing up. I think I've- I don't think I've seen- I was kind of a weird kid.
My favorite was Shemp. You ever watch the New Year's Eve Three Stooges marathon on TV? Yeah.
Yeah, I watched that every year. I was big into Three Stooges and Little Rascals as a kid.
Yeah. And my mom started, because my mom would show us those, and then my mom started showing my nephews
those little rascals. And there's just an episode where they get like a genie's bottle
and like Stimey immediately wishes for a watermelon. It's so crazy. It's so crazy that like
that yeah it's like it's racist as hell. I never knew how racist. Who's Stimey? Stimey's a little black boy.
this three rascals those three little rascals I've seen maybe one episode of
three stooges and I've seen the newer little rascals movie yeah with Trump's
and Trump is Waldo's dad dude I don't I didn't even watch it I've watched it
like five years ago what and I like just looked at my phone the whole time cuz
it's a it's got the whole movies his kids talking no Brooks is in that he
Mel Brooks is in it?
Mel Brooks is in it, he plays a banker.
That doesn't make any sense.
You don't understand that?
I don't think that's true.
I think you thought it was Mel Brooks.
I think it was a different actor, yeah.
You just saw a banker?
Just immediately?
You guys should see Mel Brooks in the Harry Potter movies.
They cloned him over and over again like Willy Wonka.
They do, I forgot about this, in the 94 Little Rascals, they go on each other's shoulders,
they go into the bank dressed up like ha seats.
- Really?
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- I think I remember that.
- I was like, oh, I think they fixed all the racism
in the new Little Rascals.
It's like, no, we gotta stay true to four.
We gotta do like the most racist thing we can do.
- I know, oh, thank God they didn't make them
the PC Rascals.
- Yeah.
- Oh my God.
- They're probably gonna make a reboot called the PC Peewees.
- Probably.
(laughing)
- Gonna ruin everything.
- Probably these days they might actually do something
to the freaking woke tykes.
- The woke tots.
yeah and there the songs like
trigger warning. Oh my God trigger. They would have that in the side. They
would have that content warning mischief. Yeah, content warning three little
kids bastards and they're bastards because they don't have a dad and that's
okay. Nowadays, it's okay to be a actually normal to not have a dad these
days. It's actually completely some because they have five moms. Yeah, five
moms all named Terry. Uh-huh. Yeah, and they have parents there. They may be
me name Terry, but they're Karens at the CVS.
They're Karens in spirit, and they wear those cotton shorts that got their fupa in them.
Oh yeah. Oh my God, that thing is so sick.
You know those shorts?
I want to bury my fucking head in that.
Yep. You know those shorts that your gym teacher wears?
Trampoline fupas.
You know that if you smelled that fupa, it'd be exactly like a library.
It would smell like a library.
It would smell like old ass books.
Or like sourdough starter.
I was about to say like bread dough.
You know when you have it in a Ziploc bag and you're...
Oh my god.
You have rising yeast.
So you can make a pizza later.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
Man, I'd be speed bagging that fupa and dislocate my elbows.
Oh my god.
Your arms would be bouncing back too violently.
Yeah, dude.
I would have her like spread her legs and then I'd get in the creases between the thighs
and the fupa.
You're getting too far about this.
And then I'd have her...
As soon as you started this with spread her legs.
I'd have her squeeze her legs back together to push the fine meat up to the fupa and just
crush all my fingers.
And then I'd take them out and I'd smell every last finger I had.
I'd be bouncing back and forth between all the five fupas like the balls in Hungry Hungry
Hippos.
I'd be addressing the five fupas like they're the Cosa Nostra Five Families.
I'd be coming to them with an offering.
The Bronx, yeah. Oh my god the five fupa's on me like that scene in the Incredibles
when those black balls stick to him. Yeah, just being completely suffocated dude. Oh my god.
Crushed like a trash compactor, a gas compactor. I'm walking around looking like the...
I know those cotton shorts don't got a string. Damn, she got a gas compactor.
I'm walking around looking like the slitulent man.
Yep, yep, yep.
Katamari, I'm like Katamari Dame Nancy.
Yep.
Because they're all named Nancy now.
No, they're named Terry and they're Karen's.
Katamari Terry.
Karen.
Yep.
(laughing)
- Yep.
- Katamari Terry.
- Wouldn't it be, how crazy would it be
if the next Mario game came out or something,
you see the trailer and you're just
one of the guys in the movie?
- Me?
- Yeah.
- Specifically me?
- No, just anybody.
That'd be a cool kinda feeling, right?
- Yeah, if someone said I looked like a Mario brother,
yeah, that'd be cool.
- You don't look like one of the brothers,
you look like Wario.
- I don't look like Wario.
- You're like a Mario cousin, I would say.
I feel like I'm the I feel like I'm the anti-warrio.
Like how Mario is like anti or Wario is anti-Mario.
You look like you look like Mariopolis.
The Greek Mario.
Maurice.
Maurice Mariopolis.
Maurice is a Greek Mario and he just owns a diner.
What?
He just owns a he doesn't have a plumbing.
Why did you say that?
of a plumbing business. He just owns a diner in his and what are you going to
say that he smells that he has covered in Greece, too much body hair. That's
where he's from
you did you are your racism is showing today. The only really I knew two Greek
people growing up. One of you so you think he eats napkins. One of them was
my best friend and the other one was the guy who owned the diner. My mom or dad,
you know, it's awesome about Greek diners. They always have a little like
of the kids is just like oh you just works there. I think I talked about this
for a day I was that kid and I was like busing tables I was like 11 and I
burned my hand on the toaster and then they asked for me to never work there
again. I wanted to be that kid so badly I watched my big fat Greek wedding and I
was like mom dad we have to get a diner. I need to become a little Greek boy.
become a little Greek boy.
That definitely, as a kid, it seemed very cool to live above a store or something.
Yeah.
And then you grew up, you're like, "Why would I want to do that?
Why would that be cool?"
Yeah.
Why would it be cool to live, like I would just say, "If I lived above a store, then
I could just get free stuff from the store."
It's not true.
No, you just have a store.
You're just paying rent to a guy who has a store.
Every kid that lived in the suburbs just wanted to live in, "Hey, Arnold."
That's what I wanted.
I just wanted to like I there's not at any city in North Carolina
I either wanted to live in hey Arnold or Dracula's castle
Actually, I wanted to live in them dragon tails. Oh my god dragon tails
I want to live in Mario that pink dragon was fine
Which one Cassie plus the ones with the two heads exact and wheezy second wheezy. I don't remember any dragon
You don't remember Zack and wheezy no I most of the shows
I watched as a kid had because you know - you know two heads are better than one you know where they added
I do remember that added a third kid to dragon it was what was the guy who's like
their cousin right beat oh it was like it was someone in Emmy and then they
added Enrique yeah it's like their cousin right I don't know I never I
wasn't watching it just put well I think it's like it's like a cousin and he's
like visiting from New Mexico or something I think they just ruined the
sanctity of the show because it's about like - it's like a brother and a sister
yeah we go to Dragon World dragon land you bring cousins into the mix I know
I know that's everything that's what I'm saying you shouldn't have done that.
That one C.S. Lewis, The Voyage of the Dawn Treader, get that motherfucking kid out of there.
Oh my god yeah.
Get that goofy ass.
Edmunds?
No Edmunds is the brother.
What's his name?
The fucking cousin.
It has a different mass Ed in his name though doesn't it?
I think it's Enrique.
Tedmund.
Enrique Pevensey.
He goes to a completely different like Narnia world.
he goes to like the Narnia he goes like Scottsdale Arizona. He goes to the like
the like the like Mexican planet from Mario Odyssey.
He goes into the same wardrobe and they're like where did he go? Enrique,
we went to a magical world. There was a talking mouse and a lion was God.
Yeah, I went to- I had to fight Bowser. I had to fight Dry Bones. When I first
there everything was icy and then I did get a star I don't know yeah they made me
keep getting stars I'm 36 is it older they need an older cousin you know when
you have an old cousin I have an old cousin had one eye I don't even know I
don't even know his name I just remember I remember going to like my like great
aunt's house when I was a kid and seeing a guy with one eye and I asked my
grandma I was like is I was like man is that a pirate and she said no that's
your cousin and then she told me that he lost it while he was he was doing a
motorcycle drive doing well he's doing a motorcycle driving he lost his eye it
just flew out from the wind I think he went so fast that the wind made it pop
out fly blue as I for a while it was just like trailing behind hitting him on
the side of the head what's wrong the eye stuff is like the worst I stuff boy do I
know that do I have a never soft intro for you to yeah I think that's why yeah
you do that that in the saw movie that shit grossed me out so much I always
happen in the movies yeah he has the key behind the eye oh yeah you know what I
always hated was that video from that one thing where they cut the eye with
the razor blade Oh and a loo what he's having a stroke that's the name of the
movie say that again Sean and a loo the one from Dead Space where they put a
needle in his eye I see that that was sick did you see me actually get some
pepper in my eye the other day that was horrible yeah that was horrifying
disturbing that was a disturbing moment in my life yeah I'm 10 disturbing I
remember a kid when I was in middle school a kid threw like a handful of
crushed red pepper flake in my eye yeah I flew out and it whizzed around the
room sanded a kid's eye and I remember I was at a pizza place and he was like he
was like sorry and his mom made him apologize to me but I was like I should
like I gotta kill this kid now. Yeah you're allowed to fight a kid.
Mm-hmm. And then if you're like 16 and a four-year-old does anything to you,
you stomp them out. Yeah until you're 18 years old you're legally a child.
You can just beat the shit out of any kid if they give a fuck with you.
And I did. I was 17. I killed a child. I do remember one time...
I think it's a sponge from my record. I remember one time when I was like 15 maybe going to like
like this, like arcade place, because they had like every two weeks it was out of
town. It was like twenty dollars. You play all the games you wanted to all day
long, and I went and like a little kid started messing with me. I was like
fifteen years old, and I really was like I'm gonna like I'm gonna fight a child
like a little ass kid. He was like nine years old, and he was like doing that
thing where I would be like what are you doing? He'd be like what are you doing?
And I was like bro, I have to kill this kid. Yeah, like I now I still wish I did
What did you do? I think I tripped him one time. Nice. Yeah and that was it.
Because I was like, I'm gonna go. That's literally like that's all you have to do. It's like the
least harmful thing. Just trip him. And then you're like, oh whoops, I got big feet.
Yeah. You know. I'm a big guy. Yeah, I'm huge. I did the, I was the opposite. I was a really, you
know, I mean it's pretty obvious. I was a really annoying kid. There's this, this
kid came over his name I forget but he was in my sister's grade he forgets
think his name was Marcus no no and I do even win Kevin win yeah that's why I
doesn't want to say it was Kevin McAllister it's Kevin McAllister this
kid I I was just being a little shit I annoyed him and they said do it one more
time I'll beat the shit out of you and my sister's like I don't know like four
four years older than me. So I was like nine. He was like thirteen. He just
fucking wailed on me. Oh, yeah, it's not. I sound like he warned you, though.
Yeah, yeah, but but what I'm glad to see that you didn't learn any lesson. I
did not didn't learn a single lesson. My friend had a had a little brother who
like I think is maybe in a in like a like a old school mental hospital, like
one flew over this cuckoo's nest style now. Yeah, but he used to chase me
ground. He was like way younger than us, but he used to fight. He used to get
like kitchen knives and like shit and just chase us.
Like he was gonna kill us. Yeah. Wow. And then we'd have to just wear
him out by running around the neighborhood as he chased us with knives until he like, he would just
fall asleep in the middle of the road. He'd have to like call his mom
and be like, "Hey, Chris is asleep in the middle of the road." Damn.
It was cool, dude. Yeah. I think I threw a grape
at my sister's middle school boyfriend and he beat the fuck out of me too.
Dude you just, this is telling me everything I need to know. Yeah? Yeah.
Which is that next time that you annoy me I just need to fight you. You've done it
before. Uh-uh. You've slapped me and shit. I'll slap you. Yeah. Yeah.
It's just so funny to annoy people. I don't find it that funny. It's so funny.
to to you it's so funny to me and that's all that matters all right this you you
just made it way worse now I'm definitely gonna kill you yeah something
about that that was that was really done yeah yeah oh it's just oh it's me shut up
okay shut the fuck up see that's annoying you stick your tongue out of me
again the tongues gonna be in that toilet I'm gonna rip that tongue out of
your mouth now cuz then you get like a carbon fiber prosthetic tongue so fast he
could probably become a rapper so much more annoying if he had like like a deus
ex like if you if you were like you had a mod on you'd be so funny if I got like
like cancer or some shit in my arm I had to replace it and then I got like a
robot arm that made me really good at fastballs I want to be I want to be
augmented or uploaded so badly. I have none of the like science fiction thing of
like oh but where like is it still you? Yeah. Like I don't think about that at
all it's like put me in a put me into an Xbox or give me two red arms. I would like to be
mutated I'm not I don't want a robot parts because then that runs out of
batteries that gets rusty I would like to be part animal. Robot legs. I would like
to I would like to look like the mutants from beneath the planet of the apes with
the big bro yeah yeah or maybe like a resident evil monster you want to be an
evil monster yeah I want to be a robot no because you know you know we need to do
is team up and we can really only oh technology you know but here's the
scenario right you two are you two are robots we're going out to fight crime
obviously and and we run into magnet man I'm the only one I have to save your
asses because you guys are both instantly non-magnetic metal in my
my entire body. The best part about turning purple is that no one would
no one would care. No one would care if you were black or white or yellow or
purple. I think if you turned purple, you would be in a zoo right now. If I
turned purple,
that'd be funny if it's like the thing where like you know like how like it's
always like in like movies and stuff. If someone if someone gets powers, the
government wants to like like cut them open and stuff. Yeah. It's that but just
because someone turns like green like nothing happens. It's like we need to
study the green senator that drink the colloidal silver. We need to figure out
we need to make our soldiers green. We need a green super soldier army.
Yeah, I mean that would be terrifying. My friend Patrick at school, he turned
purple and then he just vanished. I don't know what happened. Nobody heard
from him. The cover just disappears. You see like purple. President Obama has
eaten purple soup today.
That's in area 51.
they're reporting the color of soup.
Every day, every day. It's like today is different. President
Obama drank ate a purple soup the first time ever. Yeah,
they was that Obama truly became president when he ate a purple
soup. He had a purple soup, but no one knows that it was made
from. Yeah, no one knows the scary ingredients behind the
purple. So I could see you being
I can see you being a purple guy.
purple people. I could see you getting. Oh dude if I turn purple I gotta watch out for
that people eater. No he's not a purple people eater. No he's a purple people. Guys you guys
are seriously misremembering the song. No it's purple people eater. He's a one eyed, one
horned, flying, purple people eater. People eater. They say purple people eater. Flying
and purple people eater. Flying so I get to fly too? Okay riddle me this you fucking geniuses.
if he's a purple people eater, wouldn't he fucking starve to death on account of
there's no fucking purple people? That's why I don't see him yeah, because he's
eating them. He ate them all because he's eating him really yeah. This is
what you guys think also I've seen he's eating the purple. I mean I can tell
you for a fact I've seen him and he's green, so he eats purple people. It's
not per no. You saw a green and per people eater. No yeah, that's that one's
purple. That guy eats green people.
I'm going to end my life. What are you going to say?
what before I interrupted you I does it matter I think clearly it doesn't
because you decided to go to something you were saying something about you were
saying something about a government oh I just I love you I think you would look
right at home being experimented on an area 51 like they would have like I wish
I didn't ask him what he was yeah no they have like it's not important they'd
have some kind of soda in like a giant hamster feeder yeah yeah yeah you would
would be a great human hamster great was human hamster. I think that you
might be a perfect candidate. Human hamster human hamsterdom. Oh my God.
Yeah, I wouldn't be a good human hamster because I would just be playing
my scientist. I'll be about the boy who has to stay in the bubble, but it's
called human hamster and I got there boy yeah, they're making bubble boy,
but there's nothing to a sickness or anything. It's just you want us to be
here which Jake Gyllenhaal or John Travolta one you would be Jake Gyllenhaal
on the remake. Okay, I feel I get to me, Verne Troyer. No, it's completely
different. It's ham, it's human hamster, so they got a different
lot. It's a re walking around a hamster cage with like he's got those like
boxers on that have all the hearts
is eating like like a protein, a great ball pellets be so awesome. Oh my God,
He's like shitting all over the place and be like, "What the hell is all this shit?"
I would not have it.
Some creatures coming in here and shitting all over the place.
Little creatures, yeah.
Anyway, I'll be on my wheel.
I don't know.
I don't think I'd like a hamster wheel.
I don't think that you would use the wheel.
I think the wheel would be growing cobwebs on it.
Yeah.
You'd be too busy sitting in front of the theater drinking the most soda ever.
The theater.
I get a theater.
No.
Yeah.
Okay.
I get a theater.
You know what?
Sure.
You get a movie theater.
just like you know, like the sometimes there will be like a fake tv or car at
like the bottom of an aquarium, just like playing the plastic car pretending
he's driving it. You should pack it's like a I get out of the hamster thing
and I'm like well good news in there. I got my license
you get like it okay. These keys are way too small for my car. You get like a
a giant McMansion that's just all it's just a giant hamster cage. There's just
like a million rooms. You have like a home hamster theater. You have a hit.
You have a chef. All the movies are made out of or made or hamster cast.
Hamster cat yo, so I'm watching like I'm watching like the hamsters present.
I'm doing a first time viewing of like salo or something and it's all hamsters.
You choose to watch
as with hamsters in it. That would be pretty sale or sot follow it's
it's a lo it stands for some awful disgusting let's go shit damn some
Italians doing it different some awesome lesbian auction is there lesbian auction
in that see that's why I said first time viewing I have never heard of it I think
you know that ever heard of that movie?
I've never heard of that movie!
(laughing)
It worked man.
I don't know, I've never heard of it.
I just made that name up.
(laughing)
I've never heard of it.
Oh.
No, I think if I had to get stuck in a
hamster thing and all the movies were made from hamsters
I would not watch that.
I think the funniest movie to replace the cast
podcast with all hamsters g force yeah probably g force
philadelphia yeah guinea pig is not that funny hamsters
yeah philadelphia chicken run what that'd be funny as hell chicken run flushed
away flushed away madagascar boy in the striped pajamas zoo yeah uh is that
the wild that's on the sheep would totally be sean the hamster yes on the
hamster yeah probably be named hampton the hamster homeward bound yeah and
word be called ham word round where he did that what when do we do that I've
never heard of that you're lying no you're lying you're building up a bunch
of lies listen buddy if you want to go toe-to-toe and a game has seen it I'll
smoke you I think a documentary with hamsters yeah I still be pretty good
maybe like the act of killing mmm act of killing show yeah yeah sure you know
know what that movie would be called it'd be called show a hamster wheel.
I don't know what it's about. I just
never even heard of it. I've never heard of it. I've never even heard of it or
what it's about or anything. I actually don't you know I'm I never watched. I
think you've never heard of the show.
No, oh interesting. Do you think it what do you think about it?
I don't know I've never heard of it I don't really have enough to form an
opinion okay so he has no opinion on one way or the other on the show okay
not even being like a denier they just be like I've never heard of it never
even heard of it is that there is that is that like Yiddish or whatever Hebrew
for Holocaust yeah okay I didn't know I thought it was a different I thought it
I thought it was a different word for like it was like this sucks
narration of that whole movie just like this sucked yep so this part this part
like a mystery side yeah they're pointing at the screen like yeah I
remember that that's so yeah that was fucking shit
this part up here on that really this one was the worst oh my god dude mystery
besides theater three thousand of show over
is archival.
Yes, it is fucking sucked ass over this guy looks stupid yeah that guy was
suit yeah. I was even meaner and all the other
place suck. I don't want to go back there.
I was bull crap
yeah, yeah, that stunk.
I remember you know that place stunk yeah.
I remember that lady, she sucked. That place was total crap. Oh my god. That was the worst.
This is pretty awkward turtle, look at this. Oh my god, this guy was a total socially awkward
penguin. Oh man. Scumbag Steve up there. Dude, the Scumbag Steve documentary, they gotta make
that hamster fight hamster fight they do wait which guys like that did they like
they made documentaries about people like that yeah I know your meme.com
yes I'm thinking of window you probably want you probably watch a three-hour
YouTube video called the fall of scumbag Steve probably have I probably do those
videos they get me so good are you serious I fall for those every time I
feel like I get all for them I get trapped in a while you're mentally weak
- You're acting like it's a trick,
you're just watching the video.
- It is a trick, it is a trick.
It'll be called like the fall or like the truth about,
and then it's like a 10 minute video where it's like,
basically their life has gone pretty much the exact same.
- Pretty normal.
- Pretty normal, it's exactly how you think it would go.
- It's a genius ubermensch trait to only watch
15 second YouTube videos called zombie salmon.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, that's how you become smart.
- Dude, that fucking, I watched it on the--
- Did I show you zombie salmon?
- Yeah, you showed me that.
I watch eight hour YouTube videos.
- You watch that guy, Tom whatever.
- Yeah, Tom.
- Who's Tom? - British Tom.
- Oh, and Jerry.
- British, the British--
- I love Tom and Jerry.
- Yeah. - Yeah, he funny as hell.
- The British Tom that's like,
oh, this is the largest bridge in all of London.
- He's fake Vsauce, dude.
I'm team Vsauce Michael all day.
- Yeah? - Dude.
- Me too.
- Dude, our-- - My boy, dude.
- Dude, our-- - Big shouts out,
Vsauce Michael. - Dude, he's our guy.
I back Vsauce Michael so hard.
Oh dude.
Dude, Vsauce, I've been clicking on...
Vsauce was just like, dude, 2014 when I first saw Vsauce, I blew my mind.
Vsauce Michael, I literally know for a fact you're listening to this.
We're linking up and we're coming to do math videos with you.
Uh-huh.
Yep.
Also...
We're gonna do one plus one equals damn potato.
Real werewolf reacts to werewolf footage.
Uh-huh.
I don't know that guy. Is that a Vsauce Michael video?
Yeah.
We're only talking about Vsauce right now.
They got all these fake Michaels on the Vsauce channel now too.
Really?
He's got all these little clones that are like like he's dude. He's like the Don now. He's like fucking Rick Ross
He just sits back lets the money come in. He's such a beast. Yeah, he doesn't even make the video
He's a who else is a beast who is real werewolf reacts to real werewolf footage. I don't know who that is nobody
Explanatory what it is. No, it's not. I watch the other day. He's a werewolf any
Just watches the werewolf footage and he goes, yeah, I don't know this could be real could be I don't know. I'm not sure
I can't tell yeah you're looking by the way someone that is light you were
looking mad werewolf Ian right now I'm not aware we'll look at him look at him
right now does he not look wolfish I'm not a werewolf look I'm enthralled by
him does that's a vampire that enthralls you not a werewolf then I'm not it then
teaches yeah he does he look like he has wolf traits or attributes right now I'm
not sure I'm sure starting to think he is he's scratching his butt I'm not a
a sniffing his ass right I just pooped and ate it I didn't do that they're very
wolf-like features if I did do that it would be during the full moon get that
bone out your mouth I don't have a bone in my mouth well what's that in your
this my teeth oh those are bones bones are not teeth yeah look at that cross do
you hate that no I think it's beautiful hey where was like crosses fetch fetch
that fetch the can go fetch oh he wants to fetch it so damn bad fetch fetch it
Fetch it. Good boy. Good boy. Fetch it. Come on. No, don't look the other way.
What the hell? Don't look at that. Hey. Hey, Cam. Cam. Cam. Look at me. Look at me.
Hey. No. Fetch it. Fetch. This is the worst werewolf ever. Fetch that. Fetch that thing.
I've seen better werewolves in London. I've seen better werewolves in
zombie movies. Yep. Yeah, that's right. You know what? There's none in there.
yeah no I did watch the other day I watched the the fall of Lil Xan fine I
guess I'll fetch this oh guess I'll have to fetch this you watch the fall of
little Xan I did he did an interview with the Tim Dillon did oh he did he
didn't interview with me too but he didn't really sit yeah no I guess Lil
bought a g-wagon and his manager took it from him. His manager said you're
not allowed to have this. What? Yeah he's not allowed to have a g-wagon because he
keeps buying stupid shit. He needs a yeah he needs like a Britney Spears situation.
Yeah. Of like a dad. I guess.
I think yeah that is so crazy what they did to Britney not really what did they
do to Britney kept her in a cage that's not true
I kept Britney Spears in a cage that's what I think you're thinking of King Kong
no yeah you're thinking they took Britney Spears out of Africa in a cage
no you're no you're thinking of
you think you know ships do you are you saying that they brought Britney Spears
from Africa and chains over the sea to America and then she climbed the Empire
State Building yes no you're thinking of King Kong it wait wait do you think did
Britney's SWAT planes out of the air like who's Britney SWAT I don't know
that is years did she swap planes out of the air like flies yeah it's King Kong
man yeah and she was she's low-key bad with it right
no the woman she was holding was no she was Amy Lynn no she was right cuz that's
King Kong you're thinking of King Kong man yeah like that's a video game King
wait okay Britney Spears Britney Spears of Jack black Britney Spears Adrian Brody
twas Brittany that killed the Spears that's what I heard see that's that's
her that's her new single that's King Kong Kong's new single
scary starting to get and then King Kong song the if you seek Amy you want me to
what that's King Kong though he wants me to do what he's got a mom mixed up what
did you ask him dream since I was 17 a matter man step on the scene asked me to
do something if you see he's trying to just ignore if you seek Amy what are you
saying that if you seek Amy don't stop no guys over and over came me my butt my
balls in my ass no me if you see came my face man if you see came my face in my
butthole come on man just if you see came me you that song it's not a song
you see came me if you see kaying my belly button in my cheeks if you see came
- If you see Kamey.
- You're weird for this.
- I'm not doing nothing weird, man.
- You're doing it weird.
- Great.
This is what I get for being a poptimist.
- That was--
- Does King Kong sing that one?
- That was the original draft.
The original title of If You See Kamey
was If You See Kamey My Ass.
(laughing)
- If you see Kamey my pink butthole.
♪ All the boys and all the girls want to ♪
♪ If you see Kamey my butthole ♪
- What was the, what's the lady,
what's the poker face thing where she's Gaga she says fucker she says fucker
face it's like what the hell how'd that get on TV fucker poker fucker face fucker
face no it's poker it's admitted to a different song there's poker face and
then fucker face let's get it started yeah let's get it started let's get
retarded yeah it's like it's poker face and fucker face and then yeah there's
also telephone and there's also special phone yeah and which is similar yeah
similar to the black with the black-eyed peas did pretty much Lady Gaga's the
only artist to do this - yeah yeah can a double song she had Fernando and then
she had Ritardo or Alejandro
Yeah, oh she also she also she also similar the the fucker face one. She had she had just dance and she had butt pants
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah, she had
I don't know bad romance do that one. It's she had
Bet no bet. I'm a romance fuck fuck
fuck her pants
She knocked it out of the park first try though, yeah love game
This ghost is what it's called. God damn. You suck at no naming all the songs from no, I just know
That it was it was love game and butt shame
It's all about pants and butts
That she got the board fuck and her and her face fucking your face
It's kind of gross that song is about having sex with a guy and pretending. It's a woman
I think that's a song is about having sex with a woman in a dress made of meat.
That's right.
Nah.
Yep.
Lady Gaga's butt is low-key fire.
When it's covered in steak.
Yep.
There's something so delicious about my wife in that dress.
My guy's eating raw meat.
I would love to cook her.
You should link her up with liver king.
I would love to throw her on the grill.
Lady Gaga, she'd probably let you do it.
She's such a stupid bitch.
I don't know that she might be cool. Yeah, she could be cool. What's that?
Everyone was like like in like
2009 or whatever like when Lady Gaga was like doing like all the fucking like the meat suits and stuff like she's doing all the
Fucking she was doing she was wearing like the weird outfits and stuff and everyone was like
This woman is crazy. Yeah, this woman is insane. It is funny
I never would have expected like in like when I'm middle school or whatever hearing like like yeah
Seeing all the Lady Gaga stuff. I would not have expected her to have the to be in the space and culture that she is now
Yeah, she's just like what normal is a lady with a nice boy. She's in movies
Country music yeah, she's in movies, and she has stands
Did she do if I if somebody told me Lady Gaga had a stand in 2009? I would have killed them
That's right. I was believable as hell. Are you kidding me the little monsters?
What that was her fan base the little monsters my mom had a good friend who got no monster tatted on his knuckles
Those live under the bed and come out at night. Yeah, you're thinking of mucinex. Yeah
There was a lot of guys that looked like mucinex people
Think of green athletes foot that lives in your toenails and watch his TV. Yeah, it opens up
That's his nail like that's the Jubilee a trap door. No. Yeah, the little the little yellows name is Julian
Who Blia no he does her twitch no it's not him
Just wrong. They're Marco Marco Rubio
That's a Florida man. Don't even get me started. I started on a Florida man. Yeah. Yeah, oh my god, Florida, man
This is what you guys do this Florida man fucking died. Yeah
Really Florida man fucking kills himself
Florida man pays for sex and then kills himself later floor man. Yeah freaking died
I hope not you could change Florida man Florida man ordered a freaking venti coffee at hipster Starbucks. Oh, yeah
That would pretty much be on the news
Zombie face zombie. Yeah
Florida man Brooklyn man wears thick frame glasses
Yeah
Florida man
Brooklyn man found wearing skinny jeans on the sidewalk with suspenders and skinny jeans
And dr. Martin boots. Did you see this zany headline science man wears pocket protector?
Flying man up in the sky nerd man has calculator
Don't even give me started on these nerd man story
Nerd man stays post credits at the Marvel movie. Yeah. Yeah, I heard Marvel man did that
Marvelman that was credit a woman Oh
Credits man
Lunch man enjoys a meal dude
The fucking the have you seen that that clip of the it's like the Batman post credits thing
where they have like the like the only thing at the in the post-credits scene of the Batman is just the Joker text that says
Goodbye, and everyone in the theater goes
Six society are the Riddler Joker sent a text message the Riddler sends a text at the end of the Batman
I don't think it goes to everyone's phone in the theater. I don't think that people should have like villains have phones and movies
Yeah, like that's not that's what he had a computer the Riddler who's paying for the phone
He had a computer with a webcam.
That's goofy as hell.
He shouldn't have a ring light.
He didn't have a ring light.
He did have a ring light.
Remember when he did the Twitch streams?
Oh, where he put the...
Where Riddler does the Twitch streams.
We should get those microphones that look like ears that people use.
I kept trying to tell Julio to buy one of those.
And he said no.
He said no.
He should do that for the Twitch.
Yeah, I know.
That's what I said.
We should do Jubio ASMR.
Yeah, that's what I was trying to get him to do.
It wouldn't work.
What am I doing? It doesn't taste very good, but I guess I will keep doing it.
What's he eating? The ear, that's what they do. Oh, they eat the ear? They like
put their mouth up to the ear and go like. Well, are they eating food when
they- If I could lick my own ear, I'd be out of my shit every day. No, they're
just- it's not very good, so I assumed he was eating food. So we just talk about
taste of his own mouth. I'm going to be doing the my it doesn't is very good. My
breath is not very good. I'm doing the bars meal into the ear. Dude, there's
that girl Amaranth and she like goes on twitch and she she's like the smacks her
lips in front of the yeah. I'm barely watching for two or three hours. How do
you spell it? A M O U R A N T H dude. You knew that too well. Yeah, she's
basically like it's disgusting. She sits in a bikini and plays just dance. Really?
And then she goes and she's she swaps into new different outfits
And she also writes her name on your her body writes your name on her body
If you yeah if you give like five or six bucks. She just like writes. Did she write Jubio TV?
So just write like Caleb like right on her arm
It's really really disgusting Wow sounds nasty Sodom and Gomorrah. Yeah, yeah, we need we need a we need a play to wipe out
title wave twitch streamers yeah yeah we need a big title wave and an arc where we have one
of every restaurant's food that'll be a good arc why not two two of every restaurant so
they can yeah they can have baby yeah burger two every restaurant could have babies if
you could have two if you could get like there was no if you could have that had a baby if
there if you salt and pepper if you get paprika if you could if you could cinnamon if you could
have if you could have a hamburger if you could have a hamburger and a hot dog and
you just like you put that you leave them at your house that you like leave
for a while hot burger with some mood yeah you come back hot burger exactly my
dad got a hamburger you guys dads ever make hot burgers for you hot burgers you
never made hot burgers you really didn't was that just a thing my dad invented no
you split up a hot dog cook it and put it on a hamburger bun oh I thought it was a
different burger but hot burger you know the hamburger meat into a hot dog shape
oh no that's that's a sausage that's a there's a thing on the on the Cosby show
that might that I was obsessed with as a kid which is the bacon burger dog
Cosby show episode where Bill Cosby makes a baby you were obsessed with his
attitude no yep but you got some say you could leave them together in a room with
maybe say what's up some nice music playing some jazz and then you leave and
you come back and it's a hot dog that the bun is a hamburger man I love fucking a
jazz yeah fucking the bitches brew dude that's what I do
no it's jazz. If it has a trumpet or like any... synced up perfectly.
This is losing my fucking mind. It's jazz, it's my favorite jazz song. Hold on, hold on, listen to this part.
My car plays jazz when I back it up. That's my smoke detector. It's my jazz smoke detector. Okay, yep, they pretty much did that,
that Nathan for you they did yeah. Oh no, it's a blues. Oh blue it was blues you're
out mm yeah you're out. I'm telling Nathan for you.
Hold on. I got for me right now. Hey Nathan
for you
I oh I just got I just understood the name of the show. Yeah, it's Caleb and
it's me and I don't remember why I'm calling you. Patrick's out Patrick's out
basically. Thank you. Remember that, remember... I don't know if I should say this.
Bet you don't.
We have a friend who lives around him, near him, next to him. And someone like...
He lives in his air conditioning.
Yeah, he lives in his air conditioning.
It lives in his ducts. It's an elf.
He's got a little Pomeranian.
We know a borrower, okay? We know a borrower. Fine.
he had to fight a Pomeranian. Our friend who's a borrower in Nathan
Fielder's house had to fight a Pomeranian with a toothpick. And it was huge.
Because they were going for the same ball. Yeah. Which is the problem.
The ball to a borrower is basically an RV. I mean well yeah a ball like if you
think about like humanity inventing the wheel, the ball is the borrower's
wheel. Yeah. That's like the most important invention of all time. I
I didn't I feel like the world would be completely different if we had invented
the ball before the wheel. Yeah, because the ball is a is a wheel on a three
dimensional wheel. I think we did invent the ball before the wheel because I
don't think it's just like it's just a role as a concept for a perfect a
perfect ball. Oh perfect. Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't realize it had to be perfect
in order to do it. Super bounce. Yeah, perfect ball. Once we invented rubber. I
mean boss I mean I like God I invented rubber before the week yeah you don't
have we have all this rubber but we don't know what to do with it rubber
rubber is a naturally occurring no it's not so you invent you invent a ball you
don't invent a ball you invent a ball but not rubber is what you're saying
yes no you're wrong a ball is not naturally occur before the wheel we'd be
bouncing everywhere yeah same if we invented rubber I think we'd be better
rubber comes out if we invented rubber at first rubber first we would have
flubber by you guys are pissing me off rubber is a tree thing yeah but you have
to turn it into the rubber nope you just spit on the rubber buns and liquor
remember that joke no what are you even saying I don't remember it either I just
remember the punchline is a rubber buns and liquor you're useless I need
something to throw I have to throw something at you how did it see that I
got fucking deflected it back to you damn there's like link versus Ganon your
favorite it's like link versus no it's his favorite that's why it's his
favorite game you it's like versus Ganon you got that for me it's right there
It's Caleb's favorite game. I'm sorry. I don't have awesome alternative comedy posters like you over there. What chocolate cake city
Yeah
Yeah, but you have you do have a drawing that I made for you. I have your drawing
I have another drawing says I am my ancestors wildest dreams. I
Have it's kind of that's kind of that's a dangerous thing for you to have on. Yeah that phrase
phase. I think that's the phrase doesn't come off great. Wait till I 23 me comes
back
yeah. I guess we should do that. Yeah, we're gonna figure out what we're gonna
do. Look at this guy. What are these freaking months? We're going on a game
show called What Race Are You? Yeah, I'm the control in this experiment. The
controller sent something 100% and we're gonna play the game like with your body.
Yeah, you're gonna become our human. You're the joystick.
Mm.
What the hell
the other day something fell out of the ceiling really yeah, that's a wood
piece or up there. I love it.
Yep,
I do that a lot. We see that you see that hole in between those two pipes.
There's like a loud. There's like a clattering noise and then it's a few
like rocks fell. Oh cool. Yeah, whenever whenever the manager comes up to me and
I'm like sitting down at TGIF Fridays he says how's your buffalo chicken mac and
cheese? I look at him right and he's like I LOVE IT!
You say I don't care! Yeah it's like oh we ran out of medium cups is a small okay. I don't care!
I love it! We ran out of large we're at Cold Stone we ran out of large cups or
what's a gotta have it's uh gotta have it's. You ran out of gotta have it's. What do you want instead?
head. What do you love it? I've been getting they be getting so mad at me at
Starbucks. I keep fucking instead of using their venti. What I just say like
it love it got to have it. They get pissed off. Can I have a got to have it
coffee with a Reese's peanut butter? You know you're going to put the butter
fingers in there and I want to see you chop it up. I want to plus is my
birthday. Sing the song. They sing this on me. Yeah, it's when you tip places
my tip day. Sing my song. Yeah, it's payday. I'm going to tip you. They should
sing the song if it's your birthday and you don't have to tip yeah that's you
know they didn't do that at my cold stone. I didn't know that they didn't do
the tip song. I don't know if it's like mine or franchised and like they didn't
make no though that sounds like a rebel cold. So you have to report that it was
fucking crazy. I didn't know that that was you. You probably left too soon, but
that's like if you go to this was there. What would you do if you went to and
That's like if you go to a McDonald's and you see in the back one of the employees is sitting
down.
Like you need to call somebody.
Yeah.
You know who that employee is, the ice cream machine.
Here's what I do, take a bite out of my straw cover, load that bad boy up.
I'm sending a fucking ball of my spit over 200 feet.
Spitballs, I miss.
I've been practicing on my ligature.
I miss spitballs, dude.
I miss shooting spitballs.
Shooting them.
What do you mean you miss?
You can do it right now.
different when you do it to the substitute go to the school. I'm not
going to go to the school. It's not allowed because I first of all I'm a
grown man. I don't need to go to school anymore. My school is now the school of
the streets the hard knocks second of all change your school to be the school of
the hard knocks it went from you got transferred. Yeah school hard knocks is
not really a good school. No, it's not accredited. It's like full sale. Yeah. Are
I'm studying game design.
I'm studying game design at the school of hard knocks.
I'm studying game design at the school of hard knocks and yes the game is CeeLo.
Nice.
I'm trying to reinvent CeeLo.
Yeah.
Adding another dice.
I studied game design at Hogwarts.
Really?
Wow.
Was the game Quidditch?
No, it was Wizard Chess.
Oh.
The other game from Harry Potter.
There's a third game in Harry Potter that people don't talk about.
What is it?
Buffalo Soldier.
It's Chase the Goblin.
Yeah.
queer yeah big game at Hogwarts. I think it was defeat the Voldemort and I think
Harry Potter got up a man that wasn't a game that was real shit. I think he
a hundred percent of that game speed run. I don't know. I think I think one
horcrux is one there's a game there's there's the fourth game. So there's
defend defeat the Voldemort in the fourth game was defend the defend the
bathroom defend the bathroom yeah yeah bathroom tower defense bathroom tower
defense and great and if you see if you see anybody yeah trying to go into that
morning Myrtle stall uh-huh mm-hmm for somebody who's so obsessed with who uses
what bathroom JK Rowling you let boys go in the girls bathroom yep mm-hmm I said
it and you let ghosts go in the bathroom and you let a moaning ghost yeah oh
Oh great, and you let a dragon go to the Quidditch tournament.
And you let a troll in the dungeon!
There was a troll in the bathroom in that movie too!
Dude, she'll let anybody in the bathroom.
Uh huh, but now, you know what it is?
She's trying to repent.
In the bathroom.
Just keep him at the bathroom!
I saw a big troll in the bathroom!
(laughter)
Yeah, I think she's trying to repent for her sins
of letting too many damn people in the bathroom.
bathroom yeah now she's now she's going way too far she's gone she's gone mad
listen bitch just she's got absolutely bollocks stop it at a just crazy
werewolves and monsters uh-huh I mean mm-hmm she's you've gone bloody
you've got a bloody baller on blade aft man you're definitely listen mate you've
officially gone mad mm-hmm yeah and I think blokes and and and birds should be
able to use whatever bathrooms they want it's true whatever lose whatever lose
they please. It's funny that that's just exactly what like Congress in the UK
sounds like. Yeah yeah. I think that bloke should use the bathroom. Yes I think bloke should use the
bathroom. I think these Tories are mad todgers yeah. Oh well I've got a todger for me nonce.
Mm-hmm yeah. You got a todger for me nonce? There's a nonce in the neighborhood. You have your own nonce?
There's a nonce in the neighborhood and he's gonna get a todgering from me.
Nonce in the neighborhood sounds like it was like a very popular kids show in the
UK until yeah, I call Jim will fix it yep. Okay, all right, stop it swag poop
dot com slash shows. We had a late Chicago show. It's eighteen plus. So if
you couldn't go to the first one because it was twenty one plus, you should get a
ticket of this one. There's eighteen plus and four minus. So if you're under
four, you're welcome. Yeah, if you're above eighteen, you're also welcome.
Yeah, and but that in between ranges no four to eighteen, you're going to have a
really hard time. Yep. All right, bye bye.