Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
- Premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Now you can turn on your video now.
- Happy New Year.
Hey, say Happy New Year first.
- No, my webcam's really not working.
- Happy New Year.
- Happy New Year. - Come on.
You're telling me you're not faking your video off
because you were wearing a pink dress
and you wanted to reveal it?
- You have a costume on.
I know you have a costume on right now.
- No, I don't.
- I know for a fact you're wearing a costume.
I look like grayscale Charlie Brown. You do. You actually do. I know. What does this say?
Wow! Tom and Jerry. Where did you get that? He just said he got it from Kai. I didn't hear it.
The infamous double act in a merry song and dance. Nice. That's beautiful. It's so beautiful.
I uh I I've been um I think the Big M maybe is gonna kill my whole family.
Why?
I think the Big M Riverboat Casino is where my entire family got COVID.
Did your entire family go?
Yep. Grandma, Grandpa,
I think you went and you gave your whole family COVID.
I don't have COVID! I'm the only one who's not positive, bro!
I think you're patient zero.
I'm patient zero? Bro, I'm patient hero. I'm gonna I'm I'm yeah.
I'm Captain Save-a-Patient.
No.
Watch me.
Mm-mm.
Brother's got it.
[Laughter]
Oh my god.
What's up?
Oh man.
He left the room.
He's so mad.
Wow.
When he comes back I have to ask him something.
I'm not fu-- I'm not fucking doing this!
I can't do this!
I just turned this webcam on.
And boy is he wearing...
Caleb, I have to ask you something.
Why do you even own this?
It's Halloween, it's Christmas!
I have to ask you one thing.
Do I make you horny, baby?
Yes! That's why I can't do it!
Why is it so intricate?
That's a velvet blazer.
It looks so good!
My brother got me this for Christmas.
Oh my god, dude.
Holy fuck that's so good.
Oh, the lace.
Mm-hmm.
Are you just gonna wear this every day?
I'm gonna wear it for a week.
Probably.
You gotta start 2022 off right.
Please just go, you gotta, are you gonna go skateboarding in it?
Have you already gone skateboarding in it?
Oh, I wish.
what do you mean i i was scared dude i'm too scared of what all in down and
scraping this thing is just a lot of skaters are going to see you and and
yeah you're scared that thirteen-year-old in a welcome but he is
going to make fun of you
yeah
maybe
yeah you are
i mean somebody do you have to take the frill off it's like it's choking me so
it's so small
uh... god
we didn't show you there's a finalist to
on that is great like is there a pretty little a situation going on to you and
on these
are you aware of the other guy it comes with its got velvet pants
are you wearing them
yeah can you stand up and do it world
but i cleaned my room
you guys you can tell it off
i'd holy shit bro
yet the idea to bunch of laundry and now
My room's clean.
Whoa, dude.
Oh my god.
I gotta say, I mean.
That is, dude.
I hope you know this means war.
Yeah?
Yeah.
For the rest of the year?
I'm coming, I'm coming correct next time.
Yeah?
I'm coming correct.
You're not the only one who can wear costumes now.
There will be no lacking next time you see me.
I will, I mean I'm gonna pull out something crazy.
Check this out.
What?
No, no.
What is it?
- It's Boston Powers.
- Damn.
- That's pretty good too.
- That's pretty good.
- Now it's Boston Powers too.
It's a double costume.
- Yeah, so do like some jokes about Boston Powers now.
- Yeah, do Boston Powers now.
- Put your headphones on to do Boston Powers.
- Now it's Jacqueston Powers.
- That's Jacques hat?
- Yeah.
- Nice.
- Speaking of Jacques, if you hear this,
I think this is either Jacques or Palmas, but this is a custom one-of-one CBS News Seeking
Derangements hat that ended up in my backpack at the live show back in July.
Ended up?
It did.
That boy stole it.
Ended up.
Look at what it says on the back.
What?
Gay?
Yag?
No.
It says F.A.G. on it.
Yag?
Oh, okay.
Can someone, could you take a screenshot of this?
Don't worry, I got it already.
That's pretty good.
Yeah, so you had an amazing Christmas, I see.
What are you gonna do?
Those MAGA powers?
That doesn't even make sense.
You put on my MAGA hat.
It's so easy, Austin White Powers.
Wow, okay.
Okay, you can do that next episode.
I'll let you borrow the costume.
(laughing)
- Oh, fuck.
- Yeah.
- Did you get any other good toys?
- My brother also got me big skateboard wheels.
He got me 60 millimeter wheels, dude.
They're so big.
- Is that really big?
- Is that good or bad that they're big?
- 60 millimeters don't seem very big to me.
- I don't know if it's good or bad that they're big.
I've just always wanted to try them.
- Okay.
- And.
- All right.
skateboard expert so yeah you don't know whether big wheels are good or bad kind
of mix well okay okay okay now it okay big wheels big wheels are good for
transition and for cars yep bicycle I guess you know what I could do is if I
go fast enough if I go fast enough definitely ride through grass rains
could you put on a skateboard a tank style tread that was high right be so
cool you can climb up the wall yeah I think that might really help yeah that
could be awesome yeah it'd be helpful yeah or or put like what's that shit
pine tar on it like oh yeah like a bad girl like you're a yeah throwing a
baseball what about a skateboard that you ride inside of for four wheels with a
a handle. A handle? No, a wheel. You need another wheel. Five wheels. What about a need to go
with a model? Dude, I'm sore that you ride inside of with tank treads and a gun on the
front. Don't in the Austin Powers outfit tell us you're so hungover. I am so horny baby.
Okay that's better. I'm so... Nah, I'm hungover as shit. I wish I went out in this last night.
would have been fun tell you what I did if I went out some some Aldi wine and
listen my brother throw up last night that's swag that was a yes I was I
watched Borat and today I flew home hey here's a question what this so these
days you what you go to the airport you see that they have a cell phone parking
lot here we go right so I don't understand no I already don't understand
- It's just, I got this.
So they have some, they have a--
- I don't know what a cell phone parking lot is.
- Well that's what I'm saying.
They got these signs that say cell phone parking lot, right?
And it's like, okay, what the hell is that, right?
You go, but then you go over there,
like today I went over there.
Nobody's on their cell phone.
You know what people are doing is they're in cars, right?
- Whoa.
- So here's my, well, here's my question.
They should call it a car parking lot.
- Uh-huh.
- But I see why that is confusing, right?
- I don't, I'm already really confused.
I have literally no idea what you're talking about.
- Let me finish!
I see why that's confusing.
So they probably just called it a cell phone parking lot
because it's a little less--
- What is a cell phone parking lot?
What are you talking about? - I don't know.
That's what I'm talking, that's what I'm trying to ask you.
I've never seen a sign that says, "It's a cell phone parking lot and you see people in cars."
What is happening right now?
You said there's a sign that says "cell phone parking lot and you see people in cars."
Cell phone lot!
And the people aren't, there's no one on their cell phone, everybody's in their car.
Why is, what?
In the parking lot.
What are you talking about?
There's lots at airports with little photos of cell phones.
Yeah, they have restaurants and planes and stuff, there's a lot of stuff at the airport.
I don't know what you're talking about.
No, I'm not saying there's lots of stuff.
I'm not saying there's lots of stuff.
I'm not saying there's lots of stuff. I'm saying that there are
Lots that are at the the yeah, there's lots of cell phones a lot of people there's the set there's lots of cell phone
At the airport. What are you saying? No what you're talking about the airport every airport now is okay
I have a lot of cell phones. Yeah
Cell phones has lots no has cell phone parking lots. And what does that even mean?
What is a cell phone parking lot?
That's my question because you go to it and everybody's in a car.
Okay, so I just found I've googled it. A cell phone lot is a parking lot.
That's what it says.
Oh, you know what it is? You got to be kidding me.
It says a cell phone lot is a parking lot typically located at airports where people can wait before picking up passengers.
Why would they call it a cell phone lot?
I don't know. You did a really bad job of explaining that. I did not...
I didn't know what it was! I just see the signs!
You said it was in an airport, first of all.
It's in...
It's clearly outside an airport.
An airport? Okay, so...
You think a parking lot is inside the airport?
Listen to me.
Yeah?
Do you think that the fucking runways are in the airport? Yes.
Do you think the parking lot of McDonald's is in the McDonald's?
that is in mcdonalds at mcdonalds no not at not at it's at I said at you said I
say that they have a lot in the airport they should have yes actually yes they
do you know why well because it's a parking garage it's a parking garage it's
an airport or different buildings airports are multiple buildings with
Ever heard of a concourse, idiot?
No.
What's that?
Fuck, I don't know.
I don't know what that is.
Now you're getting in a preacher zone.
He's taking off one article of clothing every five minutes.
I can't wait to see where this goes.
Now you're not so on, not so on Powers.
I'm Sebastian Maniscalco now.
Austin Powers, I need-
How can you-
I need in the friends who can ease did you got you know nowadays kids are there on
their cell phones in these parking lots but and they seem to be harking not to
the music of the angels from on high yeah I the we used to love watching awesome
Austin Powers but now these these kids are more worried about their awesome
passwords. He's taking off more clothes. You're not even committing. There's nothing Austin
about you. You literally didn't even do the Boston Powers thing. You're so lazy. This
is why Caleb is the one who wears costumes. Yeah, you know what? This is a big responsibility.
Because when I wear the costumes, I embody... He makes us argue about the costume for an
hour straight when he wears a costume. That's a very unique skill, I'd like to say. We got
- Barely one minute.
(laughing)
- We got one minute of audio off of,
like a very expensive, obviously.
- Best costume that's been on the show so far.
- The best costume, by far.
Beats the chef, beats the Jacques.
- Thank you, Eric.
- That was Eric?
- Eric got me that, yeah.
- Yeah, I bought a bigger. - Hey, check this out.
Check this out.
Did I ever show you this?
I bought, remember those t-shirts I bought?
- Yeah.
- Oh yeah, we talked about it on the episode.
- You have a t-shirt with numbers on it.
- Yeah, I bought a bootleg Hanes Tee.
How are you talking about this more than the fucking Austin Powers outfit you were just
in?
I'm still wearing the velvet pants.
The numbers are not it.
I'm so comfortable.
And he's like, "Yeah, check it out.
Look at these numbers.
Look, eight, three."
What do the numbers mean?
This could be a phone number or something.
Yeah, you should head over to the airport cell phone lot and try to use your cell phone
to call the phone number there.
Well, that's the only thing.
Is there really good service in the cell phone lot?
I think that's it.
I think maybe you get better service there because...
I think that is what it is.
I guess that makes sense.
Yeah, because there's so many planes.
I thought that they just wanted a different lot and they didn't know what to call it.
Yeah, well it's like when they name a concert venue like the Xfinity Center.
Yeah, this one is cell phones took care of the bill for this.
I'm pretty owned for my flight, man.
I'm yeah, luckily I flew not knowing if I had or did not have COVID and then found out I don't as soon as I land
Nice, so you're not a criminal. I was gonna be really bad or really but it turns out I'm really really good
Yeah, yeah, it was up in the air there for a minute. I was almost a well get it later like I did
What doesn't it know?
- Get it later, what does that mean?
- That means it could be in your body.
It could be in your body right now and then it could like--
- You didn't like fly, like what do you mean?
You can get it later.
- You can get COVID later.
I mean, I guess you can, yeah, you can.
You can get it later. - Do you wanna go
get it later?
- No, I don't wanna go get COVID.
- Yeah.
- Do you wanna go grab some later?
Mm-hmm
Yeah, I seriously do. Yeah, I miss you guys. I think I think everybody should have like
Should get like 10 free flights without having to get tested first. Yeah, I agree
Also, I don't really care if I if anybody dies ever
Yeah, you know what I mean? Yeah, that's it like the the thing like everyone's like
Oh like don't go home for Christmas or like don't do this. You'll kill grandma
Do you I don't care like I'm waiting on like probably no
Inheritance from I don't know my grandma
Yeah, you know like I don't like my grandma's been dead forever
My grandma is basically a like a food machine to me. Yeah, like I have no I mean
I love my grandma as much as I love a like a vending machine
Honestly, like I walk up to her and I say
E7 which is her lasagna. Yeah, and then I and then I get it it's free. There's the best vending machine ever
And she has a big TV. Mm-hmm
It's honestly more likely that if you go home for Christmas your grandmother's probably gonna kill you because I mean she's what yeah
She's pretty old. She's probably got some insane diseases
festering somewhere in her body my my grandmother is a
Spanish colonizer actually so she has a lot of really weird diseases.
Yeah, that's like she's like an incubator to create the next strain.
You know what I just remembered is that she actually is Spanish.
Really? Yeah, isn't that weird? Are you white Spanish? I'm white Spanish. Yeah, her mom was
Spanish.
Whoa. Dude, I'm Espanol. Yeah, you're like Judy Cortez.
I'm straight up Cortez family line. That's why I'm so good at rolling my arms. Are there any spies in your family?
I'm also there's a heavy spy current. Yeah. Yeah, I fan. Yeah, there's a it skips a generation though. My dad was a spy. I
Mean that the spy kids were Mexican though. Yeah
That's a I mean, you're the one who brought them up. So yeah, I didn't know that like why are you?
You're doing you're doing race watching you well you were
You brought up Juni Cortez and then you thought we were
Just talking about Mexican people now like you are tried to I said Spanish and you were like, how can I get to Mexican?
Mexican my Spanish accent
Yeah, I I
I think we should talk about Spy Kids.
Spy Kids is awesome.
I re-watched Spy Kids 3 recently.
I watched Spy Kids with my nephews.
I talked about this last episode.
Yeah you did.
Fuck.
Dude, you're in a loop.
You're in a fucking loop.
You're in my brain.
How about we talk about our beautiful New Year's Eves?
Yeah.
You did Borat.
Yeah, I did Borat.
That's the only one I did.
I set up a couch.
It's something actual.
He went out and partied.
Uh huh.
And that's why it looks like this.
up and he's a degenerate piece of shit oh yeah me I was having a nice I was having
a Spanish New Year's Eve yeah my fully Spanish family we were eating what's
that shit hammo ham bone ham ham bone ham sandwich what is now what's that
expensive ham on ham on ham on what? Ham on cheese. Ham on cheese and bread. Ham on...
Ham on Swiss. Ham on cheese and toast. Ham on the Kruger. Ham on the Aldi. Ham on Iberico.
Oh, that's what I'm thinking of.
Jamona Barrico.
I ate that for New Year's Eve with my whole Spanish family.
Girlfriend wanted to watch the New Year's Rockin' Eve thing, the music thing, and she
made the fatal mistake, which I tried to warn her about.
She turned it on at like 6 p.m.
Oh.
Can you believe that?
So it just sat there all day?
Yeah.
Just doing nothing?
That's when they're not even doing anything yet.
just like we turned it on when she was like oh let's watch the New Year's Eve
coverage she turned on it was like it was just like Kyle Rittenhouse Kyle
Rittenhouse was it that is sick dude it was our boy it was Pete D there we did
we literally we turned it off before then because it was so man that's a
I started way too early.
Wait, who's Pete D?
When Pete D was on, dude, I was watching B Sagdieff.
Shit, they need to get Borat into the next New Year's Eve.
He'd probably say something foul shit.
He'd probably compare the ball to some other kind of ball in a disgusting manner.
Do you guys hear about Betty White?
No.
I just found this out.
What?
you were dressed as her? Apparently yeah, apparently they found her in her apartment. She looked like a
crumpled up napkin. Yeah. Yeah. She fell down the stairs. Yeah, she apparently fell down the stairs
and then fell through the floor at the bottom of the stairs into the basement and fell into a bucket
of bleach. Apparently she fell down the stairs from the emperor's new groove and she's still
falling. They know she's dead but she's still on her way down the stairs. Apparently she was
playing basketball and some kid like crossed over and totally twisted her ankle and her
foot fell off and she died from blood loss.
I mean we gotta get this fentanyl out of these drugs.
I know.
Absolutely.
It's killed so many.
So many.
Especially Betty White.
Apparently like Betty White, like right before she died she was skydiving and all her limbs
flew off like a Lego man.
Yeah, yeah, she fell in that she got sucked into an HVAC system. Yeah, yeah,
for her hundredth birthday, she wanted to get really, really close to a jet
turbine. Yeah, it's like she was like, oh, it's only I plan my hundredth big
a hundredth birthday bash. I've only I only have a few days till I turn a
hundred. I gotta make sure I don't die. So I'm gonna lock myself in this room
and then she got sucked into the central air. She said I'm gonna lock myself in
this sealed room with no windows and no no air conditioning and just take some
deep breaths to relax. Betty White was uh she was sitting on her couch listening
to a happy birthday but the the speakers were too big and too loud that it shot
all of her skin off when happy birthday started to play. It was like at the beginning of Back to the Future.
bones flew. Like the Mortal Kombat Fatality. Like multiple rib cages and skulls.
She basically fell into all the clogs and big bin and she got turned into nothing.
Yeah it was really fucked up and sad. Yeah. She actually fell into an assembly
line and got turned into a toy. Somebody found her in their chili at
Wendy's and he complained. Apparently she actually died like months ago. She died
in a spirit Halloween in October and they didn't find her body. They just
thought her body was part of the decorations for like months. She would.
The thing is, I'll say this about Betty White, she kept it tight for a hundo. Oh
definitely. Have you ever met a hundred-year-old? I've met one
hundred year old before I don't like I was like 96 or something great aunt Ruth
and I don't like I don't like old people at all got really confused and started
taking her top off right in front of me I saw her boobs okay
score and then I she like got really confused she started getting naked and I
looked at her I was like seven or eight I said you look like a dinosaur yeah like
a real bad back. Oh my god. Oh yeah, the curved back. Yeah. Yeah. Oh yeah. I met somebody recently
who is like maybe 37 or something. A woman who has a hunchback. But like not, but I've
known her for a while and she didn't always have a hunchback and she developed one. I
was like that's tough. That year where you're finally like. Yeah. I, oh, I, my, my. You become
I'm an old person.
My posture is irreversible now.
Millennials be on the computer so long they get a hunchback.
Me I sit at the table I eat my lunch comma snack.
Yep.
Or lunch pack.
I mean that works too.
Yeah well I said lunch comma snack.
You could say snack pack too.
The comma's silent so it's lunch snack.
Well no, lunch.
It has to rhyme.
What?
Fuck.
Woo wee!
Woo wee?
Is that your...
Woo-wee!
Is that you bringing that in?
That's how I get my brain back. I'm really shutting down.
Alright, let's wake you up.
Okay. New Year's resolutions.
What are we doing different in 2021?
How are we coming in 2021?
As a squad.
I'm coming in a sock.
I'm gonna tell you, I'm gonna...
I'm coming in a different sock than last year.
The big two. I'm changing it out. Okay. One, first million. Two, no more Mr. Nice Guy.
Wow. That's my big two for this year. That's a good one. Pretty good, right? Yeah.
I'm going to quit making excuses for women and I'm going to try to hold my poop in the whole year.
Those are my two. If we just get two.
I'm gonna try to hold in my poop until I become a big poop balloon.
And i'm not gonna make any excuses for these women no more.
That's facts.
Oh, you already got you three strikes bitch. Can I add a number three to mine?
Uh, if I can add a third, yeah. Yeah, my number three second million.
Whoa.
Okay, my number three is at the end of the year after I held my poop in the whole time
I lay a giant poop egg. What does it hatch into? And then more just shit all the way through.
My new year's resolutions is I'm gonna, I guess this year 2022, this is the year I find a wife
and immediately have a kid. Nice. I could see it happening. Yeah, that could work for you.
I don't think you have it in. Number four, become more cybernetic throughout the year.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck. I want to lose a woman.
Number three, I send the kid to Iraq.
[Laughs]
Right when he's not even a year old?
And he has to find his way back to me.
You also, wait, you only have four women.
If any women want to help me out with this, I'm going to have one giant kid.
You have to be the biggest woman in the world.
You have to be like a seven foot tall spider of a woman.
Spider?
You have to be spider woman and you have to give birth to my son and we put him in Iraq
and he has to get back to us.
You realize the gestational period for a human child is nine months so you have very little
time to get this woman, this huge woman pregnant and find her.
I have to find her by the end of the month.
much yeah if you especially if you want to like like sign him up for the military
like you know no no not them no no no he goes over there lone wolf you want to
sing goes over there alone well baby with a bandolier and a bandana into the
middle of be a sire rat that should be the name of the movie they make about
about his life they rack which is here which is just a just a country by the
way Iraq is just a country you're the one who assumed he was going in the
military yeah I guess you're right yeah I guess I do that there's not a war
there's not a war going on in Iraq right now number five I will I will put on and
perform the biggest beatboxing concert ever in Central Park I think will the
stars be there okay wait wait wait every star number six make friends with every
star yeah number four for me is that my son has to go over there and start a war
with Iraq single one man or yeah like the assassination of Ferdinand
literally Pat you're kind of describing doing here no this is what happens in
no because he's a tall baby yeah and it's Iraq what about Iraq is anything
like dude okay first of all like a wreck is the planet from dude I don't I don't
believe you I don't believe that that's what it's called
and how did you go from awesome powers to fucking gangsta so fast no uh-huh oh
that's another thing I want I'm trying to be more hood this year yeah definitely
more hood I'm trying to be more hood and mo ghetto yeah this year specifically
yeah yeah I feel like I got to turn it up way higher after being in North
Carolina and seeing some friends from high school I'm like they've lapped me
uh-huh yeah I gotta make it back I think Jacques said that I should start
wearing bandanas and I think that maybe that's true dude no you don't think I
look good right now you look like don't are you kidding me you look like shit I
don't look like shit are you kidding what are you talking about you look like
the fucking guy from office space which guy the guy who turns down the wrap in
car that's you. Yeah? Yeah. I don't look like Bret Michaels? No. No. Sorry. Number five
resolution I start dressing more like Bret Michaels. Honestly that's a much
cooler resolution. That is good. Dude yeah have you oh my god my aunt did you guys see the
shirt my aunt got me for Christmas? No. No. She got me a true religion v-neck.
Nice. Oh dude. It says true religion on it with like the logo but like pretty deep
v-neck dude I look like I put it on I look like I own a cell phone kiosk it's so
sick you guys should have seen the fits that Noah was taking on the on the river
boat casino I saw it bro it was insane the Fendi belt with the big suit he also
the next day so yeah he had a giant tan suit the Fendi belt and then like a
giant chain and he like dyed his hair black yeah crazy and then the next day
Send me a picture.
Yeah, we gotta see this.
The next day we went to, we went and got some sushi and he pulled up wearing, he wore the
truey jeans.
He wore the Fendi belt.
Dude, I gotta get truey so bad.
He wore a glow gang football jersey.
Dude.
He's 24 years old.
What are you talking, why are you saying that like that's a bad thing?
No, it just looked, it was awesome.
I loved it.
And he just sat there eating sushi.
Dude, that's-- Noah's pimp as fuck.
Dude, it was next level, bro.
I've never seen anything like it.
He's come out of his cocoon in a major way.
That's so cool.
Yeah.
No, I forget what resolution number I'm on.
I think seven.
No more rolled foods.
No more rolled foods?
No sushi, no burritos, no wraps.
Whoa.
What about a fruit roll-up?
If you unroll it?
No rolled foods.
If you unroll it and I don't see it before it's unrolled, I could pretend it's a fruit
line and not a fruit roll up.
Well, what if I like, you know, like you deconstruct the sushi?
As long as I don't see it while it's rolled, I'll eat it.
What about...
What do you know it's sushi?
What about like a nigiri, like a hand...
Just a hand thing.
If it's rolled?
It's not rolled.
I wouldn't call that rolled.
Okay, here's the thing about rolled food, it's a circle.
And that...
Are you off of all circles?
No.
Or all...
Just rolled foods.
just rolled foods yeah okay so about a crescent rolled food symbolizes that's
more of all that means you're never going to digest it what about it just
stays in your body forever it's got all those layers in a circle that's a
crescent old food so I could eat half of it yeah okay that makes sense yeah top
or the bottom I could I could just eat I just can't eat at all hmm okay I think
I think this might be the worst resolution.
I was at the word is going to get on that tip soon. You'll see you say no
rolled foods.
No,
I think so.
no,
no foods.
You can't have any rolled food.
We're only eating triangles from now on.
You can't have any world food,
snap any food that's been rolled. If you see if you if you see it after it's
unrolled,
it's okay.
You just can't see it while it's rolled, or your body will know that it's rolled.
He has like no, like, he's not tying it to any sort of his like weird philosophical like
man-woman thing, he's just like...
And also, you just, you cannot eat anything rolled.
It's just, it's just, you just can't.
I won't even say it's not right, actually, I'll just say you can't do it.
You shouldn't be eating it.
You just shouldn't be, it's not for you.
It's not for me.
It's not allowed, it's not for anybody.
You can't do that. You can't have any rolled food.
I'm gonna read.
Rolling is for a cigarette.
Or a sleeping bag.
Or my sleeping bag.
Also you sleep in a sleeping bag.
You have to sleep in a sleeping bag.
The biggest problem here is that lobster rolls are...
What's he trying to say about lobsters?
Connect it, Pat!
What's he saying about lobsters?
You had a good one!
Fuck dude
What does he suck so close? I know I know dude. I had to sabotage the I sabotage myself
He says they're red right yeah, what's he say about lobsters his whole thing. Maybe we should start reading
I don't understand to fight each other or something have to fight Rob
Monster there's some kind of hierarchy where they all have
Yeah, think about a dinner roll is it's not a rolled food. You can eat it
That is true a dinner rolls not a rolled food. It just has the word roll. Yeah. Yeah
Sweet rolls, what did the butter sweet? What did the butter get at school? What Jordan?
On a roll, I just got it
No, I have to joke from a joke book. I had in like second grade
Yeah
Hey Pat, hey Pat. What did the second place a butter who didn't get on our roll say? He
said, I've never been so unsalted in my life. That's a pretty good one, right? That's also
a joke book one you guys have a parking lot at the airport called a cell phone
lot and there's no cell phones. I admit it. I think that I don't I think that might have
been a one of the minor Muppets that has no name you know when they do like a
finger puppet basically yeah who yeah usually it's a bird it's a bird sitting
has no name. The minor muppet who has no name. The other day I remember. That's a two sentence
horror story. I saw a minor muppet he had no name. Yeah. Hey what's ET short for? What?
Because he's got little legs. I said. That one's pretty good actually. I said what not why so your
answer didn't make any sense. No it's pretty funny. No. It's like. Sorry it didn't flow grammatically.
You know what I did get for Christmas and I'm pretty excited about this damn keyboard.
I'm gonna be- What's brown and sticky?
Your ass and your butthole and probably your penis and your balls and your taint too
because all the shit that you've been squirting on it because you wear a diaper
and you pretty much live in a diaper and you never changed it.
A stick.
You wear a diaper with a chastity belt on top so that nobody can unlock your-
Cameron, wait, Cameron got it.
Brown and sticky, a stick?
Okay.
What did the ranch say to the refrigerator?
What did the ranch say to the ridgerator?
I don't know what a ridgerator is.
Close the door, can't you see I'm dressing?
Do you guys want to know something that shattered my reality yesterday?
What?
What I just remembered?
I did one of those Instagram "what animal are you" filters and it said I was an ant.
Holy shit.
It's like the most- What?
The worst experience I've ever had in my life.
Are you fucking serious, man?
You like shattered me spiritually.
You ant.
It was the worst- You ant ass bitch.
It was God getting one last jab in at me in 2021.
You're an ant?
Why is it even an option?
I don't think...
You're nothing.
It's literally Imbia.
The data doesn't add up.
The other ones are like
you're a monkey, you're a cat,
you're a lizard.
I don't think that
test has enough like...
I don't trust it.
I don't think it's backed by science.
It's not peer reviewed.
Yeah.
It's not peer-reviewed.
No, it's powered by magic.
I'm not letting them say that about my friend.
That means it's the most true of all.
Tell me who the app developer is.
Tell me who that created that app.
God really made...
I don't think God is involved.
My sixth New Year's resolution, or my fifth, I don't remember which one it is now, more
threats.
Yeah.
More threats of physical violence and harm.
That's a good one.
What was that?
I'm gonna take control of my life
and I'm gonna force this app to no longer call me an aunt.
I'm gonna take control of my wife.
I'm gonna control her.
I'm so hungover I thought that Caleb
just played a sound at me,
but I just realized I had EA Origin open.
Why did you have EA Origin open?
No, it's not open, like you know,
like the little dashboard at the bottom thing?
Backpedaling.
Why would you think that I played a sound at you?
What does that even?
I thought you played a "dung-a-dung" at me.
You think that's the sound I would pick?
No, I'd pick a fart, man.
It's a comedy show.
True.
Yeah.
Obviously.
Duh!
I would pick the funny fart.
Yeah, I'm pretty excited about my keyboard.
I'm going to become a synth-pop musician.
You play us a song right now.
It's all the way in the other room.
Go get it.
You wouldn't even hear it.
Go get it and play it.
I'd have to plug it in.
It'd probably take an hour, honestly.
Really?
bad I am at plugging shit in these days.
You don't have batteries in it?
No, it's like a plug into the wall type keyboard.
I still have Christmas presents for you guys.
Oh, I have my Christmas presents for you guys too.
We should do that sometime.
Do you want me to show you yours?
No.
Right now?
No, no, no, no.
Wait, Cameron, I got...
I kinda wanna see mine.
I got Cameron something crazy.
You guys, did you get me something crazy?
I don't wanna see you on a video and not be able to reach into the screen and play with
it.
Yeah, you're right.
people yeah yeah they know us you know what they get they get a late episode
yeah where we read joke books and it's got to be one of the worst ones we've
ever done yeah this isn't the worst one we've ever done well let's make it the
worst one we've ever done all right do you guys want to silence for a little
bit yeah we still got 20 minutes to beat it let's see guys I'm gonna watch a
video together it's to read out loud what's watch a video together and not
talk no no I feel bad that the episodes late we should all right yeah all right
We're coming up on 20 at 40 minutes.
We try really hard for the next 20.
- Okay, we have like 45 seconds.
- We close it out really strong, prepare.
Okay, I'm gonna do some mental techniques right now.
- What kind of mental stuff are you gonna do?
- I'm just, I'm doing warmups.
(mimics beatboxing)
I'm a little weirdo.
I'm a little weirdo from France.
(mimicking gun noises)
- 15 second warning boys, 15 seconds 'til showtime.
- Ow, ow, that really hurts.
Ow, that one's gonna hurt me.
(mimicking gun noises)
You just hurt me.
- Okay, four, three, two, one.
All right, and go.
Happy New Year.
Happy New Year everybody. - All right, horrible start.
- No, that's a bad start.
Let's talk about cars.
Oh, let's talk about cars.
Happy New Year!
No. Wait, no. Fuck. Hold on.
What's the craziest car ever?
Mitsubishi Eclipse.
Probably a monster truck, right?
Do you guys want to see a car I got?
Can we go to a monster truck rally, man?
Oh, dude, we have to.
Are they expensive?
Yes.
My mom got me this for Christmas.
That is fucking sick dude.
Woah.
It's a Hot Wheels rat car.
Can you imagine how fast that shit would go?
It's a green rat dude.
Do you want to see?
Looks like a gator.
Yeah.
Watch this.
Woah.
That reached fucking 0-60 real fast.
Yeah that was insane.
That was pretty crazy right?
That was really cool.
Okay what are the things that we're going to buy in this new year?
Because I want some stuff.
Oh dude I will definitely be buying things.
I'm gonna buy a humidifier.
That's a baller pimp-ass joke.
I was talking last night about how I get mine stuff.
Get a lot wetter all the time.
They should have been putting humidifiers in Pimp My Ride vehicles.
That would have been good.
I'm also gonna do a lot of experiments with my humidifier where I put strange liquids
into it.
They need to bring Pimp My Ride back, honestly.
Dude, holy shit.
A pimp my ride reboot right now would be so fucking choice.
That would be tight.
That would be so good.
You know what would be cool?
Who would host it?
Yeah.
I feel like they'd probably get a new host.
It probably, I hate to say it, it probably would be Pete Davidson.
Yeah.
It would probably be Pete Davidson or McRiblet.
No it would be Machine Gun Kelly.
Oh you gotta give it to fucking Kells dude.
Killa Kells.
They would not make it a white guy.
Hey, whites can be pimps too though.
No.
Straight up.
You know who it's gonna be?
Who?
What?
Maya Angelou.
I don't think so.
Is she alive?
So you're gonna bring her back to life.
I feel like that'd be way worse than Machine Gun Kelly.
Machine Gun Kelly might be pretty decent at it.
Yeah, he could.
I think he could do it.
Maya Angelou would be terrible at it.
What are you talking about?
What would Maya Angelou put in a fucking, in a Subaru?
Maybe for once they could have a host that's a car scientist and actually knows what the
hell he's talking about when uh...
Bill Nye.
Oh my god.
That is a good, Bill Nye.
I put a magnet in your fucking car, pimp.
Pimp.
Pimp ass playalistic magnet in your damn car.
You know who'd be the best host?
Who?
Who'd get my ride?
Us three?
exhibit exhibit would be really good they should get exhibit yeah I forget
he's still alive.
Can you get off your second monitor please?
He's trying to spell exhibit.
I've seen you the entire time.
He's playing a typing game.
The whole episode.
He literally is playing fucking Mavis Beacon the whole time.
What is wrong with you bro?
Listen to that fucking giggle dude.
And then he's just like yee.
I waited 40 minutes to bring it up.
I'm sucking my job.
Are you online shopping right now?
Yes.
Are you googling?
Can you be allergic to an Austin Powers costume?
I'm looking up stuff. We were talking about buying stuff and I'm looking up stuff right
now. He's literally sitting here, he's googling on Amazon, he's searching on Amazon, "Most
expensive annoying shirt ever." So that he can buy it for himself and wear it around.
Say, "Hey look at my expensive annoying shirt." Most high-pitched instrument. Yeah. This is
why we gotta record these in person. Also because I miss you guys. I can't get COVID
this week dude. I'm sick of not hanging out with my boys. I'm locked down this week. I'm
I'm sorry. Yeah, Cam can't leave his apartment.
And I'm going with you to the crazy festival.
Yeah, so I'll gladly get COVID on the way there or the day before,
but I cannot find out that I have COVID before it's time for me to go.
Just go anyway. Who gives a shit?
I mean, I would, but I wouldn't say it on a podcast if I were going to do that.
[Laughter]
I think everybody does that right. I've thought I've had covid and traveled with it probably
six times. You can't just not travel. It's fucking expensive. I'm not just gonna not
yeah bro. I don't have my computer at my mom's house. What am I supposed to do sit there for
four days? I was so right before I yeah right before I was I was I was going home back coming
back to New York, my mom took like a rapid COVID test and I was so pissed off. It was
like if she got a positive, I had to stay at home for like another week.
Just wait till I got home.
I thought you were going to say, before I left, my mom took my computer and I was so
pissed.
That sucked when she did that too.
My mom took my computer and she typed on it.
I played so much Fortnite over the holidays. That's literally all I did at home. I stole
a table from my sibling's room. I brought it to the basement and I played Fortnite in
the basement all night every night. That's sick. Dude I just got fat at my house at my
mom's house. I ate so much bullshit. I ate so much candy while I was playing Fortnite.
Dude I was a candy animal dude. Yeah. I had a good Christmas with Joe and Alex.
Oh yeah how was your roommate Christmas? What'd you do? It was
good. It was honestly yeah I still I'm waiting because I only have $50 in my
bank account right now. You shouldn't be saying that out loud. Yeah. Yeah that's an inside thing.
Why? Why not? Because now people know that you're a target and you have 50 bucks.
That's true somebody could try and take my 50 bucks. That's an easy 50 dollars.
Oh man I hope no one takes my 50 dollars. Honestly if you ever see Patrick walking around Brooklyn
you should rob him. He'd be so easy to rob. I wouldn't be easy to rob. Are you kidding me? I
I have a skateboard with me most of the time, I would smack the shit out of somebody.
Actually, try it!
Actually, come up to me!
Come up to me and try it!
Literally, your hair would shoot out like spaghetti, like this.
Your eyes would pop out.
You'd go, "Ahh!"
All your money would fall out of your body like you were a defeated video game boss.
I would not turn into spaghetti.
And then you would get really, really small and you'd run into a mouse hole.
Not true.
Yeah.
That would not happen.
It's not true.
You'd look at these people like the guy from Warheads and you'd run away and you'd give
them all your money.
I wouldn't.
You'd be giving them, you'd run out of money and you'd keep giving them shit.
You'd give them lint out of your pockets because you were like, "Please, take everything."
I'd probably apologize to the person robbing me.
"Please, I'm so sorry I don't have even more money.
Here, take my ID.
Take my teeth.
Here you go."
"I'm so sorry.
money right now. That's one of my New Year's resolutions also is I will not get mugged
this year. I didn't last year, I want this year. I kind of want to get mugged. Really?
Yeah, because I like getting hurt and I like when bad things happen to me.
It is really nice to every once in a while a bad thing happening so you get to go "ohhh".
I think I'd probably be just as easy to rob as Patrick, but I never have cash on me.
Oh, I never have cash on me though. That's the thing.
Then you're gonna get killed.
You'll be killed.
I've always just thought a good idea is just pretend you're deaf.
Yeah.
There's, yeah, that is, that is one of the things.
What if the person robbing you is deaf though?
You gotta stand around every once in a while and just brainstorm different ideas to do if you get
mugged. Different moves, different runs, different...
I mean, not moves as in like fighting moves.
No, no, no.
Moves as in like, what do I say that's so...
like if I can I think fast enough that I can just instantly run yeah can I think
can I process the situation at enough speed and do the math of the length of
the guys looks the question is like maybe in that moment like when when moms
like lift up a car to save a baby yeah right like maybe in that moment you
discover you have a time ability yeah yeah right you pause time so cool yeah
Yeah, you pause time and you walk behind the person and then now you're mugging
them when you replay time to go again, right? Because whoever's behind the other
one, that's the mugger. Yeah. I think that's pretty, I mean, I would be counting
on that. Right? A secret, because superheroes always discover they have
powers when they're getting attacked, you know? So that's what I would probably have
that happen to me. Or when their parents are killed. So you could also maybe try and... I guess I could kill my
parents. Yeah, you could tell the mother like my parents or you could kill my parents.
Yeah. Hey, on your way home to somewhere else in New York, could you walk all the
way down to North Carolina, kill my parents and then come back? Yeah.
Hmm. So that I can have a revenge on you? I can do that for sure. I'll do that right now.
My dad would be hard to kill I think. Yeah. Yeah, I honestly think my dad has like...
I just went and killed Caleb's parents. No, my dad has no blood in his body.
body. That sounds like I did it. Maybe he's already dead if he has no blood in
his body or he's a Dracula.
My dad is some kind of undead construct. He's red. My dad is a red guy. You'll
ever meet and he has a lot of blood. Yeah, well, it's all in his skin, though
he's none in his body part. I'm really dead has blood in his skin, but no one
in his body part? My dad is literally like he looks like one of the fucking one of
those jazz raisins but red. Yeah the California raisins. Yeah he looks like
they are kind of red are you just saying your dad looks like a California raisin?
He looks honestly exactly like a California raisin. I don't know if I've ever seen a
picture of him. My dad? Yeah. I thought you're gonna say the California raisins. I
haven't seen a picture of your dad either. I haven't seen a picture of the California raisins. We
We really, we were all pretty buddy buddy with each other's moms, but our dads are-
I think you met my dad one time and you refused to remember it for some reason.
I've never met your dad.
I have never met your dad.
I don't even know what Cam's dad looks like.
Your dad met a fucking, like a different bald guy in Boston.
That's- there's millions of us.
No, you definitely, you definitely met my dad and you erased it from your memory because
you didn't want to be experienced for some reason.
Well you guys know my mom and dad.
You guys have hung out with my mom and dad.
I know your mom biblically. I'm going to shut off my camera. Please do. You're wearing a
black bandana. I wish you would. Hey, we didn't shut off the camera. When with me and your
mom. Oh! He filmed it! Oh my fucking god! And then it went to theaters and it made it
oh my yeah and then it went to theaters and it made 10 million dollars oh my god
he did a one of those event things they do in theaters what is that called you
know I'm talking about yeah it was a fan you like it screening like one night
only and in three night owners over America and it would open at your mom
Fathom Events Presents. One night only. I just did a curse on you. January. Did you see that?
It literally made a hundred million dollars in the first night. It made more than Avatar.
Yeah. I just put a curse on you. You didn't even see it Cameron. I put a curse on you.
It was in 4D because she was there doing the same thing to everyone in the audience.
It's not true. It's all true man. I'm looking it up right now. It's not true.
And then they made a dark ride out of it at Universal.
My mom bought you guys beer koozies for Christmas and you guys pay her back by saying this crap
about her.
I didn't know that!
Yes you did!
I showed them to you last episode and you guys say all this crap about my mom.
I had barbecue brain last episode.
It's not crap, it's sweet.
It's not nice what we say.
It's not nice what you say.
I'm calling your mom a beautiful young woman.
She likes it.
saying no you're saying that you put things in her who's saying that I put
thing in her that's what you said I didn't say anything about putting things
in her yes you did I thought it I didn't say it I considered it I'm sick and I
did it in 2022 anytime you guys say something about my mom you guys have to
give me a dollar worth it.
Yeah, he's giving me she's giving me way more than that.
I'm still way up on this deal, bro.
Oh, yeah, 2022 even more gambling way way more.
Oh, yeah.
I want to say I won $30 on a scratch ticket for on for Christmas
scratch.
that's not a good omen. It's funny that you and me are the two that like gambling a lot
and both of us have dads that give us Christmas scratchers and have since we were kids. Like
I've done that since I was like five years old. Yeah, that's a Christmas tradition. Dude,
it's a classic Christmas tradition. It's the best. What's the most you've ever won? The
$30 I think. I feel like somebody won like a hundred bucks one time but it wasn't me.
I did. Do you have that fucked up rule where it's like anything over a hundred everyone
splits it? No, we never, I feel like if that did happen. The thing is also is like for most
of my life, it's like my parents just counted on like us kids being too ADHD to remember
that we won on scratch tickets so they could just take them. Yeah, I think that's why my
dad has that rule. Yeah. Because he's basically just getting us to open his scratchers for
Yeah, yeah, it's an excuse to buy them. Yeah, it's great though. Yeah, but now now my now all the kids
My family are 18. Everyone could cast their own parents. It's nothing. They don't get anything. We're high a depression
Good. I parents can get fucked. That's right. Mm-hmm
You want to learn about winnings on a scratcher when and I bought an external hard drive with it in in the eighth grade
That's not where you're supposed to it's basically a coupon for more scratchers. Yeah
You're wrong. You ever grown your money exponentially
Dude, I just remembered I won I won I won like 20 bucks on a scratcher at the beginning of 2021 - oh
God, it's and that and this was that was a great year. So this is gonna be an even better one
That was yeah, I got our real job gave us one gave us a scratcher when we moved in
And honestly yet
Hmm, how much did you win on it? We only won like two dollars on that one
But I had already won like 20 bucks on another one. Whoa, I think I I think I'm gonna plan on finding buried treasure
Yeah, that's a good risk. That's a really really. That's a really good one. I had a metal detector as a kid
I could go look at my dad's attic to see if we could find it. We could go to Topsail Beach in North Carolina
That's where Blackbeard's treasure is buried. Whoa, really? Yeah, it's like it's like 30 minutes away from Wilmington. Damn. Yeah, it's pretty fucking cool, man
That's crazy just pull out the pull out the dude if we find blackbeard's treasure just be sitting in some retirees garage
Mm-hmm. Just like no, you don't understand. It's it's beeping right where you're
Where your plumbing system is? I think that this is blackbeard's treasure my eighth ninth
I can't remember. Okay, my my ninth resolution
For 2022. Yeah
double my IQ
10th resolution, double it over again.
Damn.
Whoa.
Yeah.
Okay.
You'll be sitting pretty.
At a cool 80.
Come on.
You're smarter than that.
You have more than 20 IQ points.
My 20's pretty good.
The average is zero, you know.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh, I believe it.
Yeah, I believe it these days.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
people walking around nowadays with 16, 64 gigabyte iPhones. It's like, yeah, it's more
like your 64 IQ.
IQ.
That's right. We used to, we want to have our IQ and now everybody wants to have this
Shanghai flu.
Whoa.
Definitely.
What does that mean?
I don't know. Oh, by the way, my grandparents who you met, they are loading up on ivermectin
because of my whole family getting COVID.
Nice.
They are pounding it right now.
Damn.
They are just beasting on packages of ivermectin right now at the crib.
That sucks.
Nah dude, it's cool.
It's sick, bro.
Doesn't it kill you?
No, it kills worms.
No, it kills COVID-19.
Nah.
Yeah, dude, it kills it in one shot.
One shot, one kill.
Really?
Yeah, instantly.
I think I might try it out then.
They offered to give us some.
I was like really have come. Yeah, I should have just taken it dude. I know it's no way
you don't know I'm talking to Patrick. It'd be really funny the next few months Patrick
gets covered like every two weeks.
Yeah, Patrick says the worst year ever.
He's like, I must have the antibodies by now. Yeah, it's immediately gets it again. Just
constantly getting COVID. Yeah, that would be pretty. That's not an impossibility. Yeah,
I think there's going to be, I think we're going to move to the new strain every two weeks.
That's my 11th resolution is I'm going to make that happen for you.
You're going to inject me with COVID.
Oh, okay.
No.
12th resolution, profit even harder off COVID-19.
We need to make a lot of money off this disease.
You know what we got to do?
What?
Get into the, well, I think it's pretty late in the game now, but we start making masks.
Oh, yeah.
That's a really good idea.
What should we make?
We could come up with like funny-ass masks too with like jokes and shit.
It says the mask says "I have COVID."
Yeah, that'd be a mask with a smiley face.
Oh, what about a mask that is my teeth like this?
What about a mask that says...
That's a bit egotistical, don't you think, Patrick?
Yeah, like why are you always trying to make it about you?
Well, we could have your teeth too.
What about...
I don't want my teeth. My teeth are shitty. I don't want them on a fucking mask.
What about a meme on the mask?
Oh my god, no wait.
So it's the Grateful Dead logo, but it says, it says, "I am one grateful dad."
Do you think that would do numbers?
Yeah.
What about like this?
What about a mask that says ADHD in the AC/DC font?
That's, that could be good.
That's good.
What about a mask and it has like a mouth like on it, but the mouth is like beatboxing,
it has like beatboxing sound effects written around it?
Oh my god, wait, a mask that has a microphone in it for when you want to beatbox.
Yo!
Just a mask that has a microphone in general and you can amplify your voice whenever you
want.
Yeah.
You have a little remote control in your pocket and you can put effects, it has an effects
pedal.
Or like, like tooth tunes, it just, like, let's simplify it.
It just plays one kiss song, like a 30 second snippet, every time you open your mouth.
Oh, I had that one.
I had that tooth tunes.
Yeah.
Rock and roll all night.
What about like a thong mask?
Where it's just like a thin strip over your mouth and you see everything else.
Yeah, nothing to be desired.
Nothing left to the imagination.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
That'd be good if you had a mouth that looked like an ass cracker or a vagina.
Yeah, so Pat, that'd be really good.
Yeah, that'd be perfect for you.
Ass mouth.
What?
I don't have an ass mouth.
Let me see your mouth.
Looks like my ass.
big and yellow yeah yeah true little little teeth oh what if I get like
veneers you should get veneers oh yeah once we get our money up this year we're
all the whole squad's getting but I'm getting I'm getting I'm doing one of
those things where you can get like a like custom vampire fangs sculpted but
like yeah I'm thanks for every tooth like not just the two vampire fang like
uh-huh I'm gluing on on Dracula fangs on every every last tooth in my also I'm
I'm gonna go topless.
- Yep.
- You're gonna go topless this year?
- I'm gonna go topless in public.
- Yeah, also I'm gonna get that snake tongue thing
where they give you a forked tongue.
- Yeah, they cut your tongue.
- I'm getting like 20 forks in it.
- Oh, that's-- - I'm just gonna be like,
I'm gonna have like so many forks.
- That'd be sick, dude.
You'd look like a fucking sea urchin.
- Yep.
- Also, I'm getting my eyeball pierced.
- That's sick.
- I'm gonna get my entire body pierced with a sword.
- Damn. - Yeah.
- That's a good one.
That's a good move.
you have like a sword through you all the time,
somebody can pick you up.
- I'm getting a diamond stud pacemaker.
- That's a good idea.
- I'm just getting a pacemaker put in.
I think maybe get all the things out of the way.
I'll get a hip replacement.
- I'm more interested in a preemptive.
- Gonna get it all out of the way early.
A hip replacement now, a pacemaker.
- I'm gonna get a middle plate in my head.
You're talking about a pacemaker,
I'm more interested in a paper maker.
that's somebody doing yes, sir,
all to my hands. Yep, you go to the hospital and they're like, sir, he's too
broke. We need to put a paper maker into him. Yeah, yeah, and it's just grills.
All right, happy birthday,
bye.