come back and make a mess
and we see a black
so we just heard take a ride with me early that i hop was i hop
those three years ago i just have i think i just have been i think i cup
i_h_o_u_p_
would i hate all your p
you ate all his people yeah what
he he said i a_t_o_p_
That's pretty good. I'm going to read that one.
Yeah.
IHOP.
That's actually a really good one.
So good, dude.
That's going to get people really good.
You say, "Hey, spell IHOP." People would be like, "Oh, okay, he's making a joke about."
Okay, IHOP.
Yeah, you ate my pee?
Oh, you ate my pee?
IHOP.
Nah.
Yeah, I'm going to do it again.
You better not. You drink it.
Did you come up with that?
Yeah.
That's genius, dude.
That was really good.
That's like next level.
IHOP, B.
many way i a jokey p
yeah i don't know if you need to do it but i have a job you'd be it was really
good to be a good
uh... yeah they have a great span of your interest for
praying that had bridge pancakes for visit and young grinch
mother bring your grinch materials i was a british have been as the greater
halloween
you were not the great you are not a great and you are many people but you
were not the correct
yeah well that was the fucking we went to a bar that had really dim lights and
because I was in the green face paint just looked like I was in black face
yeah it was bad yeah I took a picture - yeah of you dressed as black Santa yeah
dude it just looked like I was black Santa it was so bad is really bad yeah
and I was the only one there dressed up - which but also Grinch is a good caught
like Trudeau should have tried to pass it off as Grinch. Yeah, when he's in that big
turban. Yeah, they're like, "Sir, the Grinch is green." He's like, "Well, I read the book.
I didn't see the movie. I don't know what I..." I'm not supposed to know that. "In my head, he was
black." He was pitch black. "In my head, he was a black man with a turban who stole things."
I just dressed up as somebody who I thought hates Christmas. Yeah, yeah, you did.
it's um speaking of holidays it's did to do all it is to do all which I think is
it is a Hindu holiday that means that you can you don't have to move your car
you can just park for free in New York that's the holiday today yeah I think
it's maybe my favorite holiday in the world because of that yeah it's been
actually not have to pay for parking I didn't have to I didn't have to pay Wow
thank you do all the graduations thank you do all the festival of sunrise I
I don't know what it's called. Why'd you guys both phone me?
We both got a text from Jubio at the same time. I guess you didn't.
I did but I have some fucking, I have some manners.
I wanted to see if it was something important. It was important for the business.
It was not important. You got a text from some Mexican guy you know.
I didn't know. It could have been my mom saying that she's dead.
She wouldn't send you that text message. It could be a dead woman's switch.
day could be that too
i need to see who's texting me i'm not gonna open it but i need to see what it
is so you guys have a dead man's switch
was that maybe
when you die something funny what's a good what's a good dead man's switch
what would be a good one uh... like uh... i need an idea for one for no
right now on the issue in in p and all and throw up
what like you all of your fluids at leave your body does not get a good man
says that it had been switches that's a good what happens when you die and it's
That's a dead man switch.
You have to set it up though.
Yeah.
A good one of that is if it like mailed a box of all your pee and poop and vomit to someone
when you die.
That's funny.
That's what a dead man switch is.
What about like the end of Breaking Bad just like wherever your car is parked a machine
gun just pops out of it and starts shooting.
That was so stupid.
It's cool dude.
I'm sorry.
That was like on the tier of the science rock exploding.
I was I was I was cool but I was like I was like come the fuck on like seriously
what and the guy was standing right in front of it when it opens - that's his
fault that's too much it was sick dude it would have been ass oh wait is that
Walter White does I forget how that ends yeah you explain it Walter I'm not
without giving spoilers Walter White a machine gun comes out of the trunk of
his car yeah and then without getting exposed he died it's inspector gadget
it yeah it's literally they stole it from inspector gadget super cool wait but
does it does he die before that or he does I think it does 50 or 60 times I
think it does 50 or 60 years before that yeah yeah he died so the beginning of
the show starts with him dying yeah it starts well it starts with a sperm and
an egg that combine and then die yeah and then the rest is kind of like a
fever dream exploration of what could have happened yeah the rest is basically
like the live-action Mario Brothers movie mm-hmm yeah where they're just
Right.
They go into the sewers, they see the Goombas that look like lizards.
Yeah.
What was that shit about?
What the hell was that?
Why weren't the Goombas-
You remember the little Bob-
Little Bob-omb that he has?
Yeah.
That thing was cute.
Pretty cool.
Yeah.
It was like a little-
That's what Walter White should have thrown on the ground,
instead of that fucking stupid rock.
Yeah, that little Bob-omb.
A little bomb, dude.
Mm-hmm.
Little black bomb.
Yeah.
And the guy's like, "Hey, what's that? A random black ball?"
With a string coming out of it?
out of it? It's not a normal black ball. It's a science bomb. It's actually a bomb.
Yeah. And if you jump on it once, it flashes red. What does he say when he throws it?
What's that, a tiny bowling ball? He says, "Hasta la vista." Is that actually what he
says? No, I think he says... He says, "Praise science." Oh, fuck. No, he doesn't. I don't
remember, but I don't know if he says anything. Does he say something? I think he's not about
what's he says he says eat rock bitch that'd be sick eat my dust to go eat my
chemicals to go he says he says to go he's a speed racer yeah to go eat this
yeah he says yeah he says well my nemesis and he throws it down how did you know I
hate explosions doesn't he walk out of it Scott free - yeah Scott free I mean
scratch-free scratch-free Scott free Scott free makes more sense than scratch
got free would mean that is I mean he's not like like the cops aren't there yeah
it's just like but who does walk out of it Scott free though yeah he does but why
does not why is it called Scott he has a scratch Scott free till is backwards so I
I got to spell it backwards?
- Yeah, spell it Scott, free backwards.
- E-E-R-F--
- Oh my God, he said it.
- T-O-C-S.
- You know what you just said?
- What?
- You said free of--
- I said, I said--
- You said Earftox.
- Earftox?
- Yeah.
- I said Earftox? Damn.
- Earftox money don't.
- True.
- Yes sir.
- Yeah.
- You guys have any big Duali plans?
- I think I'm gonna kill myself.
Yeah, I think I might kill myself too.
I think I was thinking...
You see, I said you guys should park a car somewhere.
Yeah, if I had a car I would definitely do that.
It's thrilling.
This is one of the best car holidays.
Does it work if I maybe just put a bag down somewhere and that could be like a car?
Probably, yeah.
We could make a car on the airport.
I guess normally I wouldn't have to pay a parking meter to put a bag down.
I do think like if you put a rock, like a big rock in a parking space, are they going
to try to tick it?
As long as, if you'd pay the meter it's fine.
It's quite fun, right?
Yeah.
like that rock. Oh yeah, well yeah, what are you going to do? Yeah, it's not it's
there's no license plate on it. Yeah, they try to you can't prove that's my
rock. Yeah, I don't have registration. Exactly yeah, we're going to send the
bill you asshole. Oh yeah, oh just because I'm just because I carried it
here on a on a forklift and put it down means it's my rock. Yeah, sure yeah
great. I love you to see you try to find my address tied to that yeah, big
rock house right behind you yeah
completely made out of rock. There's a there's like a huge like like like
like fucking like rut in the ground where you dress the rock from your
garage like all the way down this clear path. Yeah, I love to yeah. I'd love to
see you find out where I live. I would hate to be a slug. Yeah, you couldn't
get away with anything to know and you don't imagine cheating on your wife as a
one need a french fry exactly, but but you also you can't like like you can't
lie to anybody about where you've been, you know?
You don't even get a cool shell.
Yeah, exactly. You don't have a protective bulletproof shell.
Dude, I wish I had a shell. I wish I had a pouch. I was thinking about that the other day.
You have a pocket.
Yeah, but like...
You have a lot of pockets.
I do. I'm wearing cargo pants right now.
But, like, a pouch in my stomach.
Yeah, but why? You'd have to reach inside your clothes to take anything out of it in public.
Yeah, I feel like that...
It would look like you're jacking off.
No, it would be in my stomach.
Well, you'd put your hand in like this, and then you'd be going like this.
I wouldn't be going like that.
You would.
You'd be rooting around inside it.
I could put a baby bird in there.
You want to put a baby inside you?
I want to put a baby bird in my pouch.
Why?
It would suffocate.
And then I'd pull my shirt up and let the bird fly out in McDonald's.
I think the Diwali spirit has gotten into you.
Yeah.
Well, I don't know what Diwali is about.
I don't either.
I think it's basically Christmas, based on the time of year that it is right now.
I think it's I think there's a tree there's presently in there could be a
menorah I don't know
energy but what is with your neighborhood in expired energy drinks
to all Polish people bro oh yeah yeah
well this right random numbers for the experience yeah I don't know what is it
day one two three because this Red Bull can has like some promo thing
ok level up your game yeah but what can you halo to redbull.com slash solo
- I missed.
(laughing)
- Yeah, unlike--
- Oh, this isn't expired.
- Yeah, I don't know why I assumed it was.
- I thought it was 'cause your Red Bull cans
usually have the bowl in the tab.
- Why are you so afraid of expired?
- 'Cause I drank an expired can at your house once.
- It's not gonna do anything different,
like worse to you than a normal energy drink would do.
- You're already getting fucking hammered.
- You're already drinking like evil chemicals.
- Your central nervous system is so fucked up
for everything you drink.
- Yeah, but that's why I don't get sick.
I have so many preservatives.
- That's not true.
definitely get sick you're just sick all the time you constantly you walk around
you go like this you do that that's because I smoke you're a yacker he
almost did it again yeah no I you ever get like you get like a shit ton of phlegm
yeah yeah when I'm sick yeah when I'm congested and sick oh so maybe maybe
you're right yeah you sick motherfucker you know you
You know what I didn't take today?
What?
My...
A nap.
You're cranky.
I did not take a nap.
He is cranky.
I'm not cranky today.
You're cranky.
Did you hear how he just reacted to that?
I didn't take my ginseng today.
I'm not cranky today!
That's what he did.
I didn't take my ginseng today for the first time in a while.
And he is cranky because of it.
He's very cranky.
And my balls, I went to go pee, my balls are hidden in my body.
Not in my sack.
That's a problem I've only heard of you having.
Yeah, that's like a you thing.
Yeah.
Dude, I feel like it's like a superpower.
No, my...
- My, no, that's a-- - Your balls have never retreated.
- That's a sub power.
- My nuts hang lower than my penis.
- When it's cold, my nuts will like to,
they like to touch my, they like to hide in my butt cheeks.
- When it's cold, that's a different story.
- You never have had your nuts go up into your stomach.
- No, they don't go up into my body.
- My nuts hang-- - Something's wrong
with you freaks.
- My nuts hang a foot below my penis.
- A foot?
- Yes. - Yeah.
- So they hang nine inches down?
Come on.
- Oh my God. - This guy's got
a reverse penis.
- Yeah, I do.
- It's three inches reverse.
three inches reverse and
my butt
and it's in his ass too. It comes out of his butt and it goes back into his butt.
It's like a little, you can hook your finger into it and swing him around.
It's weird.
It's weird but fun. It's weird but that's me. Which is actually the name of my new
variety show. You guys should check it out. I have to take my ginseng right now.
You guys keep talking.
Yeah, I got a hemorrhoid right now. I don't know.
is nasty yeah i know how you are you you're looking at your phone too long on
the toilet
i think so yeah
i think that might be a or maybe just like that is i feel i was going on that
is one of the makes me feel like a
like in uber meant so i can i be like superior like mentally superior to other
people's that have never like sat on the toilet with my phone long enough to like
then i got a little bit health problem and i got a like
sink while moments will it
i look at my phone but i don't i don't sit there for an hour like i just people
people talk about that all the time and it's like oh, I think I'm just like
mentally superior that I don't it doesn't happen. I fall asleep on the
toilet in the morning. So that's what I'm talking about. I literally feel
like you're like cattle. I'll wake up. I'll wake up at five. I wake up at
five in the morning almost every single day to take a shit or a pee. Yeah, and
I sit down on the toilet and then I will just fall asleep and I'll wake up
twenty minutes later and my head is on the dude falling asleep falling asleep
early in the morning. I used to do that. I used to like whenever I would wake
wake up like and not like have an alarm. I would like wake up really early and I
would like I would try to get out of bed, but I'd be too tired and I'd have no
energy and I would just like pick up my phone like to like you know like lie in
my in bed and like look at my phone, but I'd be like completely asleep and I
would just like every morning. I would just like message a different person a
bunch of random letters and then fall back asleep like I just wake up and I'd
like sent my friend is like give a little bit of a little do okay. So you
know I told you guys the other day. I don't think I said on the podcast. I had
dream that I was at the most beautiful candy factory of all time and I I don't
remember now I so I always fall asleep with headphones in yeah and I had a
dream that I was at like the best candy factory in the world I was sampling all
these beautiful caramels and then I woke up and I just put my headphone in my
mouth and I was like sucking on it I was like well that's fucking weird and then
last night I had a dream that I was drinking something and I woke up and I
I put my phone charger in my mouth
my mouth
my dream and then I wake up. We're going to where you're going to die from that.
I know
thank God, I don't sleep with a spike in my yeah yeah, that'd be bad. I'd
probably have a dream that I was eating. It used to be a
your pet poison dart frog yeah, yeah, put him in my mouth and be bad dude and a
I was eating a poison dart frog and then I woke up and I put I put Lenny in my mouth. Yeah, yeah
But I I gotta stop doing that that is dangerous. Yeah. Yeah takes me so long to get up in the morning now
Yeah this morning. I woke up and I was like you
You you came over my we recorded a video that might be out
with home planet
Wow
But you came over and I was just getting out of bed
head yeah and you were naked yeah don't tell him I said this, but he was naked
when I saw you see his nuts and I saw his eyes. He has this weird like black cloth
on his body around his wiener and butt region that was confusing me yeah and
it's like a band a waistband type like yeah protrusion out of his body.
Who is weird and then he and then he went into you went into the bathroom and
I could hear all this like noises and they came out and he had his whole body
this like cloth hanging off of it is like it like he grew some kind of like cocoon
really yeah he was completely completely naked when I said to deal with that
every day tell me you're from New York without really tell me you're from New
York walk out in a cocoon that was the funniest fucking shit like like oh yo yo
tell me you from tell me you're from Staten Island without telling me you're
from Staten Island.
(imitating gun noises)
- What the fuck is you talking about?
Tell me you're from Canarsie
without telling me you're from Canarsie.
- My wife.
(laughing)
- That's what's up.
- Oh man, we should make that video.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Let's start filming, bitch.
- Okay, I'm gonna record you and then you go.
- Oh, I'm nervous.
- Oh, okay, then if you're nervous, we don't have to do it.
- Thanks.
- Okay.
- I love being nervous.
Yesterday I watched Transformers The Last Knight, the fifth Transformers movie, the last
Michael Bay Transformers movie.
And you know how in every Transformers movie they kind of like retcon some of human history
to be like about Transformers.
Like in Revenge of the Fallen they have like, oh one of the pharaohs was a Transformer.
And like the third one, they're like, oh the reason we went to the moon was to like find
a Transformers ship.
the fourth one they're like dinosaurs were transformers. Actually the fifth
one, the premise of it originally is that like oh like King Arthur and
Merlin were real and they had a dragon that was a transformer, which that's
already pretty cool, but then they have this whole sequence where they're in
like this guy like this guy's mansion, who's like part of like the Knights
Templar, but like for transformers like a secret society about transformers,
okay, it's gone on for ages and they're
they're listing like people who are like parts of the Knights of the what is the
the Knights of the Wit Wiccan and like like Sam, with Wiki Shia LaBoeuf and
listing them and they're like they're like like JFK, Harriet Tubman,
Benjamin Franklin, but Harry is so they like show a picture of like
Transformers and like the Civil War and then they go they're like looking at
this like this like like case where they have like an evil like watch
transformer trapped in it and it's Sir Anthony Hopkins is like the is the
the transformer guy and he like he's showing them he's like and they're like
trying to touch he's like don't touch that that's very dangerous that's the
watch that killed Hitler. It cuts to Bumblebee like killing a bunch of Nazis.
It's so crazy dude. It's so sick. But yeah, so a transformer killed Hitler.
Okay, so a transformer killed Hitler.
But it was a bad guy transformer that killed Hitler. It was an evil watch.
It was a Decepticon?
It was a Decepticon killed Hitler.
So they're setting it up, it's Minion style. Even the Decepticons didn't like
Hitler.
Yeah.
Wow.
That's so funny.
That's crazy cool.
The Decepticons and the Autobots had to get together to kill Hitler.
Yeah.
But yeah, such a good reveal.
That's a crazy...
I would rather watch that movie.
Yeah, that's...
Dude, oh my god, Valkyrie but with the Transformers?
Because there could just be a Transformer named Valkyrie and he's a desk.
Yeah.
Dude, they have a...
That's what that movie's about, right?
The desk bomb?
Frederick Douglass was also part of the Order of the Witwickens.
Also they would have to bumblebee since he doesn't have a voice. He would have to
talk with like nineteen fucking forties. Yeah, like that is so funny that they
reckon it to be like like in the original one. There's like oh they
landed here in like two thousand and eight, but then every time they're
recon it to be like earlier and it's like oh they actually were here
millions of years ago, but they still like look like like samurai and there's
one who looks like a like a just a British general and stuff and it's like
a mad. Yeah, yeah, very funny. They should make a transformer that turns
into a phone. They did in the first one. And I should get to use the phone. No, for
free. And I get to play a game on the phone. What game would you play? Angry
Birds. I don't think the Transformers would take too kindly to that. I would
play Bit Life with them. They would not like Bit Life. They would love Bit Life.
Are you kidding me? No, they would love Bit Life. Their entire life is a Bit Life. They don't care for
puny, the lives of puny humans. That's right. Oh, also, sorry to just talk about
Transformers. I would love to. Barricade, the Decepticon who turns into a
a police car yeah, so i'm sure you've seen when he is for the police car that he
transforms into you know on the side of police car just says to protect and
serve his on his car. It says to punish an enslave that is and then when he
turns into a robot, he has brass knuckles to say punish and enslave.
Well, so sick do so cool that's who I want to be when I grow up.
I mean those movies are objectively so they're awesome. Yeah, they're like so
last one like that one's the best like that should be a Walberg one yeah I
have it on I have a blue ray we should watch is that it's a second Walberg one
or the yeah the second Walberg one is TJ in it no post TJ I've talked about it
numerous times but that scene where he finds the transformer he's like I think
we just found a transformer transformers and we found a transformer I think we
just found a transformer we just found a transformer yeah and this one it's like
like it's like they're like like they're like it's like an like a an
anti like like ice and like DHS theme to it because it's like the
transformers are like illegal aliens. So like but then like like
mark wallberg yeah well yeah exact mark wallberg is like it's like
years after the like the first wallberg one or whatever. So he
like rides around and like a leather jacket and is like the guy
who's like protecting like the the illegal alien transformers like
smuggling them around it's so sick pretty hard pretty easy to smuggle a
transformer I would say yeah yeah turn into a book some of them can't transfer
the dinosaur ones are just dinosaurs they brought back the dinosaur one
yeah the dino bots are in the fourth one and then they're also in the fifth one
so according to the transformers lore is every dinosaur fucking just I don't know
bots I don't know okay unless all of them I don't think so okay I just yeah
- That was fucked up learning that those motherfuckers
had feathers.
- But then they went back on it.
- They went back on it?
- Yeah.
- Not all of them, some of them have feathers.
- They said that there was not,
it's not nearly as many feathers as they originally thought.
- Yeah, but--
- A couple feathers every once in a while.
- What, which animal--
- They might have like a plume.
- Is it velociraptors?
No, it's not velociraptors.
- Yeah, velociraptors were probably feathered.
- Well, no, no, I know, but which one did the ostrich
like originate as?
I think someone was telling me this the other day,
that like an ostrich used to,
like it's like, I don't know what the fucking word is,
but I think it's velociraptors.
- Speaking of dinosaurs, I've had a new gator obsession.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- There's a, I have to show you this guy.
His name is Wally.
He's a registered emotional support animal
in Pennsylvania, I think.
- I thought you were gonna say Pensacola.
- No, in Pennsylvania.
Oh, is this who you're talking about?
No.
Wally Gator.
Not Wally Gator from Hanna-Barbera.
Caleb watched a Hanna-Barbera cartoon.
This is the coolest alligator I've ever seen.
He's way kinder than most gators.
He wears a collar.
He has a hat.
He's very funny.
I see him here.
No, he has this old guy who basically said,
I was going to kill myself until--
Yeah.
He's like, I was going to kill myself until I picked up Wally.
And apparently he just like walks around and puts this fucking alligator on like women in the grocery store.
It says he loves attention.
Yeah and he uh...
Oh look at him.
Dude it's the best. I want an alligator so badly dude.
21 year old pet alligator named Wally dies after getting hit by a car near Lansing.
What? That can't be true.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Dude he's dead.
Are you fucking kidding me? I watched a video about him that came out like a year ago.
I think this might be just a different animal.
Where did it come out?
This is in 2019.
All right, we're good.
Okay.
I think.
Yeah.
Where was?
In Lansing.
Oh.
It's in Pennsylvania.
No, it's in Michigan.
Oh, damn.
It's in Pennsylvania.
There is a Lansing, Pennsylvania, I'm guessing.
Oh, it is a family.
Okay, see this guy's just a single dude.
Yeah, okay, Wally's fine.
Wally's fine.
But yeah, I feel like a pet alligator might be a good late life move.
Yeah, I think so.
I think so.
life move for me. Yeah. Janet dies, you know, just pick up a gator. Yeah, it
could be nice. There's no there's no Lansing, Pennsylvania. I was thinking of
Lancaster.
You're so dumb. I'm also I just don't want to die. I just did opening that
like news article reminded me that when I was I said this is another
Transformers thing. I found I found a news article when I was looking at
barricade the one who the to punish an enslave yeah some guy in
Massachusetts like bought a car and like made it look exactly like the
Decepticon cop car and a bunch of police tried to arrest him for it and
then he like they took him to court and they they ruled he was like
innocent. They're like it's fine. Of course, it's so sick to do
this fucking so in slave on his car mission in slave. Yeah, so awesome
that's anyway. We could keep talking about wall. I just remembered that
- No, I just don't, I'd like to get some more info
if anyone has it on what the cost is,
how free, probably, how much. - I don't know if you could
have an alligator in New York.
- I'll fucking, dude, I'm looking every day
for a reason to move.
- Yeah. - That might be the reason.
- Yeah. - That finally
pulls me. - You don't wanna stay here
and hang out with me?
- I think I'll probably live here for a couple more years.
- Yeah? - Yeah.
- But I just-- - You don't wanna hang out
with me? - I like being here.
- Yeah, what about me? - I like being out.
- You don't wanna hang out with me or Cameron?
- Yeah, I'll stay here then.
- Okay, cool. - Yeah.
- Yeah.
- This sucks.
- I think I might move, actually.
- So I've been thinking of moving, actually.
- Yeah.
- No, I just--
- Have you actually moved to New Hampshire?
- I would love to move to New, yeah, sure, let's do it.
- Yeah, let's move to New Hampshire.
- Get an alligator?
- Yeah.
- You could totally get an alligator in New Hampshire.
- Yeah, absolutely.
- Yeah, definitely.
- Yeah, it might get too cold for them, though, actually.
- Yeah.
I'd just keep it in my--
- Well, you don't think of Pennsylvania.
- It's not gonna leave its slave quarters.
- What?
- It gets cold as shit in Pennsylvania, too.
- I guess.
bath that he keeps it in. Okay that makes sense. Wally. He has multiple gators but
Wally's the sweetest and kindest of the three. Oh okay what are the other one's
names? One is named Carl. Okay. And I don't remember the other's name because I
didn't focus on him because it seems like he's a bit of a problem gator. He
might be a little snappy. Uh-oh. Yeah but Carl and Wally would be a good name for him.
Snappy yeah you might you might be right. Slappy? No. That's a clown's name. That could be good to have three alligators
seem like snappy slappy and crappy or like.
- Crappy's got the bad into that stick.
- Yeah.
- He pulled the short straw.
- Okay, flappy.
- There you go, that's fine.
- Flappy bird.
- Dude, when we went to the, what was it,
Alligator Adventure?
- Alligator Adventure, Myrtle Beach, South Carolina.
- When we went there, like finding out that like alligators.
- That's never heard a siren before.
- That's barricaded.
When we found out that,
they don't want me to say this.
they don't want to talk about the salamanders not uh...
uh...
trying at the lake alligators mouths aren't like
like my mouth
you know it's like
like it out there now doesn't have a hole in it is just like a really i don't
see them just sit there with their like
mouths open but i think there's nothing that looks so freaky dudes hot out the
cool off by because the other close their throat
yet to do that
i wish i could close my throat
like that and what
yeah
you literally can't look
not that it looks different
that was my tongues and i can't
making it
it might be a great while
are all if a gator could talk that's probably how he fought a nice i don't
get
yes he ever has a gator and i actually a little bit of a gator was talking
price on this
Apparently they do, they purr and growl. They hiss. They also purr and growl. They like
to hiss. They were hissing a bunch when we were there. Yeah. Dude that one bucked at
me remember? The crocodile though. It's a crocodile that bucked at me. Crocs are pretty
fucked up except American crocodile is closer to the alligator as far as like how tame it
is. Like it's much more chill. Like you can have a pet American croc. They get too big.
Crocs?
Yeah, American croc.
I thought crocs are way less chill than alligators.
Yeah, they are, but the American croc is more chill than like a Nile crocodile or like a
wild crocodile.
A wily croc, or there's one called the evil crocodile that is actually surprisingly mean.
Really unchill.
Yeah.
Where do you guys land on, what pets, what animals are okay and not okay to have as pets?
Everything.
Ball python.
I think, I'm closer to everything is okay.
I think that you could have, like I could...
I mean we kind of, we kind of just already like...
We're getting there.
We kind of, we kind of just like, humans as a race kind of already just like jumped the
shark on like enslaving nature enough that I don't think there's any animal you could
make a pet that wouldn't be like, like wouldn't, there's probably someone has done worse already
like you know what I mean?
Yeah.
Like I think we've, I think we've subjugated the earth enough.
Giraffe.
But they make all these fucking documentaries and shit about oh we put orcas in, in the
most beautiful place of all time fucking SeaWorld who doesn't want to spend time
in SeaWorld first of all right what are these orcas hate fun yeah unlimited food
they get to swim around they get to fucking kill one person every five years
that's like an ideal like what it doesn't need to be out in the wild dude
I think you just pool I think you literally just can't be the first person
to ever have an animal as a pet right because that's yours might be you got to
have like some there's has to be precedent yeah can't be Mike Tyson Mike
Tyson you got a point at somebody and be like damn well that guy has one I can
have one too yeah yeah yeah first Tiger guys the first Tiger guy he wasn't
they were Tigers they had Tigers back at they like have you ever seen Aladdin no
he was the first Tiger guy no Mike Tyson Aladdin happened way before Mike Tyson
was who don't think so do you think was the first person to have like a like a
gator probably mr. gator the gator scientist yeah yeah he actually
like develop them in his lab and then crazy how crazy you think that person
was being like I'm gonna pick up this big dinosaur keep it in my backyard the
first person who picked up a gator must have been crazy mm-hmm true yeah yeah
what's the first guy you like yeah he looked at like he's like see this gross
swamp I'm gonna have a pet of the first thing that's in here and then I'm gonna
do I'm gonna swim in this swamp and whatever tries to eat me will be my pet
he's probably probably like he probably was pretty crazy I'd like to think he
as a prospector.
- He might have been digging under the ground.
- He was a pioneer for sure.
- 'Cause you know that for a while,
they didn't know that gold was in the arid desert.
So they were just checking everywhere for gold.
They were digging through snow.
They would suck all the water out of a pond
with big straws to try to find
if there was gold underneath there.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- We should start prospecting.
- I would love to.
- Would that be, we should go panning for gold dude.
I've been panning for gold before.
Really?
Yeah.
Did you find any?
I don't think so.
You panned for dirt, my friend.
Pretty much.
Yeah, you can go to like...
Yeah, there's some in the mountains of North Carolina.
There's also like in Montana, you can go to like, quote unquote, like ghost towns that
have been like touristified.
And you can like go there, they'll have like a candy shop in like an old saloon.
Yeah.
And then you can like go and like pan for gold there, but it's like not like real panning
for gold.
- They might like, they'll like, yeah, they'll like,
you can, yeah, exactly.
And they'll like put stuff into it sometimes, yeah.
That's like, I don't know, that's fun.
- I'd rather just get the candy.
- I love any--
- The candy was good.
- Any like lollipops. - Old West.
- Oh!
- Oh, did you ever get that?
- Montana lollipops, dude.
- They make 'em different there.
- They're famous for a reason.
- Rock candy.
- Do you ever get those, that bubble gum
that looks like gold nuggets?
You ever get that?
That's a damn good bubble gum.
- I had the bubble gum that looks like
a chunk of coal. Did you ever get that bubble gum that looks like a roll of tape? You ever
play the game you can only play when you're high? I have. Yeah, we watched that again.
You watched it again? Yeah, on Halloween. Whoa, I didn't know that. It's way better
than I remembered. I remembered it being like, oh, it was boring to watch and that one line
was the only funny part. It's so funny, the whole thing. It's really funny. Yeah, the
Chucky. Everybody go watch Chucky Friends 'Til the End on YouTube. It's a real Chucky
movie that was made for a little but we need to make a fan movie. I know we need
that's what I'm saying that that I mean we need we need to make our I think that
Jason vs. Pennywise I think that's our $20,000 goal. That's what I was gonna say.
I think that could be our $20,000 goal is we make a feature-length fan vs. movie.
That would be so sick dude. What would we purchase? Just get like 20 costumes of different
characters. Yeah we spend it like Party City costumes. Yeah that's actually
really such a good idea. Can we do that?
Yeah, we'll set that up.
Like a tiger electronics camera.
The ultimate showdown.
Oh my god. The movie.
We get Neil involved.
Dude, we get Neil Cicerega.
Holy crap.
I was supposed to say holy cow,
then I said holy crap, and then it turned into holy craup.
Why'd you try to say holy cow?
I'm off my game today. I'm sorry about my performance this episode.
I know my pay will be docked for this.
We always, any um
that you throw in, I dock you $10.
- I know.
- Anytime you give up in the middle of the story,
because you can't remember the end, I dock you $100.
- No, I know, that's why I've been hurting
this past couple months.
- As your mental deficiencies kind of start to show through
more and more, you've been losing a lot of money.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, and me and Cam have been doing really well
for ourselves.
- Interesting.
- Very interesting how that works.
- Strange.
- Yeah.
- Rather strange.
- It's crazy.
- A rather strange phenomenon observed on the podcast
about list podcasts that would be like if a nature documentary was about what
was going on.
Oh yeah, and here we have Patrick completely still.
A rather compellingly strange organism, they might say.
Patrick in his natural habitat, the couch, leaned back, not a care in the
world.
You're sitting in a really funny way.
Look at his legs.
You look, honestly, because of the clothes you're wearing, you look like
you're 400 pounds right now, dude.
I gotta stop wearing this sweater.
You look so huge.
This sweater makes me look like way fatter.
You look like Baron Harkonnen dude.
You're like floating on that chair.
You look like a Russian stacking doll.
Like the sleeves are so small but then like the rest of the sweatshirt itself.
That's crazy.
Yeah.
Dude it's so fucked up.
I think they like, I think it was made to look like this dude.
It was made to make you look huge and fat?
Yeah.
sexy. Oh my God. Wait, you're actually beautiful now. Yeah, I have a lot of clothes that do
not fit me at all. None of my clothes fit me. I just got to do a whole like, I said I was
going to sell. I think we should do a yard sale. We should do a yard sale. We could go
to a big tall... Selling some of my crap. That's such a curse, dude. Having to choose
between it. I can either get like shorter pants that are like super, like too baggy
more like to short
is like my head over the big and tall store brother i guess i don't care
enough to help you salvation brother we're getting i would love salvation
uh... casual mail excel
the other side of me
yeah
now i would make you look
i'll make you look beautiful you know i think i'm a little bit of a like flavor
flayton
you know i think it is a little machine so i can that's not what i would do it
was i was like uh... extreme makeover person
every single time I'd be like so we're gonna start we're gonna start with a
very tasteful humongous clock hanging from your neck and then maybe hmm have
you ever considered a purple hat I think it would bring out your eyes and your
name it's gotta go and it's gonna be right now
Flava Flav. There's like a copyright dispute so it's become flavor flavor
for taste man tasty tasty tasty tasty tasty taste yeah yeah yeah you are now
tongue-y tongue have you considered also being seven or eight inches shorter and
having a big fat friend next to you here all right we have legally changed your
name to dr. scrumptious that's just I think that's a good like if you're on if
you're like if today one of us got replaced replaced the guy on queer eye
for a tan France right that's like the clothes a great name yeah, it's one of
the best names and friends like that's what a two year old would call him if
you saw
like literally like a two year old.
Tan France is that his fucking name is somebody saying and Frank while they
are half asleep yeah. I don't know
there's a there's a show me the body song where he says dead friends, but
I first like I'm so bad at hearing lyrics and songs that I thought he was saying
tan I'd be sick but I think it's Madonna rock if one of us was replaced him which
and we wouldn't cuz we are well they would change they would make it
American trade I yeah well yeah we're straight out for the normal I we should
do straight out for the gay guy yeah we just teach them how to keep their room a
mess yeah yeah how to get it hey you're not you're not eating enough cheese yeah
you're going to need to make your keyboard really sticky. Right. We just go in and just like,
just like, like financial district gay guy and we just teach him how to keep his apartment messy.
Just like, just just like, just flicking like, now these are called Doritos.
Their TV and and and computer monitor. Yeah. These are called Doritos. Yeah,
you got those from my pantry. They are delicious. Do not wash your hands.
crumbling toritos into like his fish tank.
Just taking the top sheet off his bed.
You're not gonna be needing this anymore.
This has gotta go and just like be just hitting the fuck out of his bed frame with hammers.
Walk around, take every priceless piece of art in his like financial district apartment,
just replacing it with a flat screen TV.
Just as like 80.
You're turning this apartment into Chili's?
Just getting, just gradually, just gradually getting like not even just like gross guy
guy stuff, but just like it just turning it into like like just leaving like
like standing water in the bath,
yeah,
hand,
because also we're
five five giant pigs.
What a straight guys like I don't know you should never flush
keeping your bathroom just completely disgusting, smashing all the window
yeah, make him dress like he's doing Kabuki theater.
Yeah, but yes, the straight guys like yeah, you're going to need to dress like
Wolverine.
His claws are cool to straight guys.
Yeah,
like me just having just like just raw meat sitting in his pantry for days and
days.
We're like he has to eat the maggots.
He just needs more flies.
We're just describing the apartments we hung out in in college.
Yeah, that is kind of what my apartment was.
Yeah, I used to have a mountain of recycling.
Oh, dude.
I'm about to close right now.
Our recycling in my old apartment, it used to, it was in the pantry.
Oh fuck, I remember that dude.
And it would get so high that it would cover up the food in the pantry.
And you'd have to take the recycling out to even get to the fucking food on the bottom
two shelves.
Dude, I remember.
And then we would take it, we wouldn't even put it outside, we were too lazy.
We had a room that was like a little, it was like a closet that was blocked by our couch.
So we would move the couch, open that door, and just put all our recycling in this room.
I think when we left there was probably, it was like honestly filled like, like probably
like mid torso level of just can.
There was a window next to the trash though.
What?
Yeah, in your old apartment, wasn't that, didn't that kitchen window open up to where
you threw the trash out?
I wasn't gonna, I'm not an animal, I'm not gonna throw trash out of my window.
Dude, no, you're allowed to, if you live close enough to the trash, you can throw your trash
bag out the window.
I would have had to bullseye fucking 100 360 no scope it to make it into the trash can.
You have your other roommate go down there.
That was the problem, was the going down part.
I lived on the third floor.
I'm not going to walk all the way up and down the stairs.
Also they put a fucking code on the lock to the trash cans.
Really?
Yeah, because people were fucking throwing their own trash in there that didn't belong
to them.
Oh, okay.
Scumbags.
Right.
Ruining shit for everybody.
at my apartment.
Just give it to a homeless person instead.
They like it.
They build clothes and house out of it.
I will say the people, the homeless people in this neighborhood seem to have a serious
fucking trash addiction.
Yeah.
They're like fucking.
They're digging through it.
They're eating it.
They're snarfing it down.
It's like not even out of my hands before there's a guy with a black and mild in his
mouth like picking out all the cans.
The way that people around here wear like.
Can you just do that when I'm not looking?
wearing like like like suits of armor made of like cardboard and like like like
six I just wanted a plastic rings like they look they're walking around they
look like a like a clickbait article it's like best Halloween costume ever
made from trash yeah yeah was that guy in Boston who had a throne mmm remember
him which one's a bulb oh was it no there was a guy who had a he was sitting
on he had a cardboard throne and his face was completely bandaged all the
all the way around and then he put glass like sunglass on top of it like he was
the invisible man. You don't remember this guy? No. I think you might have
dreamed it. No, no because I talked about it. I talked about it with all the people at
Mooya. Oh, the invisible king. Yeah, well also I was like I'm not gonna give you
money dude. You're like, you're on a throne. Yeah, nobody on a throne. I never saw the invisible king either.
I might bow down to you but I'm not gonna like give you my money unless you say it's
taxes and then I guess I kind of have to right or else I'm gonna fuck my wife or
something yeah, but I was like that's that was that's what you should be doing if
you're homeless. You should be making the you should be breaking Guinness World
Record with cardboard pretty much every day because like yeah, what else are you
going to do you fucking lazy moron? Yeah, you know I'm saying yeah. I said yeah,
what you got to do you got to scratch the wound on your leg. That's what you
have to do for eight hours every day building a that's your job a particle
accelerator out of cardboard. That's what you should be doing exactly. Yeah,
society that yeah you should be on science you should be you should be
developing a doomsday I mean because here's the thing right is like they
could just they could be using you as Guinea but they could just be sending
you to other dimensions yeah that's I mean that's the bar you have to pass
exactly with cardboard and trash materials they could be shooting you into
space and learning like how what happens when the human body freezes in a vacuum
you know what I would be doing if I was homeless I'd be sign up for every
fucking medical trial that they have cuz yeah who gives a fuck right I'm gonna
- I signed up for the G League.
(laughing)
- You know, there's like two or three guys
who made it from homeless to the G League.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, it's pretty cool.
- I didn't know that.
- They have like open tryouts.
- I think they stole my idea.
- They have open tryouts, but also like,
how hard is it to, like, if you're fucking,
like I heard one story that was like,
a guy was homeless, I can't remember the guy's name,
and he tried out for the--
- Homeless Jim.
- I think it was Homeless Jim.
He was homeless, and a guy came up to him
and he was like, "Hey, like the Pistons are playing,
"or the Piston G League thing is tomorrow,
are like you should go like try out for that and ended up getting it and i was
like how stupid you have to be to be literally seven feet tall and on the
street and never think once like maybe i should play basketball.
Like maybe i'd be good at basketball yeah like that guy that guy deserves to
be homeless. If i ever if i'm ever like about to have like a if i'm ever going
to have like a big break i'll probably be homeless for like a day beforehand. So
i can say like i made it from like being homeless, you know, like the king of the
world, because that's coming for me. Yeah, yeah, I would look. I remember there's
this guy, like a pastor in my hometown, who did this thing where he was like,
he was like, I'm going, I'm going out tonight to be, to like live with the
homeless people downtown and be, like experience what it's really like to be
homeless for a night. Yeah. Meanwhile, like on the way downtown, he got
Chick-fil-A and then he like brought his phone there and like watched a movie in
a tent. Yeah, yeah. He just went camping downtown. Right. It was like, that was
a life changing experience. I didn't realize that people were addicted to
realize how much fun it is I'm gonna do this every night hmm I'm not gonna be
your pastor anymore yeah I've decided to become homeless full-time but I just
that's so cool dude because like me to do a service I will give them any money or
help them at all he just went can't in front of them and it was like he just
took finally yeah finally I know what yeah yeah he took the best spot the spot
with the most shade yeah so fucking cool yeah dude I would never do that you would
I would do that I would do it I'd really ham it up though yeah like it's like
bear grills like this is I cross into skid row just to dress up like the
opposite I would dress up like a haunted house actor like a Victorian orphan
ghost just be covered in blood every homeless guy be like what the fuck do we
need to take you to hospital or something I'd be like no I like it yeah
What are you see?
Undercover I'm undercover. I'm a police officer. I'm a
Firefighter you know any secrets about homeless people is it no drugs to you
It's a good idea. You should tell me yeah, it's a pretty good idea. There's
Apparently there used to be a lot of like
I would like to buy some drugs, please, and you know they're going to be
evidence, and you know you better go to jail when you sell them to me,
don't and I'm not and you know I'm not doing them send him to be a spy on
the Russians.
Yeah, look on red good to see and you know I'm an American spider.
You know that's just as me. My name is Brian, don't you know my name's
Brian, and you know my name, Brian, and I'm from Tulsa. You know I went to
Quantico and shit damn
like what yeah what what is he saying what these day with the way you talk you
say you say you spy we spit this is just this is riselka I'm not a spy though
I'm a spy you know I'm like the best you're not a sneaky spy and you know I'm
going through lasers and you know I'm gonna crawl under a laser later and I'm
gonna take some stuff from you how many lasers do you think you really get
involved with this by.
And you know I'm sneaking up on you right now.
And you know I'm...
Did you hear that?
That's behind you.
You're just sitting in your house.
Just guarding a nuclear warhead.
And you know I'm sneaking up on that guy.
And you know I'm gonna be right behind you.
And you know my glasses are a camera.
And you know I'm gonna stab you in my pen.
And you know I'm quiet as a mouse.
And you know you can't hear me.
You just hear it in the vents above you.
And you know I'm crawling through the vents.
You know you can't hear it in the vents above you.
And you know I'm crawling through the vents!
[Laughter]
Yeah.
You know I'm crawling, oh, you know I'm stopping at the girls locker room!
[Laughter]
The girls locker room in the Russian nuclear base.
Yeah, dude. Dude, fucking huge babes there, bro.
Yeah, dude. The Russian military outfit for women is literally a fur bikini with a funny hat.
Yeah, and it has been from a 60 years. No, I'm trying that on when they look at
And you know I'm gonna check all the lockers for their lunches
And you know I'm using the bathroom, and you know I don't know what country I'm in yeah
And you know I'm gonna use the girls bathroom because I want to see if the bathrooms are different from boys bathroom
They are different. Yeah, the toilets are wider. They usually have a dip
Toilets are wider to account for fat asses. What? Because only women can be fat. No, well women have big fat asses and big juicy tits
Wider things for the they also have a shelf that sits right in front so they can lay their humongous boobs on them
They're big tasty
fucking
boobies
Yeah, I love boobs man
And you know I'm gonna look that up later
And you know I'm gonna look up pictures of boobs later?
*makes weird noises*
I'd like to know where you've been Dave.
Nowhere, honey.
And you know I was at Samantha's house though.
*laughter*
And you know you gotta get tested later.
And you know I always hated your dad though.
And that's why I did it though.
What?
he can't go ahead and get here you mom fighting
no son go to bed
and you know that in my kid
uh...
you know i mean i can't get
he's got brown hair you know what i'm on
uh...
that that'd be like a affiliate guy like that like he he has the the
if he's cursed with their forever haven't speak the truth of the world
it'll be the characters ever to what i mean absolutely
here i am some are bright work ever
he's also has so much is a possibility of becoming like the greatest man of all
time
earlier only fully realized bearing themselves as a shun truth yeah
who's telling no ability to not tell the truth a hundred percent of the time you
know
you can you know i'm
okay that ups
got any twenty bucks yeah and uh... three twenty bucks off you had a really young
you know i think thirty and you know actually take a forty
It's just endless fun to me. It is yeah.
And you know I'm having an epiphany right now.
Yeah.
Ninja...
I'm just staring into nothing.
And you know I'm about to change my life up after this.
And you know I just realized something.
And you know I'm going to try and fix my relationship with my father.
Yeah, if you guys could take a pill that made you
Made you a DeBriant?
Made you really high
*Laughter*
Yeah
Yeah, I would too
Nah
So yeah, would you rather press like the button that like makes a bright red
light or like a button that makes a bright green light?
If you could drink a drink that made you drunk, would you do it?
Yeah, like what food would you eat?
If you could eat food, would you? If you could have anything in the world,
would you? I would. Yeah, would you rather have like fingers on your hands
or toes on your feet?
(laughter)
- Alright, you get two ears and you get to hear out of them.
- Yeah.
- But, when you put your fingers in them,
you can't hear anything.
- Okay, yeah.
You have $10 to build your perfect woman.
If $5 is beautiful, $5 is perfect.
(laughter)
- You have $10 to get a chicken salad sandwich at Subway.
What do you get?
- What do you get on the side?
- Yeah.
What are your free topics? Hypothetically, this is all hypothetical, right? Yeah. This
is the hypotheticals. Are you taking a million dollars? If you had a job that paid you a
million dollars a year and you got a million dollars, would you take the job? If you won
the lottery, would you rather win one million dollars all at once or whenever? Just randomly.
would or wall at the same time. Do you guys trust yourselves enough to do the lump sum
with the lottery? No. I would have to. No you, okay. Here's what, no lump sum, lump sum, lump
sum. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I don't know. I'd have to do the math on it. I feel like, I feel like
like literally what I would do is I would sit down and be like, I have to do the math on
it. No, I would sit down and be like how long do I think I'm going to live? Oh, true. Like.
Well, but it's not like they...
Yeah, well true, because I don't know what happens to the rest of the money if you die.
I would like, if I won that much money, I literally, I would sit down and be like,
"Do I think I'm living to like 40, 60, 70?"
Like, how much money should I like be aiming to spend?
Because that's a lot, like if you win like that much money,
I guess you probably want to leave some of it to your kids, but still.
I honestly think in my life, I will win the lottery.
Yeah, it could happen.
I have a true belief that I will win the lottery.
I feel like it's coming dude.
Yeah?
How often do you play?
Never.
I've played one time and it was wins.
That's it.
It's only wins.
The lottery can smell when you're a stinky old lady who buys a hundred scratch tickets
a day.
It won't let you win.
Have you ever won a scratcher?
Yeah, I won a bunch of scratchers.
Oh really?
Yeah.
My dad gets...
I got a hundred bucks on a scratcher and it's nice.
Since I was like six or seven.
I know.
My parents let me scratch it and then I got to buy whatever I wanted.
that dude I bought an external hard drive for the computer and I put all my games
on it. Nice. Doing a scratcher when you're underage is so sick.
Yeah. You have to give it to your... Especially if you win too much dude it sucks though
because then it's like your parents are in charge of it. Yeah. But I was since ever since I was like
six or seven my dad's gift to me at Christmas every year has been five
scratchers. Yeah. So sick. Yeah. And I won one year but then we have a my dad
makes this fucking lame-ass rule where it's like if you win over $500 everyone
splits it it's like oh dude fuck you yeah yeah I'm 13 you have a job you fucking
lazy piece of shit you're fucking waiting on me to use all my luck so that
you can have 200 bucks dude fuck yeah yeah but I didn't ever tell him that I'm
really scared of him actually there were guys that would play games of skate for
scratchers yeah and scratchers is like they bought like $20 worth of scratchers
Absolutely.
Yeah, it's so sick though.
I think one dude won like, they bought like 20 bucks worth of scratchers after he won a
game of skate and then he won like 120.
Which is like man, fuck.
You won twice that day.
That's crazy.
It's basically getting one spin of a slot printed out and that's what you have.
When we moved into our apartment in Boston, our realtor just gave us a free scratcher.
wrote like I like thank you for like choosing like me or whatever and then
like put a scratcher and we won like like 25 bucks on I bought one every once in
a while like fuck you and then she and then I never emailed her again or print I
pretended she didn't exist yeah nice yeah bitch if I have if I have five bucks
and I'm like getting a soda down at the corner store I'll pick up a scratcher I
for some reason thought I think it's Powerball isn't it like you have to be a
resident of the place that you bought the ticket. You are a resident. Yeah, but like
legally. You are legally, you reside in New York City. Yeah, but my ID. That
doesn't mean anything. Yeah. Okay, so I could be buying scratchers? Yeah, yeah you
could be buying, well scratchers, you can buy scratchers, I mean it's literally you
hand a guy five dollars, he doesn't even ID you. You know what we should do? You buy them out of
vending machines. We should go and just buy like a whole roll. The entire roll?
We buy a whole roll of scratchers.
That would be sick though.
One dollar scratchers.
Yeah.
Spend the entire Patreon one month.
Just see what we make, dude.
We could swing a thousand dollars to buy a whole roll of scratchers.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
That's doable.
I mean, I have a thought like that every month, though.
Yeah.
Every month I have some thought where I'm like, "What if we just put it all on one horse
that we bet on or something?"
Yeah.
And then maybe we get really rich.
Who fucking knows?
on or something. Yeah. And then maybe we get really rich, who fucking knows. Yeah. That'd
be cool, right? It would be cool. Just 100 times whatever we make. Horse racing would
be cool. I would love to go to a horse race. We should do the Kentucky Derby. I'm down.
I'm small enough to be a jockey. Costumes. Costumes. Yep. Kentucky Derby costumes. And
you know I'm gonna have a biscuit. And you know. You know my hat's gonna be big. I'm
thinking guy dressed all in purple with a big clock. Yeah. For the Kentucky Derby. That
could be good yeah. I think that'd be a good one yeah. What where is like yeah
where is the Kentucky Derby? I know I'm thinking of it now I'm thinking of our
Brian character but he goes like another level into it like he like he like gets
food at a restaurant he's like he's like and you know I'm gonna be stealing that
and you know that means I'm not gonna pay anybody for it. He explains it further yeah. In a higher voice yeah and he keeps going just yeah and you know I'm
I'm stealing that and you know I'm just kidding that's after he finds himself
and he becomes a better person. He introduces another layer yeah, yeah,
we're kind of just making a guy with like a little like disorder yeah. More
we get into this. I think this is I think most guys are that guys with mental
disorder. Most guys have mental disorder. It's okay. My mental is completely
clean you they've done tests. I'm disorderly. They've scanned my brain and
they found I don't know really they found nothing there. They said, sir, you
of chaos in there. No, no, they said that to me. Oh, really? Yeah, they're too
scared. And I said, I said this, yes, no, you blew their minds. So you have a
bunch of you have a ball of black and red crap in the middle of your head.
Yeah, you have there's a bunch of tangled string in there. It'd be cool to
get an x-ray from a doctor and they're just like all right cool. Would you
rather get an x-ray from a doctor or a nurse? Definitely a nurse dude.
male nurse. Because if they fuck it up, male nurse. Because they're gonna fuck it up probably.
And then I get, I sue them. Yeah. You know? And you know I just irradiated my patient.
Malpractice is one of the scariest things to me. Medical malpractice. Why? They're not
doing anything to you. You don't go to the doctor. I know. Because of this I'm afraid
of it. You're afraid they're gonna like, they're gonna prescribe you the wrong knee brace? No,
have you ever seen that Malcolm in the Middle episode where he's like, oh I'm fine now but
but then the doctors are like,
oh, I'm gonna go through with the surgery anyway.
- No. - No?
- You think you're gonna go to the doctor
and they're just gonna operate on you,
you're gonna have no say in it?
- Yeah.
- What world do you live in? - You don't think
a doctor would do that?
- A doctor cannot, - What?
- Can't just operate on you - You don't think a surgeon
would just do that? - Without your consent?
- True, I guess it's not a problem for me.
- Unless it's a life-saving operation,
and you have to, and if you're unconscious,
and you still have to have somebody
who can talk for you. - I guess this is a problem
that you would only have as a child.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause your parents have to be the ones
to give the consent, right?
- Okay, yeah, yeah.
So your problem is that you thought that doctors--
- You thought your parents were gonna let the doctors
like tear you apart for no reason.
- But you still think now that doctors,
just you don't have any rights.
- You think that a doctor's gonna see you
and be like, "We need to cut you open right now."
- Yeah.
- We have to take his bones.
- He's got bad bones.
- Yeah, sir, there's something inside you.
I think a doctor, what if I wake up on the operating table
and my whole arm bone is gone and it's wiggling around
like that scene in Harry Potter?
- Oh yeah.
- Oh, that would be scary.
That scene's scary.
I think that scene did scare me
when I watched that as a kid.
The wiggling bone.
- The fact that it hurt when it re-grew scared me.
I was like, ugh.
- Broken bones in general scared me a lot, I think.
- Funny medical thing.
I was, funny little medical story I have.
- What a tidbit.
- So my left eye has just been like
watering constantly recently.
And I think it's like just an allergy or something.
But when I was having lunch with my buddy the other day,
and I was just telling him about it,
I hadn't seen him in a while.
I was like, oh yeah, it's so weird.
I have this like fucking watery eye thing.
Like, it's so annoying.
And I was like, who knows, maybe it's brain cancer.
And he was like, oh yeah, that's funny.
You know what's also funny?
I had this friend that I used to work with
who his left eye would twitch constantly and then we make all these jokes like
maybe it's brain cancer or something and then it was actually brain cancer and he
died. Wow. And I was like that is a funny little tidbit. Don't tell me that
when I said that I have like the exact same thing going on my eyes. It's
different. Yeah. There's something weird with my eye. Water is different than a twitch. But it
also twitches. Have you ever considered you might just be sad? No.
Okay. Open up your heart.
Anything to plug?
Ummm...FUCK YOU!
Poop store.