Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
Premium content!
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately!
I love my birthday, I love my birthday, I love my birthday, I love my birthday, I love
my birthday, I love my birthday, I love my birthday, I love my birthday, I love my birthday,
Stop singing.
I love my birthday.
Oh, he's not even singing.
He can lip sync it.
Because I wasn't there.
I love my birthday.
So, wait.
So, what happened?
I love my birthday.
Get this, man.
Craziest shit ever.
It was this guy's birthday.
It was this one guy's birthday and we started singing.
I love my birthday.
He started singing it.
No, we started singing it.
We antagonistically.
We tried to get him to sing it.
He was like.
We started singing that like really loudly all around the bar.
Yeah, well, no.
What happened was he kept singing it was his birthday and he kept, he was very stupid.
stupid. He was he was honestly one of the stupidest people I've ever seen. I kept showing him
stuff and he would just do like I would like we showed him the thumb trick where he looked
like a fucking thumb. I ran up to him and was like hey it's your birthday right you
want to see a magic trick and I started just like holding my thumb like this just taking
it off of different parts of my hand and he was like whoa. I showed him the ibeer app
and he just stared at me blankly. And he basically yeah he kept saying yeah he was like. How
I just when he was we're playing, he just like insert himself into our group and
he was like yeah,
then he was like I have to go pee. It's my birthday.
I kept like he also when he would go get a drink, he would like start skipping
and then like realize that he was in a public place and like stop halfway
through and yeah, but basically he was on the other side of the room. You
would have actually like we would have been like this guy. So I was trying to I
I was trying to like get him to react. I just was standing across the room and I
just kept saying really loudly like it's my birthday today. I love my birthday.
It's nobody else's birthday today and he literally just didn't process like he
just did not say he was he just really fucked up. He did not seem drunk as the
thing. He was kind of drunk. I think he's kind of drunk, but he was not he was
not like sloppy. He was clearly very stupid and then you at the end. So then
we started saying I love my birthday really loud. He just he didn't react or
no. They got him right there and then at the end right before I left I was like
Hey, birthday boy, sing along with me.
I love my birthday.
And he just like stared at me.
He was like, I love my,
like he just couldn't figure out how to sing it.
- That white boy had no rhythm.
- Yeah. - No.
- He's cool though.
- Yeah. - I don't know.
- I would have stopped you guys.
I would have saved him.
- But that song is stuck in my head now really bad.
- I literally can't stop singing.
I love my birthday.
I think it might be a top 10 hit soon.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I agree.
I think we put a little...
We need to produce it. We need Pharrell.
"I Love My Birthday" is the chorus and then like...
"Will.i.am"
And then there's a verse about presents.
"Damn, it's my birthday"
"It wasn't just the first day"
"Smoking on that Chronicle"
"My birthday got Bionicles"
"I just got Bionicles"
"Lego Life on Mars set"
"Nerf gun the Vulture"
"Yeah"
I'm 12. I just got all editions of Spore. I love my birthday. I love my birthday. I love
my birthday. I love my birthday. I love my birthday. I love my birthday. I love my birthday.
I love my birthday. I love my birthday. I love my birthday. I'm gonna check it out.
Yeah, we have Kai with us today.
Hello.
I'm live from New York.
It's 7am, Kai.
I'm in the hallway office.
We should turn this into a museum already.
I think it would be cool to have one legendary bus.
One bus?
See that corner, we have Sullivan, we frame that, and then I think maybe frame the Plaza
meter too but then like in the right there is like a 3d that we need it a 3d
printed bust of okay well we don't frame the way we got a 3d okay here's a bust of
okay I think instead of I think instead of a bus looking at the wall I think
instead of a bust maybe we put oh I got Caleb a new maybe I think that what we
could do here is we put a lot that one pardon me sorry I think we put a rail
down the hallway here and we have like kind of like a car like a dark ride that
people can ride through a dark ride a writ you know his junkie has a skateboard
on it that's true yeah put anything like yeah well we'll put like gears and stuff
so if he tries to spike grind on it it'll grinds his feet like a glass divider
right here and then like an old couple could walk by with their hands behind
their backs when we were looking at office space I really wanted to get a
place that had like like like a retail space on like a busy street
know that we can just have open all the time while people guess why we're
sitting at a table that would be cool yeah yeah this is sort of like a
basement yeah we got a basement with a basement infected by flies yeah I've
been decorating Caleb's space for him what do you think I already showed really
beautiful mm-hmm did you notice the new poster I mean I don't know what new
poster is the one on the left no what the Batman yeah yeah dude I saw
that earlier. You did? Well I... Like last week. We were recording, we just got done
recording and you were in the bathroom and I acted really quick and put that up
and you had no idea that I put it up. Yes I did, I just didn't care. Oh. I just, I'm
numb to this by now. Yeah. This is not a prank or anything. I gave Caleb space, I gave him
this Batman, the Batman poster that I got when I saw the Batman at AMC. The thing?
yeah we got this big uh breath of the wilds um this big frames
in my corner i'm not gonna take it it's it's a framed breath of the wild
like like me and pat had a really good idea for what to put up next i'm not
gonna tell you you'll just see it and then uh this one looks expensive
my girlfriend gave me her old naruto uh thing
from middle school i like that every poster has gotten progressively bigger
The Naruto poster is a giant.
I know, there's like no space.
Caleb, can I ask a question about one of your decorations?
Yes, sir.
Are you your ancestor's wildest dreams?
I mean, I guess so, if it's in my car.
That one I found when I moved into my new place.
I found this in a poster tube in my closet.
Did you think you bought that at some point and you forgot about it?
No.
It's signed, too.
It's signed by the artist.
Yeah.
Caleb, you're your ancestor's wildest dreams.
I think I am my ancestor's wildest dreams.
I think I am my ancestors wildest dreams. I'm my ancestors wildest nightmares. I think my
ancestors were probably Irish travelers. If your great-great-grandpa got American Pickled,
do you think he'd be proud of you or not? My grandpa? You have to stop using that movie
as like a frame of reference. I think you're the only person in the world who has seen
that movie. My mom told me the synopsis so I know what he meant. Yeah. But I think you're
probably the only person who watched that movie. I think American Pickled has entered
the lexicon is like a something like a verb no yeah I got time machine do you
mean yeah I'm a really it's more of a time barrel that he's gonna be in and
yeah he's gonna be wet and green so what would you call that
well you're green yeah I'm green like the weed I'm smoking mm-hmm yeah oh my god
oh my god I back him dude dude yeah back over him
my damn truck bitch-ass fuck you mm-hmm I'm sorry he's one of those guys that I
wish would get would be in like a new jackass movie so you can see me a hurt
real good. I'd love to turn him into an American pancake. He looks like you? A little bit.
No. I guess I look like him, he's older. That's not the rule. That's the rule. I look like
him a little bit. I don't think so. Okay, thank you guys. I appreciate it. Have you
been told that a lot? I've been told Jack Black, him and- I've been told Jack Black by
my aunt. Yeah, I can see that. Every big guy who laughs, people will tell them they're
Jack Black doesn't laugh he makes you laugh. No he laughs. He tickles my funny bone. He's
funny as well. I'm not Jack Black. I'm getting back there. You getting back there? I'm getting
back there. You know what it was? I started drinking beer again instead of clear liquid.
Water. Water and clear Pedialyte. Natural Pedialyte. That stuff gets you so fucked up.
I love Pedialyte so much.
Dude, Pedialyte gets you so messy.
Electrolytes are fucking... guess what I'm sipping on right now.
Don't tell me it's electrolytes.
Electrolytes.
You just throw it in that?
Yeah, it's like a powder.
I think I have more in my bag actually.
Oh my god, give me some dude.
If I actually took them you can have them.
I need to try this shit.
Dude, I want to get like...
Oh, I did.
I wish I had...
Holy shit.
Is this Liquid IV?
No, it's the Walgreens brand, but it's $5 cheaper, but it's the exact same ingredients.
I'm going to just put it on my fingers.
You're going to gum it?
Yeah, I'm going to gum it. I'm going to drink it like a fun dip.
Snort triple hydration.
I'm the only one of us that doesn't have a fucking water bottle. Are you kidding me?
What do I have over there? I have a Codsby Surprise Egg. I could put it in and fill it up with water.
Water bottles are goated.
Dude, I had to get like a Nalgene or something. I keep buying fucking like water bottles when I like
What happened?
The fly got in there
There's fucking ten foot dude, I told you the bathroom has literally been taken over
Maybe you could use this cap - no, no just it's protein, dude
No, that's we have those are those are flies that braid in the toilet eat those. Yeah
No, these are so
So what happened was like how did the flies get it's that crack in the wall, right?
No, they they they lay eggs in warm and wet places. So I think what happened where they come is
I think they know oranges. Yep, they got in here by the oranges and then I think the heater was on
I think somebody left the heater on yesterday and the bathroom door was open
And so it got really hot in here and they all laid eggs in the toilet and sink drain and
spread out.
It's crazy.
I feel like with fruit flies, they have the ability to just like spawn out of nothing.
Yeah.
Fucking air.
Dude, they're like bacteria born or some shit.
They do player at place at me.
100.
Well, your place.
Myself.
My kids.
Yeah.
It's really cool.
That reminds me of like speaking of guess what I just got 15 out of my drink.
What flies through flies?
Hell yeah.
And they're all in that cap.
But like, if you ever heard of those medieval recipes for like, recipe for an ox.
And it's like, bury a, you know, a bees nest on the fourth day of autumn.
Yeah.
And you know, that kind of shit.
And then you just get an ox according to that.
That's what flies are doing constantly.
Yeah.
That's probably what Minecraft was based on.
They're being summoned.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
I wish I could summon animals.
You can summon flies by being stinky.
You can do that.
Yeah.
will follow you like a familiar. You can summon super fly by being a hoe.
It's true.
I guess you can summon humans by shooting your gunk.
By calling them.
Oh, you can also summon rats by wearing like tights and playing a flute and
dancing around.
That's true, yeah.
True.
And by being pied.
Yeah, pied.
Yeah.
Really?
Yeah. If you're pied.
You're pied and you got a pipe?
Nah, that's different.
The creamed pied piper did something different.
That's the cream pied piper.
It was actually the cream pied pipey.
You summon, if you get cream pied, someone summons nine months later.
Yeah.
Wait, what the hell?
That's true.
Wait, let me think about that.
Wait, let me think.
It's actually true.
Wait, so I can summon one million white frogs by just tickling my thing?
Yeah.
One million tadpoles.
No, they're frogs.
frogs that first fish that crawled out of the ocean summoned all the people.
That's true.
Just took a long spell to cast.
If someone had had frog sperms instead of tadpole sperms and they come down something and they
could see the cubs crawling around.
Like the chocolate toad in Harry Potter?
You busted a nut.
I would love my sperm to jump down Ron Weasley's throat.
I'd love to feel my sperms four years old.
At the end they're like 16 really.
No, specifically in the second movie.
I'd love if each of my sperms was one inch long so I could feel them coming out like a
boba straw.
Oh my god.
Have you ever seen that video, I'm sure you've heard it, but it's like the loudest orgasm
ever and it's just the guy nuts and he just goes like, "Eeeeeeaaaaaahhhhhh!"
(screaming)
- That's not that loud, I could definitely, like just,
- You could just yell.
- It's not so hard to do a loud orgasm.
- I guess he had, I guess he--
- If that's the record, I'll break it tonight.
- The YouTube comments I read said that he had a kidney stone
at the same time as him nutting.
- That's just, why would they know that?
- See, I don't think that's true,
but I'm choosing to believe that.
- Yeah, I'll choose to believe that too.
- Based on the pitch of his voice,
he probably had a kidney stone at the same time
as he was nutting.
- My favorite thing is honestly,
like when there's a video somewhere
that's clearly somebody or either a person or an animal dies in the video.
Yeah.
And then you look at the comments and somebody's like, "Don't worry guys.
He's okay and he just suffered like a broken arm."
It's funny that I always...
Yeah, got a bullet going slow motion through a guy's head like Sniper Elite.
I always believe that comment for like 10 seconds.
Me too. I just choose to be like, "Yep, I believe that."
There was that one video of the...
The dog.
The dog, yeah. The dog flying...
What is it? It's like a propane tank or something?
no it's a it's a soda bottle like a two liter soda bottle with some kind of gas
yeah and they throw it up in the air and the dog runs after it and then it goes
like oh and the dog just goes like stiff as a board and just flies and not just
that the comments like the dogs fuck and the explosion is so powerful that it
sets off a car alarm in the parking lot and the dog is like completely stiff like
a hamster in a fucking cage is dead god bless the person who just said the dog
That person is like honestly doing so much. Yeah, that's a white lie that we need. That's I think that's a work bomb
Have you ever heard of that? It's oh, yeah this toilet cleaner my neighbor
Aluminum foil. Yeah. Yeah, my neighbor used to make those. Yeah, I used to like make those and put them
He would bury them underground so that like the ground would explode. Yeah, was he just being cool or was he trying to do?
Yeah, this is the same neighbor that showed me three guys one hammer when I was like nine years old. I got you
He's an older neighbor?
Yeah.
Oh, cool.
He's my sister's age.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Dude, people who are your sister's age are the best.
Yeah, he showed me a lot of fucking shit.
It's true, dude.
We had this neighbor, his name was Phillip, and he--
He had a cousin named Phillip.
That's really cool.
He was like a kid who's--
This is my cousin.
His dad was like old and crazy and was like a mad scientist, and his dad would do--
- We had this neighbor, her name was Franny K. Stein.
(laughing)
And she was a crazy scientist.
- He was cool, he had hovercrafts.
- No.
- What?
- Yeah, it's like a--
- Like propellers?
- Yeah, it's like a boat that has a real powerful fan
and it lifts it like a half inch off the ground.
- That's all you need?
- It was so cool.
- My neighbor was the exact opposite,
where it's just like we were all very white trash.
And that's why he had a go-kart and dirt bikes and stuff.
it was a good word used to throw waterproof firecrackers into the dam
pond
told them i'm breadon
to trick the fish into eating a firecracker
uh... lol yeah i never held his wife hostage
route really uh...
uh... he came in and i think that the
uh... awesome all cool is not so that's very one time i got a letter
that's
every time i try to have a little with my neighbor one time my little killed
JFK with a sniper rifle. My neighbor was one year younger than me. Okay, my
neighbor was my babysitter once. My neighbor was my cousin. That is actually
that my neighbors had a fully blue room in their house. My dad lived in my house.
My dad married my mom. Really? Were they your neighbors? No. They were neighbors
with my aunt who married her husband. I do I wish I wish that I had the I wish I
had the the Boston Catholic everybody lives in the same house and next door
oh my that sucked that sucked growing up because it was like all my cousins were
like basically my like brothers yeah and your brother's like that's like what my
brothers were like my dog was like my mom and my mom was like my like my dad
had that and I think it's not enough yeah that I didn't get that yeah dude
it it's fucking horrible like you it would have been cool though like you
can't do shit with everything like oh like I can't sneak out cuz like my
fucking aunt lives next door. Why the hell would you want to sneak out? There's this one time
where like my... You only sneak out what to go see your cousins? They're in
the fucking house with you. No, I'm sneaking out to go to a damn party. With your cousins?
Yeah, you just take your cousins. The whole house is a party if you got all your cousins. There's this one time my
aunt, my aunt Kathy who lived directly next door, like my brothers were fighting
and it got so loud that she like did like she was like I have to do something
And she tried to like walk into my house to like yell at us
And I like shut the door on her was like what the fuck are you do like you're like just walking into my house
Yeah, you can't do that like you this is like can't say that to your aunt. I don't think that's
It's not my brothers from fighting so that they came over and were like hey
You can't just walk into our foot like my brothers were like beating the shit out of me
I would say she's I think neatly in the right
probably but like I think if your aunt is also your neighbor I think that that's
probably the number one thing that she can do is walk into your house.
Yeah, because that might as well be a noise complaint from your neighbor but it's somebody who is
your aunt and and can come over and also why are these kids fighting?
You know why they were fighting? They would get into fistfight like
full-on brawls because they just couldn't play video games with each other.
Oh dude, that's... Yeah. They were like they were they were still doing it when my
brother was like like a week from turning like 18. Yeah. It was like if he like hurt
him bad enough he would like it would be like counted as like a domestic. I was
just saying that they can't play video games with each other do you mean like
they just like they weren't allowed to? No, well my fucking parents should have
done something. That's a good rule. It's like okay you guys can't like that it's
not like I was gonna play fucking NHL with them they would play NHL and then
get into real hockey fights.
Like sometimes he would like and then they would fucking play
hockey together in the driveway too. And like that would also
turn into just hockey fights. Like it was they they were very
committed to the hockey fights. Yeah, fights are cool. Oh, yeah.
No, I think they did it just so they could fight each other. But
then like my aunt would also come out and yeah, reports just
be like, what the fuck are you? Were they angry fighting or just
angry fighting okay they were like genuinely pissed at each other and would
like pull the shirts over and just like beat the fuck out of each other Wow
dude the biggest fight I ever got in with my brother was because I was just I was
just using the computer and he just unplugged it yeah and I just went ape
dude I was probably doing I was probably googling like our rappers good guys
unplugged my computer I just started wailing on him yeah yeah I used the computer the most in
the house and they would everyone to getting mad at me was just one time I
can tell this year it was like I'm calculating whether or not I'd be like
super I was calculating whether or not I'd be super embarrassed I had just
discovered like like someone forgot to clear the history I'd like just
discovered internet pornography when I was like 11. I just found like, "Oh this is
like the website where all the porn is." And I kept like
scrolling through because like I'd never seen a vagina before and I looked at one
and I went, "Oh my god! What?!" I kept like scrolling through stuff and I was
like I think I had opened like a hundred different tabs. I think I came home from
school earlier I like stayed home or something yeah yeah I stayed home from
school and my sister got home from school at like one o'clock mm-hmm and
she'd walked down so I closed it as fast as possible and then I opened up I was
on this like Batman fan website.
I was looking at like action figures and shit.
And then my sister came downstairs like,
"I need to use the computer for school."
And I got up from the computer and ran outside.
(laughing)
And I hid in the woods for like an hour.
And then like, I finally walked back in,
like tried to like sneak past everybody.
And then my sister and my dad were already talking.
They were like, "What the fuck?"
(laughing)
There was like 100 pages.
- One time in middle school,
my friend Jackson, like, just was like, "Kyle, look at this!"
And like really quickly on his phone, or his iPod Touch or something, just like showed me like
a video of like a woman just squirting way too much.
And I was just like, "Ugh!" And then he was like, "Ugh?"
And I was like, "That was nasty! What was that?" He was like,
"That was a woman's vagina." And you said, "Ew."
- Oh my god, I love you. - I just got checkmated.
But like, it was a nasty video when I was like 12. Like, I still think that's kind of--
I don't want to know I don't want to see a picture of a vagina
I don't see that's disgusting. That's what clothes are for. Yeah, that's why we fucking invented clothes. Yeah, that's the only reason
I don't want to look at boobs or butts
Male form no
Didn't man no
Perfect V lines honestly. I'd rather I was a man pretending to be Atlas
I would rather see a penis than a guy's abs.
Okay.
And I would also rather see a penis than a vagina.
Yeah.
But I would rather see boobs than a penis.
Okay.
What about girl butt?
Girl butt?
You can just see that on the street.
Girl butt's just like, not even on the street.
You can see everyone's butt.
I'll see butt, you know.
If you look close enough, you can see everyone's butt.
Oh, it's just there.
You could see Girl Butt on the street and like stopping in the middle.
Yeah, that sounded really bad.
Yeah.
I was like, you can just look at any girl's butt on the street.
What are you guys talking about?
Yeah, that's not...
That did not sound good.
Girl, I mean, butt, as far as I'm concerned, butt is just a matter of...
I mean, just go to the beach.
Yeah.
That's what butts are about.
Or the bathroom.
Yeah.
Yeah, just go to their locker room.
If you want to see any of this shit.
Just go to your security.
I'm sick of kids getting hooked on porn so young. Back in the day we just snuck into the girls locker room.
Yeah, like a little nerd outfit, bring a ladder and binoculars around.
I mean if you want to see a girl butt just go to your surveillance screens.
Right? Just go to your Dark Knight giant wall of every blink fitness.
Put some of my computer up. Alfred, Alfred, Alfred show me the biggest butt.
I won't be part of this, Mr. Wayne.
Here she is, Mrs. Nicki Minaj.
He's plugged into the Grammys girls locker
Batman's using that like sonar thing
Effect where it's like it's like zooming around
Alfred Winnie dead smell a vision to this now
Master Wayne Master Wayne is really incredible what you've done with this, but picture smells like Joker gas
He's shoes on. The Joker's in her butt. The Joker's in her butt Alfred.
I don't think that if the Joker's hiding in Nicki Minaj's fucking ass that explains
why it's so damn big. I was born a poopy. Which is why I'm inside a butt. He's born a poopy.
The Joker was born a poopy. I don't know. We're talking about being inside a butt.
That's what's in there. Yeah I do kind of believe that girls with big big butts
have poop in their butt cheeks. Yeah, totally. And that's why they are so...
Do you think Two-Face had one red butt cheek? Yeah. Two-Face had two cheeks. One baboon ass.
I don't know. One half baboon ass, one ass. Baboon ass. Baboon ass. Baboon ass. Baboon
ass. Baboon ass. Baboon ass socks. You know those socks with the bees on them? You know
what we need for this... He had one really low hanging ball. You know what we need for
this office? What? It could be help with the flies is we need a Zabumafu. Yeah. That's
that's so we need to get it. I know I've said this probably a hundred times right
now, but it's still fun to me every time, like having a fly problem. You like
guys, we need to buy a venus fly trap.
We need a
hundred tiny venus fly trap. Yeah, well, just getting one and like in your
brain, it's like in a little shop of horrors and like walk around and
there's so many flies for me.
pretty good little shop of horrors plant boys his name is
fuck you Audrey - Audrey - my name is Kevin I do not sing I do actually I do make
screen printed dance dance and for a job I screen print t-shirt wait he already
dances Audrey - already dances Audrey - is a she I'm a mean green mother from
outer space and also she has children's mm-hmm oh she's a she the logic hammer
just bounced on your head okay I guess I can hit with a water hammer. Feed me poop Seymour. Feed me poop now. Feed me all your poop. Feed me poop more. Feed me poop more yeah I guess we're back here.
I mean feed me food more is something that gets stuck in my head pretty damn
often. Feed me food more. Feed me food more right? Okay I'll feed you food more. So here's the concept Kai.
Food more is anyone who gives you food. Yeah that's a food more. So whenever if
if somebody has a potential to give you food you say could you feed me please
food more? Or you could sing feed me food more and you or you say you'd say can you
pet me pet more yeah so anything that you need is that thing anymore
yeah and that's why because there's the plant needs to see it has no eyes see
more mm-hmm this is all a little too high concept for me yeah this is scary
that's okay you don't need to get it earlier when we're talking about like
imagining a vagina or a penis. It reminded me of,
there's this guy that I knew in college who was just definitely like an
aggressively closeted guy. And he was just like,
I was making a joke about Jack Black's penis. I don't remember what, why,
but like I wasn't, he was like, Oh, like how, I can't even, like,
I can't even like think about a penis.
About like the fact that we were like imagining a penis and a joke.
And he was just like, Oh, like I can't, Oh, like I can't even think about that.
That's so, Oh my God guys.
What?
It was just like such a poor cover.
And I found out like later, um, like later in the year, one of my friends who liked
to get really drunk and get smoochy, um, he'd like be like, and like, you know,
smooch when he was drunk, this guy was just like, it's interesting what you do
with your friends, like the smooching.
And he was just like, yeah, I just think it's funny.
And the dude was just like, maybe we can be friends like that.
Oh, it was such, it was a tragedy. I hope they did.
I hope they did smooch and it opened something up in his brain. I hope so.
I think he's still, I think he was very religiously raised.
Is that Flintstones sock? That is a Flintstones sock.
That's awesome. You wanted me to comment on that so bad.
I did not want you to comment on it.
You've been showing me that, that your damn sock, like a Victorian leg.
I'm gonna have my foot up because my leg. Your socks are not interesting.
No, I couldn't remember what I had on.
Wait, what's the other one then?
Is that Iron Man?
I think this is Voltron.
Why are you wearing a Flintstone and a Voltron sock?
I didn't have any other socks that weren't knee-highs.
How about you...
I'm a down-ass fool.
You're not a down-ass fool.
These are not cool-ass Mexico socks.
Flintstone socks?
No, my other socks are.
Wait, you could get a Haritos.
Jubio sent us a whole Fiesta pack.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Whoa.
A Kookaratcha.
Why are you calling him a kookaratcha? I was just saying like you're calling my friend
Dubia a kook that's a that's a that's a bug a cockroach. It's a dance. Do you guys not know anything about culture?
You're saying he's not a cockroach. It's not a dance. It's a car horn or a bug. Yeah, is is it a car horn?
Yeah car horn
In this city. Yep
And that's a cool car horn to have and it's okay like that you can have that car horn
Yeah, it's okay. You guys want me to change all your text tones to that? Yeah
And these shoes are these shoes have like a thing that like pokes my feet when I walk I know
Do you guys remember?
Fairly odd parents where where the green man the green fairy becomes
Mexico green mix and he's saying his name is greenie. He sings el cucaracha el cucaracha enchilada blah blah blah
(laughter)
- That's kinda awesome.
- That is really funny.
- That's so, dude, Butch Hartman,
devout Catholic.
Did you know that about him?
He's the creator.
- I thought you were gonna say something funny.
- I thought he was gonna be a wizard.
- Him believing in magical fairies
that makes everything happen in the world?
- Yeah.
- I'd say it sounds like a bit of a religious nut.
- He's also--
- I hate that God shit.
- He's, I heard from somebody,
he's a real big piece of shit and he stole all the character designs from
fairly odd parents from fairies from Denzel
from his friend Denzel yeah and that's why he's in the show like that yeah that
makes sense yeah yeah I got is not Butch Hartman it sounds like the name of a
death-stranding character yeah Butch Hartman does have a really cool name for
somebody that's like that lame he he draws like that's a cool name butch
Hartman yeah Hartman that's a sick name that's an action figure name yeah that's
a rescue it's like Max Steel that's not cuz a dog's name yeah that's that's not a
clue name Hartman is you know it's a cool name Voldemort's
what's a cool name Phil Hartman yeah how do they come up with those names for
movies in television. Emmett Brown. J.K. Rowling. That's a cool ass name. Say what you will about
that old bitch. That's a cool name. That's definitely a cool name. Fulgencio Batista.
Don't know who that is. Chuck Testa. Cool ass name. How'd they come up with that one?
Success Kid. Chuck Norris. Chuck Norris, cool ass name. Masumoto. Masumoto? That's a cool
on it. Okay, that Bowser there is that guy, the monitor.
That's
I need to I think I might legally change my name to Evan Pevens. Oh,
dude. I do not change your name to Edmund Pevens.
What can sorted by Turkish delayed all the time. If you change the other day,
I was just like I was I woke up real early. I was walking Phil and I just
I was like I wanted to listen to something and I so I just put on this
podcast. It's like so it was called like the oral history of the office and it
was I listen over like five minutes and it's hosted by the guy who plays Kevin
and he's like hi. I played Kevin Malone on the office and you might be saying
yeah, you don't really sound like Kevin and yeah, sometimes it seemed like my
character didn't have much going on up there
and you about him.
Realize that he played a disabled guy on TV.
It's making me laugh so hard.
It is.
It's so funny that that people like like people figured out how
to cash in on that of like, oh, I played like a minor character
in a TV show.
I can I can every fucking like person who's on the office
except Steve Carell has some podcast.
Yeah, like the office thinking hour.
Isn't there a Sopranos one like that?
side smile. The side smile. Jim did like the ultimate like he went the Harrison Ford route.
He was genius because he made awful movies and yeah.
Rainn Wilson also did some stuff. Rainn Wilson is like a he's like Baha'i. He's Baha'i and he
made some like. He's behind you right now. What is Baha'i? I don't know. It's like the
fourth Abrahamic religion. Oh what? Yeah. It's like very small though. That's strange. Yeah.
It's very strange.
Yeah, he made some shit called like Soul Pancake.
And then he was like, "We're going to make content that's really good all the time."
Did you watch that superhero movie that was kind of like...
Oh yeah, Super?
Yeah.
I really liked that when I was a kid.
I don't know if it holds up.
That's the one where Rainn Wilson gets raped.
Yeah, and also Elliot Page gets like...
Elliot Page is the one who rapes him.
Gets like shot in the fucking head.
Really?
Yeah.
I don't remember Elliot Page raping him.
the movie he also his brain gets touched by God whoa yeah yeah I think so it's
kind of what was the Nick the one with Nick Cage and that little girl gas yeah
it was the really weird father-daughter relationship that was weird I just
watched kick-ass - and the guy who plays like the mother plays kick-ass he's like
Oh Aaron Taylor Johnson he's like oh so he from the first one to the second one
he's he has aged like 20 years and he's fucking shredded yeah and they're still
like he's 16 years old. Dude, Aaron Taylor Johnson yeah cuz he was filming like
does he married to like a 90 year old? He's married so he was playing John Lennon on a
John Lennon on a movie when he was like 19 something like that and then the
director like divorced her husband to be with him and they have like six kids now
that's so awesome. I think the number of kids is way smaller but being in an
indie movie more like he's living an indie movie.
That's right.
I'm saying he's living in Nicky and Nora's Infinite playlist.
Oh, yeah, and that playlist is making damn kids with an old
woman.
Did you guys see that movie about a box?
It's like I built a fort or something.
No, okay.
So I called like I built a fort out of boxes.
No, it's like some some movie.
That's very twee.
Never mind.
I'm I those movies all suck.
Yeah, dude.
It sucked.
It was like Zooey Deschanel.
Mumble opened her mouth and went.
I just created a movie.
It was, I mean, she's not even involved, but it was,
but it is her fault.
Dude, that era, like 2009 to 2013,
where every like, like the 500 days of summer era of like media,
500 days of hell. Yeah. More like it. That shit was fucking like the,
the tweet bullshit or Mumford and sons shit.
I hate Mumford and sons so much. I hate that band.
Oh my god, did he just say that?
Oh my god, holy shit!
He doesn't even fucking like Mumford and Sons!
What?!
I hate that shit.
Really?
Do you remember that, though?
How do you feel about Iron and Wine?
There's people wearing like suspenders and shit all the time.
I'm not acknowledging this.
Wait, wait, you hate a band that won multiple Grammys?
[laughter]
How is that supposed to make any sense?
But their songs were on the radio constantly!
Yeah, what the hell are you even talking about, basically?
about basically. Okay at least do you at least like Little Lion Man. Please tell me you like
Shovels and Rope. What is Shovels and Rope? Is that a real song they made? No it's another another band
like that. We could make up names like that really easily. That's just all the bands were something
ampersand another thing. Yeah dude that oh fuck I hated that era. Anchor and Wood. Wagon Raven.
Wagon Raven.
It sounds like it could actually be a black metal thing. Yeah. Okay. Is ho
hay the lumineer song? Hey, what I say to you when I see you?
I heard that.
Wait guys, guys, hold on. Cam say that. Hey, is what I say when I see you
saying on the damn street corner. Oh my God. That's fucking fine.
Lumineer.
I'd like to hit you with shovels and tie you up with rope.
Yeah.
Okay.
Craft beer is bad too.
And I'm going to hit your mom with a Ford and her sons.
We're hitting on hipsters.
Yeah, IPA liquid.
That's exactly the same as this.
Yeah, I did realize now.
Huh?
Oh, what?
I said I realized now that, yeah, I'm just saying like, oh, I hate hipsters.
I'm saying I hate hipsters in a roundabout way.
Man bun?
More like, man, I'd have fun chopping that thing off with scissors.
still a bar around here that gives you a free drink if you chop your man bun off
yeah there is booby trap Lee sigh well I mean that place is so stupid yeah yeah
I love it it's great but it's dumb it's just so
funny to see someone who has a mustache on the side of their index my cousin has
really yeah she has that she yeah she has that she has a and then she has the
word Elvis tattooed on her arm. It'd be so funny to just get like a square tattoo.
Each finger you have a different mustache like it's a Swiss Army knife
and they're like oh what's that one like on your ring finger? I'm like don't worry about it
don't worry about it. That's for special friends. It was a long time ago I was
young okay when I got these tattoos. I was supposed to it had a fast forward
rewind pause and play this is supposed to be the stop button and then I had I
didn't like that idea so I changed all of them to mustaches and figured hey why
not just keep that one in the back pocket it would be funny if you just color the
entire side of your fingers like Steve Harvey
yeah you get frostbite on one finger yeah cool hey you guys ever noticed how
- You know how the pause sign looks like an 11?
Yeah, 'cause I have to pause every damn movie
11 times to go pee.
- Yep. - Oh.
- Yep. - That's a classic take.
- They gotta make movies easier to pee in.
(laughing)
- You ever notice a record button
looks like a dinner plate?
Yeah, 'cause I record it.
I go to dinner. - 'Cause I record my dinner.
- And I record myself eating.
- Or record me screaming at my family during dinner.
- Do you ever notice that the play button
looks like an arrow because it's pointing
where I want to go play.
(laughing)
- My living room, I guess, is pointing that way.
I'll go play over there.
(laughing)
- That's a good point.
- That's a really good point.
- What if things are on a remote?
Hold on.
(laughing)
- You ever notice that the power button
looks like Pac-Man smoking a joint?
- No, but that's a really good point.
Because that's power.
- Yeah.
- No, it doesn't.
- It does.
- Yeah, it does.
- A joint?
- Yeah.
- How does it look?
What the hell are you talking about?
- Look closer.
Look closer on it. Look closer at it.
Did you ever notice that Paw Patrol the movie looks like an incredible film?
Ow! What the hell?
Yeah, I did notice that.
I just got hit in the head.
I think I've watched, yeah, I've seen Paw Patrol the movie.
Yeah, I've seen Paw Patrol the movie.
You know, that era of like Paw Patrol the movie and like PJ Masks, I fucking hate.
I just like, hate.
I actually like that era.
That era of like...
Dude, that era of like, weird Al and Perry Grip.
Oh my god.
The era of like, like autotune and like T-Pain and A-Side.
Don't get me started on the news and do a bad lip read.
Oh my god, dude, I fucking hate that shit.
You know what era I really didn't like?
What?
September 11th, 2001.
That was a very short era.
That was a very short, it was a bad era.
One day.
Yeah.
That was a bad era.
Not fun to be in kindergarten.
Yeah.
Getting told what to do.
I got, I got take, my mom took me out of school because she was worried that New Hampshire
was going to get attacked.
Yeah, I mean, same.
my mom thought that Minnesota was gonna get attacked.
- Yeah.
- And it did.
- Yeah, no.
- Mm-hmm.
- Wait, you don't remember that?
- Sorry.
- Minnesota was attacked.
- Why do you think it's called the Twin Cities?
- Yep.
- Oh, fuck.
- Twin Cities, Twin Towers, City, New York City.
- That's where the New York City towers should have been.
- Yep, think about it.
- The Twin Towers should have been in the Twin Cities.
- Minnesota, what's on a plane?
Many sodas.
- Oh my God, that's true.
- Fresca, Diet Coke, every option.
it's usually complimentary on certain airlines.
- The Mississippi River runs right through it
and what do terrorists do to stay hydrated?
They take a little sippy--
- And they never miss it.
- And they don't miss it.
- And Mississippi did die on the plane.
- They take a sippy from their Mrs. Pepper.
- And what else is pepper?
Dr. Pepper, back to the sodas.
- Yep, and you know what else they put pepper on?
Schwarma.
- And do you know how many letters are in Schwarma?
2023 which is a prediction for that's next year. Twin Towers 2, the fall.
Why didn't they put the Twin Towers in Minneapolis? Why didn't they put them in the Twin Cities?
It would have made way more sense.
It would have made way more sense and it would have been harder to attack.
Nobody ever would have fucking touched them.
And also less people would have died.
Yeah.
Yeah, because there's less people.
I heard that.
It'd be like an abandoned mall by then.
I heard the true motive for 9/11 was they were trying to knock down the Twin Towers because
was there mad that New York copied Middle Earth? That's right. I heard the
same thing. I heard they had the two towers and- Where they're from. Middle
Earth. Yeah, exactly.
They're not orcs, okay? If anything, they're elves, but they're not orcs or
dwarves. You guys see Bright? Bright? The Max Landis movie? Oh, I remember that.
It's the orc movie. Dude, I watched it really high, like a year ago. It's
incredible to watch. Really? Like, there's just like orcs and durags, like...
Yeah. It's like an... Actually, I think I've seen the first 20 minutes of it.
insane. Nextlane just said like like tweeted something I just finished my
screenplay that yeah may very well be my if it's done right this could be my
Star Wars yeah no thinking that that's your magnet yeah it's like yeah it's
like an all lives matter movie with Will Smith it's insane I remembered him
recently cuz somebody posted a screenshot of his Instagram story that
was it said like Chris D'Elia speaking truth oh yeah like it's so funny to you
like your dad is a child murderer and you're like I guess I'll be a mega
a rapist. I have to live with my father. I'll never be my damn dad. Yeah, yeah,
do John Landis like if you he had he like threw a party when he got a
yard for the murder of any major children. He forced Michael Jackson to
endorse the occult by making thriller. Yeah, he also threw a kid out of them
airplane or something. I don't remember the story. Yeah, two Children were
murdered by a magic helicopter. I mean, yeah, I guess it in the grand scheme of
things if you're gonna kill like kids helicopters cool way also like if
you're gonna kill kids if you're gonna kill kids they better be like child
actors also yeah like non-union go bigger go out like an annoying kid same same
difference they're having a tantrum in the Walgreens you guys bet I'm gonna
take them out back is having a tantrum in Kmart and you pull like a walkie-talkie
out and you just like crash it here. When I see a kid I see a tango. I see a bogey.
Yeah John Landis was like okay for this scene like okay the kids like for this
scene I'm gonna need to stand on this target right here. Didn't he leave this shot?
This is your mark. This bullseye. He left the shot in the movie I think. Really? I think that
shot is in the Twilight Zone. Yeah I love that. So a kid was doing well.
yeah kids you have to you're supposed to stand on the H, because that sense for
here
the H in the circle. That's your and stretch your necks up really tall, so
you can see
and here where this poncho
yeah dude. I had a I was walking fill the other day and we walked by this
lady. It's like older lady. She's dressed all in white and she and fill
fill. Angel made maybe was an angel, but she was actually she acted like the
devil okay they'll walk on a drill and she said oh she said hello puppy hello
puppy and then and then like like we didn't get down just like kind of put
her hands together and look hello puppy and then looked me said I don't much
care for dogs yeah she walked into a door that was on my brain and I don't
I don't care much for dogs.
- I was Catherine Hepburn.
- It really freaked me out.
I was like, are you a celebrity?
Yeah, like I honestly was like,
is she like an old movie star or something?
Why is she acting like this?
- Yeah, you can't just talk like that.
- Why is she like wearing all white
in like the middle of like Ridgewood?
Like it's just weird, dude.
- I think there's just probably a lot of weirdy freakies
crawling around New York City.
- That's true, man.
- Keep New York weird is what I say.
- Yeah, absolutely.
- I saw my first acidic people.
- Nice.
- Congratulate me on that.
- How was that?
- I thought it was hilarious.
It's the funniest thing ever. They're so funny.
They're really funny. I'm Jewish, by the way, but...
I'm not. They are funny.
Those guys are...
They look funny.
They have antennas.
They actually do.
They have antennas and they speak...
We're not going to say feelers. Antennas.
No, but... And they have their own rules and funny hats. I was like, "This is awesome."
I loved it so much.
It's always... I do... It's a little bit embarrassing how many times I've told people
when it's their first time in New York, you have to go to South Williamsburg.
Yeah.
You have to just walk around.
I'm just like...
It's crazy.
The place I'm staying, Tommy's place is right over there, and it's awesome because I'll just
go to get a sandwich, and then I'll see a guy walking around.
Yeah.
I'm like, "Oh."
And they have the bars on all the windows.
Yeah.
I remember when I first moved here, I was telling Kyba, I took the bus somewhere, and I went
through that part of Williamsburg or whatever, and I felt like I was in the Jeep from Jurassic
Park.
I felt like I was like in the alien hub world where all the species intermingle because I just like
seeing these guys like he like when I was driving to the apartment in my in an uber
a city guy just stopped in the middle of the road and got out of his car and calmly walked into the
store and like did something for like three minutes while people were just like blaring their
horns and then he walked back out to get into his car and he didn't like even ignore like he wasn't
like, "Oh, sorry." He just like, "Boop, boop, boop."
Yeah, dude. They have the biggest Toyota minivans.
The biggest what?
The biggest Toyota minivans.
The biggest toy?
They have the biggest toys, and they're keeping them from us.
Why?
Interesting.
They have these big minivans, and they'll fucking park them on the sidewalk, sideways.
That's insane to me.
Dude, it's like-
I don't know how they get their cars where they do.
Yeah.
The car would be like teetering on like a light post.
It's like half on the curb.
Half on the curb, upside down, and they just get out and walk out.
I was buying like...
Like they have some kind of magical powers or something.
I don't know.
They're hiding from the rest of the world.
I was buying an SD card reader for my PC when I first moved here.
And I went to the...
I was like, "Oh, there's like an electronic store in Williamsburg.
I'll just walk there. It's pretty close."
And...
first of all, it wasn't close. I didn't know, I still didn't know the area. I walked like 30 minutes to this like
That's close.
photography store in the middle.
Lazy.
Literally in the like the the middle of this like neighborhood and I walked in and it was like
It was in the middle of the neighborhood?
Middle of like South Williamsburg like like the like where like every
Why are you making a claw with your hands?
and stuff.
Why are you doing like Dracula teeth with your fingers?
making like a shape with your hand like you're doing like a hook nose.
Well I paid way more for that yesterday.
Another funny place that I visited on my trip that made this place feel like a hub world
is I went to Chinatown and that was very funny as well.
Ease up there.
Listen, the Hasid's are all fair game.
Once we get to Chinatown, you gotta take the slow train to Chinatown.
I love Chinatown.
It's so awesome.
The one in Flushing is my favorite.
That one's cooler.
one I like the one in Flushing I've been like through there briefly I think
that's the biggest one in the US and it's like can we go dude I would love
it's like it's like its own little city I want to buy like little knives and
cool like just like weird little cool strength you can buy you can buy you can
buy stuff there you can buy like the organs of a fish that doesn't exist yeah
vegetable yeah I was looking at spices that just looked like caterpillars yeah
It was so cool. Also, it was it was like pretty I liked it. Yeah, sounds cool
Canals, I love the there's a jeweler on Canal Street
Who has like pictures of like her with all these rappers and there's this one big like on her storefront
big photo her and
Macklemore and it's a picture of her and Macklemore and him like pointing to her and it just says my second mom, you know
(laughter)
- It's so awesome.
- That's so fucking cool.
- All the tourist trap shops in Chinatown
have the perfect mix of items,
where it's like half shirts that say
"Motherfucking Fortnite in New York City"
and then it's half mahjong sets.
- Yeah, mahjong sets.
- Every store should be like that.
- The perfect Goku Supreme.
- I love the Chinatown shirts.
- My fucking child died in New York.
- Yeah.
- It's awesome.
I saw in multiple of those stores. I saw like the hats that have like braids attached
Like a cartoon baby Groot wearing like a headband and like holding a joint and I was like this is this is so
They have shit like the fucking like Goku like for Fortnite with the like for tonight guy
We're like the supreme bogo like on a shirt and like go like Vegeta smoking weed and shit
Yeah, so but dad and then like and then I read it alien like an auspicious tiger. Yeah
Yeah, the reason that I think it's so awesome is like they're just like vaguely picking up on like this is what people like yeah
Yeah, they're just not paying attention to licensing and throwing everything that's someone who's 15 might like on yeah, and they're right
It's awesome. Yeah. Oh, you sure it's like that. Oh, man. I mean like Goku backwards t-shirts
Yeah, I feel like most of this most of the the shirts in that's in those stores
I see people buying them, but I never see people wearing them.
Yeah.
I think they're a gag gift.
If you hang out at Maria Hernandez long enough, you see like sexy Goku Supreme shirts.
Yeah.
Last time I was at one of those stores, I bought Cameron a lucky coin.
I do.
It might be in my wallet.
Tell me.
That's a nice--
I want to check.
I think it's probably been-- it's been about a month.
I'd like to check in.
Cameron's gotten taller.
It's been a month and a half, actually.
That's true.
Do you feel more lucky?
Have you been-- have you had a lucky month and a half?
I've had-- I would say I've had a lucky streak.
- Well honestly, I think I've had a pretty unlucky month
and a half since I gave you that coin.
- Cameron, you should give that coin back.
- No, I think I just have to get my own.
But then like--
- No, I'll get you one for your birthday.
- I feel like that's, I feel like I have to be gifted one
'cause I gifted him the coin.
- Yeah, I'll gift you one, don't worry.
- We have to like gift, each of us has to gift a coin
to each other.
- Mm-hmm, I think it's on my desk at home.
- I wanna get a lucky coin really bad now.
That sounds like a great--
- It's a really cool coin.
- I had a lucky coin in high school.
it was like one of the pure silver quarters.
- When Caleb-- - It was like a 1963 quarter.
- It's gotta be Chinese for it to be lucky.
- Yeah, only Chinese stuff is lucky.
- Yeah, I also drilled a hole in it
and tried to put it on an necklace.
- When I handed you what?
- When Caleb handed me the lucky coin,
he was holding, he got takeout food,
and the second he handed me the lucky coin,
the bag ripped and all his food fell on the ground.
- Oh yeah, yeah, that did happen.
- The second that it left his hand.
- It was literally the second I handed the lucky coin.
And I remember you were telling me,
you were like, it was the perfect moment
'cause I forgot that I had it in my pocket,
and then you were like, "Oh man, I'm real stressed out this week," and I was like, "I have a
literal solution right now. I have a solution," and then I gave you the coin immediately.
I felt terrible.
Yeah, and a kid laughed at you, too.
Yeah, dude.
You got a hangover without drinking?
Dude, it was awful. It was so fucked, my lips started swelling up.
It was like a started cracking.
It was bizarre, dude.
You started flaking away.
I can't eat chocolate anymore. It was really, really bad.
We're going to get you a coin.
You guys wanted a shot down today.
You guys want to go to Chinatown today?
You guys busy after the...
You guys want to go to Chinatown?
Maybe.
We have to do a lot of fucking bullshit.
Well, I might just go to Chinatown again
and buy myself some little trinkets.
Can you get me a lucky coin?
If I go there, yeah.
Can you get me a dragon flavored lollipop?
Dragon flavored lollipop?
I'm going to buy you the most cursed item in all of Chinatown.
I think we need a...
I think for the office we need a...
like a dragon incense holder okay let's get a lot of cool shit yeah you should
also let's get away these curtains yeah oh we should have done that oh I mean I
guess we're still time or shower curtains well these ones were supposed
to be sound dampening but they're just actually gray you could paint on them
yeah I think that this whole office should be China themed yeah I'm really
down can we cannot does that mean I can get rid of the Naruto poster? No, no, that
stuff all stays. All right, yeah. That's your that's your flair. My flair? That's
your flair. And look I drew Caleb up here too. Can I put something at your desk Pat? No, no,
don't even think about that. All right. Is this all revenge because I wrapped up
because I put a piece of plastic on your desk? Oh that was a good prank. And put a post-it
note that said prank? When? You don't remember that? We put plastic all over
everything on your desk. I put a there was a piece of plastic. And then we were like oh I
I don't know if he'll be able to tell you that's a pretty good not we didn't want
you to think it was like an accident or a prize so we're gonna pray I put a post
it knows on it what do you mean it was covered your computer monitor and
everything and it was plastic and it said it was a post-it note that said
prank on it I don't remember I don't think this happened I you think
absolutely happened I did have yeah I remember I'm we there then the post-it
note that said prank would still be over here no no it was on the place like a
a month ago. I sat on the plastic yeah. You don't remember this. No, I don't
think this happened. It's such a good prank. It was such a good prank that it
wiped his memory. He's such a fucking good prank. I think I'm going to do more.
I mean, I guess what probably happened is that you walked in and you saw a
giant sheet of plastic covering everything your desk. You're like, Oh,
guess I left this here last night and then that is probably what he thought he
didn't even see it was a prank and it didn't process it idea that you could do
you want yeah you could like reach around in his computer and kind of mess up some
of the stuff in there I just like fucking use like my keys
a really good prank but again I'd need to put a post-it note that says that's my
I'm fine with ranks but just at least leave a note yeah you know like a car
accident like just leave a note if you if you prank somebody mm-hmm prank
you had a prank prank didn't even happen prank didn't work it did work did
work obviously because you forgot it that's the point of a prank it's
supposed to blend in it's supposed to be so innocuous that's why you need the
post-it note to say I'm pranking you right now yeah yeah cuz otherwise you
would never even know that's how good I am at it yeah it's true I guess I pranked
you and you didn't even realize it god I'm fucking good I guess I'm gonna put
everything you own in jello including your penis and your balls whoa yes and
jello your penis your penis I mean don't say that I mean don't talk about your
your penis that way. I'm going to put the entire world in jello. Don't do that.
I'm serious. So many people will not eat your way out of the world.
He did it. He did it. How much jello do you guys think you could eat?
I feel like I could probably eat a bathtub full of jello.
I don't think I've eaten jello since I was like seven years old.
Jello's like cotton candy, right? Yeah. How much cotton candy can you eat?
I mean, you could, I could eat one bag and then be like, oh, but if it's like,
It's disgusting though is the thing.
If you had to eat a pound of cotton candy to save your family.
That's a lot of, I mean yeah, to save my family.
I mean I'd try.
It's not an issue of like, yeah, it's not an issue of being full.
It's just like disgusting.
Which one's heavier, a pound of Jell-O or a pound of cotton candy?
I didn't ask you the question last night, Patrick.
No, Jell-O.
I didn't ask you the question.
Oh yeah.
Okay, if you're dating somebody for a really long time, right, like a really, really long
time and you're like very in love, right, this is a hypothetical that we were talking
last night and then you find out that that person is your identical twin sister
do you keep dating them no no no we us three all said yes we all were like yes you would keep
you're in love yeah if you're in love yeah it's like whatever it just makes our bond even fucking
cooler you could pilot a pacific rim mac because yeah exactly also now that you know that your
twins you're gonna start like saying shit at the same time dressing the same that's the problem
that starts the relationship is like, "Oh my god, we finish each other's
sentences." We dress exactly the same. We are telepathically connected and we
grew up together in the same house. Identical twins though. It has to be
identical twin sisters and a brother. Okay, new thing. You're
triplets. Which one would you date? Not only do you have your
your beautiful wife. Now she's got a damn twin sister. Oh, it's kind of and and
she's coming for Thanksgiving.
She's coming well your your brother. I would totally right. I mean you're in the
same house. Yeah, she's coming for Thanksgiving. Okay, it's quadruplets
actually. Okay, yeah, it's quadruplets and there's three hot sisters. Would you
okay? Here's a question. I would hate I would you let three girls suck your
penis. No, I would hate if it was quadruplets and it was two boys and two
girls and it's like okay this is all set up perfect I'm being one of the boys is
gay and it screws everything up but then you see you've just it doesn't matter
it's all twins yeah if three girls tried to I would get too nervous okay would
you rather your girlfriend or your twin sister probably my girlfriend okay
interesting well what if they were the same but yeah see how is my twin sister
like Boston Boston like me and her name's Helga her name is Helga but she
hiding? No, she looks like Amanda Bynes. Okay. Amanda Bynes, 2014. Amanda Bynes, 2005.
Amanda Bynes, she's the man. So I'd have to say no because she was like 16 in that movie.
I don't think so. Probably not. I think probably my girlfriend. Interesting. If I found out my
girlfriend was my sister, it wouldn't change anything. But you know, if given the choice
to date my sister or my girlfriend I'd go girlfriend every time. Every time? Maybe one time out of a hundred.
Just to see what up. If you found out your girlfriend was, what if your girlfriend was like, like oh yeah just
found out I'm Hitler. If you found out that your girlfriend was Hitler? Yeah. I mean that's even
less of a question. I mean like. You would have sex with her still? Yeah. She's Hitler in a wig.
Yeah. But what do you mean she's a hundred and twenty years old? She's obviously hasn't done anything Hitler-y
when I've been alive. People change. Girl, that's the old you. I don't care about the old you,
I care about the new you, girl. Okay, what if you find out your girlfriend,
Jeffrey Dahmer. We've all done things and you stayed the same and my heart didn't change.
That's really true and like a poem. What's a life with no fun? That's what I would say to her.
Okay, all right. When does this come out? Where can people find your art and look at your art
and buy your art. Oh, go to my Twitter page, which is Kai Klops, but the O is a zero because
I got banished. But it's got you. Yeah, I hated it. But it's K A I K L zero P s on Twitter
and it's Kai Klops normal spelling on Instagram. Uh huh. And then also another plug is for
monster crazy. That's right. Do you? Yeah. It's a podcast that me and Kai do about monsters
that you'll like if you like monsters. We just did one on Pacific Rim that's really
really good. Well by now we just did one on God knows what.
Oh, okay. And tour starts next week when this comes out so
buy your tickets. We're recording this backlog so I don't know if there's been any updates.
There's a second LA show, there's a second Chicago show, there's a San Francisco show,
and there's a show on Mars too that you should buy tickets to. So please buy tickets for
that because it's going to be so much fun and we want to see you.
live long and prosper. Bye everybody! Thanks for having me, bye.