come back and make a mess
and we see a black
the
that was a horrible start yet it is like a room in the episode
it was a little while now
that was like a fucking terror you are going to commutes is dropping dead
not bad i hope their ears you hope you kill people
yeah no you don't that's demented yeah whoa you really had that in your pocket
for this i did have this in my pocket the fake gun that we've that we've all seen
i should get a new fake gun that you pulled out one that looked a little bit different i would
have been a little worried yeah yeah if it had like some silver on it there is i mean it's like
the paint's chipping because we use it so much that gun is a really good like tell for when like
a new person comes over to the apartment to see if they're like weird or not
because if they like pick it up and like instantly start playing with it it's
like oh yeah you're maybe kind of weird. I feel like it's the opposite.
I feel like it's completely normal. Yeah no I feel like it's that's a yeah if this is a boy girl
test. If someone picks it up they're a boy. If they're scared of it they're a
girl. This apartment is kind of a boy's paradise. It truly is. A boy's fantasy land.
We have my roommate you guys live in the apartment from a shitty version of the apartment from big. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah
Just stop the play with everywhere
You really need to say that but thank you, bro
Appreciate it man. Yeah, you get bunk beds. That would be so sweet
I got hope there any sleep in one triple bunk bed and the other rooms are just play with that in the new apartment
Yeah, the new ceiling the new apartment located at
that. You can cut that out. Great. No. Delete. Delete the file. Did you guys ever, was it
always going to be like this in here? Or at any point were you guys like, we're going
to have a real apartment and then it just kind of happened? It just kind of happened
like this. Oh really? I think at the new place we're probably gonna try.
Oh really? No. No it's gonna be like this but just like bigger. I kind of like it.
I think it's cool. The other day I was like standing by the fridge and I was
looking around like wow this looks awesome. You had that thought? Yeah.
You were so proud of the fridge. I was standing by the fridge and I like stood back and did
like the you know like the point five yeah of the whole apartment.
I don't even think this place is nice.
I always think this is...
Every like two square feet of this apartment is like a different kind of hoarder's apartment.
Yeah.
Like there's like the food hoarder is over there.
Well this is to me the most egregious thing which is that next to all of your food you
have your shoes.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, it's like basically one shelf that is like cereal into like shoes that you wear
And then it's also cleaning supplies. We should just pay like one woman $50 to come in and fix this you think is a
This is a job this is a contract amazing because it's such a small space but it really is just like
Crazy it's fine. You're excited when you do bursting with life for like what you're not excited to move
You guys are gonna find so are you guys getting a truck?
We're gonna rent a you we're all gonna go in on a u-haul. I think with yeah, Joe
I'm scared of any of you driving a u-haul. I don't know how to drive. I think Joe's gonna drive
He likes driving so hold the mic closer to you. Yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah kiss the mic and call it Caleb mm-hmm
Stop looking at me. I'm uncomfortable.
Oh yeah, because we have Alex on because he's going to be at the live show on March 31st.
I don't think that's why he's on.
That's why he's on?
I think he's on because he's in the apartment.
Because I was just standing here.
Yeah.
Because the other option was he was going to cook a pizza while we did the episode.
Wait, speaking of which, I'm gonna go see if the oven is ready.
It's not. It's gonna beep if it's ready. You know that it does that.
You guys have an automatic beeper? The oven beeps. Oh, I need a beeper, bad.
You don't have a beeper pre-heaper? I don't have a pre-heaper beeper, no.
No, you have like an old-ass oven. My oven, I just got replaced and it still sucks ass.
Yeah, dude, are you kidding? Your place had gas in it.
Yeah, it did. They're not gonna put like a...
like and they're gonna put like a fancy all my all my neighbors have also had
gas leaks. It's kind of a chronic that's in my apartment old old ovens like the
one that in your apartment. They always freak me out like that to me like I look
at it. That's just like a Mad Max contraption like the one where you have
to read like the pilot light with the like his oven at like holes in it all
over it true. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's
it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's
like steampunk thing like I don't I don't trust those it look like it ran on no
like I fucked up like old oven do you know you know exactly yeah yeah like one
on disenchantment season three on Netflix one time I got up to season three on
yeah I'm on the podcast to support is to plug disenchantment I worked on that
show really would you do story like script supervisor I voiced on max
I don't do the voice of Max that the audience knows. Max is the uh he's on disenchantment.
Do the voice. I don't want to give any spoilers. Okay then say something say I'm making a pizza
in his voice. I'm making a pizza oh Matt and Max is a lot of like uh whoa. He does
he says
from the episode. Why do you think that he edits any of this?
There's no editing in this. He's sitting the closest to the equipment. That is true.
Yeah. I mean, the only one with headphones on. I export it, but I don't, I don't,
I don't edit it. I don't listen to it or anything.
Look at him just having like a horrible time realizing that.
Really? Everybody's going to think I'm mad. You've been on the show before.
You were on like a month ago, but I thought you guys like cut around stuff.
No.
Okay.
How was the, I hear Malibu's Most Wanted was a great rewatch.
Unbelievable. I've never seen it before. Have you seen Malibu's Most Wanted?
It's so good.
Have you seen Malibu's?
You seen the boo?
No, what's it about?
It's about a vanilla gorilla who's just fucking out there in Malibu doing his thing.
White Kong. It's Jamie Kennedy and he thinks he's a black guy and his dad is a rich...
He's running for governor and he's gonna tarnish his dad's image.
And so...
Exactly the plot of Black Sheep.
Yeah.
So they should have just called it Blacker Sheep.
It's good. And then he hires... Taye Diggs and Anthony Anderson are actors and he hires
them to pretend to be gangsters like kidnap Jamie Kennedy and like take him to
the hood and scare the black out of him yeah and it's great it's really funny
really good they get mixed up with some actual way with some real fuck tech
actually yeah Snoop Dogg voices a mouse yeah plays a rizz at it's it's that like
it's that perfect like like era of American comedy where every single movie
had to have an animal that spoke English. Yeah. Where it didn't matter what movie it was.
We were saying that afterwards where it's like just like early 2000s like comedies,
like studio comedies, just like big broad comedies like that are just always great.
Like I don't like they're like that holds up way better than any fucking comedy that came out in
2018. That shit's better than Juno. Yeah. By a lot. And I and we don't say that lightly. Yeah.
And I'm the biggest Juno fan in the world. I love Juno.
Juno's some funny fucking shit.
You like Juno? Try living it, bro.
Try some funny ass bullshit.
Yeah.
Really?
Try living it.
I can see you Michael Cera-ing a teenager.
Yeah.
Thanks.
He's doing it right now.
Yeah.
What'd you say, Pat?
His girlfriend is 15.
Oh yeah, I heard that.
Yeah.
No.
What, Pat?
What did I say? I don't remember. You seemed like you were going to ask me an important question.
I don't remember. Okay. Did you guys see the prequel to Juno, Mayo?
Mayo? Get it? Like May and June, but it also sounds like mayo, like the food.
Good. Pretty good, right? Yeah, and did you see the one for that? April-O?
No. Don't even get me.
Yeah, but you got to watch March-O to get April-O. Yeah.
And February-O.
and January. Oh, it's like a Greek guy's name. Yeah. February. Oh,
maybe we'll add a little bit.
I am February. Okay. Geeklobblist.
And I am going, I am going to sell you a prequel.
Did you guys see the prequel to January? Oh, December. Oh, the year before. Oh,
it's different from December. Oh, which is the 12th movie.
That one has Santa in it. Yeah.
Santa delivers a baby. Santa's pregnant. That's why he's so fat.
The whole movie is a teenager slowly sees like a stork way off in the distance and it gets closer
and closer. Yeah, and Jason Bateman's the father. Yeah. Is he the dad in that movie? No, he's the,
he wants to adopt him. Yeah. Jennifer Garner want to adopt. Michael Cera's the baby daddy.
And then Jason Bateman is. They should have called that movie Baby Daddy instead. They
should have. Jason Bateman is the one. Isn't that already a movie? Jason Bateman's,
He's finna adopt a baby.
But then he like falls in love with Elliot Page and like...
'Cause he like whispers that's in the scene.
I've never seen Dune-O.
Really?
That's good.
There's music playing in it.
Yeah.
I do remember they had that...
One of the great mysteries of cinema.
They had that guitar scene and everyone loved the soundtrack.
Oh yeah, the soundtrack was that like folky...
Fuck those soundtrack movies.
What was that other one?
Nick and Nora's Infinite Playlist?
Both Michael Cera movies.
Dumbest fucking movie in the world, dude.
I think it's his fault.
It probably is his fault.
Trying to make him- He's a musical guy.
Trying to make him some damn indie.
Yeah, he plays the bass.
And Scott Pilgrim.
Fuck him.
I'm going to fillet him like a salmon.
No, he plays the bass in real life.
He was really good in 8 Mile though.
He was great.
That's a good soundtrack movie.
I guess that one is a good soundtrack movie.
8 Mile is so good, dude.
It's one of my dad's favorite movies.
I watch it really often.
I watch movies.
Really?
Yeah.
I watch it every other year.
I've never seen that.
Every other year?
Yeah, I watch it every other year.
My dad, you can do keep track.
I watch, I watch, I watch, well yeah, one year I watch 8 Mile, the other year I watch
Remember the Titans, and I just do that.
That's a good movie.
Every other year, dude.
Remember the Titans?
Yeah, I remember, I had to watch, in high school I took like a, it was like a movie class.
It was like a class that seniors could take where you're supposed to like write like reviews
for movies basically.
Yeah.
by like the lacrosse coach who only his only other job at the school was this
like class he's like an English teacher so he could just coach lacrosse and like
fish for the rest of his life yeah so sick Russ his name was rusty brand I
remember I had this I had this I had this like I played peewee football we
had this like older like black dude who was our like head coach and I remember
one time like I played for like three seasons and after our first season we
we would always, at the end of the season,
we would always have a fun movie night thing
to cap off the season.
We did Remember the Titans,
and he acted completely differently after watching that movie.
(laughing)
He had never seen it before,
and he used to just be like,
"Okay, we're gonna run these reels,"
and then he would come in
at the beginning of the next season like,
"Listen, boys, it's about courage.
"It's about honor.
"It's about respecting each other."
And then we lost, and we never won a game
entire time I played peewee football. I'd love to touch down your peewee. I'd like to see
your peewee. You don't want to see my peewee. I want to see your peewee. I want to see your
peewee in your footballs. I have seen Caleb's penis. Today is one of those days where you
wake up. Today is one of those days where you wake up and I looked at my penis when
I woke up and I said that's a baby's penis. That is the smallest penis I've ever seen.
I don't have that problem. You never wake up and look at your penis and say that's a
- You know when I wake up, it's like midday,
when I'm like, I stop into a Starbucks
'cause it's like cold out and I need to pee,
and then I go into the Starbucks bathroom
and I like look down and I'm like,
damn, I am not packing at all.
- I slept with the windows open.
- I'm packing nothing.
It's like a Q-tip down there.
- Yeah, I looked at my shit and it was pretty much all.
- Ever heard of a little thing called morning wood?
(laughing)
- That is my morning wood.
- That stinks then.
yeah you keep your morning ball of morning zing balsa wood yeah in the
summer dude I wake up with it I wake up with a heater that's as good as my penis
gets yeah is when I wake up and I fucking for me the biggest ever guess is after I
use my penis pump what so is it there's a penis pump growing is it growing your
penis I think it just pumps it it doesn't it doesn't give it like a bicycle group I
get yeah some some guy sold it to me that's not a target and you just put the
needle in the top yeah he said the label says it's a bike pump but don't worry
it's a penis pump and you have to use it in the bath I I think I would enjoy
using a penis pump yeah yeah I feel like what do you have like a thin penis no just
You look like one of those guys with a very thin penis.
What's that from?
I don't know.
That's from something.
I did not steal that.
Swear to God, you stole that.
You stole that from Nick Swartzen on the Norm MacDonald show.
No.
Nick Swartzen, one of the co-writers of Malibu's Most Wanted.
Nick Swartzen really, really good.
Yeah.
No, because that, I know what you're talking about.
It's Danny's.
No, no, no, no, no. Because that's a completely different joke. Fuck you.
No.
Yeah, because the joke is Danny DeVito looks like one of those guys with a short but fat penis.
And all I said was you look like one of those guys with a thin penis. That is not the same at all.
That's called a remix.
Exactly the same joke.
That is not the same at all. Fuck you.
You're a biter.
That's exactly the same joke.
No, that's not. Fuck both of you.
It's the same joke.
It's not the same joke.
My penis is like, it's pretty big. It's like probably like two pencils wide.
Two carpenter pencils, like the ones that are like really thin and flat.
Number two, Tychondorogas.
It's exactly the same shape as two of the carpenter pencils like side by side.
So it's like, it's a perfect box. It's like a, yeah, it looks like a shoe box for like,
like for a barbie agonal my my dad my penis is two pencils wide two colored
pencils my penis is two pencils like mechanical pencils more like two crayons
But my balls on the other hand. No, my balls are bigger than my penis.
Would you rather have, okay. Okay, all right. All right, here we go. Settle in. Okay, really long,
really like, like, nine. I got long balls playing. No, no, nine inch penis, right? No. Nine inch
penis, but it's like. That's too big. That sounds like a hash. Girls actually don't like that.
I heard. Girls hate that. Yeah. Nine inch penis, but it's like probably like as thin as this.
this this which you have to describe it out loud this part oh it's a it's a the
Spitfire they have every half inch or three-quarters of an inch in diameter
yeah yeah yeah it's but the or or like a we're like a reasonable chode what would
you consider to be a reasonable chair I think you need to put some measure okay
so like like five inches five and a half long five and a half long but like
pretty girthy. Oh definitely that one. But I mean I'm talking like... Five and a half
isn't it? That's not that bad. Like it's shaped like it's probably shaped like this this
HAL seltzer bottle. Oh that one 100% yeah. Yeah. A small like a biggest penis I've ever seen.
Five and a half. Yeah. Or an even bigger penis but like pencil thin. Definitely not the pencil thin one.
You don't want to have a pencil thin penis. You can just like break. Yeah that I would be worried that I would
would damage my also I would just be walking around and it would break in my
pants. Think about the inside of a woman's vagina. It's a triangle.
Okay, it's a trial.
It's a bunch of hexagons. Yeah, overlaid on the inside look like
I don't want to think about it. I think it's like it's like a paper lunch bag
and never done. Hold on. I'll wait hold your make to make two Spocks with your
hands right.
mm-hmm and now put them sideways and put them on the mind now look in yeah that's
what the inside of a vagina looks like it looks like the entire world I think it
looks kind of like the insert inside of a sweatshirt sleeve it feels like it - I
I do think that yeah the cavernous part of a vagina has got to be it's like the
Would you rather have a very deep vagina or a penis?
Okay this is a better...
Very deep vagina or penis?
Deep vagina.
Yeah?
Cuz I'd be a girl.
That would be cool.
Yeah.
Next question.
[laughter]
You'd fit like a spray paint can in there.
I'd be doing all kinds of pranks.
Like if I... can you guys imagine if I was the like girl of our group?
That would be so fucked up.
Dude, I would be like, pooping shit out of my vagina on your floor all the time.
I would ask you out on a date.
I would let you guys play.
I would let you guys, I'd let you guys finger me.
Just whenever you want.
Yeah.
Okay.
That'd be cool.
Yep.
I'd install myself in the wall.
I would.
I'd be, I would be at my head hitting the studs inside this wall.
And you guys could fuck my butt in my thing.
Damn.
You can just do that now.
- I need that for real.
- I'm married.
- He doesn't even have the ring on.
- Oh my God.
- Wait, no I'm not.
- How big is the ring you're gonna get?
- I'm getting a pendant ring.
- Oh, what's that?
- It's gonna be gold.
- Whoa.
- That's actually sick.
- Pure gold.
- You should get, you know what would be sick
if you got like a Super Bowl championship style ring?
(laughing)
Like it just says like embroidered Stewie's head.
- Yeah.
- But like big Super Bowl ring.
- Get Johnny Dang to do it.
That'd be sick, dude.
That would be tight.
That's your wedding ring, just like a giant fucking...
Yeah.
That'd be tight.
Well, now it's my idea and you can't take it.
That's fine.
This motherfucker.
This motherfucker was stupid as hell,
didn't get a big ass ring.
Do you pick out your ring if you're the husband,
or does the girl pick it out for you?
I don't think the ring matters at all.
The ring matters.
No.
The ring matters, for sure.
You're a materialistic.
You should get married to a guy then.
You don't know the true meaning of marriage.
I don't.
Yeah.
Well you're not doing a very good job of learning. It's about saving money on your taxes.
Yep. Yeah. That's basically the only... Oh now he's interested. It's about enslaving a woman for 50
years. That's right. Signing a contract. It's about endless toil. And making sure you get a prenup.
Not for you. It's about sharing a damn credit card. Oh yeah. Whoa. Whoa. Dennis. Mm-hmm. What up? Yep.
What up Dennis? Yep, my credit card is used more than the the fingering box at Caleb Pitts' house.
The fingering box? You really botched that like really hard. That was rough.
The fingering box.
That was like teed up.
My credit card is used more than the fingering box.
Pat just ran up to the tee ball and like threw the bat at the umpire by accident.
Did you ever play little league? Yeah, no inside the park home run for the
Reading the Marlins in third grade. Whoa, dude, that's the
They did not get any hits on the when I was on the Jett trass team sports blue jays
Nice and the laugh of tea in the laugh of farm league. We did not get any hits
I was scared of baseball when I was a kid that thing comes fast at you when I went to like a
AAA, AA, a minor league game.
Yeah, AA.
There was one right by my house and we went and I was like probably five years old.
We got really good seats. We were like really close.
And there was a girl like my age like sitting in front of me and there was like,
I'd never been to a baseball game before and there was like a foul ball and it like went up
and the girl was sitting right in front of me and I just will never forget the sound,
but it just was like, "Oh!" like right on the head, bro.
And she just started like screaming.
There's all these videos of like guys who are like really young like 19 year old
dudes like right in the NBA or the MLB who are just like NBA National Baseball
Association that it should be called that you're just hitting dingers and
there's there's like a compilation of these guys hitting home runs and being
like yeah home run cuz you don't get that many home runs in a season and then
the ball hits like an infant kid and just like immediately kills them and
And they're just like, "Oh, fuck."
And then they just continue playing the game.
What are you gonna do? Stop?
The show must go on.
Hospital.
Like some of these people get like permanent brain damage.
They're never the same.
Yeah, there was a player, John Oldrood.
He had to wear a helmet all the time when he played.
A player?
Yeah.
I'm talking about people in the stands.
Well, no, it's the same deal.
He got like hit in the head with a ball or some shit.
But he's still doing okay.
He can still play baseball.
No.
Well, why'd you say he had to wear a helmet?
everybody wears a helmet when you play baseball.
Yep, no, but not all the time. You wear baseball caps.
Yeah, like the batter, well, like even when he's on the field, like they just
wear the hats. He'd wear a helmet on the field so he
could still play, like if he was playing like first base or shit. Is it because
he just like, he just got hit all the time, like he just,
the ball was just drawn to him? The ball was magnetized to his head.
That's bad. He had a cork magnet in his head.
Yeah. And it just... There was somebody in the stands casting a spell on him.
yeah that's all rude head that would be a great that would be a great uh jackass
prank for the future they could have a remote control baseball that like flies
around and hits a little star wars ball a good jackass prank in the future would
be they have to fight a robot
i will i'm excited to see future jackass yeah they can probably come up with some
really good shit yeah flying machine trapping somebody in
virtual reality forever yeah yeah i want to do that so bad i want to trap
someone a virtual reality for the entire life. Once we get like a matrix kind of
plug in the back they're just gonna start killing each other it's gonna be
awesome. If I ever figure out how to how to found a micronation I'm
absolutely raising a child in VR where the police can't send me to jail.
Convincing them that like the headset is part of their head. Yeah that's your brother Sonic.
you can run with him Gary's mom do you think that you're gonna have the best
time I also that that my I also really want I would love to have a huge compound
to do that to like a hundred chimpanzees hmm oh you know the house now yeah I saw
that like they stole my house in VR basically just show them like the
default windows background and the cows get really we're like way happier and
they produce more spunk and milk yeah yeah that's good for animals it's good
that we do that to him I think yeah I mean it is terrifying that we're just
like putting cows in virtual reality no it's this it's this scariest shit ever
cuz maybe we're the cows shit no couldn't be maybe we're in virtual reality
yeah it doesn't make any fucking sense yeah oh cows are putting in virtual
reality cows are putting flies in so that they can eat them better.
Yeah.
Do you guys ever do that thing where you look at a thing, it's like...
Yes.
You show someone like something that's white, like I'm picking up a white face mask.
Okay.
Cameron, what color is this?
White.
What color is this?
What do cows drink?
Water.
Ah, but you almost said milk.
Oh, yeah.
The trick is when someone says milk.
Oh yeah.
Make them look like an absolute fool.
Yeah, I almost said milk.
I've done that.
Yeah, I've done that.
You've done that to me before.
Yeah, there's a few of those.
I think the thing about that though is you don't really need the set up.
You could just ask somebody what a cow drinks so they'd almost say milk most of the time,
I feel like.
What a toaster's milk.
I would say milk, like if I was in a job interview, I'd say milk.
I think cows do drink milk.
No.
Well, that's the thing.
When they're babies, yeah.
Of course they drink milk.
Every mammal drinks fucking milk.
No.
But then also they drink water later.
You guys are wrong.
Oh, I thought about this on the way over here. I want to talk about this. I've been reading about
feral people, people who are raised by wolves and shit, and there are people who have been raised by pigs.
Really?
That's so cool. Yeah, and they suck on pigs' nipples and they think they're a pig.
Wow.
Isn't that cool?
It is. It's crazy.
- You're finally opening up to us about your childhood.
- No, I wasn't raised by it.
(laughing)
Isn't that cool, and that'd be like a cool guy
you wanna hang out with?
(laughing)
I just never should bring you guys,
like introduce you to my family ever.
(laughing)
I live on a farm out in nowhere.
- Too far to go to.
- I don't know, they're really conservative.
(laughing)
It is interesting, most of, the most feral humans
have been raised by wolves though.
- That's cool.
- It's like the jungle.
really like babies I guess. Yeah well it's where it's it's it's dogs and humans the
eternal bond. Yeah yeah then they bred that out of pit bulls. Yeah pit bulls.
That's true. You never meet a person who was raised by pit bulls. I don't think it's that they bred it out of pit
bulls. I think they bred in hatred. Yeah. I think cuz like wolves will I think wolves
will raise a child. The wolves have the love in them. Yeah. But but pit bulls have
been there they've been spiritually strangled and smothered. Yeah pit bulls I do
feel like have a little bit of like alligator in them yeah look at their
heads they're kind of cold-blooded. Pipples look like a guy that just got turned into an animal
yeah yeah exactly exactly like we talked about this it looks like halfway between
like when when scrappy-doo is halfway between human and dog in the movie they do look like
that yeah they're like all muscly and what we I've been I've been seeing these things on Instagram
because I just get like dog shit on on like Instagram now where like guys will take photos
dog shit of New York. Dogs will take or people take photos of their pit bulls or
like Rottweilers that are just like ripped. They'll take photos of like how
ripped their backs are and like put them on Instagram like trying to get people
like fuck your dog. Like how hot my dog is. I think that like a
thousand years ago they like somebody showed a dog like did the like clockwork
orange thing to a dog and then that dog had a baby and that was like the start
of the pit bull lineage. Yeah. Like that was I think it's like a mental evil thing that's
followed them. Maybe a curse by a witch could have been the culprit. Also pit bulls will
switch up on you. Oh yeah. They'll be normal. Dude, so scary. I fucking, I hate, it happens
to me like every few weeks I'll be walking down the sidewalk and I'll see like a pit
bull, like somebody walking a pit bull like towards me and I'll look behind me and somebody
else will be walking a different dog like behind me coming like you know that it's
and I'm able to I'm like oh I'm about to lose my legs yeah this is it are the
soldiers and you are the battleground yeah yeah they said we're dueling at
Cameron at noon I will genuinely cross the street if I if I see - if I see a
pitbull approaching another dog with with me and that is really funny I try
to rub their bellies crossing the street when you see a pitbull I don't trust
pipples is really funny because of it could come across really bad because of
who usually come across really racist I don't know you mean no it's can you
explain what you're saying to me like no it's not you it's your fucking dog just
every day the same guys is walking it's not if I just see a people that's fine
I'm saying if it's a pincer formation, a people and another dog, okay, I will get
out of that situation. That's not okay with my what if it's a chihuahua. It
any dog. Are you kidding me? Slurp that thing up like spaghetti. Exactly. Yeah,
it's not that like the dogs are gonna fight. It's that the people is gonna eat
the other dog and it's gonna eat through my legs to eat the other dog burrow
through you. It will. It's gonna chomp a hole straight through your stomach into
the other dog. It's gonna dive through your body straight up and it's gonna
come back it's gonna do a Mortal Kombat fatality the dessert yeah I do I don't
try I don't trust you sweet he looks mmm don't don't do that if I was a dog I'd
eat your meat don't say that I was so scared of dogs when I was a kid I was
like terrified like like yeah I and I grew out of it but I guess not for
pitbulls. I think I love dogs. I like dogs a lot. I was scared of big dogs and now I'm
scared of pitbulls. That's what I would have been like when I was like probably until I
was in like probably till I was like 14. Like I like a very very there was a dog that lived
like in the my neighbor had this like really mean dog that they just like whipped or whatever
to make it evil you know and I'll go out to play and it would just be like
just like the entire time I was outside. You know how dogs do that?
I'm gonna do a pizza check because I think my pizza is probably done.
It's Alex's pizza corner. Let's see what kind of pizza is it?
Oh yeah it's done. It's a little bit of everything.
Okay if you can't hear he said it's a little bit of everything.
What does that mean?
He got a supreme pizza.
Oh, that is a little bit of everything.
I think I might like frozen pizza more than normal pizza.
Frozen pizza is really good.
I like frozen pizza more than any New York slice.
Frozen pizza is great.
When we were in Tampa, there was a bar where the only food they had was you could order
a frozen pizza and they'd just make it.
That's so sick.
There's some places around here that do that.
Really?
I've never seen that before.
the bell house does that best it's so tight dude it literally saved my life oh
fuck where is the corner is it cozy corner yeah cuz there's another oh there
is another one in Williamsburg yeah I was telling you about that place yeah
yeah there's a barn in Ridgewood that you you go there and they give you a free
pizza with every drink free slice of pizza but it's good pizza
Yeah, damn good pizza damn frozen pizza. Just no number one type of pizza. I love I had one last everyone
New York Chicago now deep frozen frozen. I don't know where North Pole. Yeah, North
North Pole good as a
different a
North Pole slice. Mm-hmm. Oh, man
What's that? What's that? Can't be cans on Tony's that has a little Mario looking guy on it. I'm a tombstone man. I'm stones good
Tombstone, that shit's good.
Tombstone is really good, dude, yeah.
The pepperoni tombstone, dip that in some ketchup.
What is wrong with you?
And some mustard.
What? You can't eat on the mic.
You're not allowed to eat into the microphone.
You can eat, but you can't pick up the microphone while you eat.
Okay.
That's not allowed.
I'll just keep it right here.
Just tempting you?
And no, you're not allowed to have any camera.
I don't want any.
Not anymore.
You lost your pizza privilege for saying that.
Oh, but it looks so good!
I'm honestly surprised you picked the microphone over eating it.
I would have just eaten it.
Oh my god, it's so hot.
That's why you can't eat it.
Yeah, no, wait for that to cool.
Yeah.
It's good.
How much time do we have left on the episode?
Like 30 minutes.
Yeah, you got that.
You got that down.
Yeah, it's fine.
It's really hot.
450 degrees.
yeah that seemed too high for a frozen pizza but I guess the perfect amount of time to wait for a
pizza is like 20 minutes anyway so we can just spend the last 10 minutes of this
episode watching him eat and saying how hungry we are. Sounds good to me. I don't think so. No? No.
Why not? Because I got I got I don't want to get super hungry. I want to get super hungry.
I'm getting lunch after this. I don't want to go you never want to go into a lunch that you're
paying for super hungry. Yeah. Really? It's a mistake. I pregame lunch like it's a bar. You're
You're crazy, I love going to a restaurant hungry.
Me too.
I don't know about you guys.
I always get something, if I'm too hungry I always get something fucked up.
You go into like a, like going to the point, you're hungover, you wait until like 4 to
eat and then you order like the appetizer sampler at a diner.
What?
It's so, it's good.
I've done that many times.
What do you mean?
Many times you've done that?
Yes.
What is on the appetizer?
It's like a fucking thing.
It's like a fucking thing for four people.
At the airport diner.
At the airport diner in Manchester, New Hampshire
they had the appetizer sampler
that comes with like mozzarella sticks
and like corn fritters and uh
fries
and chicken wings I think.
Oh, that's so nasty dude.
You're like eat that fucked up.
You've already like fucked up your body
and then you go eat mozzarella sticks,
fries and chicken wings in one order.
an order for five people yeah you know what she I remember ordering it one time
and the waitress being like you guys know when you're like two people right
guys know when you're hungover shit and you wait till four and you go and you
eat an entire apple pie oh that's just apple pie for lunch oh my god that's good
dude it you won cuz it's gonna give you the itis you're gonna knock out and then
I'm like you're not allowed to say that I'm not no I didn't know that I'm sorry
for saying the I you get you get it you get it yeah it and then you knock out
yeah then you knock out and you have the best sleep of your life mm-hmm you're
like a hibernating bear I like to drink orange juice when I'm hungover yeah I
like to drink water yeah I would prefer to not get hungover in the first place
oh my god I'd rather read Ulysses yeah I probably would read Ulysses every single
night instead of drinking alcohol. Oh my, yeah, I'd rather. It has a similar effect on the psyche.
Mm-hmm, that's right. Poison in small doses. Mm-hmm. There's something intoxicating
about Joyce's prose. I just can't quit it. I'm addicted. I'm addicted to Ulysses,
which is almost like *gibberish*. Yeah, it's so cool that he's supposed to be like the best writer
ever and all of his books make no sense. That's genius. Yeah. Yeah. That is, that's
that's that's a that's that's the how they trick you dude mm-hmm yeah it's the
Emperor's new clothes that's book the best books are on sir at the end of this
book the true the actual best books yeah they're like Harold in the purple crayon
now the actual best books are like like fantasy books that you get yeah 100%
hundred of them like the wheel of time series just it's like the best type of
book is a fantasy book where it's not even like it's not even like a book like
it's just like a collection of like ideas that the guy had in every chapter is
like the first chapter is like there was a dragon and then it's like there was an
ogre and you know that's fucking that's sick yeah that's cool as hell and then
you just it just keeps going and nothing happens except for cool fantasy yeah and
you read Ulysses and there's a there's a 15 page section about him getting a
glass of water or something yeah and you're like fuck you man I could be
getting a glass of water in real life in like five seconds yeah be easy I'm not
thinking all this bullshit when we get a glass of water. I'm not like, "Oh, the
waves of my water." I think that when I get a glass of water, I think, "Oh, there are too many waves in my water. I should stop shaking my hand."
Damn, they took the appetizer platter off the menu at airport diner. I saw you just
completely checked out, laughing at things that you weren't actually hearing.
I was laughing at the waves of the water. And looking up the menu of a diner for the
last four minutes mm-hmm that is unbelievable yeah I was waiting for it to be over before
I drew attention to it that was next level it's kind of a left brain right
brain thing going on right now it's like you guys talking about books and then
thinking about food. Pizza, diner. We're divided you guys are on that half of the
room we're on this half. It's like the north and the south in the Civil War.
I'm sorry if you read books why do I get this out
fine I'm the South fine I'm in I'm the South of the Civil War fine you say it so
shamelessly if that's how it's gonna be I'm gonna start calling y'all boy that's
That's right, it's coming.
Tread lightly.
I'm gonna do it.
Alright.
I'm happy with this half of the room because we got the TV.
No!
And the Xbox.
And the video games.
We got the bathroom though.
That's true, you guys can't pee.
I'll just pee on your floor, it's not my apartment.
Please don't do that.
Crap, please don't.
Our floor is so clean.
We got the Wii.
Yeah, I'm gonna Wii on your floor.
No.
If there was a small dog shit in this room, how many days do you think it would be till
you guys found it?
is a small dog shit in this room. It's like fossilized. Or like black mold or something.
I vacuumed in here before you guys showed up. No you didn't. There's no way. There's literally
not. Look at that. Look at that. Look at the floor in there. You did not vacuum this fucking
room. If you actually vacuumed, you should like go back to elementary school. You need
to do like occupational therapy. Pat should do Billy Madison. You need it like again. I did that when I
was uh I did that and all they all that I really got out of it was that um I was allowed to chew
gum in school in elementary school. Really? Oh my god I should have done that shit. Dude I dude
the having a 504 plan you can just say like. Being having needing needing like a special education
accommodation stuff it's all it's it's it's cheating the system. Oh yeah. It just means you
to leave class whenever you want and draw pictures.
Yeah, yeah.
I got longer on tests and I was allowed to chew gum in class because I said it helped
me focus.
That's the best I did.
Y'all were both mad disabled.
I was one of those kids who would just finish the test in like 10 minutes and not check
my answers or whatever and just hand it in.
And I still got like extra time on tests for like a thing.
So I just like get to like leave the room and go like walk around for like an hour for
no reason.
That's sick.
Yeah.
That was the best.
when I had to take like I got a study lab that I got a credit for in high school
and see only reason I like graduated what's a study lab like like it was a
room that I went to with like a it was like a counselor and she would like she
was there to like help you with your homework if you need a help but I never
did it yeah it was called the learning center mine was called Lancer lab the
Learning Center is way more is way more in the hood yeah yeah yeah Alex is
pretty much from the yeah yeah Virginia yeah it's fine I was saying about like
Virginia North Carolina border each other but they're so different so I was
went through Richmond not that long ago and they took they had like the
Confederate statue they like they just took it down they like for at but first
they like destroyed it. There was like toilet paper on it every day. And in my hometown,
there's like guys who like defend the statues. And they're like four hours apart.
Yeah, Richmond is a weird, Richmond's just kind of like, it's kind of like
Boston a little bit. It's just like a lot of like, students. Yeah, it's really small. But
yeah, Virginia, it really isn't like, I mean, it's like a blue state, you know, it's yeah,
it's like North Carolina. Yeah, I don't think it's really even technically,
I feel like mid-atlantic, you know, yeah, I don't know explains your mid-atlantic accent, right? Yeah
Go to Virginia everyone just walking on like monologue
It was Tuesday it was a big
hankering for some grub
so i headed to the local cheeseburger spot
i'm a chicken, sure to do the trick
it's just you just ever *blah blah blah*
it's like 20 people all doing it at the same time
it's like walking into the guitar center in times square
but it's just everybody's just like
and i was gonna have a big mac
today
no soda, i wasn't thirsty
she was an ugly waitress
name's nicole
fat legs
fat face, fat arms.
Just fat all around.
She was like a bowling ball.
But she held the key to that which I need.
Two spicy McBickens.
Four McChickens, two McDoubles,
a 20 piece McNugget, and a large Coke.
All in 20 minutes.
What is that called? You've been talking about that all fucking week.
I don't know, it's just something that Juvio said.
He said that that's a challenge that you do.
We were in VR
and he was just asking
asking everybody if they could eat that in 20 minutes. It's making me laugh.
Oh, you, someone, you asked, did you ask me that the other day?
I probably did. Yeah.
Could you do it?
What is it?
Four McChickens, two McDoubles.
Four McChickens I could do.
Two spicy McBickens.
I could do that. I could eat six McChickens.
Will you stop?
You're fucking eating a challenge.
You're scaring me.
I don't give a fuck if you can eat part of the challenge.
He can't let an item of food be said without saying.
be said without saying I could eat that.
Two McDoubles, a 20 piece McNugget, that's where you get caught up.
Yeah, that's what would kill me.
I think also, and then I think a McFlurry.
No, that's where you lose me.
God, I love a McDouble though.
That might be my favorite item on the McDonald's menu.
Well, the secret is, it's a 20 piece, so you hide like two to four chicken nuggets in every
sandwich.
it's less food that way.
- Oh. - Yeah.
- It actually reduces the amount of food.
- Oh my God. - You're tricking your brain.
- You're tricking your brain
into thinking it's less food.
- I can't believe, you actually think that that would work.
- Look, look man.
- I know that you do.
You think that it would work if you handed the McNuggets
so that you don't individually eat it.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- All you have to do is get two giant slices of bread
and put every piece of food in between them
- I pretend you're eating one.
(laughing)
- It's a good point.
- The real trick is--
- It's like hiding a pill in peanut butter for your dog.
- Yeah, the pill doesn't work when you do that
'cause they can't see it.
- Exactly.
- But I think that I couldn't even eat 20 McNuggets.
- No, I would throw up within like 20 seconds
of trying that challenge, I think.
- I can't do that, I can't eat like a 20 piece
McNugget anymore.
- I couldn't do more than two McChickens, I feel like.
- I don't really like the McNuggets anymore.
Those were my go-to when I was a kid.
pizza is really good. They just have such a leather exterior. Yeah, they're not good.
Something changed and it's Michelle Obama's fault in 2012. That's right.
You're not trying to make me healthy you fucking long arm bitch. Dude, they had Doritos
Jacked. Get your big-ass arms out of my McDonald's. Stop reaching in there and flipping all this shit.
You're trying to turn my McChicken into a McChicken salad. She's using her long arms to switch out my fries for
apples. Fuck you, bitch. Yeah. And your man.
Chicken salad. Not for me.
If you want me to eat some kind of cranberry walnut salad at McDonald's...
Then you're gonna have to blow me.
Yep. That's right, Michelle Obama. Come on here.
Come to the back. Blow me from the back.
Come fucking... Oh, you want to get me to eat a grapefruit?
How about you grapefruit technique my fucking dick while you blow me, Michelle Obama?
Plus I get to see your armpits.
And I'm eating chips while this is happening.
yeah that's right and I'm rich and I'm the president and I'm Barack Obama
and let me be clear, my fellow Americans, let me be clear
six McChickens, what is it? four McChickens, could you eat?
two McDoubles, four McChickens
two spicy McBacons, a twenty piece McNugget
and a McFlurry and that's what we're changing to school lunch
and that's gonna be school lunch
and that's what makes america great
the republicans are saying you can't do it
they don't think you can eat all the mcchickens
or the double mcbickens
i believe in you
school lunch will be over one hundred hamburgers
it's gonna be huge
one hundred huge hamburgers
people have been asking me could you eat four mcchickens, two mcdoubles
two spicy mcbickens, a twenty piece mcnugget and a mcflurry
uh... yeah
how did you have a joyful efficient
and i could do all that
i like that your uh... your trump impression is the uh... the steroids
dealer from the special olympics episode of south park
very niche i don't think that the public that i don't think that there are any
other people who are you talking about it
you're a little bit around for a second
right what is this and you have your child we just watched the south park
episode Joe showed it to me the other day it was the one when he steals like the
um like the like the really fast ball and puts it in like the race car oh yeah
and then they come the alien comes such a good episode yeah really funny yeah
we've been watching a lot of South Park here that's why I said I love a Randy
episode of South Park those are always yeah it's like a Squidward episode
Spongebob dude I'd love to hang out let's spend a day with Randy is it a new
season like all Randy though yeah no that's like the last season I think that
That's too much Randy. Well he owns a pot farm. I don't give a fuck.
They're saying it's too much Randy. They're asking me do I make you Randy?
and I think I was watching a different show. There's a guy he's asking me if I make him
horny. Yeah I do. Yes you are making me horny. You're making me horny. You're
making me very hardy now you turn into a mother goose you did an impression last
night that was really good I can't remember what it was I don't remember
you did it and then it was I was like you should do a one-man show sponge Bob
yeah the the one-man show where it's just impressions of people you know people I
know my mom is my mom my brother it's a whole Frank Caliendo show but it's just
yeah people in your immediate mm-hmm yeah yeah and this is my mailman and
this is my neighbor I'm gonna kill you and then you win a Tony yeah yeah I go
EGOT hmm hmm Lin-Manuel might go EGOT yeah do you guys hear about this really
I think he's just missing an Oscar yeah and then know what his Oscar could be
for what's that movie just made I thought you were gonna do it you really
set it up like you're gonna make something up. No, I really want to talk to Alex about this.
Encanto. Encanto. Encanto. Haven't seen it. Oh, you know what I saw the other day?
What? Worst person in the world. Really good. What's this? Yeah, you looked in a mirror.
Damn. Bro, they named all the like dogs from the like litter of dogs that I'm adopting my dog from,
they're all named after fucking Encanto fucking characters. Really? My dog's name is Augustin.
Augustin Madrigal is his name. He's played by fucking, what's his name?
John Leguizamo?
Yeah.
That's actually...
Kind of cool.
You should name your dog John Leguizamo.
His name's Phil.
Yeah.
That's a good name.
I think it's a funny name for a dog.
Human names for a dog are always going to be good.
Yeah. As long as it's one syllable. If you go past one syllable, you're getting into fucking stupid.
Dude, you guys got fucked up. Listen, this is Augustin Madrigal. So it's like,
Encanto's about like a magic family, right?
Yeah.
"Having married into the family, Augustin has no magical gift of his own.
However, his accident-prone tendencies allow his wife to continuously refine her healing magic."
He is kind of stupid. The lady that we're adopting the dog from is like, "Yeah,
he's like the slow one from the litter."
Yeah.
This guy's thing is that he just gets hurt a lot.
That's funny.
Yeah, I'm reading the wiki right now.
You can tell that he's dumber than all the other dogs because in the photos of all the dogs,
like all the other dogs are like like look like cute young puppies and then he's
like has all both all of his legs are like turned in and he's like he like
looks bad yeah yeah he's like pretty I think that's good you always want that
dog yeah so what the what's that Marley and me it's okay I'm gonna I'm gonna
beat I'm gonna beat him till he's normal yeah yeah I have some I have some true a
piece of trivia about Augustin so keep keep this in mind when you get your dog
yeah this is a piece of trivia from the Disney wiki similar to Winnie the Pooh
Augustin has a conflict with bees. I think most dogs have a conflict with bees.
I don't think dogs, people and things have a conflict. Yeah, nobody really likes bees all that much unless you're in armor.
Bees suck. Unless you're in armor? Yeah, you know that armor they wear? It's true. Oh, like the beekeepers?
Yeah, I thought you meant like a knight. I do kind of want to do a bee beard. A bee beard?
You know when you put when people, oh yeah, people make a beard out of bees. Who's it? Big Sean just did like a music video
video no one saw and he's like covered in bees. That's got a sting. They did that in
the new Jackass. What up? That was good. Yeah. His penis. They put the queen bee on his wee-wee.
The queen? Yeah and all that. They all make a big, they make a big. You haven't seen it
yet? You haven't seen it? Oh man it's really good. It is really good. I would see it again
if you want to see it. I'll see it. I'd be down next week. Alright. Yeah. Okay. Is it
an IMAX? No. Oh come on. I know they should have put it in IMAX. Is it in 3D? I don't
Jackass 3 was in 3D, what are they doing?
Well they should have put this one in 4D.
No it's not.
They have a guy come into the theater and shit on the floor.
4D Jackass would be so funny.
That would be great. Scratch and sniff Jackass.
That would be awesome.
Guy walks in and shits on the floor
whenever, at least in the theater I was in.
Somebody got into the theater
and started doing Jackass shit.
Kicking people in the balls and stuff.
Yeah but he said he was a king.
That was his thing. He walked in and he kept saying
like I'm the king of France. I don't think he said that. He said that. No. Me and Joe went to see-
He's wearing bags as clothes. Me and Joe went to see Jackass and we- I probably told you this-
we ended up at the same theater by accident. Oh yeah. We went to see it separately but we went
to the same show. Well the the the power of Jackass. I know it brings friends together. It is
one of the it is one of the best movies of this year snubbed at the Oscars. Yeah. For best picture.
Does it, is it even eligible? Didn't it just come out? I would say Don't Look Up is the best movie of the year.
Scary. Oh, they should make another movie called Don't Look Up, but it's about pornography. Yeah,
they should do one about every obvious social issue in the world. They could make a bunch of
sequels and call it Don't Look Up, colon, and then like whatever you're not supposed to look up. Yeah.
Yeah. Oh, that's a good idea. Yeah. Don't Look Up, bomb recipe. Exactly. Don't look that up. Yeah,
- Yeah, they could do a whole movie
about how you're not supposed to look that up.
Yep, that's another good one.
- I think you can look up crystal meth recipe.
- Don't look up Brussels sprout recipe.
- Yeah, 'cause it's too--
- Don't look up Patrick Doran arrest record.
(laughing)
- Don't look up Patrick Doran 2017.
- Yeah, never been arrested.
- It doesn't exist, so you might as well not even try.
- Yeah, so it basically doesn't exist, right?
- No.
- Yeah.
- It exists, I've been arrested for bank robbery.
No, it was actually a misdemeanor charge.
You barely missed a minor.
And that's what you got arrested for.
I was arrested for...
No, you shot one out.
You barely missed a minor.
I was arrested for graffiti in 2017.
You tried to tag your name on a child like you owned it.
Were you really arrested for graffiti?
No.
Oh, okay.
I was just trying to get around them calling me a pedophile.
Sure.
I wasn't saying that at all.
i was saying i was a player shoplifter
uh... which is actually worse
uh... small businesses and uh... yeah
dot instead of doing small business
you know that's nasty
you want to know that i have a look at that
has made everything so god damn nasty sorry guys disgusting what you do
are you guys are going to a list on this episode
No, we don't do lists on the premium ones. Oh, I didn't know that. That's right. You're premium. You're gold standard. Yeah, cool
How's that feel feels pretty good. I like that you
You were you waited to bring that up until there's five minutes
So, uh guys
This is a list start
We should just do a three-hour episode make pat late for everything he has to do today. Yeah. Yeah as payback
Yeah, for every time for three years. Yeah, I said I'm it's fine. I can I can just tell them. I'm not like I'm gonna be late
Fuck
Damn, he's too good at being valuable. We'll do it another time. Yeah, that's right
Wait, so when you have something really important coming up, we're just gonna make you so late to it. Yeah
Just fuck you your wedding. Yeah, pat. Oh, yeah, pat. We need to record an hour before your surgery
I hope that's okay and you're gonna eat a bunch of food
Yeah, we're doing a food challenge right before your surgery.
We're going to do a magnet eating challenge before your MRI.
You have to eat those little magnets that you throw in the air and they make rattlesnakes out.
I get kind of worried. I think I probably have a coin in my body and if I go do an MRI.
Coins don't get attracted by an MRI. They're not magnetic.
I have a super magnet coin that I got from a magic set.
Is it cool to hold a microphone like this?
No.
It's not cool?
I'm thinking about doing that in the future.
Oh, that's how Anthony Jeselnik does.
Yeah?
Yeah.
And a baby was killed.
Yeah, and then a woman actually died.
I farted on a woman's corpse.
What does he sound like?
They're saying I farted on a woman's corpse.
They're saying I farted on a woman, and I pooped in her mouth.
That would be so...
And I did that. I did all of that.
the piss tape or whatever and it was like farting stuff he was like farting on people
well i you know i forgot it i was so that's why he just mentioned it
i was so mad that it didn't exist well also the thing is like if it definitely exists
there was a video 100 no it's not real it's not real okay well tom arnold was on it it's not
like tom arnold was on that case it's not it's not real he's definitely doing shit like that
though i mean he's a he's like i'm sure he did it but he's he's he's a genius he's not gonna get
recorded yeah okay I can so smart he's like Odo from Deep Space Nine he can
shapeshift into anything yeah exactly Trump looks like that because he's like
he's clay he was he's orange clay the other thing is if he was pissing on if
he's pissing on girls and fucking hot women of making them eat his farts I
think his approval rating would have gone way up yeah yeah there's like it's
definitely if he was the one doing the pissing but it wasn't the thing that he
was getting pissed on Chuck Berry sold still our albums after that no things
people who like him are just gonna be like that's cool well I don't like him
because he gets pissed on you know and then the people don't like him or get
like I would have voted for him after that I would have been yeah I was sick
dude if he if he released a video of him peeing on like a toilet no not a toilet
like human a human yeah yeah he thought it was just a video of him peeing we
We have found a video of Donald Trump peeing in the bathroom.
He does not lift the toilet seat before he pees into the toilet.
He gets it all over the seat.
He pulls his pants all the way down.
And then his son comes in and sits down on the toilet and he gets his dad's pee all over
his butt.
And he gets pregnant.
Yep, and he got his son pregnant with his pee.
He got his son pregnant through pee.
I got my son pregnant through pee.
Yes, I got that.
It's insane.
I'm the number one.
I'm number one at getting my son.
I'm pregnant with your kid.
I'm pregnant with your pee, kid.
wait to put your p-kid out. I'm gonna give birth to it so good dad. He's cool.
You're so good at impressions man you should really do like a show I'm like
you're really good. I did see Trump jr. outside of Londonderry High School. Yeah
yeah. What you did to him? Huh? Did you disrespect him in a political manner? I
I did I did behind my ballot. I did a little finger. Yeah
Cool, I blew you know, I put my my mouth thumb and then I blew up my middle finger. Yeah, I pretended that was something
You Trump jr
Skipped away you threw a glove at his face. I
I want you to make my butt pregnant with your pee, Trump Jr.
You guys ever suck your thumbs? I was big into that when I was a kid.
I knew this girl who sucked- I didn't do it because I knew this girl who sucked her
thumb so bad their teeth like pointed directly at you.
Ugh, yeah. Gross.
My name was Lauren.
Why did you say it like that?
I fucking hated her. She was so annoying.
Yeah.
I think you have no choice but to be- like you're not gonna be cool if you've been
sucking your fucking thumb for a decade.
I sucked my thumb until whenever Madagascar came out because I remember I saw that movie.
I think I was like seven.
There's a thumb thing in that, right?
They make fun of Alex the Lion because he sucks his thumb.
Yeah, wow.
And I was like, whoa.
That's mean.
Like, that's straighter schizophrenia than most people.
That happened to Brian Wilson.
He like went to see that movie Seconds and like the main character in that movie is named like,
his last name is Wilson.
And it was right when Brian Wilson was like, kind of like losing it.
and he like walked into the theater and he got there late and he walked in the
theater was just like hello mr wilson and well it was like that's cool i'm
crazy that is sick yeah all right then you put more calebs in
movies yeah yeah i'm glad they don't make them hot
women that's a good idea
it's a really good idea all right um oh watch home planet videos check out home
planet home underscore underscore planet yeah
how many underscores? I think it's two. Home two underscores planet on Twitter and
then home planet on YouTube. Well it's Black History Month so right now it's
homey planet. In 15 days it'll go back to home planet. Alright. It'll go back to white planet.
It'll go back to white. Okay. Bye!