Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
*Demonic voice*
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase your premium membership immediately!
*Explosion*
Get out, bitch!
Hit the road, hoe!
Don't come back, bitch!
Hit the road, bitch!
Don't come back, hoe!
We got to get the chief in here.
Oh dude, we got to get Chief Kufra.
Chief, if you're listening bro.
Chief Kufra.
Chief Kufra, if you're...
We would love for you to write a song for us.
We want you to write our new theme song.
We want to get plugged in.
Yeah.
I need to get plugged in with you.
He's on some next level shit that I never even considered.
I think that's the new $20,000 goal for the Patreon.
I think we just do that in general.
Give Chief Kufra $20,000.
That's the goal.
Chief Kufra $20,000 to write us the new theme song.
I don't even care if he does that.
I mean he's got like he has some of the greatest songs of all time.
I think.
It's Time to See You Nude is a classic by now.
Yeah.
Which one is this?
Oh, this is Time to See You Nude?
They all have the same beginning.
It's time to see you kiss It's time to see you kiss, oh, forever
It's time to see you nude It's time to see you nude, oh, forever
It's time to see you dance It's time to see you dance, oh, forever
time to see you bend over, time to see you bend over, forever, dude forever, oh man, wait,
hold on, you didn't even, woah, man you're a fan, full of hell could feature this guy
That'd be amazing. We need to do just a collab with him musically maybe. Yeah. I mean we're
all musicians. Oh dude look at this album art. Dude I mean he just looks so good. I love him
so much dude. I love Chief Kufra. It's good to have a hero and a role model. Yeah. Yeah.
Man if he ever wanted to collab with us on a track. We need to get him and Doug Stanhope
in a room. We need to see those two. We need to get those two on the ranch.
So the song, it's about...
So wait, it's about...
You gotta see it dude.
You're saying, "Fo-Fo-Evo?"
What's a pussy carl type...
I could never be with one woman fo-evo.
What's a pussy carl?
I could never see a woman sexo.
Tell you what I could do fo-evo, drink!
I could drink fo-evo.
I'm not kidding, I could drink forever.
I could drink foevo. Bobo, I got Bobo. She bendovo foevo. I saw her sexo foevo.
Chief Cooper, I gotta tell you, like, I played that song for my wife and it worked. I saw
her nude. It took her out of the coma. Yeah, it took her out. And then we had to bring
her back to life, but then she came back. Dude, I need to catch an invite from Doug.
I think me and Doug might really get along.
He's, I genuinely do like him.
He's a man.
He's such a good.
He's so cool.
I love that, what's that special he did where he's like talking about.
Beer Hall Putsch.
Is that the one where he talks about like.
Killing his mom.
Killing his mom, yeah.
I think so, yeah.
Yeah, killing his mom.
It's one of the best specials ever.
Yeah, it's so cool dude.
Yeah, dude that.
Yeah, it's like one of the best closers ever.
Oh yeah, dude.
That one hit me in my feels.
Really?
That one hit me right in my feels.
I'd kill my mom for a dollar.
Really?
One dollar.
Dude, if I had to kill my mom and like...
Kill my mom for nothing.
I would not kill my mom.
Are you kidding me?
I would never kill my parents.
I would come up behind my mom and I'd like do the Halo melee on the back of her neck
and I'd kill her in one second.
I would do Team Fortress 2 disguise kit and then become my mom.
I would literally...
Become my mom for a little bit.
Yeah.
do that no I wouldn't I would hate every minute of it but I'd have to do it to
keep the family together oh I have to fucking kiss my dad you hung out with my
dad recently it was awesome dude yeah you missed out on that dad is so much
cooler than him yeah like I'm like I would so much rather hang out with your
dad than you he's so cool yeah like why why did what why are you worse what
happened to you because I'm a combination of him and my mom I hung out
your mom's cooler than you - yeah look I don't know your dad was such a good
hang did and you were there you were there the whole time just trying to run
it I was trying to what you ruin it I wasn't ruining you're ruining he was
telling every stories of my childhood yeah and you were going like um dad
actually it hurt whenever he would finish the stories no yeah what the
stories about. He's telling two cool stories about throwing you off balconies and... He
never threw me off a balcony. Strangling you. Strangling me. Yeah. Saying, "Why you little!"
Yeah. All the stories about the power plant. This is dope. Quite a lot. Oh my god. He had
crumbs all over his mouth. Yeah. Sprinkles. All over his mouth. Icing. He just kept eating
donuts the whole time. Yeah. It's always crazy when you meet someone... Everybody's dad is
pretty much cooler than them. Yeah. I feel like for the most part. Well, it's because
you're like seeing the person, like I didn't meet your dad, but I'm sure once I do, it's
going to be like, oh, I'm just like looking at the person Caleb's trying to become. I'm
really nothing like my dad. Yeah? Yeah. Oh, I guess that's different for me. Yeah, my
dad is like a very quiet. He's like a stoic. Yeah. Yeah. I thought my dad was like that,
but I just realized like, oh yeah, no, he just doesn't like talking to me. Yeah. Yeah.
he just I was just I'm just I'm just annoying in high school. Yeah, I bring
you guys around my dad. He's doing like Jim Carrey shit.
He's like fucking really getting it. Yeah, your dad's he literally like the
mask like he's doing he's doing like Cuban Pete on top of a cop car. I guess
I've never seen my dad out of his shell really. Oh, that's interesting.
He's doing the fucking, the Beetlejuice song.
Jake, Jake, Jake, you don't know.
He's like pumping the air.
(laughing)
Yeah, that would surprise me.
But I guess, I mean, that's kind of how my dad,
whenever my dad gets around like his family,
all this, like my dad's not,
like I would never say that my dad is like funny.
But then when he gets around his family,
he like, everybody's like, oh yeah,
he's like the funny uncle.
Yeah.
And he's just sitting there.
That is, it's so, yeah, it's so funny.
It's just like my cousin will order a salad
and my dad will like lean into the table
and be like, "It's kind of fruity."
- Yeah.
- And then he just crushes.
- Yeah, the funny uncle is such a funny,
'cause yeah, it never translates.
- Oh yeah.
- It's always that the person, that the family member
found like one or two jokes that like really work
like 10 years ago and you never have to come up
with new stuff.
- The funny uncle--
- Are you kidding me?
I'm a family member.
- I'm trying out all my new material on my nephew's knees.
You're not the funny family member.
The funny uncle is also just the one who, the uncle who's the most drunk at everything.
Yeah.
That's the funny one.
I know.
See, that's what I'm saying.
It's funny when the uncle, it's funny when you...
He's funny because he falls asleep.
Yeah.
It's funny when you make your nephew get you a beer and...
Yeah, and then pretend that you're going to let him have some.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's funny as fuck.
And then it's also funny when you pick him up and you like pretend you're going to throw
him at the couch.
Yeah, you do it.
Well, they like that.
the couch. Why do you say that? You're saying that you pretend that you throw them and then
you do throw them at the couch. No, I don't throw them at the couch, but they think it's
funny when you pretend to get mad at them and then say, "Why you little..." and then
pretend to throw them. I need to get some nephews, bro. I need to get some nephews.
I got in-law nephews, that's it. Being an uncle, swag as hell. You can't kick your in-law
for Thanksgiving. No. I can't do, I can't like fucking prank my in-law nephew. Yeah. I can't.
You can't, yeah. I can't teach him how to curse, like it's all off limits. Yeah. I got cousins
that are the same ages as my nephews. Yeah, that's weird. Yeah, it's so weird. Yeah. But I can't like,
because it's my cousins. I can't kill them. It's my cousins, so I can't treat them like my nephews.
It's my cousins though. It's my cousins, I can't treat them like my nephews. You know. You can
treat a cousin exactly like your nephew. I have to, no, I have to treat them like they're on the
on
hookah yeah that's what the Thanksgiving walk is about. You're just carrying a hookah around.
What is that? This is my phone. Yeah hiding a hookah under your shirt trying to leave.
That's my phone. Thanksgiving. That's my gun. Yeah coming back in your Caterpillar. Big
AK-47 hookah. Coming back in your Caterpillar from Alice in Wonderland. What are you doing
I'm just walking around. We just walked around the neighborhood we didn't do anything. Your
eyes are like spiraling yeah yeah they're falling into your eyes big smoke rings
yeah that you that are carrying you through Thanksgiving yeah what did you
do I don't remember nothing everything disappears but your smile yeah nothing
the cousin walk do be like that though yeah me were my cousins you guys were
are
delicious restaurant yeah we should check out delicious restaurant now yeah yeah
just check out your anxious food yummy food yeah beautiful lunch yummy foods a
really good name for yeah tasty delicious restaurant is like probably as
good as it gets right yeah yeah yeah I'm sure there's like there's like at least
ten places called delicious restaurant in New York okay I'll bet on that
delicious 88 probably yeah you think it is what not see 88 you're a Nazi delicious
is two boobs or four boobs actually never mind never mind that's actually the coolest thing
of all time that's right if there's a place called delicious restaurant we have to go
to delicious restaurant there's a place called delicious restaurant in brockton oh wow mass
yeah oh my god it's a haitian restaurant whoa called delicious restaurant i would go there
in a second yeah fuck how's your guys's thanksgivings what'd you guys we had the same one yeah no
I was actually like oh right you guys were home I went back and saw my family
yeah I mean me and can watch James Bond yeah yeah nice there's also a place
called delicious restaurant in wherever this is and their website is business
dot-site I don't think that's it in Bengaluru Bengaluru India bang I thought
I thought we're gonna get to go to the dr. Seuss world so you think of India no
You think it's a Dr. Seuss crazy upside-down world?
You think there's a lot of different places that speak English?
Yes.
That's what you think about India?
You think there's a river of floop?
There's so many places called delicious restaurant in India.
I like that a lot of stuff in India is named in English.
Yeah.
I was like, have you ever hear somebody speak?
There's so many places there called like Hitler clothing.
Yeah.
I went on a, I have probably 50 screenshots of places called Hitler in India.
Hitler's Hitler restaurant.
One thing, I saw one that was Hitler medical.
Whoa.
Yeah.
Pretty cool.
Damn.
Maybe, maybe Argentina was a false flag.
You think Hitler's in India?
I think Hitler went to-
I think the next Hitler's gonna be in India.
Well, no, no.
I think that's where his soul fled after he died.
i think you know you're in a car and they are argentina everybody from operation
paperclip went to
india as you think indians are horrible nazis no
well there's one that
there's one on twitter
indian hitler yeah
there's a there's also a reserve circle of indelicious that's a pretty good
name all
i have no i have no qualms as for a delicious food incorporated
i love indian people
I just don't want anyone to be mad at me for saying.
Bok bok chicken delicious.
Do you guys want to go here?
I would.
Dude I'd go there in one second.
Yeah.
Bok bok chicken delicious.
I've been having multiple dreams the past couple weeks that take place in India.
Yeah?
Yeah.
You've never been?
Of course I've never been.
How do you know it's India?
What do you mean?
What if it's in America?
'cause in the dream it's in in my name in the in the dream
you don't know where you are in your dream you know you're not in the west
indies
someone says
we're in india welcome to india
uh... india my friend
that's a not soft authentic of the
as a shrimp
was too lazy that come up with a columbus joke
you would a crush if you had a columbus joker you know that is a little
Listen to this show for the history
Can we take this opportunity to just tear into that fucker yeah, what you guys have never torn into me no
Columbus oh, I thought you were you looked at me when you saw her into this one. I ever tear India
Yeah, you dumb fucking idiot. You must be a fucking moron to think I'd tear India and
Columbus cripple
What the fuck did you just say?
We both woke up at four in the morning today.
I did.
I went, I drew myself a bath and I read about the English monarch.
And then Pat probably farted on his own balls.
No, I made my roommate and I coffee.
Yeah, by dipping your balls like a tea bag into the water and farting into the water
as well.
Let's not deny that dipping your balls in coffee, pretty good.
I'm going to deny that.
Why?
have I don't have you have holes all in your balls yeah yeah it's like a
you know on your nuts that's not true yeah you do you Pat swings his his balls
like a like a sensor and you can see like the the smell of a breeze like like
yeah yeah and they just have they oh yeah you know when like a priest like
swings the sensor to like yeah to like spread the that's what you know yeah I
put coffee on there then I swing it around so yeah all those women pregnant
on the street. I hate that dude. I have so many kids. You do a disgusting dust all over the sidewalk
and they breathe it in. Yeah. And then they pop out. Yeah. In nine minutes they pop out. That's
how the ninja turtles were born. Really? Yeah. Yeah. My seed got in the tunnel. Did a turtle
fuck a woman? No. No. They were lab experiments and then the spirits of ancient ninjas got
reincarnated into them. Lab experiments is like they definitely like made a turtle fuck a girl.
They definitely all fucked April.
Yeah.
Facts though.
Mm-hmm.
I'd like to see that.
There was a girl turtle too, Venus de Milo.
Mm-hmm.
And then they made another one.
They probably fucked her too.
Yeah.
Yeah, and they probably fucked me.
They probably fucked every female character in that stupid franchise.
Those stupid thoughts.
Fuck.
Probably sucked a lot of turtles cock in that show.
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles?
Um, okay.
Yeah.
Yeah, like I'm supposed to believe they're Teenage Mutant and Ninja and Turtles?
Hey, it's like, listen, pick one.
one yeah okay let me watch this show. Let's just watch turtles. Can we just watch teenage?
Can we just watch teenage for once? I was watching mutant. I've seen all of mutant. I don't need
to see anymore. Ninja that's actually pretty cool. How about teenage? See any combination
works there. Teenage turtle. The turtle is really. The teenage turtle show. The turtle
part really I mean if they just dropped the turtle part it would be way cooler. Yeah. Teenage
mutant ninjas yeah fucked up ninja kids fucked up little freakers or a little
freakers oids yeah also and they as if it's not already a hat on a hat you're
raised by a damn rat yeah you're raised by some kind of kung-fu
fight I'll we're finally wearing into this that's why I'm tearing it doesn't
Oh, yeah, and we're your somebody there's a guy named a rager
Crasher Slayer Slayer Slayer shredder shredder
There's beat there's there's be Bob Rocksteady
Sure the good or the bad guy called shredder. He's bad. I'm praying. Yeah, I read like like
250 issues of the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle comics like a year ago, and then who's that guy's name is
Oh, there is a guy named slash and over or something. What's the name of their like white?
That's your Casey Jones Casey Jones. He's cool as hell. Yeah. He is cool actually he does the sickest he's played by
Elias Cody ace in the in the
Cody and he got bald as soon as that movie was sounds good. There's an evil turtle named slash. Yeah giant
They're all giant well. They're fucking no
They're both slashes giant.
They're giant!
Bigger than a person, giant.
They are bigger than a person.
They're huge.
They're big for turtles, they're human sized.
Understatement of the century.
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles are big for turtles.
They're huge for turtles.
Sea turtles get really big.
Nah.
You get big for turtles.
Have you seen Squirt?
No.
You've never felt the joy of getting squirted. I saw it at your mom's house. Yeah, in a soda can. Yeah.
Yeah, the soda squirt. Yeah, after I was done. You didn't make my mom squirt. She got all the
squirt removed, surgically. Surgical squirt. Her squirtatious glands have been sealed off.
they duct-taped her squirt glands so nice try douchebag the thing that pissed me
off about Venus de Milo as a kid though is that they made her also blue like she
was like a light blue for her headband yeah like why did I should have made her
pink they had yeah they had every color that's a baby boy's color they had every
color at their disposal and they make her light blue not green no she's already
green point they could done red yellow no green wouldn't work they're already
they are green that's what I'm saying they're already could done they could
done black black headband that's just you're getting in a normal food
territory there yeah could do uh like a like a puce what what color what color is
is
a dark red or purple brown but this is pink that's on my screen there's so many
fucked up colors of stupid names yeah taupe chartreuse chartreuse is a type of
blue right no it's green are you that god damn it's like a light green you
think everything every color is green that's like a green right yeah right it's
like the color of money yeah yeah yeah what's another fucked up color
Perry Winkle. Perry Winkle's cool. Shut up. Let's not. Shut the fuck up. But then they
got some lazy ones. Baby Blue. Yeah. What the fuck is that bullshit? That's just blue. Sienna.
Burnt Sienna. Mauve. That's a cool color. Moss. That's a plant. Remember, you ever see
The Y2K Crayolas.
Why are you gay?
What?
Gay-ola.
Why are you gay-gay-ola, bitch?
What?
You're a dingleberry.
The Y2K Crayolas and they said like, one of them was called like www.purple or something.
Oh yeah, those are cool.
That's good actually.
Yeah.
You ever see, I don't know if you've ever seen it, but there's a guy named, I don't know if
Oh yeah, those are cool.
Yeah, yeah.
You ever see, they're like, you could get, they're like, they did like crayons that were
like, as you know, it always say like skin color, it'd be like a white crayon.
Yeah.
There was like one where there's like just like 10 different skin color crayons.
Really?
It's a bunch, like it's every possible skin color.
That's powerful.
They're all called skin.
That's really powerful.
Yeah.
It's actually cool.
It's like flesh color band-aids.
It's like, what I'm gonna draw with these.
They're all like, they're like, like, like pinkish brown.
these are you can draw the people of the world you never thought about that huh
you can't draw I feel like I feel like crayon draw black plant shut up you can't
there's a black plan I would much rather have like red and green and yellow and
blue than every skin color racist racist much I don't know if you're red green
blue or purple okay if your skin skin skin skin or skin it's all skin to me
Have you seen the skin colored band-aid? Have you seen that shit?
Are they doing black flesh colored band-aids yet?
Yeah.
Really? That's funny.
I never realized that band-aids were supposed to be flesh colored. I thought
they were supposed to be band-aid colored.
Yeah. Yeah. I kind of...
I never had that thought.
Racist.
I never had that thought until those band-aids came out and then I was like, damn,
I do not look like a band-aid.
It's not like it's going to blend in.
It's honestly grosser if it looks the color of your skin.
Yeah, right.
What the fuck is wrong with you and that one little area?
There's a huge bump on your leg.
Why do you have a pill-shaped area of your body that looks like shit?
Yeah.
And it's falling off.
You have tiny holes on a pill-shaped area of your body.
Yeah, exactly.
The tryptophobes gonna hate that.
I like the band-aids with characters on them.
Yeah.
Dude, I would...
That's good for the characters.
I went to...
Skin.
Oh, dude.
I didn't realize how...
If you're Spongebob, a Spongebob band-aid's gonna look pretty damn fine on you.
That's a good point.
Yeah.
How come there ain't no Caleb band-aid yet?
They can't, you can probably make 'em.
They don't, they're not like M&Ms, you can't get 'em custom made, you fucking...
If not, band-aids should jump on that.
They absolutely should.
I went to, I think last Saturday, two Saturdays ago, went to Dave & Buster's.
Yep.
Some people went there.
And I cut my thumb open before I got there.
So I had to use all my points to buy band-aids.
Did you do it as a joke?
No, I was skating before I went there.
And then...
At Razor Park?
I think I cut my thumb on my truck.
Or something.
You tried to grind a needle.
Yeah.
I was grinding a straight razor at the barbershop.
Because you're one foot tall.
We could buy custom printed band-aids.
I had to spend $300...
I mean points at Dave & Buster's.
on you also spent three hundred dollars
yeah
that's different story
i spent three hundred points on band aids and the only thing that the only
money i had her points i had left was
enough to buy
dracula teeth
nice so they're going to be a i want to get a custom and a_b_s_ says fucked up
police and a m_a_
this custom band aids you can like upload a uh...
image file
to the band aid
And the minimum amount you can order is $5,000.
The minimum price is $2,000.
What?
How much is--
On this website.
What the--
Maybe there's another way.
How much are these expensive Band-Aids, dude?
What the fuck?
That's crazy.
It's $0.39 per custom printed Band-Aid.
And then there's a setup cost.
That's awful, dude.
But we might have to do a run, though, low key.
But hey, if you order $25,000 or more,
it's only $0.31 per Band-Aid.
Should we do a Band-Aid merch drop?
We should.
How much would it cost to order 25,000 band-aids?
That's like not a bad idea.
7,800 dollars.
Let's just do it.
The band-aids I got did not work.
You got defective band-aids.
Well, they were prank band-aids.
Yeah, they were pineapple shaped.
From Dave and Buster, you got...
You bought a sticker.
Basically.
Yeah.
I bought stickers to fix my thumb.
Yeah, how'd that work out for you?
Didn't work out that well.
Big shot.
Yeah.
Hot shot.
You think you're hot shit, hot shot?
Who's there with us?
matter no one cares I love that Dave and Buster's trip with my friends that you
guys didn't go on even though I invited you and you said no Patrick's every
story that Patrick tells has a beginning middle and and list of everybody who was
there at the time yeah that's why we didn't ask him about his Thanksgiving
I ate turkey and then I left and my mom was there and my dad was there and my
sister was there shout out to my sister yo if you're listening sis you popped
off at Thanksgiving she did do she's good she made chocolate soup yeah I was
gonna let that play out just because I was like and here's a world-famous
chocolate syrup with ice cubes in it yeah it's a chocolate gazpacho chocolate soup
but that's literally like I feel like it's probably like the you know like the
aunt Myrna's party cheese salad like everyone's like grandma has some
disgusting 1950s recipe that they bring to like Thanksgiving yours no sweet
potato souffle. Yeah, like shit like that. That was really good. It was good, but it
looks fucked and weird and it has eggs in it. Some weird grandma recipe like that. I hit
my Nana up for that one. Mm-hmm. Have you seen the little Aunt Myrna's party cheese
salad will be making an appearance at my next Thanksgiving. I hate hitting up my Nana for
for fucking recipes, bro. She has this old ass recipe book. It's like from like 1910,
right? She just sends me the recipe cards and I just have to hope there's not like Brazil
nuts isn't an ingredient. I'm like I'm not making this. It's always fucking awful.
And I'll be like what is like fucking what is China man's afro and she'll
be like oh that's parsley. It's always some crazy ingredient that just doesn't exist.
Just like some fucking stupid shit they used to call it back then. Yeah.
Shit there was one thing called like creamed cutter. I was like what is this? It's milk.
It's just like milk or half and half. Okay whatever. They had this candy. Yeah it's always
some weird ingredient that they use a like stick and ass pick. Yeah. And yeah, I
have to have it explained to me. And then also none of it is weighted. It's always
just like one box of whatever. It's like I don't think boxes are the same size now
as they were in 1910. Right, like you're putting like a whole box of like powdered
mashed potatoes. Yeah, exactly. Yeah. Those are kind of good. Back then every box was
the same size. Yeah, standard. That was a... Well, there was like there were like
ten boxes in the world that they like switched off using.
That was an imperial measurement.
And they were wooden boxes.
One box.
Yeah.
They were all made of wood.
They were East India Trading Company boxes.
Yeah.
Yeah, just a thing that had a seal on it.
I think if-
There's a lot of blood on them.
I think if we went back in time, I might be one of the heads of the East India Trading
Co.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I'd be a famous movie star.
I don't think you would.
Yeah.
Oh, dude, are you kidding me?
I'd be such a good silent film star.
I'd probably be a computer programmer.
When?
in 1600 and 21 if we went back to the 1910 1920s Cameron be the greatest
computer programmer of all time no I'm gonna be the first I'm gonna be a 1600s
computer programmer I'd go back in time and I do I do Lenny Bruce's shit like a
year before I'm just gone stage but I'm gonna go back in pee I'm gonna go back
One of the greatest comics that ever lived.
Stinky poopy wiener!
My socks smell!
He got on that stage for three days and the cops came in and destroyed every set that he
tried to do but he was fighting for his freedom.
Let me say, you can't see butt on stage!
Hey!
Gah gah gah gah gah gah!
Get down!
Get down off that stage!
What did I just hear you say?
Stinky poop!
I'm gonna wash you!
You're gonna have six days in jail and each day I'm gonna wash your mouth out with soap!
I'm gonna eat a diaper. Oh that's the other punishment we were gonna do but he
just said it. I'm gonna go back to the 1800s and do Tim and Eric. Change the course of history.
You should do like it's like Shakespeare and you doing Tim and Eric stuff.
Yeah you're doing the office sketch. You're doing like Tim and Eric bits like as
like a Civil War performer yeah and they're like writing home to their wives
and it's like, "Well, darling, it's the strangest damn thing. He mixed up a bat and an owl."
There's a drummer boy who can't finish a sentence without stuttering.
"He was just so damn awkward. It made me cringe."
There's a difference between a pregnant pause and an awkward pause,
and this drummer boy, he toes the line near perfectly.
my dearest martha
it's been very cold out here in the
in the winter months of
december something
i don't know
uh... anyway
i watched this guy
diarrhea into a pair of pants
they're plastic pants and then the pants spilled out at the bottom
i didn't even know we had plastic back in these times
there's a fella been coming around the camps recently goes by the name of meatwad
funniest damn shit I've ever seen.
Well, I wouldn't have...
He's driving in his car, he's living like a star.
Well, he said, well, I mean, these days would be almost unbearable if
that boy Spaghet hadn't come around.
If it weren't for you, my darling, and of course, Metalocalypse.
That Nathan Explosion can really play a guitar.
Oh no, he didn't play the guitar.
NOOOOO!
FUCK!
I WANT THE BILL!
Actually, Nathan Explosion did not play the guitar.
He was the singer!
Fucking owned.
That William Murderface, he's got the craziest voice, I tell you.
Those damn Venture Brothers.
Always coming around this Civil War act of fools.
Well, the damnedest thing happened today.
Uh, what happened?
There was a squid billy.
I seen a squid billy.
I saw a squid billy outside.
Yeah, it's like a jackalope.
It's like a new folklore creature.
There's a creature, we'll call him a squid billy.
He sat on his porch, couldn't understand a word he said.
he had a shotgun and he pointed it at me or something.
A strange fella named Oblong came by.
I would go back to the first late night show and I would just do Eric Andre for the first
one.
Yeah, that'd be cool.
And that's Jack Parr just going on there.
You push Jack Parr over, start taking a shit on his mouth or something.
Teabagging him.
Asking him what if it was purple.
But it's ruining late night.
because it never starts because of that.
We could let this on TV, no way!
We would not have gone to Iraq.
We would have saved everything.
We have to send Eric Contre back in time.
That's what's going to stop. To destroy American culture.
Because I mean, no late night TV,
None of this counterculture starts. We're all in a straight and narrow.
Yeah.
None of these hippies.
Mm-hmm.
Ruining society in the 60s.
Damn hippies.
Oh my god.
Get a freaking haircut.
Honestly, it sucks that hippies are still around and that they're so annoying.
Yep.
Dude, they're the most annoying people in the world.
I hate hippies. They basically, they smell bad and they look ugly.
Take your leather jacket off, you fucking hippo.
Yeah, these hippies walking around with their scarves drinking their who knows what Starbucks choco latte or whatever the hell
Listening to the Arctic monkeys all the time supposed to be black. That's right. That's right. Take your damn skinny jeans off and let me
These hipsters walk around their skinny jeans take a model. Let me suck your cock
Take off your pants on your attempt
Show me the balls. I
I can see them already through the pants.
Your pants are so fucking thin and tight.
They're hugging on your...
How much spandex is in those pants?
More than 2%?
I want you to put your balls under my ground.
I'm going to suck all the spandex out of your pants.
Make them tighter on you.
Oh my god, I'm going to vacuum seal you in a plastic suit.
Have you seen those videos?
I saw one the other day.
It was a guy in a vacuum sealed bed thing, but he also had like the...
also think the b_k_ bulge size balls you know you should watch instead of all
this crazy shit yeah
fail army
i do watch that so spent you should be spend i'd only watch fail army and i
live a happy life i mean i these are just things people send me on the
computer you should do what i do and don't look at those things and i have to
look at you don't have to you know you know i see that there's a lot of mail
army is a lady
it is there's a message on my phone key on the way to answer
and meanwhile i mean while i have had a few five hours to respond to a text
uh... he telling on himself
by any time i was so i have a d_h_d_ bitch
uh...
the
you don't have a she doesn't exist stop rubbing your leg
over a m_e_a_ standing whatever i want
i'm rubbing the thing you think you
you think you've gripped you peter griffin diplomatic immunity i think i
I got diplomatic immunity.
So damn it you can't sue.
I can riot, loot, not give a hoot, and touch your sister's teeth.
Yep, that was on my mom's iPod.
That shit was funny.
That was a LimeWire download.
That was the best song.
Can't touch me.
That was uh...
Cause he made his house fucking Kurdistan or some shit.
They found out that he was in the one part of Rhode Island that was not claimed by the
US.
And he claims it.
I would love to start a micronation and go to war.
Yeah, that's exactly what happens in the episode.
Everybody.
Just the world?
Every other country.
Okay.
Oh man.
Do you think one of, I mean like what, okay.
Well okay, well obviously.
Alright, let's beat it out.
beat it out on the weekends like you beat it up yeah so you're at your where's
your micro nation where I don't know is it the sea or is it landlocked I've
probably just my house okay so you're gonna be like a part of your just my
yard my house and yard okay I'll have a house and yard for this scenario okay so
what you said that you want to declare war mm-hmm on every nation yeah so are
Are you making any sort of military strike on any nation or are you just inviting?
If my neighbors walk on my yard, they're dead.
Yeah, my first move is becoming a spy for the US to spy on Cameron land.
You're not welcome.
You step foot on my yard, you're dead.
You won't know.
Can I come?
I will know.
You won't know.
Can I come?
Are you a spy?
No.
Okay, you can come.
I'm secretly a spy.
a
99% approval rate. The King of Awesome has been executed. The King of Awesome Land has
been executed in the streets today. The King of Awesome Land. His successor has been shot
by firing his entire family his success his only successor a parakeet named
steven
successor it as for his well it do nick from new girl i would love to be the
ruler of the most evil country on earth and call it awesome awesome fun land
yeah yeah it's pretty cool just doing like fucking robert mugabe stuff yeah
yeah under the name of anything is called awesome way yeah yeah
yeah possible and anything but awesome
and then that's that's what the article is and then immediately
he's killed by awesomely and spies in the u_s_
possibly i just got a little more approval of a lot of spies in every
country when national news
yeah i show up to also land of wearing like a big flower on my
on my uh... jacket
stand and say go this is not a camera
you know i'm trying to film all the the atrocities of also let me know we would
run quarter you immediately and other night you know the
we have a we have a we have a we have a we have a vice detector
yeah at the at customs i'm like
my pre-interview with vice is like
so uh... about to get on the plane to go to awesome land uh...
you know i'm i'm
kind of uh... nervous what's gonna happen thankfully i just took uh... six
hundred milligrams of psilocybin mushrooms yeah that's the vice detector
is that there's just a guy who asks like do you want to smoke weed with me for six hours and like
chop it up and whoever says yes gets they get chopped it up
Oh yeah oh yeah and there's ghosts there. Has Vice sent a fucker to North Korea? I think
so. That was so chill. Yeah. Smoking weed in Pyongyang hat. Yeah Pyongyang hat. Pyongyang
rack. I think there's a there's like there's some article I read like yeah you know some
fucking propaganda piece about like how there's like children children of like
leaders in is it Pyongyang like the biggest city in North Korea?
That's the capital. Yeah so like kids in like the capital like live like they live like
the girls from girls basically. Yeah yeah. It's a pretty normal place.
Oh these these these kids are living like this meanwhile there's Korean slaves all
over the country. Yeah. Is that true? I don't even know. K-pop is Korean slavery. That's
South Korea. That's, but that's where, you said Korean slaves all over the world? Over
the country you said. Oh, okay. I think North Korea people say that, South Koreans like say
they have slaves and then they're like, what, they're like yeah I was in a labor camp and
then the interviewer's like what happened and they're like they tickled me and they made
me smile. Yeah. Yeah, we're pro DPRK here. I honestly, I don't care. I don't care. I don't
really care what any, I don't know what goes on there. I don't care if China is like killing
a million people. China's awesome. China rules, dude. Yeah, I love China more than America.
But I love America probably just as equal as I do China. I wish my parents taught me
Chinese as a kid so I could move there. Yeah. And I trust pretty much any country that will
eventually rule us yeah China maybe like China's like don't be France like
someone Oh Iger Muslim like fine I'll just be normal I'll be like Vinnie Paz
style Muslim then mm-hmm like you're not gonna put you tell me you're gonna put a
hundred million Vinnie Paz's into a labor camp oh yeah you imagine the songs that
would come out of there yeah the spirituals the video crazy row like God
Also, imagine trying to-
Honestly, there would be so many truths in those songs that they would have to kill you
immediately.
Bro, there's not enough fucking rice slop in the world to feed those slaves.
You'd probably be like, "I'm treated like a slave.
My leader should be in their grave."
You'd probably say that.
And then, "You're a knave."
You're naïve.
Yeah, and naïve.
And stuff like that would be probably really hard-hitting.
kidding. They're probably just make more songs about like being in the civil
war and stuff
it's like yeah story. So King Arthur at the round table
Merlin the shit he gave me got me twirling.
It is funny just to be a conscious rapper. I've new run out of Bush Bush
gets he's not the president anymore and then you just have to start doing the
Yeah, you have to be doing the fucking yeah, yeah, you do fucking what's it called the magic treehouse books
Yeah, you run out of like historical events
you start doing the ones where it's like they went to the rainforest to like meet
gorillas or something. It's like not even like...
Was it just to teach kids that like this thing exists?
Did they ever do the future in the magic treehouse? They should have. I don't know.
I used to tear through those books. Yeah, I loved those. I loved them. I used to listen to them in an audiobook when I was little.
I'm smoking dope in an igloo with the Eskimo.
Basically they got a hundred words for snow.
(laughing)
- That was fire.
- I'm a caveman, I'm treated like a slave, man.
(laughing)
I got hit with a rock, now I'm in my grave, man.
- I'm at the Gettysburg address.
This civil war will be the baddest.
- It's cool, dude.
- Freed the slaves, man.
- That's a cool ass gimmick to have as a rapper.
- Yeah, dude.
Yeah, time traveling.
Yeah, that is actually really cool.
Rhyme unraveling.
That's what he does. Vinnie Pat's a creator.
Yeah.
I like that he has a super group that has like
30 white guys in it called Army of the Pharaohs.
That's so cool.
It's really cool.
And they think the Necronomicon is real.
That's like their whole thing.
That's what being a white Muslim
rapper is about. Pretty much.
It's about, yeah, you believe in evil dead.
Yeah, you're like, yeah, we believe in Islam. The boogeyman is real. He lives under my bed.
Yeah, the Ninja Turtles are real.
The Ninja Turtles are real. Yeah, well, he's also the conspiracy.
Yeah, the government's hiding a Ninja Turtle.
Yeah, he's like, 9/11 is an inside job. Godzilla exists.
Yep, I'm a werewolf.
Yeah, plus I'm a werewolf, though.
Werewolves are still the funniest conspiracy theory to me.
Yeah.
People who think that the government is covering up the existence of werewolves.
I think if the government made a werewolf, they would make me one because it's a perfect cover.
That's just so funny over like aliens or ghosts or even like zombies.
Like werewolves is like...
Zombies is like...
Even the creature from the Black Lagoon.
Even that is like...
I would believe that more like splicing human DNA with a fish.
I would believe it's like...
I would probably believe Santa before I believed werewolves.
Yeah, werewolves is like the last...
You don't?
Believe werewolves?
No. Santa?
I do, that's the point.
Well, okay, so you believe werewolves then, right?
you said before before before I'm not at werewolves yet okay Santa my whole
fucking yeah so before means like if like something like it happens like oh
yeah three yeah it's like a war so it's like I can only it it's like a head like
keep all your words three letters right yeah Pat Stu
bid well what's a pid you personal identification those were too long was
that
Identification yeah, it's so good. It's such a funny job man. I wish he never died I stands for ID stands for
Yeah, yeah, but he pretty much died yeah, so all his jokes are ours now yeah
That should be true. Yeah when somebody dies you should just get to well. Did you ever like get like a
Like a joke book as a kid yeah
And then like you realize that like they just like like a lot of the jokes in there are just like yeah
they're just like stand up jokes. They just like take from people. Yeah, there's a
you just do you can do that. I guess. 101 Silly Billy Jokes and it's like like so
this family walks into an office. Yeah. It's just the aristocrats in its
entirety. Yeah, I mean literally though like they're like every once in a while
they read like a joke when there's one joke that's just like so out of place.
Yeah, it's just yeah it's like a Richard Pryor joke or something in the middle of
like knock-knock jokes it's all these knock-knock jokes and then like the
entirety of like Chris rocks yeah it's good of you motherfuckers is in there
why does he why does he keep saying kick it yeah I have to say kick it when I do
the kick it play music yeah yeah did you guys ever do like when you had a joke
book you ever do those jokes to your family yep oh yeah oh yeah dude loved it
Mm-hmm thought I was like fucking I was a king's a comedy dude
Table I've been getting into Cedric recently. Yeah, dude. I've been watching his old stand-up. He's so fucking
He's also that's why they were the Kings dude. He was a king for a reason. Yeah, give him the crown. Mm-hmm
He's a man. I remember my mom. Give him a big gold hat. I
When I was a kid, I tried to I tried to get
this hat. I mean, just so you guys know the normal Cedric the
entertainer had plated in gold. So he can't wear it without
breaking his neck politically. The kings of comedy are not
recognized in awesome land.
They are not treated as kings.
No, that's disrespectful.
You're an acting comedy.
This is the worst place in the world.
You know, you know, you know, like what terrible land, you
know, it's funny.
Awesome land is actually terrible, but terrible.
very
head you literally can't talk slowly because you're too impatient yeah yeah
so it's so guys what's really the joke it's so funny that you carry around that
die even though you hate casinos and you hated gambling there he just thinks it
looks cool no I have the die I have the die on Mikey see I was like a chip no
it reminds me of a good time I had with my friends oh yeah well that's sweet
idiot stupid and you put your die I think I was so upset that I left it at
my mom's house yeah really yeah like you did with the the tiny hat on the boat
yeah yeah Caleb I'm a costume through Caleb like just four year old that yeah
You like threw your head back so that the hat would fly off the boat.
You told an old lady you were gonna kill yourself.
Yeah.
That old lady with the blue colored contacts.
That was the oldest lady I've ever seen in my entire life.
Oldest woman wearing colored contacts.
She was so fucking old.
She was Cameron's like, she literally had like dune like spice eyes.
Yeah she did.
It was so fucking crazy dude.
I think she was.
I think she was a Fremen on that boat sent to give Cameron good luck.
Yeah, she's a friend of mine.
She literally, she was, yeah, I kept running into her.
Yeah, and she kept coming up to you being like, "I just won $400 more dollars."
Yeah.
I was like, "God damn, good for you lady, when are you going to buy more colored contacts?"
That's right.
Old people use all their luck up at the end of their lives at the casino.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, yeah, you don't want to die without any luck left over.
You get a luck buff.
Why don't I have any luck?
At the end of the life.
You got to wait until you're old.
Yeah.
I guess.
That's why I hate gambling now.
I know that when I get older-
hate gambling now. The luck of the Irish is gonna happen. You hate gambling because you
suck crap at it. Once I get so old that my body shrinks down to leprechaun size. How the
fuck are Irish people lucky dude? Irish people's lives are dog shit. What are you talking about?
They're terrible people. There's nothing lucky about Irish people. You guys, you guys, you
guys. Are you okay? You guys escaped. There's so many four leaf clovers in Ireland. You
guys escaped slavery. You guys escaped slavery and were like I guess I'll just drink every
day forever. This is way better than being a slave. And then the one guy who tried to
do anything got his head exploded. The one Irish guy who ever tried to stop being a piece
of shit and do something. What are you talking about? St. Patrick. Yeah, he got assassinated.
He got assassinated by an angry little snake. It was like, "You kicked me out of my apartment
in Ireland." Yeah, that's true. St. Patrick was a landlord. Yeah, all Irish people have
ever done their entire existence of Ireland.
Choose your words carefully.
Just get shit on and fucked.
Pretty much.
And then just make the worst bomb of all time and mostly kill themselves with it.
No.
Yeah.
Are you kidding me dude?
The car bomb deaths?
Yeah.
They got a lot of fuckers with those.
They were still in the car when they set it off.
Oh, I was in the car and I got a key.
Well somebody's got to press the button.
I've never heard of a fuse.
Ireland number one, number one in the world.
Number one is in their pee.
You ever heard, have you ever heard of Crack Boy Mental?
Number one most servile slave.
Yeah.
You heard Crack Boy Mental?
No.
The Irish autistic rapper trying to--
Yeah, I did hear that.
Trying to stop oppression.
I have heard that.
800 years, never again!
I'd like to stop this impression.
Yeah, please don't do it.
Oh my God.
I love Crack Boy Mental.
He's autistic, he has mental in his name?
Yeah.
It's pretty funny.
Well, it's a different meaning over there.
Yeah.
He's bloody mental with his bars.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
And he's got a mental disorder.
How come Pop Smoke can say the R word all he wants?
Well, isn't he dead?
Yeah, but nobody even cared.
I've been listening to you talking about they killed him for it.
Yeah, exactly.
He got the death penalty for that.
a team of young activists
broken a post looks
los angeles you know you imagine
it
the react to the american like that
the news cycle
for like a little like months after that yeah
yeah i think it's a little bit saying the r_ word yeah
and i would really that would with that would start the next civil war yeah
Yeah. But it wouldn't even be state to state.
What? Like the Civil War, it wouldn't even...
It's not even like split up evenly like the states.
It would just be like different houses.
What are you talking about? You know what I'm saying?
Are you saying that...
Are you insinuating that the Civil War would be between mentally challenged people?
No. No?
People who want to say it versus people who think you shouldn't say it.
Oh no, that's a north-south divide.
I think.
It'd be the same Mason-Dixie line, but it stretches up, covers Massachusetts.
That's what I was about to say.
Only Boston. It's like Boston versus Cambridge.
Yeah, exactly.
Boston versus Cambridge.
That'd be cool, dude.
Boston versus Cambridge, and then pretty much everywhere else is on Boston's side.
Yeah, pretty much.
Except for, oh, Boston.
It's like eight neighborhoods.
Boston versus Cambridge and Brookline.
It would be the eight neighborhoods in the world where there's a, like a...
That horn.
You liked the horn.
You think that's an ice cream truck and you follow the garbage truck all around.
I think that the ice cream truck shouldn't play a song.
I think it should play one loud...
One long...
One long, like...
Well, it's easier to hear.
Yeah, like one...
It should play like the same...
It should play like a tornado alarm.
Yeah.
I've saw this before.
but like a tornado alarm that's not like a law ice cream truck should play a
really loud car crash sound effect
so many runs exactly all my pictures repeating
all my god it's a truck the uh... car crash loop
screaming
they should play
well now gunshots when people run yeah yeah
what about the quickly put it's a gunshot what if it's like a scream what
if it plays are really catchy beautiful song
in that signals the neighborhood that ice cream stir by national anthem
that's actually not a bad idea
vision i think they are there are a bit of a large stream trucks that play the
national and turn it up
veterans ice cream
that's my shit you know they only sell the captain america popsicle
the captain america popsicle
and they do sell the like the puppets
do you know if i get those guys i guess i'm here the trial is living in like the
the marvel universe or whatever and as a veteran i'd be so i'd hate captain
America so much dude. He got like he got powered up and he has to fight like like
one guy every year and he's like they call him a troop. He doesn't have to like go
and... I'm at the VA I'm fucking addicted to heroin. I'm trying to get a $200 check to get me
through the next six months. He's the most famous guy in the world. Yeah I have
no legs, no hands. He punched the red skull one time in the 1940s. Yeah. And
and he's easily is the immortal that
i literally has to do is i was in vietnam for thirty seconds and i got so scared
by a guy popping out of a tree that i fell off a cliff here
and i'm all my leg loss every limb that i have
you get a shield
if they have the technology to give the shield they should have been a nice
little cousin
because head-blown haha
why you do what it is make everything out of the shield yeah
fucking assholes well that's the thing is wakanda's hoarding all that vibranium true yeah what kind of
bullshit is that? yeah the u.s should invade wakanda. yes sir let's go. u.s should definitely invade wakanda. yeah facts
well that's the thing about like take the power like what like wakanda's like the secret city
what the hell were they doing during the freaking holocaust
It's a good point. You couldn't have sent a Black Panther over there too?
It's a really good point, yeah.
Blame Africa for the Holocaust?
Go ahead Pat.
This is, we're speaking in MCU terms. So the MCU, I'm a little racist.
We're all just playing pretend.
the MCU did was there also was there Nazis and Hydra or is Hydra just the Nazis?
I think it was there so was there like was there were there like there were
Nazis and they were like were they superpowered Nazis? Yeah I think Hydra was the evil Nazis.
Yeah yeah but then the Hydra really just want to be like evil for no reason.
They don't even have like the whole like Aryan thing. Everyone's gonna be like there's gonna be one person.
Red Skull's not white, dude. He's red, bro.
Like, you fucking hate all these other people. You're the only red guy in the whole fucking world.
There's gonna be somebody who's like mad at us for getting all the lore wrong, and I just want to say to them...
*blows raspberry*
Yeah.
Nerd. Bitch. Fuck you.
You forgot to take your insulin.
You try to correct us. You try to correct us on this shit. I'll fuck your mom.
Yeah.
What?
No, no, oh God. You try to correct us on MCU bullshit. I become your new dad. I'm
gonna fuck your mom's butt. Nothing's off limits. Nothing's off limits. I'm gonna
I'm gonna fucking. I become your new dad and I show you I show your mom my webs
like a spider-man. Why didn't spider-man do anything about Adolf Hitler? Yeah, yeah.
I mean there's so many people who did like totally the Tony Stark doctor
strange this fucker can control the world go he'd go back in time stop the
Holocaust he ain't doing shit it is I know everybody said man everybody said
it a bunch of times before but in like the end of a end game when like Captain
America like goes back in time and he just used it he just like dances with
his girlfriend and then dies. He did nothing to help six million people. It's so funny.
They didn't think that maybe people would realize that they're sending him back. He goes back
to the 1940s. I will say Hitler did a lot of fucked up shit but he also just ruined any
movie that where they go back to the 40s. You can't fuck every time travel thing has to
have some kind of Hitler either Hitler has to have never existed like dude Bill and
Ted. Yeah they don't do crap they just want to go back and smoke weed with
Aristotle. Kill Hitler bro. Yeah and you know they would have the funniest Hitler
kill. Dude. They would kill him with rock and roll. You know what the problem with killing
Hitler is is that uh funny Hitler's son would be become like an evil Batman and
would be even more powerful than Hitler. It's actually better just to let him become Green Goblin's son.
Yeah exactly. Oh yeah. Yeah Green Goblin's like the Hitler in New York City.
It's true. It's facts. Green. Yeah. Yeah. Big-ass green motherfucker. He's a German
goblin. Yeah. What? I don't know. I was gonna say Kraut Goblin but then it's like.
like
crowd goblins kind of a cool
yes a cool cool phrase
yeah
that's me that's me that's me when i get a coney island dog i'm putting so much damn
sour crowd on that
you're a crap goblin basically
and a cap goblin
you could try to go back in time and let hitler into art school to prevent everything but
then he still does all the same shit but all his like battle plans just look way nicer
(laughter)
- It's like a really like,
lovingly painted landscape.
- It looks like a Lord of the Rings map.
- I mean, one of history's most evil people of all time,
but his, I mean, god damn, do you see,
look at this map of Poland.
- Yeah, it's beautiful. - Oh, it's gorgeous.
- Absolutely beautiful.
- We're done.
- We're done?
- We're done, it's been an hour and two minutes.
Let's go for an hour and three.
Alright, I gotta go.
59.
Suck my dick, bitch.
Bye!