you're listening to Israel's number one podcast
this is premium content
if you are not a premium subscriber
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately
*laughter*
I have extremely exciting news for you guys
yeah?
that I've just seen on twitter
um, this comes to us from Eater
everybody knows Eater
oh that's the food magazine
yep
I don't know what it is
see there. Chris Angel is opening a fast casual restaurant called CABLIP, which is spelled
C-A-B-L-P, and it's short for Chris Angel's Breakfast, Lunch, and Pizza.
He named it after me, dude? Whoa!
Dude, I'm CABLIP. What the fuck?
That's crazy. This was reported on 10 minutes ago, so we're
on the cutting edge of the story. Oh my god.
Dude, I mean, this is huge. Which will come out in, I think, five or six
days I mean yes people I don't think anybody's picking up the newest copy of
eater I think we might be I am breaking this news you are yeah why either yeah
y'all don't read either I don't read here where to go either where to eat and
why it matters in the world's best food cities do you think you're like that's a
killer slogan eat eater like the offices you like walk in and everybody it looks
like the clumps. And they're just like rolling around the office.
Yeah. When I hear Eater, my brain immediately goes to like a dark like fantasy like wizard
like an Eater. Well did you hear about their editor in chief of Eater?
No what did he do? Purple People.
Oh no dude. Don't tell me he got in trouble. He's on the shitty media men list.
She's hitting the media monsters list.
He got in trouble.
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, I'm surprised that people didn't see.
She's not going to come out.
Yeah.
I mean, this new CEO, Hannibal the Cannibal, I mean, is a huge...
He's a big step up.
I mean, that's horrible.
But, I mean, what more, what would you expect from a publication founded by Peter the Eater?
True.
Yep.
Yeah.
I mean...
That's a good point.
his one horn you know yeah I don't want to go in too much about that but you know
now that you say that people I think there might be an entire song about him
and how he eats people yeah I'm surprised nobody fucking yeah the info was out
there I hope one day to have some kind of evil nickname like Vlad the Impaler
mm-hmm yeah but I don't have a good name first name for that
Caleb the molester. Don't say that no no not molester or pedophile or any of that crap.
No, you know like molesta like in like Spanish. What does that mean? Is that a sauce?
Doesn't that mean embarrassed? Caleb the embarrassed? That's even worse than being
a molester. I don't want to be a shy pussy. Does that mean...
Oh, upset.
Caleb the upset.
I get upset like Drake.
Oh my god.
I'm reading about K-Blip, about Chris Angel's breakfast, lunch, and pizza.
I mean, like, the best name for a restaurant I think I've ever read.
It's inspired.
He bought a restaurant called Sugar's Home Plate, and he's converting it to K-Blip.
He discovered the restaurant while dirt biking with his family.
Aside from fast casual food, the restaurant will periodically convert into the magic room
with entertainment from Angel and his friends.
Down the road, Angel plans to build Chris Angel's Escape Camp Adventures on 14 acres at the start
of the Logandale trails.
I think it might be on a trail.
On a dirt bike trail.
Oh, okay.
See, I like this.
The restaurant.
I like him moving into...
This is a long time coming.
Him moving into new industries.
You know what?
If he follows the Cableb naming convention, then his Criss Angel's Escape Camp Adventures
is gonna be named Caca.
I mean, it sucks that you gotta get like, like Magic certified and OSHA certified to
work at cave lip yeah like magic inspector comes yeah we have to make
sure you guys aren't using any dark are you are you measuring the wands and shit
excuse me I'm sorry I know you're new here but did you just make did you just
make those loaded nachos disappear yeah I'm sorry you you cannot be doing that
in your first day just store the vegetables on top of the disappearing
rabbits it's actually very unsanitary you realize that right a bunch of guys
carrots there in wizard caps come in and they're walking around with scrolls on
clipboards and they're like we just want to make sure that you know it's all
illusions there's no real magic and they like this scoot the mummies tomb out of
the way and there's a pentagram underneath it and they're like oh no no
this one we're gonna have to write you up for this one yeah this is uh this is
not an illusion and then they write your name down on the scroll and you're
sealed away for eternity it's magic with a K dude I don't fuck with that
Magic, you see?
Blood sugar sex magic.
Ooh, blood sugar sex magic.
Is that like a diabetes type magic?
Yeah, that's what the diabetic menu is called that came with it.
Blood sugar sex magic?
Yeah, it's named after that Red Hot Chili Peppers album.
Yeah, I think maybe we should start making songs like the Red Hot Chili Peppers.
I was saying before this episode that we should do a doo-wop album.
I was going to say we have to drop that as a surprise, but...
Yeah, too late now.
Imagine a world where we do a full 17 track doo-wop album.
I'm thinking it's pretty easy right?
At most...
It's got to be the easiest kind of music to make.
At most we could do six.
At most?
You mean at least?
Genuine, no genuine answer here.
We could make six doo-wop songs.
I could really...
Unless it's covers.
Doo-wop songs are really easy to write.
Covers...
It's all in the same key.
Six originals, seven covers.
Alright, well let's write some lyrics. We gotta get to town here.
Okay.
I think I'm the baritone. I think I'm the bass.
I got some really good low notes.
Yeah.
Can I be, uh...
I can do the pig squeals.
*Badly imitating pig squeals*
Did you just go *Badly imitating pig squeals*
That's not Doo-Wop.
No, it's Blue Moon by the Marcells.
That's Roo-Wok.
And Roll.
*Laughter*
no yep yep uh that's rock what about uh
what about like yakety yeah that's not doo-wop that's got saxophone that's cartoon music yeah
you guys different dude i don't want to write cartoon intros we got i'm telling you peanuts
by frankie valley and the four seasons that's the perfect song for us okay it's got some like
funny noises in it because they go they go like peanuts peanuts and i think we could like play
around with that. I'm not much of a fan of doo-wop. I'm not very familiar with doo-wop.
You're not familiar with doo-wop? No, I'm more of a pooh-wop fan. The music created by Italians
for Italians. You like to listen to your pooh-wop. I like to get pooh-wop-y instead with my peonus.
It's crazy how many doo-wop songs are like that stupid and those guys got like so much
just like get like the like the guys just going like baby baby boom boom boom
boom boom you're getting prime shit - that was like that's how you fuck Betty
Draper did Betty Draper saw that she's fucking fainting dude it's like she's
watching Axl Rose yeah it's so funny to see I mean I really maybe it was probably
hyped up but just like the videos of the people fainting for the Beatles yeah so
crazy I mean you know mistaking like a one of the pleats and their slacks for
some little bit of side pipe mm-hmm that's that's a that'll get a woman's
hi it's we're a lot bigger back then - I mean it's would yeah there's show show
until the 70s 70s when pants started getting tight up top and then huge at
the bottom yeah in the 60s that was like big old fucking big old really big pants
- Pleated slacks, not jeans.
- That's why also you could have, if you were famous,
you could have the shittiest body in the world.
- Yeah.
- You know, 'cause you were just eating like,
you were just eating like whatever,
every food back then was just like Funyuns and Jell-O,
and they would just eat that constantly.
- Yeah, Jell-O was like a status symbol,
it was just to show off how good your fridge was.
- How good your fridge was?
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I don't think my fridge is good enough to do anything.
- Ambrosia salad and like--
- Ambrosia, what's that?
water
It's called like aspic.
A-S-P-I-C.
Aspic is disgusting.
Yeah, that's like when you put hot dogs in it.
Grossest looking foods in the world.
Jello, gelatin
is fucking like horse bones.
Yeah, but it doesn't look as
disgusting. Like they were working really
hard to make it look bad.
Like normal jello, the ingredients
are pretty disgusting, but it
looks fine. I'll eat jello
any day of the week. That's a refreshing snack
- Yeah, I miss Jell-O at the buffet.
- That's a keto night's delight.
- Yeah, but just literally just go to Google images
right now and search ASPIC.
- A-S-P-I-C-S.
Look up ASPICS.
- And just look at any of these pictures.
Imagine looking at this and wanting to eat this.
This is like the most horrible thing I've ever seen.
- I guess in Russia it's like a grandma food.
Like a food your grandma used to make.
- Maybe a grandma food.
You know, like a grandma food, like fudge, jello, aspic.
- Bro, my grandma eats like--
- Beans.
- That bitch eats beans all day, dude.
Now she eats like, my grandma is like obsessed
with staying alive forever.
- Yeah, so is my grandpa.
- She only eats like spirulina and shit.
They should fuck, honestly.
- Yeah.
- We could get a--
- Oh my God, could you imagine?
- A new uncle, dude.
A shared uncle?
- Could you imagine, you and I get a new uncle.
- Oh, fuck.
and you become my cousin yeah you guys get to be related oh my god I found out
in middle school I found out that like one of my closest friends was like my
third cousin you fucking southerner. It was sick dude. You fucking southerners are all cousins.
And the thing is he wasn't even from my hometown he's from Florida and he was like talking
about his aunt in Florida and I was like oh I have a like some relatives in
Florida and then they had the same last name then I asked my grandma and
and she's like, "Oh yeah, that's my fucking great,
"that's my great cousin."
- There were two kids at my middle school
who had the same last name,
and they lied and told everybody
that they were cousins when they weren't.
But they weren't even like friends.
- You should go to jail for that.
- Like how do, like I don't,
how do you get to the point
where you decide to make that pact,
where you together lie to everyone that you're related,
and you don't even like hang out with each other?
Like that's something's going on.
- You know what's worse?
- That's not right. - You know what's worse is
when you are cousins with somebody,
and nobody believes you 'cause your cousin's taller than you.
Dude, my fuckin'-- I never had that experience.
My fuckin' dad told me--
High school experiences, no one believed,
no one believes my cousins were my cousins
at my high school and my middle school
because they were all taller than me
and they all played like football
and like basketball and shit.
Yeah, no way those two came from similar holes.
I'm the only-- It's just impossible.
Boy cousin in my family.
Dude, that's hot as fuck.
(laughing)
That's fucking sick dude.
No.
Yeah dude, 13th birthday party, all the cousins invited bro.
Oh shoot.
What?
No.
That's not right.
What? You didn't read all their diaries?
What?
They bring the diaries to the birthday party?
Dude, I just want to read.
You need to cool off dude. You need to go dunk your head in ice or something.
Yeah maybe.
Before you come back to recording. That's too much.
No.
It was cool. It was really cool.
I don't want that. No that's coffee.
coffee stop dude you're gonna get too caffeinated you're gonna be bouncing off the walls.
You don't need that. You're fine. I'm gonna start hurting your head dude. Stop. I've been just getting full-on panic attacks.
Drink, what's, what's the, what's that, what's that to the side of you?
That is computer duster. Drink that instead. You've already done this. Don't do it again.
Don't. Do it. Don't. Do it. Okay. Alright. I think he's dead.
I had to explain, I talked about last episode how I fucking killed mice and dumped a bunch
of oil out of my third floor window and then got a note on my door this morning that says
"Hey this is Arthur downstairs, give me a call" and he gave me his number and I called
him and he was like "Hey man, did you fucking throw a bunch of cooking oil out of the window?"
(laughing)
And I was like, oh yeah, but it was because of the mice.
And he was like, what are you fucking talking about?
And apparently he was like out of town
and he just came home and there was oil
all over his kitchen.
(laughing)
On his cat.
- Did he leave his window open?
- Yeah, his cat was like covered in oil.
And he was like, did you fucking throw oil?
- You know what that sounds like to me
is that the cat went after the mice
and tracked oil around everywhere.
- He couldn't have, dude.
There's a fucking, I think it went through the screen
in the window.
- Was it like really windy?
- I get, I don't know how it happened, but he--
- Maybe they had their fan in the wrong way.
- He was like, I don't know.
He told me, he's like, I thought that maybe you like
made french fries or something
and threw them out the window.
I was like, nah, dude, I had to actually kill
a bunch of mice and drown them to death.
- That's like, at least he didn't get
dead mice in there too right? That would have been kind of funny. Well if that
happened I would have just said I did it on purpose. I'd have been like yeah man fuck you
call the cops I don't give a fuck. Yeah. Whatever dude fucking pussy ass Arthur
come get it bro. Yeah it was not fun dude. I hate having I want to live on a giant
farm with nobody around me. Right no no no there are no mice on a farm no animals will come into your house.
Yeah, except for the mice. The mice is not my problem. I'm fine with the mice I just hate having neighbors.
You were crying about having to kill two mice.
Right now I'm talking about neighbors.
If you lived on a farm you would sob every time you had to milk a cow.
I've lived on a farm.
You could never farm. You could never be a farmer now.
I've lived on a farm. I'm the only one of us who has ever lived on a farm.
I lived on a farm in Louisiana.
What?
For a summer.
For a summer doesn't count.
You've never talked about that.
It was fine. I worked at a soybean farm.
Okay, there you go. It was a soybean farm. It's not a fucking farm with animals.
That's not a farm.
That is not a farm.
I have more farm experience than both of you combined, probably times a thousand.
No, I've stayed at farms.
My parents' house-
You've stayed at farms?
My- Fuck you!
Animal farms?
Farms with animals, dude.
My parents' house had a barn and we had chickens.
Not fucking soybeans.
And that is way more farm experience.
I don't give a fuck.
Chicken is fake shit, dude.
Way more farm experience than you have.
I've taken care of goats, I've taken care of horses.
You guys don't know me.
You have!
I have!
My cousins have goats and horses!
That's not true.
It is true!
They live in Bakersfield, California!
California you see how red I'm getting this is what I'm how serious I am about farming
It's in my blood you could never we went to your family's houses in Bakersfield
I did not see a single animal you went to my grandparents house. No we also went to
Oh, you're all about my cousin my uncle Tim though. I don't know about his farm house. No you didn't no you went to my uncle Mike's house
My uncle Tim has a whole fucking farm
But now that you ask about that shit or give a fuck about my farm experience or care
I've fucking seen different kinds of animals give birth and I've seen their milk and shit. I'm gonna clean all that out
So you never ask about that?
You just care about it. If I'm
*Gibberish*
*Laughter*
I've seen every damn animal
on the carousel, in real life.
No you haven't!
You've never seen a
griffin.
I saw a griffin on a carousel once.
Yeah, I wrote a hippogriff.
I've taken care of giant sea turtles.
No you haven't!
Yeah I did!
No you have not!
They thought you were one of their eggs because of your head.
I got lost in the aquarium for two years.
I had to take care of all sorts of shit.
I used to feed the sharks.
This is a straight up lie.
You're lying.
I used to feed the sharks with my mouth.
You fed no sharks.
I used to shotgun weed into the sharks' mouths.
I was at the zoo recently and the animals were talking to me.
They didn't talk to you through the glass?
Like Harry Potter?
First of all, it wasn't glass that they talked to me through.
They came out and they talked to me.
You are in a very dangerous zoo.
I let them out.
I did the Harry Potter thing where I made the glass disappear for a minute.
So there was glass.
Mmm.
But then there wasn't.
I didn't talk to them through it.
Okay.
I've been defeated.
Whatever.
Man.
I haven't been to the zoo in so long, dude.
I went to the zoo like two weeks ago.
I know you went to the zoo.
Did you go to the Bronx one?
Yeah.
I went on a Saturday by myself like a fucking moron.
Yeah, I think I think when I when I get older and I like stop I stop having anything interesting in my life
I think I'll probably just get a zoo membership and like go weekly. Yeah, just like I think it'd be
I think it'd be cool to be like an old guy who like knows what all the animals are up to and like, you know
You can go like week by week and be like, oh like you can recognize them be like, oh he's play this time
He's playing with the ball. He didn't do that last week. You can tell the
Zoo employees and they'll they'll ask you to leave
I can't go to the zoo without my mom fucking saying that Rocky quote at me.
The one taken to the zoo, our words love the zoo.
I've never seen Rocky.
I've seen it. I sent the picture.
I thought your mom was just saying that to you. I didn't know that was a quote.
Yeah, it's a quote from Rocky.
My dad made me watch four Rocky movies in a row one day when I was a kid.
He was like, he was like this is what we're doing today. It's nice to come today.
Whatever he was trying to do to you, it did not work.
Yeah.
You ended up a comedian.
It was one of those things where like, when you're a parent who has like your kids for like two days every couple weeks,
you just are like, we gotta make it something, you know, we can't just like fucking do nothing.
I don't know that experience.
Yeah, yeah, oh, my parents love each other.
My parents hate each other.
Why do you think I ended up in Louisiana, you fucking idiot?
(laughing)
Anyway, my dad was like, every couple weekends,
he'd be like, we are watching every single movie
of the worst movies of all time.
So it was like Revenge of the Nerds and fucking Rocky.
- Oh, you watched all the Revenge of the Nerds?
- Yeah, dude, the fucking-- - That's brutal.
That is fucking brutal.
- It was really brutal.
And my dad was like, these are some funny ass bullshit.
- The original, the original's not very good.
those sequels do not hold up at all.
And then one weekend my dad was like, kind of ran out of 80s movies, let's watch extras.
And then we just watched extras.
Police Academy is great. Police Academy 4 featuring Bones Brigade, David Spade.
I pretty much just imagined jacking off during every movie that I ever saw as a kid.
I don't really remember anything about it.
You imagined jacking off with your dad?
pretending my dad was in there and I was pretending I was in the bathroom and
maybe I had some hand soap.
The things I would be imagining in the bathroom right now.
Oh dude.
I would be imagining.
I wish I was imagining stuff right now.
I was imagining myself in the bathroom and then that guy had a thought bubble
where he was imagining something you know.
One actress who was in the background of one scene of Rocky.
Yeah yeah exactly.
From 20 minutes ago.
dude that was a I remember my dad the big thing was that like we never had
anything but like basic cable and my parents got divorced my dad was like I'm
fucking yeah dude I got a spring for all the all this all the Cinemax and the HBO
and shit and then after like five o'clock every night that it would be
caught there be a movie called fuck vampire and Zane sex chronicles yeah
- Yeah, shit like that.
- That would be on Cinemax.
- Or like, do you ever see Real Sex?
- Yeah, my cousins at like 1 a.m.,
1 or 2 a.m. they would play on channel, on HBO,
I forget which one, but it was 206,
where we were from, we used to call it,
me and my friends used to call it channel 206,
'cause it would be a funny game to see,
like to put it on, and then see how long we could watch it.
- Without checking off.
- Yeah.
- Four or five hours, it turns out.
But then there was another one, like my cousin's,
we would like, like when my cousin was like 10,
he would like click to it for like a second.
It was on Zane's Sex Chronicles on Cinemax.
We would click to it for a second,
then change the channel and just go,
(laughing)
like laugh like super hard 'cause he did that.
- Real Sex was fucked up because it's,
you know, you would think that that's a good show
to watch when you are-- - It's not.
- No, 'cause every episode is like,
here's a it's like a journalistic show so it'll be like here's a deep dive into
the fattest people that ever have sex and you'd be like I guess they're naked but
like mm-hmm I don't want to see these butt cracks I watched one of those once
when I was like 12 I think I saw a real sex and it was it was an episode about
like like because all those were shot in like 94 or something like that yeah and
And there was an episode about like an FMV porn game and they were talking to the developer of the game
and like the woman on the screen was like, "Do you want to come to like my fucking fantasy world or
some shit?" And I just remember the guy on the computer like looking at it just like, "Yes, I do."
Dude, they always get the worst guys. You know why? Because no self-respecting like hot guy
would ever agree to be in like a like real sex unless they're a fucking porn star
you know what I mean the only people they could get for that shit who were like so
shameless the most disgusting people of all time just horrible
nerds with tiny fucking balls and wieners and they just thought I mean it was bad
dude yeah it was really bad and then they also did you ever see that show bunny ranch
I did yeah so that was like they would just show prostitutes having sex with like
clients and then and they were just the weirdest fucking freaks in the world and
they'd be like they would just like show all this shit on TV and the guy would be
like can I smell your crap they'd be like no you can't that's against the rules of the
bunny ranch. That's rule number one. Yeah that's rule no crap smelling.
No toilets in any of the rooms. They took all that off of like the Cinemax
like streaming services. That makes sense they're awful. Yeah it's so they like they
took all that shit off and it's like yeah fucking good like that that shit sucks
yeah there was like who is like I have to get an HBO login to watch porn now right
you know I mean that is to be the thing that used to be like what you had to do
yeah well that's cuz you could get you could get evil viruses from the computer
right yeah I wonder what the I wonder I wonder if kids nowadays there's still
still there's shows like that for because I feel like there's that type of show is
not doesn't really exist anymore it's kind of like made for like 15 year old
boys yeah it got it got either those like it got split off into like half half of
it is just on the internet now and the other half is like like just Game of
Thrones yeah sure is that type of thing yeah that's a good point I guess they
did when they phase those shows out now yeah now they still make those shows but
They're based on books now.
That's the real difference.
- You started making really sexy shows like Girls
with tons of hot nudity.
- Yeah.
- My roommates made me watch Girls with them.
They've made me watch Girls with them twice.
- I've made myself watch Girls twice.
- Yeah, you're like a huge fan.
I've watched two episodes of Girls
and each time I've been like,
- Black.
- Like I fucking hate this so much.
- It's funny that you're such a Sex and the City fan
and you turn your nose up at Girls.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Why is that?
Cause they're the same show.
It's different.
Why?
Because Carrie and the girls are in Manhattan.
And they're in Brooklyn, you're right.
I'm such an idiot dude.
Shoshanna and the girls are in Greenpoint.
Shoshanna? You wouldn't say Shoshanna and the girls.
I don't fucking care to learn Lena Dunham's character's name.
I actually can't remember right now.
Yeah.
Dude, I've been having such an awful time.
Critter? I don't wanna know Critter's real name.
Critter?
(laughing)
- You've never seen that?
That like--
- Call her Critter?
- Somebody on Twitter like compared Lena Dunham
to Critter from those books.
- What books?
- What the fuck are you talking about?
- Look up Critter from books on Google.
- Okay.
Crit, Critter from books.
Oh, this guy.
- Lena Dunham looks like Little Critter.
- Yeah.
- I forgot about Little Critter.
- Oh, that's kind of funny.
- I didn't forget about him,
but I forgot that was his name.
That was like one of the funniest comparisons of all time.
Yeah, that's a pretty funny comparison.
It definitely rakes up there.
Yeah, top 10 funniest comparisons.
Yeah, that's definitely one of them.
Apples and oranges.
I mean, look at these two things.
Do they have any similarities other than fruit?
Yeah, I think they're sweet.
They're round.
There's plenty of reddish.
That's true.
There is plenty of things you can compare
with apples and oranges.
Yeah, they're on the same side of the color wheel.
- Except for a green apple and a green orange.
- Don't even get me started on a green apple.
What a fucking sorry excuse for an apple.
- Granny Smith? - A Granny Smith apple.
- Granny Smith apples are pretty good
depending on the time of year.
- It's funny that pretty much every apple is good.
Pretty much every apple is good,
and the one that just sucks ass is called Red Delicious.
- Red Delicious is horrible.
- It's a terrible apple,
and just the fact that they had the audacity to,
like all the other ones are just like names like the Macintosh. It's also great
that apples are at the forefront of just turning fruit into candy where just like
they have bred these apples like honey crisp apples. A honey crisp apple is like
has like as many calories as like Oreo cheesecake. Really? It's just like a
fucking like it's like an actual dessert. That's not true. But it's like has way
it's like so like disgustingly sweet and it's so fucking fake and it's the best
I mean I will eat them at any opportunity.
I grew up...
Like a Honeycrisp or a Red Delicious Apple, they like, to another apple, they look like
the family from the Hills of Ice.
100%!
Like that's what they are.
You know it's also, it's such a bad sign, like the state of fruit.
When you like walk into the...
Listen, you guys hear about this, it's fucking...
Listen, listen, the state of fruit, it's getting out of control.
You walk into the grocery store and like any fruit or fruit should be the same forever.
Vegetables and fruit should be the same forever.
You walk into the grocery store and there's a brand new kind of fruit.
Yeah.
That is fucking crazy.
Yeah, that's nuts.
Yeah.
And then you get home and it's and it tastes like cotton candy.
They have cotton candy.
Yeah, the cotton candy grapes.
What the fuck are these scientists doing?
In my hometown, like I grew up like the high school was right next to an apple orchard.
Yeah.
just like go though I think the worst type of the my least favorite type of
apple it might be Macintosh just because those are the ones that like we would
have the Apple fights with you like you just go to this like fuck you go through
the woods you go through the orchard and you just take whatever apples off of
this guy's like fucking you like a whole fucking farm in the town like the whole
town was basically built around apple orchards and we would just fucking steal
them from this guy just pelt them at each other.
It's funny, yeah,
like apple picking
is an activity that you can only do if you're very young or you're very old and
any other age it's the worst thing in the world. Yeah, at fucking sixteen, seventeen
you gotta throw them at your friends. Yeah, you throw them at your friends.
You try and get the wasps that are flying around the rotten apples to
get your friends too.
Yeah. You walk around, you twist your foot in a gopher hole.
That's why I like--
And they have those bars of soap on the tree
that you're not supposed to touch,
but you wanna touch 'em.
Like, I don't think you can pick
like Honeycrisp apples, really.
Like, I think you only pick the shitty apples, right?
Yeah, I think so.
Honeycrisp, they're probably--
Cooking apples.
They're probably like, grown on like a server farm.
Is it Macintosh apples?
Like some indoor thing.
Like a Bitcoin mine.
Yeah, yeah, they're like--
A monolith.
Beep, beep, beep, boom, boom,
Apple done, apple picked.
Is it Macintosh?
You can probably pick them online.
Is it Macintosh that's like the kinda small one
and you bite into it and it kind of has like a,
it kind of--
- A disgusting mealy actual apple taste.
- I don't know.
- Yeah, it's like, it definitely mealy.
It's got kind of like a paper skin.
- That's like what an apple is.
It's not like a--
- Like all these fucking cross bread, like--
- Yeah, I feel like I'm eating like an ice cube
when I take a bite.
Why is it always cold?
You can leave a fucking Honeycrisp apple
in the blistering heat for hours and take a bite
and it would be so cold.
yeah it's like it's like a it's like a uh... uh... burger king milkshake
but it's not a a son of a jackley
yeah it's just not they did the uh...
and cuties to what the fuck they don't have to use our talked about you this
is your
i don't want to get back i don't know i don't i don't want to get so mad at you
and i don't have this fucking conversation i i don't know if they're
the wikipedia page for red delicious and this is how you can tell that you should
not be eating these listen this is the first of that not even the first
sentence
the first is up to the first comma
the red delicious is a clone of apple cultogen.
What?
Dude, this is why they don't, this is why no country on earth will give scientists like,
like, will make it legal to like clone humans.
Yeah.
Because they saw what they fucking did to apples.
That's, they're gonna start, yeah, cloning humans and just be like, we're gonna make
a thousand Neil Patrick Harris's right now.
That'll look, that's what it's gonna turn into.
Yeah, and they're gonna taste like cotton candy.
Yeah, yeah.
They taste exactly like Froot Loops.
Yeah.
It says here that the apple became a victim of its own popularity.
I'm reading the Wikipedia page.
There's also a sports section, which is so funny to think about.
I never really considered this, but apple orchards, the fucking farmers are probably
cross-pollinating and making their own apples all the fucking time.
Yeah, but they're not evil.
True.
I don't know, maybe the orchard I grew up on, or grew up around was like an evil orchard.
Like the old farmer's man's, his face falls off and he has a robot body behind it?
I don't want to talk shit about Max Apples.
I hate Max.
I'm on the Golden Delicious, I'm on the Wikipedia page for Golden Delicious now, and they have
a picture on this page that's just a picture of a seed, and the caption is just "seed".
(laughing)
- Yeah, but they have this sports thing
and it's like, they have all these inventors.
Shotwell invented the Red Delicious.
- Which even--
- You can get a plant patent.
- Yeah.
- That's so fucked.
- See, any fruit Wikipedia page
that reads like a viruses Wikipedia page
is gonna be a diabolical kind of fruit.
I just think that those,
they must have fucking fluoride in them or something.
- Yeah.
There must be some kind of mind control aspect to these very sweet apples and oranges.
Dude, I'm waiting for the fucking barbecue banana right now.
That might be a game changer, dude.
See, 'cause yeah, all these fucking vegan like, like uh, like-
All these fucking vegan.
I didn't mean to say it like that, but like all these fucking like vegan like fruit meats
and like wheat meats and shit, like all these like meat substitutes that they're making,
they're gonna breed like a fucking like, like some type of plant that tastes exactly like
ribs.
You guys eat the 3D printed meat they're doing now?
No.
That's where I draw, that is honestly...
I probably would.
Why not?
That's where I draw my line.
It looks like fucking yarn, dude.
Have you seen it?
Yeah, but why would you...
I'll eat anything you put in front of me as long as it's natural.
Okay, but you...
I mean...
Or candy.
Both of you guys drink so many energy drinks and you're gonna turn up your nose at that?
Like come on.
Well it's different because that's...
It's not different.
An energy drink is like actively destroying your insides probably.
No
Yes
You you saying Patrick specifically you saying you'll put eat anything put in front of you as long as it's natural is like I can't let
That slide yeah
That's not acceptable every day you drink an energy drink. That's called like
the KKK
It's a knockoff of red called white hood. I've been switching. I've been switching from energy drinks to energy sparkling waters. Oh
In my head that's healthier. Yeah, it's probably not I don't know what Taurine is
I don't know I should have that much
Honest anything that's like also artificial but they're like this is the healthier version of it
I like it's absolutely more like less healthy. I just haven't discovered it yet. Yeah, it's like diet soda. Yeah
It's like yeah exactly. Evil dude. All that shit is just fucking... dude I remember
when I was in LA and I was drinking like Coke Zero all the time like I
would drink like four of them a day my leg would just hurt every time I had one
like my left leg would just hurt so bad. I do remember you talking about that. And I was just like well
fucking what comes with the territory I guess of being the greatest Coke Zero
It's so fucking funny that I drink all these like energy drinks now because
literally like in high school I learned about aspartame and like like
aspartame giving you cancer and shit and I was like fuck that shit I will never
like I didn't drink energy drinks until I was like 20. Yeah the thing is... I didn't do
any of that shit till I turned 20 when it's like not like like not even
fucking like when you're a kid and you're drinking energy drinks it's like kind of
cool but then when you're like 20 it's like what the fuck is that like your
favorite thing is fake mango flavored battery acid yeah the only thing is
here's the thing cuz I didn't like the taste of coffee too which in hindsight
it's fucking the reason why I drink diet sodas is because the dying of cancer is
to me the third worst thing that can happen in my life the other two are
are number one, get insanely fat,
and number two, not be able to drink any soda.
(laughing)
So, that is like, I would rather fucking die of cancer
than have either of those happen to me.
So I gotta go diet, I really have no other option.
I've been forced to do this.
- What do you mean you've been, no one's forcing you.
- I've been forced to be in love with diet soda.
- Diet soda, you could just drink fucking sparkling water.
You could just drink like a polar.
Hmm, sparkling water.
What is it missing?
Oh yeah, fucking sugar and soda and flavor and Sprite and lemon lime.
Sprite is sparkling water.
What?
Sprite's sody.
That's a sody pop.
It's clear like water.
But it doesn't...
But it's not...
You're right.
That is a sparkling water.
I'm sorry.
Once they figure out how to make ginger ale clear...
Mm-hmm. It's yeah change me clearness is the thing I'm doing this clear is good
anything's clear is good imagine imagine a clear Pepsi that's why yeah didn't
they bring that back or do people say did I the ones on eBay that make you
vomit they brought back crystal Pepsi in like 2018 2019 and I drank that like a
bunch just tastes like Pepsi right yeah but I liked it cuz it was like oh it's
Crystal Pepsi. Because you can fool somebody. Yeah. Yeah, your roommate walks in, "Hey man,
what's up?" I'm not drinking Pepsi. I'm drinking a different, like Sprite or something. You
believed me. You definitely believed me. You look at your fucking face, you stupid you look.
I saw it in your eyes. Look at your fucking stupid face. I can tell, the last thing you
thought this was, was fucking Pepsi. You're surprised. You're fucking, you're pissing
your pants. I see piss in your pants. Yep, it's your squirt, the Crystal Pepsi. You just
squirt a little on it. Yep, see? You peed! Yep. You pee-peed! And you didn't see that
because you blinked while I did that to you. And don't smell it because it won't smell
like Pepsi. Just trust me. Oh man. Yeah, they should be making other clear foods so I think
that is maybe a trick to, that might be the next step in tricking people into eating unhealthy
things. That's just aspects, huh? Oh yeah, I guess you're right. Aspects, putting stuff
and clear stuff. You guys see the aspic I sent to the chat here?
Yeah. Picture of the shrimp. The aspic. Yeah. It literally just looks like the thing.
Yeah. It has like legs and arms sticking out of it. Dude, I don't fuck with crab at all.
Really? I don't fuck with that crap. I like crab. I think crab is the seafood
I've eaten the least. I found too many. Unless you count crab ring boots. I found and smelled too many dead
crabs on the beach on Cape Cod like as a kid to like ever like that did not really
enjoy crab. Did I ever tell you about that when I went clamming? It's like a dead crab is just
disgusting like it smells horrible and the way that it like decays it's just
like they're nasty. They're nasty as hell dude. I used to catch crabs with my shirt when I was a
kid. Yeah? Yeah and I was vegetarian but I just thought it was fun and I think that's
probably why I don't like crabs is because I remember my mom like put after
I caught a bunch I would she would like put them in a pot to boil them and
They just make like a like a very loud whistling noise
Screaming it's fucking horrible dude. Yeah, dude. I fucking I like caught like a bucket full of clams
Once when I was 11, I just went up the beach that my uncle taught me how to catch clams
So I was like, all right, I'm just gonna do this all day
It's pretty easy to catch clams cuz you don't have a lot of choices
All you gotta do, you just dig super fast and you just gotta like scoop up like a-
you'll- eventually you'll pick up like a handful of sand that has a clam in it
and then uh you just throw them in a bucket, bring them home, steam them.
Yeah, maybe I'm a little braver than you but catching a crab is like a battle.
My mom was making lobsters recently and she brought the lobsters home
and she put them on the ground to let my dog play with them before she killed them.
I was like that is the most like fucked up like-
That's fucking evil dude.
Nicest person I know in the world, but that's the most fucked up horrible thing I've ever seen somebody do
Can you have a lobster like a pet? Can you like walk it around and shit?
I mean, yeah, they'll run around if you put them on the ground. One of my friends in high school at a pep rally
He bought a lobster and was like pretending it was like the basketball team's mascot and then he tried to bring it out
In the pep rally on a leash and killed it
The thing about killing lobsters too is like you either like boil them to kill them
Which is like you know fucked up in one way
Yeah, or if you want to kill them fast you do the fucking you like take a knife you go like
It's not good dude
They do not have a good life
Live forever - like yeah, like like it's not kind of there in the matter their misery. Maybe yeah
I mean, you know something is it's not like you can like take a lobster
That's like about to die like they have to be like they gotta be happy
Have you and have you seen like in the fuck every like couple of weeks?
Every year there's like a new rare lobster. That's some yeah, some like weird color size
Yeah, like that like a couple weeks ago
It was like red lobster had like this spotted yellow lobster that they named freckles
yeah, and there was like a like a like a purple lobster or like
Someone called it like a lesbian lobster. That's like the store. That's what the
Kill it it's it's Funko pop for 70 year old guys for me. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah
That's really like a man like a guy from like fucking Bangor yeah
Guy who gets pissed off whenever Stephen King is mentioned because he's like we're not really clowns a lobster I
Finally collected the rare lobster. Yeah, I got this one's got spots on it
Scream yeah, I fucking I found I'm putting it in my no. No, I don't have too many fucking yeah
I grew yeah, I actually grew up with Stephen King. I used to throw rocks at him at school
Dude, wait
True fucked up dude. He probably Cindy Lou who he wrote Christine after me cuz I hit him with my car
Stephen King young his son his son looks fucked up - oh, he just look he just looks like a nerd Joe Hill
Yeah, Joe Joe Hill. That's his pseudonym so that nobody realizes who he really is right and then you fucking look
This could be
Yeah, just like being Jay Leno's daughter, right?
Walking around Hollywood high with that big-ass chin. It's gonna be unlucky, dude, man
I mean, yes, Stephen King young just looks like yeah, just a nerd but like then you see him in a
in creep show when I first saw him in creep show I had no idea that was him so
I guess I searched Stephen King as a kid one of the one of the images that came
up as a thumbnail from the Dick Cavett show and the video title is Stephen King
I was warped as a child they put him through a wormhole and that's yeah they
give him the idea for the shining dude whatever I was crazy he's the best I
I love him.
Does he have some dark past?
Were his parents evil or something?
He's from New England.
True, I guess you're right.
Yeah, that's something he didn't know.
I guess he was like the first one who got out of New England.
Yeah.
Yeah, so nobody really, everybody's like, "Oh, what the fuck?"
"Who the fuck is, what the fuck is that?"
That's the thing is, if you grow up in, yeah, like a town like Bangor, you're gonna come
out, if you're not like, you're either gonna be a townie or you're gonna be obsessed with
monsters.
Like those are the two options.
Right, true.
you is like like you just live in you live know what the fuck's going on in Maine
yeah you live in creepy creepy world yeah like Maine and like northern New
Hampshire northern parts of like New Hampshire and Vermont and then like none
of good like Connecticut and Massachusetts and Rhode Island are all
like a little bit like cosmopolitan I guess yeah you only have you only have
two neighbors and one of them is just a giant dog. Right. Like half of the year I
guess I guess it's kind of the same in like the Cape like half of your year is
just like you're in some fucking shack. Yeah all the like all the four corners
like states of the US are fucking just they're weird. You know what I mean?
Like any I think yeah there's something about being like Washington yeah and
like like those like it's crazy just how many fucking like gun nuts there are in
like Portland yeah and so many senators and presidents in Washington yeah
Congress - that's true that shit's actually true that is very fucking
stupid that we have two Washington's yeah Washington should be named
something else why should I call they should have called Washington DC at
least like Washington plus mm-hmm well I guess that's what the DC is for they
should have called it the capital the capital exactly Washington the capital
yeah that would have been a way better name or just I mean just make up a name
dude we also don't need it just leave it just have it be in in fucking Virginia
yeah it's just Virginia that's whatever I don't care let Virginia have it they
don't have anything else doesn't matter well cuz I feel like I talk too much
shit about New England just now yeah let it be known let it be known we love
Best part of the country.
Best part of the world.
Uh-huh.
Better than the South.
Better than the Pacific Northwest.
Better than the West Coast.
So you think the South sucks just you wait?
No.
For what?
Just you...
I don't know.
We can talk shit about New England because we're from New England.
I'm from the South.
But if any of you fucks try to...
If I find out you're not from New England and you try to say some shit about it...
That's right.
New England sucks cock.
It's terrible.
People love to talk to us and try to make Boston jokes.
It's like you better you better shut up. Yeah. Yeah. Hey, there's gonna be trouble your parent
You got you better at least have a fucking cousin from like Springfield or something. What unpronounceable block you from?
Yeah, completely people
impossible
doubts
To talk shit on Boston, then you find out that they're they're from a town named the hooded Huntsman's Haven
White power, Texas
There's no white power Texas.
Listen, I don't really fuck with Texas because that's the West. I don't consider that the South.
The South is like...
Texas is the South.
I have love for all parts of the world.
Personally.
Yeah, actually, I'm talking about the global South when I talk about the South.
So you guys probably feel really shitty for saying it sucks now.
I didn't say it sucks. I just said I have love for all parts of the world.
I mean, if you talk shit about Rhode Island to me, I won't care.
was yeah also yeah i should be clear when you say new england i'm just i just mean massachusetts
and maybe new hampshire if patrick's also in the room yeah i mean new hampshire uh like parts of
maine massachusetts i don't i won't i will not go i won't go to bat for maine i don't if you make fun
of maine that's fine i i like maine i like me but i would i'm not going to defend connecticut i don't
give a [ __ ] about rhode island yeah rhode island's funny to make fun of connecticut [ __ ] off you
Half of your state does not even-
Half of your state does not support the fucking socks, kid!
I love being here in New York City, the best single city in all of New England.
Makes me very happy.
You fucking take that back.
I love just staying in New England, you know, moving from Boston to New York is a great-
If you're a Yankees fan from Connecticut, fuck you.
Are you gonna cry?
No, I'm not gonna cry.
Kinda seems like you're crying right now.
I'm not crying, I'm just standing my ground.
You have never watched a sport in your life.
What are you talking about?
The only reason that you should ever go to Connecticut is if you have to pee on the way
from Boston to New York.
That's it.
True.
That's a good point.
Connecticut does suck cock.
Connecticut is a terrible, terrible...
Is that the...
Wait, no, that's not...
That's where Rob Zombie lives and he tried to get that skate park shut down.
That's where they invented that fucked up clam pizza and shit, right?
Yeah.
What are you doing, bro?
What is that, Frank Pepe's?
Yeah.
What the fuck is that?
Frank Pepe's opened up at the Arsenal Mall and my dad, every time I see him, tells me
that he wants to try it.
And he tells me that they have really good clams there.
Frankly, I'd rather be fucking putting my pee-pee on this damn pizza than putting my
tongue on it, because this shit tastes like crap.
Yes, sir.
What are you doing?
Do you want to put your pee-pee on stuff that tastes like crap?
Honestly, it might be good.
I would...
Does it taste like crap?
Yeah.
It might be good.
I don't know.
I don't want to talk shit about Frank Pepe's.
I've had it.
Yeah? Well I haven't had it.
I might like it.
I don't think you would, dude.
You don't know me.
Yeah I do.
Talk to you every day.
Eat with you all the time.
What do you mean I don't know?
I know a lot about how you like to eat.
Fucking dumbass.
I know you wouldn't like a fucking clam pizza.
It tastes like shit.
The thing is about clams on a pizza.
Clams are boogers.
you put them on a pizza it's just like fucking you're talking to your ass
pizza you're talking to right clams seafood for me good as hell yeah oh I
clams some of the best you can have is like Pat has been frozen in time yeah
that's the other thing is it like boogers are they do there's a reason
people like to eat their boogers they're salty so like if you could like trick
somebody like you know that they like will put breast milk and food in like
France yeah like you could trick somebody in the thinking that boogers
were something tasty. Yep, I've heard of that one. Sorry, I google places to eat fresh milk
almost every single day and recently they started doing it in France. Fried clams at like uh
what's that place? Woodman's. I used to go to Arnold's I think it's called. Yeah Arnold's rocks.
Yeah great great great. Arnold's in Eastham. That's the that's the place you go when you're on the way
to the Cape for my family. We always stop there when we're going to the Cape when we left the
cape we always only place on the Cape I've ever been is Provincetown and that
town Pete Town fucking sick Pete I love Pete town it sucks dude what are you
talking about everything there is like $300,000 it's like yeah it's like I go
there to buy anything you go there for like lunch it's it's like Salem dude you
just go there to be there it's like yeah exactly it's like Salem is rockabilly
Israel and P-Town is like the other like it's like the other quadrant in the in
the like you know the compass. Provincetown is like... it's like... it is dude I was there and I came to that realization.
Provincetown is great because it's if you ever want to see like like the
closest thing to identical twins that fuck each other you go to Provincetown
and there's a million there's a million like like billionaire gay guys who have
like perfect they follow the exact same workout regimen and they get the same
like yeah like surgery and they dress exactly the same and then they just fuck
each other it's awesome. You know who has a house in Provincetown is John Waters. That makes sense.
And when I learned that in high school and like we would go yeah like I wanted
to like like see him there I wanted to see his house so bad. Yeah and also like
like the funny thing about that place is they they will put a drag show in
anything yeah you'll be at like you'll be at a library and then you'll find
yourself you're at a drag show now I was at a I was at I was in Provincetown I
was at like some store with like my ex-girlfriend and we like we're standing
in there and I was like they had like an Allman Brothers tapestry and I like made
fun of it a little bit yeah why do they have like a fucking Allman Brothers
tapestry and I heard like a like a couple of seconds later I heard like a lady
like like breathe in and then she left or like she's about to leave and someone
who's like you're right like what's going on it's like an employee and she's like
yeah I have to go it's just um there's some bad energies in this and then she
like went outside and just started like meditating it was so fucking weird yeah
yeah it's it's a it's a very weird place you walk into like a like a butcher
and they'll be like we're doing the MF Doom drag show right now.
The MF Doom drag show?
And you, and by the way it'll be $80.
That would never happen in Provincetown.
It happened.
They did a MF Doom drag show.
They did Jackass the drag movie.
That'd be sick.
They did that.
I think Salem probably has one of the highest like noise pollution levels
during the day in New England because it may not be like a city,
like there might not be like trains and shit running through it but every single
person that is in Salem just feels the need to narrate everything they're doing
out loud. They're all the type of people who look at strangers and go "so I guess
they're playing music in the street now huh?" Everybody doing that to each other.
Is Salem one of those places, I know Provincetown is, but is Salem one of those places where you can just
fucking have your balls out all the time? No I know Provincetown definitely is but
Yeah. Not Salem.
There was a record store my family and I went to.
I think it was like 13.
We went to Provincetown and my mom brought us in pretty quick because there was a surprise after the store.
I cannot imagine walking around Provincetown with your family.
Oh my god.
We'd be in a lot of trouble.
My dad, there's a place called the Fudge Factory.
My mom and dad made us take a picture under it.
I bet they thought that was fucking funny.
So we go like we went in the record store like we're just looking around then we went out
my mom like showed us that they had like this big like paper mache dick in the in the window
and there was a bunch of like Barbie dolls sitting around it like it was like a pool
party and she was like isn't this funny?
It's like yeah.
I don't know why we had to go in the store like that.
There are two different kinds of tourists in Provincetown.
are gay guys who go there because they like it and they feel like it's like you
know and then there's like Boston fucking morons who go because they think it's
like the zoo and they walk around and they're like everybody is fucking dressed
like Borat this is funny as fuck it's very cool what a beautiful city yeah you
do hear a lot of like there's a lot of like Boston accents down there they're
like yeah very Eugene Eugene Merman had a really good joke about it I don't want
to just like yeah Eugene Merman's joke yeah I mean why even bring it up you
know well it's really fucking good it's all right but don't say it but it's
really good right look up Eugene Merman best gay jokes compilation and you'll
find it I don't know that's pretty hard to scrub through yeah it's a 15-hour
video of every joke he ever did yeah oh come on
come on dude he's a good guy yeah he's a Boston staple dude mm-hmm
anytime he's a lot of Bob's burgers there's a lot of jokes about Portsmouth
New Hampshire too so I have to I got a show respect to my man Eugene Portsmouth
- I feel like this is the only city I've been to,
or the only town in New England I've been to
that feels like the South.
- Really?
- Yeah, kinda.
- So we got it.
- Not as far as the people there,
it's just the look of it.
- Just the buildings?
- Yeah, it's like a weird,
it feels like it was transplanted
from like Georgia or something.
- You would think like Concord would look more like that.
- I think I would.
- We should take Caleb to like the Berkshires,
or like rural New England.
- Rural New Hampshire?
- Yeah.
- I gotta take you guys to North Carolina, bro.
- Put him on a farm, see how he's gonna fucking react to that.
I will fucking immediately activate.
We could run up on the farm.
You don't understand.
We could, oh yeah, we, no we drove by it.
Let's start trying to drown all the baby animals.
We drove by it when we did that stupid fucking video episode, but like the farm that I like
grew up kinda next to.
The apple orchard?
That one?
No, not the apple orchard, but like in my old neighborhood there was like a guy who had
like his horses run around, he had like this whole like, this whole like fucking farm thing.
It was like, you'd like grow wheat or any shit.
And I think it was wheat, I don't really fucking know.
Because I called it the farm,
but it was really just 'cause the guy had two horses.
- Yeah.
- And we used to like feed the horse--
- That makes a farm, that's fine.
- Yeah, it had like an electric--
- More than one animal that's not a dog or cat.
- It had an electric fence surrounding it.
- So you're saying if you have one cow,
that's a pet, right?
- Yeah.
- But two cow makes a farm?
- It's not that it's a pet, it's just that it's not a farm.
just a house with a cow. I think the requirement is you have to get some sort
of material, some like Minecraft from these animals. Well yeah, that makes it a
farm to some degree. Okay that's fair, I think that's the second requirement.
Alright, third requirement, you need a big-ass hat. It needs a red barn.
Four overalls, red barn. It did have a red barn. So, well that might be actually a
farm. Broken down car somewhere. Yeah, broken down car that the guy just like
always has he just like keeps unscrewing and screwing the same bolt with a wrench
all day. Yeah I've been working on this Bessie for about 20 years. Covers it with a tarp
because he thinks someone's gonna drive a hundred miles to come and steal it
somehow like out of the barn. Yeah. Dude. We used to play a game with the the fence
because it had an electric and barbed wire fence around it. Oh dude electric
fences I mean. We used to play a game where you could just see. It's a holy grail here.
Who could touch the electric fence the most? Yeah, because it doesn't it's not like it's a low like it's a low shock
It's not like it's not pain like I felt I felt the worst
What you're if you put your hand around it it just goes like
Yeah, I went I one time my dad all of his outlets in his house were completely exposed
He just like never put on the face plates to him
So one time I plugged in my phone when I was like 15 and I got like
Electrocuted so bad. I like couldn't remember like the last couple minutes
And that was way worse than electric fence.
Electric fence is like a hand buster.
That makes sense.
They're not trying to kill the animals.
They should though.
They should make one that kills the animals.
Yeah.
Because then they'll really learn their lesson.
Yeah, that animal's not going anywhere.
Is it true that if you pee on an electric fence, your penis turns evil?
That makes sense, right?
I mean.
I guess.
It would conduct it.
It's a stream.
Yeah.
if we tried that or not. Then you did get electrocuted.
Yeah. You absolutely got. It shocked my brain.
You got completely electrocuted. Yeah. Yeah.
God. Well, now I like, now I can't go back and try it because it's not my home anymore.
We'll find an electric fence. And the guy-
Showing up, a 23-year-old showing up, you're like, "No, I just want to try something. I
used to live here." I'm actually trying to conquer like the fears
I had as a kid. So this is like the big one. So if you could just let me touch your fence.
the thing they do in horror movies where you show up to a house and you're like, "This
used to be my childhood house." But instead of like asking to like look under the bed
or something, you just go out back and start peeing in the yard.
You walk up and you're like, "Yeah, I actually used to trespass here when I was a kid. And
I like come back there and piss on shit."
I think the guy got rid of the barbed wire, like the barbed wire fence and like he just
had like fence posts up. He got rid of the electric fence. Like I think the horses died
or something but it yeah we like the electric fence was gone after I was like
seven or eight so I never I never got to like never get the true electric fence
yeah I never got to like yeah exactly like that's so sad dude yeah yeah you
missed out I had a friend who lived right next to a farm and had an electric fence
like 10 feet from his house yeah we we would just go up and slap it because we
didn't really want to like hold it very long but we would just go fucking slap it
And he turned into a juggalo pretty shortly after that.
That'll do it.
That's a direct correlation.
I mean, who knows, man.
Yeah.
I think it probably had something to do with it.
No way it didn't.
Supercharges your brain, makes you more intelligent.
Yeah, makes you way too smart.
The only way to go is down with the clown.
That's right.
Alright, bye.
Bye.
*sigh*
[BLANK_AUDIO]