you're listening to Israel's number one podcasts
if you are not a premium subscriber please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately
we can't we can't miss this
watching a video
it's called the goat and your mom
uh...
oh I've seen this
quack like a duck
Yeah, it's fun. Is any of it picking up? I don't know people hear it
It's hard to tell cuz I'm a guy touches his balls guys are hitting his penis
That guy looks good
He's making it about him though. Yeah, you know
It's about uh-huh. It's about music this guy. He's already yeah, is that just a random fan? No. No, that's his brother
Yeah, it's his brother Calicious. What's the name of this video?
so people can watch it. It's called the goat and your mom quack like a duck. That's enough
of goat and your mom. Yeah, it's enough of videos. Hold on, let's get into the part.
What? I can't hear any of these saying. Yeah, it's not. I hate you. I hate you so much. Wait,
this is the part. Yeah, here it is. Guys, this is so funny. It was. You gotta listen
the lyrics here. Wait listen listen this is where it gets good. No we're not. YouTube is over.
YouTube. I will get in front of the TV. Yeah. I'll block it like a mom. Don't. I'll do the mom block.
I'll get in front of the TV. Oh my god this sucks. I dare you to watch something now. Yeah.
Maybe Patrick just shouldn't be on the podcast anymore. That's not true.
If he can't handle not watching a video. You're getting kicked off this episode.
- No, this is a big-- - You're going back to the--
- We're still gonna record in your house.
- Yeah.
- But--
- You can't use my TV then, 'cause I'm gonna be--
- We don't need the TV.
- We have our own TV.
- Where?
- In our brains.
- You don't have a TV.
- We also put one under your bed.
- No!
- Yeah, we need an extra TV here.
- We go under your bed and watch.
No, you weren't.
- We have contingency plans. - You weren't on the second
level, we have another level under the floor,
under your bed, where we have a TV and a popcorn machine.
- It's official, dude.
- I'm rocking a machine that makes money.
I wish I could go there.
You can go there but it costs you $100 per minute you're down there.
What?
Yeah man.
We're actually renting it out right now.
That's roaming rates.
I wouldn't go down there then.
We have our own wifi that's way better and has a cooler name.
You would want to go down there.
Even if it's $100 an hour dude, I'll tell you what.
I wouldn't want to go down there.
I'll tell you what man.
Xbox.
I have two.
Do you have an Xbox original with Halo on it?
No.
But I have Xbox One.
You don't have it?
Oh that's so weird.
We have Xbox compatible.
of Xbox one Xbox 100 no 100th Xbox it doesn't come out yet we do it hasn't
come out yet there's an in 65 down there did you guys did you guys have
like did I felt like kids at my school didn't know what Nintendo 64 was and I
just remember talking to this kid Owen one time and I was like I was trying to
like make friends with this kid and then he said like I was like oh yeah I was
playing Nintendo 64 at my home and he was like yeah well I was playing Nintendo 64
at my home he said I have a Nintendo 100 I was like damn it's literally just a
joke we do all the time yeah and then I just remember it specifically because
someone next to him turned to me and went you know he's lying damn I was I
remember liar and as a kid I told everybody that I first day of school in
third grade like I'd gone to a new school and I told everybody that I yesterday
had gone skydiving. Damn. I was like eight years old. That's pretty cool. Like that's
I think that's illegal. You can skydive as an eight-year-old. Yeah you can. Yeah you can.
Because I did it. You get strapped to your mom. Yeah. Yeah I do get strapped to your mom
when I go skydiving. I do. You get strapped to Caleb's mom. No. Because she's the parachute because
she's got no bones. She's billowing. She has giant billowing folds of skin between their arm and
legs like a flying squirrel. She glides to the ground. No she doesn't. Yes she does. I do
that with your mom. She glides from tree to tree. Your mom's like a sugar glider. Yeah.
Your mom's... Because I call her sugar. What? That's what I call her. It's not reciprocated
though. Oh that's fine. Yeah. Because she actually calls me F-A-G-I-T. She calls me
F-A-G-I-T. But in a loving way. That you should be really jealous of. I don't care. I'm going
do the rest of the podcast like a ventriloquist while I drink this water.
Out of my collector's Ghostbusters cup.
Ghostbusters cup.
The Ghostbusters.
So this is better than not.
This is better than the TV.
It's better than the TV.
Yeah.
It is better than the TV.
You drink tea?
Two verse one.
Damn.
Okay.
That's called a majority report.
Yeah.
Sam's Seder.
That's what they do on majority report.
Have you guys seen Spitting Image?
Yeah.
I just watched all these videos last night.
They did the music video for Land of Illusion by Genesis.
That doesn't help me.
I don't even know.
I don't know what anything you just said is.
What?
Should I pull it up?
I know what an illusion is.
No, the video is like Ronald Reagan and they're like, the whole, it's the video is like the
Ronald Reagan puppet and he's like with his chimp and stuff and it's like Phil
Collins is telling Ronald Reagan that he needs to shape up or the world's gonna
end and it's all puppets. Music has never changed anything about the world. No.
It's true. No song that anybody ever wrote. What about Hurricane by Bob Dylan?
Hurricane caused Hurricane Katrina. Hurricane by Bob Dylan let Bob Dylan say
the N-word. True, that did change the world. Yeah. That was huge for white guys.
it's like Dylan had two periods there was when he went electric yeah and then when
he said the n-word when he went n-lectric he broke the color barrier
with the n-word yeah you know who else says the n-word you know Gino Marino
you know him from Deftones? No. You don't know Deftones? No. Alright nevermind.
You know Jello Biafra from the Dead Kennedys says the n-word in Holiday King. Marilyn Manson says the n-word too.
my granddad Pete. Yeah, who else does that? Yeah, he loves it dude. I don't think I've
actually ever heard him say it. How many white people have said the n-word in music? Zero.
Eminem got in trouble for it back in the day because he said it about a scorned lover.
Yeah, if I'm like some... Didn't, not white people. He'll be funny in the middle of Kim,
just just the Edward like man yeah she's not white well John that's true he's not
white yeah yeah yeah he's in the end of property yeah who else has said it
ill bill ill bill has a song called owner bill called white and then the
inward boner bit Oh Elvis Costello says white yeah in Oliver's army yeah ill
Bill and Elvis Costello, two legends of the game.
White musicians who said the n-word.
Oh, here's a list.
How about you turn that brightness up?
Because I don't want my computer to die while we're recording.
Why don't you just plug it into the wall?
I'll just turn the brightness of my eyes up.
Which white entertainers have a hood pass to say the n-word?
That's quite interesting.
Let's see here.
Krayoshan, I guess.
2012.
Oh, is that V...
Oh, because this was about the V-Nasty thing.
V-Nasty, yeah.
I remember this. Let's see here. Quentin Tarantino. What white people have the
hood pass? It's just Andy Milonakis. Yeah and then also the picture of the
author. I just want a list of John Mayer. Oh look at this list of white people who can say the n-word. Oh there I am in the middle.
Oh kind of weird, kind of weird how I've been allowed to say this. I'm gonna
to accept it graciously but it's a little bit weird I just doing so much research
on this John Mayer but he doesn't look like he said it John Mayer didn't say
the end said my dick is sort of like a white supremacist yeah I've got a
Benetton heart and a fucking David Duke cock yeah he said that he would never
fuck a black lady whoa yeah Neil Brennan that we seek a new
Neil Brennan was the guy who co-wrote The Chappelle Show.
And he's one of those guys like Michael Rapaport, who's like,
they're white comedians, but they're like, "Yeah, black people fucking love me. I may be white,
but man, I'm really black." Like Chris D'Elia. It's the same thing.
Yeah. It's like, what's that fucking... never mind.
Yeah. Neil Brennan has...
It's like that fucking whatever, never mind.
He has like a whole 15-minute chunk on his special that's just him like...
And it do an AAV.
yeah and he's just like yeah i'm like the blackest guy on earth probably and uh people are like whoa
say it i think he does say it actually yeah yeah um let's see here your white chet hanks used the n
word yeah chet chet hayes baby yeah yeah pretty awesome we are the golden globes that video is so
funny um and his mom and the carita wilson in the comments of the instagram video and she's like
"Oh great job buddy!" It's so obvious that like Tom Hanks just does not give a shit about Chet.
Yeah I can't wait to have a rapper son. Yeah. It's gonna happen. Oh I can't wait till I teach
my kids only to speak in patois. Yeah. Yeah, pigeon. Got little white kids running around
fooling like "Excuse me can I have the candy?" "Papi!" They call you Papi. Yeah.
um yeah there's no i can't homophobic i can't find a list um we don't need a list
this is oh no i mean a list of celebrities who said the n word in songs okay well we have two
right here but these i want right here celebrities who have used the n word jay-z
Gina Rodriguez from um... Oh yeah I remember that. J-Lo. What? J-Lo? No. In 2001 J-Lo said it
in the Ja Rule song. All right that's it. I'm never jacking off to her big ass again.
That's Lindsay Lohan. Lindsay Lohan. How do you not know who Lindsay Lohan was? She looks bad.
She doesn't look like herself. Yeah that doesn't look like Lindsay. Justin Bieber. I thought that
that was Lindsay Lohan. Yeah. Yeah, Justin Bieber's a girl. Yeah, Madonna. What? Madonna
says it in... It says she referred to her son Rocco as an n-word on Instagram. And it says,
"I am sorry if I offended anyone with my use of the n-word. It was not meant as a racial
slur. I am not a racist. There is no way to defend the use of the word. It was all about
intention." Jesus Christ. "It was used as a term of endearment toward my son who is white."
[Laughter]
Yeah.
That's pretty awesome.
Why can't everyone just relax and I call my white son the N-word?
Sean Penn's son, Hooper Penn, Hopper Penn.
Oh, Hopper Penn.
Sean and Hopper Penn were on the--
Lisa Lampanelli.
--the Steve, the Jackass, or the-- what the fuck?
--Johnny Knoxville episode of Evil of Am.
Oh yeah?
Yeah.
Because I remember Sean Penn showing up in that episode just being like, "Who the fuck
is that?"
[Laughter]
I had no idea who he was.
How about his son?
Yeah, it was just like, "Sean and Hopper Penn are here," and then I looked him up and I
was like, "Oh, he plays I Am Sam."
Sean Mayer did actually say it.
Oh, he did?
It says here, yeah, he said he used the N-word in a Playboy interview when talking about,
of all things, having a hood pass.
Nice, dude.
That seems like the right place to use it.
Dog the bounty hunter, I'm not surprised.
Dog the bounty hunter, baby.
No.
Yeah, Eminem, Charlie Sheen.
That was a classic one.
Yeah, didn't he say, "Create Sean"?
- He said pack of beep.
- Yeah, he did a Gibson level kind of thing.
- Gibson was on here.
Elvis Presley.
- Whoa.
- Yeah, so that's all the celebrities--
- He actually invented that word.
- Yeah, he stole it.
He stole that word from black people.
- No, he made it and gave it to him.
Just like, "All right, roll."
- I'm just gonna let this slideshow go.
I don't know what it's--
- That is, these are pictures of Stacey Dash.
(laughing)
- Oh yeah.
- Oh, no.
- I don't know what this slideshow is about,
we're just letting it roll. Jesse Williams. We're letting the good times roll. Don't know who Jesse Williams is.
He's the guy... Mitt Romney! It's a picture of Stacey Dash. It says Mitt Romney. Here's a picture.
So it's just it's just it's just the thing talking about how Stacey Dash is a
Republican. Yeah. Okay. Yeah she likes Mitt Romney.
Yeah, all right. I'm gonna yeah close out of BET.com. Yeah
It's his home page. Yeah. Yeah, I like to stay on on top of things
I don't say his name, but there's a kid that showed up to auditions and a white kid showed up in a BET hoodie
Sick. Yeah. Yeah, pretty awesome. I would have done that when I was like 16. Yeah, I would do that tomorrow if you got a
You would wear it like every day. Oh, yeah. Yeah, I would wear it and try to show off that you were wearing it
Yeah, I'd be like hey, I'd have a I'd have my jacket unzipped but only in that area
Yeah, go is kind of a lot of the round with your fist. Yeah, and how come I would zipped everywhere else?
Yeah, break the zipper. So it's like it's like a Superman. Uh-huh
Yeah, you jump into a telephone booth with shoe polish
No.
[Laughter]
Yeah.
That's what you would do.
If you got to be too funny.
And I come out, I walk out and I just go home.
[Laughter]
I just go home.
Yeah.
And I just open the door, sit down on the couch.
Eat chips.
That's the whole.
That's the hero.
And then I wake up, I wake up and I have a stain of my face on my pillow.
What happened last night?
What happened?
I don't know.
What happened last night? Oh my god I must have blacked out and then I wink at the camera.
I must have blacked out. Yeah. Pretty good. No I wouldn't do that. I'm a... You absolutely would
do that. I would not a racist. You would do that. You would do that every day. You do do that. No I
don't. You do do that. No. Yeah I'm thinking you do it. I'm thinking you do do. Yep. You better
take that back right now you son of a bitch. He'd be doing do do. I don't. I'm gonna kill you cowboy
style with a gun. No way. With a gun with six shots. Yeah and you have sex with Heath Ledger
even though he's dead yeah i would yeah why really why because why because i had
the story of from having sex with him i would totally get on this is not happening
right this is not happening with roy wood jr so here's a time at sex with heath ledger's
was actually health ledger yeah health yeah so um he is so dead right yeah
and it's and i fucked him all right thanks guys everybody have a great night yeah where's ari
Shafir where'd he go Ari I I don't think you should be doing that with your face
did you should not be putting that makeup on your face
Kobe tweet no everyone got mad at no what did he say I don't remember yeah I
don't know he said he said something along the lines of like Kobe you were so
you sucked like major and I'm glad your daughter is dead too and everybody he
had like people canceled shows at like places he was gonna play in LA it was
pretty awesome that's nice I hate that dude yeah his whole thing is like what
did he he had the amazing racist or whatever yeah this whole thing was just
like oh my satire is just agitating black people into hood and see yeah he
did Joey salads yeah he was originally a proto Joey salads yeah where he would
just like go into a black neighborhood and hire like a black dude to come out
and like do like a like a fake stage punch on him in the face yeah and then
afterwards he'd be like man I'm never going back to the hood again that's
crazy yeah yeah and Joe Rogan was like I need to get this man on this podcast
every single episode yeah I need to have him on here and now here we are mm-hmm
here we are thanks for coming out Ari yeah yeah you are on the show now yeah
that was the joke I was making. I just remember Dom's dad almost got tickets to his show at the Wilbur for free and he was like
"Who the fuck is this guy?" Aaron's mom saw him at Fringe without knowing who he was and was very upset.
Yeah. Yeah, which makes sense. He was upset to be at Fringe? No, she was upset to see him perform. She's very anti-semitic.
yeah no she is Jewish so and she was very uh... She hates Ari Shafir's big Jewish nose
yeah yeah really bummed her out. Yeah you should call her the amazing racist yeah yeah she was mad
I just remember getting shown an amazing racist thing when I was a kid and I was like why would
that guy do that yeah what are you doing to the XLR cable? I'm just squeezing it. Stop.
That's it makes his voice go high. Yeah
Don't that's why the
That's probably why the other one kept breaking. No, it's not true because you're fucking jacking it off the whole time
I wasn't jacking it off. That's what you do to your penis is you just squeeze it like like with your heart rate
Yeah, you squeeze a little bit. I have a good story, but it's kind of visual. Okay, there's this
kid
at my middle school who this is like I heard this story like through another
person so it's definitely just not true but um yeah he uh he apparently he
jacked off in the back of his like he was sitting you know there's like a
third row of seats and some like SUVs he's sitting in the third row of seats
and it's like we're just driving with his family on like a road trip and
jacked off in the back and they're like why did you do that what like people were
like what are you and apparently he he said that he jacked off like this oh my
okay so he did he did a he did a tp a Rockefeller Illuminati triangle with his
fingers and then his yeah he did he put is that to his fingers together and then
his penis was in but was in the little v-shape that's probably like the most
realistic way to jack off yeah realistic yeah you make it close to a pussy yeah
you make oh I see what you're saying yeah yeah well no cuz it's only that
it's really the top is a way to jack up with the best graphics yeah it's like
that yeah there was a I had a kid like that there there was always like a in
middle school there's always like the weird jack-off kid yeah like guilty as
true yeah and it was always me but there are weird jack-off kid told me that he
fucked his shampoo bottle and obviously I was gonna tell everyone immediately
yeah we were at lunch and he told me like he fucked his shampoo bottle and I
was like what the fuck you fucking shampoo bottle dude and then you try it
what did you know I would go to try it I'll probably try that yeah yeah but you
don't tell anyone that you're gonna you tried it or you don't tell anyone well
if somebody asks you you try I'm gonna tell them did you try it if you're
jealous yeah I'm gonna go on this is not happening until the story of how I tried
Yeah, it was too big.
But my dick was too small for the opening.
Whoops.
Yeah, that's what everyone kept saying.
And that's my story, thank you.
Everyone kept saying he had like a small thin penis after that.
Yeah, that's why he didn't try it.
I have a small thin penis.
I don't have a small thin penis.
My penis is like a spaghetti strand.
Angel hair.
Yeah, it's a strand of horse hair.
Yeah, it is.
It's a mare's hairs.
Mine looks like a...
Yours looks like a beetle.
Beetle.
Yeah.
Yeah, yours has pincers.
Yours looks like a tortoise beetle.
Wait, look at this beetle.
This is...
Mine looks exactly like the inside.
I don't want to look at my penis.
Mine looks like an inside out vagina.
Yeah.
It's perfect.
This is what Patrick's penis looks like.
It's completely clear.
It has a molten core.
It looks a little bit like a ladybug, but it's slimier.
Here, this is like this one.
The golden tortoise beetle.
Google the golden tortoise beetle.
That's what Patrick's penis looks like.
Mine is speckled like a jawbreaker.
And it's many layers.
I was laughing though, just imagining just a guy getting kicked out of the mall for eating
a jaw, like one of the big jaw breakers, too weird.
You're being too weird about this, man.
Just like, just a guy, just like sitting there just licking it, like it's sitting outside
of like a Forever 21.
This is what my penis looks like.
Sir, what are you doing?
Sir, you can't do that here anymore.
I'm trying to lick a single tongue-sized hole into the middle of this jaw breaker.
This is what my penis looks like.
A tumbleweed?
No, it's a...
Yeah, because you can't see it through your massive pubes.
You have too many pubes and they're all, they look like Bob Marley's hair.
They're long and they're black tentacles.
Yeah.
They're badass, dude.
It's cool.
This is just making me want to watch The Mummy.
Yeah.
These beetles.
Because they have the scarabs.
Whoa, look at that thing.
Ooh.
That's awesome.
I'm saving that to my desktop.
You should upload just a screen recording of your computer during the episode because
there's a lot of stuff people can't see today.
All right.
We should become a visual podcast.
We should become visual artists and start painting.
Let's buy like a house.
Let's buy an easel.
And then get like a studio.
Yeah and paint the walls outside with Trump equals dump just on every window.
Yeah.
Because like the ugliest house ever.
Every artist house like has like in the front lawn they have like just a bunch of signs that
just say -
Pete Buttigieg.
Yeah.
There's a bunch of like portraits of Pete Buttigieg like nailed over the windows.
There's a poster down the street that's like a picture of like a bunch of SS guys, like Nazis
and like -
This is the one next to the seven?
Yeah, it just says like, "If Trump is reelected, this could be the reality."
Yeah, who the fuck - it's someone all around Austin just hangs up those posters.
Can you imagine that guy in the public library just like photoshopping a bunch of Nazis together?
And people would just walk by and then -
There's a - at school in one of the bathrooms, there's a political cartoon on the end of it.
inside of a stall. It's so funny. The Monopoly one? Yeah, it's literally just, it has a picture.
It calls the school Emerson University. Yeah, it messes up the name of the school and then
it's just a picture of a Monopoly board and it says like, it says like, like pass go,
collect tuition money and then it has like Emerson with like dollar signs and it's like,
they're taking your money. Yeah, it's a school. It's crazy. It's like the properties are just
just like the names of the dorms. It's like this is a great political cartoon.
You're really saying something here. You fuck yeah except you pass go and you
don't even fucking get any yeah. Well, you have to pay money. Whoa yeah, go
yeah, Christmas. You know what the best way to resist yeah, and all the houses
those your friends yeah, yeah, that's right your presence yeah, yeah, free
parking that's those are the classes right and community chest. That's right.
that's lunch. I can't believe this. Yeah. Yeah, we need to do something about this.
We need to make a political cartoon. We need to put a political cartoon in the
bathroom so you can look at it while you shit. We need to do something about the
principal. We need to go on Judge Judy and tell them there's something seriously
weird about our school. I think if all of us kids group together and we sued the
principal we would win. I think we might win. There'd be enough testimony. Yeah, we need ten
minutes longer on lunch yeah we want to put just got breaking news from CNN
Tyler is going to detention they've ruled in favor of the kids in the issue of
putting Mountain Dew and all the water fountains when yeah that's my heaven
that's right why they now they got fruit in the vending machines yeah I'm gonna
put a fruit in the vending machine Patrick no that's right yeah a thousand
dollars to get him out yeah we're gonna have to call your mom she's gonna have
to give the vending machine a thousand bucks.
- That would not happen.
- I actually took a--
- The vending machine would be too small for me to fit.
- I took an HTML programming class over the summer
and now I know how to do stuff like that.
- You don't know how to use the vending machine.
- No, I actually do.
No, you can actually get anything that you want for free.
If you walk up, press zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero,
zero, and then just select something, dude.
You can get it for free.
I'm serious.
- You press the number, you press the price backwards
of the item and it gives you two of it
and it shoots the money out.
- Here's what you do.
So you go out and get money out of the...
And it comes out really fast, so you have to be careful.
If you use like the T9 keyboard on the vending machine thing,
if you type in jackpot all over the place...
If you go to the back of the vending machine, there's actually a USB port.
If you connect your computer, you can download the snacks.
I'm serious. If you walk up to the keypad...
I uploaded all those snacks, I downloaded them from the vending machine
uploaded all of them on Pirate Bay.
Oh dude. Snacks for all! If you go up to the pin pad on the vending machine and
then you take out your phone and you dial 9-1-1 and then you call them and say
yeah I'd like for you to come arrest these snacks they'll get them out for
you. Yeah. And then all you have to do... Did I ever tell you about the time I did that?
Yeah I did do that. I went to I had to pay off I got a ticket for I hopped the
the the tea. Nice. Tried to get it on for free.
Hopped the train. And I got caught. Style. And uh
fuckin' I had to pay like a hundred dollar
fine to the MBTA. That sucks. That's like the only place that I
I had to turn it in in person cause uh
I had till the end of the month to pay it off. And I
went down to the MBTA like police
offices. I had to get a money order. Went down to the offices
and then I just went to their vending machine like the police
vending machine I got a thing of peanut or pretzel M&Ms and then...
You made your money back. Yeah I was sitting there waiting for the friggin the cop to come
out like the the sergeant to come out and like get my money order and I like
ordered peanut M&Ms or pretzel M&Ms and it wouldn't come out and I asked the cop to get my pretzel M&Ms out of the vending machine.
cops have that power yeah he like was hitting that's part of it'd be funny if
that was a part of a police officer's duty is like protect serve and also you
deal with the vending machines no he was serving me yeah yeah and yeah and I was
protecting my snacks from him because I don't want yeah yeah he was like he's
like snack tax and he tried to take one of the M&Ms out I still do that I would
grab his gun yeah yeah if that man if that cop touched my snacks I'm fast
enough grab his gun and hit him yeah I'm fast enough I grab a gun I shoot his
when you grab I shoot his hands so he drops the snacks and then I put my other
hand down so I catch them before I hit the ground shoot a hole through his hand
so anytime he tries to eat snacks and then I fuck it that honestly that's why
that is a pain worse than death what imagine your hand fucked yeah every time
Every time you pick up a candy piece to eat, it falls through your hand like a ghost.
That's like Sisyphus.
That's what ghosts are like.
That's why ghosts are so angry.
That's why they say "boo."
I will never die if it means that I can't eat candy.
They're booing because they're crying because they can't eat candy.
They're saying "boo hoo."
Where's my Skittles?
Tropical flavors.
Have you seen the sweet heat Skittles?
No.
Doesn't look good at all.
The ones that are spicy?
Yeah.
Who would eat a fucking spicy Skittle?
You would, dude.
you probably definitely will yeah and I see it and seven I had it for free
trying to bait us who would eat this skittle oh you do it a delicious spicy
sweet so weird yeah he's reaching but I'm some as a joke reaching behind
ourselves with the skittles like the stinky jelly beans who would hide a
giant stash of spicy skittles under their bed who would do that probably
just like a regular guy now yeah I don't know I'm very normal it's like a normal
You guys would do that, right?
Yeah, we would yeah, I would I never say no to candy. It's true
It doesn't matter no to that candy
You gave me a candy and you said kill this tastes like the stinkiest poop in the world rolled in the most
Disgusting crap, but it is candy. He would eat it. I would eat it. You'd eat it with his mouth
I do with my mouth because I would say well
I all I heard was candy and me know where candy goes and I'd pop it you pop that shit
you eat no candy I do eat candy what's the last candy you ate last candy I ate was a
KitKat cinnamon about six days ago six days ago yeah you don't eat candy dude
cinnamon KitKat is really good this guy eats candy once a week. Is it like a Japanese one?
or um a Japanese guy gave it to me but it's an American candy. Baller status yeah that's
right I got to touch a Japanese one that's cool they used to have a fish
market. I used to have a Japanese guy at my school I don't know what happened to that guy
Ah shit, I wonder what happened. But they used to have a Japanese like fish market by Spikes Hot Dogs.
Nice. And they sold like peach Kit Kats there. Yeah, they have a green tea Kit Kat. Yeah,
those are the matcha ones. Yeah, those are good. That's what green tea is.
Have you ever had that? That's what green tea is? Yeah. The sweet potato.
Matcha's just green tea powder. The purple sweet potato. I didn't know that. Kit Kat.
I haven't had that. I haven't either.
Have you ever had the crap flavored and poop styled Kit Kat? I bet Patrick likes that one.
You guys have the wavy poop lays?
Have you ever...
They're really bad. They taste like poop.
It's not good.
You guys ever had liquid lays?
Have you ever seen at a Chinese restaurant it says like stinky tofu?
Oh yeah, yeah. There's at
Dump Calf there is stinky
tofu in old pot. That's
Dump Calf dude. Stinky stinky tofu
with pickle at Dumpling Kingdom.
Yeah. Love stinky tofu.
You guys went to Dumping Findoom.
We did not go to Dumping Findoom.
Kung Pao chicken feels like Bruce Lee to fucking Kung Pao.
More like Dung Pao stinking.
To my stomach and my ass.
Dung Pao stinking.
I'm a guy too.
I got General Gao, it was very good.
That's because you were respecting the military.
That's true.
Yeah.
You're rewarded.
Dung Poo stinking.
God, that's so far from the original thing.
It's like nothing.
Yeah, how about Crap Fart House?
Kung Pao Dung Poo.
No.
Dung Poo does not sound like Kung Pao.
That's why it's funny.
You'd have to say Dung Pao.
How about dung cow? That's better. No it's not. Dung pow chicken. You can't even say it.
You said dung pow. Kung pow chicken. How about that? Okay. And it's delicious. That's not
funny. It's funny to me. Hey Pat. What? Kung pow chicken. That's pretty funny to me. Well,
guess who's now the new guy off the pod? Yep. General poops chicken. Woo! Yes! Okay. Alright,
now he's back. We should design a whole Chinese menu. Just of poop. Yeah. Instead of dumplings
it's dumpings yeah poop pizza pooping dunk pooping dunk that would be bad yeah
Joe poop pizza Chinese poop yeah I had a tikka masala pizza the other day
speaking of freaky diarrhea poopy crap Allah mm-hmm yeah I'm gonna get that
again it was really good yeah Tiki Malala whoa whoa it's a Indian restaurant
called Malia Obama there was there was a guy in my there's it there is a Chinese
place in my hometown called Yao Ming. It was so funny as a kid. It was called Yao Ming.
I was like, "That's a guy! Come on!"
There's a place called China Garden. My little brother used to have like a
slight speech impediment when he was younger.
Where he would talk into Chinese accent.
Yeah, where he would talk to, yeah.
That's cool.
But we used to say that he would say "Gina Garden." He used to get very mad.
Whoa.
I think I told the barrack story on here. Yeah. Where he called me Fatrick. I said it was
barrack. Yeah. Said he was barrack and that means poop and he cried. Yeah. He called me
Baleb and said that means a stink weiner. Yeah. I'd probably cry. Stink weiner. Yeah.
I'm sorry, are you hungry now? You gay guy? Stink weiner. Stink weiner. That sounds delicious.
mind if I do I'm sick yeah I've been sick for like three years through I threw up
this morning cuz I cuz he drank three white claws no I drank like it was a
variety pack and I drank most of them you're not supposed to mix the flavors
yeah that's what makes you throw up oh my god oh it was really bad go before
raspberry I threw up it was just clear clear those clear liquid nice yeah water
with chunks in it. Chunks of white claw? Chunks of water. Chunks of the can. Yeah. Shoot up the can like a goat.
Yeah, and for some reason I was vomiting all morning. Yeah, I don't know what made me so sick.
White claw doesn't usually hurt me. He didn't, he just ate the whole box.
Unhinged his jaw and ate it. Have you ever eaten a pack of like a penny? Yeah. I ate a quarter in the pool once.
I ate a quarter. I played this game where I'd throw the coins at the bottom of the pool.
I hate them. No, no. Playing this game where I would be in the pool and I'd just eat coins.
I made a quarter one time. I had a quarter in middle school and I freaked the fuck out.
I thought I was going to die. Yeah. Yeah. And then like a few weeks later I had an MRI for
a thing and I was like this MRI is going to rip the quarter out of my stomach and like
kill me. And I like told the technician, I was like I ate a quarter a few weeks ago and
they were like yeah you're fine. I ate a penny and then I was like freaking out and I went
told my dad and I was like and it was a perfect joke I was like dad like I ate a
penny and I was like eight years old and my dad was just like oh cool now you're
worth one penny like damn you man and you fucking yeah I ate the quarter
because I was swimming up while the quarter was going down and you can't
with your mouth closed. I opened my mouth because I was like what if I catch the coin with my
mouth because I was like trying to like make the game more fun and then I like caught it
in my mouth while I was swimming up and it just like went down my throat. And out your
ass immediately. Do you guys remember pooping the quarters out? No. I remember pooping the
the penny out yeah yeah cuz you see through it cuz it landed in my brother's
well yeah and he's like I think there's a penny in this yeah no I just remember it
being like kind of a bad poop yeah and I looked in and it was it was covered in
shit yeah you used your inspector you picked it up and you went yeah yeah you
said this has to be worth more than one penny I just get put a pile of shit on
the on the counter I was like yeah I love going to the dollar store yeah dollar
store is still rocks there's just no one near me there's one right that's like
um there's not my younger siblings like thing with my dad is to go to the dollar
store that's like what they do on the weekend to like hang out it's not done
so I go with them sometimes great they just have like DVDs that are just like
yeah yeah mysterious DVDs I got got a copy of of Theodore Rex for a dollar ooh
And you can get like the Bible for a dollar and shit.
You can just get a bunch of shit.
It's great.
I don't remember if I got this.
Toy gun.
Yeah, exactly.
Toy gun sharers.
I don't remember if I got this at the dollar store
at Goodwill, but it was called Gemstone Adventures
with Jerry Sisk.
That's cool.
That's just some guy that just like buys gemstones.
I got an awesome DVD from the dollar store one time
that was a creationist kids show.
Yeah, you get a lot of good stuff like that.
And I watched it.
I was a kid though, and I just wanted to watch it.
You can get books too.
Yeah.
You can get like household.
I get a bunch of notebooks and shit there. That's how I get my school supplies.
Yeah, that's where I go for my meat.
Yeah.
I go there, I get a dollar pound of chicken.
Yeah. I take it home.
Yeah.
It's a perfect, beautiful green chicken.
Have you seen?
That's right. Yeah, gray and green with like yellow fat parts.
Yeah, it's beautiful.
Yeah, it looks great.
It's beautiful marbling on this chicken.
Yeah.
Just a fucking--
Whoever painted this chicken.
Yeah.
Have you ever-- have you seen those videos? It's this guy called the Wolf Pit and he goes
to--
Yes.
he'll be like feeding 50 people for 60 cents and he'll go to the dollar store and he'll get like a
oh there's a different guy no the wolf pit does these videos he does those yeah and he gets like
i only watch his what what are we eating series but he'll make like a like a disgusting beautiful
gravy yeah that's how we talk have you seen the thing have you heard on one of his videos he's
like he's like uh because all the hands that you see have fingernail polish on it yeah and he's like
I've had a lot of people asking recently about the fingernail polish in my videos.
I'll have you know, I'm not a woman. I, because of a degenerative disease, have
not been able to use my hands properly. So I have my daughters or my wife prepare
the food. Like, can you do another YouTube channel where you just talk about whatever
is wrong with you? Like, how can you do every other part of this but not the-- you can't
touch the food? Yeah, yeah. That seems like you-- that's cheating. Exactly. That's
what I tell it it has a woman's touch in it yeah come on that boosts the food at
least one level food tastes so much better plus one woman what's that a
woman made this yeah a woman's time was taken up by this you're telling me a
woman fried this rice yeah do you have any non poop items we have a woman fried
Rice. Yeah and then we have poop Red Rice. Yeah. Sorry the cat's running around.
Yeah. The cat is trying to end the recording. Get the fuck out of here.
Where's he going? His house. Man they walk so funny. It's so it's so crazy.
They still, we were talking about it earlier how they just look like a layer
before a cat dies. Yeah. And then Caleb said "finally I can see how a cat moves."
I heard that from the bathroom. I started laughing in the bathroom.
I've been thinking about like... all my whole life I've been thinking about
what is a cat doing under all that fur? And now I finally get to find out.
What if a cat took off its jacket? Yeah, what if a... wait, okay. What if a cat was naked?
Okay. I'm thinking about it.
Yeah, I can't stop thinking about it. Why? You're not? I'm not, because I'm thinking about
important things like money. Now, what if I told you it was a guy cat? Are you thinking about it now?
thinking about it even less. He's thinking about it. I can see it. I can see it. I'm
thinking about if the guy cat was a girl cat. I can see through your eyes and both
of the guy cats are turning into big t-bone steaks in your imagination. Yeah,
because I want to eat it. No, because you want to have sex with it. No, I want to eat it. You want to
eat a t-bone steak and then have sex with it. That's what happens to me. Yeah, that's a perfect night.
When I walked down the street. The perfect Friday night is to eat a giant t-bone steak and then have sex with a boy cat.
I meant the T-bone steak. You're fucking about the T-bone steak.
You know that little circle part?
I want to eat a big steak and then fuck your cat.
The little circle part that they push out in the cartoons, you use that as a jack-off machine.
Circle part?
The circle bone of the steak.
Oh yeah.
You push it out and you fuck the meat in the middle.
I push it out?
Yeah.
You fuck the bone's marrow-gina.
I had a friend in high school who had two girl dogs, or he had one girl dog and one boy dog.
his mom used to say puppy gina
Talking about like the dog. Yeah, my friend's dog said something was wrong with the dogs puppy
My friend used to call
Puppy gina is really terrible. This lady used to call her dogs pussy, which also sucks but called it her coochie
Yeah, she's itching her coochie. I
I don't want to think about it.
Just don't say it.
Just don't talk about it.
You're literally ruining dogs' vaginas for me right now, lady.
Yeah.
Call it the vulva.
Let's be accurate here.
Yeah.
Call it that Bahamas.
The dussy.
Yeah.
Disgusting.
This podcast has gone off the fucking rails.
We're a couple of grocers.
We're in just a whole new planet right now.
planet fucking stink I'm a planet Sheen yeah what a show dude I'm on planet she
can get my dick sunk they let a little boy go onto the planet Sheen yeah yeah
and they named the planet after him yeah it's kind of like I didn't have a name
until then no it did that's what they got him onto the planet oh it's a whole
planet of Sheen I don't remember it's a really bad show that ruined Sheen's
character they made him a bad character the Sheen I saw that show a few times
when my younger sibling was watching it and yeah it's just uh it's not Sheen you know it's not
my Sheen. What's the last cartoon that you watched like as a kid that was like a like the one that
you watched all the time? Adventure Time probably. Yeah. When that first started coming out I was
watching that religiously when it first uh when it first started airing because I guess I watched it
in like high school. I think it was middle school was it it was either middle school or high school
when it was coming when it for when did it start? It started in like middle school I never watched
adventure time. I think I would probably still like it. The only thing I watched, I watched a lot of adult swim.
Yeah, but I mean like kids cartoons, you know. I didn't watch a lot of kids cartoons.
Yeah, I watched like the important ones. That's what I'm asking. I started 2010.
I watched a lot of like real monsters and stuff. Yeah, like 90s stuff. Did you watch uh you watch Flapjack?
No. Flapjack was good. I didn't watch Flapjack. I didn't watch very much TV as a kid. I was just
on the internet. I watched too much TV. I was addicted to TV. I was not. I wish I had been.
It would have been better for me. I did. I watched TV while I was on the computer. Nice. That's a
grown man. I was just on random forums and shit. I should have been watching real monsters. That
would have been more fun. I remember I torrented a bunch of old like Nicktoons stuff when I was in
middle school and I got like a oh do you remember Kablam? No. It was on like
Nick 2 or whatever yeah and it was a it was like different cartoon shows and they
had like this thing called the action team now and it was all action figures
that thing was tight and you're like I wish I was an action figure mm-hmm I did
I wished I wish I could hang out the scuba guy. Patrick you kind of look like
a rescue hero. No I don't. You always have giant pants and shoes on. I don't look like a...
These aren't giant shoes. That hat, that's a Rescue Hero hat. No it's not. You're one of the Rescue Heroes.
I'm not a Rescue Hero. You are. You have a Rescue Hero's body type. No I don't. They're extremely strong.
Yeah but you're more like a Rescue Zero. No. Because of your zero brain IQ. If I was a
Rescue Hero I'd be the one... Yeah you would be the one. You'd be the girl one? No. With the big boobies?
I only remember the fireman. What's it like to walk around with huge boobs?
Just wondering. I don't know. I think people might be interested. I don't know. What about you Cameron?
I love it. You love it? Yeah. I love it. Watching you. Yeah. Yeah. Don't poke him. Why?
Because he's Cameron and he's my friend. My cat. And do whatever I want. Oh, whatever you want?
They like to smell each other's asses. Yeah. Cats and dogs do some gay ass shit.
Yeah, they sit, all they do is sleep on top of each other all day and then they
get super annoying about food. Do they kiss? Yeah. Do they ever... are they both...
do they... have they both had their penises and balls taken off of their bodies?
They don't have balls but... you saw his penis. Yeah but that was... I thought
that maybe his belly button. No. It was really small. It looks like he's got like an
outie belly button penis. Oh he's mad now. He's looking at me. He heard me talk about his dick.
He's pissed. His eyes are crossed outward. Yeah. He's got... he looks like freaking
pennywise the clown he's got some shit on his eye he's think he's been like
scratchers shit into his eye yeah well and now he's scratching it and it's a
problem you're trying to train him yeah when someone does this move he's so ugly
yeah Patrick's touching the cat we on his you know what no you know what he's
giving him a massage I'm not touching you know what job you're talking touching
is you know what? He's giving him an Italian job. I could go get an Italian job. He's slurping
his penis like spaghetti. That's what an Italian job is. At 7-Eleven? At 7-Eleven, yeah. You're
at 7-Eleven and you're slurping a guy's penis like a penne pasta. I told you earlier, there's
just a woman with pink hair screaming at an elderly European couple and she was asking,
clearly she was asking them for money, but she was sitting there screaming and she was
like I want to fucking kill myself and she said something like now we got this
bird flu going around. There's no bird flu. I told him on the way walking over here I
walked by the Burger King and there was a there's a security guard outside and a
guy with no shoes walked up to him and like pointed at the Burger King and he
he's like "Burger King!" and the security guard just looked at him and shook his head.
That's a really good interaction. Yeah. Yeah. I was glad I took my headphones out for that one.
I saw, I had like a bullet time moment where he was walking towards the security guard and I
was like "No shoes, this is a Burger King that has a security guard so stuff has
happened in the past. I'm gonna take my headphones out." I love moments you
can tell you have you're about to have to take your headphones out yeah there's
this one crazy fucking bus driver who drives my bus yeah I see every once in a
while he's a crazy and he just he's crazy he just like he won't pull up to
the bus stop he'll like just stop in the street and go like go like come on come
on and like like flail his hand and people like make like old people like
walk into the street to get onto the bus he's like in a huge rush for no reason
yeah he goes so fast that he has to pull over the bus and wait sometimes to like
get back on schedule but he always just whenever at the end of the route at the
end of line he always just makes a speech as we pull into the station it's a
different one every day he's like today he was like the date today is January
30th and everybody is waiting for you have a great day like what does that
mean that's crazy one time he yelled because someone got on the bus this was
like in the winter this was last year he somebody got on the bus wearing like axe
body spray and he started freaking out and he's like "Who is putting on too much
body spray? I have like I'm allergic to it it's gonna kill me!" and he opened up
the this like skylight the like emergency escape on the top of the bus
and whenever the bus would stop at a red light he would open both of the doors
he's like freezing fucking cold everyone's like shivering and he just
kept like he was like waving his hand trying to air it out like you couldn't even
- I can even smell it, it's crazy.
- That is anti-guy prejudice.
- He's just an insane guy.
- That's, the thing is about being a bus driver
is like, you can just do, like, nobody wants that job.
You can just do that.
You can just be whatever kinda.
- There was a, when I lived in Revere,
there was like a driver one day,
I was waiting to go to class and I was already like,
kinda late, and she like, pulled up to our stop,
like not really, she like pulled up into this like,
it's like this on-ramp to like route one.
and she screamed at me and the other guy who were there.
And she was like, "Come on, let's go!"
And then she took us through the wrong neighborhood
and went through, like it was the 426 bus,
but she was doing the 428s route.
- Yeah.
- And she was like going through like all this shit.
And then she just went to Haymarket
and like didn't make us pay.
So that was pretty good.
- Yeah, that was not a bus driver.
That was a random person.
- That was a long car.
- No, that was somebody.
I one time was on a bus and this guy with a bunch of bags was sitting right next to the
bus driver and he was like, "So if I wanted to become a bus driver, what would be the process
for that?"
And the guy was like, "Oh yeah, you just go online and you apply."
And he was like, "Interesting, interesting."
And then he didn't talk for ten minutes.
And he's like, "And if previously I had had four DUI convictions, would that affect my
application?"
And the bus driver was like, "I mean, probably.
You might be fine."
This is the kind of people who I am forced to say thank you to by the internet hive mind.
I hate when they make me say thank you to the bus driver.
They won't let you off the bus until you say thanks.
Thank you.
Shut up.
I hate that your bus makes you pay to get off.
One time I was getting off the bus and I tapped my card and it didn't take and I didn't notice
and I got off the bus and the bus driver got off the bus and followed me and screamed at
me and was like "Hey your fucking car didn't go through what the fuck is your
problem?" I was like "Oh sorry man" I like went by tapped and I was like "I'm sorry I
didn't notice" and he's like "Next time you better notice!" I was like "Okay"
You imagine like getting off- no it's just a random- like another one I don't know I
don't remember who- I don't get why they don't need to the bus drivers.
Imagine like getting off the fucking bus to follow somebody. You should be able to pay their food.
I feel like your route's crazy. My route definitely has a lot of crazy drivers.
Well you're on one that has a string attached to it. Yeah. You're on a puppet bus. Yeah so
all the bus drivers are puppets. Yeah, they're puppets and they're being
controlled by it by the puppet master from Spy Kids 3 or the game master
whatever. The game master. The game master from Spy Kids 3. He says I'm the game
master. I want to re-watch Spy Kids 3. Can we do a watch along of Spy Kids 3? I recently
watched the first two and it's funny with like those movies because it's
Robert Rodriguez directs them so you know there's just a lot of a lot of it
that's like... For adults. For you know for people our age. There's a lot of
a lot more nudity than I remember. Yeah, beautiful women. Yeah, close-ups of
pussies and vaginas and buttholes. And yeah, he just shows Salma Hayek's nipple.
I always thought... He says that's Uncle Machete. The only part of any of those
movies that I remember is in the third one, when the grandpa gets up to run and
he's like, "Junie! I can run!"
No, he says, he says, "I can stand!" And he's like, "Oh, grandpa, that's awesome!" He's
like "Junie! I can run!" and then he runs away for like 30, he's like gone for like half the
movie. He just leaves and then at the end he saves them. Yeah we have to watch that movie.
But for like an hour the grandpa was just like "Oh I can run? I'm out of here bitch.
They uploaded me to this game so that I could save the world but I can run!"
this is ricardo multobahn it's con i don't know from the wrath of kim wrath of ricardo multobahn
ricardo's wrath star trek 2 ricardo's wrath um yeah now that you're back we should do a few
watch alongs yeah i would love to we have to do wally and the matrix reloaded okay why do we have
to do wally wally because you've never seen wally matrix reloaded because that poll that one of you
you guys made on the Twitter account, that's what won.
- Yeah. - And then--
- I gotta tell you, I rigged that poll.
- Yeah? - Yeah.
- With what? - You're fucked.
In the head. - I just hacked it.
- Oh, all right. - Yeah.
- And then-- - For real.
- Compromise. - SpyKids3D, game over.
- Sup Yoda?
- What up Yoda?
- Oh. - I'm using the force
against Yoda. - You're using the force
on him and he's not, he's not having it.
Look, you're scaring the shit out of him.
- Yeah dude, I force scared him.
- I was gonna-- - Force scare.
Yeah, you know? - Yeah.
that was a move the palpatine darth ghost use that in the halloween movie
darth skeleton used to always do the force scare
and he would make force xylophone noises and then the advanced like level two
knights of the old republic version is force freak where you freak someone out
just with your hand
the sith lords are dangerous they can freak you out
they can freak you out for hours
Darth... Darth Pumpkin?
Isn't Darth Nihilus a ghost?
Yes.
Yeah, he's a... he's a Sith ghost.
Yeah, what a genius name for that guy.
Yeah.
Oh, it's so funny how like...
Darth Tyrannus and like...
Darth Tyrannosaurus Rex.
Darth Meanie.
Yeah.
Darth Bad Guy.
I'm Darth...
What the fuck?
They're fighting, dude.
Oh, man.
Dude, I got money on...
They're scratching each other.
I got money on the humans.
Yeah.
There should be a game where plants fight zombies.
There should be.
You know what I learned the other day?
In the end you would think the zombies would win.
Yeah.
But it's crazy.
You know what I learned the other day?
Plants vs. Zombies was originally supposed to be called Lawn of the Dead and that's why
it's plants and zombies but they couldn't get the copyright shit.
So it just makes no sense.
So it was all based on a pun and they just couldn't make the pun.
That sucks.
Yeah, it sucks dude.
That would have been so much better.
That would have been so mad.
I probably would have played it if it was called Lawn of the Dead.
I've played all those games a lot. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I love they weren't they phone games. They're originally
Mac games, uh, yeah, they're like very simplified like tower defense around as advanced as a tower defense game on they're not as advanced as balloons three
Calm, I remember balloons me. I would play balloons in class all of them. That's all it was like not working anymore
Uh, you're not working anymore. What when since this summer? Oh, that's actually true
fist bump
imagine we did a fist bump
give me a pewdiepie brofist for that one mom
how about poopie pie
give me a poop pie
i bet that's what you want to eat
hey mom can i have a poop pie for christmas?
it's been a long time since i had poop pie
mom won't you please make me a poop pie
he's got his claws in my... somebody the last time i sang a song
direct message me and let me know that it was
It was stuck in their head all week.
Yeah, it was a cringe song.
Let's get this one stuck in people's heads.
♪ It's been a long time ♪
♪ Since I had a poop pie ♪
♪ And I want a poop pie so bad ♪
Everybody's distracted by the cats
and I'm paying attention to my concert.
This is like an NPR tiny desk
that you guys are just missing out.
♪ It's had a long time to make my poop pie ♪
That's beautiful. ♪ Mom, where is my pie ♪
that you have put my friends poop in.
It's a beautiful song.
Thank you.
It's really beautiful.
We're probably going to do a couple different versions of it.
We'll do an acoustic one that's like, "It's been a long time."
We'll do a version with a cup song.
We'll do a "You're going to piss my poop pie."
"You're going to piss my poopy pie."
"You're going to piss me by my poop."
"You're going to piss me by my pie."
You're gonna piss me by my poopy pie.
My poopy pie.
My icky breaky are my poopy poopy pie.
My poopy poopy diapers.
Don't change my diaper.
My stinky poopy diaper.
I like the smell
when I'm playing games.
That's pretty good. I like to wear my diaper when I play games.
When I play. How many like, how many
Starcraft players
do you think
wore diapers? Wore the Asian diaper?
A hundred. A thousand. And two. I think that was the thing was like people at
Internet cafes in Korea were like wearing diapers so they could shit and piss while they play. Yeah. Yeah
They should just make the chair a toilet. Girls shouldn't be so weird about that. Yeah
you should be able to wear that and then beg for a
Blow job without taking a long-ass shower. It's true. I mean you should be able to do anything to your penis
They should make they should make a the blumpkin for real. Yeah, they should make a stupid a
Stupid girlfriend who will do whatever you say. They should admit that
Yeah, yeah, damn. He's got a cave. It's 530. We need to go. Yeah, you guys do all you know
How much time you go grab our spots for more three more minutes? Oh, we can do three three minutes. All right
Yeah, we could do three. Yeah, then do okay. Keep it with the Australian thing. I
Lost my family in the way. I lost my family in the fire. That's not funny. That's
Dude millions of people have died. Have you have you heard that?
Koalas have you heard there's a poison no and
They they are you poison and they sleep and they sleep and they all have chlamydia
if you
Heard of a person like that. I'm wondering why Darwin hasn't taken over. We should start writing crack calm articles like that
I gotta stop doing go grab the show
Crapped calm version. That's our version. Yeah, ten celebrities who said crap in a song
I actually wrote an article for cracked one time that got to the editing phase and then they were like
This is completely factually inaccurate
Yeah, but the general gist of the article was like was seven geniuses who were actually retarded
And they were like this is really good until I was like they were like so can you prove that Albert Einstein had?
Asperger's and I was like no, but
Like 15. Hey stuck his tongue out. Yeah, who does that? Yeah. Yes. He obviously can't pick up on social cues
Yeah, look at him. Yeah
And he's smart at math
Crazy hair crazy hair doesn't know how to comb. Yeah
I don't know, that's about all I know.
Does he sound like I'm making him talk?
No.
Kinda.
No, not at all.
You should take him and use him like a puppet.
Yeah.
I'm a puppet.
I love when puppets say I'm a puppet.
Yeah, that's one of the best.
It's one of those stock puppet jokes.
That's a...
I am the puppet.
Yeah.
That's Jose the Jalapeno.
Mm-hmm.
Bringing it back.
Yeah, and then Peanut's like, I'm the puppet.
Peanut doesn't sound like that.
Peanut sounds like that.
No, Peanut's like, yo, yo.
Mm-hmm.
what's up keep going yo what's up it's peanut I'm about to I'm about to I'm the
puppet of the all time Jeff Dunham's puppets just say I'm a puppet of all time
I'm a serious puppet okay Jose and what about you I'm the puppet I'm the
Macy again pop it okay what about you old man puppet Walter what about you black
puppet that black pimp puppet yo what's up I'm the puppet I'm the pimp like
kind of what's his black pimp puppets name peanut is the black puppet but no
he's like us he's like Bigfoot why did Jeff Donna make his black puppet a
monkey cuz he Bigfoot is not a monkey okay take it back
Take it back. Bigfoot is a monkey. Take it back.
Take it back or we can't add the episode.
We're gonna do another hour if we talk about whether or not Bigfoot's a monkey.
Bigfoot is a rat. Bigfoot's a giant rat.
What's the pimp character that Jeff Dunham has?
It's not Bubba J. Bubba J is the redneck.
Oh, yeah.
Why is, yeah, Jeff Dunham made that black puppet but then he made it look like a California raisin for no reason?
Well, the California raisins were black guys.
That's true.
Yeah. People just thought they were raisins.
It was just five black dudes.
He's older. Yeah and they were like and a bunch of kids were like these are
raisins. Anyway. Yeah they didn't get the message across. That was over an hour.
Perfect. Okay we love you. Bye. I'm going to kiss you.