You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
So Waffle House.
Waffle House.
I went to Waffle House before this, so, you know, I had coffee, but I also had hash browns and toasted eggs and bacon and waffle, so...
Yeah, I would say Waffle...
It's kind of like more than counteracts the coffee.
Yeah, waffle does have whatever the opposite of caffeine is.
Yeah, waffine.
You know, it has waffine in it.
I think it's identical.
There's like warine, taurine, and waffine.
Waffine, yeah.
Waffine's the one that makes you laugh like the Joker.
Oh, I hate waffine.
Yeah.
I hate when I accidentally drink something.
I ate too much.
And I go, "Does this have any, does this happen to have waffine in it?"
Well, that's why it's in, you know, it's in cream pies,
Which is why when you get hit in the face with one, oh, that's why them damn clowns are so damn funny
seltzer water
Yeah, and a certain kind of flower that is a little tiny hole in the in the middle of it
That's great you're lucky to have you ever been to Waffle House before today? Yes, my second time at Waffle House. Oh
God, dude. Yeah, and it's one of those things where people from the south will be like there's nothing like it and I'm like well
Well, it's just a diner chain. I think there's a lot of stuff like it, but I'm willing to
drink the Kool-Aid. I think it's pretty awesome.
The thing is about Waffle House is it's like getting, you know, in a driving game like
Need for Speed, when you hit a floating nitrous bottle, it's that but just for drunk driving
home from Waffle House.
Absolutely.
As soon as you eat the Waffle House, it powers you up. You drive as if you're somehow more
than sober no matter how much you drink. It's really, it's an incredible magic.
Yeah. It's also, it is insanely cheap.
Oh yeah, dude. The Grand Slam?
No, All Star Breakfast.
Yeah, All Star. Yeah. I feel like all the fast food is expensive now, right? Am I right?
All this damn fast food is so damn expensive now.
That's so true.
Dude, speaking of Denny's, when I was in Bakersfield, California, I went to a Denny's with a full
bar in the back.
And not like the kitchen had a bar, but you walk down a long hallway to a completely empty
bar where the bartender told me that it was empty.
It was empty, yeah.
The bartender told me there hadn't been anyone in the bar in three weeks and he had just been
like a year a year amount.
In 25 years.
And he walked into the bar from the side.
And then he aged really fast in front of me and his jaw fell off.
And he went "he he he" and spiraled away out the window.
And then I stayed and I kept drinking and eating.
But it was like the most insane shit.
Bakersfield is like a magical place.
They have the corn sign and I looked it up, it's one of the only three Denny's bars in
the country.
Wow, what are the other ones?
I don't know.
Let me guess.
Arkansas?
And Hawaii?
Hawaii, they definitely would have one.
Those people in Hawaii?
Those, I mean,
those day drinking pieces of shit in Hawaii?
They're surfing all day instead of working.
Yeah, just sipping Kahlúa
in Malibu out of the bottle,
not mixing it with anything.
Yeah, I think that's a good one.
a
to be in one of those but at least go to Alaska and get some like oil stuff done or something.
Yeah that's why Obama was such a bad president. You're slacking on the clock right now pal.
Because Obama sat down in the Oval Office and he was like uh uh surf's up and they're like no sir
you have to sign bills and and write laws and give speeches. He's like I don't understand I've been
I've only ever vacationed I am from Hawaii. Yes thank you very much. Yeah. Just an embarrassing
place to be from. Yeah, horrible. I would say ugly, ugly landscape. Would you say that Hawaii
and Boston are the most opposite states in America? I will, you know, I wouldn't probably
write state. So Boston is a state. Yeah. Most opposite places. I mean, I would say that
Massachusetts has more beautiful beaches than Hawaii. And if you ever been to that's undeniable
to
Just rocks didn't have McDonald's wrappers and people who look like you
That's like me what a beat should be
I know I'd rather be be looking at like pedophiles mansions in Manchester by the sea then living in doodle god in real life
What the fuck is that dude, I don't want to live I mean
Come on, what do I want to I want to live in the fucking grumble volcano from Mario Kart. Fuck. No
Fuck. No, dude. I want to live in a place
I want to live in the midst of the movie and know that behind the midst there is a beach somewhere exactly
Yeah, I want to see like like a hundred clones of
Kathy Bates from misery just walking walking along the beach behind me. Yeah, I don't want to
Like in Hawaii you sit on the beach and all the monsters for my singing monsters come up and start singing to you
Yeah, leave me alone
Yeah, I mean, what is this damn island Hotel Transylvania?
When I was fucking kooky characters when I was on the
Hotel Transylvania a lot. Why he's exactly like Hotel Transylvania, dude
Hawaiian Transylvania, maybe the most similar States. That's true. Yeah. Yeah
When I was on the the plane here, they had it, you know, they have like like you can play games on like the seat back
Monitor, that's always the first thing
I look I look at when I get on a plane that has like a seat back TV is I look yeah games because it's all
They always got some good ass games and they had bird versus a turd. Oh
man, do you ever played bird versus
No, is it do you shoot the birds into the other birds? Nope?
Shit, what do you do? It's the worst game of all time
It's like a math game
Level thing where like you is a bird like it takes turns moving on the board and you have to draw a line around it
To stop it from escaping
That sounds awful last time on my flight back from California. I played on the back of the head rest
I played bejeweled - and I played the time trial version. So I was like playing really hard
It's like fucking pounding that fucking screen and then like 20 minutes in the lady
It was sitting on the seat turn around. She was like, can you stop?
and I was like
I'm so sorry, but I got so into bejeweled that I
I was like, oh, yeah, I was playing all the games. I was like, oh this one's called like fruit attack
This looks cool. Like this is probably like a fruit ninja game, right? Cuz yeah, and no it was it was bubble bobble
but with fruits.
I was like, "Oh, this sucks."
But this game, Blitz Blast, this looks pretty good.
I guess I should play this.
And it was Bubble Bobble, but with explosions.
Oh my God, dude.
At least I had the name brand games on my shit.
Tetris.
I mean, they had it down to a science to make you expect one app when you click on it and
you get Bird vs. Bird being a cool math game.
And then Fruit Slice or whatever.
I remember before phones were like high, like, like had like any sort of computing power,
you would download like modern warfare mobile, and it would just be like a version of Yahtzee
with like guns as the different side of the die.
The modern warfare mobile right now, he was playing and showing me, and you don't, all
you do is you just put your, you move your finger to move the like view.
There's no like fire but it just shoots automatically when you're, you're crosshairs over somebody.
My God, really run around and point at them and it just kills
them instantly and like everybody still lose like it's all just
like kids so they can't do it.
You just running around is tapping people.
There's dying.
It's like damn if only the only warzone was like this.
I'll be the champion of the world.
I'd be the king if all it was was pointing at things that I
wanted dead.
Absolutely life was like this.
I've only I'd be the king.
Well, that'd be tough because you know, there's some things
I point out that I don't want dead.
Like for example, if I'm ordering off the menu, I want, I don't want it.
I don't want to destroy the hamburger.
I mean, I want to destroy the hamburger, but with my mouth.
Yeah.
I don't want to fucking just kill the turkey stuffing sandwich at red Robin.
No, I want to, I want to, I want to eat that shit.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
I have been, um, I just found out right before we started recording
that I have, I have been hacked.
Yo, my, my Facebook and Instagram accounts have been permanently
disabled because I was I was hacked by somewhere, somebody in China.
Somebody was trying to hack my Instagram literally every day for like a month
and then I just changed my I just switched the words around in my
Instagram name and it just stopped. Learned my mistake. I got every day I
would open Google Chrome and it would say warning you have 400
uh compromised passwords and I just go that's probably probably fine right and
this person whoever whoever hacked me set up a two-factor authentication so I can't even like
I can't even like get back into the accounts they're just gone forever oh oh my god so many
fucking so many so many Facebook events lost no the worst comedy shows of all time dude
Fuck. Yeah, so many poster tags that are broken now forever.
No.
We're gonna look at it and be like, "Who's this guy with three hairs on his head?"
I don't have three hairs like Charlie Brown.
I guess it's, I guess he's Chinese. This is weird.
No. No.
I guess his name is Free Ray Bans Beijing.
I was worried. I was worried when I first found out because I got something that was like,
"Your account may have been compromised." And then by the time that I tried to log in,
They'd already suspended it, but I was really worried for a second that
Whoever cuz you know what those people always do is they just like mass message everybody?
Yeah, so I was just like was imagining my mom getting like a message from me. That's like hey horny want to fuck me and
I was like
What if she says yes, dude? No
Yeah, it is so it's never I've never been hacked like that
But it is so humiliating like I feel so bad for like a person like in high school like someone
I maybe talked to like once or twice and then it sends a link
It's like what you posted these sexual pictures of me with a link and then they have to like a day later be like, I'm sorry
Yeah, oh man
Can you imagine having to do that to like or or the people that people?
You make the you make the post just so you don't have to do all the all the specific messaging
you just make the post on your page.
It's like, I'm sorry for my post the last few days.
I was actually hacked.
I do not like diarrhea.
I think that it smells and it is brown.
So disregard all messages and posts.
What diarrhea is actually delicious bit me.
I got that from someone I would click right away that diarrhea
as covid cure in India.
Click here now.
Meet Hot Diarrhea.
[Laughs]
I got a bunch, cause I joined a bunch of random Facebook groups that are all about like, you know,
extinct empire, conspiracy theory, stuff like that.
So I get put on a lot of lists where like a page will just auto-tag me and stuff.
Like, yeah, like not even someone on my friends list, but it's like a page that's called like,
Crazy Pictures. It'll be like, "Crazy Pictures tagged you in a post."
And it'll be like the new 18 plus video that's sweeping the nation. It's like me and like
people and it's like this better not show up on like my family members timeline like Cameron was
Did I miss all that I miss like
Find those groups and then just watch like videos that we would find all those videos of people claiming the Statue of Liberty moved
Yeah, and like some of them would just be like camera shake and one of them would be like they're like a CGI breakdancing
The coolest shit ever. I the new wave I've been on for Facebook groups
Is there people who believe in and I don't know the details of this?
I haven't I haven't like done any research
So, you know if I'm wrong you can yell at me and Twitter DMS or whatever
They believe in the Tartarian Empire
Which was like a technologically advanced empire that used to exist and I think was wiped out by like a flood of mud or something
and
So fucking press it then, what are you doing?
Like like an ancient like like
Technologically advanced like alien utopia and they're like and this window will look like a play button
So that we are quite advanced
Yeah, I I need to look into what the details of that that one is because um
There's a lot of groups about it and they're very fun to look at
Dude, i've been thinking about doing some ancient exploring recently some indiana jones shit. Oh, absolutely
I was watching some.
I was watching like one of those movies recently.
I can't remember which one.
And I was just thinking myself.
I was like the like pay off.
Oh, some shitty like horror movie called like as as above.
So below. Oh, yeah, that movie.
Yeah. So I was watching it and I was like,
these people were just getting fucking murdered.
Yeah. And like destroyed. It was horrible.
And then I was like, why don't you just like just why don't you get a normal job?
Yeah, like why do these people like Indiana Jones?
Like why what is so worth it like Indiana Jones is not rich every movie. He's fucking it starts off
He's teaching a class like why is he still like?
Jumping in front of arrows and like dodging laser beams to get like a golden head
Like just fucking working it at a normal job
You're gonna stay be a teacher if you're gonna be a teacher be a teacher
Yeah, just be a teacher. You'd be probably like the best teacher ever, you know?
Like you can fuck your students normally if that's really what you want to do in DnF.
Yeah, you're not gonna like...
They're not that impressed that you got like...
You're not gonna get more pussy because you like brought back some like fucking...
That is definitely...
Some old guitar, you know?
That's why you're still...
They're not gonna be doing it though, right? Like you can tell.
I have to suck your cock now.
Yeah, I mean, I guess that's a good point. He goes...
The bitch who has the "fuck me" written on her eyes or whatever,
He says like come to my office after class and then she walks in and he just like opens up like his like trophy case of all of his like ancient shit.
Yeah and she wasn't gonna fucking before but now she's seriously gonna fucking slurp him up.
The funny thing about that movie as as above so below that I remember is like it's about like the like.
like indiana jones explorers who like go into like the catacombs and like find hell or whatever
and the like writers of it clearly just ran out of ideas for like um indiana jones stuff because
it starts and they're like oh we have to like sneak through this tunnel and find this entrance
and escape from this cult and then like the rest of like like and add the hour that's left in the
movie is just like the roof of the cave just collapses six different times because they
Think of like another trap.
There's like, oh, if you don't solve this puzzle, the roof will fall down.
And it just happens over and over and over.
Also, that is a great movie because it it it posits the idea that hell is
about 80 feet underground.
If you dig down 80 feet you get down.
So yeah people I remember people being like, oh, this is like a cool
depiction of hell, but they get to hell and I think like the first thing
they see is that there's in like underground.
There's like a car that's on fire and like that.
You think that's what's in hell like a scary car.
You could see if a car crashes on the highway.
You could see that you don't have to go to hell to see a car.
It's on.
Also, I guess it would make sense that hell was in in Paris like
France because it would just be like easy like hell is mostly
French people like so they just have an easier kind of shorter
walk to hell once they die.
Cuz yeah that that is a I would say it's a uniquely bad depiction
of hell because it's mostly just like everybody sees like one one weird thing that happened
to them a version of it in the in hell.
Yeah, and then they crawl out of a manhole at the end.
It's a very great story.
Sorry for the spoilers everybody, but I don't care.
I'll freaking yeah, you hear that damn you should give a shit.
I'm savage as hell.
Yeah, it is funny.
The hell will be like you see one scary thing.
Yeah, the worst eternal punishment is your your underground and you see a scary stuff.
Yeah, yeah. Remember that time that you stubbed your toe really bad?
What if it happened again in hell?
Yeah, that is one of those movies though that every
horror nerd loves that movie because it's such an ingenious concept.
What if hell was the world but upside down?
You're in it, so it's right side up.
That would be scarier. If you were just if you got to hell and you started on the ground and then just fell up
That would be actually pretty scary. Yeah, that's like a way more terrifying idea than just like you don't know that
It's upside down until you leave. Yeah
Yeah, they have no idea
It was upside down the whole holy shit. That's insane. Yeah. Yeah, it's pretty cool
I did I did LSD this past week nice and I I learned.
I learned a lot you know to learn I learned that.
That's a sponge bob is very scary to watch on LSD.
I just sat there and I was about the whole time yeah I mean that's squidward fellow he.
Yes it or a yeah there is pointed when i was really peaking where and this is terrifying where sponge bob looked almost orange.
Which is really that was kind of reality bending for a shirt while you are looking at mr crabs.
'Cause Mr. He's the orange one.
It's fun.
I'm saying with SpongeBob.
Yeah, he says, oh,
when I was peeking on as it was crazy,
SpongeBob was red and he was saying our money, money, money.
And I just turned to my entire family said, that's SpongeBob.
I I definitely wouldn't recommend watching a children's show
with your entire extended family.
Well, it seems like a recipe for a bad time to me.
It was actually a pretty good time because in the end I did just get to watch Spongebob.
Spongebob's nice. It's a good thing.
Yeah, it was fun, but we did also, and I wasn't choosing, we did also only watch the scary
episodes of Spongebob about like time and like all that shit. So that wasn't great,
you know, like the one where he's in the time machine and then he goes into the white void.
I watched that episode. I had a Spongebob DVD that had like a few episodes. I think it only
had like four episodes on it or something. Um, and that was one of them and then the ripped pants was
on there too. I just watched those two like over and over and over. If I had watched ripped pants
while just high out of my mind, I think I would have had what do they call an ego death.
Yeah. Yeah. That one's good. Also, I sing the song in it. Spongebob style. I ripped my pants on the
the beach that very day. So that would have been pretty terrifying.
Did you pretend to drown too? Like Spongebob?
Yeah, yeah I did. In the sand. Yeah. I pretended to drown.
Yeah, I don't believe you, but that's okay.
Whatever man, you don't have to believe me.
I don't have to believe you.
What can I do now to try to stop myself from being hacked ever again?
What kind of security measures do you need to put in place?
Just if you see notice yourself getting hacked just switch the words around and it stops. That's my funny. Does that work for you?
Yeah, yeah. Well, I don't think I don't think they care about my account. I think they just were like, oh, here's we're
Putting a username on a giant list and we're gonna just like brute force it every day because I was just getting a like an email
every day that was like
This you somebody's trying to log into your account
So, I don't know. I don't know if they're so stupid. They just couldn't find
You know, I don't know maybe that works maybe I don't know also I mean two-factor authentication
I think is the thing you have to do trying to think of what might what the perfect password is for my perfect password
It's very the thing is it's has it's very short because nobody ever get everyone has long dress where it's nowadays
Yeah, I'll guess in long stuff. My password is just like for example, if it was just one two, three
No one's ever getting in. I mean 3 2 1 might be how about here here. How about 1 3 2 3 2 3 2 1 is too easy
Cuz that's what I think I'd be when I'm one it went three trying to hack. They say 3 2 1 I'm in
Yeah, they're saying it out loud 3 2 1 time to try wait a minute let's try 3 2 1
That's why I think 3 1 2 might be the perfect password
That's a one three two really good password or two one three any or two any version of that
I think might be insanely strong because nobody said no no self-respecting hacker who knows how to count
It goes okay one three two. I'm in two one three. I'm in yeah exactly
You know and I'm gonna actually throw you a curveball here. That might be even better. Okay about
three two four
But the hacker would be able to say that because that's just illogical
What about six six six because they might get scared when they're typing it in
That might be pretty good might be good. Yeah. Yeah, I could work. The thing is nowadays all these damn password
companies they need you to put in a an emoji and
And a color yeah a color your favorite food your favorite food and a fucking and a and a photo of yourself
run through the "Tunify me" application and that all has to be part of your password
or else you try to enter it and it says "no you're gonna need one of these 50 things"
Yeah, your password is too pathetic, that's what they say too.
It's like, I know what I'm doing.
Hackers can easily get a picture, a tunified picture of me. It's public record.
Yeah, this isn't adding any more safety, like I'm not safer with my password because I added a question mark
at the end and just made myself sound like a pussy when I read my password out loud.
You know?
Yeah.
Caleb is awesome?
Like that's not a good password.
That's also what hackers do.
Caleb is awesome is a good password.
Whenever hackers try a password, they immediately, if it doesn't work, they just try it again
with a question mark at the end.
Yeah, just to, and also, it mostly works.
Usually.
An exclamation point, I'm never that excited about the password.
Yeah.
You know?
A one.
really good password is for everyone out there to use is
hello 111 exclamation point cuz that that's easy to remember.
Yeah, you need your if your friend needs to log into your
Netflix or your Hulu or your Bank of America. That's easy for
them to do to remember how to do it exactly everybody. I do
think everyone should just have there should just be no
passwords. I think that honor system honor system. Yeah.
Cuz like these baddies these bad naughty's they are they're fucking no goods. He's nasty. No gooders. They're fucking
Logging on, you know, but it because they know my password safe. I'm gonna fucking hacker exactly
They're you get passwords if you had to look
Oh, here's what it is
If you had to log into a specific app to hack things that told everybody your name
I bet you a lot less hackers would happen in the world. We should if
We should have it so when a hacker moves into the neighborhood they have to go introduce themselves
Exactly. Yeah. Yeah, I'm required by like tell you me. I'm a hacker. I'm a hacker
Can I see your phone or your microwave? Yeah, do you mind if I look at your doorbell? I?
Just like to take a look at your ring. I could never hack your doorbell
Come on, I don't even know how to do that. I'm not that good of a hacker. Come on. I'm your doorbell
I hate when I get an alert from my ring doorbell. It says alert hacker is trying to hack doorbell and I look and it's a guy and his fingers are typing
Just tapping them
And I have to go I have to counter hack with my alexa I say
Alexa, let's begin hacking. Yeah, one zero one one one zero one one one one one. You know, that's what it could be is that
We could make it really easy to hack everything
And then everybody would stop hacking because like, you know, if a hacker hacked me, I'd hack them back. It's easy
That's a good point. Yeah, it's like it would be like it would be like it'd be like nuclear weapons
Which is a really good situation, I think to have it should be like like like, you know, all those all that shit
It's like well learn to code. It should be learned to hack. I feel like hacking is much more
Useful because you'll to have coding and hacking is completely different coding is lame hacking is cool
So also the thing about hacking is like, you know, with coding, it's like, oh, I have no money.
Oh, I have to learn how to code to get a job and then get money.
Exactly.
With hacking, it's like, oh, I have no money. Here, let me learn to hack and then hack a
bunch of money away. That's one step removed. It's easier.
Right. I mean, and just look at, yeah, a coder, you know, they're like, okay, I'm going to create
a website where when you scroll, the menu bar stays in one place. I mean, that's not creative.
Everyone's doing that. A hacker says, I'm going to take that same website and I'm going to put
put a picture of my bare ass right in the middle of it, whether you like it or not.
And that's real creativity.
You know, a web designer wouldn't think to do something like that.
Well cause also, so if you were a hacker, what would your calling card be?
Probably I would say you've been hacked by Cameron.
Could be one idea, but I'll keep brainstorming because I know you didn't have much of a reaction
to that.
I was expecting more of a cast.
You've been hacked by... wait, can you say it again?
Say it like you're making a robot voice.
You've been hacked by Cameron.
No, see that that would be scary to see that actually did get a really good reaction. What about okay?
I've actually got a new idea. What about virus engaged?
That might be pretty scary - yeah or like welcome to the matrix bitch could be one I think getting a bunch of I
Think the nice thing about like most people is you could just make them download a picture that says like like yeah
Virus downloaded or something and that would be enough for them to did just like their computer their computer in the trash, you know
Yeah, kind of a mental virus. It's like morgulons. Mm-hmm. Yeah. Yeah. Oh shit brain worm. I
Can't believe I forgot to tell you this about that Denny's
No, no, it has nothing to do with that even a little bit
but I
I did see a waiter named Shrek.
S-C-H-R-E-C-K.
Shrek.
And before you ask, he didn't look a lot like Shrek to be honest.
Yeah, no, he just looked like a guy but his name his name was Shrek
dude, you know that guy that guy that guy applied to like a bunch of different jobs and
He was like he applied to a bunch of jobs that didn't require you to wear name tags and none of them accepted
And then the ones with name tags only accepted him because they were like this would be like a feature the restaurant
You know, it could be like our mascot. Yeah. Well what he should have done because this is in
California he should have tried to get a job at Universal Studios as a Shrek walkabout character, right?
And then when somebody was some little kid walks up to him and kicks his leg and says you're not really Shrek
He takes off the helmet and they don't know who he is because
No, what do you think now and then says? Oh, yeah, my name is Shrek you guys
I forgot that you guys wouldn't know that I guess I'm not a guy the guy who played knows for a to his name Shrek
Is that true? Yeah, it's a piece of true max Shrek. Oh
Okay last name though. So yeah, but I mean I like his friend. Oh if your name was max Shrek
I feel like people would call you Shrek
Yeah. Yeah, my name was Caleb Superman. I would hope that you would call me
Superman I was I was double-check when I before I said that is double check in and make sure I remembered it
Right and I searched max Shrek and it has the like people also ask thing on Google and here are the questions
I think the questions are it was max Shrek a method actor. What is the meaning of nosferatu is nosferatu scary? I
Don't think nosferatu is very scary any they didn't figure out how to make a scary movie until like the exorcist
Yeah, I think
Hmm, I think he's I think he's scary looking. I mean, he's like ugly but like that's not scary to me
I think he's scary. I think he's one of the scariest guys in the world. You're just lying me
You're just me trying to make a point you have no you're not you do not think knows for us
Have you seen if you saw nose for ought to right now you'd say oh, he's a swimmer. He has more fans
And I wouldn't say that I would say that you were out to you
Well, that might be your first thought but then you'd say Nosferatu, obviously not a real guy.
So that guy who looks like Nosferatu has to have Marfan syndrome.
He's a real guy. He's based on a real guy named Max Nosferatu.
You're just making shit up now.
I'm not making that up. I'm reading it off the Wikipedia page right now.
There was another guy who worked at that Denny's whose name was Nosferatu.
Nosferatu. That would be a really good last name.
Well, I will say that I think Shrek is the of all fictional characters.
I think Shrek is the least likely like like the most unexpected actual name I've ever seen.
Probably.
Like I could not think of another fictional character.
Wait, I have to go real quick.
Okay.
My groceries are here. Give me two seconds.
I'm gonna keep recording.
All right, I'm back.
All right.
Got my LaCroix in the mail.
Yeah.
while you were gone I was uh I was googling Tartarian Empire mud flood just to see just
to get a surface level idea of what this is and the first the first article about is from Bloomberg
about the conspiracy theory and the second one is from is from the Crimsonian the voice of Dover
High School. So this is the two sources. High school newspaper article about about the Tartarian
Mud Flood and it says at the bottom, "Please note that the opinion expressed in this article
are not representative of Dover City Schools Staff Administration or Board of Education."
They should put more like, so like op-eds, you can say whatever you want in an op-ed,
right?
They should let more like just completely crazy people write op-eds in New York Times and
Washington Post and shit.
You know?
I feel like they should let Shrek do it.
I bet he has some wild opinions.
Shrek?
I mean...
Oh the other thing about Shrek is that this guy...
I'm sorry to be stuck on Shrek.
This guy was probably like mid-30s and so I was like, "Okay, so that means that he was
around middle school when the first Shrek movie came out."
Right, yeah.
I was just imagining his first day back, his first day at school, and his best friend comes
up to him, like right as he enters and he's like, "Hey, did you see the news?
I'm so sorry.
I can't be friends with you anymore."
Yeah, I'm sure also because like, yeah, he probably went to see a movie and the trailer
was like, "Before."
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah exactly, it was like this summer this green monster's making fairy tale land, he's
a bitch or whatever and he's sitting in the sea like oh this looks great.
Coming in 2001, Shrek.
Shrek.
Farting mud stink over.
Yeah, yeah, he farts in mud and he fucks a log and he's like oh this looks funny as hell.
best friends a black donkey and he and they're both stupid as shit.
Oh my god they're ugly too.
Awesome.
And he turns into a prince and it's funny because he's so ugly normally.
He kidnaps a girl and tries to fuck her.
This guy's seriously fucking weird as hell.
I wonder what this movie's called.
His ears were like fucking disgusting.
He's so fucking ugly that his wife caught it.
also turned ugly. His skin looks like green salami and he smells like it too. He's so
gross. He pulls a candle out of his ass because there's so much wax in it. And he's fat. He's
fat because he eats bugs like they're candy. Yeah. He's like Timon and Pumbaa and the Mucinex
monster all mixed together. If he was real and in middle school he would be bullied for
this if you knew a guy who's named after this fat piece of shit you should kill
him coming soon Dreamworks Pictures presents you
just comes out it's a 3d movie this points right at him it comes it actually
comes out of the screen and everyone got it this fucking kid it was like a
Premier screening for a different movie. So they're doing a special promotion and they're like, they're like check under your chair to see if you
Would be like be the name being the namesake of our new
That's right, it's fucking stupid kid
Yeah, and this other kids gonna be the short prince. Yeah
Yeah, and here are the rules of people named Shrek number one. They don't get any presents on their birthday number two
They have to skip lunch
number three no recess
He's green and stinky and fat and ugly get this we're gonna make like a thousand movies
Yeah, plus we're gonna do this every year and a bunch of specials every time. There's like a like Cinco de Mayo
We're gonna make a special he's gonna be the face of our brand
I bet you can't wait to wait to play Shrek all-stars brawl on Game Boy Advance with your
Cuz in you can beat you just like you've always wanted to you can beat this shit out of Shrek
Fuck Shrek and fuck this kid
the guy who's talking in
Like we actually used motion capture to make Shrek move exactly like the kid
Yeah, and then it's like
His farts were actually designed from Shrek's real-life parts that we captured in the classroom
Cut to the kid Shrek in a bathtub just farting so hard it makes
Sometimes reality is stranger than fiction
We found the nastiest little fucker in Texarkana
And we turned him into a green fucking monster and we passed a law
Federal law that means that he specifically can never change his name
We followed this little fucker around and fed him bugs he only got fat and green from being sick
Director sitting on a chair is like so basically we started by finding just the worst most stinky green kid we could find
And we patented every part of Shrek's character on the child.
We actually, we forced him to live in a hut for several months and we put a psychic driving helmet on his head and actually forced him to listen to a Scottish accent for months until he developed one.
Oh fuck dude. We squeezed his ears until they looked weird.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- See that's what that brown disgusting outfit.
- I think if that was me,
I would just get plastic surgery to look like Shrek.
- Yeah.
- You know?
- 'Cause then if people, you know,
you obviously, you look like Shrek.
You're walking around fucking Shrek'd up.
- And then someone comes up to you.
- And they're like, well, you just like,
this isn't that cool 'cause you just like paid
to like have all this shit to look and be Shrek.
And then you show them your birth certificate
And they go, Oh my God, I'm rethinking all of that.
Well, the Shrek movie, it also, it was an innovative motion
capture technology where they actually, every character in
that movie was based off of a real person.
So they had, they had Fiona, the beautiful princess, they had Eddie
Murphy, the donkey, you know, um, they had, and then they had Shrek.
Yeah.
And they basically, they, they would, uh, what they did is they
convince the kid that there was a they sent the kid to a slumber
party, which was the slumber party was actually all producers
of the movie and they played a game in the movie called or in
the the slumber party called who can have the most tennis balls
duct taped to their body and then they they just basically
recorded that and the kid is so stupid. I mean Shrek come on
and he's like, oh okay. Yeah. I'd love to play that game and
they were like. Oh yeah and then the second part of the game is
you have to like pretend you're picking up something heavy and
And then you have to do a hug and then you have to run for your life.
Yeah, they had hidden cameras all over the slumber party that got it.
On every piece of that now pretend signing this release form with a
real pen now pretend you're kissing your mom.
They motion captured him signing the release form to there just like
and now pretend you're writing your name and then they use that
technology to actually digitally add a signature.
yeah the worst part is that they get the game
the shrek logo
believe me and they also
they motion captured it his own mom to be fiona
just to make it even more better
company came out
uh...
a fun fact when they film that scene in the hot tub
that was a mud those poop
and it is a good
because and here's a very much like how they use the back back in black and
white movies he used to use like chocolate syrup for blood.
Poop has a better consistency for the screen than mud does.
So you know, you gotta take it to the team and send this poop kid.
And then Shrek got put into witness protection because he wanted, he was, everybody wanted
to kill him.
And they sent him to, they sent him to, to Bakersfield, California where he works at a
Denny's now.
Yeah, the only one of the only three Denny's with a bar.
That was that was they were like we're gonna send you to work at this this high-profile bar
There's only three in the country
Yeah, and they again these legally not allowed to change his name so he keeps a Shrek name check but
Everyone's on the walk by a table cuz he's busting dishes and a kid will will a burp up a Pepsi
And then his dad will say, Hey, better out than in.
I always say, and then Shrek's eyes just go completely black.
Yeah. Uh, we're sending you to, I mean, a luxurious new placement,
you know, this, the city we're sending you to it's industry rich. I mean,
I don't want to, I don't want to put any ideas in your head, but like oil.
So I'm just thinking like Dubai, Dubai,
any direction you look buildings as far as you can see.
Oh my God, I'm going to Dubai.
I'm so excited.
I'm going to get gold out of a vending machine.
And there's a Korn Street sign too.
And then he's like, well that's an interesting feature in Dubai.
I didn't realize that they were such fans of Korn.
Well, gee mister, where am I headed?
Well, Shrek, we're putting you in Bakersfield.
That is the best place for a guy named Shrek to live, I think.
And at first he's like a little hopeful. He's like, Bakersfield, Haiti? No, no, you wish
Buster. Bakersfield, California.
Yeah, and we're giving you two choices of jobs. You can either be a bartender at Denny's
or you can taste the oil that comes out of the Derrick's to make sure it's good.
I'll take the oil job. Actually, that position was just filled
after I told you.
Unfortunately donkey took that one.
It's all the Bakersfield.
Bakersfield is a perfect city, man.
It's just like it's geographically.
It's like the fucking biggest city in the world.
Like there's you it's impossible to leave yet to drive through.
It takes like three hours and it is all just oil.
Derrick's just pumping up and down. Yeah, it's so cool. I recently got to see the
Gorgeous skyline of Gary, Indiana. Oh
No, oh my god, dude. Yeah. Yeah very at some point very fun. Look at it not be in
Ditties are so gracious and and gorgeous that at some point you have to refer to them as she as if they are a boat
Absolutely, and I think Gary, Indiana and Bakersfield. I mean those those girls those pretty girls can sing
You know what I'm saying?
Yep.
Every night, I mean, just the people are howling at the moon because they're so excited to
be there.
You know?
Yeah, absolutely.
I crushed my foot with an ATM!
Howling beautiful siren songs.
Yeah, those are, I mean, if they're not sister cities, they should be.
Yeah, twin cities.
And you know what I would do to two twin girls.
Oh my god, what would you do?
live in both of them at different times.
Yep.
Or at the same time if I was brave.
Yeah, if I was mega rich, I would have one house, Dunkin Donuts front property in Gary
Indiana, you know, wake up every morning, look out on my beautiful view of the wall
of the Dunkin Donuts right in front of my apartment.
And then I would have an underground bunker in Bakersfield, California, where the tubes
of the oil lines, they were sucking the oil straight from under my apartment, through my
apartment, and those were the support beams of the entire building, and then up to the
surface.
I would live as a mole man.
And that would be kind of my vacation home, you know?
Although both of them could be considered vacation homes.
And then in the winter, I guess I Airbnb one.
Yeah.
I mean, if I was mega rich, I'm talking a house in Baco.
I'm talking a house in Gary, Indiana.
I mean, I'm talking a house in Lowell, a house in Des Moines.
I mean, I have a house in Poop Town.
Oh, Boise.
Yeah, Boise and Poop Town.
Poop Town.
I mean, really beautiful in the winter.
I really thought that the Brooklyn Nets were going to move to Poop Town.
I really thought that was coming, but you know, they aren't so lucky.
You know, Poop Town hasn't won, do you know that they haven't won a major sports championship
in Poop Town?
That is insane reverse the years. I don't think ever you know, because they don't because the because poop town isn't real
And don't have a single
Sports championship in a major sport at least you know, I don't know about double-a titles
You know
Yeah, I heard they have a really good ping-pong team. I
Would love to do a tour of all of those kinds of cities. I that would be so sick, dude
Gary, Indiana, Bakersfield, Baton Rouge.
Yeah.
Um, uh, what's, what's the one in Texas?
It's like that.
I don't know.
I feel like Fort Worth kind of sucks, but it's not like that kind of, I'm sure a ton of people
will tell us all the cities that suck after this comes out.
I'm sure we, um, more people than we want to will tell us which ones are good and bad.
I mean, if you ask me, only good cities, Boston.
I mean, only good.
Cheers to that brother.
Right.
Dude, I just got, I will say there's nothing more exciting than getting LaCroix in the
mail.
Yeah.
And just fucking, oh dude.
Because also, they don't put that in another box.
There's no wondering what it is.
It arrives, you know?
It's LaCroix.
It's not in a cardboard fucking whatever.
It's cheap as shit if you buy it online.
I don't know that I've ever had.
And you just pop it open.
I think I might have had LaCroix like once or twice in my life, but I can't even remember
what it tastes like.
Is it just water?
Is it one of those things where people make a tweet that's like, it's like water, but
you smell a fruit when you drink it?
Well, this one's key lime flavored, tastes damn near a key lime pie.
Plus, there's two satisfactions to the act of drinking La Croix.
Number one is drinking it.
It's just enjoyable.
Number two is walking up to both the recycling bin and the trash bin right next to each other
and consciously throwing it in the trash can.
just
recycling into the trash at the end of the day. So I mean,
I don't want to be the idiot who's making extra work for the workers.
Well,
my big thing is if I walk outside and if it's too hot,
I throw it in the recycling. If it's too cold, I throw it in the trash.
And then it kind of, I do that enough that in the months of like, you know,
like September to November, it's usually pretty cool.
And then I guess I overdo it a little bit and it gets cold again.
Right. I, well in my, the system I use in my apartment, I have,
I have a blue bin and a brown bin, okay?
And the blue bin is recycling and some trash,
and the brown bin is trash and some recycling.
- That's a really good system.
Yeah, 'cause I don't know if you've seen Toy Story 3,
but they use a magnet to suck all the toys out anyway.
- Exactly, yeah.
- So it's not a big deal, you know?
- Plus I'm not colorblind,
but I like to pretend I am when I'm throwing away trash.
I don't even know if colorblind people have a problem with blue and brown, but I do.
Did you know that like 1 in 10 men are colorblind?
Is that true?
Yeah.
Like some level of colorblindness.
That's one of the, I don't think I only know like one colorblind person.
I wouldn't, if I was colorblind, I'm not, but if I was, I don't think I would admit
it.
I think a lot of people don't even know they're colorblind.
I think it's humiliating to be colorblind.
Yeah, it's embarrassing, dude.
Yeah.
Oh, I can't, I can't tell the difference between, like, imagine playing chess.
Yeah, I mean, well, this is do people to imagine playing chess on a pink and green chessboard
Do colorblind people genuinely have to memorize the position of the red and green light on a traffic light?
It was like if I pulled if I suddenly became like if I became colorblind tomorrow
And I was at a traffic light and I couldn't tell like if all the lights didn't have color
Yeah, I don't know. I don't be able to do it
Well, you could also like I know the middle ones got to be yellow, right?
Well, the middle one has to be yellow.
But also, I feel like as long as you're at somewhat of a crowded intersection,
as long as nobody's running the light, you can kind of look around
and look around at everybody, like, both feet, one foot on each,
either the gas pedal and the brake, and then you look around and you say,
"Oh yeah, we're all stopping, yeah, we all know it's red.
Yeah, we're just gonna stop, it's a stop sign light.
We're all gonna stop."
Stop sign or a go sign. I would have a lot of trouble. Yeah
Yeah, it's listen. It's gray light. Okay, we stop at the gray light. Everybody knows that we go at the gray light
It's just how it is
Everyone knows our rules of driving and that's why I'm stopping with all you guys if you're convertible down
Yeah, okay, oh yeah yet another gray light for me to stop at yeah, I know what to do I'm a great driver
Okay, but here's the thing what if what if it's one of the ones with the arrows?
Because those turn green and red right no they don't
Yeah, they turn green they do turn green and red is there one where the arrow can be green or red in the same spot
It can there's one where it can be green red and there's one with a hundred lights
And it can be a million different colors, and you don't know what any of them mean
Is there one that's like a Christmas tree is that what you're asking is there one is there a Christmas tree I?
Think that might be a more efficient way to do stoplights, right?
I think a more efficient way to do stoplights is if we listen
This is how we this solves the economy this solves traffic just put a guy at every intersection
Every single one he tells everybody go then you know if you're in a big hurry you say hey, man
It's like taking a really long time
I got to go pee really bad and that guy over there. I can tell just looking at him
He doesn't have to go pee. I mean no guy who?
Would have to go pee would be sitting that still and the guy would be like that's actually
Holy shit, that's actually such a good idea is like a like a lot
You know
Sometimes you'll be sitting at a stoplight for like two or three minutes
Like you should be able to plead your case for why you should be able to to just run the light
Yeah, exactly. That's what I'm saying. There's okay, and if you don't you know, whatever if you don't want it
I mean, I know the government hates giving freaking people jobs nowadays, you know, that's all they all they're trying to keep us down
So if you don't employ a crossing guard or a traffic light guard or whatever kind of guard that is Coast Guard
I don't know whatever the hell
You can just make an app. Okay, and I can type it
I can yeah, I can put to the green light and I can type into the app. I'm actually not in such a hurry today
So I'll just wait at this green light and let the other person go you press send
Someone in like a call center or something. They read your your request about 28 to 30 minutes later. They approve it and
You're allowed to wait a little extra time
To let the other person go absolutely and eventually, you know - because you know, that still involves government hiring people
They could have it be an AI system, right?
Where you text of basically a robot but then if the smart people I guess would start texting them kind of robot
Excuses for why you have to because they could relate to that a little easier. Uh-huh, you know
I have to get it. It could also just be the president's job. They don't have to hire anyone then
My cuz everybody always says I am off to the president a little bit
Oh, the president doesn't do anything. All they do is fucking play golf and watch TV
Okay, well then give him this job, you know, exactly make him into a traffic light judge. Yeah, they sit there
Maybe maybe it can just be on every other judge also has to do that
So they in the middle of their trial that they're judging over they get a ping on their phone
They have to look and they have to judge like okay. This guy is
is having a baby but the other person
at the light is having
to babies
you know what
what was the judgment here yeah they have to order it also screen swerve around
each other that could be an option
and then they get the notification on their phone
and it tells and it reroutes them on google maps to see what around
exactly it's a perfect okie over a thing around each other and children turned
fifteen degrees to the right it says
yet could also be like
Circa go around each other in a circle. So it looks really cool from a satellite because
They're doing traffic pictures right now both of you
Yeah, because also it's it's easier for them to film stuff like that
It could be good for fast and furious the directors wouldn't have to wall anything off
They just send to people's traffic apps. Okay crash your car now
Yeah, that's the future of government subsidies for film
Yeah, is that we will start having just random cars random teslas will be hijacked to do that's what they're gonna if we get self-driving cars
That's what they're gonna do. You're gonna yeah, you're gonna be like you're testing
Lock up the controls and be like oh you are now on set for fast and furious 23
And you yeah, so i'm required to flip this car over and launch it into space
Dude I I rode in a tesla for the first time ever and it was uh, and it was a lift a lift picked me up
An $8 lift from the movie theater to my hotel was in a Tesla and then the lady
told me that they were filming she this is in LA she was like I was like oh yeah
like I'm a comedian she started asking me about shit and she was like oh oh you do
you do movies and television and I was like not really like all movies and
television recently Dave they come to my house and they are filming pornography in
my house. I was like, what? She's like, Oh yes. And one,
one man he comes in and I think he is so handsome.
And my, and my, my daughter, she comes up to me and she says,
he is almost as famous as Justin Bieber.
So I, that was like, you're one of the only experience I've ever been in a Tesla.
You're a guy who tells people in an Uber or Lyft that you're a comedian.
I didn't say it to me. I just said that. I was like, I was like,
I do like I was somebody I see like, oh, what do you do?
I was like, I you know, I just do stuff.
I gotta say with your chest hang out a little bit.
Yes, with your chest.
I although I did my dad's friend while I was on vacation.
He was like, so I hear you have a podcast.
What's it called?
And I just said I'm not allowed to tell you.
Yeah, and then let me think it's not that I can't have like
a bit embarrassed, but I just don't want if you tell a Lyft
driver, they're comedian.
They assume that you've seen whatever stand-up special that
Is the only one they've seen in their life. They're like, oh, oh my god
They're like have you ever seen like this jeff foxworthy routine and they talk that's actually 30 minutes
That's actually why i like doing it is because with like taxi drivers
The the if they ask you what your occupation is the crazier thing that the craziest thing you can say pulls out
To them it like makes them think that it's okay to say whatever they want. That's true
Yeah, they will they do start saying they do start saying insane stuff. Yeah
So like maybe like I think the best move is like if somebody is like,
hey, like, what do you like?
What do you do for a living?
And you're just like I'm an evil clown like they first of all,
they'll just believe you because like, oh, yeah, I tried to kill a kid
once actually.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, like they'll just say anything, you know, and she was one of
these people who like that who like won't like let you roll down
the windows unless you talk to her, you know, so like I really was
trying to get a lot out of her. And I got that she's a she is a has a
pornographer's house and a famous famous pornographer came there. I don't want I
don't mind the Lyft driver I don't mind talking to Lyft driver but they better
be talking telling me about their life story. They better be telling me a whole
lot of interesting stuff. I'm gonna tell even one detail about my life. A hundred
percent dude. I better hear the early years, the middle years, the now years
before I'm getting to anything. Yeah I need to ask them more shit. I had a guy
one time in Providence tell me that he was he he was like there the people
there the he always he was like a just tell me about like the cops and he was
like yeah if you like if you like steal like a like a power bar the cops will
take you to the train tracks and beat you to death and then he just started
talking about how much he wanted to fuck like girls.
And he was like, yeah, like he was like, yeah, dude,
like I want to fuck like a 20 year old girl.
And we were like, oh yeah, man,
how about a 19 year old girl?
And he's like, oh yeah, dude, that's even better.
And we were like, oh yeah, how about an 18 year old girl?
And he was like, oh yeah, that's seriously good.
- The Uber driver I had when I was going to Chicago
to the airport, I was in an Uber and the guy was like,
oh, where are you headed?
I was like, oh, I'm going to Chicago to visit some friends.
And he was like, I went to Chicago once.
It's a beautiful city.
It has an incredibly high homicide rate.
Which is what he said to me immediately.
I was like, nice man.
- Damn dude.
- Yeah.
- That's a, I think as an Uber driver,
you do have to have some facts like that,
no matter what somebody says.
- I think he was trying to find out if I was racist or not.
So to see if he could say racist stuff to me.
- Why do they always,
these guys have to know other racist people.
Just have that conversation with them.
Yeah, you don't need to do like, "When is the narwhal baking?"
You're not, why are you trying to kite me into that?
Yeah, like, why are you trying to like, get me to like, talk to you about, you know, like,
and also they're like so, they start so subtle, you know?
Yeah, and so you start out agreeing with them, because you're like, "Oh, you're just trying to make conversation,"
and then they hit you with something, something crazy, and you've already, you got, you got lulled into it.
Yeah, they'll still always start,
"I don't know, man, I don't know."
Yeah, cuz they'll always be like, I'm in the fucking the
Seriously some bad traffic today. You'll be like, oh, yeah, man. They're like, you notice what kind of people are in those cars
Yeah
And then you look around and it's all like the same looking Hawaiian guy wearing like
coconut bra
And you look at him and you're like, you know what?
Now that I think about it, there is a lot of big Hawaiian guys driving cars today.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
Shrek, if you're listening, please get in contact with me.
Yep.