You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
What about now?
What about today?
What if I'm meant to be more than I'm made to be?
Okay, again.
What about now?
Nice. Okay. And again.
What about today?
Wait, wait. Again? Twice as fast?
Who sings this?
Hold on, I have to look up the lyrics.
Just sing the same part again.
I don't even know if that's right.
Just keep singing it, it was good.
No, let me...
Oh my god, let me sing...
If I'm singing Daughtry, I'm getting it fucking right.
I'm losing that tingly feeling you were giving me.
What about now?
What about today?
what if you're me all that I was mad never went away what if it's lost behind
we could never find baby before it's too late
no we're gonna do that in post we're gonna do that in post no we're not you're
gonna make him edit news and you think it's a fast high-pitched and I'll slow
it down to sound normal okay beautiful that peaked I gotta turn my mic down
another premium did we yeah ever we want uh-huh that's true
from New York it's Saturday night it's not Saturday night and there's not that
many people in new york
there's not even that many people in new york
if you look at the numbers
Adolf Hitler
featuring Adolf Hitler
yeah, Chewbacca's there too
Adolf Hitler and Chewbacca are the two new SNL featured players
my friend Dan
and me
me, the swaggy, the swaggy
yeah and that's me yeah that's me Kayla Pitts I'm here too
that's what I read yourself had this crazy white boy good on SNL you guys
want to read more Daughtry lyrics no dude not really my daughter's lyrics
shadows fill an empty heart as love is fading let's write a Daughtry song right
now we could honestly I love drinking beer on the no doctor no you're going to
country did not trees about yeah not trees about finding love when all hope
is lost yeah through the fog I see you that's right
and we got it from shelter dog has a 10-foot tail and it's broken it's a limp
tail dog has a 10-foot tail I could fix your 10-foot tail a dog with a 10-foot
tail scary yeah that's that could be a creepy pasta that was like Dautry's
horror classics yeah Dautry comes from like a weird point into like the post 9/11
like we need to make movies about a family rescuing a dog that dies at the end
yeah yeah like Marley and me and Dottree are like synonymous in my mind for sure
yeah they should have done a Dottree Halloween album oh my god
finding love while you're being chased by a vampire?
Monster Mash!
Now it seems like a monster may be chasing us
But we can't find true love
love was a mummy what about Dautry goes goes hip-hop Dautry goes Dautry goes
crunk okay that might be good crunk so is Dautry
right so it's the Dautry voice but the lyrics change to be yeah okay so it's
Dautry but he's singing like Cobra Starship snap your fingers and do your
step wait no cuz that's a different level so what if it's Daughtry goes punk goes
crunk Daughtry goes R. Kelly
who would say so if he's singing same girl he's got to have somebody on the
song with him it's just R. Kelly it's just Daughtry and R. Kelly I was gonna
say like a Dautry and David Cook sing same girl together. Dautry and Dane Cook that might be
a hit. Oh my god that would be great. How did Dane Cook never make a rock album? He should have.
Before he died how did he never do that? You would think that that's like. Dude he could call it Dane
Rock. That would be great I would love to see him walk into a guitar center and point at like one of
those V guitars. Yeah. Immediately just be like that one. Yeah. That. Not the Gibson one but like
like the Randy Rhoads signature one. Yeah, yeah, like a Walmart guitar.
Like that's it. Dane Cook has a new line of first act guitars being sold at
Walmart. This is actually news. This is just... I'm just reading the news. Is this news? Are you breaking this right now? Yeah.
Whoa dude. This is huge. Yeah, Dane Cook, one of the first... Dane Cook, I mean, come on.
When he played with the Stones it was just, it was crazy. It was just electric, you
know yeah yeah when he picked up the the Grateful Dead spot after John Mayer also
died yeah that's huge man yeah yeah two great comedians filling in for Jerry
Garcia. Dane Cook on iTunes they used to have like celebrity playlists
like they would ask celebrities to post like oh what's on your iPod right now
and the Dane Cook I listened to the Dane Cook playlist a lot yeah one and the
Carlos Mencia one. Carlos Mencia had a lot of disturbs.
Yeah, he had the disturbed sound of silence. No, but he actually he had liberate by disturbed
on it and I thought that was cool because it was in Tony Hawk's Underground too.
And he was like and you got to listen to the lyrics too because it's saying
liberate your mind and people don't do that nowadays. Yeah. Do you think Carlos
Mencia has ever done any any mind expanding drug like LSD or mushrooms?
No. I don't think he doesn't need to. He doesn't need to. He's already got a mind. Dude, if
you if you put LSD in the mind of Mencia he would be normal. That's right, yeah.
You can, if you pretend to be Mexican long enough you start tripping. Mm-hmm.
Yeah, it's true. Yeah. Yeah, it's called the mind's peyote. Uh-huh. Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, his pineal gland. Yeah. Yeah, puts out peyote. Mm-hmm.
peyote is the one psychedelic I don't think I would do the one you would do
ayahuasca you do salvia on a dare a dare that's a disrespecting the fucking tree
gods dude you can't do that no I wouldn't do ayahuasca either I think I
think if it's got too much of like a spiritual thing I know that it's just
like if it's not just like LSD or mushrooms or it's just like you do it
with your friends you know you're gonna leave that leave that to the engines no
No, that's not what I'm saying.
That's kind of what you're saying.
You're a cowboy and there are engines.
I don't want to appropriate their drugs.
You want to get rid of their drugs and the people who use them?
We should do an ayahuasca trip, dude. Wouldn't that be sick?
No, are you kidding me?
Freak the fuck out.
It'd be the next documentary we do. It's us all going to fucking Brazil and vomiting.
Yeah, just having the worst time of our lives.
Just all of us just screaming.
(laughing)
My eyes are too big for my head!
- Our heads are being patted by the Oompa Loompas
fucking giving us the drugs.
And we're just screaming, no!
- I think it would probably ruin all of us forever.
- Yeah, I don't think that.
I don't think I would survive ayahuasca.
- I don't think any of us would.
- Everybody who does ayahuasca,
everybody either invents Google,
or they come back and they're like,
yeah, I haven't been able to look at a TV for like 15 years.
- Yeah.
- They just freak out too much.
I left my wife there. She's still doing ayahuasca.
He had unlocked a demon that was in my house the whole time.
I would do...
The textures in my house don't load anymore.
[laughter]
Gary's mod errors is everywhere I look.
And my son...
My son's just a floating, giant, red, flashing error.
Yeah, the G-Man is in my house now.
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
I would do Salvia with you guys. I want to get trapped in Salvia like Ari Shafir did.
It's legal in Mass too. I've said so many times that I would do it and Caleb's like,
"I don't think you would." And I kept saying, "I changed my mind."
You did change your mind just now?
I don't think I could do it.
I just remembered Ari Shafir got stuck in a fish society when he did Salvia.
Yeah.
yeah he took Salvia on a podcast and then he just like passed out and then woke up
and he's like put me back in put me back in what happened he's like I lived seven
years as a fish and my family got destroyed when I woke up that's that's
what every Salvia trip I've ever heard of is like it's like oh I turned into I
turned into a barrel and I rolled down a hill for 10,000 years and I had an entire
family of barrels up Patrick froze yeah I just froze he just did he froze cuz he
did salvia yeah I froze I did salvia and I froze yeah it's always fish I always
hear fish stories about salvia I always hear wood I hear a game a I hear came a
carpet yeah I hear wooden object stories mostly I feel like people are like I
turned into a fence or a table or something my friend's brother said is uh
uh... his he took it and then
everybody around him had fish heads
that's kinda cool like a captain beefheart thing yeah yeah or like the
song fish heads maybe he was listening to the song fish heads and that's why that happened
he wouldn't even take the salvia
what if his friends were fish and salvia just let him put on the
they live glasses exactly that's what they fish that's what salvia does
they some fish it shows you that you actually have been
you actually have been a carpet for a thousand years and salvia just kind of opens your eyes.
Yeah it expands your mind to realize that oh no reality is just like I am an oscillating
fan oh reality is just carpets barrels made out of wood and fish people and nobody actually
realizes that until they smoke salvia. Yeah it's not DMT that takes you to the higher
dimension it's salvia. Yeah the real higher dimension is is where everyone is a blade of
grass and there's a dog peeing on us yeah that's what it's like I feel like I
can't do the only time I can do psychedelics is like watching Austin
Powers the only time it's worked for me yeah I don't think I can nature thing
yeah it just ruins me I don't think I could do psychedelics for like I think I
would have ears I would have too many like like cups of coffee unlock memories
in me yeah I can't do fucking like seriously I had a cup of coffee like a
month ago and remembered that I saw a double murder suicide scene one time in
high school and I was like damn this is a strong drug this is stronger than like
caffeine strong as shit yeah and I then I just had I just replayed that in my head
for like a week it like ruined my week cuz I just was thinking too hard yeah
it's bad bro it sucks yeah you know I hate getting too much coffee I actually
I feel like that's a good zone to be in.
Patrick drinks too much coffee on purpose.
I drank too much just before this.
On purpose?
That's true.
Yeah.
Is that why you're so sing-songy today?
Maybe.
Because you have to shit and you're doing the pee-pee dance?
I haven't shit yet, so maybe that's it.
Uh-oh.
You're cruising for a bruising right now.
Ever?
Drinking all that coffee.
No, I haven't shit.
You haven't shit yet ever?
No.
Not ever.
Oh my god.
Not once, not ever.
family who shit once every two weeks. That's pretty cool. That'd be the life for me. Oh my god. Wouldn't that be sick?
They like know like at Wednesday at 11 a.m. I have to be not at a
TJ Maxx because otherwise I'm gonna shit on the floor. Damn. That's a good life to
live. It's pretty yeah. Yeah, a scheduled shit? Yeah. Yeah. That's pretty great.
That would be amazing. On command? I wish I could shit on command. That'd be
even better. Yeah. Right? I might just hold it in and get
hugely fat yeah yeah yeah poop lining and then just use it for one one giant
prank yeah one biggest prank of all time just spill a bucket of shit on a girl
at the prom the most epic epic poop prank yeah exactly go if that happens in carry
would end a different yeah she would have been happy
She'd be like, "Oh, it's a prank."
"Oh, it's a prank."
"You guys, you guys."
She saw the blood and she thought that they were trying to kill her.
If she had seen poop, she would know it was just a smelly prank.
Yeah, she would think that there's a big animal taking a crap on top of her.
She would have used her telekinesis to like play really cool music for everyone to dance to.
Everybody still would have died from just laughing so hard though.
Yeah, that's true.
It would have been the same ending.
they would have gone just completely berserk laughing and slapping they would
have hit their knees so hard they fell off they hit the knees so hard that the
bottom part of their leg flies off popped off like a Lego pop-off and it causes a fire
somehow yeah yeah yeah we go into the punch bowl we should write that
disgusted Carrie but with poop yeah her name's stinky yeah yeah
smerry smellery smellery smellery toilet toilet poopy crappy crap crap fair
very
what about hairy and it's all hair that they throw a bunch of hair on her yeah
just a bunch of different like a locks how much like donation bin they just how
How much hair do you think you would have to collect?
50 feet.
50 feet of hair?
Yeah.
I'm saying, like how much hair do you think, in a bag, how much hair do you think...
I thought you were asking how much to have at 50 feet.
No.
That's my bad.
How much hair do you think you would have to put in a bag for it to like actually hurt
you if it fell on you?
Like hair, hair from the top of a building.
What kind of bag?
kind of bag well that's the thing a steel bag yeah it's gonna be in a steel bag
yeah okay regardless of anything a lead bag dropped off the Empire State
Building how much hair how much hair do you think would need to be in the bag do
you guys think you could survive a penny to the head from the Empire State
Building I could I think I could my skull is very I'll be wearing a hat first of
all yeah I think a hole would go through your head like a sniper a hole would
realize I would hit the brim the brim of what the brim on camera tatted my
baseball hang so penny would fall and it would bounce off the brim and it would
kill you do you think it would go through the brim no yeah not my brim I
have a special brim no I've got any going it I got a different I've got a
different kind of brim I put kind of rim I put special metals and chemicals into
my brim you don't have a fucking I have a power for him did it's basically it's
it's invented so that if a super villain could try to attack me I could deflect it
using the brim only they should do like a cool metal hat yeah it's called a helmet
have guys like a hat that's hard just have like just have like like like lids
like new era like wiggers walking around with their heads we should bring back
chain mail punched Oh do the chain mail hat no I think I think we should bring
back chain mail but specifically like those jokes your grandparents send you
yeah about fucking Polish people yeah yeah that's what I'm down I got a lot of
those is a king that back yeah that's what I meant maybe I should start I know
that's what you meant original that's what I know we should maybe I should
start wearing chain mail shut up to me you shut up shut up dude you shut up shut
up Caleb if you got on wait Pat can you hold on having a shut up war shut up you
shut up shut up shut up the hell up shut up shut up right now yeah you idiot says
shut up guess you just said it you said what said what the s-word what s-word
the su word I don't know you're talking about shut up I went falling into my
friend's trap Caleb if you got if you got chainmail or any kind of Knight's
armor people would think that you're too into Crusader Kings and I think that
would be a problem yeah no I was a great gamer yeah what a nightmare
Is that like people were radicalized by Crusader Kings or something? That's why they say like days full to really like the alt-right people
I think I think they just like history
Deis was in they said it in some I don't know if it was Crusader King Crusader King
That that radicalized all those are all right people
I think is I think the people who said deus vault were in a different game
But I think castle crashers definitely did turn people to the Nazis
Not after I sure is fucking Crusader castle crashers
Turns people it's the chainsaw. It's the chainsaw that does it they see it, and they're like this is we need to go back to living
like yeah
Embrace tradition yeah
Three guys who look like you different colors. Yeah, we need to start dressing in different colors again. Yeah
Yeah, we would have been a good a good night trio. I think we have I
I think we could we could probably take down like a Medusa.
Yeah or a dragon I feel like. We could kill a dragon.
What would you guys knight adjectives be?
Sir Patrick the...
The round.
You would be yeah you would be like the round table.
Yeah.
They'd call you the round table.
They'd call me the pound.
I'd sit at you.
Sir Patrick the pound.
Yeah.
Whoa.
That sounds pretty cool.
Obviously I'd be Caleb the Great.
I'd be Cameron the Greatest.
I think that might be the plunderer.
If there was a group of knights and one of them was the great and one of them was the greatest.
I am Caleb the Awesome.
And I'm Derek the even more awesome.
King Arthur the most greatest.
King Arthur the king is his.
Arthur the I'm on a boat mm-hmm that might be scary
King Arthur the swaggy and then he's uh-huh yeah yeah yeah King Arthur the
Mr. two-fly we should have we should that's what we should instead of buying
a house or doing whatever with it the castle yeah yeah I feel like we could
afford one in like Malaysia have you seen that uh you know that episode of
doomsday preppers where the guy has a castle and he's making his family
compete to see who gets to live with him in the castle but it's like a really
shitty castle we could probably buy a castle like that yeah have you guys seen
that episode I think I have it's really the best one is the the out the ranch
one yeah that one's so good a muzzle break where the guy yeah yeah that's my
date or the guy cries yeah I think the only one I've seen is the one with the
like the 13 year old kid whose mom is like would you save me if we were in an
apocalypse yeah she's like no no and she's like you're grounded and he's like
"Okay, fine, I'd save you!"
Wait, I'm trying to find the text.
This is the best episode of Doomsday Preppers.
Let me...
It's called the Alamo Ranch or something?
And the guy looks exactly like Quentin Tarantino.
Not exactly.
He looks like he could be Quentin Tarantino's cousin.
And he's got all the fucking mannerisms and everything,
but it's just Quentin Tarantino as a Doomsday Prepper.
What about Ben 10 Tarantino,
and he uses his casio to turn into the Wu-Tang Clan?
Yeah, so then he can say the N-word.
That might be kind of cool right?
Yeah.
It's so quintessentino kid.
No I was the Wu Tang Clan when I wrote that script.
Yeah.
He don't understand.
Season 2 episode 4.
You guys should watch season 2 episode 4 of Doomsday Preppers.
It's one of the best TV episodes of all time.
Yeah.
Keep going.
Of all time?
It's so good dude.
It really is so good.
Usually they do two families in an episode but this family is just so fucked up they
do the full episode on them.
It's like I'm going to rewatch it after this.
- How do they decide who gets to live in the castle?
Does he put them in trials?
- No, that's a different episode.
- That's a different one, yeah.
- Wow.
- This is the ranch.
- They live on a ranch in Texas,
and yeah, it's really something.
Highly recommend.
- What would we call our castle when we buy one?
- Castle Cameron?
- I said it first.
- I was thinking Castle Daylock Caleb.
(laughing)
- I was thinking the three guys.
- I was thinking Castle Tayo Cruz.
- Hmm, Castle Dynamite?
- Yeah, Castle Dynamite.
- Castle Dynamite sounds pretty cool.
- Castle Dynamite's pretty cool, yeah.
- Nobody has to know it's named after the Taya Cruz song.
- Right, but it is the doorbell.
(laughing)
- But people think that's just the theme.
- Yeah.
- People will be like, well that matches the dynamite.
- They won't, yeah.
They don't know that we actually do have Taya Cruz
in the dungeon and he performs for us.
- Every single time somebody presses a button,
it pokes his belly button.
(laughing)
- He sings into a little gramophone horn.
- He lights up the door.
- He starts singing.
- Every time that they ring the doorbell,
the feeding tube feeds him.
- So, he gets one drop of sweet water.
- Yeah.
- He gets a snack that looks like him.
(laughing)
- Would you sing the doorbell song for a Tayo snack?
- Yes.
- Yeah, and he says--
- I think, no, I would let Tayo Cruz live with us.
- I would let Tayo--
- Just like a guy.
- Yeah, but in the dungeon and he can't get out.
- I wouldn't let him live in the dungeon.
I would let him get out.
- I would torture him.
I would put on a big wooden plate. I would throw knives at him. I would hear his party stories about how he hung out with David Guetta.
I would do it for no reason. I would literally torture him to death for no reason. He wouldn't do anything to me and I would just hurt him really bad. I'm serious.
I would put him into a big bowl filled with hot black oil.
Pat, you can't be a-- we're not gonna let you be a knight if you're not gonna be
willing to torture somebody. There's no such thing as a knight who doesn't kill people.
Well, what did he do? He hasn't told us about any gold. I believe I'm Patrick the Fair.
Yeah, he's in the dungeon, so he has to have done something. Patrick the Fair, because you're eating funnel cakes and corn dogs.
That's right, bitch. Yeah, I'm guessing my weight constantly. I'm bringing you to the dungeon, but the dungeon in our
castle full arcade Chuck E. Cheese style yeah with a mini carnival. That's why I'm called
Patrick the Fares because I set up a fair. It has one of those roller coaster simulators in it mm-hmm
that are really awesome. Yeah I got the VR one that has Rayman Raving Rabbids on it. Has Rainbow Six Siege in it.
Yeah you're getting you're getting the input of a roller coaster you're shaking around playing it
trying to play Rainbow Six Siege. Yeah you're playing Rain Man Six Siege. Yeah yeah you are
Yeah, you are I'm playing it. I was talking to Patrick. No. Yeah, you are Patrick. So
Me Kayla when we and Caleb said you we both are talking about Patrick anytime. Yeah, and all those times we said shut up earlier
It was a bad
Why do you guys like to torture you in the dungeon with Tyo Cruz, I think maybe if you don't get this castle
I think maybe this castle is better
But dude, you better put on shoes or the castle creep is gonna tickle your feet while you're sleeping in the dungeon.
Oh, I would hate that.
I'm gonna chain you up.
I would hate that so much. Don't let him do that.
I'm gonna have a 50 foot long feather that I tickle you with from upstairs while I watch TV.
Don't!
I'm gonna do it.
Don't, dude!
I'm gonna actually, I'm gonna outline different parts of you like I'm doing plastic surgery on somebody with a sharpie.
And those will be the tickle spots.
Oh, serious?
feather I'm serious it has a curve to it the feather so that I can reach it
downstairs and then I'm gonna tickle your feet and your belly button I'm gonna
Patrick I'm gonna chain you up and I'm gonna give you your bass your bass
guitar and I'm gonna connect it to the pedal but the firmware is not gonna be
updated it updated the but in the dungeon the firmware is not gonna be I
updated you have no actually I guess what and you can't even use your you
can't even use the you can't even use the Xbox Wi-Fi you can't roll back the
firmware update on it or getting you a new pedal that's older the same model
but it's not updated what okay I'm gonna stuff a Wi-Fi hotspot up your ass I wish
I'm gonna keep your head off and I'm gonna slice you why I don't know I'm
just gonna shoot you with a gun I'm just gonna kill you how would we - what's
what would how would you torture us I feel like I'm pretty immune to nature
You couldn't get any info. I don't think I would torture anybody. No, I'm saying if you if you had to torture if we all
Had to torture. It would be so easy to torture. You just keep him up past 11 o'clock and he'll start crying
No, no, I'll do I'll paint I'll paint eyes on my eyelids so you think I'm still awake
well, well, we'll
defend against that I
I will simply counter that actually so it's easy.
Yeah.
Cameron, I'd pull his hair like I'm picking a beet out of the ground.
It would just come out.
It's not real.
No.
Really?
You have a piece?
No, I have a lot of them.
Each one is fake.
Maybe I should get into toupees now that my hair is short.
I thought about it.
I thought about getting a toupee.
It would be pretty funny.
I thought it would be really funny.
Right?
Oh yeah, I forgot about Patrick's funny hair right now.
Yeah.
It's not that funny.
It's pretty funny.
No.
How is it funny?
It's not funny. It's normal.
Yeah.
What's funny about it, Cam?
It was funny. It was funny to look at.
Why is it funny?
Just the way it looks.
How?
It doesn't look good.
What's funny about it?
It's like orange. Bright orange.
It's normal. That's a beanie.
That's a hat.
Oh, my mistake. Oh, his hair isn't funny.
I thought that was his hair on the top of his head.
You fucking hairy piece of shit, Cameron.
You don't know what we go through, dude.
I don't care.
I don't have to care about it.
Yeah, you're right. You're right, it's our fault that we're bald. Yeah, you guys should have worked harder.
At least all my hair will grow back. Yeah. I spend a lot of time meditating and focusing.
My hair doesn't grow on its own. Yeah, you focused on how to not get testosterone.
Yeah, that's right. Mm-hmm. Me and Pat are just high-T'd. We're too high-T. That's the problem.
Yeah, people look at me. They think that guy is running on only testosterone that motherfucker. He'd be dead if one for testosterone
Mm-hmm. Yeah, my balls are pumping too much. You have no blood in you. It's all he all tea purity high tea
Yeah, yeah British tea like an old British lady. Oh, see only you would think that cuz yeah, you're
Immediate thought is your grandma. Yeah, my grandma's not
Yeah, she is.
That's not true.
No.
Her name is Agnes Francis.
That's not true.
Get Agnes Francis Cameron.
When you guys are trying not to cum while you're having sex, do you imagine-
I don't imagine my grandma, if that's where this is going.
Not your grandma.
A grandma?
But an old lady.
That would just make me bust quick.
Because I was talking to Noah about this.
You basically have two moves you can make there.
Baseball or grandma.
bit no I go poop or grandma sometimes I imagine poop yeah yeah and and I have
had to stop because I just lost it and it just killed it for me dude I don't
know I have ADD I can't think sorry baby my imagination is way too good I'm just
way too talented as yeah I thought of 3d 3d rotating a poop in your head sorry I
baby I just I was thinking about poop and then I ended up thinking about a
really great movie idea and now I'm gonna go write that down instead of have sex
with you yeah I thought of the best sitting completely naked at a
typewriter and just clacking out the 3d poop that was that I was fucking to
care of a poop character to my penis you know it's probably the best thing to
think about to keep your to keep yourself going but it's definitely not
good is uh any ISIS beheading you think that would stop me you think I don't
would stop you think that would ever stop me you think I don't know me with
You think you could stop me by making me think about that?
I'll never stop.
You can never stop fucking.
Even if you behead me, I will never stop.
It doesn't fucking matter.
Yeah.
I won't stop, dude.
No, 'cause there's...
You can't do anything with a hole, 'cause I'll just zone in.
Doesn't matter, dude.
Okay, what about just like...
Just zooming in really, really far in your imagination.
If you squint, the trachea could be a pussy.
Oh.
Caleb.
Jesus Christ.
First you do a Saturday Night Live Hitler.
Now you're talking about a fucking...
When I want to keep myself going
I uh...
I think about Jim Gaffigan.
Yeah, but then I'm thinking about
Hot Pockets and then I'm hard again.
Yeah, then I'm getting hard again.
I got a Hot Pocket for ya.
Hot...
Penis.
That's right dude, that's pretty good.
Dude, he's a stand-up.
What about-
We could get him on the show and you're crushing, you're burning that bridge.
Hey, make America gaff again.
Whoa.
Uh-huh.
Ooh.
Yeah.
How about that?
That's good.
When he takes down Trump, he already did.
I think that-
He did.
Yeah, he was mostly-
What the fuck is-
What is Jimmy Kimmel gonna cry about now that Trump isn't president?
The healthcare again?
No, he's gonna be like, "It's all fixed."
No, 'cause he wouldn't cry.
yeah he wouldn't cry about health care yeah he only was crying because his son
that whole thing was like yeah people need health care I mean yeah I'm crying
because my son is who is the son of a billionaire is getting like the greatest
fucking health he was crying because the teleprompter was too bright
teleprompter had cry on yeah just does that yeah no it was scary they turned it
on and they accidentally hit the brightness and it flashed up really
bright and it scared him he started crying he was gonna laugh he was planning
to laugh yeah he was actually gonna do that he was gonna do that late night
whatever it what is America's late-night hosts what do they do now dude yeah dude
Dude, SNL is screwed.
They're just gonna keep doing Trump material.
That's true.
They will, yeah.
For the next few months they're gonna do like
Trump realizing he lost the election sketches every week
and then after Joe Biden's president
they're gonna be like, here's what Trump is up to
at Mar-a-Lago right now.
Dude, I really fucking want
like a late-life Trump reality show now.
Like just follow him until he's dead.
He'll do it. He'll do it right after
he's out of office. He's gotta do it.
of like keeping up with the Kardashians,
but it's just him like renting out like water parks
and rides by himself.
- Yeah, dude, he'll never die.
- He beat COVID.
- That's true.
- He can't die.
- Yeah, the fact that he beat COVID is so insane.
- The fact that he beat COVID is so insane.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I mean, I guess they used all the like
experimental crazy shit on him,
but his whole build is like, you can't.
- Yeah, that's like, that is like,
that is the build that COVID is looking for. Like 80 years old and just a blob under there.
I want to get in that blob, dude.
Oh, poke around on, let me, ooh.
Oh, yeah.
Let me flop on that thing, let the wind escape.
I want to fucking, I want to fuck his, I want to fuck him, dude.
I want to fuck his thigh meat out.
I want to explore his crevices and canyons like a whitewater rafter.
I'm gonna go through him like a fucking hot knife through butter.
Just fucking...
Like a...
You know?
Like a hot...
Just putting a fucking metal rod through a wax figurine.
Like a hot piece of metal drops onto the fucking iceberg.
I'm gonna make a just bore a hole.
Like putting a hot coal in peanut butter.
President Trump, all due respect, I'm gonna make you sizzle.
I'm gonna get in him like a hydraulic press.
like a greasy hydraulic press. I wanna get in his thing like a Barbie figure in a hydraulic
press dude. I'm gonna fuckin press you like a panini baby you better watch out. You're
gonna be a cubano and I'm done with you. I'm gonna turn him into the sharpest knife ever
made from cucumber yeah he's gonna be oddly satisfied it's gonna be odd but he
will be satisfied dude I'm gonna play with him like moon sand yeah I'm gonna
squeeze him - yeah oh I'm gonna shoot a non-newtonian fluid up in his butt oddly
satisfying this podcaster's penis fits perfectly within Donald Trump's asshole
I don't think his asshole is what you want to fuck on Trump did yeah I would
get all over him I'd start there and I'd work my way outward I think you could
titty fuck Trump more successfully than like Lisa Ann like I think he'd be like
an easy titty fuck you know because if you're fucking Lisa Ann's titties it's
like fucking a butt crack but if you fuck Trump's like he I bet it forms like an
Illuminati triangle it feels good on my triangle penis mm-hmm I see you know
just it's an idea you I see you I hear you you're valid yeah and also his
sternum is ribbed for my pleasure oh do you think he's got I'm hitting it like a
xylophone as I'm please God what if he's got like peckless and I have it on dude
yes concave chest uh-huh I'm just gonna fuck that oh I would fit right in I could
we could fit together like a puzzle piece I got the reverse I got pectus
Karanatam I curl up in there like a tauntaun mm-hmm I thought he smelled bad
on the outside
I got a fucking smearing off ice. I'm about to go LMFAO
And that's just the bestest facts on area I'm gonna have to apologize for what I do when I party rock that's
That's party rocking too hard man, I did a little party rocking last night. I've you know, I've post party rock brain right now
Yeah, yeah. Yeah
You got you a while you have postpartum depression
New York is so fucking gay right now because last night I just got like trashed
And I was doing coke and I was like, oh fuck what I gotta go home
What time is it and it was 1030 and the bars were closing and I had to just go home and sit in my bed until 3
owned
Life sucks here destroyed do everything. She's now that Biden's in office and
Another hope it's over. Yeah, just fucking just open her up dude. Yeah open up this thing open
(mumbling)
- You guys are coming to New York soon, are you excited?
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah, we're gonna play so much in your apartment, dude.
- Yeah, dude, we're gonna play around.
- Caleb is leaving for an evening to go,
I heard he was going to like some male toy store
or something.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Something like--
- I belong there.
- Yeah, you're the test subject.
- Yeah, I'm one of the toys, like Richard Pryor.
- Yeah.
- It's some kind of toy store that's like--
- Me and Patrick are gonna play so much in your apartment.
- Caleb's going to an adult toy store.
- We're gonna run from the kitchen,
we're gonna run from the kitchen to your bedroom
back and forth, we're gonna jump on the bed,
we're gonna finger paint on the walls,
we're gonna use this stuff.
- Caleb and Jenna, look what we made you!
(laughing)
- If we paint the fridge completely black.
- We put chalkboard paint on it.
- We're gonna take all the food out of your fridge
and freezer and we're gonna play army men with it
'cause you guys don't have any army men.
- I'm gonna get one of those like kids cash registers
and put it down and be like,
"Can you guys watch the register while I'm gone?
"Like this is your job."
And I'm gonna hand you those like plastic baby car keys.
- We're gonna have a twins pool party
in the toilet and bathtub.
(coughing)
Where we hold hands across.
Twins you say?
Yeah, 'cause one of us is in the toilet
and one is in the bathtub.
Yeah.
If you come home early, you get a piece of it.
I can guess which one you want.
You get a piece of the action.
You want a piece of me?
Hey man, you want a piece of us?
We're gonna be playing in the toilet and the bathtub
if you want.
I have been wanting to go to the pool really bad.
Hey man, you wanna step outside
and play in the toilet and bathtub with me and my friend?
Hey man.
Hey buddy, how about we step outside
and play in the toilet?
(laughing)
- How about that?
- How about we split?
- It's gonna be you, me, the port-a-body.
- Yeah, you and me.
- We're gonna be splashed around.
- The bathroom, a few plastic beakers,
maybe a spoon, an eyedropper,
one of those little floaty rubber duckies.
- And I got a Chewbacca toy.
- There's a log in there,
there's a log in there
'cause I couldn't figure out how to flush.
- I got this Chewbacca, it kinda looks like a poop.
(laughing)
- Why do you have a Chewbacca toy with you?
- I do actually have a Chewbacca with me.
This is Chewbacca, Shadows of the Empire.
This is him in Bounty Hunter disguise.
Yes it is, look it up.
- Okay.
Says no.
- It is.
- No, I just looked it up.
- No.
- Yeah.
- You're, don't even try to lie to me about this.
- Sorry, am I ruining your fun?
- You are.
- Don't care.
- Damn, I should have bought this in the pack
instead of just at a flea market
because in the pack it comes with an axe and a big gun.
- I hate you. - Wow.
- I actually hate you.
- Could have had a cool toy, but no.
My toy is not cool enough at this point.
- Of course Patrick is the only guy
who would have a cool toy and say,
"Oh, it's not cool enough."
- Also, that toy is style over function, dude.
- What do you mean?
- I don't care if it--
- He's in a bounty hunter disguise.
- Style, that's style.
Sorry, sorry, excuse me, this is--
Do you know what that does for the story?
Does his gun shoot a projectile?
No, it doesn't.
But he has an axe.
He has a vibro axe.
No, it doesn't shoot a projectile.
What the f- What can you use the toy to do?
Okay, so if you have the other, if you have regular plainclothes Chewbacca.
Which you don't.
How do you know I don't?
You can play a game where he becomes a bounty hunter, but you don't have that.
Exactly.
- I'm at 2,200 by default, dude.
- You guys are so rude.
- You're rude.
- What do you mean I'm rude?
You're fucking rude about my toys.
- This is a real toy, okay?
- No, that's a PlayStation controller.
- This is a PlayStation 4 controller.
- That's not a toy.
- This is function over style.
- No, it's not. - This is not a toy.
- No, it's not a toy. - This is an adult's toy, okay?
- No.
- What you have is a toy for a paralyzed child, okay?
What I have is a toy for a thinking adult.
You love you.
- Nobody say what this is.
Nobody say what this is.
But this is an adult's toy for you.
- A penis pump?
- No, it's a penis pump.
Yeah, I use it to fucking make orange juice.
- A syringe full of saline?
(laughing)
- Yeah, dude, it's an adult toy.
- You freak.
Freakazoid.
- Does the Chewbacca's arms and legs move?
- Yes.
- Are they fully articulated?
- It doesn't have, no, it doesn't have.
- How many points of articulation?
- It has four points of articulation.
It was a 90's-- - That's so few.
Oh my God, he's a baby. - 90's toy.
Look, it's not a baby's toy.
- It actually is.
- It's not. - So why,
then tell me why it rattles.
- It doesn't rattle.
- It rattles when you shake it.
- Okay, shake it right now.
- Shake it right now. - Shake it in the microphone.
(shushing)
- That's you doing that.
- That is you doing that with your toy.
- No, that was you rattling.
- I hate this.
- I'm getting so owned.
- I just wanted to show you guys my cool thing that I have.
you should fucking bury yourself alive I'm not gonna bury myself alive scum I'm
not worthless your dog shit you're in my dungeon dude you haven't you haven't
earned your way out of the time we're so much more your gum from now on every
episode you start in the dungeon and you have to earn your way out yeah yeah and
it's just every other say recess say like three funny guys or you know you
already said three funny yes solve a riddle okay here's the riddle here's the
riddle I am I am so lame and stupid I am stuck in the worst in the world yeah I
I fucking, I fart a hundred times. The whole dungeon smells like my farts cause I can't stop.
I like it when the dungeon creep gets in my feet.
Yeah, no. I don't.
And I'm racist.
And I'm secretly a Nazi.
No. Who am I?
Caleb.
Wrong.
It's Caleb.
You're wrong.
Guess who has double dungeon duty?
Mr. Fucking Farting Nazi.
I'm not a farting Nazi. You're not a party. Not that's a farting Nazi. I'm not the farting not sir Patrick the farting Nazi
Yes, you're a sodding tosser
Whoa, oh my god, you just sold a Polish man. He's a sodding tosser. Yeah, not cool
It's kind of guess this guy really does have tea in his veins instead of blood if you know what I'm saying
That's right the tea for the Third Reich
No, yeah
You guys, can we just have one episode where I'm not the punching bag?
No.
What did you say?
Like, what?
Stop dressing like a punching bag.
The punching bag.
Punching bag.
You are the punching bag, because you're chained up in the dungeon and we're fucking
trading blows on you right now with a wooden sword.
Yeah, you guys are trading blows on me.
Yeah, we are.
You chained me up so you could suck me.
Now we're blowing at you like a wolf at a brick house.
Yeah.
You better not.
I'm going to blow you away.
I'm serious.
You better not.
I'm going to blow you away, you little piggy.
Better not blow me away.
I'm going to come to your house.
I'm going to blow it away, brother.
No, you better not do that.
You're getting blown.
Oh, oh, curses.
I hate that.
I hate getting blown away.
I'm gonna put you on a peloton in the dungeon and make you fucking sweat.
AHH NO!
Yeah.
No.
I'm gonna put a picture of a donut on the iPad and make you fucking--
You better not!
--fucking fight me towards it.
I'm gonna.
You better not.
Stop pretending you like the dungeon!
This is not gonna work on me.
I'm not gonna let you down there.
You hate the dungeon.
You better not.
You hate it down there.
You hate the dungeon.
You better not do that.
If you like it, it's because it smells like your fart.
There's no computer in the dungeon.
I'd hate being in the dungeon so much.
I hate it.
- Honestly, this is kind of working on me.
- We can't, he didn't answer the riddle.
He can't get out of it.
- Oh, you like it so much in the dungeon, Pat?
How about this?
You're out now.
(laughing)
- No.
- Fooled ya.
- You fucking idiot.
Yeah, no, get out of there.
- Why?
- Come on.
- Oh.
- Get out of the dungeon.
- Come on.
- Listen.
- Please let me stay in the dungeon.
- Listen, I'm telling you right now,
Yes, for a couple more minutes.
Can you stop?
Just get out of the dungeon.
Just get out.
Oh, please.
Okay, listen.
Please let me out.
You're out.
Alright, you're going back in.
No!
You're back in.
Alright, it's locked.
This didn't work like I planned.
Are you stuck in this voice now?
I got hit in the head.
(laughter)
- Yeah, one of those times in the dungeon we fuckin'
- The chain hit the back of my head.
- Crashed you into this wall.
You actually got really hurt.
- Oh, I got so hurt.
- This guy with brain damage,
you only talk like that.
- Yeah, I'll have a McDouble, yeah.
- But like specifically in a--
Oh, totally, yeah.
(laughing)
I want french fries too.
So you want the meal?
Oh yeah, I would love to have the meal.
(laughing)
It's a kids in the hall sketch.
Please stop punching me in the head.
The sarcastic guy is a kids in the hall sketch.
No!
Yeah, we have to rewind it.
No.
You were the one who did it.
I was being sarcastic to you guys about the dungeon.
That's different.
So you stole the idea?
Why are you such a, not only are you a joke,
joke thieves you know where they go oh no the set you go in the second dungeon the
dungeon under the dungeon no it's called the under done what Kayla was doing was
from kids you have to do one good impression to get out of the dungeon
okay oh no I'm stuck in a dungeon again!
I'm bored of you I grow tired of your Gilbert Godfrey impression my thumb is
wavering towards thumbs down right now in my big throne hey Chris I'm stuck in the
dungeon right now is that a guy you know that's the movie that's the movie guy
from Family Guy that's John Benjamin wait hold on let me do Bob's burgers you
Bob's you're gonna say Tina hey data you can you fry up some burgers how's that
how's that
wraps of burgers for me my wife my wife's name do you wanna do you want to get
married to me about a bird shop later
as a bigger what it is so they are not
you would have hit me in the legs peter
i can't feel it you wanna pitch my but
there's a good idea to do it
you know i think they're pretty much but
theater anything you do down there i can't feel like
have been a respect joe from family dot
that is how you know
has joe family dot and i'm here to
right now we have a chance to have a good idea to get the
it is your neighbor
uh...
and welcome to my show
uh... we've got a lot of fun things for you tonight
the dungeon show
featuring
cleveland
hitler
is the same
he's back
he's back again
now hitler would so i was on tender lately he he
he just comes out and starts doing a
attender monologue i'll say this much i hope there's never a hitler run
late-night comedy show
to imagine how bad that would be
him crying about trump
yet do you think it's only so
the heart bad
this is a great hitler who was that was that no i mean here is that is that hit
after picking up the accent from Argentina? Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Hello, I'm Hedler. I'm trying to fit in. I am Hedler.
You know the hardest part about Hitler running away to Argentina was... was his
freaking penis, dude. Everyone could tell that it was him from the mustache. He just refused to
shave it. Yeah. He just made it really thin. Yeah. He was wearing the uniform still, too. He said if I shave this off
Hitler wins the armband yeah he should have definitely changed yeah he should
have changed his clothes that's right ran away his attitude mm-hmm change this
freaking wet diaper they should have made they should make a movie about Hitler
running away to Argentina and then the locals teach him a little something about
the meaning of friendship and happiness and he finally changes his ways yeah
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, it's called-- - That's what I'm saying.
- It's called Finding Hitler.
- Finding Hitler at the end of the world.
- Yeah, and it's called Jojo Rabbit.
- Yep.
The thing about Jojo Rabbit is he did teach that boy
a lot about friendship.
- Yeah.
- I haven't seen it.
- I saw it, it's pretty bad.
- Yeah.
- Pretty not good.
- They took back Hitler.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Finally, somebody did it.
I'm gonna get it. Just Tycho, just Tycho Atiti did. Nobody else did. Yeah. It was just him.
Everyone has to do it. If we really wanna, if we really wanna get rid of the power that
Hitler holds over us, even today, everybody has to dress up like him. Yeah. Tycho Atiti,
you call him Psycho the Creepy. What kind of guy makes a Hitler movie? I mean, come on.
Yeah. Steven Spielberg, I call him Scary Screamsburg. Why the hell would he make a movie about Hitler?
I think that's probably what Hitler would call him.
Yeah.
I think you're inching towards being Hitler right now.
Okay I would call him my favorite director.
Now he feels like you're compensating.
What did Steven Spielberg make?
Everything.
Uh, Hitler.
E.T.
The Jaws.
He made Jaws.
He made The Twilight Zone.
Jurassic Park.
No, did he make The Twilight Zone movie?
No, that was that was uh, that was Jordan Jordan peel. You're right. Yeah, I
Think yeah, I think he made the mid made he made war of the worlds the 9/11 version
Steven Spielberg made
The Twilight Zone movie and then denounced John Landis or something, right?
No, I think that's true. It indiana's down. Yeah, he was a director of a party
So he made the Indiana Zone movie. Oh
Right and he denounced John Lennon. Yeah, you're so stupid
Yeah
It's crazy that that's where there is named Indiana Jones
The what the character of Indiana Jones being named India?
There's probably this is probably like a stand-up bit from 2006 like kids in the hall sketch
No, yeah, I bet it is
What's that what is it say what you say what the joke is that you're stealing the joke would be like some guy
I'm not seeing the joke here. Well one of those schlubby like 2006 comedians being like
So you because you're the one who said it. Isn't it weird that his name is Indiana Jones?
You can't you're the one who just said it so it's not good to say what just
literally just say it. It was the thought that I had in my head. Just say the thought you had in your head.
It's weird that Indiana Jones is named Indiana Jones because that name could
have been anything his name could have been Arizona Smith or like Montana
that's great no that is a good 2006 comedian joke yeah you just put yeah
just it's just like a plug-and-play yeah you just switch out one of the words
Kanye West how about Kanye East yeah you know one of those kind of thing yeah so
this so this Snoop Dogg fellas thinks that says that when the pimp is in the
crib I drop it like it's hot is that a crib he wants me to drop my baby okay I
think hip-hop is seriously a disease all these hip hoppers going in a baby crib
that was that was a big that was a big thing then and stand up to is like these
rap rap fellas are backwards like their hats yeah I'm sick of these rappers
wearing their pants backwards and telling me they're gonna make me jump
crisscross wear their hats forwards and the rest of their their body back no I
think they wore everything backwards cuz it was wiggity wiggity wiggity wack how
do you wear your shoes backwards you get special I think maybe they didn't wear
laces and the shoes like MDMC maybe they had backward shoes it was just the pants
that way they could have backwards shoes how do you mean in that you have to take
your pants all the way off oh yeah you're just going to a stall or you just
eat your pants pee out of your butt yeah I think crisscross is called crisscross
because they the crisscross their penis between their legs to pee behind nice
their bodies could have been backwards you know and they were close normally
that's true I didn't think about that maybe their head was back maybe that's
That's why that guy died so young, because his whole body was backwards, including his
internal organs.
He had backwards body disease.
Yeah.
His heart was backwards and it gave up on him.
His body got confused by his clothes.
Every time he looked in the mirror, his kidneys just didn't know what to do.
Yeah.
They started pushing the toxins into his mouth.
Dialysis is wiggity, wiggity, wiggity, wiggity whack.
I'm bringing wiggity whack back.
No, you're not.
Yeah, with how you look and act.
Because you're wiggity wet.
Oh man. That's like an arrow to my heart.
And you're gonna get slippity slapped.
Oh, you better not slap me.
Yeah.
I wonder if those crisscross guys
when they were older and like fucking groupies
if a girl ever like
unzipped
their pants
and sucked their butt.
you I know what you want zip Oh Pat froze again no no no you're bad you're unfrozen
you'd be thought okay my internet connection is unstable even though I
have it plugged in the fuck thank God is at the end of the episode I think it
knows you're in a dungeon right now no yeah they don't know I'm in a dungeon I
I think Comcast is getting revenge on us for our shenanigans towards them.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's true.
I forgot about that.
Yeah.
They probably narrowed down Patrick's address.
Oh, they finally did.
Yeah.
Yeah, one dungeon road.
I'm going to narrow down Patrick.
I think my router just got here.
Whoa, dude.
That's why it was so slow before.
Your router wasn't even here.
It was...
That's true.
You were connecting to it in the mail truck.
That's a bad connection.
uh-huh i've been thinking about becoming a mailman
yeah really be cool yeah honestly i feel like that would be a cool job i think my
brother was a mailman for a little bit i think you get like all the holidays off
and like government benefits including mailman day yeah it seems like it seems
like a cool job you'd walk around a lot too
yeah the two best jobs two best government jobs to get are probably new
hampshire liquor store and mailman or and president white white
house white house uh not too much
responsibility okay King no too much responsibility now if you're the king
you read does it breast tester okay hold up hold up okay yeah good candy getter
okay all right yeah tester candy tester poison tester that's actually a really
good no because then you then you you should be the second poison tester the
one who gives it the double check just to make sure in case the first one is like
this is like a bride like style he's been yeah the poison exactly exactly so yeah
and then if the if the first guy dies you don't have to eat it yeah how could you
not tell that something what poison testers like green poison tester yeah
they give the poison tester like all right you have to test the Kings porridge
It's like I don't like porridge
Yeah, that's not for me. No, can we put more salt in this please?
Texas Pete I don't like chalula. I'm not gonna eat this porridge until I I don't eat porridge unless there's an antidote in it
Yeah, just
Just come that's what they should do put the antidote in everything the president eats
just covering the entire pig roast with ketchup just to taste one bite of it.
Just ruining the whole feast. Yeah, you know what's poisoning me?
Cilantro. That's what. Drinking out of the soup cauldron with a straw and just spitting back into
it. Man, I used to, when I worked at Clover, I used to sample the soup the whole day.
Really? Just with a spoon?
Yeah, you get little sample cups and I would just drink soup out of a Dixie cup.
Do you guys wish you could swim in a giant pot of soup if it wasn't boiling and didn't burn you?
If it was at like 100 degrees, no.
Well, I just said if it's not gonna burn you, it'll be...
Okay, here's the parameters, okay? Would you guys swim in a giant bowl of soup if it was the best experience of your life?
- It would have to be, first of all,
it would have to be clear soup.
- Excuse me?
- What?
- You know, have you seen those YouTube videos
where they make tomato soup clear?
- No.
Oh, well, they did it.
- So it would have to be--
- It would have to be that soup.
- So it would have to look like water.
- Why would you want it to be clear?
- Well, 'cause--
- Would you swim in prep powder?
- No, let him answer.
- If it's like a thick soup.
Oh, I froze out again.
- Oh, you got frozen again.
Oh, man.
gonna get my answer. Unfreeze dude, come on, get your shit together man. It's almost over.
Hurry up. We literally just wanted one answer from you and then the episode can end. And
this is what you fucking do to us dude? I said my answer while I was frozen. No, you
have to repeat the answer. Okay. Well now I forget what we were talking about. Why does
it need to be clear? Why does the soup need to be clear for you to swim in it? Cause it's
soluble or whatever what yeah okay what are you imagine okay the whole pool and
some more water what are you talking about what I didn't know what water
soluble meant why do you want it to be clear I cuz then it wouldn't phase me as
much that it was soup. Because if it looks like water I can be like yeah this water
tastes like tomato soup. You would be scared if it didn't look like water? No it would be weird. I just wanted to feel normal.
In that river in Chicago on St. Patrick's Day when they make it green? Well it's still
water. But it looks not like water. Yeah but I know it's water. Would you swim in clear
soup if you thought it was water? Yeah. Why wouldn't you swim in- That's what I was trying
to say. I was saying it in a roundabout way. You would have to think it was water in order
to swim in it? Yeah. So you wouldn't swim in soup. You would only swim in soup if you
thought it was water. Yeah. Well then it's a surprise. Okay, so you'd just have to say
no. You wouldn't swim in a bowl of soup. If- then it would be a surprise and then a- So
You have to be surprised. Yes.
All right, well when you get to Caleb's house, there's gonna be a big bowl and it's full of water, okay?
Yeah, red water, but it's water. Okay. I promise you that. All right. All right. I'm gonna go set up this fucking router
All right. Yeah. All right. Bye y'all. Bye
Bye.