[Music]
We, uh, uh, we, the, the, the screen turn on, and, uh, we see, um, a man's face.
Looks a little bit like, looks a little Iberian.
Um...
Alec Wahlberg.
The first sensation you have upon regaining consciousness is a searing headache.
Wincing from pain?
Yeah. You shut your eyes tight before they even get a chance to open.
And only after a few seconds of this do you realize your eyes are swollen and you're shut,
and the feeling of closing them is not unlike a knuckle needing a bruise.
The last time you felt this way was St. Paddy's Day, 1985,
when you got trashed with your brother Dickie, stole a police car, and drove it into an Italian-owned business.
Tell me about yourself, Alec Wahlberg.
Look, I'm fucking innocent, dude. I swear, I shouldn't be here.
You have any idea who my fucking brothers are? My name is Alec fucking Wahlberg, alright?
I'm the bruiser of the Wahlberg family.
I do the stuff the other brothers are too fucking afraid to do, alright?
Oh, sure, Markie blinded a Vietnamese guy in '88.
Oh, he's so fucking tough.
You have no fucking clue what I've done, alright?
You don't know what I'm fucking capable of.
I can't even talk about the fucking shit I used to do for those guys back in Dorchester.
If they wanted someone roughed up, that's what I fucking did.
One time I chased a guy all the way to Ruggles from the Twin Donuts in fucking Austin, just fucking looking at Donnie kinda weird.
He's lucky he fell out of the train tracks, because what I would have done would have been ten times worse than touching the third rail.
Irregardless, I have done no crimes and I shouldn't be here.
All I do now is work at my family's restaurant in Linfield, far away from everybody else,
and mind my fucking business. I shouldn't be here.
Fully awake, Michael dangerous.
You start to see the red light flooding the room from above.
The low buzz of near-dead bulbs, threatening to extinguish.
You've been lying quietly on the cold stone floor,
caked in what you hope is just one person's blood and your own feces.
Quietly rap-rocking to yourself to stay calm.
What's going on Michael Dangerous, tell me about yourself.
Yeah! My name is Michael Dangerous! I am a 29 year old Fred Durst impersonator!
I'm just a crazy motherfucker, living it up, not giving a fuck, living life in the fast lane!
The first time I heard "Rollin'" air raid vehicle by Limp Bizkit, it changed my life forever!
Finally I saw a niche for myself in life, a career path where my tasteful goatee, backwards red Yankees cap,
and playful hip-hop demeanor could make me successful, not a laughing stock!
I quit my job as round-the-clock caretaker for my 29 year old son Ben Stiller
Dangerous and became happy for the first time in my life
The most important thing to me became getting up on stage at a child's birthday party and dropping a knowledge bomb about a psycho
Females nasty nookie or if a $3 bill could ever really exist
Little PS dangerous died in a tragic energy drink accident and I was left grieving
The only thing that brings me joy anymore is grooving and wrapping up on stage and making huge amounts of paper and fucking big-ass
Pussy and going nuts like a monster
Deeter dimbre
Your eyes adjust quickly to the room's red light and the familiar stench of death and excrement doesn't faze you
You reach for the back of your neck something itches your nails scratch across something like rusted metal
Could it be an exciting growth?
No. Your hand feels around to the front of your neck and it becomes clear that you have a collar perfectly fitted for your gangly farmer neck.
Dieter Dimpre, who are you?
My name is Dieter Dimpre.
Sorry, wait. My name is Dieter Dimpre.
I'm a fancier, steward, stockman, cowboy, and all-around animal husband from Cuntknuckle, Oklahoma.
I ain't never knew my parents on account of growing up in an open-air truck stop bathroom
Where I done learnt English from a glory hole, and ate vending machine critter crackers dipped in dish soap.
Did that for a couple years till my testicles dropped, and I started itching to wander.
Hell, I guess you could say I was heeding the call of the wild.
Anyhow, I made a blunderbuss out of faucets and pop cans and took off.
Started seeing all kinds of critters on the plane, shaped just like those toothsome crackers
I loved so much in my youth. I saw the strangest little critters you could picture.
Four-legged critter with a long face, two-legged critter with a pebble mouth, and a no-legged
critter with some kind of jangling boot on its tail.
Come to think of it, that no-legged critter was my first wife.
I know it's stupid, but I thought it was the prettiest little thing.
I saw her beady eyes and her double tongue and that clangling dangler on her tail and
I thought, and I knew, I had to build a house with a bed and lay on it with it.
lay on the fuckin bed with the fuckin thing and so I did hand the gun and she bit my fuckin
finger so I shot her head off and ate her.
I've been married 1, 2, 3, shh dude I'm getting dizzy, 4, 5, fuck it must be a fuckin hundred
times married to a rock, married to a cactus, a bird, a cloud.
Right now my wife is a darling little critter I found rustling around outside on the ground.
She's got about a hundred legs and two sharp fingers and a tail with a tooth on the end.
I brought her inside and she lives in my bed.
I raise all kinds of critters on my little ranch.
Just been sitting around and watching them for years and years.
Makes me so happy to see them give each other bedroom eyes and start humping and make a
little critter litter.
And it gives me so much joy to squeeze and suck the milk out of their pink little wieners
and pull them shiny slimy white eggs out of their cooters.
And when they get slow and big and jiggly,
shooting their fucking heads off and eating them.
And I don't even mind when they bite my finger no more.
Did I say my name?
It's Dada Stamper.
Now do you have a fucking toilet I could use?
- Okay.
Okay.
Jedediah Ezekiel,
You are sitting up right pleasantly in the filthy room, the flies buzzing about the other corpses
inside, the air heavy with death and the stench of rotten flesh.
The Amish lifestyle has made these living conditions familiar to you.
Even the collar that is around your neck is something that you've worn when the elders
punished you for shaming God for smiling at the crops.
But what is shocking to your virginal self is your stark nakedness before God and man,
Or men, I should say.
And what's more, the ring around your neck having a smaller twin wrapped around your pee-pee.
Tell me about you Jedidiah Ezekiel.
Arden Meneer, my name is Jedidiah Ezekiel.
I am from a small village in Lancaster, Pennsylvania, and I am on the Rumspringa, my ultimate quest
to find the true meaning of partying.
I love to have wild nights with my friends Plush and Flucklick, where we do MDMA and recreate
various photos of Britney Spears leaving limos without any underpants on.
Ultimate cool.
I'm here to be sexy singles and find love, or overdose before I turn 21 and have to mow
corn again.
One fact about me?
I go both ways, but I prefer girls about 60/40.
I am a complete pusshound.
I love to eat pussy, ever since I was a child practicing on a bowl of milk.
I have had the time of my life these past four weeks experiencing English culture, like being
nervous that my cell phone is spying on me and forgetting about AIDS.
I don't remember how I got here, and I don't know where I'm going, but I have a feeling
we're going to discover the true meaning of friendship.
So, alright.
You all wake up in this room.
You're all naked.
all have those metal collars around your neck and these tiny little penis collars
around your penises and your tiny little peepees. Alec Wahlberg you try to pull at
the chain and as you do you feel the ring around your peepee grow a little bit
tighter and start to prick the skin. Yeah you stop pulling. Michael
dangerous you shoot right up when you hear that stop quietly whispering to
yourself and the first thing you see for some reason is a clock on the wall
opposite you it says it's midnight you all look around and see you're sitting
in a circle a large circle and in the middle of you seems to be a large
gruesome looking pole as you all begin to stand up each of your chains makes a
jangling sound as they yank down your peepee.
Suddenly music starts to come from somewhere.
Maybe the floor, maybe from speakers.
It's getting louder and louder until it's almost deafening.
It's "You Spin Me Round" right around by Dead or Alive.
And as each of you try to plug your ears,
you feel airpods inside of them.
Dieter, you try to pull them out and realize
they are glued in, hot glued in.
Suddenly, a voice comes through each of your AirPods.
"Hello, gentlemen.
Seems you're in quite the pickle.
Let's play with some toys.
You are all selfish loners,
who play by your own rules.
But what happens when you have to submit your will to someone else and work as a team,
or else you bleed to death from your pee-pee?
This is the first of my many tests,
to see what three men such as your-"
"Bull-"
Who's that guy?
Who the fuck is that you hear back away from the speaker?
Who the fuck is that?
No, the fucking, the Amish speaker.
What's up?
Who the fuck?
Who are you?
I'm just happy to be here.
But...
Okay, um...
So, I didn't prepare anything for you, I don't really know who you are.
I'm really sorry.
I'm the life of the party, baby.
Tell me something!
I can tell. I'm a big boy.
life or not. Okay. Um, well the four of you have all done something terrible, probably. Something
you cannot forgive yourselves for. Something that proves that you don't know how to live the mass.
I'll let you all figure that out for yourselves while you're here. What you could have done
differently, but first you must make it out of this room alive. Before you is a maypole I stole
when the carnival came into town three and a half months ago. I've since smothered it in shit and
blood mostly mine and attached it not colorful ribbons but horrible drab chains. Each of those
chains has a mechanism tied to the base of your peepees that locks the chains to your peepees.
If one of you pulls with too much force the mechanism will squeeze off all of your peepees,
the door will lock and you will be left to bleed out from your peepees.
If you walk to your left or to your right a mechanism will shift atop of the maypole and
you will begin to pull the other members of your group with you in the direction you choose by
their peepees. If you do so too fast, you may trigger the mechanism attached to your peepee,
not only for yourself but for the others with you, and all your peepees will get snatched right off.
However, if you walk in a slow circle, in the correct direction, you just may be able to undo
the mechanism and free your peepees. Try to work as a team, while this song, "Dead or Alive" plays
too loud for you to hear anything or communicate with one another. Live mas or die, the choice is
yours. And you hear the Taco Bell bong ring and the voice cuts out. And so you are all
in this room. There is what he described it. There's a maypole in the middle of it. There's
chains attached to all your peepees. And you have to find a way to undo this mechanism so
you can leave the room. You can't hear each other. You have to, you're going to have to
make gestures, probably, and convincing looks using any tools you have, anything you see
on the ground around you to try to communicate the ideas you have to one another.
I start dancing.
I look at Caleb right in the face and I just start pointing at my penis.
When you paused I thought you were going to say my character name.
Yeah, me too.
I didn't say my name.
But then I look at Jedidiah and I start pointing at my penis and I'm screaming.
Oh yeah!
I know what that is!
I know what you're saying to me!
And so I jump on the pole and start doing Demi Moore's striptease.
Okay.
I'm just wiggling my toes and gliding my finger over the contraption on my penis.
You're all gonna die.
I start running around the pole.
Okay, okay, okay.
Alright, you all feel yourselves get tugged.
Wait, which direction do you run in?
Counterclockwise.
Okay, you all are start getting dragged by your peepees.
Oh yeah!
Woo!
Um, okay.
You all take four damage.
Oh my gosh.
He's going to fast.
Man.
Patrick.
This is like a Prince Albert.
Do you want to continue to run or do you want to slow down?
No, I stop dead in my tracks.
Okay.
I start slowly crip walking counterclockwise.
The chains are to pull at you guys.
Do you want to follow that motion?
counterclockwise, I'm going with it.
Okay.
I'm also going with it.
But if it was clockwise, there would be an issue.
If it was clockwise, we'd be having a whole different conversation.
Yeah.
Okay.
And so, if you do that, you all do that.
You're all doing it.
Okay, you're all tripwalking counterclockwise, very slowly.
I never said I was tripwalking.
You're all tripwalking.
I never claimed it.
I'm like imitating what Cameron's doing, but it's very clear that I don't know what's going on.
So it's kind of like a fake tripwalk.
I'm moving like an emaciated guy who just found gold.
I don't know what the reference point is, but you know what I'm talking about.
Yeah, I think so.
So you're all bleeding a little bit from your penises, and kind of crip-walking slowly counter-clockwise.
You do this for about a minute, and...
[click]
It unlocks.
The Puppies unlock.
The door you see the door and below the clock that is that
Michael dangerous was facing and you see like a metal sheet in front of it shoot up and
You hear a voice in your head. You hear the song start to turn down said
Okay, when he started to dance like a stripper, I was I thought I had you there, but um, you figured it out
So I guess on to the next room
You're welcome boys
the
on
All right, I think I'm gonna keep them in though. Well, no, no, you could roll a constitution saving throw if you want to take those out
All right, constitution check really? Yeah
Okay, yeah you take them out there's scarring
But you don't take any damage you're you're able you're you're you're Irish Boston Irish strength
You've had wet willies that are worse than that. All right. I also want to take mine out. Yeah me too
I like mine because of the look
Okay, okay, he's not even fucking real app. Oh, no, I got a six Dieter Dieter. You're fine
You've done weirder things to your ears before
Michael dangerous you're sensitive musical ears can't stand you taking them out
You take
Another two points of damage. What's your bleeding from your ears now? Oh my god. Is there a door open now?
Yeah, the door is open on the other side
Okay, come on fellows. Let's go. Yeah, let's go through the door. All right, check it out
All right. I'll go first. I
Walk in first
Okay
Who walks in first me, okay cool, this is uh, this is this one's probably the this one's should be the least dangerous
It's pretty good. Honestly. Yeah, you walk in looks like a
Just looks like a karaoke room in k-town
Fully lifted up and planted in whatever the fuck sort of construct you're in right now with couches a little karaoke machine and a TV
You hear a voice over the loudspeaker
In front of you is a state-of-the-art sound beast Pegasus karaoke machine and portable PA speaker system for kids and adults
With microphone and Bluetooth blue portable singing PA speaker system plus two wireless dual microphones plus LED and disco lights
Plus TV and aux cable best Christmas and birthday gift for boys and girls
karaoke machine with 300 songs by popular artists that you and your family will love
However, the only songs on there all have the n-word in them
our fact and you are currently being live streamed on jib jab.com to 37 36 back to 37 viewers
you could pick any song you like but for each word you get each note off key the colors
that are around each of your necks will tighten further and if you miss any n words your heads
will be cut completely off.
[laughter]
Oh no. Michael Baydress.
I say the N-word.
[laughter]
I immediately
also say it.
[laughter]
Oh, okay, well, this wasn't even
addressed to you two, so this, I mean,
great. Good for you.
[laughter]
Add that to a list of reasons why I feel
Justified having you all in here, but but hold on okay, Michael dangerous your career is on the line
This is live streaming on jib jab calm I say it again
Because I'm gonna get taken down
If you keep doing that they're gonna flag it
We're up to 30 and one more time
Wait guys if they have to flag the live stream, then this trap doesn't work
I
Do not do this I'm not saying it I'm saying new ones
I'm saying antiquated
They're only Boston guys no, can you get out? Can you get on he's taking to somebody else you get on that shit
Okay
Okay, the live stream is down so
That doesn't mean you get out of the room yet, okay?
Okay, that doesn't mean you get out of the room.
You still have to do one more thing. I'd say it again.
I'd also say it again. I think that it's the only way out now.
I started dancing to their chorus of N-Words like it's Depeche Mode.
Yeah, we're saying it to the tune of Personal Jesus.
Yeah, we're holding hands and running in a circle.
This is not this is not OK.
I'm from Boston. What do you fucking expect?
I didn't. Well, I would.
This was for so as I was explaining, this was for Michael Dangerous.
OK, where if he said and then where he is, might have difficulty getting hired.
Right. If it gets live stream.
But now he doesn't have to worry about that because it's been taken down.
I don't know how long it's been.
You know how long it took me to get a license to do that on jibjab.com?
Do you know how...
they make that so difficult?
To stream like three hours a week.
It's so hard to do.
A fucking jibjab?
I'm up behind the TV trying to change the input seeing if there's a
PlayStation connected.
No, stop. There's nothing else. It is a red, yellow, green TV. There's no
a c_n_n_'s one thing
because it's a good colors for a t_v_
it was
the karaoke machine
to some people of the you know what i'm trying to
you know the doors locked
you will you will start
you wanna get out
yeah
now
uh... ram hearing mixed results i don't want to stay here do karaoke for a
little bit
now i read it and i should get back
okay so you could do karaoke
and and and and then we could
we could deal you could do that
one could join us
uh... but i'm not going to hear
i'm not that this time trying to tell you how to get out of here
the whole and
okay
michael dangerous
you spent your life impersonating a rap rock artist
never fully committing to either rap or rock
to the life of a real rock star and most importantly
never committing to the responsibilities of being a father
became are you just
there was other stuff you were gonna have to do but now
okay
you let your child die
by getting into some poison energy drink
no it wasn't my fault
it was your fault
yeah it was
we flash back
to
what's what michael dangerous described to me what happened how did this happen
to you yes so
uh... i was just
i was just getting into the
the impersonator business i was just finally hitting it big
and i've made enough money that i didn't have to worry we i didn't have to worry
about
about get put it food on the table anymore everything i know you can learn
well you know you're me i'm your manager michael you know i think it's good you
doing amazing work okay everybody loves your impersonations the children love it
They don't even know who Fred Durst is, but they love you.
You are killing it.
- They're just drawn to my groovy style and hip hop rapping.
- That's right.
- It's a timeless combination of heavy guitars
and socially conscious lyrics.
(laughing)
- Like I said, you stick to that Wikipedia entry
and you're gonna go places, okay?
It's incredible.
Now, I am a little concerned because I remember
you used to have a son you would bring around. I was just wondering where he's at.
As a friend, I know you're a manager and I know I get 90% of the cut, but as a friend,
I want to know how your son is doing.
Okay, so then we cut back, we cut to the dangerous household where my 29-year-old son, Ben Stiller
Dangerous, is just kind of sitting around watching TV. He's sitting there and his stomach
starts growling and he goes, "Hmm, I could really go to eat or drink something right now."
And he gets up and he goes to the kitchen and he sees a blender sitting on the table filled with a
mysterious but delicious looking and smelling liquid that's labeled the hot dog flavored water.
This is an experimental energy drink that I've been developing for some time, but he doesn't
know that. And he sees it, he walks up to it and he takes a big swig and just like that, a
blood vessel in his brain explodes and he collapses dead on the ground because I wasn't there to stop
him. And Michael Dangerous, the concert you were playing at, I believe it was for a Wahlbergers
Rio opening, right? It was, yes. So this isn't... The Wahlbergers at the LAX airport?
Yeah, you were there, you were running that show. What was that like, Alec Wahlberg,
that Michael is playing. It was great they didn't let me out.
They didn't let me out of the back. I had to do all the fucking dishes and stuff.
Basically I was the only one there. I was the only chef in the kitchen. I was
doing the dishes. I was making all the burgers.
It was very fulfilling work. And before we continue on with that,
with the rest of his storyline, we're gonna back out and back into the room
here. Michael Dangerous, you let your child die. Now, so originally I had written here
that if you don't fully commit to the songs, you know, in the machine, now you
won't fully commit because the idea would be to make you say the word but
that's not up. So now what I need you to do is answer five questions about your
son who you know so little about with the help of your friends. This is gonna be
Easy!
If you get three out of the five of them right, you pass.
And you're able to- that's 60% which is passing in jigsaw school.
If you don't, then you, you know, you're fucked.
So.
And so the way I want to do this is, you all, I mean, you all can like, can help or whatever
in however way you want to help.
But you're the only one, Michael, who remembers, knows anything about your son.
So what you're going to do for each of these questions if you want to, is roll a history
check.
It's one of the things you can do.
And depending on the success of that, will determine how good of a hint you get, basically.
Likewise, all of you can look around the room, see if there's any clues from Michael's life,
things like that to see if you can figure out how to help him.
But yeah, if you get this wrong, it's game over for you only.
The other one was going to be for everybody, but you guys undid that, which was smart.
Because I opened the door for that.
I used a very smart strategy on that one.
The smartest strategy we could.
You use that strategy many times.
So um, so suddenly you hear out of the karaoke machine a woman's voice.
What was your son's favorite color?
One, red, blue, green, or whatever dad I liked.
Brown?
Was it brown?
Roll roll you can roll history.
I'm rolling a history check.
uh... so it's a net twenty
we have to learn around the room
to why just let me know if you got it right okay you got it perfect yet net
twenty uh...
you remember it was green
he was a green
he loved green
that's why he tried to create energy drink
that is correct
next question
who was your son's best friend
she your neighbor
sherry's dog leopold
or Frank McNamara I'm thinking of myself and I'm mumbling Milhouse I feel
like it is on the tip of my tongue god I got another cricket it's Sherry's dog
Leopold you remember seeing him play with the dog what the fuck it was
"It's Sherry's dog Leopold! I remember seeing him play with the dog! What the fuck?"
Okay.
Ding ding ding!
That is correct.
I'm the smartest guy alive when it comes to my dead son.
Next question.
I think that we're about to leave.
I saw you cheering.
when your son did his silly dance was he hungry tired horny or wanted to talk
about his pill addiction problem that was a for that role that's no good
your son would do is silly dance and then and it was just kind of
impenetrable to you just kind of what are you doing
I don't really get this.
It was when he was hungry!
*laughs*
*fart noise*
That is incorrect. He did it when he was tired.
You're wrong!
No, no, no she's not.
Can we get a fact check on this one?
Please don't. You can't get a fact check on it.
Okay, sorry!
Okay, next question.
*speaks Japanese*
*laughs*
The machine's playing it in reverse!
Or, Monster Energy Otter Juice Chaos.
I'm sorry, that one was in Japanese and I couldn't fix that one.
I kicked the machine.
Yeah.
I tried to do a Fonzie to it.
it uh it tries it it uh roll a uh you know what roll roll a slight of hand i want to
see how skillful your kick is yeah it's it yeah you kick it and it does it again in japanese
and it just like says all the options again can i kick it again
Do I roll a Japanese check on this one?
Yeah, you can roll a Japanese dice.
I got a 16.
You can roll what you can do.
Well, also, like, you have Amish magics too, Caleb.
So...
Okay, this is new.
Yeah.
I guess I haven't looked at any of my abilities.
Yeah, so what that means is, there's a...
Basically, you have 10 uses of Amish magics throughout this campaign,
Which allows you to cast a random spell from a table of Amish spells on your solid stone tablet. I have the spell table
Um, you basically pray
add religion
And if you get 20 you get to pick a spell from the list 15 to 19 something helpful 11 to 14 something somewhat helpful
6 to 10 somewhat unhelpful
Uh, two to five somewhat something harmful one you begin to transform into the humble chicken
Okay
uh... i'd just remember that i have a homage magics and then i i i wrote him
which i wrote this in the time of all religion and make your prayer ok
hold on i have to pray
that in a year twenty four
you know i was really managed
it's on the a always with advantage but you take the first number uh...
or yeah
so something somewhat harmful when we look at your spell table
what do you say what do you say to your god we ask of him
dear all i do know how it
what
can you please please have jet is not a good idea which for
yeah okay i wrote a tackle
okay
which is saying the wrong name of the wrong god
is my homage magic's again to defend myself from uh...
dean urdine peace pitchfork
the
and that's a that's gonna definitely you
but all that's all prayer
for a lot of tears
and then my god you thought a ok ok so i need to resolve a few things
so first of all something somewhat harmful has to happen
so uh...
okay
uh... you create a bonfire in the middle of the room
that uh...
that uh... if you get anywhere near it
uh... you're going to light on fire you're gonna take some fire damage
the one second
i have a
i think this is a good thing
it could be good
yeah
uh...
now
that's all that happens when you pray now next that happens is deter stabs you
with a pitchfork
uh...
tries but
with that nineteen
uh...
you
you uh...
who picked up the you do
to make sure i got this right
Okay, yeah with that 19 you accident you accidentally
Uh give the ability
to uh, you you cast comprehend languages on um, cameron on uh, uh
On um, uh, alec not alec. Fuck. What are your names? Michael dangerous?
But you still get stabbed with the pitchfork. So do damage. Uh, oh my god
Hey, hey pagan piece of shit, just hit pitchfork in the in the chat. Fuck you
So early
But you could understand the language
I was just trying to nip ya.
You're gonna kill me so early.
But now you understand the language much more dangerous.
What's it saying?
The question is, what was your son's favorite food?
And we have a 5.
Apple, soup, tongue, or monster energy, ultra drink, and ultra juiced chaos.
Can I roll history now?
Yeah.
I'll say with advantage because now you understand the language.
is
with the monster energy option.
Ding ding ding ding ding ding!
You are correct.
Um, yeah, and with that, the door opens.
You've completed the next puzzle.
Let's fucking go, dude.
Let's fucking go. Boston fucking strong. Let's go.
Okay, yeah. You can all walk.
Caleb, how much HP do you have left?
I have 14 HP.
He's kind of beefy. He's like a beefy omelette.
Yeah, I have 14 too.
beefy. Can I give Caleb a kiss on his wound because I feel so bad? Yeah, you can do whatever you want.
Oh yeah. Alright, come over here. I forgive you. Let me see if I can't tongue kiss you back to
health like I do with every single one of my critters. Come bring that big tongue over here.
Alright, so I eat out Caleb's open wound. That's right. Alright, I think that is gonna... Here's
some of that that creepy gore that the series the saw series is so well known for
yeah really a madness
honestly this is disgusting i don't i don't know if i'm comfortable
this guy doesn't even fucking like it look
i i i was hoping your heads would your heads would come off
this guy's weird he's on a fucking tricycle
you're weird
i'm not on the tricycle
you're a puppet on a tricycle
i am not a puppet
you're weird as hell
no maybe i'm maybe i'm different
look at you dude you got you're wearing makeup
he does a saw laugh and it's a scooby doo re
you're way to self dude
can i take some of the stray pieces of caleb's viscera and cook it on the fire
and give it to him to heal him
yes do it that's not a bad idea i'll have you roll a medicine check
did i not get any points for him eating my fucking body pussy he just
no he's just like in your wound oh ok i thought that i was gonna give me
closer now our bond is
medicine check okay yeah uh you make something in if
kayla beats it uh uh well jenna are you gonna feed it to him
we play that out play that out here eat this
pinch your nose and swallow it only if you share it with me no i'm not
a it's all yours come on come on all right
And then we we uh lock arms like in that way that people do when they're trying to be gay in a will ferrell movie
And they yeah, right we eat my body. Yeah, you guys each heal back 3 hp. Yeah from
I asked caleb if he's accepted jesus christ as his lord and savior and not whoever whatever fucking pagan god. He spoke
Absolutely
Love Christ, dude. I love Christ.
Oh yeah, you're gonna love this.
I propose to Caleb.
I accept. I accept.
Oh, we all have another wedding in this one?
Yeah.
I decline.
Yeah, you go to the next room.
Wait, does Caleb get healed at all?
Yeah, he healed 3 HP.
Oh, okay, cool.
You go into the next room.
And you notice, you know, you walk in, the first thing you notice is the change in air pressure.
And your stomach starts to drop. The room resembles the inside of an airplane.
A very particular airplane.
Looking behind you, you still see the door to the other room, but when you look to the window,
it appears you're tearing through the sky. In front of you are people.
I start screaming and holding my ears with both hands.
I put the AirPods back in.
I'm doing the the the safety presentation with the seat belt at the front of the plane.
In front of you are people appearing to enact their final moments aboard the plane.
Couples like holding each other, the men of the cloth taking their final vows, children crying.
The sound of this commotion is overwhelming.
Overwhelming as you get closer to the people though you realize that they are just corpses animated by puppet strings
And that there is just the audio coming from somewhere else and as they make their motions gross blood and viscera squirt out of them
Up ahead you see the culprits
three terrorists
With no further description necessary to clarify what they look like what they believe in
What the United States did to their country to get them so riled up in the first place?
Oh my god, I know what this is supposed to be. This is that terrorist attack that destroyed the set of the music video for Roland
No, this is the soul plane
Just go dancing down the aisle
You could make it more obvious see there's a black guy
I
black exploitation films I feel like no he wasn't in Soul Plane. Racist! He's a white guy. Racist!
This is your captain speaking. Let's play with some toys. Alec Wahlberg, growing up you were
always the underdog, taking the fall for your brothers various hate crimes and raising many
of their illegitimate children until they were around three and could forage for their own food
as is Boston Irish custom. It wasn't an easy life but it was one you should have appreciated more.
You still got to be the real turtle's footstool that one time he couldn't reach the guitar hero
controller. You get free Guinness, the worst fucking beer in the world, in every bar. Take
that back! Take that fucking back dude! I won't. Take that back! Fucking sucks. Take that back
That's everybody who's listening to this if you drink Guinness and you're like mmm yummy fucking sucks. It's a dinner be a dude
Drink it and you eat it you drink it for dinner. No you drink it at dinner. You don't you don't drink it all the time
Oh, well, yeah, that's what I was doing wrong because I was drinking Guinness all the time instead of just
Fucking do it wrong
At one time you shot a bow and arrow into a cop car and only had to pay a $40 fine because the officer was a huge
fan of we own the night. Alec.
[Laughter]
Alright.
Sorry.
It's okay, you made me laugh, so.
To appreciate the Wahlberg lifestyle you were afforded,
this constant chip on your shoulder only increased your anger
anger and culminated in an act of heinous violence on an unsuspecting Asian man.
Forgetting which one of "those guys" you were supposed to hate, you put one of your
pubes in the wall burger of a Tibetan monk visiting Boston to get catfished by a 300-pound
whale with the most busted face you've ever seen.
and let's flash back to that let's back to that party that uh... that no brand
open
that might help you guys i said that was an l_a_ acts yeah i know who's a
jeep back to l_a_ actually were celebrating in boston because he had a
little more fluid from l_a_ acts
it's uh... yeah you're all in boston mark fluid from l_a_ acts michael dangers
what song are you performing at the celebration
i'm i'm performing uh... don't go off wandering by limp bizkit which is a very
a very touching and and emotional song about
about being broken up with
can you perform it right now? yeah can you do a little bit of that for us?
because i missed the performance check i wanted to have happen
let me just look up the lyrics really quick
uh...
everyday is nothing but stress to me i'm constantly dwelling on how you got the
best of me wanna know something i can't believe the way you keep testing me
you mentally molested me yeah the crowd is going nuts they're all like they're all crying and
they're loving it they're shoving wall burgers in their mouth they're enjoying it um and the
camera pans over back into the kitchen where uh uh our friend um alec walberg is all alone
um and cooking everything you're doing everything alone you said right yeah yeah it's too hot
I
Don't know the fucking dial wet
Shit's too hot here at that point
Uh, we got the air conditioner on or something, please you see mark you know what you see marky mark bust in
Through the kitchen door and he says Alec what's going on over there?
People need their burgers. Okay, he's performing is reaching the crescendo. We really need those burgers are right now, okay
I got a million fucking burgers. I gotta cook. Okay. Well you about to make it 2 million if you don't speed it up
All right, I make 2 million burgers. I
Have to go to wake up at 4 a.m. Okay right now, so I'm gonna go wake up at 4 a.m.
I'll be support the troops. Are you gonna work out? You gotta support the troops. You're gonna work out
He starts doing push-ups in the kitchen. Yeah, that's what I like to fucking see. Yeah, I know you like. Oh, yeah
Push-ups right
Squats do your squats. Okay. I'll sit on your shoulders. Not a problem. It's very easy for me to do squats cuz I'm Mark Wahlberg
Yeah, let me sit on your shoulders. I didn't really apologize when I did that to that man
When I was that you didn't have to mark you didn't have to right? Yeah, of course, you're gonna have to apologize
All right. Look get those burgers out. Okay. All right. All right, and remember do not put your pubes in anything. Oh
Even if they're Asian. Oh
Oh boy.
All right, okay, good man.
And he walks out.
I didn't say yes or no.
No, you didn't.
I said, oh boy.
He's remembering with you, the Saw guy, Jigsaw.
No, you didn't say yes or no.
What did you do next?
This is all being remembered while there's like
corpses dangling in the airplane and like noise everywhere.
Well, I looked at the name on the order and obviously,
You know you know when you know you fucking know it said it said dolly llama.
Definitely didn't say that it's I that's look I was written in some other language I could read.
I like how Wahlberg is looking at a name that's like vaguely Asian and it just turns into
the Dolly Lomond.
And right away I grab the Philips Norelco out from under the grill.
I shave the whole.
Is that where you keep it?
I keep my deodorant under there too.
I grab the Philips Norelco, I shave a big clump of pubes under the Thanksgiving burger
that we have. The Thanksgiving burger? It's a turkey burger. It's a turkey burger with
cranberry orange stuff on it. It's pretty good. I had it at the airport. Do you mean sweet
potatoes? Nope. No, it's not sweet potatoes. It's a cranberry orange relish. Oh, interesting.
Orange like the fruit?
Orange like the fruit, yeah.
Okay.
Uh-huh.
That's really exciting.
It's good.
Honestly, it wasn't bad.
But then you handed that pubed burger to who?
That poor Tibetan monk, Alan.
And then we just partied.
That's...
Nothing else really happened.
You've always wanted to be like one of your more famous brothers, not stuck behind the
grill.
While I'm looking at the flashback, I look at the cabin and I go, "Oh fuck, now I know
what this is!"
And I have another flashback.
I have another flashback and it's a flashback to me and Mark sitting on the couch, September
11th, 2001, in the morning, like 8.30.
Mark nudges me and just looks at the TV and says, "I could have fucking stopped that."
[laughter]
And then we go back to the camp.
[clears throat]
You've always wanted to be like your brothers.
But consider me generous, Alec.
I'm giving you the
opportunity to be better than they ever were.
You have two minutes
to defeat the terrorist puppets in front of you
before the plane crashes into the towers.
Which, in this instance,
means the release of a deadly poison
gas that will kill you all
in 30 seconds of breathing it in. If that happens, there are three gas masks
hidden in the compartments above the plane seats. That means, should the gas be released,
one of you will have to die. Stop 9/11, Alec. Do something not even Marky
Mark was ever able to do. Live or die, the choice is yours.
Wait, there's three? Yeah.
Yeah, there's one guy. Who's this guy? Who's the fat guy with the
sword. He's just also there. Okay. There's two of them. Yeah,
there's two of them. Oh, I didn't see him. I only saw the
top one. Okay. Yeah and also in that flashback.
Dieter what were you doing there? Cuz now everyone was at
the the this opening of the Wall Burgers place. What were you doing there?
Where was it taking place? It was taking place in Boston, but
Markybar came from LAX.
Okay.
Um.
I, uh, I followed a porcupine
into Boston.
Uh, and, uh,
yeah, I was, uh,
I was in the back alley, uh,
sniffing
discarded abortions.
At Walburgers.
This is, yeah, raffling through the Wahlburgers dumpster looking for a--
Hey man, I told you, you can't be ruffling around in here looking for abortions, okay?
Alright, my mistake.
And then I go, "But you also--"
"My mistake?
It's the third time you've done it this week, you old mistake."
I just-- I just go back to Oklahoma.
It's your only connection to that event.
Yeah, all of you roll for initiative.
You're about to fight some fucking terrorists.
I look at all the dead bodies and I get really scared and I go, "Oh my god, I remember!"
And then I flashback to when I watched IT Part 2 in theaters and I got really scared
there.
(laughing)
- Yeah, are you there with,
are you there like on "Rum Springa" when you do that?
- Yeah, it was the first thing I did
when "Rum Springa" started.
- Okay, your friend,
your friend Abraham is next to you.
- Yeah.
- I was like, oh wow, this is real scary.
(screaming)
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- You also remember there,
you also remember every time something funny happened
in the movie, there was a voice from the back of the theater
going, "Yoooo!"
[laughter]
How often was that in IT Part 2?
They got jokes in IT Part 2.
They got mad jokes in IT Part 2.
What's your fucking problem, dude?
You didn't do your prep work?
Also in the theater,
also in the theater, at the intro scene
with the hate crime, you hear a voice
of the pet going, "Let's fucking go!"
[laughter]
In the scene where IT eats the gay guy.
guy. You also see me in the movie as an extra.
I played one of the I played one of the bullies who attacks the
gate. I didn't know they're recording a movie because I've
never seen a video.
okay cool uh...
alright it's so clear that patches just told us off mike that we can do flashbacks
yeah i know
you just hit four in a row
so yeah you guys can tell jokes too
uh... okay cool wow
i flashback to i was eating a sandwich
okay go back
now you guys are just being silly
i flashback to being in the bathroom and you have to make all the noisiest patches right now go
"Oh, I'm Caleb, oh!"
"No, not Caleb!"
"Not gonna love poop poop!"
"What the fuck are you even talking about?"
"I don't like eating, I don't like making poop!"
"I like eating it too, is that what you were gonna say?"
"No, no, I was not gonna say eating poop, but I don't like doing that either."
"You know what, this game sucks."
"Give me another flashback, huh?"
"That was it."
"That's all I have."
"I'm flashing back to a business idea I had."
"I converted a computer to a computer."
"I'm gonna go back to that."
uh i convergently invented an ice cream uh substitute called worm water which is
ground up earthworms and water that you put in the freezer
and i was there too
yeah and we were all there
i i flashback i flashback to kindergarten and we're all there as baby versions of ourselves
Yeah, wait, you all realize
There but you never see the top of his head you never see us we're all
We're all burying jigsaw in the sandbox
So yeah, the first person who goes in this turn order though is Jedidiah
You've got to jump on these terrorists. Awesome
Awesome they are not 50 feet away from you. They're all 30 feet. These two are 30 feet
This is just the map size. I messed up so you can reach them
Look at my powers and my ability. You also can do you can use your Amish magics as an action or
You know move. I'm gonna keep doing that
Yeah, okay, so you have you've used twice
No, that's not. Oh I have
It's a more yeah, and you just crit failed so you're going to do it again. Can I use my ability to give him a bonus?
No because he was first in the turn order
Did this is action you just bend the rules once no, can you let us win?
I'm doing my best. So you
You have begun the transform into the humble chicken. So the first thing that happens is your mouth becomes a beak
very cool
That's what that's what's happened. So far. You have four more times that can happen. Yeah, I just wore you
That's all I wanted out of it. This was a
Was our was our marriage successful or did Caleb decline the proposal I
Said no, I think yeah. All right. I reproposed to Caleb now that he's a chicken
I'm only the beginning stages of a chicken, but this time I accept okay, great
Yeah, you're probably the only man that'll take me now with my beak
It is your turn
Michael dangerous, so you're not even gonna talk about how I got married. Okay?
No, I wasn't sure if that was happening. Yeah, I get it. Yeah, so there's a priest no one of the core we have two minutes
Well the corpses is a priest minutes the perfect wedding each round in combat is six seconds
So you should be okay. We're doing a six second
Well, I still consummate the marriage
And one of my goals before you get married
One of my run spring of goals was to break a Guinness World Record for so now fastest marriage will do it
Okay. Yeah, you see a priest
puppet string over
He says I now pronounce you man and wife and his eyeball rolls out of his head
Will you be my best man, okay, can you give a toast?
To
Jedediah Ezekiel Jedediah when I first met you I changed your penis up to a to a maple I
Didn't realize
I didn't realize that you were probably not a bad dude, you know, I think my assistant fucked this up
I think I told him to get three four people and
Then I gave him a name of somebody else and then instead it brought you so I don't know if there's anyone else's name similar
To Jedediah, but here you are
Anyway, you seem cool
and
You know cheers to you. You have a minute now to get out of here before the poison gas comes but
it up.
What?
May I kiss the bride?
No!
What's the range of my shotgun?
It's a 15 foot cone, so you have to move up a bit to do it.
Alright, I move up halfway up the aisle.
Or actually, I guess a little more than halfway.
I'll move not close enough that they can get me in melee range, like up here.
And then I shoot my shotgun at them.
is
kurch of kurt coban shotgun at them
that's a seven
that is the uh... you shoot at them and somehow all the the spread just goes
around that place it's just like
goes right around them you see the terrorist like
puppets like kind of haphazardly dodging
uh... they all look like a committed that terrorists of course
uh... and uh...
it is now your turn
Okay, uh, I take Jedediah's hand and lead him into the lavatory.
Oh no, we're all gonna die!
Finally, joining the mile-high club!
Can it be that during our lovemaking we, uh, we tamper with the smoke detector?
Uh, yeah, I'll have you roll... to wait, to what end?
Uh, you're not supposed to do it!
it's
uh...
the
which should that be
i guess role in our contract is it's got a magical
uh...
uh... yes
or just a straight intelligence check because it's fine
yet again
yet you're able to successfully tamper with that i mean that's not hard to
to
the
it
okay
yet he's seen
right cool
he not sits away christmas folks
mhm
while
this year and a
for my first and
you know the uh...
we have a good kid now
i put the head into my overalls pocket
yeah you have to sit on it like a male penguin okay yeah that's what i put in my
ass
there we go. That might hatch in a later scene
uh... and so
you do all that uh...
uh... you don't hurt the terrorists but the uh...
it is now uh... it's now your turn Wahlberg
i'm gonna use my
do what you've always wanted to do
i'm gonna use my irish pistol
but i am gonna move up a little bit
so here
and i'm gonna come up with a day for that i think right here
it's so much better
but i think you creatures within five feet
okay so can i move up
more tell you a ago go for a bit
is this five feet
i go right here i cocked a pistol sideways and i say this is how we
fucking do it in dot just a kid
do it
nicely that hits
nice to hit both
uh... you know one of them which when you want it
uh... green guy
at the green guy
role for damage
six nights yeah
uh... you should have been a good right through uh... shoulder
uh...
uh... and uh... the
the puppet lake jangles about we do that
uh... it's still it's still alive but it is her uh... it's it's it's uh...
there's some sort of like colloquially did blood slowly using out of the wound
uh...
and uh... it is now their turn
so they're going to come up on on you
though so you got a lot of that's
yeah yeah jigsaw is controlling them he's like
gold my puppets and uh... they get mad about the smoke detector
oh yeah they're at this event on this because that is a critical debate but
i think the projects are bad
because they are not that happened at their time as they are so i was tampering
with this flight as they approach you pat patrick they they they said to be
like
the jigsaw like no the smoke detector i need to fix that and he's is attention
is divided between the puppets of the smoke detector
so they get this advantage of this attack
okay
what is your a_c_o_u_ your strong issue forgot
uh...
okay
who
no
okay so one of them
uh... okay and then the other one
all my god
i'm scared
so one of them uh... just fuckin with the green guy with c like flails that you
buddies he's it's that hand jigsaw is working on fixing the smoke detector
the other hand
jigsaw is on a sheet in this guy fucking cleaves you in the head with a critical
hit
uh... how bad
i'm not critical
we're all about to find out
on now
He hits you in the head with a terrorist billy club
Yeah, damn I'm at six oh
Yeah, you can die in this I forgot in real life
It is now we're back to the top. It is now
It is now Jedediah's turn you're you fully come you laid an egg
What are you up to now? Yeah
Help us!
I'm gonna keep doing this Amish magics thing because you gave it to me for some reason.
I'm gonna keep rolling my religion.
Oh my god.
Just a 20. Just a perfect 20.
Okay. It's an imperfect 20, but it's good.
You don't include my religion?
Oh, well, I just don't say it. Look, it's just that it's a natural 20.
Oh my god.
I'm sorry. It is a 20 though, so you do get to pick a spell from place to place.
- Seems like Caleb's 20 had some work done.
- No. - No.
- Yeah.
- So let me get out the list, the spell list and--
- Give me the worst one you have.
- No, no, no, you get to pick now.
- Yeah, I know.
- Oh, okay.
- Do the best one.
- Oh, you're right, I'll do the best one you have.
- You can ask me about these.
- This is the entire thing?
- You can ask me about any of these,
we can cut out as much as you guys need to.
what is auto is irresistible dance
mcdonald's
what is animate dead
you know you can animate one of the puppets
you can meet that big guy yes
i'm an animate that big fat piece of shit
okay yeah do it uh...
yes you cast animate dead using your omish man don't know what you're right
my one prayer
what you're here to whisper
do you say jesus christ instead now
yeah i guess i that my husband doesn't beat me up
I say Jesus Christ.
That's all you say.
Jesus Christ!
You just go boar hat for some reason.
Yeah, so what happens is you, basically you give that creature an order, a command if you will.
And so you can decide what action it will take, where it will move during its turn, all that stuff.
that's a bonus action each turn. So as your bonus action now you can you can do that.
Okay. You can make one of the big guys. I'll do the one closest to the
terrorists. Yeah. And I'm gonna have him do a I'm gonna do a front flip. Okay so
you animate this like giant kingpin looking guy yeah and he's a
in a past life I was don't care do the front flip rest okay yeah he front flips
I'm gonna roll the acrobatics check for him I don't know why you're making him
do shit cuz I want to see I want to see if you can do it he's alive I've never
seen a front flip before. He like front flips and lands flat on his back. He's fine, it
just wasn't very good. Yeah, it's understood, he's huge. Yeah, he gets up, he walks over,
is he gonna try to attack those guys? Yeah, he does try to. I wasn't sure. No, I feel a
little pressured into it. Yeah, I guess he'll attack. Absolutely not. I want you to play
this game the way you want to play it. No, you know what he does? Oh no. He walks up to
me, he has a sword right? Yeah. He stabs through himself into them. What? Yeah. Why? Just cause
I think it'd be cool. They would kill him. For when I'm at home, I randomly put two giant
naked guys with swords in the map and Caleb is making one of them stab himself through
to attack the other guy i decided to be cool
let's do this again all my not to cattle on me
uh...
okay
all right yeah that's gonna hit that guy
and it's not going to hit him
uh... i
'cause seven through his body
whatever patches
okay and then uh...
it is doing
okay
uh... he still standing heat but uh... the green guy is dead how does it how
How does your fat zombie kill the green guy?
He uh, like I said, he stabs himself through his big fat body and he, just because he's
so big, his sword just barely, just a little bit, just a little bit pokes out, but it hits
him in the jugular.
Yeah, it hits him just right in the right spot.
Yeah.
It instantly kills him.
It hits him in the right spot.
It hits him, I will say this, he gets hit in the right spot.
Yeah, the green guy topples over.
more dead is a non-functioning puppet now
uh... and now i have now he can use the that my guys still alive right
nice and i have a horn
he's going to have his tummy
uh...
so now it is uh... your turn michael dangerous
i'm gonna move up next to uh...
next uh... alec walberg
and i'm gonna blast this other terrorist with my uh...
career actually what
is my uh... is my thing where i take half damages that was that replace my attack
is that like a full action
uh... yeah that's a full action okay i'm just gonna attack them
okay do it
twenty-nine east yet he's role for damage
seven ice
yeah you fucking like tear up this guy's like shit
and uh...
but he had the public is looking worse for wear but he still holding up
uh... in a church in deter
and so there's this fact i a on the uh... on the rear side of the plane
all right i'm i guess i'll throw my pitchfork at him
we know he's not a lot of you know that it may be
he's going to be
you know you are excited
and we would like to do it
the only enemies of the guys with guns
the
but that these guys are on our team i guess i completely only one guy is only
one only there is a dead
has a little animated
uh...
and so i did look really alive to me
best-looking guys on the plane
parallel that i have a large markets
i get i get into this position to the room and fish fork at the uh... the guy
uh... right in front of the cockpit
they do it yet role for an attack there
Yeah. Oh, yeah, that hits.
Nine damage, right?
Nice.
So you threw that?
So yeah, you throw that through the window of the cockpit and
there's a terrorist there just like blankly terrorist puppet
blankly just like pointing a gun and then like a pitchfork just
like jams into his head and the puppets are to jangle a little
bit and it is now and yeah, you do that damage.
You want to move anywhere?
Yes, you moved a little bit.
a little bit more to if you want to but that's uh yeah all right I sort of tip
my hat over my eyes and take a little nap
it is now it is now Wahlberg's turn all right so I'm at 6% health so I move a
little bit over. Okay. But I immediately hit him with the go. I'm close enough to
hit him with the go patch lately right? Yes you are. So I just fucking whip it at
his head. Nice do it. Roll for that. How much time do we have left by the way?
Seven. Oh time in terms of oh yeah. In terms of the the catch. Yeah I just realized. Gas. Yeah so
So after this you'll have, you'll have I guess 1, 2, 3, 4, you have a lot of rounds.
You have like 10 more, you'll have like 8 more rounds.
Oh, that's easy.
Come on.
You have 6 seconds to round it.
Get back in the bathroom.
Oh shit, sorry.
What just happened?
I'm sorry, I moved my desk weird.
I whipped the shillelagh at his head, I got 7 damage with 12 bludgeoning.
No, so that's a 7.
That's what it says.
(laughing)
- I've just done this so many times.
- I know.
(laughing)
- But you still have not,
you gotta hang what it says. - It's an attack to a seven.
So attack roll seven means it doesn't,
it's not gonna hit him.
So you swing the shillelagh
and you just like whiff,
you just get too into it.
And you whiff this puppet.
But it's a hardy whiff.
You knock it to the seat next to it
and you just like take a chunk off of the seat
with usually
and now it is their turn now
and they are this this this terrorist the terrorist in the back is now they come
out
uh... because he has a hand with a fork it in his face
and he's gonna try to attack the zombie
uh...
my god shit
in no
the attack reflects off of his stomach corn
that's right
so in the senate
no instead he he takes the pitchfork out of his head
and just james it in this in the the fat zombies sternum
just james it in there
uh... and the fat zombies alive but
whatever you want to call it
but barely the stuff of the
uh...
to collect like uh... it's a good job
yeah uh... that's a healthy
uh... okay
and uh... yet the other terrorist
uh... is going to go after uh... going after you again
uh... warburg
no seem to be targeting you for so long to do that
you want to be better than your brother
fucking leave me alone to do it i'm fucking of com
juicing out over here
still in my shoes
the red juice coming out of the in our forgotten or it's called
You're very lucky. It did five. It did five damage.
Is there, can I, can I jump in front of the bullet? No,
whatever man. It's not how, not how the game works. We can,
we could change it though. Later. I'll change it later.
Can I do that later? Can you promise me I'll do it once? Okay, cool.
I could promise you you could do it once. Okay, cool. I love my friends.
You take five damage. You're so far away too. It's like,
it's not a very powerful jump i spent my my my childhood
yeah holding logs in my back
are you a flashback to that
yeah
i'd like to keep it
yeah i think i think you're pretty good shot and then what do you remember
i'd like to make me doing the dishes of the log on my back
uh...
seared and committed as
now remember get rid of all the stains are they'll be demons tonight
of course that why don't you talk like me
I don't really know how to talk like Amish.
Is that like a weird robot?
Like how are you doing?
Can you show me?
Nope.
That's Amish.
That guy knows what a robot is.
All robots are weird.
Dad, I know you love robots, but please stop talking about them.
I'm trying to get the dishes done.
Okay, son.
I'm at a loss now.
That sounds good to me.
In the flashback.
in the flashback.
My life is flashing before my eyes right now.
I flash back to the first room where we had the things on our penis and I go, "Wow, that
was crazy!"
What happens, Patrick?
Your life flashes before your eyes?
My life is flashing before my eyes.
I'm sitting here, I'm at one health.
I'm remembering being in the background of the Good Vibrations video.
I'm thinking I'm just I'm just thinking about that video. That's the only good memory. I have in my life
Yeah, you see you see
Mark turn to you and he goes like one two step get the steps right okay, Alec. Are you not gonna be in the video?
fuck off
No you fuck off
We're going to digitally edit you out of this video frame by frame we're shooting on film dumbass
How you gonna fucking digitally edit it? I'm gonna digitally edit your dick out of your mouth. I would hold on I'm figuring out
How do you like that I
Don't like Donnie better than you fucking let me be in all the new kids videos
Yeah, well Donnie Donnie's not gonna be ever be as successful as me because we're about oh, oh, we're already kind of big
We're already kind of big but you know this is really gonna put us on the map. No, it's not
It's just all a pipe dream mock it really is nothing ever
You know a craving for Boston Boston action stars for some reason people love it. Nah
They have it of not another be an underweight model
They could never have a underwear model from Boston that would never fucking happen. I know
I know that's what dad said, but I can prove him wrong. Okay, you're not gonna prove shit
And what's going on Peter?
And that's the best memory of my life. I
I also have a flashback to my good vibrations, which is when I put a cicada in my asshole. I
Like that whenever one of us has a flashback we all just have a flashback at the same time
Yeah, it's like imagining the Saw movies and it's like just the plot is the the pacing is so insane
Cool yeah, so you're just screaming in pain by the way, you're down to one HP
It is now your turn, Jedidiah.
Can I heal Alec?
Uh, you could try with Amish magics.
Okay, I'm gonna try and heal him with Amish magics.
This is not gonna go well.
It's gone well every single time.
Oh!
Twenty.
So do you count my religion bonus on top of it?
Yeah, I do.
Okay, so it's a twenty again.
Pick a spell here. You have spells.
Look at my...
I feel like Bless is probably the only...
It's...
What about Mending?
Both of those spells actually don't...
Wow, hmm. That's pretty funny of me.
I feel like I don't have a lot of healing spells.
Try Web.
You can make another fire.
Try Create Bonfire.
What does Web do?
Oh, I know. Here, wait, wait.
heal patrick try using web you can put webs in my wounds try using phantasmal killer on patrick
yeah make patrick go to the kingdom of heaven uh instantaneous try psychic scream
what does so can i heal why is it why is there two spider things why is there spider climb and
What's it what's beacon of hope?
Beacon of hope in
D&D just basically allows you to have like advantage on wisdom frozen and death saving throws
But yeah, do any of these can I save him with you make if you make a pitch or a bonfire we can cook more meat
the
bonfire yeah okay yeah yeah yeah you create a bonfire over this little girl
corpse and then little girl dude I can't do that you move the bonfire over this
guy do the fat guy he's got he's got great fucking cuts in him I can do it
over the fat guy you kill the fat guy no the other fat guy the other the other
the
That guy's too far away from you guys.
Oh, hell yeah, dude.
Fifteen.
Nice, yeah, you throw that meat over.
Uh, uh, Alec, how do you, how do you catch the meat?
Do you just do full...
It's just, just hands behind my back.
Yeah, I wanted to make sure.
Whole steak, my mouth goes like that.
Yeah, you see, you swallow it and your neck does a little, you see it out, you have it in your neck, you go whoop.
Yeah.
yeah yeah he was flesh and you feel
uh...
seven points of health so nice
so far concert
i'm only doing this 'cause you're donnie walberg's brother
uh... i'm so glad you know who is
you could come collect dot is reached the amish community
yeah
uh... in riot
it is now michael dangerous is turned here you're crying and eating human
flesh
uh... is your turn michael dangerous
all right so now i can hear both of them with my shotgun
i say i say
i hope you know i pack a chainsaw
and then i'd shoot them with my shotgun
i like that the shot guy... that's a crit one
okay yeah uh... so
what happens is the uh...
the is on the misunderstands
uh...
what's going on
and jumps in front of the to terrorists to save them
it's just a little
by the shotgun bullets and is just dead now
he's jumps in front of those no
or at least it's the zombie we get it is on the
for a little bit of a random with the bonfire and i did not have to not hate
the zombie i was just trying to make what a crit one what i think should have
and i've been let it live
novice and why can't recruit one be better than a crit twenty
you know that should be like a space yeah i feel like a softball by limp
is kit
yeah
the other zombie jumps in front takes the full buckshot in just like
dies uh...
and uh... it is now
dealers turn
All right, can I sniff the air to see if there are any animals on the plane?
Yeah, roll a perception check.
No, sorry, roll a nature check, actually.
Okay, yeah, you sniffed for sure a very much plagued rat
that is scurrying between the seats.
All right, I get on all fours and try to locate the rat.
okay yeah you find it pretty easily i would say that all the a you can find
the rat you want to know that
yet that the rat with my you can't so you can either grab at it right which
will be uh... you know some sort of uh... check you need to do
they also have the ability animal whisperer so you can talk to animals and
also you can charm them
uh... charming them what means that i control them
yes or that they
they say that they like you and will be safe small love with you
yeah
okay don't realize how much you'd be fucking animals when i gave you that
ability and i'm okay happy now yeah does it is the rat giving me bedroom eyes
uh... rolling inside him for eyes to demonstrate
ronan's executive c_n_n_
okay inside
that's the rest of it
uh...
you can't quite tell if it's giving you better my turn up but you assume it
probably is
okay i attempt to charm the rat
Okay, the rat has to beat a roll here.
It's not very wise, so.
Yeah, rat got negative two.
The rat is instantly charmed by you.
You see the rat like stand upright
and start to give you like, start to,
- Oh yeah.
- Raise its eyebrows and do a little hubba hubba dance.
- That's really good to me.
uh...
uh... all right i a whisper in the rats here
uh... that i would like the rat to give the plague to one of the terrorists
you can't
the rat uh... runs over to one of the terrorists and
to have advantage on this attack
of the terrorist with that has my pitchfork in his head preferably ok yeah
yeah that hits
uh... terrorist uh... gets bit on the leg
in your jigsaw go how i mean
uh... well you know and uh...
uh...
and uh...
this guy takes
what is that noise is that that takes uh...
uh... six uh... plague damage
and uh... describe how the plague kills this guy
uh...
it uh...
Well, beginning with his leg, his nervous system starts to shut down.
His leg starts to feel like it's asleep.
His dick falls off and his brain turns to jelly.
And yeah, then now his other leg is asleep.
And after the brain turns to jelly.
And then his fingernails fall off and he sees the face of the one that got away.
and uh...
her her face melts and uh... becomes gravestone
i start reading
i start crying because it's that's exactly what happened to my son
uh...
i see i see the penis on the ground and i have a flashback
the whole flashback is just
the whole flashback is just all black and all you hear is like a high pitched
ringing sound
and then i come to it i go oh god
and then i never talk about it
Yeah, that rocks. That guy's dead.
Um, okay.
Uh, shit. Alright.
Good turn, Dieter. Uh,
it is now
your turn, Alec Wahlberg. You come
to. Alright, so I come to,
I say, "Oh, Father O'Hara!" And then
I shoot.
I immediately shoot the pistol at
the... I, I'm
imagining the...
Never mind.
uh... i come to you and i just spray fire the pistol at the uh... the remain
yet role role the attack on that
so what are the heads
careful for the end
shit yeah uh...
yes guys have been been hit really yet so you should have
uh... you get 'em right in the uh... in the rib cage with the gun
and part of it
just blows off it's a puppet so that happens
and i'd still like standing there and hanging on
uh... and it's now it's turn
and it's going to uh... uh... commit you michael dangerous uh... now
well no
all
and
that hits by the way to create
what's
uh... i don't know what's happening
bro
you have that you have advantage on is gonna kill me i don't have a demand
van john
then he threw out starts whacking you in the head with the billy club
uh...
and uh... with and you take a living damage all my god i met three
and i start i start saying
nobody knows what it's like
the the sad man
uh...
six-year-old
you to be a little h_p_ man beautiful voice michael dangerous no one but ever
or accuse you of not having that.
(laughter)
And it is now Jedidiah, it's your turn.
Okay, I'm gonna finally use,
I think I'm gonna finally use my Bible thwomp,
the Bible thwap,
on the only remaining terrorist.
Yeah, you run up to him,
and you try to thwap him,
but you miss with your big thick Bible.
It's actually not the Bible, it's Message to the Black Man by Elijah Muhammad.
Okay, well you miss with that.
But it's a lot cooler.
Everybody's like, "Damn, that's so cool!"
Yeah, you turn into a dance move when you miss.
That's what I meant to do.
It is now your turn, Michael Dangerous.
Again?
right
the
i issued him and uh... he flies
back in the one that i realized
he uh...
he hits one of the windows on the side of the cabin and he gets he gets sucked out
like it's a spaceship
you can't
any flies into the world trade center
and the world trade that was up
uh...
yet and with that
with with time to spare
the uh... cause we successfully cause not a lot of
yeah
that he's successfully cause i can never fucking do that
and i don't want to do that
in the able to stop it but you could have never got a stick with it
started
you've sought you've
you've done it all of us and you saw a flight nine eleven puzzle
uh... and uh... the plane begins to fall away
uh... it sort of like sir select because it
like opens up and you all drop like 10 feet to the ground.
And in this chamber,
I like this.
This is a red room with a giant pig for everyone who's
as a giant pig spinning on a rotisserie
is a big blue ribbon on it.
that says, "World's Pig."
(laughing)
And a note that says,
"Climb into the pig to find the key, Dieter."
- That's all we get from the Jigsaw Man?
- That's all you get this time.
- A note?
all right i i can make my way to the pigs haunches
okay yeah
you wanna go get up in there
and i'm not i'm over here
the okay
you walk over uh...
he's my husband now so i go with them
and also i can't really read the know very well because english is my third
language
okay yeah
so you both uh... uh... crawl into the launches and describe your describe your
traveling through the pigs hole
uh... well i i i sex the pig
what is the sex of the pig
uh... mail
okay
and act that testicles like the monkey bars
he's okay
seeing that seeing these guys crawl into the pig i have a flashback of my son's
birth
and i'm not going to go into any more detail on what that means
and uh...
do you call to the piggy crawl through its it's it's all it's like holding on on
his pierce's defeat
this as he as he crawls with his arms
yeah you're digging through the pig commando style you two are just sort of
outside while this is happening
and uh... eventually you reach a part of a pig in you know anatomy of pigs pretty
well pierce that's right just i feel like a close my eyes
and you start to realize your your you are closing your eyes summary and you
should realize that's true is
a
divot in front of you that you don't recognize and uh...
uh... you
sort of like your arms are to go through it
and then you start to
slide down through it slide down to this viscera of the inside this pig
it's on an estin of any kind you can tell so i almost like it was carved
out to the
uh...
and as this is happening
uh... you start to hear a voice now booming over the loudspeakers in this
room
uh... and uh... at least from what you can tell you here it didn't and from
you guys on the outside you see the pig's mouth moving as it's spinning
probable product
peter temporary
you've always been a curious young man have achieved by a slightly through the
test and switch it and i a m
ever since you were a boy
you can try to do that
things sit in toy story did except with a real baby in a real spider
you've always been interested in the experimental world of animal silent
science and hybrid creatures in your own perverse way.
As you grew you found there was more freedom in running your
own ranch experimenting on animals there.
Rather than going to some school where there's rules and
ethics you experimented wantonly fucking any creature that
came your way don't matter to the species.
But finally that came up to you caught caught up to you.
I'm sorry.
I'm reading from a it's a very not a lot of light here.
You did something so wrong, so crazy, that even you knew the second you did it, that there was no going back.
Say it.
Uh, what do you want me to say, man? I was young, I was hungry.
I was dumb and full of cum.
Say what you did.
I jerked off a bull and had a cum into my hands.
You filled a chicken egg with pig cum and shot it into a cow's pussy with a bumper
bus.
Oh right, I was young, dumb, and had a bull cum from a cow's ass.
So many animal sins that you don't even know.
I was trying to help it get out.
You can't even narrow it down.
Was it bull cum from a cow's ass?
There's a lot of reasons you could be here right now.
It was pig jizz and a cow's cunt?
it was that one where i...
uh... put yeah...
you had a flashback where you put a cicada in your ass
and that was the first thing i was thinking maybe this will be it
but then you did this... no i remember i filled a chicken egg with pig jizz and shot it into a cow's cunt
or
what was it the other way i don't even fucking remember i was... i can't believe you don't
remember this... i was stupid back then i was so hungry i didn't know how shit like that worked
you just slide it
test it
you have a
you try to have a flashback but it's just like
i was too hungry
i've been married
to all sorts of f*cking critters
i didn't know that a critter had to be married
to a critter that just looked like it
i didn't know that a pig had
to be with a pig i don't wanna live in a
world like that so sue me
anchor plunk
you land in this lab mid
rant and you're suddenly strapped to this table and sitting and before you I'm
still like hanging off the table holding before you is one of your experiments
long-forgotten back when you were a little bit more academic in some of my
pursuits okay you thought you're Dieter Dimbre you thought you could experiment
with the lives of others, but now you will be the experiment.
Meet my assistant, experiment 1175936, as you called him.
Do you remember him?
He remembers you, and you see before you a dog head
on top of a frog's body with Doug Benson's legs.
(laughing)
- All right, I flashback to getting Doug with I.
- Right, caught a contact high being on set
from getting Doug with high.
Was going through Doug Benson's trash.
- Yeah, more trash.
- Yeah.
- And then Doug Benson comes out and says,
"What are you doing, man?
I'm stoned."
- Is that what he sounds like?
- Yeah, that's it.
(laughing)
- I walk out of this flashback,
I'm also in the green room with Doug.
i'm in the green room with doug and i just sold him a pound of heroin
i'm also i'm also there and i i say
uh... i say puff puff past the marijuana cig
i don't even smoke i just love the way it smells
and
uh... and uh... yet the uh...
the the experiment
with the dog had the frog body and doug benson's legs comes up to you
And he says, "Do you remember me, dear?"
"You must be one of my one, two, three, fuck, I'm getting busy, one of my hundred kids."
"You brought me into this terrible world. You gave me a name. It was just a number. I gave myself a name. It's Davinder."
"Hmm... What was your fuckin'... What are you, four, five, six, seven? Shit, I'm getting
busy. Eight, nine, what was the number?" "Now I'm going to attach bugles to your fingertips
and then kill you!" And on the outside, meanwhile, this pig is spinning and was talking. You
start to see the fire underneath the pig you too
uh...
uh... alec
wallberg and michael dangerous
the fire keeps getting bigger
the only way out of this room alive will be to get the key
i said the information
no that's not
that will not work this time
say it again
Please I mean it's just bad. It's bad. I
Shouldn't choose these ones. Why can't I fucking say it? I was saying it in a song
No, that's not you couldn't know. I don't want to live. I'm not here to do this
I was just saying it a fucking song you're singing along to a Marky Mark song. I
Was singing along to what a marks fucking demos
Okay
That's fine. I mean like whatever you do
- Look, there were a lot more in the fucking,
there were a lot more of those in the--
- I'm losing a jigsaw voice.
The more I talk to you about this N-word thing.
- There were a lot more N-words
in the Good Vibrations demo, I'll tell you that.
- Really?
Sorry, that was an accident.
- You're fucking weird.
You're weird as shit.
- The laugh just gets triggered sometimes.
- So yeah, both of you roll initiative.
All four of you really roll initiative
because you'll all be acting within order.
Um, and, okay, cool, let me add this.
So the idea here is that you're going to have probably only, let me think,
yeah, you're going to have like three rounds before the fire consumes the room.
You need to get to kill him and get the key before that.
Or you need to get the key and burrow out of the pig.
the key you will notice is on
uh... a belt loop of uh... the of uh... davender
so you can try to snatch it from him
and is that is that
did i in the room with me yes i'm with you
yeah that was a good move
you know you're gonna be a smart easy yeah hitching myself
yeah
getting hitched alright
we did get hitched so wait who goes first
uh... about to find out
looks like it's gonna be
allocates your you go first alec walberg
what can i do here
chemistry smarts
right on the is my street smarts i'm gonna assess whether or not this is
bullshit
uh...
okay
that's so the way that
uh... that ability works is on any check
uh...
that you're suspect of, whether it's an investigation check or whatever, that you've seen made or
that you have, you can just change it to a 15.
That's not really happening right now.
Okay, so I can't use that right now.
You could, if you want to find another way out of the room or you want to find a way
to stop the fire, you use one of those checks and then you can use your street smarts if
it's lower than a 15.
Okay, all right
All right, I'm gonna use an investigation check and I'm gonna try see
I'm gonna see if I can shut off the fire because there's definitely I've worked in kitchens before yeah, I like I know
I know that the fire has to come from some propane source. Yes. Okay. Yeah do an investigation check on that
Okay, you can swap that out using your street smarts, all right, I'm using that okay, so yeah, you got a 12 but your street smarts
What do you remember? What helps you? What's what kind of you know genius you got going on here?
That's helping you wanna fucking we had a luau at Wahlburgers before
Fire doesn't go on the side of the fucking pig it goes under so obviously this guy's never been to a fucking luau I
Never got invited
Yeah, that's right bitch look at you. You fucking look weird. You look weird. You can't see me right now. I can't
Earlier, and you look like I did look weird
Out of your pants. I'm not no it's not you look like a fucking puppet dude. I don't look weird
You look weird. You're a puppet. You're a puppet. You're a second. I recognize that voice is that is that Tobin Bell?
So what happens when you realize so what you happens is you you remember from your luau days
wall burgers. Wall burgers Hawaii. Yeah, and you notice that, um, that, uh, I see two,
I see two little like, like little things poking out of the ground that like the propane
things. Yeah, and, and if you, you could potentially, what you could do next turn is go in there,
you can move there now, but then you'll take fire damage. So I would, I tell Cameron to
the
like undo the propane tank. Okay, it is your turn. My turn. Oh,
Cameron. Okay, nevermind. I dangerous. Wait, so it would be
better if I helped him undo the propane tank. Yeah. So here's
what Pat here's what Patrick would have discovered is that if
you smash the the propane nozzles, you can have it so that
the flames don't have any room to come out and it builds back
up underneath the ground and can make it malfunction. Okay, I
that
else
my
dot com towards the propane tank that's the
here
people who are very close to the protein for it's like the nozzle sticking out a
fight i shoot the nozzle
yet what we get in a prone position will you shut up
uh... home
uh... in the proposition to shoot the nozzle
okay five okay now you know what i won't take my turn what do you guys take my
turn for me go ahead
you okay role role attack them
eighteen
yet that that's gonna hit the nozzle roll for damage
twelve shit okay well
okay
from the issue that the uh...
the propane nozzle you get a hit on it
uh...
uh... and this one you see the flames are dish of shit i move the pig bags
all shit
what happened
patches made a pig appear for a few minutes
uh... sorry
and
and other flames while you guys by yourself uh... a little bit more time
uh... susie the flame shrinks a little bit he sort of squeeze up the nozzle bit
on that one
uh...
and now
it is
uh...
of dealers turn
uh... i flashback to the the day in question where i don't know how to connect
with uh...
pages and shot into a because pussy
uh...
so can someone be my rattlesnake wife and then can
uh... and i think it was three separate
to it
so i've been uh... eating payo de as an eight-year-old for ten days straight
and with these four animals
he
Shoot I'm getting kind of bored and hungry
Do you all speak English to me
Why I'm uh, I'm the bait I'm a bear
I'm a girl cow. Yeah, you're a girl cow. Yeah. Oh, well my pussy feels okay
So don't do anything to that, please. I want to make some so good
Take some of my come
Dinner it's your birthday. Happy birthday. Look what I got you
I just got I just laid his egg over here
Like where this is going oh, no, I don't want to pick open my baby's egg with the river he drinks vodka
He tries to do this
Tastes like chicken and pork and beef all in one delicious sandwich
All right, that sounds pretty good. All right now. I'm gonna put the comedy egg
No, I'm as I'm the wife
No, please actually I'm okay with this so we don't we avoid that
Yeah, you shoot it right in this cows
Days for it just dates for two weeks and then a beautiful egg. What do you do for those two weeks?
I eat all of the living animals.
Except for the mother cow. I wait for her to give birth to the hybrid.
Here she blows. There she comes.
I eat the newborn. The newborn slides out of the pussy and right into my open mouth.
And then I pat my belly three times before even getting to know the hybrid in question.
And Davinder is cowering in the corner for the past two weeks watching this happen.
Yeah, my first time in a place like this.
And he's remembering, and he runs away from you.
Ah, now I remember that little critter.
[laughter]
You scat me! You ate my brothers!
This is giving me an ad beer.
No.
I give the blunderbuss and the egg that I made with my wife or husband to Jedidiah.
I say, "Try to get this out of here and put pig kame and shoot it into the pig's pussy."
"I have to go jack off a pig?"
And then I pat his head twice and blink.
Yeah, that's a yes.
Okay, so I start crawling back through the intestinal tract to get to his...
Now get back here is Bruce Tate. Yeah. Yeah, so roll a heavy roll and
Athletics check. Okay, it's very athletic to do a move
Nice yeah, you get you get a little bit of way in there. I mean both you can do that
If you're the one doing it, you're just doing that in your turn. Yeah
No, I'm not doing your turn and we'll play that rest of that out in a second
But Dieter, so what else do you want to do in your turn? You can still attack or move.
Alright, uh, I sniff the room looking for animals. Other animals that are not, uh, Davinder.
Yeah, roll Perception. Or Nature, or whatever the fuck. Whatever you want.
What the fuck I want? I think I have a Nature bonus or something.
Yeah, I want you to like, take, yeah, it's your ability, so, yeah. Nice, yeah, okay.
So you see that in the back in the behind Avender there is a
There's an ocelot just licking its paws in a cage
And it says Davinder sister on
Yeah
All right, is that my move or do I still get to do something you can do something that's just you noticing shit
All right, so now I do insight to see if the animals giving me bedroom eyes yeah do it try to see okay
I've negative one to inside
Yeah, you can tell that she's and she's kind of into it you're kind of a wily
All right. So what so I I speak to her. I try to see what she's communicating. Yeah. Yeah, let's see
Okay, she yeah you try to you try to a charm her you can't but you can speak to her
She says to you so you couldn't you could still try to persuade her to do things but
You know where her deal is. Yeah. Okay. She said she's a she says what's up? What's going on big boy?
Howdy
So my brother seems mad at you
Show enough
(laughing)
- I'm just hanging out here.
I'm just a pretty little ocelot.
- All right, I don't know what to say to her.
I'm nervous.
(laughing)
- Jedediah, hype her up.
- Boy, I sure wish my brother wouldn't keep me
in this here cage.
Not sure what his problem is.
Seems like a sins of the father situation, you know?
i ask ask you what is uh... what his greatest fear is a it's a
what you gracefully what is greatest fear and then tell me yours also if you think
i'm if you think i can handle it
the role persuasion check
uh... with advantage it's a because it's it's a good idea
so just rolling will take the bigger number
always show
will
net twenty
okay uh...
she says uh...
his greatest fear
is experimentation on his back
this is a good
it's a little bit
yeah that's a good
and then she also tell me her greatest though yes she does uh... she said that
but she says that she says that
if you make it look like you're doing an experiment on him he starts a freak out
and go pp
now as for me
my greatest fear
to be elected in cage forever
and i think that it
uh... i want to be free
i'm an oscillant dammit
okay like to be a pretty
but
shore
and uh... it's
yet that's your uh... uh... that that i'll say is enough for an action
but uh... now you know
yes and useful information uh... it's the
uh... jenna diana
you're crawling so it's pigs
intestines
mhm
you made a solid athletics check
uh...
uh... so you can you can uh... on how do you make to fight to get up into the
whole
i'll have you make one more to see if you can uh...
crawl out of the hall
seven o'clock still
you're still sort of like making your way through the site crawling
uh... with my own and i'll go to the saving private ryan
is anything else you want to do though like you wanna try to help get yourself
through that are now
uh... yeah i i'll use my amish magic city and yet yet do it
is there a little of their called make big cub
better be
okay something else i want help also let me look at the list here
uh... somewhat helpful
uh...
some pig porn
but i mean i think that
and i can
and make it come from anywhere
uh... that's too helpful then
also a that uh...
i should have someone had a
somewhat helpful then is i would say where is that and looking at it and
that's gone
fuckin
yeah okay
i would say is uh...
reduce
so you cast reduce on yourself
which makes you a bit smaller and you're gonna have a easier time crawling
through
uh... here
and i think that i think that they can
and
uh... and now it is davender's church
uh...
and
uh... so yeah uh... sorry i'm trying to move everybody around all the time
there we go
he's coming at you
now you're you're not here anymore
of shit wrong guy
you're not here anymore
uh...
so yeah he's coming at you he's gonna try to uh... uh...
attack you with his knife his big science knife he has uh...
okay what is your a_c_ deter it is
thirteen that hits my friend
yeah he slash you across your uh... torso
for uh... six damage
so that he had to be a s and uh... to scrap slash you cross your torso
now
and i think we have got me
and
that yet he got me
and so that's not going to attach bugles to your fingers
and
there
it is now your turn alec will burke
all right so
i look at the other
uh...
flame yeah and the uh... the flame by the way you know this flame gets bigger
well it's
damn i'd for a couple
i throw a bottle of uh... mark walberg's brand of water aqua hydrate at it
brought athletics checked it to her and also
since shit
wide just a wide of it uh... if you have this is water on the ground like over
here
like a good
like fifteen feet away from the flame i'd move over there and start like trying
to throw it off the ground so i can start trying to put the bottle at the
water
and yeah i know what
yes i work it yet there's just like it's is getting worse out there
uh...
uh... this one gets only a little bit bigger though
uh... so yet is now your turn michael dangerous
all right
uh...
I'm gonna try it can I uh...
my getting someone else dangerous
ability
how does that work I can add
add stuff to people's rolls do I have to do it when they roll or can I do it like
preemptively? You can give it to them and they choose when they want to use it. Okay I'm gonna use
I'm gonna use this
uh... ability
on uh...
on on Dieter Demphry
so that uh... so that next time
you next time you need it
You'll have a bonus on a roll.
Yeah.
So what will happen basically works like bardic inspiration except you don't
need a line of sight.
Oh, yeah, of course.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
This is for the people who you know, somebody out there is like, oh boy,
so, you know, all right, but for you Dieter you can add a d6 to any d20
roll.
You're going to make so like an attack role or like an ability check sort of
what you've been doing.
So, yeah, yeah, and to inspire him.
I'm rapping along. I'm just I'm kind of rapping to him
Through the pig's mouth. Yeah, and I'm guy go up to the pig's mouth and I start I start rapping into it
Ain't it a shame that you can't say fuck fucks just a word and it's all fucked up like a fucked up punk with the fucked
Up mouth a nine-inch nail gets knocked the fuck out fucked up aids from fucked up sex fake titties on a fucked up chest
I'm flat back to the first time I heard rap and I'm
I'm filling with rage.
*laughter*
Uh, yeah, and it is- it is your turn.
So you can- what are the results of that rage?
Uh, I take my pitchfork out and I try to stab, uh, Davinder, uh, in the mouth.
Yeah, go for it.
Make it look like a science experiment.
I don't care. I'm too angry.
I was never really that good of a scientist anyway, if I'm being honest.
this
Yeah, what do I do attack strength? Yeah attack. So just go to your your attack
Attacks and spellcasting yours pitchfork is oh, that's right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah that fucking hits and then hit pitch right inside the chat. Yeah
Nice. Fuck. Yeah, where do you want to stab him in his mouth?
Okay. Yeah, you just stab him in the mouth with a pitchfork
You just do a quick jab in there and jab out
And like blood just like squirts out of the back of his throat onto your face, okay
Yeah
You and
Yeah, he's not looking. Yeah, that was pretty good. He's easy. See he's not looking too hot right now. Let me tell you that
uh... and now it is your turn to judges is is is is it a diet
and i had to take falls yet
uh... yeah you crawled out at this point all what you call out uh...
but uh... uh... now you have to do used to do one actually try to get the
retarded jerk off this
spinning
so you need to do and and athletics check the hold on their strength check the
hold on to the pigs at
uh...
which can be too hard 'cause it is just a it's spinning
It's not like and I have done this before.
When I hit strength.
Yeah, go for it.
Oh, not one.
Nice try.
I'm not taking that.
So, oh God, I actually hit it.
Oh my God.
Yeah, you're holding on to the balls and you just start to slip
off the balls and they start to turn up again.
So this is a smaller pig that I'm used to.
I don't really know what I'm doing.
Yeah, so you'll have to make an athletics check again next turn to make that work.
Now it is your turn.
Your turn, Davinder.
Okay, me.
So Davinder is now going to try to, oh, you know what I should do, by the way?
Sorry.
You could take this out of the recording.
I won't.
Okay.
You always do that when I ask so it's sort of like why am I
No, there's no there's no free. You know it in roll 20. There are no free ocelot assets. So
Get on that roll 20 instead I will put the closest thing I can think of which is a
fat tiger
This looks like fucking shit
sister
how how is it that i've heard that needed to be a disease
seductive okay it's it's a very very very uh... there uh... i don't have to
explain this to you
uh...
you can't talk to the sibling c_n_n_ davender says uh... to his sister
are some of sister
get out of the cage
any presses a button on that
you know i like a panel near that wall
and uh... the cage opens up
and the ocelot starts to uh... wander out
uh... i'll give you this chance
Dieter to try to convince this ocelot
to be on your side. You've already persuaded it enough.
Yeah, I feel like this ocelot wouldn't have been here unless I sniffed the room.
Yeah, no, you figured it out. You figured out that there was an ocelot in here.
uh... okay uh...
okay uh... what what i'm right now it's not my turn but i have the chance to
persuade the ocelot to... Yeah, I'm giving you like a "use your reaction" basically. To stay in its cage?
uh... to to either be on your side to be your friend to stay in a change yeah i
want to ask what to stay out of this
yet talk talk to her
and uh...
don't don't don't worry your mover do anything just stay there
pretend you're sleeping and go to sleep
there's a lot of act go to bed
okay here for persuasion check
actually i'll do it which i charm your try charm it
let's get charming it into sleeping
when i'm a yes she fails
so she she uh... she goes uh...
uh...
we know what you're right i don't need to
my brother's stinky i don't
i don't need to do anything he says that she starts a slowly drift off
into ocelot dreams
uh... he's a no
my stupid
or sister
she's totally uncalled for
uh...
and uh... yet he's gonna try to swipe at you
and uh... he misses he swipes he's too distracted by everything going on
uh... he misses at you
uh... now it is your turn walberg
so
and i'm looking at the fire a little bit bigger
all
i look at a glass sheet
and that's my turn
alright
maybe i should just try to throw water at it again
or hit the uh...
nozzle on the other one
yeah i'm gonna hit the nozzle on the other one
i'm gonna use my irish pistol
nice, roll for damage
nice yeah
uh... you
hit that nozzle shooting propane mysteriously from the floor
any shrink down the flame it's it's gets bottled up more buying yourself a little
bit more time that's good because you were
you're running out of time obviously uh... so now
is your turn michael dangerous
yeah
uh...
if i shoot the nozzle again
is anything gonna happen
on that nozzle no it's a sort of down as much as you can you can choose a book
i thought we are to get both the nozzles
television is there
there's a new nozzle
the flame that popped up
what the hell
yes we are not sure i'll shoot the new nozzle then
yet to enroll this it's easy to me
i know exactly what it is not yet did it
the role for damage
forty-eight shit
you basically like straight past that one when you really nice
Yeah!
So it's never gonna produce a flame again?
No, it's producing-
It's never gonna produce a flame again.
It's never gonna produce a flame again!
That's what- that's what-
That's what Jigsaw promised.
He said-
*overlapping*
Did Jigsaw promising you something he didn't?
Yeah.
Jigsaw pinky promised me with this-
*overlapping*
I have a false flashback on-
Stop having a false memory.
Do not have a false memory.
yeah i have a false memory to to finding
or to this dungeon and i think it's deadly
and that's that's that's a big kidnap tonight
and i think
and
i have a flashback to what i survived all the traps and got away
and i think that's right away deter
uh... alright i guess i can't stand this kind of fun with the pitchfork again
so she also
but i think it'll focus realize that uh...
who
because it's a six twice
and begin three back
uh...
and instead of my pitchfork
before
yet it's role for damage
and i see it describe your killing your experiment
all he's dead
yet you didn't sit on damage him earlier
uh...
Yeah, I stab him in the belly and a few tears leave his eyes.
It was the closest thing to a family member he's ever had.
Far closer than the stupid fucking horror of the Mother's Thoughts.
Shut up! I loved her!
You can't hear my thoughts.
Yes I can!
Oh right, because we have a telepathic bond.
Yeah, right.
Why?
Yeah, so I see his life flash before my eyes.
and uh...
see him remembering getting a frog body and remembering getting doug benson's
legs attached to him. See if he'll remember how to set up the uh... the
propane
yeah right yeah i'm scanning
well i don't know if he set up the trap i feel like the trap was set up by jigsaw.
yeah no the memories you see from him though are of him
bagging all of you and bringing you here. Oh my god. He was jigsaw's assistant.
oh jesus alright he was the one who tied us to the maypole he touched my penis i can
see that very clearly. Yeah, you see him touching your penis, you see him lingering a little.
The flashback, the flashback from earlier where I blacked out and it was a ringing sound.
I look down and it's David Dirk.
Um, I wanted to be a porn star and he just slowly dies. Yeah, um, oh fuck there was something I uh,
Oh yeah, as he s- as the life leaves his eyes, I start to salivate and then I eat his corpse.
Oh yeah, I forgot.
Yeah.
And then his purpose is finally fulfilled. He was bred for meat.
After you belch out a bone, like a cartoon, uh, you then belt her with three of the most
delicious meats, a frog and Doug Benson and whatever the other one was.
Dog.
And you also belch out a key.
Oh, awesome.
The key to the door.
I have to look for the key.
I'm ready to die at this point.
I don't care if I get out.
Yeah, and so, yeah, you can now get out of there.
You know, you all get out of there.
You all sort of defeat the...
You crawl out of the pig as fast as you can.
I'm still trying so hard to jack off the pig
because I haven't gotten the news yet.
- He's inside the pig, I'm fucking jacking it off.
(laughing)
- The flames slowly subside.
- I think of Charlotte's Web.
- Pulling on a big pig dick.
- The flames slowly subside,
you're just spinning around on this pig
trying to jerk it off.
And the door, you have the key to the door now,
so you can all go to the next room.
well i also have a retreat the oscillator my way out
yes you can you may
yet he's charmed so she's yours
uh... i have to enter into the next room
uh... home i guess i already have two wives at this point so i also just
proposed to her also
yes she says yes she's like i love being married
and she had a yeah
uh... three wives right now
and so now you're in the wish i thought of that
uh... and your jigsaw
say arm
so i didn't again i didn't know there is going to be a fourth guy
what's up
i didn't have a lot of time uh...
that's my nephew adam
uh...
i gave him a gun
and uh... i see a mickey he's like
you see him as i thought he's like texting
uh... it looks up
and what looks back down
and uh... you have to uh...
the trap is uh... he's gonna show you with the gun
that
uh...
i don't have any visuals in here either i can see what's going on
i really didn't have any time to set this room up it's not a problem
i'm really you know i feel bad for you again
jenna died did not mean for this to happen
and frankly they're all you've all survived i'm feeling
pretty pretty bummed out right now
and while he's like so saying this
you see adam's writing on a piece of paper
he's saying again i can't hear any of this
uh... i can see anything that's going on in there
uh... you see it but uh... you know
uh... you see adam hold up the piece of paper
and show it to you guys
uh...
and uh... uh...
it says uh...
underneath the desk lamp there's a switch that'll open the door
can one of you stab me in the leg or something so it could look like i
I
is
I was like like like here's like very faintly like laugh track and she's like what's what's happening in there. Shut up, bitch
What do you always do this?
I attack the nephew. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. I've always wanted to be in a fight
Nothing that we just did
Yeah, wow my own room
Yeah roll the tack roll do I need to roll initiative first or
I know I'm just I'm just kidding a surprise round on this nephew
All right. Yeah roll initiative because it will be combat if you don't kill it, which you can very easily
But I had to hurt him. He is just a teenager
Oh
Yeah, you're just rolling to hurt him then yeah roll
So yeah, he lets you, um...
You hit him. What do you do with the Bible?
What do you do?
Am I using my Bible?
Well, how are you hitting him?
I guess that's my only attack.
Can I give Caleb my gun?
Yeah, okay. He gives me the gun.
I also give Caleb my gun.
Caleb also has my gun at this point.
Guns.
I mean Jedediah. I give Jedediah my gun.
Yeah, right.
I use all of them to shoot him in the kneecaps.
Okay, shit, roll, I guess, roll an attack roll for just a d20.
That's three attacks.
Just do forward slash.
That's three guns.
Okay, thank God.
Yeah, you just clearly missed his teenage...
We're just going, "What the fuck, dude?
What the fuck?"
Your note said to hurt you.
Not to shoot you.
What note?
What is he talking about?
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Are you seeing this?
I see the kid like runs, like grabs his pencil he used to write the note and just stabs himself
in the leg.
He's like, "Get the fuck out of here!" and just yells at you.
I slap him in the face.
I also, I also, I throw the shillelagh at him again.
Yeah, he throws shillelagh at him again.
Yeah, he's, roll an attack roll.
Okay, roll for damage.
Uh, yeah, describe your kill on this weapon.
*laughter*
I...
He's not like a person that you could think, he's just a regular NPC.
Oh, he's dead now.
I throw the shillelagh's head so hard that it hits off.
Like, just this whole, the whole right side of his head goes back into the wall.
With the shillelagh and the shillelagh stuck in the wall, I can't even get it out.
Okay.
Yeah, you do that, you murder this boy.
(laughing)
Even though he was trying to get you out.
And you go to the lamp, you lift it up,
you press the switch, you open the door, you've done it.
You've solved the saw, jigsaw,
and you step outside of the room.
And you notice that everything is kind of weird.
All four of you as you step outside.
- Everything is kind of weird.
(laughing)
I was just about to say that, dude.
"Something's funny about this."
It's all really green, and it's all very salty.
And you start to remember, you have a flashback to a jigsaw saying,
"Quite the pickle you're in."
And you start to go forward in time.
And you see that you're in the karaoke room and the microphone is a pickle.
And you go further and then the plane is a pickle.
You just realized that pig that was spinning was not a pig, it was a pickle.
And the nephew you just killed, you look down, "It's pickle, Rick."
And you now are realizing that you are literally inside of a pickle.
- You're trapped inside of a pickle. - I knew it.
And the camera slowly zooms out, and you're in a jar of pickles.
And you see a hand reach into the pickle jar and take a bite out of it.
- And who is that hand? - A jar?
It's a jar. You're in a jar. You're in a pickle.
inside of a jar of pickles. That's the saw twist.
And the hand that reaches in, that takes out the pickle and takes a bite, who is it?
It's Black Hamtaro from the anime Hamtaro.
Good night, everybody.
One of the most clever plot twists in the series, I have to say.
I was trying to think of the dumbest plot twist possible.
I think you got close.
Yeah, thanks.
Wow, that was something else.
What was the... the black Hamtaro was named Oswald, right?
I don't remember his name.
Patrick definitely watched Hamtaro.
I watched Hamtaro's key.
Yeah, his name is Oswald or something.
Something similar.
He's like... his tattoo is starting to itch.
Alright, happy Halloween everybody.
Happy Halloween.
I'm gonna stop the recording now.
(dramatic music)
[Music]
I'm not the one to blame
(dramatic music)
[Music]
[BLANK_AUDIO]