Come here, come here, come here, let me see your butt.
(laughing)
- Do it.
- Go to the hood, I must.
- Say it right over.
- Get holicious, I will.
- He's gonna become get holicious.
- That's from our new movie, Yoda in the Hood.
- I thought you said it was Yoda de la Ghetto.
- Oh yeah, Yoda de la Ghetto.
(laughing)
Why'd you hit ghetto? Why'd you say ghetto? It's a French film. Yeah. Oh,
Yoda de la ghetto. Yoda de la ghetto I am. Je suis. What kind of pants you have on Yoda de la ghetto?
Janko!
Janko shorts? That'd be cool. Pants on me. Pants on me they are. Pants on me they are.
Janko shorts. Me pants on they. Pants, pants!
I yeah and then what I said was my big black ass
I didn't say my big black
When did I see you never said I don't even do the other way you said you do the Yoda voice you were the
Yoda Yoda's in here Yoda. It's not me. So you didn't say my big grass. I've been here
It's Yoda's in the room Yoda. How'd you fit your big black ass in this room?
from space car space Royce space Royce is that a nice car does it go to like a
rolls-royce if it's a rolls-royce but it's space does it even have the stars
on the top or is it something else yes no it does have the stars you have like
grass on the top I feel like that would make sense because when you're saying
yeah I think it makes perfect sense is it wheels or were like jet boosters or
that was it does it worse for force force. Oh, you said it was a space
Roy.
Well, that's a different car. That's way, way better. That is
I love being. I thought you might
so cool.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I miss Yoda. Oh dude, you know, what's great about
that? What it's Grover to
can be Grover in the hood. But Grover doesn't. Same voice. Grover would end up in the hood.
Yeah. He'd probably shoot his cannon too far. He'd bring his cannon to the hood. Yeah, Super
Grover. Yeah. It would be Super Grover first of all. Yeah. He would be in there. And he'd
end up in the hood. And they would help him out because it's good there. There's a monster
at the end of his hood. Yeah, dude Yoda in the hood is very, that's a, I mean if we were
on Newgrounds in 2003. There has to have been a Sesame Street in the hood. Yes. Yeah. You
remember Elmo's Got a Gun? That wasn't in the hood though. Yeah it was. No that was
like we need to talk about Kevin style thing. No no Elmo's Got a Gun cuz the end
of the song is like the I mean it's like. Weird Al didn't do hood humor. It's not
Weird Al. It's wrongly attributed to Weird Al. Yeah it was a radio DJ. Everything's weird.
It was all Weird Al. It's true on LimeWire it was Weird Al. On my mom's iPod it was Weird Al.
That was Weird AI. Yeah. Oh. It's the AI that generates parody songs. So what. It was a
radio host, a radio host did that and then at the end of the song he does like
black voice and is like "You want me to walk through Setsmiss Street without a
bulletproof vest? Forget about it!" Whoa. Yeah dude I remember all the words to that.
Weird Al wouldn't have done that. I listened to that probably when I was like nine years old I heard that more than the Beatles I think.
The Hood was a frontier that Weird Al would never, no he never pushed. Yeah he's a respectable man.
Maybe that you see they're making a movie about a biopic of Weird Al with
with Daniel Radcliffe playing Weird Al.
- The Daniel Radcliffe show.
- And I think they might touch on the hood years.
- Really?
- Where he says that he'll never do hood stuff
until White and Nerdy,
because he doesn't want to disrespect that community,
and then White and Nerdy comes along.
- And he gets kind of tempted by the money.
- Yeah.
- And so he finally goes into the hood
and does ghetto stuff.
- Yeah.
- We basically, I think we just,
in the last five minutes, did our entire hood era.
And I think our hood in Ghetto Era might be over.
I think it's good that we stop.
I think we're done with the hood.
I think we had 5 minutes.
I think it's good for like, yeah, at least 5 minutes and then you kind of tread into dangerous waters.
Yeah.
And then you sound like an asshole.
You think the hood is dangerous waters? Is that what you're saying?
No, there's no waters in the...
(laughter)
See what I mean?
Look, we hit 6 minutes.
Now we're at 4 minutes and 30 seconds.
Well, we were doing it 2 minutes before.
That fell within the purview of hood time.
I don't want to see 5.01.
I don't want to see where Pat takes it at 5.01.
We've got 15 seconds left, Pat.
I want a bowl with...
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
I've got all my hood shit out on every other episode.
This is your time.
Okay, we're done.
No more talk about the hood.
about the hood. Whatever you do, don't say anything about Yoda being in the
hood or what he would do in the hood or what he would use the force to do in
the hood or...
Do you think he would...
Of course I am. Hold my lightsaber sideways, I do.
no more talk about what Yoda would wear if he was in the hood or how he would
address people.
He doesn't, does Yoda wear anything?
Yeah, he has a robe.
He wears a Jedi robe.
A Jedi robe?
He wears a chain.
People forget.
He's on this robe.
He's on a chain, but he wears a necklace.
People forget that.
There will be no talk of what Yoda's necklace would have.
Yoda's necklace, well here's what it actually has.
It's like, you know, it's like a, have you seen the Tu Wong Fu?
Huh?
where Patrick Swayze and John Leguizamo and Wesley Snipes are drag queens?
No. No.
I think it's too unfair.
Sounds really hot.
Too unfair and thank you for, I don't remember, but...
Thank you for smoking?
I think in that movie one of them has like a turd on a necklace.
Whoa!
But Yoda has his semen in his necklace just in case he wants to make another Yoda.
And there will be no, we will not talk about what it would be like...
He pops out to a woman like a cartridge.
If Yoda was having a child in the hood.
if Yoda was making a baby in the hood or having sex in the hood, we can't talk
about it.
Kayla and I are shaking in our chairs.
There's nothing to be said about the kind of girl that Yoda will be having a
baby with in the hood. Yaddle.
And that's it. Just yaddle. There's no suffix at the end that goes on for a
while. Just yaddle, okay? We're done. We're done with Yoda in the hood. I'm
making an executive decision as one of the executives. Yeah, it's over.
Nobody wants to hear about what kind of hood shit that Yoda was doing.
Nobody wants to hear Yoda's freestyle that he does on the corner of the
street in the hood. Nobody wants to hear that. No, it's not for you.
It's not. Nobody wants to hear... It's not for us. I remember you was
conflicted. Nobody...
(laughter)
Okay.
Okay. We're done.
I don't think you said it right.
Remember you was conflicted, I do.
That's better.
Yeah.
But we're done.
What has everyone been up to?
We just got back from Los Angeles.
It sucked.
I like it.
I can't even.
I actually like LA now.
I like, the first time I ever went there was to film the Patrick Goes to Jollibee and I
slept in the trash.
That's it, this was a big upgrade for you.
Yeah, I got to sleep, I only slept on the floor one time because I wanted to give your
brother a couch.
He slept on the floor and my brother, I thought, at one point Pat started snoring so bad that
my brother left the house for two hours at like five in the morning.
I wish I could have done that.
He went and slept in his car for a little bit.
Yeah.
It was pretty cool, yeah.
That's how bad my snoring is.
Your snoring is horrible, dude.
You are one of the worst snorers I've ever seen.
You beat Pete, dude.
You beat my grandpa, yeah.
I really got to get that sleep apnea mask.
My ex would be so scared that I would choke in my sleep.
You sound like you're constantly choking in your sleep.
Do I?
Yeah.
It's horrible.
That's not my problem.
If I die, I die.
Damn, he's living on the edge.
Whoa.
If I die in my sleep, at least I'm having like a crazy dream.
Yeah, if I die in my sleep and I don't even know about it, I don't care.
If it's completely painless.
I'm having a crazy ass dream where I'm having crazy sex.
I'm getting choked by a bug queen.
You're going to get choked by the bug queen.
I've been having crazy dreams.
Oh yeah?
I had this dream the other night that I was this is a very very like like
revealing dream of the kind of stress that I have in my brain. Most of the
time I had a dream that I was on a plane and the plane started to take off and
it like couldn't finish the take off and it crashed and like exploded and I was
fine like I got out of the plane crash and I walked back to the airport and I
walked out of like the like the like security thing you can't go back into
and then I was talking to somebody. I was like yeah, I was just on a flight
that like crashed like can I get my money back and they were like no after you
leave the airport, you can't come back in to get your money back and I was like
oh no. I had a weird dream last night. So sexual dream. Nah, shut it down. Who
was the victim? Victim? Come on man. Or the other. Who was the, who was your
lucky target? Well here, the whole dream was that I was about to hook up with
friend dresser, but I couldn't because whoopee Goldberg was coming over.
We were supposed to have a dinner party. We may have misjudged him. He might be
in the old stinky granny's.
Are you? He might be a tomb raider.
Are you into old stinky? If it makes you stop calling me a
pedophile. The opposite of a cradle snitcher is a tomb raider. You could go
both ways.
It was like nanny friend dress. You're a crypt defiler. I was in the 90s.
You were in the 90s? So I was a baby.
So yeah, it happened in 97 and I was a baby.
Was she old then too? No. Are you kidding me? Friend dress around the nanny?
I don't know who that is man.
She goes "haaa" that lady. She laughs like that.
What? French Montana?
The fuck is that?
You know she'd be sipping the Hennessy.
She would.
We got into an Uber to Rex's place that was like...
Stop messing with that desk.
Alright.
Alright, if you don't want me to tell.
We got into an Uber that was like this...
Like a 45 minute Uber.
Like with this like 50 year old like cinephile like older black dude.
Yeah.
And he was just telling us about like Scorsese movies and stuff.
Yeah, I recommended Mean Streets to him.
And he was...
But he held out until the end that he was...
Whose brother?
Oh, Cali Swag District.
He was the guy from Cali Swag District's stepbrother.
- Yeah.
- Wow.
- Or half-brother or something.
And he held that the entire time.
- If I was an Uber driver, I'm leading with that
every time someone comes in.
I'm playing like, teach me how to doggie in the car
and being like, guess whose stepbrother this is?
Mine.
- That'd be cool if that was your stepbrother.
- It'd be cool if my parents got divorced
and I had more brothers and sisters.
- You had the entire Cali Swag District and the pack.
I don't want my parents to get divorced, but if that means two Christmases and the present is...
They can just adopt.
If you want extra brothers.
More brothers and sisters?
That is the ultimate gift.
Yeah.
The ultimate gift is if you're...
More playtime.
Is if your parents divorce and then your dad marries somebody who has a hot daughter your
same age and then you fall in love with your sister.
No, the ultimate is...
That's one of God's great gifts.
That's happened to people.
Ultimate is expensive dog.
I heard us. I think it happened when I was home. I heard somebody tell me that
they like. That's actually like one of the leading causes of love in the United States.
Isn't that the plot of Clueless? I heard somebody. That's the plot of a lot of movies. Yeah, many films.
Many films I've consumed. Many a day at the cinema.
Oh, remember we were in Tampa. We walked past that fucking. Oh yeah. When we were in Tampa we were
walking around because we didn't want to take like Ubers places and that's a place
you're not supposed to walk at all, but we literally from our like our city like
a con a lodge. We were walking to a waffle house and we passed by three
different like adult video centers and and I like when I looked up the route to
walk there. I was like oh we're gonna walk by and like an adult adult film
center or whatever and the one that I saw we were gonna walk by we didn't even
walk by that one. We walked by three different ones. There was another one
that we still walked. They still exist in the south because they can afford rent.
yeah, it's crazy. When my friend turned eighteen, he turned eighteen like right
around Halloween, and so on Halloween he was like dressed up as a ghost and he
like, we were, he was like let's go into the adult, like the adult movie thing,
and I wasn't old enough, but he was like let's go to the adult movie thing. I'll
run around like a ghost, and so he's going to get come done. Yeah, I mean it
was it was cool. I know yeah, you're just like a in there. It's not a ghost.
It's just a rag. Yeah, I walked in dressed up as a like a sheet ghost, and
there's like a decompression chamber where they have to like check your ID and like let
you in.
And so he did that.
He steam washed you like it's an airlock.
He did that.
He like gave the guy his ID and then he goes in and he just ran around the video store
like knocking videos off saying boo boo I'm a ghost.
And then he came back out and then we got like a mile down the road and he was like
oh shit I forgot my wallet in there.
So then he had to go back dressed as a ghost still and be like hey I left my wallet on
the ground. Yeah, we also walked by a porno theater. Yeah, a porno movie theater. And
when we saw somebody going in there at like noon. We made a joke. We like saw him
driving by and was like, "Oh, this guy's going to the porno theater." And then he just
pulled into the porno theater. I was like, "Wow." Also, in a place as small as... Oh, there was a
like a bar attached to it too. Yeah, well that's... You need the... No, you need the...
It was a bar that had like... It was like an arcade or something. Yeah, it was like an arcade attached to the porno theater.
You need the plausible deny it needs to be porno theater and like yeah
home we're talking about like imagine like going there for the barcade and you're like hanging out and then it like
Whatever like like midnight the movie gets out and like it just fills with like a 50 year
Like oh fuck. Oh, I'll walk up to you like I got next they're tapping you on the shoulder. They got sticky fingers
They're walking up to you. They're asking if you can point them to where the water is
You pull my quarters apart like a play game
Yeah, just like imagining the flood of them coming back into the bar. What is
it? Yeah, it would be a flood. Yeah, probably just busting open like the
shining lepping. It sounds like they're walking through a snowstorm.
They got their galoshes on. Oh, hell no, not for me. No, no, no nasty. I would.
They probably smell more. I would never smell good. Yeah, probably smells like
Nagasampa. Oh my god, it smells like spring. Is it just for guys who just can't figure
out how to open the Internet Explorer? I think it's guys who are afraid of Internet Explorer.
One thing is probably guys who are married. Yeah, yeah, definitely. Who need somewhere
to go to jack off because they don't know. It's guys who are married. Guys who are married
and got their computer taken away. I mean also like if you're homeless, like not too
many places to hang out in Tampa I think if you're homeless. That's true. Applebee's.
Remember you said that guy sticking in front of Applebee's? Oh yeah, oh he was sticking.
- So he was sticking?
- Oh, he really was.
- Yeah, he was sticking right now?
- He was sticking right then.
- What did he say?
- He was sticking.
- I don't remember, he was just going like
(mimics gun noises)
like right in front of the door.
- He was sticking, sticking.
- He's like, oh, we gotta show him our Vax Carbon IDs.
(laughing)
- Yeah, I think, I guess it's for,
you ever go to a guy's, someone's house?
I went to someone's house recently
and they don't have a lock on the bathroom door.
You're just like, how do you jack off
in this goddamn hellhole bathroom?
- Right.
- You have your fucking, it's like one of those
like stay out of the cone of vision of the teachers,
like flash games, but with your--
- Do you usually just walk around just throwing open,
like kicking down bathroom doors?
- I go to take shits and pisses.
- You don't knock?
- You don't knock, though?
That's what I'm saying.
- No, you're supposed to knock.
- Why wouldn't you knock?
- No, you're supposed to put a lock on a bathroom door.
- I, my, the lock on my family's bathroom door was broken,
like my entire childhood.
- You still don't have a lock on your door at your parents'
place. - It was your house.
- Yeah, I know.
- He's talking about your parents' house.
I went recently to a to a name names. I went to a bowl bop grill okay and they
have a code they have a code for the bathroom door but then lock on it okay
well yeah if it's like a restaurant yeah I asked the lady I was like hey can you
open the door and she's like sure and she goes over and she put punches in the
code and then she opened it like this like presenting it to me and in there
was just a woman taking a shit. Everybody just screamed and then I saw the lady
when she came out. She didn't look happy. No, I can imagine. Yeah. That happened to
me. You ever like think that it, you know, it's worse is a lock that's like not
heavy enough. So when you twist it you think it's locked but it's not. Happened
me at that fucking that breakfast spot that we went to with the big RBG mural.
Oh yeah. You know what sucks even more than that is when there's a lock
but it doesn't like go like you have to like you could there you can tell there's
some trick that you have to like push the door in or pull it or something while
you're in the lock but you have to go to the bathroom so bad you can't just like
hang out yeah the fucking we went to a Korean pool hall that had no door or
toilet oh you know what it was that's sick a guy who worked there sat right
next to the bathroom yeah no they had a door but the door was the door stopper
was drilled in front of the door so it would just stay so there was a door that
said bathroom but you couldn't open the door like it opened up until the door
stop it was cool I thought it was a very good design the feng shui and that oh
yeah no if you're I mean you're you know it keeps all the girls at that's true
yeah it was a serious unless the guy wants girls to come in so he can just
keep poking his head around the corner yeah being the kind of pervert where you
want to see girls going to the bathroom is so funny yeah Chuck Berry that's just
that's disgusting no he wanted to go to the bathroom on the girl you put cameras
in his bathroom in his restaurant.
- Yeah, but that's always the funny,
like you're gonna put cameras in the bathroom
so you can see them. - Why do you wanna, yeah.
- Yeah, so you can hear them farting
and see them shooting out poop.
- I mean, guys like poop and farts and piss.
- Maybe you do.
- Maybe you. - I hate pooping and--
- Why are you saying it like that?
- I hate pooping farts and pisses.
I hate that stinky crap.
- You like it, don't you?
- Nope, never seen it. - If you did--
- So I wouldn't know.
- If you did, that would really change our friendship.
if i got shit on all the time yeah if you were like the if you're like uh... like
paul giamatti and that i would i would i was on your list and stuff
i don't like i think it would cast a really negative light on the past like
three years i've known you were talk about pooping yes i thought you were
getting like a couple of times i'm not the whole time now i'm i'm so disgusted
by
who
that's a i i i don't know how to say that he is a it's a so disgusted by poop
Is that why is that not believable?
It's not believable.
The thought of poop is repulsive to me.
You're doing like DreamWorks face when you say it.
No, I'm not.
I'm not.
My God.
It's disgusting.
You're saying it like Megamind.
Stop saying it like Megamind.
I hate poop with corn in it.
Poop with corn in it.
It's bad.
What about red peppers?
There's not red peppers in poop.
You can get red pepper in poop.
Yeah, I've seen a red pepper in my poop.
Yeah, you can get red pepper.
I was looking at your shit. Actually, I look at my shit every single time. You
guys look at what you just are. Why are you guys looking at your I looked at a
shit that I took yesterday and your shit took. It was like I knew it was
really bad, but I looked at it before I wiped just to get an idea. So I would
cover it with toilet paper so that I like I get a survey of my shit and it
looked like you know when you in a port a potty, how everything just sits on the
top of the water. It was exactly like that. It was completely like rim to rim
just covering the complete toilet. Why are you burping?
What? That is really nasty. It was a heave. It was cool. It looked like there was like a
uh, look like there's a brown. You know what it was? I saw a gross video again and it's
like been it's been affecting me. What was the video? I told Cameron about it but
there's like a it was like don't make him talk it's just it's just gross.
It's not funny? Yeah. It was it's funny for the end part of it the end part of
it but most of it is just like a shock value video. Somebody like reposted
something that was like it was like a trailer for like a porno video. Uh-huh.
They're like damn what the fuck is this? Yeah like you know those videos just
come to me. Yeah. And yeah somebody. That's a one way to put it. Yeah. No it's not that.
I have. It's not. It's not the other way around. You don't come to them. It's not
like we have a friend who sends those videos to us. Yeah. But yeah it was
like there is a woman in a glory hole porta potty and there's a poop that
falls down. That's funny. It's pretty funny but the video itself because it's like it's shot like
Texas Chainsaw it looks really gross and and then the like the last shot of the
whole trailer is like a whole human head up a woman's ass. Whoa! Uh-huh. Do they do
an inside camera like no like no 27 hours I'm sure I'm sure they get an after shot
but that like literally like you imagine what that feels like for both yeah yeah
that's nice like wearing someone like a helmet do you like hold your breath you'd
have to breathe in someone's yeah there's not air in there like a reverse
snorkel that points down?
It's like having your...
Stop!
What?
A snorkel?
I'm not...
Goddamn it!
What?
Stop it!
Why are you lurching?
Why is that making me kind of...
I have such a high tolerance for stuff!
I have such a high tolerance for shit, but this is like genuinely affecting me.
It would probably be like having like...
A snorkel?
Pet, I want you to...
Pet, look at me.
I mean it'd probably just be like having like your head in a grocery bag made of pork.
Gross.
Imagine trying to take a breath in like a grocery bag, the lining of the person's asshole like
sucks up to your mouth.
Yeah, well Julie it's your fault that I'm dry heaving, so if you're listening to this,
don't ever say that.
That's the name of the woman. Yeah, at least you wouldn't be able to see
anything. That's true. You wouldn't know that you were in a person's ass. You
would not be able to see that how much people you were stuck in a balloon up in
a butt. Saw style. It's like stuck in a balloon. Yeah, it's like really, really
tight down here. It's like you look like the airheads. Did you say wake up in a
butthole sauce. You wake up and it's like yeah.
I can't hear a thing. You're saying yeah, they just die in 30
seconds. Yeah, your goal. Your only goal is get out of the
right. Okay, so you have to feed you would be the person who's
but you're inside laxatives fast enough that they poop out.
You you would probably be the person who woke up with a dead
person's head in your ass. Yeah, and then you have to eat the
you have to eat to poop them out. You have to eat a bunch of prunes. I like prunes give you
enough shitting power to poop out a human head. Yeah you might need to give yourself
any Mediterranean food. True. Yeah. Dude I leave Zatar. Hey freaking Taco Bell. Yeah. Damn. Hey
freaking Taco Bell spicy food. I eat the falafel at Zatar. Great I mean you know no disrespect to
Zatar but I eat the falafel there. It's it comes it goes in smelling the same way it comes out.
I went to Arby's the other day. Oh, jeez. So good.
Nope. The other day when I was leaving town yesterday, grab some.
It would be like being inside an Arby's sandwich.
It would feel exactly like that. Yeah, that's exactly what it would be.
Yeah. Yeah. And in a juice.
Sauces. Yeah. Yeah. Horsey sauce.
Yeah. Arby's red sauce.
Curly fries. Yep.
Fries hitting you in the eyeball.
Oh, you remember they had the curly fry vodka?
No. Arby's came out with a curly fries vodka.
What does that mean?
That's none of my god damn business.
That sounds atrociously awful.
But I think Arby's comes correct most of the time.
I think Arby's is very strong.
Yeah, no, I think everybody hates Arby's for no reason.
And just get the beef sandwiches.
The sandwiches I think are kind of gross, but I like their fries.
The fries are crazy.
The sandwiches, and I've eaten a bunch of them.
I'm not saying they're gross, like I wouldn't eat them.
I just think as fast food sandwiches go, they're not very good.
I'd rather eat something fried.
There's so much more normal than like a McDonald's hamburger.
Yeah, it does.
Yeah, they're more normal.
I don't go to a fast food place to get like a normal sandwich.
Yeah, the horsey sauce is good.
I go there and I'm like, I'm healthy.
Horsey sauce is just mayonnaise and horseradish and it's good.
Yeah, exactly.
I like horsey sauce.
Horsey sauce?
I've liked horseradish ever since I did a Passover seder one time and they gave me horseradish.
Horseradish and beets?
Yeah, and I said, I literally got up on top of the table at Passover seder.
I said these bidders are bussing. You did that like Tom Cruise with Katie Holmes. I said I
love this. I love this. I love this. It was cool. I made a sandwich the other day. I bought
a thing of horseradish and beets. Did your older brother ever tell you that Man Witch
had human meat in it? Never. I didn't eat sloppy joes until I was like 15. Speaking of
human meat I got to show you guys my new favorite video. I saw it. Did you see it?
Yeah with the human hand. Yeah did you like it? Let me pull it up. Hold up. This video is so good.
It really grossed me out. Really? The hand part really grossed me out.
It's just like a... I know but it just looks weird. We're talking about a lot of really gross videos
today. And that's what gets... but that's what gets Caleb is the is the hand. Yeah I'm sure Caleb
saw this video. I saw he... I'll watch any dookie shitting pisser vomit movie. Yeah. But I don't
like gore no it's not gore it's not it's just too much no but I don't like gore
that's not really going I hate watching hit by train pack well that's not even
gore that's like it's a firework that's nothing to me and it's not even he
doesn't even get hurt all right here's here's a video called human meat in New
York restaurant you won't believe this where is this new people here that's
right well I'm gonna hold the mic up to a computer speaker but it says it's a
woman green screened into a news studio that says Clearview TV News.
Must be in Clearview, Florida.
Probably.
Must be.
I think it's from the big monitor.
I think you need to turn it up.
It's up all the way.
All right, well, I'll just say everything she says.
- That's why we've--
- Oy!
Oy!
- There's a human hand flesh New York City.
- Well this is a bus. - See that's gross looking.
- Here, I'll pull it up on my phone,
then I'll be able to actually hold it up to the speaker.
- That's disgusting looking to me.
- No, this is normal.
- That's not normal.
- That's not a real human hand.
- I know it's not, but it grosses me out to think
that it could be. - Why does it gross you out?
- 'Cause I don't like meat.
- You like meat. - You don't like,
you like meat.
- Raw meat disgusts me.
- I saw you eat a burger.
- I like the taste of meat,
but raw meat is really gross to me.
Actually, you know what? We went to a burger place.
Here's a video.
We got a quinoa bowl.
Cannibalism.
dusty a four-star Michelin chief
we are at the top of the food chain and the only meat left to tackle was other humans
we battled long and had to be able to search them into our restaurants
our government finally conceded that we were in the right end of court
just to say that he has been fighting cannibal ordinance laws for over 10 years
people who ate it in colonial times
who's eating these people?
cannibals
who's doing all this cannibalism?
the doner party
what's that?
it's that little musical called cannibal
the musical written by Trey Clark and Matt Stone
this is the best part
I don't think I will
We have to keep meticulous records and there is a lot of paperwork someone has to fill out
before they die and before they can be eaten. We do pay handsomely for body donations though
and the money can be used for anything since funeral expenses become zero when you donate
your body to be eaten. Dossi says that there are plenty of dishes on the menu that do not include
human meat. But those leery of the process should not order at all. According to Dossi,
just like on those packages of candies with allergy warnings that say the machines also
are used to make items with nuts, our utensils are also used to cook human meat. So don't
come if you are not down with what we do.
So do not come if you are not down with what we do.
I think that's fair.
Yeah.
I don't know, like have you ever seen that picture that is like sometime during some famine some
people are like selling their kids meat?
No.
It's pretty cool.
Have you ever seen that picture and it's a...
Pretty cool photo.
It's like that baby and it's screaming and it says get to the choppa.
That is a funny, that one's funny as hell.
That one's funny as hell.
Have you seen the one that says I like waffles?
It's the same baby but he's not, he's out of his fatigues.
Yeah.
Have you seen the one where it's like good guy Greg?
And it has words on the top and the bottom.
Yeah.
Damn.
I don't think I could eat a person. I don't think I could eat any raw meat ever.
What about sushi?
I don't...
You ate sushi. I saw you eat sushi.
But those are different fun colors.
Yeah, it's true.
I just proved Caleb wrong with logic so hard.
Have you guys ever had liver?
I've been meaning to.
It's so weird tasting.
I've been meaning to eat like a...
I've been meaning to eat a giant chocolate bar.
Yeah?
made of candy. Where would you even get a face made of candy? Oh my god, you're
putting some crazy ideas in my head. I can't drop the name of the restaurant because I
don't want... I need to be able to get a reservation. That's ice cream stop. It's not
JPLix. Okay. Don't ask me to give any more information about this candy factory. I
I mean we need to do a pod trip to Hershey, Illinois.
It's Pennsylvania. Home of the ocean blue. We should just do a series where we get
to go to every candy factory in America. Okay. Yeah. We do we say that we're from
The candy tasted good. And the candy was delicious. Years later they produced a
chocolate bar that tasted delicious to me.
(laughing)
- And what do you have to say about reports
that you make one of the best candy bars in the world?
(laughing)
- Doing like, framing it as like a true crime thing.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Be like, a girl, we heard a girl went missing
at the Hershey's factory.
We'll have to taste every kiss
to make sure none of them have any flesh.
- We sat down with a fat guy to hear
what he thinks about Hershey's chocolate.
- Yeah, basically it's one of my favorite foods.
(laughing)
- Whoa, that's a long time.
(laughter)
- Interesting.
- And do you have any Hershey's with you now, sir?
- Yes.
- And could I have a bite?
- And would you consider Hershey's chocolate bars
to be brown?
- Brown.
- Mm.
(laughter)
- Very interesting indeed.
- Back to you, Caleb, with your chocolate bar.
- My name is Chocolate Hershey.
- That's good.
- That's my full name is Chocolate Hershey.
His name is Chocolate Hershey?
And he sounds like that?
Sounds like that.
Kind of sounds like post-stroke Cleveland.
What are you talking about?
Becoming Meatwad.
We sat down with Meatwad
to see if he likes chocolate.
I love chocolate.
Of course I love chocolate.
Damn, I love that shit.
We sat down with Yoda De La Ghetto.
- Yoda de la Ghetto.
(laughing)
- No, we're passing as Yoda.
- We didn't sit down.
- It's just normal Yoda.
- This just in, Yoda de la Ghetto has been shot
outside the urging factory for trying to steal all the candy.
- Why is he, no.
- To feed his family.
- He wasn't trying to steal.
- There we go.
That's what I like to hear.
- And we don't want to hear what his family would be like.
- We don't want like some kind of club style situation.
so yeah, we don't want him to dress up as every member of his family.
We don't okay and we don't want to hear and we do not absolutely definitely
one hundred percent do not want to hear about what happened on their road trip
to the Hershey's factory.
We don't want ninety minutes of that
so that can't make five million dollars at the box office and I would hate that
last and be blacklisted from why Hollywood I don't want to see there yet
are we I don't want to see it as the last movie that's the last movie I want
to see is there yet are we to know I still want to see yeah yeah I'm gonna go
to the Hershey factory though I think one day well I want to go to Hershey
Park I mean we really should just be going a bunch of different places all
the time. Yeah. Man, what if there was a way for us to go to a bunch of different places?
I can't get out of my house. The door's locked. There was a cool way for us to go to a million
different places. What are you trying to do? What are you doing? Magic carpet. Look behind
you Cameron. No shot. It's not magic. Fuck. Well, all we gotta do is find a genie. A magic
ones in the other room. Fetch. Yeah, he got mixed up. Our magic carpet. This one's
magic you can pee on it don't smell. Not all magic carpets are magic but they
fly. That's just one of them. One time. You can pee on it and I can't smell it. My
girlfriend can. One time my little brother just dropped trow in our, we had a
basement. It was like unfinished, you know, like concrete floor. One time he just
drop trout pissed on the concrete and let it dry.
- Yeah.
- You, didn't you tell me that you were putting nasty water
all over a concrete floor?
- Oh, well I was emptying the dehumidifier in there.
- Your family's obsessed with doing stuff to the floor.
- He loves sleeping on the floor.
- Yeah.
- This is all making sense.
- Did you like, did you have a traumatic experience
when you sleeped on the floor
and your brother peed on you on the floor?
- No.
- Did you have a,
- And it make you wanna sleep on the floor forever?
- I had a traumatic experience with a reclining chair.
- I bet he had like a,
I bet he had like a very young, early life sexual experience with a floor where he was like
rubbing his dick against the floor and that's why he's so attached to it.
Something outside?
There's some kind of music.
It's New York, baby.
It's the music of the street.
And we don't want to hear about Yoda's music of the street.
Ever tell you about the reclining chair incident?
I had when I was five.
Probably.
It's one of those horrible family group chat stories.
- No, I'm--
- He's like, you know what--
- You could kinda hear me and Caleb both go,
"Uh-huh, yeah, uh, uh, don't make this into--
- Is it like scary?
Okay, let me do, let me ask some questions.
Okay, does something scary happen?
- Something scary happen to me.
- Okay, does something crazy happen?
- Yeah.
- Okay, does something funny happen?
- Does it involve your family?
If you answered yes to all four of these questions,
you should not tell the story.
- Really?
- No, tell the story.
- No, tell it.
I can just sum it up. I got my head stuck in a reclining chair when I was five.
This one sounds good. I feel bad now.
How did you get your head stuck?
Okay, go. Just run it.
So I thought there was something under the chair. I thought there was like an action
figure or something. You know like the little toy guns that come with the Star Wars guys?
No, but I can imagine.
So we were always losing those, so I thought I found one. I put my head under to try and get it.
With your mouth?
With my head and my hand under. You know how it's got like that system of
you pull the lever and then the chair goes up. Yeah, they're terrifying. Yeah, so I got my head.
That's like getting caught in like a roller coaster. It's like getting caught in Big
Shane Ray. Yeah, I got my head stuck between the bars somehow. It's like getting sucked into a
lathe. Yeah, I got my head stuck in between it, couldn't get my head out, and I was stuck under
there for probably like 30 minutes trying to like call my mom to get like help, and my little brother
was jumping on the couch. So like every time he would jump, the bars would close in and out on my
like she like whoa and so you were without oxygen to your brain for an
extended period of time no I wasn't without oxygen but my mom for reduced my
mom severely reduced severely reduced oxygen or machinery hitting your head so
there might be some kind of permanent mom freak the fuck out and told me I
could have been decapitated I was like well that would be kind of probably
could have been my dad knew a guy got a decapitated yeah stuck his head out of a
a bus and a tunnel chopped his head off. Your dad did? Yeah, my dad did that and
he died. What happened to me? He just glued his head back on. He was fine.
Yeah, they just stitched it back on. I got decapitated, but my head bounced
back on, so it just stayed on. Yeah, it healed back on. There was a guy who
did, he did like, he watched like, like fucking a thousand decapitations and
just like made notes about like how much the people blinked and shit. I was like,
"That's a pretty cool job." There was a guy? What are you talking about? He's
is a scientist. What does that mean? There was a guy who watched a thousand
decapitations and took notes. He was a scientist. He was a teenager in Illinois.
He was on assignment. I don't understand the premise of this. He was like French
Revolution. He was a scientist. He wanted to study how their heads, what happens
after they- He was in the French Revolution. He was a guy- You are being
unhelpful right now. You know exactly what I'm talking about. He was a scientist
during the French Revolution. See that's what I'm saying. You introduced us by
saying there was a guy what his job is he made notes and he said that everybody he
said that everybody he would tell them like once your head gets chopped off can
you like stick your tongue out or something and then they would it was a
she and it was a lead singer of the yeah yes I don't know heads will roll
I know. I don't remember that. Yes, I do. I listened to it earlier. It's old.
It's done. Remember that one? It's over from Project X. It's done.
Your corduroys are folded. So it looks like you have a very wide boner.
Yeah. It's an episode of curb. Is it? Yeah.
It's probably one of the first or second episodes. This is your boner.
This is your episode where you have a boner. Cameron's trying to lick it.
So if it's not your boner, I'll test it with your mouth. Yeah. Don't mind.
If it's not your boner, let me just stick my hands in both your pockets and find the real
one.
I have penile excavatum.
I pushed it in.
What?
Penile excav-
Oh, because you pull it out like a sword?
If you pull it out, it's carinatum.
Did you know there was a guy who looked at 1,000 boners to see what the science was of
them?
Yeah, I believe that.
It was you.
Because I'm a good friend.
That's why I believe it.
It wasn't me.
Yeah, it was me.
That's why you perked up.
I've probably honestly through my life seen I probably yeah, I guess not a
person, but if we kind of pictures and videos, I've seen a thousand. I've
seen a lot of those probably at least
I've probably seen more than that over my whole life. That's nothing. Yeah,
nobody knew like I would be nobody knew what boners were till I came on the
years ago. A hundred fifty years ago, I might be the guy in the world who's
seen the most penises ever. That's you could probably look probably any person
in the world right now. If you sent them back, yeah, number one all time guy who
saw the most penises, they probably even know what everybody thought everybody's
penis look like theirs. They don't know about the thing is, though, if you if you
went back in time and and tried to get like a Guinness world record for that or
something, they probably just kill you. Yeah, definitely. Guinness world record
world immediately Guinness world record for like not even they wouldn't even
like ask you like they wouldn't even try to check if you really were they just
claiming to be that they would just immediately kill you.
Yeah, absolutely.
You're like, there was an entire wing of Guinness World Records that was just a honeypot for
people who had seen a lot of penises.
Also, if you are time traveling, I thought you were doing Guinness World Records for
biggest penis back in the 70s.
Because I feel like back in the 70s, biggest penis probably like...
No, that was awesome back then.
Six inches.
No, that was pre-microplastic.
World's biggest penis.
No, yeah, that was back then, the biggest one was like six feet long.
Whoa!
- We didn't have microplastics,
everybody had a huge chalk, man.
- Yeah, that was when--
- We got fucked by Teflon.
- Yeah, I know, you know what?
If Ron Jeremy, that piece of shit, had that hog.
- Ron, yeah.
Ron Jeremy would have been laughed out of the--
- He should have been rolled down a hill in a tire.
- Out of the penis club in caveman times.
- I think that should be one of the terms of his sentence.
- What should?
- Rolled down a hill in a tire.
Because it would be funny to watch--
- That freak would probably like that.
probably probably fuck the tire always rolling down that's a problem him any
punishment I'll just fuck it yeah yeah it's true lethal injection he's gonna
lethally injected into his own mouth you know you suck his own lethal injection
needle he could because it's pretty much this yeah that's that's how he got hired
in the business he always looked like shit - you ever seen like picture of him
young I've seen every single photo of him every photo ever taken around every
my video. I've seen every last one
is all sitting in my head. I think they should. I think that the CIA should
hire him as like an executioner, like how they like hire like Nazi scientists
and stuff. True. I just have them kill people. Yeah, I just have them be like
an old fat like this chop people's heads off. It'd be cool. I think that'd be
I think you do really well under like a that was a black hood. Yeah, it's like
if you're like you're about to get your head job purposely didn't say anything
Any last words?
Yeah.
You see his dick in his pants?
Yeah, oh he's so hard too.
He's hard all the time.
That scene where he gets the fuck shot out of him in Boondock Saints, pretty good.
In the whole movie, pretty good.
Boondock Saints, oh I think, wait I have my Boondock Saints shirt on.
Are you wearing it?
I think so.
Wait maybe I'm-
You're wearing it because he said that you never wear it.
No, no I wore it yesterday.
Yeah he talked about it in LA, because we were talking about how I have to get rid of so many
clothes and he said that he's like oh yeah no I never wear it it's like I would
wear that shit every fucking day and he's over here just like you dress but
you wear funny stuff on my toe it's just my slipper you like wearing really funny
shirt I don't wear a lot of really funny shirts he's a funny guy yeah yeah he
likes funny shirt it's important I it's important you're saying that to get me
to remove stuff no all your clothes are funny right now
that you have on, but keep 'em on, yeah.
- Yeah, it's important to grow out
of being a funny shirt person.
- Unless you're, I think Patrick, it works for him.
- Yeah, I think--
- 'Cause he has a funny shirt personality.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- He doesn't want me to kill myself.
- No.
- A funny shirt can come in a lot of different forms, right?
'Cause it can be like a, you know, a snorg tea type thing,
or it can be something ironic that, you know,
like, or whatever, it's not something you really like,
or whatever or it can just be something that looks like what a clown would wear
or it could
you should get a shirt. This is I'm chewed. I would do you would literally
he would pay eighty nine ninety nine for a shirt that said I'm chewed with it.
Yeah,
he would you would if I think you would probably spend like sixty dollars on a
shirt that had a picture of Mickey Mouse and said, "Chewgy normies back off."
I would pay. I mean, it depends on how old the Mickey Mouse shirt is.
It's one day old.
It's one day old, but it's listed on Depop as being 70 years old.
It's one day old, and Ben Mora put a sticker on it that says, "Chewgy life." Would you
buy it?
Maybe.
Yeah, you would.
Honestly, just to support my friend.
Yeah, that's very sweet of you. I'd probably buy it, too.
I am wearing one of Ben's shirts under this.
I am wearing the Wikipedia editor-in-chief shirt under this shirt.
So nice.
See, you like shirts.
Yeah, shirts are cool.
I only have like six shirts right now.
They suck.
Every last one of them is terrible.
You can come to my closet.
You can come take some stuff.
I would love to see.
Yeah, I sit here talking shit about funny shirts, but I just only wear just stupid band
shirts and I need to grow out of that pretty soon, I think.
When are you going to?
You don't have to grow out of it.
I just recently got out.
like in your late 20s and wear just band shirts like I think once I think I have a
few more years left of wearing band shirts and then I just have to be like
it's like an office there is a point where you have to stop caring about swag
yeah yeah I think once I'm 28 I gotta stop what's your 28 you got to stop
caring about swag yeah completely literally just have to dress like a
normal guy yeah if you try to dress cool and you're there that old like you
should know I don't know we did well no I think you just devolve it you evolve
the swag into grown man swag? Yeah, you start wearing like shoes made out of
leather and like like that's not swag that's class. Yeah, exactly.
Swag is evolved class or class. So you want to turn your
chuggy swag into normie class? Yeah. Maybe.
Patrick's gonna turn 28 and immediately start dressing like one of like a like
one of those guys that like the people always post that's like a dominator on
tumblr who's like dressed in like do you have you seen those gifts of the guy
that people who go like yeah like a belt like a like like a blue dress shirt but
a vest with it yeah exactly the worst the worst possible combination of clothes
blue shirt black vest black tie yeah yeah and they like make those tick-tock
videos are like you here now I'm gonna be your worst sexual nightmare my cum is
poisonous. They're also wearing a bowler hat. They're wearing a bowler hat and a filter that gives them fangs and red eyes.
And they're just like, it's like a... I have done a lot of thinking about this. I do think no matter what age I am or what tooth I lose, if I lose a tooth I will be getting a gold tooth.
Oh me too. Me too, absolutely. I had a silver crown when I was in the third grade. It would look so fucked up if I just like all my chipped teeth I just filled in the blank space with like just a little bit of gold.
Yeah, I'd be fine. I get a diamond in one of my teeth. Yeah, I want to get a computer in my teeth
I think I might get a tooth tattoo. I think I'm gonna get a car stuck in my mouth. Yeah, it's gonna be cool
Yeah, if you shave all your teeth down, so it looks like a Lamborghini, you know when you see a guy
The worst line of a Lamborghini like oh, that would be sick. So every time that you close your mouth, yeah
It's like you can eat Lamborghini shaped foods when your mouth is closed
Recently, I've been
I'll hold in the wall. That's my superpower. I can eat lamborghini dippers
with my mouth closed.
Sweetest lamborghinis. That's what I've been eating.
Or anything smaller than a lamborghini shaped food.
Yeah.
The reason I've been meeting too many...
Like a forked pinto bean.
I can smoke fifty cigarettes through the whole MIT.
I've been meeting too many like thirty year olds where like they look, they
dress like blady and then you ask them how old they are and they say they're
like 35. Yeah. And you're like, it's dangerous. That's man. I'm gonna, well,
they look young. They should live, they should live on an Island. If they look,
if they look super young, like if they have like a youthful,
it doesn't matter how they look. If they are that old,
that's a problem in their brain. Yeah. What's like, what is lady dress?
They could look, I mean, they could look cool. Like an elf. Dress is like,
yeah. Like a cyber elf. Like a gay, a 33 year old computer soldier.
V-Lone Soldier. I saw V-Lone Soldier at the bowling alley while I was in Wilmington.
Yeah? Yeah, and I saluted him.
It was pretty cool. Dude, the fucking...
the minute I get into V-Lone...
You need to start wearing full V-Lone, bro.
Honestly, that would be so cool. I get really into V-Lone, I get really into Antisocial Social Club.
I get really into... That would be big. What's that third one?
Revenge, the Travis Scott shoes that are just Van's old school...
Walking around with a cacti. With the lightning bolt in the side.
Uh-huh, maybe sick dude. I saw I saw never saw somebody wearing those in my life
I might have to get a v-loan shirt for the next live show. Yeah. Yeah, you got it, dude
You got to get the Travis Scott revenge. You know, those are the fucking the who's the Ian Connor?
I'm my fucking rapist guy fully v-loaned up. Yeah, I think I need it. I need to start planning a fit
Yeah, I already got my window. I think I guess don't spoil it. Oh, well, I don't care
I don't mean unless you want to what the fit I don't know what it is. Should I get is it?
- Park, tummy rocker tattoo that says doo-doo.
- That would be really sick.
- You should get, well, I mean--
- Old English, just doo-doo across the belly.
- Yeah, that would be really tight.
- That'd be cool.
- Is it Ian Conner?
I don't wanna, I said something very crazy just then.
- What?
- Ian Conner is the raper.
- Okay, all right.
All right, 'cause that name just is like--
- From Smosh, yeah.
- Yeah.
That name literally is like--
- Anybody's name.
- Yeah, I know.
That's like--
- He needs to be called--
- That's like you making up a name.
- That's like a demonious ex trying to make up names.
- Exactly.
- Yeah, it's like demonious ex coming up
with a white person's name.
- I think I'm coming up on a swag turn.
- Yeah?
- I think I'm gonna change my whole swag soon.
- I think I'm pivoting towards no swag.
- I think I might turn into a biker.
- I think Cameron might be going chewggy.
- I think I might be going zero swag.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- I feel like there's something to that.
I think I think it's going to be the next big thing. I've been where I've been
literally wearing the past two weeks. I'm wearing was so twenty four. I've been
wearing sweat pants and and and Tom and Jerry pull over sweatshirt. If you I
think I might just wear that forever. If you want full China, though full China
could be really so okay. The the China thing is so hard. It's so difficult
because they're really like what it is missing and I know I said this before is
missing the crucial element that there is no hat that I'm allowed to wear. You
wear a rice paddy bro just pop it on i did oh actually i could i did see a cool rice patty
hat i didn't buy it because it was really expensive for no reason but like a there was a hat in
chinatown there was like a red baseball cap with like a dragon golden dragon that's perfect and i
think you know you might have to do you guys want to go to chinatown i'd love to go to chinatown
yeah i just get full china fits yeah i'm gonna i'm gonna let's go like next week yeah i'll go
I'll go whenever dude. I just finished up my Covid quarantine that I definitely didn't have all along
and it was just my girlfriend that had it and I never actually had it so I didn't spread it to
anybody or give it to anyone. I completely beat it. You went to Chuck E. Cheese every day.
I spread it to thousands and thousands of people.
I've never worn these socks before. I'm sorry.
Yeah, no, go ahead. Say what you're going to say.
- No, talk about your stuff.
- No, you could get is the--
- No, what did you never see before on your stock?
- The RDS.
- Oh, and when we go to Chinatown,
we're gonna finally buy a fucking Mahjong set, okay?
- Oh yeah.
- 'Cause they have those on sale all over the place.
- No, you could get, there's this,
RDS Red Dragon Skateboards, their logo,
it's like the Red Dragon thing, but it looks like a penis.
- I'm not wearing anything that's skateboard related.
- Yeah, you, you're wearing something right now.
- What?
- Pants.
- My seed.
- What? - I nutted on him.
- You nutted?
- I nutted on him.
- You nutted on him?
- I can't be wearing anything skateboard related.
- Why not?
- Not because I don't think skateboarding is cool,
or whatever.
No, but if anybody, I can't be a person wearing
like skater stuff and then people come up to me
and start talking about skating.
- I like that.
That's like, to me that's like the best feeling
in the world, 'cause then you just go like--
- Yeah, you could get that hat, the flex hat.
- Skaters hate when you don't skate and you wear skate gear.
- Yeah, they--
It's so funny to be like, I lost it,
but I had that frog skateboarding beanie.
- Oh yeah, you lost that?
- And a couple times I was home, yeah,
I lost it while I was in Wilmington.
A couple times I was home, somebody would be like,
frog skateboarding, I'd be like,
I don't skate at all, and just smile.
(laughing)
I bet they got so mad at that.
- No, I just can't be, my nightmare is somebody--
- They think it's FUBU.
- Yeah, I just can't have people trying to talk to me
about something like that.
I don't care, I don't want it,
I don't want them to talk to me.
It is funny when like you guys, we run into like my friends who I skate with at a bar and
then you guys are trapped in the conversation with me and them.
That happened one time and me and Kim just left.
No, you guys stood there for like a couple minutes.
Yeah, and then we left while you guys kept talking.
Oh yeah, because he was like, "Oh yeah, the fucking owner of this bar did like a nolly
like a nolly wall ride at the school."
I swear to God, I thought that was the RZA for like the first 20 minutes you guys were
talking.
Really?
Yeah.
Damn.
It is funny how every skateboarder that you hang out with just looks so homeless.
Yeah.
His big ass clothes.
Big ass clothes.
I was thinking about...
Little jar that they shit.
How the Wu-Tang Clan like they form because they all love like martial arts movies or
whatever and like...
Well, but two of them love martial arts movies way more than the rest.
Well, yeah, okay.
The rest of them don't give a fuck.
Yeah, but like you know their whole thing is like oh they're all named after different
characters from martial arts movies and shit.
And think about like in like ten years like just what the next Wu-Tang Clan will be like
themed after.
I was thinking about like like like a Wu-Tang Clan that grew up like watching finger family videos and they're like, yo, that's spider-man
That's Elsa
Like sample all the like the like learning colors
with horses
Elsa give birth
But I'm trying to figure out what the next like thing when the next Wu-Tang Clan will be that was it was all the fucking
like all the the hip-hop blogs would be like odd future the next Wu-Tang and they'd be like fuck you were not the new Wu-Tang and
Then like Haji like mellow hype like had a hook in the song that said we're the new
None of them fucking figure out who was which but Wu-Tang did the right thing if they just like
Stuck together for so long odd future only lasts like five years. Yeah, it's true
Then Haji beats knocked up Nelly Furtado. Did he uh-huh do good for that fatty?
No, you're thinking of a different guy.
No, it's Jasper. He's in Jackass now.
Oh, good for that fatty.
Yeah, good for that fatty.
Haji Beats is the one...
Nelly Furtado, the promiscuous girl? She had sex?
Oh my god.
Haji Beats had that...
He had the first line of a song.
I think it's a Wu-Tang sample.
The first line of his song,
his verse was,
"Eat a cock and cum mayonnaise ham sandwich."
That's disgusting. That's a good line. Didn't Big Sean date that girl from Glee who drowned to death?
Lee Michelle? No, no, no, not Lee Michelle. What was her name? The other one.
Oh, what's her name? Cori Monteith. Cori Monteith. Yeah. Half the, like most of the cast of Glee is
dead. There's three of them. Three of them. Six or seven, yeah. The curse of Glee, man.
God's punishment. Yeah, God's punishment for being gay. For making a gay show. He struck them down
down where they stood. That show is crazy. It is. It's nuts. I never saw it until
like this year when I was watching it. It's a good time. I was just like, whoa,
like this is what people are watching? Like what the fuck is this? People loved
it. People went crazy for it. It's crazy. Yeah. I can't believe that people like
watched that show and then like, were like, like grew, like tried to like grow
up and were like, like calling people out on Twitter and stuff. Yeah, those are
the people who dominate the world now. Yeah. The glee, the glee enjoyers. People
like yeah like those are like the people who are like woke or whatever yeah it's
like you want to know it's like what the fuck yeah it's so it's also such a like
2009 idea of what a like diverse cast yeah like it's like a black wheelchair
yeah well no it's like yeah it's like gay wheelchair to black people who date
each other to Asian people who date each other like yeah yeah it's for their
they weren't willing to go to people who will soon kill themselves who did each
each other. Yeah. Wouldn't a, isn't there an episode where like a student
with down syndrome accidentally becomes a school shooter? Probably. Yeah. Yeah.
There's that show is like insane. I would not. That's like, that's just
sounds right. Yeah. It's all shit like that. It's crazy dude. I'm conflating
something or maybe it's a different show, but I think a student with down
syndrome accidentally becomes a shooter.
Accidentally?
They have a student with Down syndrome who is essentially the slave of the evil teacher.
Oh, the Jane Lynch character?
Yeah.
Why did you say slave?
Yeah, slave is a little...
I said essentially.
Okay, I guess that covers it.
Yeah, no, that's fine.
I think that passed in any lit class in America.
It's the show.
The show made him an essential slave.
Made her an essential slave.
That's my thought.
Slave-ess.
(laughing)
- Yeah dude, that show is--
- It's nasty.
- That was like the first of its kind.
- Yeah, my mom really liked Glee.
- Oh dude, my mom.
That fucking show changed my mom's idea on gay marriage.
- Oh yeah, Becky Brought a Gun to School
was the episode there.
(laughing)
- What the fuck was wrong with these people, dude?
- It's nuts.
- No, I mean, I would probably have killed myself
if I was on that show.
Would have made me completely crazy.
She brought her father's gun to school because she was afraid of being out of school after
graduating.
That's how they wrote that episode.
So she was going to keep everyone in school with a gun?
Yeah.
I mean, I guess the writers were like, "Well, it doesn't have to make sense."
It's like, who cares, right?
Yeah.
Who's the writer of that show?
What's his name?
Quentin Tarantino?
Yeah, well, Tarantino's the director for it.
Quentin Tarantino's the guy who does American Horror Story.
Oh, really?
What?
yeah also fucking crazy yeah no it's the what's his name? I forgot his name. That show sucks shit.
What's his fucking name? I don't remember his name but yeah I know that's yeah Ryan Murphy yeah that's
the same. He did both of those? That's why they're both like that that's why the same people like
them. That show's that show also is dog shit. That show is committing me so mad. Sarah Paulson's
married to the mom from Two and a Half Men. I don't know who either of those people are. Sarah
Paulson's the lady from American Horror Story. In fact Connie Brittney was American Horror Story. And
who else is in it the people versus OJ she plays the lawyer thing that pisses me
off most of an American horror story is people try to pull the shit where they're
like well yeah it sucks now but the first season was actually good yeah turn the
first episode is like this is the worst thing I've ever seen in my life I think
it's like it was in a season it's like a ghost story haunted house with like
everything in it yeah because it has to be 21 episodes yeah every episode it's
like there's a there's a dead girl in the well yeah there's a there's a ghost
Is it Ryan Murphy? I thought the person who did American Horror Story also did Nip/Tuck.
Might have done all three.
I mean there's probably multiple people who work on TV shows.
Who did The Office?
That was Michael Schur.
That's funny.
Yeah, that's Michael Schott.
They have the, on Peacock, I learned on my mom's birthday.
They have the superfan versions of The Office.
They have the superfan versions.
Your mom learned about my peacock on her birthday.
Yep.
Alright, episode over.
No! No!