You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
(laughing)
(explosion)
Of course.
Wee, wee, wee.
I still got food in my mouth.
(singing)
In high school.
We're gonna get DMCA'd for that, Patrick.
In high school, I--
My voice is so beautiful.
It sounds too much like a woman named Mrs. Officer.
It's too perfect.
It's too spot on.
In high school, we got pulled over by a lady cop
and just blasted that song, dude.
We thought it was so fucking funny, too.
We got pulled over, and she gave my friend
a $250 speeding ticket, and we were like,
we're owning you right now by playing a girl cop song.
Wee, wee.
- You probably made her day, dude.
- That was the thing, she was really hot,
and that was why we started, if she had been like,
just an ugly, normal girl cop.
if she had been like an ugly if she had been like a Miss Trunchbull you would
have gone to jail for playing that song.
No but I got pulled over by Riley Reid and I started fucking
just blasting.
Whoa.
Yeah I don't think she was a real cop yeah she was in a golf cart.
That's what you get for driving on a golf course.
I guess you're right.
And yeah we just just blasted you know three or four times Mrs. Officer.
Damn.
You were pulled over for that long that.
Yeah dude she's got a process on the papers. She wanted to hear the end of the song.
Yeah she was like "ah" She thought it was all, she thought it was just a long song that repeated a lot.
This is a song that we wrote for you ma'am. Yeah right as the as the song is ending you
see her like start to get out of her cruiser and then it starts again she gets back in.
She just drives away so slowly. But yeah I respect women cops that are beautiful.
Yes!
Man, I had grocery store sushi.
Yum.
I don't know if that's a great idea.
Paws.
What?
Don't paws.
Paws.
You just got paws, dude.
There's nothing you can do.
Oh, no.
Speaking of paws, I'm neg.
I'm not.
I still do not have.
Say that one more time.
Neg.
I still do not have.
Okay, you say, your fucking southern accent, you're threading the needle with that fucking
word.
needle means doing it right and doing it perfectly.
That's what somebody says when you do something awesome.
- You're walking a tightrope.
I'm sorry, I got my idioms.
- You're walking on a needle.
- You're walking a tightrope.
- You're walking, you're jumping on a needle
when you say that.
- You're walking the camel through a needle's eye
when you do that.
- Yeah, which is like insanely impressive
and I'm doing it really well.
- You're like a camel on a string
when you say stuff like that.
- You're like two camels in a blanket right now
with the way you're acting.
- Imagine a needle that could go through two camels at once.
That's what you're like when you say,
when you're using that word.
US military should invest in a weapon like that. A weapon that can go through two camels.
I'm sure they've had that problem. I'm sure a lot of their weapons can do that. No way.
ISIS knows to barricade everything with two camels. One camel, a full metal jacket bullet
will just rip through a camel. ISIS is the number one problem in the world I would say.
doing everything they keep their D dossing all your favorite video games
they're no yeah dude they're the reason why highball energy is sold out in
various locations that's not true that's not true
no I mentioned highball in the podcast they blew up I don't think they blew up
dude I don't think you have that kind of that kind of pushed all the cans to the
back of the shelf and took a picture no I didn't I did I walked into this no no
No, no, no, no.
That's not what happened.
He knocks over, he swings his arms around and knocks over the entire display.
He just knocks all the shelves off the wall.
Yo, I'm an influencer.
They look sold out because of me.
Yo.
No, but if, I think, I'm going to blame that on that guy I met on the train that said he
knew Caleb.
Oh yeah.
If you're listening, was it Brian?
If you bought all the high ball, if you bought all the high ball, that was my doing.
was mad disrespectful mm-hmm cuz now Pat doesn't have any idea I'm thinking I'm
gonna get a wild berry I couldn't drink grapefruit my favorite flavor that's
unlucky I'm thinking I gotta get like some kind of some kind of sponsorship
deal with Red Thunder maybe change my name to Ted Runder and Ted Runder Ted
Runder with the Red Thunder why not oh said fed is not a name run dad dad
sad runder with that red thunder red red under bad under how about Brad
bread ginger bread ginger bread ginger bread ginger bread ginger with bread
- The red finger. - In my house.
- Red ginger bought a whole house.
- What?
(laughing)
- I'm rapping now.
- Red ginger bought a whole house,
something, something, something.
- I saw a whole mouse.
- In my house. - Shit.
- Dude, I would love to go to one of those
really serious Detroit ciphers that they put up on,
what's that thing, Don't Flop or whatever?
like one of those videos of all those people rapping and yeah just do the like
man you suck some some some some some you fuck some some some some some weirdo
- Hair do, fuckin' something.
- Yabba dabba doo, yabba dabba doo.
- Dibba dee dee dee.
- Something, something, something, man, fuck you.
- You suck, you suck me.
- You suck me, suck you, something.
- I suck you, you suck me.
(laughing)
- But yeah, dude, I need to get,
they need to put me in the Cypher like so soon, dude.
- Yeah, Detroit, yeah.
- I've been ready.
- If I end up.
- I've been sending out applications.
- If I was in a Cypher like that,
I would say the whole,
would wrap all of that logic song about the suicide hotline and I'd say I hope
you don't do any of that yeah reverse yeah the crowd would go wild at that
punchline once they realized that the whole the whole thing was supposed to be
opposite hell I just wrapped the alphabet hell I mean if I was one of
them rappers up there I might just do the alphabet man I just say Mary had a little lamb
they wouldn't be able to tell the difference yeah man I mean I'd probably
just be up there fucking wrap my address or some I might get it I'll be singing
about my black sheep I'd be singing that I'll be singing fuck in I mean that my
yes sir yes sir three bags full my I mean come on my phone number rhymes
there's a nine and at the beginning and the end I could say half my phone number
and then the other half is the second the first half my phone number is nine one
six two three seven I mean fuck my phone number is not four four three nine my
name's dead Runder I mean my name my name's clay ray that's kind of a rhyme
right there that's my name's a damn rap clay ray Runder clay ray clay ray Runder
that's right up next we got clay man with the red
under you know I play Ray Runder versus evil Steve oh I just realized something I
think I could probably rhyme a cat with a bat if I could figure out a way to put
them in a sentence you know there's a lot of rhymes if you pick up a thesaurus you
know a lot of fucking rhyming words in the thesaurus did you ever have a
rhyming dictionary dude no talk about a rapper's a delight
- Rhyming dictionary.
- Isn't that just a thesaurus?
- No.
- No, what are you, what?
- What are you talking about?
- A thesaurus is--
- Oh, no, no, no, no, that's synonyms, god damn it.
- Oh my god, dude.
So put the podcast on stop mode.
You know, we need to give this kid a lesson.
I'm gonna sit you down, I'm gonna put you on my lap,
I'm gonna take your pants off, lesson number one.
- No, I don't like this lesson.
- What the hell?
- You're not supposed to like lessons.
- Yeah, dude, learning's hard.
(laughing)
What are you talking about?
Take your pants off, show me your butt cheeks.
*laughter*
No.
Come on!
Give me those butt cheeks!
I gotta teach you a lesson right now.
You're not making my behind red.
I'm your teacher and I'm gonna fucking-
I'm gonna make it blue.
I'm gonna put rubber bands around your waist and both your legs.
I'm gonna give you big, brown, bubbly butt cheeks.
*laughter*
And that's it.
It is crazy-
Pour an acid on your face.
It is crazy that like most of our parents did probably get like the shit kicked out of them by a teacher.
I don't think they got the shit kicked out of them.
I don't think they got like jumped in the hallway by the teacher.
I think they did.
I think it's exactly what happened.
Yo, what class you from?
What fucking class you from?
What's your home room?
Yeah.
You think you can get in this hallway?
206?
It's so funny too.
You're in the 400s, motherfucker.
It's 400 block.
It's so funny that it was nuns doing it too.
I know.
A bunch of people.
Well, nuns are the most evil way to moan, dude.
I know.
It's so funny how evil they are.
Dude, New England's a horrible place.
Yeah, nuns beat the shit out of kids and then priests fucking touch the kids.
It's like, what is going on?
What is going on there?
I mean, that's what happens when you fucking...
A nun is literally just like a witch.
Like it's...
It's just a woman who's exiled from society with only one working eye.
It's a witch with a salary.
Exactly.
It's one of the most fucked up fucking things ever. It's nuns. Yeah. And they never do anything
good dude. No. Nuns have never done anything good. I've never heard any good like stories
about nuns from like my parents. Exactly. Yeah. The only good story about a nun from
a parent is when your parent says, when your dad is like, "Oh man, you gotta hear the story
about this time that I humiliated the nun in front of the whole class." Or like, "Oh
yeah, I got away with it. She didn't hit me." Like shit like that. Yeah, we pranked her
so hard she had to go home for a week all the cool nuns get like murdered by the
church yeah they like smoke a cigarette. Mother Teresa got murdered yeah
she got fucking killed with rice in it 102 years old somebody put her on the
tip of an umbrella and pricked her in the knee. Didn't um what did they fucking
somebody was like saying that she was a eugenicist mother Teresa she was a
eugenicist that bitch was smart as hell she was she was so smart yeah no I don't
think she was I mean I think she was just like one of these people one of
these like religious people doesn't believe in like medicine I think she was
highly intelligent I think she was insanely smart dude yeah no I heard I
just like one of those like things where it's like somebody's trying to like
cancel like an old like figure like that's like a comm shit yeah it's like
uh did you know that mother Teresa actually said fuck you once yeah I'm
like that no that would actually be cool dude yeah
but there's Teresa smoked a cigarette flip me off she's a bad boy man she had a
leather nun outfit on yeah she walked around what's it called a back patch on
her habit for suicidal tendencies. Yeah dude. Yeah she's saying a prayer for Mike who just
wanted a Pepsi and institutionalized. That's... Yeah she's actually really cool. Did you see
Teresa at the municipal waste show? That was nuts. She was crowd killing dude. She was
fucking two stepping her right foot. She was crowd killing by not giving them medicine.
Yeah. Just letting them die of the flu. Yeah much respect to Mother Teresa. She was just
Like two stepping around the pit and just cursing people at the edge just putting just removing blessings from them. Yeah, I heard in 2013
I heard in 2013 when black flag was playing in australia mother teresa stormed the stage and said that the uh, the lead singer
Uh was done and she took over right there on the spot. Yeah, dude mother teresa bit the head off of a crow on stage
Yeah, spit the head in the crowd. Yeah. Yeah. She was a she was a bad bitch
I think. It's funny that the Black Flag, have you ever like seen their 2013 album cover for their
album What The? No. Oh man. Is it good? I think it was designed by the lead singer at the time.
The best, oh yeah, now I know this one. Yeah. It's so fucking bad.
It's a Blink-182 cover. Right.
No, like Greg Gin used to make like all the album covers. It used to be so fucking sick. And then
in 2013 they were like he's like yeah you know I want to make like the South Park
goo guy it's so funny to go from like police story to that right yeah like
slip it in looks like the Teresa mother Teresa was actually the person on the
cover for slip it in it looks like they like the just for laughs guy yeah
black flag cover wait but what if he's sick yeah not all around gonna throw up
up yeah that'll actually tight as fuck yeah the the splatter behind him that the
guy the artist just sneezed on the paper before he drew the guy yeah that wasn't
the illest possible things you can do that's like so punk rock to be sick mm-hmm
which again I'm not I'm still surviving over here still like no way I wasn't
great I serve Raymond Pettibone when I searched black Raymond petta what Raymond
Pettibone is the guy who makes all the black.
- Pettibone?
- Pettibone.
- What a horrible fucking witness protection name that is.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, being named Raymond's bad enough.
When I search black flag, what the,
in the like third row of results,
there's just a Blue Lives Matter flag.
(laughing)
- I was wondering, I was thinking about witness protection.
I was thinking.
- Like, think about getting into it.
if you if you pick if you can pick your own name do you think there's like 700
guys in Florida who used to be in the mafia who who named themselves Tony
Soprano? They just live in like Florida and Arizona? They're like yeah dude that'd be a really cool name.
They all live in like like opposite like neighborhoods that are like pretty close to each other.
Yeah 65 guys named Tony Soprano and Paul Simon. I think we found that
guy squealed he changed his name to Jeremy Innocent. And their mail keeps getting mixed
up but they're all ordering the same shit. Yeah. Oh I fucking, hold on this is addressed
to Tony Soprano but this is a track suit in a different color what the fuck. Maybe they
just got it wrong. It's 15 sizes too big it's supposed to be a triple XL. Man I don't know
- I don't know about that new guy that just moved in.
He seems like he maybe has a dark past.
Oh, what are you talking about?
You mean Michael Normal, I'm sure?
- What, you mean Michael Jackson?
What are you, he's got like,
he's like the most normal guy ever.
800 pound fucking Italian guy.
He says he's from, he says he's from California.
He has that California accent, you can tell.
- That classic, yeah.
Hey, how you fucker doing?
I'm fucking--
- I'm from fucking Long Beach.
- Yeah, I'm from fucking California.
- Yeah, man, I can tell.
- Yeah, surf's up.
- Sorry you have such a beautiful tan.
tan so you have that olive skin yeah so that's surfing yeah where's a where's the
best fuck it where's the best beaches around here I'm trying to forget try to
surf where would you go if you were on if you if you got witness protected I
would stay in the same place because they would never expect they would literally
never think that right yeah I would just change my name I would change my name to
Cameron better and I would everything else the same live in the same place I
I don't know who you're talking about. I do think the best thing you could do is
probably stay in the same place and then if they if anybody ever sees you claim
you were that person's identical twin who has nothing to do with their life.
Because then like like that is such a stupid premise that they would they
would believe it because like why would the government let you do that? You know?
You're just like oh no that guy who is ratted on everybody? That should just be the
default thing. That should just be what witness protection is. Yeah or actually
you know I like art listen you're your twin from I get that a lot actually that
I look like that guy have you ever heard of a doppelganger I think I might be his
doppelganger yeah I actually are that or our father donated a bunch of sperms yeah
yeah it's one of those it's a Vince Vaughn movie situation and then my mom
- My mom also donated a lot of different sperm
and they mixed the two sperms and they got it.
Like a million clones or something.
- You guys have me totally, totally mixed up.
I'm his clone.
They made me in a lab.
I'm completely--
- No, you don't get it.
I'm actually his biggest fan and I got plastic surgery
to look exactly like him.
And then he just disappeared, so I'm just doing my thing.
- It's a Vince Vaughn situation,
so I gotta go to a dodgeball tournament real quick.
I'm sorry to keep you, please don't keep me waiting.
I gotta go to this dodgeball tournament to save my gym.
- Yeah, I'm doing all of the Vince Vaughn movies right now.
- Hold on, I gotta go, there's a wedding down the street
I gotta go to, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I can't talk anymore.
(laughing)
Look, I'd love to stay and chat,
but I'm actually a 40 year old intern at Google.
(laughing)
- Yeah, no, sorry guys, I heard there's actually,
there's like something going on in cell block 99
that I have to kinda go and figure out.
- My brother's Santa Claus.
(laughter)
No, you guys can totally meet him, if you don't kill me.
You can totally meet my brother Santa Claus.
(laughter)
He and he will, if you're nice, get you a present.
So, killing me put you on naughty list automatically.
(laughter)
- Yeah, I think everybody always goes to like,
claims they would go to like Alaska or something, but.
- I would, are you kidding me?
I wouldn't do that.
fucking then what do you what if the you get in bad with the Bears all of a sudden
you're moving back to the store mafia yeah dude yeah what's a bear what if the
Bears think your smell is crazy you get fucking run out of Alaska you're running
out of options dude go to Arizona what if you piss off a cactus you know oh man
you're not drinking water for weeks hell no yeah no more tequila mm-hmm I would
move to the if I was in witness protection I would move to the same town
is Doug Stanhope and I would befriend Doug Stanhope. Awesome, nice. The town in Arizona that he lives in.
The one that has his like brain-dead wife? Yeah. Then you would just, you'd become his best friend?
I would befriend him and then I would get immediately killed because I would...
You'd have one like coarse salt piece of cocaine and just immediately die?
Yeah. I think, I said I would stay in the same place but I'm thinking now I think I might end
end up going to space when I get in witness protection.
Yeah, I'd like to go to Disneyland.
No I'm thinking I'm going to go to space and still just live a normal life, like get a
new identity.
So I'll have a house up on the space station, like the only guy with a house with a picket
fence and just live a normal life while everyone else is doing astronaut stuff.
Like little house just sitting on top of the ISS.
Exactly, yeah.
That's not a bad idea.
I think it'd be nice and quaint.
But yeah, Disneyland's cool too, but nowhere near as cool as space.
could mow your astro turf.
- Y'all mow your ass.
- That's the only joke I thought of for that.
- Mow your astro turf, that's what you got.
- Yeah. - Come on, man.
- I would just yell at the ISS workers constantly
for being too loud.
- Yeah.
- What is Amazon paying you for?
- Yeah, fucking get to work.
- Can you guys play Pac-Man with Rice Krispies
like a little quieter in there, please?
- You know, it's funny that it's one letter off from ISIS.
What are you guys doing in there?
(laughing)
guys hiding in plain sight? Clearly they look exactly like ISIS. Nothing! We're doing nothing!
We're being very normal in here. We're doing science. Obviously. Yeah, you look and it's
like they have like a laser beam that's beheading like a crash test dummy. Trying to get the
most efficient hey man are you a journalist by the way
you like a crash test dummy that looks like you
like a tattlet stabbing a model of you over and over you can't say anything
because he looked into his window right you shouldn't have okay it's like it's
like a rear window situation like you tore the like a Honda like safety
facility and all the crash test like attack of the clones like a pre-programmed
Scream every time I get an accident sounds just like
What is that why are they crying before they crash? Oh, we have to see if the crash would make him cry
Why do you keep backing the car up and crashing again?
Dummies watching gay porn on the vehicle screen. It's supposed to be accurate simulation real life
Yeah, if you if you were you would obviously be distracted if gay porn showed up on your your display
I'm
Do you guys be she eclipse
Do you guys really have to test for the car like the cars for what would happen if a crazy guy was in the passenger seat?
And stabbing the dummy to death. I don't think that that
Scientist walks out of the bathroom with a crash dummy zipping his pants up
Come on man, that's me
What the fuck? How come you made them so short? Why do they all have giant holes in the mouth?
What the fuck is wrong with Honda, dude? Fuck you.
Yeah. Yeah. I do think it's funny also just imagine
the people who crash test cars being scientists also.
Yeah. They're just like guys.
Well, they are, right? They're not scientists, dude.
Well, there's got to be one scientist. No, they're you what do you see you you they're the fucking mythbusters, dude
They're not scientists. They're probably monsters are scientists special-effects people. That's a science. That's not a science. It's an art
Art is science. Sometimes Wow, they wear lab coats and TV commercials. So they're scientists. That's the final word
Yeah, if you're wearing a lab coat, you're a scientist or a doctor
Doctors are scientists. What if you're a good sure? Yeah
White Dracula yeah, the white the Gandalf. That's not a lab coat. That's a cape. Yeah, it's true
I'm gonna tell me what the difference is one's a cape one's a coat. It's pretty fucking obvious
Yeah, one's velour ones like cotton. What about a cat and the cowl - yeah a lab now
That's a lab coat with a bad idea. Yeah a lab pretty cool. That's a really good idea a lab cape. Yeah
You could have like like a brooch of like a mystical brooch on it
maybe. Also why do scientists and chefs dress so similar? Shouldn't a scientist
be in like a hazmat suit all the time? Aren't you doing weird shit? Chef is like a food
scientist if you think about it. There are food labs in Boston. Jake Kenji
Lopez Alt. Mm-hmm. Supreme food scientist. That's true. He's always teaching me how
to drink and cook at the same time. Make mayonnaise. I love those videos of him
when he's just clearly an alcoholic. He's like a chef.
of course. Yeah he's just like chugging, chugging fucking like bourbon as he makes a quesadilla
at three in the morning and trying to like not wake up his family and then the videos are
everybody's like wow this guy's a genius he makes eggs and cheese. Oh yeah dude every scientist
every like most chefs are just like I'm sure I'm sure Anthony Bourdain has like skewed my
my perception of chefs. He was sober. He was straight edge famously. No chefs are...
no of course but he's a fucking what
degenerative drug addict
I know
it's not just Anthony Bourdain
the chefs are like that
oh yeah there's so many chefs that just fucking
there's so many chefs
too many chefs, too many cooks
I think chef is one of the most
I don't know what it is
chef is your favorite movie
it is one of my favorite
if I had to watch
like if there was a
death row last movie it would be chef. Alex was telling me the other day about like a
time like the first time that you saw it you went to a ccc meeting and you were like you guys i
saw the best movie last night. I love it. I love chef. Dude I fucking love chef. Oh no me too.
Unapologetically. Me too. Any story that anybody, I don't remember that. I'm not gonna deny it. I'm
I'm sure I fucking did. I'm sure I told everybody. I'm sure that I was I was talking about it at work.
It's the best movie. Oh, it's so good. It's so fucking awesome, dude. Jon Favreau.
It's just a movie about nothing. It's just a movie about like the coolest...
It's about a chef!
It's a movie about just like a cool guy. Like there's nothing, there's no stakes at all in that movie.
Fucking fat guy, fucking tens, and then he fucks an 11 at the end.
Mm-hmm. And then he fucking best friend John Leguizamo.
Dude, if my best friend was the pest and I can make a Cubano,
It is my life. I'd be the light. He's also making white what he chose Cubano's as like the thing that he makes
Yeah, like Jon Favreau making Cubano's for an hour and a half fucking Scarlett Johansson and the mom for modern family and the pasta
Pasta g l'olio make chef - I
Need you to chef in space
Chef chef anywhere dude. Do he get hired by SpaceX? I don't care if the second movie
I don't care let's let's fucking let's work this out don't suffer let's
franchise it I think - I think - too early for space I think okay yeah space
yeah that's a good chef - back to Civil War era he's making like hard tack I
still making Cubano's dude nobody knows what it is yeah yeah he's made he's
using fucking discarded legs as the pork. Yeah, oh man the letters he would
write to Sofia Vergara. Oh my god. I want to see those. I want to see the
drawings that she sends back actually. I'm more interested in that. He still has
his fucking little annoying kid. Yeah, his kid who plays TF2 on his iPad. And then get
this right the third one chef three colon three chefs. There's three of them this
time when he went back in time when he went back forward in time there was a
glitch and three of them was created like it's like the movie duplicity mm-hmm
where it's like there's a there's like a smart there's like the normal guy and
then there's like a kind of evil one and you can't leave the one lady do chef
slitty chef's that's what we'll call it chef chef's lady I thought was chef
three three chefs I like that okay okay chef three too many cooks chef three two
one show yeah okay chef three two one yeah three two one black chef three two
one blast off yeah and then chef four is when they fuck in and then they have
Jed Leguizamo is the-
- Jed Leguizamo, John's brother.
- Jed Leguizamo, yeah, and he's playing,
he's doing Sid the Sloth as the captain.
He's like, "Ready for takeoff, chef."
- He's an alien.
He's an alien who looks exactly like Sid the Sloth.
- That's a genius move.
- Okay, then the fourth one is the clones.
- Chef Four, four chefs.
- Four chefs only.
The gimmick is you can only buy a ticket to the movie
if you're a chef.
- Yep.
- Four chefs.
- Oh, it's like the drummers only.
- Just imagine-
- It's like a double meaning.
There's four chefs in the movie and four chefs in the theater.
Imagine that the, so if we're going like with duplicity rules for cloning,
Duchesslity.
And the dumb chef,
the food he would make.
Sandwich.
That's a very... Peanut butter and jelly. There's a lot of, there's a lot of
funny things that we could do with that dumb chef. Water.
Cereal with water. He makes like a,
like an Uncrustable with like salsa in it.
But so wait the original Jon Favreau chef is in the movie right? Yes he's cloned four times.
So are the clones... Three times. Wait yeah hold on hold on hold on. Is he cloned three times?
He's cloned three times there's four chefs. So it's him and then three clones. He's cloned four times
and that and every time that he gets cloned it removes a little bit of his cooking ability so
he has to hunt down the clones and kill them to get the cooking he to become a chef again.
it's a horror movie dude and then the fourth chef the dumb chef is now it's
action it's action last house on the shelf it's action comedy okay okay all
right I'll tell it's a crossover with Barry I'm still Barry involved because
it's I don't know action comedy is that show an action comedy I never saw what
about it's a crossover with funny John wick the movie that I've been writing
for a while. Okay, you mean Nobody with Bob Odenkirk? No, this is Funny John Wick. That's exactly what
that movie is. No, mine's like a stoner comedy. It's still John Wick. Seth Rogen's in it and he's
like, "Ugh, John, you should smoke weed." And John's like, "Will this make me cooler?" And he's like,
"Ugh, you know." Oh yeah, no, he smokes weed and he goes into bullet time. Yeah, oh actually,
how about this? Seth Rogen and John Wick trying to buy alcohol. They're trying to get a fake ID.
and they're 26 yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
they're de-aged to look five years old yep yeah they have to buy booze yeah
this is already but they had he's still it's funny John wick has all of his
powers still of his assassin ability yeah powers yes he does he does in this
one is up his powers a fucking gun okay yeah okay he smokes weed and it gives
him a power uh-huh splatter you're right bullet time yeah yeah now he is neo uh-
huh all of a sudden you know what if John wick was in the matrix he was the
John wick tricks what no fancy John wick tricks John wick John day tricks
fan theory John wick took place in the matrix if you think about it yep no way
you could be that good at assassinating. Exactly, because the actors are all the
same. Every actor is in each movie. Both. All right, let's just circle. Caleb, can
you explain what Funny John Wick? I told you, dude. Opening shot. Seth
Rogen. Can you read some of Funny John Wick? All right. Interior. Seth Rogen's
apartment. Night. Seth Rogen lights up a fire bowl, right? Or a bong. Or actually,
know what it's a dab rig you can rewrite it as much as yeah well no this is all
in the script mm-hmm he goes to hit it there's a knock on the door who's that
he gets up he walks over the door looks into the peephole nobody's there wait
things are getting kind of weird and funny John wick hold on who's behind him
John wick it's not funny yet but he's about to be he goes to slit Seth Rogan's
throat Seth Rogen goes no dude I fuck I don't fucking die and John Wick says
give me give me one reason why I shouldn't kill your junky ass and Seth
Rogen says how about this dude puts a joint in his mouth lights it John Wick
starts getting high as a hell all of a sudden cut to 30 minutes later they're
watching Paul they're fucking laughing their ass off on his couch John Wick
gives up being an assassin and the rest of the movie is pretty much chef we could
do that if that could be the chef prequel in our in the franchise uh-huh big
restaurant that's how he gets like his restaurant of the crowd it's all that
money yeah Charlie has that nice house in the movie dude he's funny
really is a briefcase of pirate coins - yeah true true the Assassin League
assassin the assassins families favorite money doubloons silly bucks
Fan theory John wick was a pirate he was why does he have all these damn doubloons
it's a really good point me yeah yeah anyway that's pretty much my movie some
fan theories are just lucky genius when you think about them some fan theories
just click and make sense you know it's funny it's funny how many fan theories
ruined big franchises like like Star Wars for sure got ruined by every like fan
theory channel that exists I think there was Disney oh no yeah obviously but like
every like anybody doesn't want to hear anything about Star Wars by the way just
skip yeah okay so probably the goodbyes give one extra give one other franchise
that's been ruined by fan theories we should just play like you know you
played me up people play music and podcasts like during the ad so you can
just 15 second forward until you skip past it we just play the Star Wars
theme anytime Matt talks about Star Wars so people just skip until it's over. Not really
dude come on I know you love it. I just don't think there's another I don't think he had
any I think he just wanted to talk about Star Wars I don't think there's another movie that
you could say that about. No there well Indiana Jones. So go ahead. I've been saying it for so long.
I'm thinking of one right now but I read somewhere that. I know you only had Star Wars in your head
right yeah I I read somewhere that like some producer said like like some of the
things that they were thinking of while they were like fans figured it out and
then they had to like rewrite it that happened at last right I think so that's
what I'm thinking of you should talk about lost instead why the fuck would I
ever talk about law this is not Star Wars did loss is awesome I never watched lost
well lost and Star Wars were both directed by JJ Abrams so you just had a
nerd voice checkmate JJ Abrams JJ Abrams that's exactly how you sounded when you
said that yeah well the two pieces of cinema actually share a common
director sound a bit like you sound a bit like a fool when you bring that up
you know you sound like what a jock and awesome fucking badass who comes up with
cool stoner comedy guy drinking on a John wick I'm not drinking water drinking
red thunder shut the fuck up oh that's facts I should have said something
and better I wouldn't have been able to defend himself because he had water in his mouth.
Then you could also do like Ghost of Christmas Wick or Ghost of Girlfriend's Wick.
Ghost of Girlfriend's Wick.
So this is like so the franchises are together it's all one franchise.
Well okay so John Wick 3.
Chef and John Wick.
John Wick 3 was pretty cool right?
Yeah.
But you're also like is this all this fucking guy can do is kill people all day because of
some fucking dog or whatever.
Well can't he do parkour too?
Well that's a that's a type of killing people.
that would have to be more of a web series because they have like cool YouTube
videos of John Wick doing parkour you know but I want to see I want to see him
branch out because John Wick what a talent once in a generation you know and
I want to see him do fucking rom-com and I want to see him do a bunch of cool
shit not Keanu Reeves John Wick yeah what if John Wick had an excellent adventure
how about that's a really good see John Wick should have popped up in that movie
in the new reboot mm-hmm well I haven't seen it so he could like you could have
killed Hitler dude that's probably what he would have done cuz he's such a good
oh dude a time-traveling John wick dude John wick Valkyrie let's go dude that's
perfect cuz we already have the time travels already established in the chef
franchise yep that's so very good point John and John wick is Fabro yep so it
all works out John wick fucking Mario movie fucking John wick and Nintendo land
John wick adult swim tsunami show oh all right sign me up by what's that fucking
mr. I jack or my jack no by the guy does a boondocking voices same kind of humor
okay yeah no the guy it's Jandy Tartovsky right
Tartakovsky a dirty dirty dirty dirty dirty dirty dirty dirty dirty dirty
John wick oh yeah that guy sounds Irish yeah dirty dirty dirty dirty
picture this honestly picture this sounds like a pirate a lot of these have been me
fucking around mm-hmm John wick as Captain Jack Sparrow
yo come on dude that's what they need to bring the franchise back give wait John
do John wick assassins creed movies what this is the coolest thing I've ever
- No, that's not good.
- What did you come up with?
- That's a bad one.
- I just got a frisson.
(laughing)
- A what?
- A frisson.
(laughing)
- What the fuck are you saying?
- That's French for you come in your brain.
- You know when a girl whispers in your ear?
- No, I don't know that.
- And you go, yeah!
- And you go, ugh!
- That is disgusting!
(laughing)
- A frisson?
- That's a frisson.
- You smell like flowers!
- Like a bichon freeze?
- No, a frisson is what you get when you listen to ASMR
shit yeah that's French it's French for a gay shiver yeah okay yeah so I'm getting
I'm getting one of these thinking about all these John wick possibilities John
wick extended universe I'm thinking about me Sean freeze no you're a bitch
on phrase bitch on freezing let me back inside yeah mm-hmm
anyway I'm sorry I didn't mean to derail everything with this whole funny John
Wick thing but you know you did I did kind of railed the whole thing I'm sorry
derailed the entire episode having some genius ideas and being yeah and nobody
on this podcast has ever derailed the whole episode yeah this is something
that's right that they thought of doing a fucking 25 minute video essay about
wado on the podcast mm-hmm you should start doing video essays yeah you should
where I don't know how to do it at all and the whole thing is just me being
like and then the fucking uh just remembering names for some reason you're talking about
like 70s classic rock at some point yeah just because and you know and you know plo kun he's
kind of like a fucking uh what's that fucking that uh it's not yeah not editing at all doing
doing the thing that youtubers do where they like jump cut in the middle of a sentence because they
like paused for half a second but just doing just doing it just in between just going like
"Oh, fuck, what is-" and then cut. "Oh, man, fuck, what was it called?" Just doing this,
cutting to you being confused over and over again.
When did people - when did like every YouTube video become two hours long?
It sucks, dude. It's so evil.
It's fucking crazy. I've been stuck inside watching videos, watching like - I'll click
on a video and be like, "Oh, that's interesting." Like something so stupid about like half-life,
and then I'll look and it's fucking three hours long.
yeah it's cuz of like YouTube only like pays you for the ad monetization if it's
a certain length or something that makes sense because anytime there's one of
those it's gonna be like but before we talk about that we're gonna need to talk
about the advent of electricity exactly talk about how video games happened and
then they'll talk about half-life in the last it'll be it's always it's always a
13 minute video and the first 10 minutes is just them like just clips from the
other videos on their channel oh man what I don't want to bring up Star Wars again
but like every like do yeah no cuz every fucking like Star Wars like I hate to
bring up right now I hate it now for me because I know you guys are just gonna
make fun of me what what I'm saying is like every Star Wars video at a certain
point where it's like a lore explained there's like one guy on you think I
think it's like Star Wars theory or like lore explained or some shit like that
that and he will make like a video where it's like 10 minutes long and then at a
certain point you can tell that he's just repeating himself so he's just like
Caleb do you want to start like a second call? Yeah dude that'd be fucking awesome.
Patrick I have a special tip for you okay when you start something off and you say
oh I don't want to talk about this you can just not say it yeah there's a life
hack for you it was pertinent to the conversation and I wanted to I don't
No.
Fuck off.
[Laughter]
Just tell me, is Padme secretly evil? Yes or no?
No.
Why does she have a clone of her?
Yeah, why does she have that hair?
She always has clones.
Women who look like that in real life, evil.
Why don't women have clones like that in real life?
I don't know.
[Laughter]
I don't know. I don't know about girls.
Why can't you answer...
[Laughter]
Yeah, you need to fucking have a...
Unless it's about...
You start watching Pussy Explained.
explained and I she's like a twi'lek I can't tell. Twi'leks are so hot dude.
That's so that's so weird that they got fetishized like that. Dude they're
fucking hot. Dude it's so fucked up the way they were fetishized. Well it's a woman with tentacles for hair.
That's yeah and that's the only difference otherwise she's just a
fucking woman in a bikini. A beautiful rubbery skinned woman with horns on her
forehead it's just I fuck that's a zebra X dude I'd love to know some pilots have
fucking spikes on their shit I'd be such a good boyfriend to a twilight
definitely on spikes on their head I'd braid her flaps at night yeah yeah I'd
put them I'd put them up in a bun then I'd also I'm back you know I'm saying
I'd have sex with a trend ocean oh that's their ears I thought their ears were
horns
trend ocean yeah do you know what that is no it's not sound sexy to me no it's not
no no look up bosque all right that's a yes QUE like the Spanish people yeah
that's exactly it's oh it's just a lizard guys that's not yeah come on you I
would it's not a good guy this bitch got jaws why not fucking jaws and claws
those are the two no-nos for Caleb hmm I do not fuck anything with jaws or claws
okay or paws for that matter is actually this is a pretty good fucking there's a
pretty good yeah little you know like that could have been in the Bible you
know yeah don't fuck anything with jaws or claws raw that is in the Bible don't
fuck raw anything with paws jaws or claws that's the law yeah that's the laws
that's the best claws raw in the Bible don't hit it raw if it's got paws or
claws that's there's an anti-raciality thing in the Bible right?
I don't know about any bestiality stuff there's also pro-slavery stuff so how
much can you trust that any bestiality shit you know I mean like you got to make
a decision right there is bestiality wrong and slavery right or is it
opposite you know I know where I stand I put my hand on the Bible on opposite day
that's right yep did you guys do a prank on April Fool's Day?
anything hilarious? but it wasn't it wasn't anything I was doing different
you were just still acting like an idiot you're just like April Fool's this time
no I well I've been doing this thing we're all like I'll be talking to Neil
and then I'll be like oh did you just did you see what like the like the
landlord just texted us or something like that and then I'll show him like a
picture of like a fat guy's ass or like my favorite that Neil does that to me all
that he's like it does the thing we're like oh did you see this and then it
shows like a giant dick. Yeah. But one time you texted me a picture was like, "Hey man,
did you see this?" And it was like a picture of a penis overlaid on like a Reddit screenshot
and from the Reddit screenshot you could see that just all the AskReddit links are purple.
I was like, "Man, this is way more embarrassing for you than it is annoying for me." Me and
Neil did, when we lived together we'd do that a lot. Just hand each other the phone and
say, "Hey, have you seen this?" And usually it was the same picture of a humongous penis.
mm-hmm yeah which is very funny to have a huge penis cuz I came I came home
yesterday and I was like I think I was getting a burrito somewhere I was I came
home and I was like oh did you like did you not pay I just got this email and
then it was just like something fucking like Bob sent in that group chat it was
Bob you know by at Bob oh okay I thought you maybe your landlord's name was Bob
no no no do not my landlord's name your clown name Bob I thought you said bah
bah you trust bah for sure bah I think be trusted
bah I think bah means grandma in some language yeah I would never have a I
would never any any I would never have a land doc named Robert land doc yeah
dude he's land doc hey let me get a three-bedroom apartment yo yo yo yo walk
Let me get a three bedroom apartment salt pepper mayo.
That's right.
Just put it on the floor dude.
I'll take care of it.
Yo, Ock, let me get some working window shades.
Shady shock.
Yeah, but doesn't your landlord have a very funny name?
I'm not saying my landlord's name because it's...
Bowser.
Yeah, it is Bowser.
It's Doug Bowser from Nintendo.
yeah yeah i live in a green pipe leave that guy that's that is that's one of
those things where yet there you know like to the public that you like you
have no that had nothing to do with hiring him but you know and all the
meetings are like so we have to hire bowser right i mean the new apple ceo
greg iphone announced today
(laughing)
- iPhone is a German name?
- I just want to say it's pronounced "dee-foh-nay".
It is pronounced "dee-foh-nay".
- If you're a CEO--
- I will not have any jokes like this.
- You should have to change your last name
to the name of your company.
- I agree 100%.
- Yo!
- Doug Fizer.
- Greg Red Robin.
- What up?
(laughing)
- Greg Red Robin.
- Dude, Greg Red Robin is a beast.
- Who owns Red Robin?
Is it like one of those big like--
red robin well then you know Arby's like Arby's technically owns Dunkin Donuts
Arby's stands for red robin our red bobbin mm-hmm
your Arby's owns donuts yeah is that true what the fuck give me a collab dude yeah
Arby's um fuck Oh the parent organization inspire brands owns Buffalo
Wild Wings, Sonic, Arby's, Dunkin'.
- I need all four into one thing.
I need a slushie from Sonic with a buffalo sauce
and a donut. - And that makes the fist.
They also own something called Rusty Taco.
- A rusty taco? - I'm not eating
that rusty taco, dude. - Rusty Taco, that is like--
- That's a horrible name 'cause tacos do have
like a rust quality to them, like taco ground beef
when it has that like orange shit.
- Rusty Taco sounds like an Urban Dictionary article,
like whatever the fuck, Urban Dictionary page from like 2008.
Sounds like shitting in a girl's belly button.
That, yep.
I was gonna say shitting in a pussy, but...
Oh, what the hell is wrong with you?
Shitting in a pussy.
Okay, okay, me saying that if you read some of the things on Urban Dictionary, they're way worse than that.
Have you seen what they're saying?
This dictionary, it's too urban!
This dictionary's too urban!
That was me when I first moved to Queens.
I just started walking around, and I was like, "Hey."
- Hey, what up man?
You heard of a chili dog?
Yo, let me get a rusty trombone.
(laughing)
And he's like, yeah, that's actually urban as hell.
So I will give that to you.
- It is crazy how food chains are just owned
by one giant company.
- Yeah, I'm reading about Inspire brands
right now on Wikipedia.
- And I'm fucking inspired.
- All brands inspire me.
when they it started as Arby's and they took ownership of Buffalo Wild Wings and
became inspired brands and then they also got the rusty taco chain and then they
changed they changed the rest the name of rusty taco to our taco yeah that one
this is what is the only way we really have to the country the Philippines I
I think Jollibee... oh wow they own... oh it's called Red Ribbon. It's a bakery chain.
It's a knockoff. Yeah I thought I was like holy shit Jollibee owns Red Robin. Jollibee is owned by like a
giant like... No it's called the Jollibee Foods Corporation. A giant monster that lives in a
cave in the Philippines. Yeah the bee. It's like a yeah yeah it's the bee it's like Slurm and
Futurama. Oh they own they own Smash Burger. They own Smash Brothers? No way.
Yeah. They own Super Jollibee and Smash Brothers. They should have a fast food Smash Brothers.
Where all the fast food people fight. Yeah like food fight. That could be the
name of the game. Yeah. It could be different from the movie.
Mm-hmm. It is funny that that movie the only like brand that stayed in was like
Starkist tuna yeah everything else is just made up yeah yeah yeah wait like the
fucking like the the ads for it this summer Charlie the tuna it's gonna Charlie
the whale from Starkist tuna it's gonna be fucking in your living room yeah
that's already in my living room in my damn kitchen mm-hmm
in my pantry. He's already in my living room smeared all over my couch cushions. Do you
think we could do an entire like feature film if we just got like a hundred
thousand corporate sponsorships? We could. And just like put them all in the movie
like pay for the entire movie with that like a like a like a twenty million
dollar budget. We should try to do that. Just like get a bunch of
companies to pitch in like 50 grand you know and then just every second of it is
is an ad. That's what the Marx Brothers did with Love Happy. The Marx Brothers were
idiots. Yeah, that's I think Love Happy is like one of the first appearances of
Marilyn Monroe in a movie. I'm not sure if that's true. We should we can just ask every
brand for like $20. Yeah. That's like a gimme. They're like yeah of course.
Free advertisement. And we just ask we just ask a hundred thousand brands. Yeah.
We just do like a full million dollars. We guarantee them like you get a 20
second for every for every $20 that you give you get like like a 10 second like
Transformers beats ad yeah you remember those movies oh yeah yeah yeah like we
gotta stop the damn Decepticons but first let's listen to this dr. Dre song yeah
they have one they have one transformer that just changes into a Maytag washing
machine or whatever just yeah just sits there completely still for three seconds
That's a way to make movies, dude.
That's a fuckin' way to make movies.
Scorsese should've... he could take a...
He should've put Charlie the whale from Starkist 2 to...
Yeah.
You see this fuckin' guy right here? That's Charlie the whale.
You're gonna wanna fuckin' talk to this guy.
Any seafood you need, you fuckin' talk to this guy.
"I heard you eat tuna."
"Hey, I'm Charlie the whale. How are you doin'?"
Yeah, he could've been... I mean, Charlie the whale, by the way, great mafia name.
I have lung cancer.
Look I'm not gonna be in this movie long. Okay, I have I have stage four lung cancer.
Charlie the whale dude, I'm scared of him.
But I'm gonna tell you this.
You come to the docks. I'll give you a free lobster. You can ride on my back.
One last time just like the old days.
Then he just like throws up.
up. It's just a whale throwing up a water bottle. Yeah. Yeah. A bunch of plastic. I got lung
cancer from all the fatal aids that they're putting into fucking water. That's right.
We're doing an environmental message in the Irishman. Do you say that fatal aids? Yeah.
Yeah. That's what they, that's what plastics give you is fatal aids. Fatal aids? That's
so much scarier than normal aids. What the fuck? Especially since it starts with a PH.
(laughing)
It's fat, it's fattle.
- Yeah, fattily.
Is it pronounced fattily?
It might be.
- I don't know what that is at all.
I don't care about the environment or anything.
I like video games.
(laughing)
It's just the truth, dude.
- I like computer monitor and I like webcam.
- I used to care about politics
and I used to care about shit like that.
Now I'm, dude, just give me that screen.
- It's all about sitting down.
- I love sitting down.
I want to maximize sitting down.
I have the greatest sitting down job that anybody's ever had and yeah I just love it.
I want to swim in the LCD swamp.
Until I get taxed for my sitting down job and then I will become a Republican instantly.
Oh me too.
Dude I will be doing the most swagged out Republican shit pretty soon.
You guys are not going to believe how Republican we get.
Dude we're going to be like culturally Republican all of a sudden.
Another thousand dollars and I think that's it.
No turning back.
I'm flipping the switch dude.
we're all straight I'm gonna become a bowtie guy even though I never leave my
house yeah I'm gonna start fucking oh man I'm gonna care so much about gun control
but I'm legally not allowed to buy I'm gonna change my name my past I'm gonna
get really into red meat I'm gonna have a really big head a really small face I
might change my name to Quincy Beauregard
Quincy Beauregard at Turning Point USA. Yep. I'm gonna say. That's right. Well what the
Democrats don't understand is that it's more fun to be a Republican. We need to
go back to the poop standard. That's gonna be me. Base everything off of poop. That's right.
Republicans can tell jokes too. Yeah exactly. We're gonna say that after every joke we make on the
podcast. It is kind of funny that I think you become a right-wing comedian
instantly you're just like selling out stadiums oh yeah like great like the next
day dude it's so late they're so hungry yeah they're I mean literally so many of
them are in it for the money like yeah they'll probably have like some
right-wing views but like the way that they just ham it up is just like like
dude Nick DiPaolo Nick DiPaolo couldn't fucking sell out Caroline's ten years
ago and now he like does theater tours where he's like yeah Barack Obama's a
fucking black guy and then everybody's like it is funny just how many of those
like like comedians that were on like tough crowd and shit just like weren't
like they just like weren't able to process that like like trans people like
broke their brain yeah they were like oh now I got a fucking what the fuck is this
I gotta fucking talk to this person now. It's like yeah, it's it's it's pretty bad dude. Yeah
Yeah, it's I think it's because like you want to turn my son into a girl
That's my job. Yeah, that's what I've been doing every night
How dare you take the one joy a father has turning his son into a sissy little girl
The Internet is taking it from me. I put I put the estradol in a slice of cheese
and I make him do a little dance and then he eats the cheese I make him do a spin
I make him give me his paw yeah dude I think that is easily the move and I also
do how much merch do you think you fuck oh my god how many Nick DiPaolo shirts
say black black Obama and people like dude fucking $80 for a shirt plus
shipping yeah I'm fucking wearing a shirt that says Obama is black to try and own
people just keep coming up to you and be like oh my god I loved Obama - it's where
so where do I buy it was so we're so right you were so we and we loved it
yeah we loved it and they're like what did you read it right it doesn't say
Obama is back it says he's black I know I know and I love it yeah and you definitely
ringtones definitely Nick Tappala greeting cards you know dude dude Owen
Benjamin he's his whole thing is that he was like a like a Nick Thune style like
yeah comic yeah he was like fucking mine dude he he was like okay like he was a
pretty good comic like I think he's still probably pretty good but like all of his
songs now we're just like like oh liberals want me to drive Prius he's
literally yeah he just sings like throw the Jew down the well in his voice on
stage and people are like yeah let's do that right yeah Oh and Benjamin you are
my epic dad it just rules man I need to get I need to get here's what I need I
need to get a compound see you can't you you cannot you have to grow your hair out
a little bit more you can't have any plans to become a
conservative you can't say i'm going to get a compound
with that hair you guys should get full like ld with my hair larry david style
just a yeah oh man the horseshoe yeah uh-huh i think
i should do that and then i would become a fake right-wing comedian i would look
so good with a horse literally everybody would look over the
tonsure here's what you need is it possible to look bad i'm gonna grow my
hair out i'm gonna get for some reason the biggest microphone
a guy can possibly buy for a studio, put it right next to my face, get like 60 cameras
getting different angles, one's doing an up skirt, I'm wearing a skirt, and then just fucking-
No, it's a kilt. It's a kilt, because I'm a man!
It's a battle kilt, actually. I plug 50 supplements that are full of phytoestrogens
every single episode, and I get fucking 30 Facebook Live viewers per. And then I will
become a millionaire off of that. There's no question.
It's so easy. It's so easy.
It's, I mean, and then I die in a helicopter crash and then it's like the perfect life
anybody's ever had, you know?
You're going exactly like Kobe Bryant.
Going out like Kobe, one of the greatest right-wing people of all time.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, you just gotta--
Right? That was his position in the NBA. He was--
He was right-wing. He was a right-wing player, yeah.
That's hockey. Yeah, that's hockey. Yeah.
He did do a couple of right-wing things in his past, I'll say that much.