Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
Okay.
What are you saying?
What is that?
Fuck you.
Put that down.
Don't.
Don't start.
It's not.
Oh.
Oh my god.
What the fuck is that?
He's not even, he's still muted.
I have no idea what he's eating or saying.
What is he eating?
(laughing)
- As we're recording over Discord now,
it doesn't save the video anymore,
so that's just lost to time.
- Oh man.
- What the fuck was that, dude?
- So gross.
- He just literally drank black slime
out of like a blue and white teacup.
(laughing)
- It was the bottom--
- Like a fancy porcelain teacup.
- I'm so done with Caleb right now.
He needs to turn his microphone on.
It was the, it was the uh...
He's been sitting here not, he's been sitting here with his mic muted the whole time.
My mic isn't muted.
He hasn't talked to us once.
Pat's been doing this for the last ten minutes.
He's trying to talk right now.
He's trying really hard to make it like a, for it to turn the corner, but I don't think
it's going to.
I don't think you're going to make it Pat.
I don't think it's going to hit.
I think you could maybe drop it now and then like bring it back in ten minutes and then
it might hit, like, a little.
I'm so I'm done with this already. Close eBay. Close Grailed. No, I'm not on Grailed. You are
on Grailed. You got into Drake and you closed Grailed all day. If he's gonna do this then
I might go on Grailed. Pat got into, he listened to 30 Seconds and Take Care. I'm going to eBay
and look up some audio shoes. He's been trying to install Depop on his Kindle. Yep. This
is what Caleb's doing. This is Caleb's fault. Why do you think someone would want to listen
I might buy a pair of audio bands.
This is, you're ruining the episode right now.
Who, me or Caleb?
You.
I'm not. I'm not ruining it. Caleb's ruining it by not speaking.
Oh, look at this. Audio Jeremy Reyes.
I'm speaking. You heard me sing Drake earlier.
Size 8, they benefit charity.
He's waiting for one of us to go like, "Wait, can he actually not hear him?"
And then he's gonna say like, "I got you."
But it's not gonna happen.
Pat heard, oh he just said "Mhm."
And he's ruining the episode because I know he's recording and I know that we're not gonna
hear a goddamn thing.
Caleb, what would you do to Pat's mom?
What would I do to Pat's mom?
I'd fucking, I'd fillet her like a fish.
I wouldn't even do anything sexual to her, I'd just murder her.
Damn, audio Brian Summers.
I'd eat her old organs.
Like new old stuff.
I'd probably dry age your mom.
I'd follow the recipe of a Guga Foods video and I'd dry age your mom in hot sauce and
I'd eat her.
Wait, I just thought of something, Pat.
If Caleb's mic is off, you probably wouldn't mind if he said your address right now, right?
Your full address, street address, zip code?
Yeah, I can do that.
Please don't.
Please don't do that.
Please don't what?
No, he's muted, right?
It's fine.
Here, then stop me.
Stop it.
Oh, so he can hear me.
You gotta call me.
You're at a bar.
We got a call, we were at a bar last night, me and Caleb, and we got a call from a fan.
Shout out to that guy.
But we were at a bar- Dude, I just got you so good, don't try and
misdirect.
You gotta admit, you just lost so hard.
Fuck you.
I know, this sucks.
But we were at a bar last night and some old guy starts talking to us, and he's talking
to us about how he wants to like, move out of the city.
And he's like, "Yeah, I won't move past the Mason-Dixon line, 'cause it's full of you-know-whats."
and then Caleb started prodding him to what he meant by you know what's and
then he was like oh it's full of mongrels. He said mongrels. Dude it was so crazy.
It was awesome dude. Maybe he was talking about dogs. He might have honestly been
talking about raccoons. That would be. There's a lot of raccoons. That would be better if
he was. Yeah but it was pretty it was pretty and the bartender just didn't do shit.
Jesus Christ, the bartender just fucking sat there and then after he left he was like,
"Erm, was that guy being weird?"
I was like, "Yeah dude, you're six inches from him."
I fucking hate this dude, I'm done.
"You're serving him drinks, dude."
What?
What the fuck?
Where did he go?
What is happening?
If that messed up the recording for the sink, I'd be so upset.
Why did you leave Pat?
Dude, and then tell Caleb to turn the mute off.
My mute is not on!
There's literally no mute.
He's muted right now.
No!
Say the gotcha or whatever.
I'll do the thing.
Oh what the fuck, wait.
How did...
I didn't know he could speak the whole time.
Wait, we should restart.
Because for some reason Caleb was muted on my end.
And I thought he was...
This can't be true.
No, it's not true.
I don't believe it.
*laughing*
No fucking way, dude.
Did you think that we were getting you?
Yes! We thought you were trying to get us.
No, I wasn't! I thought you guys
were trying to get me.
What the fuck? You were muted on my end
for some reason. And then you rage quit?
Yeah. You never thought to check if it was
on your end? No, I really
I was gonna say like, "Hey, check if his volume is just turned down in your Discord settings."
But I'm not gonna do that, 'cause then you would do the gotcha to me and I would lose.
And I'm not losing in that fight.
Not happening.
Dude, that was...
I'd rather ruin the episode than lose.
Dude.
I thought that you got mad because I corrected you when you sang Drake earlier, which I guess
you didn't even hear that.
You got the lyrics wrong by the way, you fucker.
You came into the, um, oh you know what it was?
You had me muted because of the stream the other day.
And I never unmuted you because you left before everyone.
Fuck, dude.
You are as fucking dumb as a rock.
I'm so sorry about this.
You didn't even hear me.
That was pretty funny actually.
It is kind of funny.
This is actually the best outcome of this.
I'm really glad that it wasn't just like a failed like bit that was getting pushed through.
That actually makes it really good.
We were both so determined not to be fucked that we just ruined the beginning of the episode.
This is really exposing in our friendship what high alert we always have to be on.
I know.
Did you really say my address?
No.
Okay.
I got close.
Thank God.
To starting to say it.
Yeah, but now it's like, now there's just like me talking over you and shit.
It's like.
pretty good job of moving around it. No, it's fine, yeah. I'm pretty much a pro. Yeah. I
think it will actually be the best episode ever. Dude, it's... You might have missed this.
I did say I was going to dry age your mom's meat like a Guga Fruits video and eat her.
And you... I said I was going to dry age her in Da Bomb hot sauce and you had no reaction.
I was like that's interesting this guy has no respect for his own mom.
He's stone faced at that.
That's pretty wild.
Jesus Christ dude.
Oh my god there's so much I missed in the beginning of the- I dude.
Cause you- I was like dude literally I'm like looking at like shoes and shit and I'm just
like oh yeah no.
Caleb wants to ruin the episode I'll do it too.
I legit thought that you were trying like you were doing like a silent bit. It was like
I
Thought you were doing a thing where it's like oh my mic doesn't work
I was saying for like like before we even record it - I was like Caleb unmute yourself
God damn dude. I do that normally that's like a thing you would do as a joke though true. Yeah
I think those things are you would also
Go a whole episode with your break
Yeah, they're both things that you would do but I'm so stupid
We just had a war yeah
We had a mental war. I've never said like a brain battle. I've never done a brain battle with you guys
Yeah, that was crazy. That was intense. I know I
Didn't I think I might have PTSD from that. I thought I thought I was gonna so I
Fucking left the call because I thought that as soon as I left the call Kayla would unmute
So now I was gonna do a gotcha where it's like you motherfucker. And no it was
my fault
the minds battle of
2022 oh man
Pretty good rage quit though that you had if I was doing it it worked really well. Yeah. Yeah, did you did you get upset?
No, you got upset you left
Were you upset that I left? No, I do hope that you leaving does I up the recording? Yeah, I know I think
I think it'll be good.
- I'm sure it'll be fine.
- It's fine, who cares?
- If I, what if I had cancer, would you care?
- Yeah.
- What kind of cancer, everybody has cancer,
what kind of cancer do you think you have?
- But.
- I sometimes get worried that I have entire body cancer.
- I'm worried that this hemorrhoid isn't just a hemorrhoid
and that it's colon cancer.
- You got polyps?
- I think I might have cancer.
I think I might have mind cancer, which is completely different from brain cancer.
I have mind cancer.
ADHD.
I have a lump on my nut, but I've been told that that's kind of pretty normal these days.
Yeah.
I've been told that girls like it, so I'm trying to make it bigger.
It's actually really...
Girls like it when you have a lumpy nut.
Girls like it when your nut has the texture of a grenade.
They really like that.
I have a horn on my ball.
Really?
But, no.
Oh, what?
Why are you lying to me?
Yeah, I know.
You just said you wanted the texture of a grenade.
If you had a horn...
I said girls like it when you have a grenade nut.
Mine only has one little grenade bump on it.
Mine has a pin.
What?
Yeah, my grenade has a pin.
All in your nuts grenades is pretty cool actually.
Yeah, hit me right in the old grenades.
The grenades.
Yeah, I mean they are volatile.
Damn, because I need someone to jump on these and save me.
Yes!
Yes sir!
Oh shit, I can't show you, that's your present, I can't show you that.
Oh dude, we can do presents tonight.
Yeah, do you want to show the presents?
Oh no, no, no, we'll just meet up later.
No, I want to give you my present in person.
Yeah.
I told Caleb what I got you last night.
I thought illness got me, but it turns out pestilence passed me by.
Damn.
That's real shit.
Yeah, rapid to rapid test negative for pestilence.
Really?
Did you guys see my new shirt?
Yeah, it's got a cartoon on it.
Yeah, it's got a little cartoon.
Dude, you're into cartoons.
I'm getting into cartoons.
You're wearing a full...
I've been getting into...
Are you wearing a full poop outfit?
You're wearing all brown again.
No, I'm not.
No, this is like a meme.
Oh my God, he's poop boy.
He's pooped out.
Hey, what's up my boy dookie doubt?
Never tell you guys about there's this kid that used to Jonathan. He talked about us
No, there's this kid who when we had like, you know, we had like a like a shitty like
Like trampoline
We had one of those like old squeaky trampoline
Like they do with the hot dogs. Yeah
He's dipping turds in milk.
And then this kid came over one time, my little brother's best friend growing up, and now you
switched to a full vagina outfit.
I'm one in the pink and two in the stink.
He has a pink hat on now.
And it's got jasmine on it.
But then this kid, he tried to pee off of the trampoline, he peed all over the fucking
trampoline while we were all jumping on it.
We were jumping a P out at everyone and then we started calling him P-Boy and then my dad
and my older brother both forgot his real name and then for just years they would just say
like where is P-Boy gonna come over and his mom had to like sit my entire family down
and be like hey he really it hurts his feelings when you call him P-Boy.
That's so funny.
Yeah.
That's tight.
I would never stop calling him that.
At that point though you got to reclaim the name.
You got to reclaim the nickname.
Yeah, he used to dress up like Spider-Man every day too.
Every day?
He would dress up like Spider-Man every- like he went to high school like every day as Spi-
in a different Spider-Man outfit.
I think you guys really did affect him.
I think they literally broke his brain, dude.
Yeah.
And then his mom destroyed my car.
Why?
The first car I ever got, like my stepdad gave me his old car when I turned 16,
and then I drove it for one week and then she borrowed it for a day and crashed it.
I never had a car again until college.
Damn.
I would never do that to my friends.
Yeah, I would never do that to the boy who tormented my son.
It did feel like a revenge thing.
Oh, it was totally a revenge thing.
It had to have been on purpose, right?
Yeah.
What if I just took my hands off the wheel of the guy who invented P-Boy?
Yeah, oh, here's your car, car boy.
She's sitting there whistling and then out of nowhere she just goes, "Whew!"
And just fucking turns the wheel into like a Sbarro
Well, you you think we had some borrow? Yes, and little old Wilmington, North Carolina. Yes. Hell no
Why not? We just got a Blaze Pizza
Really just recently. Yep
It's a cone next time we're down. It was huge. I
went with
I went with Pete my grandpa and boy was he fucking mad at that place.
Yeah he didn't like it.
He was like goddamn pizza is too fucking small.
Pizza is supposed to be as big as a wheel.
This pizza is small ass pizza.
Plus they make you make it yourself.
You should tell them what you want and they make you everything but you have to say it
with every step of the process.
He has a really hard time at places like that or Subway where he can't, he doesn't know
what the ingredients are that he's looking at.
Yeah.
So he can't say them really and like he can't, he doesn't wear the glasses that he's supposed
to have so he can't read it either.
Gets overwhelmed by the options.
So he's just sitting there pointing at things.
He's that one guy.
Yeah, he's pointing at ricotta cheese and he says that stuff or he's pointing at spinach
and he says that.
Someday he's going to invent like a new perfect sandwich.
Yeah, he probably will.
sane person would ever order on purpose. And he can't explain what's on it. Yeah.
It's that stuff. That's the most amazing sandwich ever. Yeah. Yeah, it's got a little bit of
that. It's got some white blur, some green blur. Oh, what the fuck? Oh, the Craig bot
left. Craig hates us. It's okay, we already have it synced to the beginning, right? Yeah.
I hope so. Should be fine. It should be fine. I'm crazy for Craig. This does make me upset.
We're getting mad at Craig. We gotta stop doing this Discord thing, man. I need to feel you
to
He definitely heard him.
I mean when he said "You know what's" it's pretty...
No he probably heard the whole thing.
Get the fuck out of here Craig!
I brought Craig back because for my own peace of mind.
I like seeing his face in there.
It is nice to have a little bear.
I was thinking today that we should get a fourth guy.
Yeah.
Well we have Kyle.
I mean yeah I kind of want to get Kyle into the recordings.
Besides Kyle, yeah.
Yeah we just haven't...
We do need a new guy besides Kyle though.
We recruited Kyle, but he's still out in LA.
We could get Bexley on the mic.
I don't know.
He's not funny to laugh at, but he's not funny to laugh with.
What about The Dominator?
Oh, dude.
I haven't seen him since college.
I'm playing with fucking...
I feel like he's always on.
No I know, he's definitely always on but like, I mean that's what's so sick about him.
That's what's good to have him on the mic.
We don't have to hang out with him, I mean I hope he doesn't listen to this but just
have him on the show and walk him away.
He told me he's like a die hard.
Yeah?
What does that mean?
He listens to every episode.
He told me he's a dominator.
Yeah, well that's his nickname.
short for Dominic Polisi.
I just think we need a new energy.
Yeah we do need a new energy. Or maybe an animal. That's what I mean when Kyle moves back.
It's gonna be so sick.
What if we got Zabumafu?
We got a pet?
So you know a pet would be really good but I have another pitch.
So you know how every normal episode we do a different list.
we don't have to list on the premium what if every premium episode we get a new pet we get a new pet
or we record in a completely different country that's gonna get really expensive really fast
i think yeah that's what the patreon is for right that's true we can also and once we get over to
like the small countries wherever those are we can just kind of walk from one to the other
uh we'll see it would be this guam a country i think it's a territory yeah territory is a country
to me. It would be fun to all of us get normal jobs and then just break even
with the patreon where we spend that much money every month on something with the
podcast. That would be so sick honestly. Yeah. If we spent all the patreon
money every month just to do like stupid shit for episodes though this would
maybe be the best podcast in history. What do you think I've been doing? Yeah Pat's been doing that with shirts and
beanies getting new kinds of poop outfits.
Oh this one will look like a corn.
Pat literally walks into fucking Beacon's closet and says...
Do you have anything that looks like a streak of red pepper?
No it's not Beacon's closet, it's Basin's closet.
You go to Bacon's closet and you have to look like different kinds of food.
Basin's closet is all poop and pee colored clothes.
No.
Yeah.
You asked us to, you say, "Can you make me look like a green zucchini?"
Basin's washroom.
This is getting, you're making this disgusting.
You're the one who dresses up like poop and pee every day.
You literally have, you started this episode dressed up as poop talking into a pee pee
microphone.
Do you see this?
It's longer on this side.
I have to go fix that right now.
You say that every day of your life.
Every time you talk to me you say, "I just noticed my mustache is lopsided."
I'd like to lop the side of your head off with an axe.
Why?
Why would you do-
That's kind of messed up, Caleb.
You would not benefit from that at all.
I don't know if you did anything that warranted that.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Because I mean-
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait ten minutes.
Wait ten minutes until I say something fucking stupid.
Like you could, you know, you could cut his head in half or whatever.
like they could like science could study that cross-section and like understand
how like thoughts are formed in the brain and stuff it just looks like ice cream
that's brain if you gave it to scientists it's mint chocolate chip if you hand
Pat's brain to a scientist which they're pretty you know hard to come by you're
like we study this they just like eyeball it there's no I think it might
be one of those things where they like suppress it because nobody can like can
get their hands on that technology like if like a scientist invented mind
control and like they're just like no I have to destroy this yeah I think if you
donate a pet's brain to science they might just like just crush it immediately
they'd say they'd be like legally this is an ant's brain it's just a big ants
brain you're gonna like do what they did with the third brain and spy kids and
they're just gonna make an army of stupid people to go off to war you can
I think they already have that.
I think they are Spy Kids recently.
I watched Spy Kids 3 recently, but I don't remember what happens in the original Spy
Kids.
In the original one, they have a microwave that makes food, which is huge.
That's the one with the little robot, the little bug robot thing.
That guy was so cool.
Oh, that was Spy Kids 2.
I had that fucking...
That guy rocked, dude.
What was his name?
Dude, I had the Spy Kids like play set as a kid.
I had all the gadgets and shit.
I wish I had the Spy Kids play set.
Spy Kids...
Dude, that thing was so sick.
We should get that now. We should go. We should we spend all our money. We spent all the money
on the Patreon on Spycoin. His name was Ralph, dude. Yeah, Ralph. Oh, really? Yeah, he was
cool as fuck. He was a, it was short for Robotic Arachnid Lithium Photo Helper. Yeah, I guessed
that. That was apparent to me. I knew that as soon as they said Ralph in the movie. Yeah.
I got it instantly. I could just tell by the design of the robot what it meant. Yeah, I was
like well it's a lithium photo helper and he is robotic yeah obviously yeah that
thing was sick it came in a little briefcase. It's not a pet we need a robot sidekick
that is oh yes dude yes how much do you think those Boston Dynamics dogs are
probably not that much. Three if you just take them. Well that's true if you ride away on it
mm-hmm but you can't the thing is about that compared to a normal dog you can't
lure it with a bone? No you can lure it with a computer chip. Yeah. Like a floppy
disk that has the program for the taste of chocolate without the poison.
Yeah that might be pretty delightful to a dog. That could be actually great. You
know what maybe that's what we do. We put all of our money into
getting into making chocolate for dogs.
Yeah. I think they have something like that.
I'm not sure they also just eat chocolate and yeah.
Then they could just go to the hospital. Yeah. I mean, if a dog,
if a dog eats chocolate, it's fine with me.
You have to give the dog a Benadryl first and then I can eat chocolate. Yeah.
Yeah. You got to crush it up. Yeah. Like a lactate for, for dogs.
But for sure. You want to lactate a dog? Yeah. Yeah. I bet you do. Yes.
I bet you do yes. I do want to taste different kinds of milk. Yeah. Yeah, you
know what I'm not I think I'm not against tasting a dog's milk. Are you like
honestly I think I think yes, I was talking about about with with Pierce
about the boy egg thing where I think it's okay to want to drink a dog's milk,
but not if you have a specific dog in mind. Uh-huh. Like I think yeah, I think
that's fair. Somebody hands you a glass of dog milk and you drink it. I think
that's fine but if you're like I want to milk that dog and right no no no no no
no no no I disagree I disagree that's like saying it's okay to eat lobster but
not you can't pick the specific one I'm gonna look at like okay I don't want to
fucking pit bulls milk I don't want something muscly sure I want like I want
like a an Afghan hound yeah yeah something fucking crazy you know it looks
like it has hair like a beautiful woman yeah I want to like even that like when
you're picking out a lobster you see what you're eating.
Yeah.
When you're picking out the dog you're like looking at its nipples and stuff.
I can sense the vibe of the milk.
Yeah, I'm looking at the nipples.
I'm looking at the claws if I'm getting a lobster.
I'm saying, "Oh, those are big meaty claws."
You're going to eat the claws.
Yeah, and I'm going to drink those titties, the tit milk.
No, you're going to drink what's inside.
No.
Yeah.
It's different.
Okay, do you think that bad milk comes out of beautiful breasts?
No.
It's good milk.
Maybe.
So you have to assess the breast of the dog and say...
Well, hold on.
Hold on.
Here's my new rule. You can't know the dog's name.
That's fine. I'm going to give them...
I'm going to immediately find out the name after I take one sip of the milk anyway.
If you find out the dog's name in the middle of you drinking it, you have to spit it out.
You can't...
I don't think this is right.
I think that's completely true.
If you see one dog that has, like I said...
Even if you saw a guy drink a big glass of just normal cow's milk and then say like,
"Thank you, Bessie," that would not be okay.
That is okay.
That's a gift.
Well, Bessie is like the name of most cows, isn't it?
The farmer's name, the cow...
What are you talking about?
They have names.
The farmer knows the cow's name and they know which one gives you the best milk and it's
the one with the fattest fucking tits.
So that's why I feel like if you see a dog, if you see a pit bull, right, and it's got
like six packs with titties on them I don't want that but if you see a dog
that has like a like a plump sumptuous kind of like a curve. Okay Nuru you can't say plump or sumptuous.
Plump, sumptuous, delectable curve because it's almost like the milk is like
falling out right it's like falling off the bones like short ribs you know it's
It's just like this milk needs to get out.
Okay, alright.
What happened to you?
New rule, okay.
It's too delicious to keep milk in this dog's body.
I have my new final rule, which is that you can drink dog milk unless you're Caleb.
Yeah.
That's the one situation you're not allowed anywhere near him.
Dude, you, you...
Yeah, that's probably a good call.
You fucking described that...
That, I was, for a brief second, I was like, "He's fucked a dog before."
What?
For a split second.
What point in that entire thing did I get sexual at all?
At what point?
Name one thing that I said that sounded even remotely sexual.
I don't even want to say it now.
Women who have bigger boobs make more and better milk.
They don't make more milk.
Dogs that have humongous...
Humongouses.
Humongers.
Dogs who have humongers.
A dog with humongers?
have humongous. A dog with humongous is gonna make humongously tasty milk that will taste
better when you put it. Okay, also what do you think, I feel like dog milk is gonna be
a little bit acrid, right? It's gonna be a little uh, gym-socky. Yeah. And, but, but,
I think it's gonna be an acquired taste and I think it's gonna have a really nice finish
with a little bit of a sweetness at the end like a honeysuckle.
Best animal.
Goat.
Best animal milk.
Best animal milk?
I wanna hear from Caleb.
To drink?
Yeah.
No, to what do you mean, what else?
I mean, milk has plenty of applications.
I don't wanna hear them.
You can wash a car window with milk.
No, you can't.
You can and I've done it.
Prove it.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
We stop recording right now, we go to Caleb's car, and we watch him watch the window with
the milk.
Try to say watch him watch again.
Watch him watch the window with the milk.
There we go.
Okay, let's do it then.
You can fix a DVD with it too.
That one I believe.
Milk has a lot of things going on that you guys just don't understand I guess.
But number one milk has got to be, I mean it's got to be a dog.
I've had...
I think, okay, I think I'm adding a rule that you can drink any animal milk except for your
number one.
Why are you just trying to get in the way?
I honestly now I'm like I need to like find, like I have to try this before I die.
You're going to drink dog milk.
Yeah, wait until like I don't know you anymore.
really would I don't want to see if I got it no it's not about the act of you doing
it's that I don't want to see how your personality changes you become a an
addict and you crave dog milk and you become a slave to the impulse wouldn't
become an addict that doesn't make you literally be addicted to dog milk
instantly it's probably not that good I just mean that it probably is a lot more
complex I do not want to see the videos you would be uploading to Vimeo I don't
to see anything that has to do with like your personality or your presence in the world
at all. I want you to be gone from my mind.
Guess who's not getting the password to the videos? You. You might get the URL, you're
not getting the password out of me though. I don't want it. It's probably ginormous.
Humongous, actually, is what it is. Ginormous are a different level and they're bigger than
humongous and a dog can't possibly... Ginormous wouldn't fit on a dog's fragile frame. You
don't know what about a great a great game could have some ginormous but they
have they're a little too skinny for me I think ginormous or balls and humongous
or boobs ginormous no we already said balls or
grenades oh fuck you're right exploders okay what animal then do you think
probably has the most delicious milk probably some cow and human is not
available by since when why cuz you banned me from drinking a dog's milk so I
can't make up nonsense rules now in fucking candyland go ahead and candy
milk candy the candy candy isn't an animal you have to it has to be a mammal
gummy bear yeah gummy bear that's actually pretty good that's a pretty
good point you guys don't want to go here with me you don't want to say an
animal that... Okay, what about... I said bison, I said kangaroo. You know what I think
that they should do? Where does kangaroos tits is? Huh? I think that... Where's a kangaroos
tits? On it's chest. Really? Is there kangaroos that have... Hold on. Kangaroo with boobs.
Let me look it up.
Yeah, let's see.
Oh wow.
Have you seen an elephant?
No, they don't have normal boobs.
No, they don't.
Have you seen an elephant?
Oh wow.
Oh wow, check this out.
Hold on, let me pull up the chat.
Okay, I think elephant...
Type in elephant, Biddy.
Have you seen them?
Double D Dumbo.
The female elephant with a huge pair of boobs.
Okay, I think elephant...
Type in elephant, Biddy.
Have you seen them?
Double D Dumbo.
The female elephant with a huge pair of boobs.
Okay, I think elephant...
Type in elephant, Biddy.
Have you seen them?
Double D Dumbo.
The female elephant with a huge pair of boobs.
Type in elephant, but have you seen double D Dumbo the female elephant with a huge pair of boobs
Wow, there's a lot in this is in the news I looked up kangaroo boobs, and I'm finding a lot of
I'm finding a lot of pictures
Do this thing's got a lot of normos so a lot of drawings these people have made look at this look at this fucking elephant
I know dude. It's crazy. Yeah, thanks looking up nice ones those those those weird
I've heard bot like animal accounts that I follow on Instagram like post that picture
like once a month.
That elephant's got some nice cans.
I might be changing my mind on what animal has the best milk.
Yeah, the elephants go crazy.
You know what's huge for me is that there's only two of them.
Oh, I posted in the wrong channel.
Yeah, everyone's gonna see.
I feel like the fewer nipples, like you're not like splitting the quality.
You know what I mean?
So here's my pitch though.
my
uh...
there were you see that you have a source kangaroo fetish images and
general channel so that the private recording what
uh... so what's the point of the like
if you want to like come on streamers something
and
they're gonna see it
it's the public select kangaroo report
if that's the deal breaker i don't want
that's exactly what is right here's my here's my milk pitch okay
i think that scientists
should be in the lab twenty four seven
i think that they for every non mammal animal every animal does not produce
milk they should be using like i don't know a gene therapy or like
d_n_a_ sequencing or some science shit
to create the milk that that animal would make and i think that they should
do it for every animal in the world that does not produce milk and i think you
should be able to go to a store called the milk store and you type in any animal
and it's like a coca-cola freestyle machine and you can mix them and as a
picture of the animal in a little circle that you press. I actually fully agree
there should be a there should be a milk freestyle machine. Yeah and it should be
that's up but every it so you can get snakes, worms, fishes. Snakes do make milk
it's just venom just poison. That's not milk. No. Venom is milk. No it's not.
This is one of, I'm not even gonna engage with you on this.
Yeah, I'm sorry, but I can't.
The premise is honestly, uh, pathetic.
It's moronic, what you just said.
The venom being milk.
What about a picture of venom?
What about an angel fish?
Here, I'm gonna look up something right now.
Do you think that a rainforest frog has a coat of milk?
Frog milk might actually be good.
The texture of that might be really interesting.
I feel like frog milk might have a kind of a lack of flair.
Oh, oh, what is this?
Adventures of a snake milker.
They milk the venom. Milk is a verb.
You can milk things.
Milk your cock.
What? You know, like this.
You know when you do it upside down one time for the one time?
Yeah, you put it through the hole in the table.
Milk my... And they squeeze it?
You don't get that done?
You don't remember on masseuse?
I never thought a chicken could make milk.
You are a devil.
a devil. See I waited, I told you wait 10 minutes. Yeah you're a monster for that. But
chicken milk could go hard. I think I mean I fuck with eggs in a heavy way. Instead of
Coca-Cola freestyle it's Milka Milka freestyle. I think that's a good idea because then you
can also add, you have your flavors also where you can do. Yeah so you can do like. I want
Strawberry milk, but I yeah, I want it to have I want a blueberry added to it. Yeah
I feel like it's a great idea
I think that could be really big you also I think you could synthesize just a general like you could
Synthesize like a syrup much like well, okay?
Yeah, let's also say that you accidentally in some kind of freak teleporter accident or something like you have some kind of animal
That's like. I don't know like half crocodile and half bear, and you're like. Oh, it's good. It's a baby
baby is going to die if it doesn't get its milk. There's no crocodile bear milk in the
world but thanks to the Milka Milka Freestyle Machine you go, you hold out your cup, you
press crocodile, hold it down for a little bit, then you press bear, hold it down, you
swirl it around and that mutant baby is going to love that milk and it's going to grow big
and strong and it might kill you. So don't actually.
Another kind of life or death situation, say you're doing a Scorsese marathon and you say
"God damn I'm thirsty! God damn I'm thirsty for some milk!"
Pop on over, they're in Qdoba, you gotta go to the Qdoba next door,
hit the Milk and Milk a Freestyle machine, you say, "Hmm,
am I feeling more sparrow today, or am I feeling more
earthworm?" Are these replacing...
You. You are replaced by a Milk and Milk a Freestyle machine.
Are these replacing Coca-Cola Freestyle machines or do we still get both?
No, we can have both.
Okay.
See, I was just nervous that-
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
New idea, new idea.
It's a machine, it's giant, the size of like a building, right?
Every drink Freestyle machine.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Even better.
All the drinks.
Listen.
Beer Freestyle machine.
Listen!
Listen.
A Freestyle machine, Freestyle machine.
Shut the fuck up.
You press any button to make any machine.
Hey, give me enough beer.
I become a freestyle machine that's right mm-hmm I might need to zone out on gun I
just came in a good freestyle thank you yeah I'm not that recently Pat
reignited my love of Drake and I'm thinking I'm becoming a kind of Drake
type guy yeah yeah I think cool I think Caleb you grow your hair out again or
maybe we just come over and I just draw a heart on your hairline with a sharpie
Well I need to do, I don't have any hair but I do need that little cut in that he has.
So maybe I'll just slice my scalp over right here.
Yeah, you should just get like a heart scar.
Some flesh just showing right there.
Oh, oh I can come over, I'll get like a brand and I'll brand a heart onto your forehead.
I need to be branded like yesterday.
That would actually be hard as fuck.
That'd be sick dude.
Like a heart brand on a bald guy's head?
You know what, I really want to get a subdermal implant.
Yeah?
Oh you should get a donut dude.
put a donut in my head not like you seen like the donut forehead guys no in
Japan. Is it like Dr. Manhattan? No. There's a guy in my neighborhood who looks
like the devil he has horns and shit yeah and a full entire body's tattooed
and he has horns. Is he usually on your shoulder? Yeah and he's telling me
he's telling me to talk about dog milk all the time he's saying yeah you should
you should find all that see that dog you should milk that dog and drink it
yeah check check that out I feel like that'd be a good crime spree to go on it
is it wow this is crazy it looks more like a volcano yeah oh that's it I don't
know if that's reversible - yeah you take it back out they put it in the ticket oh
wait no that's that's gotta be like Botox or something actually that's
probably saline it says oh yeah see with the with the dermal implants they just
Oh, it's temporary.
It's like a cake of rock, put it in your head.
It's a temporary 6-24 hour swelling distortion in the forehead created by staline dip shaped
to resemble a bagel or a donut.
Why do that?
It looks awesome.
What are you talking about?
I would love to get a, to eat soup out of a guy's head who got one of those.
You know what, I would, I would love to put my finger in there.
I would go to church with that and I would say I need forgiveness. I've made
a lot of mistakes and then the next day it would be gone and I would say that
God did you miracle yeah, I might try and shoot a nerf dart into it and see if
I that's just a late. I think that's a perfectly that's perfect for body shots
right mm-hmm like that guy's like a human cup yeah, I'm actually yeah like
somebody's like oh we're gonna do body shots and this guy's and his whole life
is like check this out like pulls up his shirt and he does like like like like a
bunch of shot glasses like in his stomach. I was like oh just like leaves
yeah cuz it's hard to the tire like that putting putting that yeah putting those
into your body because you're like oh dude if anyone ever wants to do body
shots like they're gonna they're gonna freak out they're gonna be so happy when
they see this and they'll just everyone everyone's crying yeah everyone screams
and then in my colostomy hole you know we just unplug the bag for a minute you
just hit the shot glass in there yeah it's cool that you can be that you can
become a poop cyborg if you get sick oh yeah yeah yeah I really want to I want
to get like shot if a seal really bad see what see difficile was that that's the
thing that makes you makes you get a weird shit thing and you have to drink a
shit smoothie. So with a colostomy bag what's going on there? Does your shit is
it how does it work? What's going on there? I'm having lunch. Is it takes the shit out of
your out of your body into the bag or what does it do? You don't shit it just
you have a slow IV drip out of dookies out of your body and the dookies go into
a poopy doo-doo poopy right ass you need to be cocked out dookie bag so it's easier
to be yeah you do poop poop poop poop poop poop poop poop bag and then and then you
give it to your friend as a prank when you're done yeah did you guys see that
video the guy farting into his grandma's oxygen tank?
It is so fucking good.
He just walks up to the tube.
It's like a big, like you know like the old ladies where they wear like the tube around
their nose?
He walks up to the box that the oxygen gets like recycled and whatever.
Just fucking farts right into it.
And then you see her in the living room, she just goes like
*cough*
That's dangerous, what if she gets pregnant?
*laughing*
Dude, it's so f*cking good
It's such a good thing
I don't find that funny, but I respect the elderly
Oh, I hate the elderly, dude, I do not have a good relationship with my grandma
Do you think if old
If an old granny
Could still produce milk, that it would taste better than a young one?
No! Are you kidding me?
I think an old granny might have that fire
No
no, no, no, no, no, no, it's not wine dude. Yes, she could make it to she could
make some sick cheese. Oh,
granny cheese
right that was that was the step to
Jesus. Would you eat granny cheese?
I think I would
I don't want to I don't want to think about that. That's disgusting. Why not
you go to the you go to like Costco and they have a sample of just cheese and
"Oh, what's this?"
The old lady who makes the samples is like, "Oh, I made that myself in the back."
She has like a machine that she's cranking.
I don't like this idea.
Okay, so the dog stuff is fine, but this is too far.
Dogs don't...
I don't have a dog.
What about a granny dog?
I mean, like an older dog might have better milk is my point.
I feel like it's the experience, you know?
It's like, you remember in that fucking Adam Sandler movie,
he gets his dick sucked by the grandma real fucking awesomely?
That's Yes Man.
That's Yes Man, and it's actually Jim Carrey.
I remember that-
That was one of my first dates.
First date I ever went on.
You and the grandma?
You and that grandma, and she fucking took her dentures out and slopped on you.
And I was in the sixth grade, bro.
I got my dick sucked when I was 11.
That is so beast, dude.
Dude, it's so funny when people like brag about that,
like old men try to like say that shit on like Facebook pages where it's like
what's like like those like horny groups that are like what's that like Cameron
joins and they're like horny ones I joined the I joined the cool ones well
it's the ones where it's like the the old guys are like it's like when did you
lose lose your virginity if it's like some old guy he's like my babysitter let
me eat her pussy when I was not good a really good Facebook post today
Well, it's like it was from it was like I figure what page was from but it was like what's the most like like unique yet?
Beautiful name for a girl like that. You've that you've encountered or whatever and there's one comment
That was like at the grocery store. I met the most beautiful little girl named Declan
It's like naming like a girl baby Doug. I think Doug is a fine name for a girl. Yeah
Honestly, I'm turning around on it. I think that is a great name for a fish dog Doug
First name for a girl middle named Heffernan last name ever. Yeah, Doug Heffernan ever
That's right last name ever first name dog
Doug Heffron.
There was another one that was like, "I met this woman whose name is Lovelin, but she
goes by Love."
Pretty cool.
Whoa.
Would you go by Love if your name was Lovelin?
I had an art teacher whose last name was Love.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Fucking stupid freak.
First name was Art.
Damn.
Yep.
Last name was Ever.
Wait, look at-- Or no, it's Love.
i just said to video
of the sky for did in his grandma's oxygen okay that's a great name for the
video to
and the fight quite for quietly in my granny's oxygen tank
ready three i don't want to use play she already watching it just so he looks
pretty sad already she'd
she had a bad life
yeah uh... so he opens this thing up
He puts a squeaker like a really thick squeaker in there and then she
Starts vomiting on the couch
That's a really great video Pat
There's a young man abusing his grandmother
Doing doing full jackass
Fucking fart mask to his own. How is it? Okay. Okay
It's funny in Jackass when it happens to Phil in April, so shut up.
But this is- I don't know this woman.
Me neither! I do.
That's my grandma. Oh, wow.
I just feel like that is a little too sexual to do to your own grandma.
What do you mean? People pay good money to sniff farts.
It's true.
Yeah.
Like, I would feel like I...
I'm done with you.
I would feel like I hooked up with my grandmama.
I'm done with you, dude.
What?
Why are you done with me?
You hooked up with your grandma?
I'm saying that's what I would feel like.
Caleb just admitted to hooking up with his grandma.
I did.
You guys have met my grandparents.
I would never hook up with them.
He hooked up with his grandma.
I have ugly grandmas.
They're not gonna...
I'm not gonna hook up with them.
And you're bragging about hooking up with them?
I literally am explicitly saying that I didn't.
You did explicit things with them?
No!
That doesn't make...
You did an explicit with your grandma.
You did an explicit remix with your grandma.
I'm gonna...
You were like, "I'm grandpa tonight, and I'm remixing your guts, grandma."
I'm not gonna remix my grandma with a fart.
You did.
I didn't.
That doesn't mean you do.
No, actually...
You turned her into Sprite Remix.
You turned your grandma's guts into Sprite Remix.
Yeah, you guys did that.
Nope.
Yep.
Caleb hooked up with his grandma.
I did not hook up with your grandma.
Nope.
Well, I did.
But only after you did.
You hip-hop fucked your grandma.
No, my grandmas aren't alive.
Mm-hmm. That's the point.
That's even worse.
Nasty fucker.
You're nasty.
Nasty fucker's what your grandma called you
You're a dead granny fucker. I'm not a dead granny fucker. My granny is ashes.
You're fucking her dead granny ashes, nasty piece of shit. You're fucking your live granny.
You sound like the, you got possessed by the exorcist. You need to calm it with the swear
words a little bit. You're a shitting a fucker you ass shitter.
I'd be a great exorcised demon kid. It'd be funny if the exorcist, yeah the exorcist
your face yeah the exorcist came out like 20 or 30 years earlier and she's going
like you crapper you you bastard you you son of a gun you're a dinky face to poop
poop crap head. You piece of shiz. You're a shizzle head. You eat your mother's poop. You
eat your mother's poop for breakfast. You're a see you next Tuesday you crappy little crud
head. You're a complete piece of crud. Get out of here I'm the devil. You ninca poop.
(laughter)
Oh, you scallywag, you get out of my--
You varmint!
I'm from H-E-double-hockey-sticks, you piece of crud!
(laughter)
You're a serious mother-lover.
You pinko!
(laughter)
You're Vietnamese!
yeah yeah we do that though we play it though lobster back you redcoat loyalist
loyal to the king are you yeah it's a spirit from the 1700s you know that the
revolutionary war was over you don't fight for freedom it would be funny to
just start calling like Catholic priest redcoats redcoat mmm yeah he's freaking
redcoats over there I fucking hate redcoats man yeah they're always taxing
my shit dude oh my god I'm getting me don't even get started on what they did
It's like, "Bruh, if you're gonna tax me, you finna better be representing my ass."
Yes, sir.
Like, "Bruh."
Like, "Bruh, I'd be saying that, bruh."
These redcoats are...
I'd be saying that, bruh, for real.
These redcoats are mad cringe.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Absolutely.
I've been saying that.
The lobster bacchety of this bitch.
[laughter]
True.
True, true, true.
True, true.
Amen.
And you know what else I hate?
I hate these damn Vikings.
Oh my god, don't, they fucking get in there and they start pillaging shit and it's like,
are you done?
Are you fucking done?
Really?
It's like, what next are you gonna do?
Oh, pillaging?
Is this what we're doing now?
I don't want to know what you're gonna do next.
Okay, we're actually pillaging?
I don't want to know what you did first in the two things that you're doing.
Because seriously, we're still pillaging in 1600?
We're still pillaging?
It's so, I mean, honestly...
Oh great, here comes Homo erectus.
You think you're so cool because you walk more upright than Australopithecus, huh?
Yeah, newsflash, Homo habilis already did that shit.
(laughing)
- Oh, he think he fancy 'cause he got two cells.
Oh, he think he hot shit 'cause he got two cells.
Okay.
You think just 'cause I got one cell,
you think I'm less than?
- How are you reproducing?
- Yeah, what are you doing?
Watch this.
I just did it.
- Now there's two of me.
What's up, what's up?
Oh he on land now.
Oh he think he too good for this hot ocean.
Oh no this steaming ass ocean.
He think he too good for it.
He want that land now.
Oh ok.
Oh he's an animal.
Oh photosynthesis too good for you.
Oh he think he too good for us now.
Oh he got reasoning now.
Oh ok.
Oh, he reasoning. Yeah. All right. Oh, he's self-aware. Oh, yeah, that's
Sapien sapiens
Don't ever forget where you came from though. Mm-hmm. That's a boiling hot ocean. Yep
One cell that's me. I'm still in the trenches. Okay, I came here on a meteor. Oh
He may eat thinking he from God now you ain't from the meteor, right
Yes sir. You ain't from the Corno Meteor. Yeah but pretty much that's what it was like.
It was basically, if Twitter existed throughout history, check for our book coming out on
Amazon. How about this, the bad dad's guide to if
Twitter existed throughout history. What about that? That might be good.
I can't wait. I mean we have some really good cover designs that are going to come out.
It's a picture of me, Caleb and Cam, and we're all doing like a snarky but knowing smirk.
Yeah, it's going to be pretty awesome.
There's going to be a lot of raised eyebrows on the cover.
Definitely, and a lot of raised eyebrows at our chapter about Chinese history.
A lot of ruffled feathers.
Yeah, we don't know, we don't speak Chinese. We don't take prisoners.
No. And we said some things that got people very upset.
I would like to get a, like, I would like for the podcast to get banned in a country.
Yeah, that would be pretty sick. Wouldn't that be great? Get banned,
didn't Odd Future get banned in like Australia? I think it's pretty easy to get banned from
Australia. I feel like we could do it. We should just like try actively to get banned from Australia.
I can't get banned from Australia. Why? I have to see you spider.
My girlfriend's family in Australia.
Well that's literally the perfect situation.
No.
Oh sorry I can't go hang out with the in-laws.
I'm banned.
They're an Australian.
Oh, I thought you were just saying.
That's an excuse for not going to Thanksgiving.
Sorry, I think I'm actually banned from your parents' house.
You're banned from your country.
Yeah.
I think I'm banned from that county in North Carolina.
I have to spend Christmas with my own family this year.
Yeah, sorry.
I feel like that's a pretty good excuse actually.
actually be great. Could be big for me. Yeah, what, Australia's the easiest one, right?
Yeah. What? Yeah. It might be too easy. I think, do people get banned from the Vatican? We should
get banned from America. Yeah. That would be sick. That would be pretty cool. I would love,
can we get banned from everywhere and just be on the run? Can we get banned from Earth?
I mean, we'd have to probably do like a humongous terrorist attack. We could try and extinct
humanity I mean I've been saying for a while that it I could I might just become
a super villain yeah yeah I think you know like I think that cuz like I they're
not gonna stop you if you just say like I'm gonna destroy the whole world right
yeah like that's pretty that's too general like they don't think that's
realistic but like I'm I'm like actually about it like I'm like creating weapons
on this destruction to destroy the entire world with a single party - yeah
I'd be down to like form a league with you. I mean I would I guess we could get like a big table and we could all
Sit around it. Oh, I'm see I don't know about spire could be good
Yeah, I don't care about the evil doing I care more about just like having a place to cheer like a tower to chill in
Well, I mean, you're not gonna be in the tower unless you like, you know
Well, I'm gonna do some stuff but it's gonna be you know, it's gonna be like minor evils
Okay, so you can be like a sidekick. Yeah, you can be you can be a I'm not gonna be a side
You could be called Boy Evil.
Actually, I like...
You could become a minion.
Well, how about... how about Doctor Evil?
You would love to dress up like a minion.
No, Doctor Evil's a...
Well, no, what if we have Doctor Evil there?
A high-rolling name.
What if we have Doctor Evil there?
Yeah, you could be Mini-Me.
Mini-Me would be a good fit for you.
Yeah, plus you're really small.
No, I'm not.
Yeah, you are.
What about, like, Patrick Evil?
No.
Evil Patrick.
Maybe, like, Boy Patrick Evil.
How about Little Patrick?
How about Child Evil?
*laughter*
How about Little Patrick?
Yeah, it's not evil enough of a name for a super villain.
Okay, Lil' Patrick.
*clears throat*
No, you're a henchman by the way, you're not a super villain.
I'm not a henchman.
You literally just said that you couldn't do the big evils and you would just do little evils,
which is like what the whole henchman job is.
Okay, then I'll do, okay, I'll do the biggest evil thing ever.
What?
I'll, I don't know, fuckin', I'll like, shut down, I'll put like a, a bike in the middle of an intersection.
You're a henchman. Henchman material. I mean there's nothing wrong with that.
If even a henchman, by the way, at that.
I put a banana in the tailpipe.
Maybe a grunt. You could be a good grunt.
Banana in the tailpipe of a van carrying a life-saving organ to a father.
That could be interesting.
I mean I like...
If maybe the father was like an important person in the world.
Yeah, the father would be like Gandhi.
You know who the father is?
Who? Andrew Cuomo.
Why does he have to be a father at that point? Like he needs to be the father of somebody very good
Okay
Stevie Wonder
It's a van carrying his eye new eyes that are gonna let him see for the first time but that like ruins his his art
which
Well, I guess that is evil. No, no, you know what it is. Go. It's a van
Driving the van to bring the ice to him to force him to see
Yeah, yeah true legacy. Okay. Well, actually their eyes
That make him even blinder. I would probably launch him into space and just watch him disintegrate
Yeah, that's a right idea
And I might I might even do that accidentally just as as
You know a casualty to doing that to a hundred thousand other people at the same time
Yeah, I don't even not even notice that I think Stevie Wonder was in there. That's actually isn't it weird that there's only like two
blind
Guys and they both play the piano
Hmm ever think about that Stevie Wonder and Ray Charles I
Don't you think I could think of I can think of five blind guys. Oh, yeah. No wait. Yo wait wait
I forgot dude you forgot the throat. Yeah the three-line roadhouse who plays okay? Yeah, so sick. There's six blind musicians
There's the three blind whites
Stevie Wonder the guy from right now. They're not musicians. They're athletes. They run. What are you talking about?
The three blind knights?
See how they run, see how they run.
They sing the song.
They sing in Shrek.
That's in Shrek.
That's a fictionalized version.
Okay.
Come on now, come on.
You know that's them.
You think Shrek really lives in a swamp in real life?
He lives in a fucking-
No.
He lives-
He lives in a fucking mansion, dude.
He lives in Beverly Hills.
Yeah, yeah, far far away.
So give me your theory.
Why do you think that there's two blind black guys who play the piano and that's it?
Why do you think that?
What is the cause of this?
No, I was just saying, I forgot about the blind guy from Roadhouse.
I didn't even see their race.
You didn't notice that Ray Charles and Stevie Wonder are both blind black guys?
No, I thought they were both blind guys, but I was blind before.
So Pat sees disability first.
Pat sees disability first.
A very...
He exclusively sees disability.
That's the only thing I see.
That's actually really brave.
And they can't see it, so...
I was waiting on that.
*Screaming*
*screams*