You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
Turn off that fucking Xbox.
There's deals. I can play Sonic Mania for free.
No.
I can play Super Mario Kart.
That's not free.
No, it's free. It's free play days.
I can play it for free for an entire weekend.
It's not the weekend.
pretty good deal. Super Monkey Ball. Sonic Mania is very fun. I like that game. I can
pull up the other controller. Turn off the Xbox. After. I want to make a Halo Forge. You
guys have to start bringing your Switch controllers over. No. Mine is in North Carolina. Mine
- Mine too. - We could play craps.
- We could play craps. - That's a board game.
- I got, oh, we got Civ 6 last night.
- Yeah, you got Hiv 6 'cause you have HIV.
- You have Hiv. - Six.
(laughing)
- Yeah, it's your initials.
- I have Hiv.
I just got the new Hiv 6.
I have HIV in six different ways.
- Six different places. - That's my impression of Patrick.
Yeah, I have HIV of the brain.
- Yeah, brain, left arm, right arm,
left leg, right leg, pinot.
I hope I don't get fucking...
You know...
That's probably the first place you get it.
Your Pinot?
Your Pinot.
Yeah, how do you get AIDS?
Yeah.
I don't know.
Well, we were just listening to a Limp Bizkit song.
That's how you get AIDS?
Hot Dog.
And he says, "Fucked up AIDS from fucked up sex."
You get it from real fucked up sex.
You do something fucking messed up when you're having sex.
Fucked up AIDS from fucked up sex.
Yeah.
And then he says, "Fucked up titties on a fucked up chest."
You know what it is?
The way you get AIDS is if...
You know how sometimes people say like to last longer in bed, like imagine like your grandma
or something.
Yeah.
If you imagine a gay guy, you get AIDS.
If you imagine AIDS.
That one slipped out of my mouth.
Thanks Patrick.
You really set me up for that.
Yeah.
Come on.
That's what you said.
No, you said it.
Patrick said that if you're gay, you have AIDS.
No.
You did, dude.
You wrote it on Notes app and you sent to me a screenshot.
You said that.
I sent it to Caleb on Whatsapp.
You did Whatsapp me.
Caleb doesn't even have a Whatsapp.
I know.
I should move to India and get on Whatsapp.
Get a Whatsapp?
Yeah.
Be a Whatsapp guy?
It's like the biggest thing in India.
It's big in every other country.
Really?
India's the biggest Whatsapp user base.
What is it?
It's just like texting for WiFi.
It's just WiFi texting and calling.
Oh, so it's like that free, that thing you would get.
It's iMessage basically.
Yeah.
used to get in like 2010 it was called like iFreeText message for the
iPod Touch. Yeah, where they made it kind of look like the iMessage but it
was like a little shitty and there's like always an ad at the bottom.
You're like I'm not fooling anybody when I pull out my iPod Touch at
school. They know I don't have a phone yet. It's also like ten times thinner. And having a phone was
such a status symbol when you were in like middle school.
- Yeah.
- It was like, yeah.
- I didn't have a phone until I was like 16.
- Yeah, I had a--
- Well, I had like, I didn't have an iPhone until I was 16.
I had like a phone for a year before,
so it's until I was 15 I didn't have a phone.
- That's a little late, I would wager.
- Hmm, yeah. - Yeah.
- I would say it's a little late.
- Wow, what age do you have a phone?
- It's crazy how that's a little late.
- I think maybe-- - You were a late bloomer.
You were a late fooner.
- A phone-er. - A late phone-er.
- Fooner.
- You were a late fooner, my friend.
You didn't have apps growing up.
I didn't have apps until I was...
I didn't grow apps until I was 16 or 17.
I did have apps because I still had an iPod Touch that I still...
You had apps as in TGI Friday's fucking baked potato skins, you big fat bitch.
I used to get those as a kid.
I'm sorry, I'm locked in.
Well, this is back when I wasn't fat.
It's a lot different.
You had apps like the celery on the side of some hot wings because you were a skinny little
bitch.
It's true.
Yeah.
What are you saying?
Flip phone.
I got worms on it.
He got worms on his damn phone.
He's putting worms on his damn phone.
It's crazy.
It was like a tiny flip screen.
Like this big.
Did it make it hard to use it?
Because you would squish all the worms.
What?
What is the cat doing?
Oh, he just fucking stuck his dick
dick in the other one's face. No, he just fucking jumped onto him like that. Yeah. That was awesome.
And his penis landed squarely in the mouth of the other one. Yeah. A little fucking gay wad.
I know, they're gay. Yeah. Yeah. That's awesome. It is awesome. Um, I cut off my fucking finger,
dude. Oh yeah. It sucks, dude. I cut off a huge chunk of my finger. Shut up. Yeah, who cares,
dude? Shut up. I'm talking about my finger. My cat looks awesome. No, he looks- Oh boy,
"My cat looks sexy!"
Shut up, dude.
We have to feed him a bunch now.
Take a picture of him and put him online.
Okay, go ahead.
And say, "This guy is like a monster energy drink to me."
Yeah, and have some fucking Washington Post reporter retweet it and be like, "These cats
are everything to me."
You fucking bitch.
I cut my finger off, Patrick.
Will you look at me?
I saw your finger.
No, you didn't.
Yeah, I did.
You showed me the finger.
Yeah, you didn't.
You were trying to do some Jon Favreau stuff, right?
You cut ginger.
I did, yeah.
because you thought it was ginger because it was all brown.
I didn't think it was, I didn't think my finger was ginger.
Your finger was brown from being stained from being in your ass.
No.
What happened was I was.
You were sitting on your thumb and your finger was.
Shut up.
I'm going to crush your cat's mouth.
No.
Your finger was so brown from your butt.
I'm going to destroy your cat on my ass.
I'm going to sit on your cat like a wrecking ball.
Your finger was brown from your butt and you thought it was a part of the ginger which is
also brown and you cut it.
You can't talk for five minutes.
No I can't.
I had a dream where my arm got crushed in an elevator and got really
fucked up and was like mangled. Was it like crooked? It was like, no it got really
thin. Yeah. And like... Your arm gets hit by an elevator and it just like shrinks. Well it was like thin and like fucked up and like...
Yeah it was like it was like the width of like one finger. Before we go on
this date, I need you to know I have a thin arm. And they were like we're
gonna have to amputate your arm and I was really sad in the dream. I was just like
I was like really upset and it was like a really emotional dream.
And then in the dream, I went to bed and when I woke up, my arm was just normal again.
I'm just like, oh.
Because I had just been like going in my dream, I just even going to my family and being like,
look what happened to my arm.
Like my life is ruined.
I can't believe this.
And it was just normal the next day.
And then you woke up?
And I woke up.
How many days did you live just with a normal arm?
Well, I just I woke up after my arm was normal.
I don't think much happened after that.
after that.
You looked at your arm and then you were like, "That shit's normal."
I'm sure other stuff happened, I don't remember.
Oh yeah, but I guess that is a dream story.
I cut my thumb off.
I also had another dream.
Oh my God, I cut a big chunk of my thumb off and I wrapped it and I have to keep the wrap
on for like a month.
It says, "My mom," because I didn't go to the doctor, but I can just feel just like how
much blood is pooling in this thing.
because it's still bleeding it's been like a day and a half. You can see it
bleeding through my bandage right here. Next time you see Caleb he's just like white. I can't see it.
Where? Oh there. Yeah I can see it. And I can just feel it like squishing around. It sucks dude.
I'm never gonna be the same. Yeah you are. You will. No I won't. You're gonna wake up tomorrow
it's coming back to normal. I swear to god. That's why I told my story. Yeah exactly. I was prefacing
I swear to God I was thinking, the fucking stupid part is I was thinking about, I was
cutting ginger and I was truly thinking about Chef with Jon Favreau and I was like, I swear
to God, my last thought before I cut the tip of my fucking finger off was like, I'm cutting
so fast right now and my fingers aren't even getting chopped off.
My fingers are completely fine.
Slice and I just thought I it's and I panicked that so I called my mom and I was like what
do you do when you slice part of your finger off?
She's like you need to throw the piece that you sliced off you need to put that in some
ice and then take it somewhere and they'll stitch it back on and then I was like oh where
is it and then I realized that in the immediate panic after I cut it off I just threw it in
the trash can.
(laughter)
'Cause I was like, 'cause my brain went into little kid mode
and I was like, I'm in trouble.
(laughter)
And I threw the piece of my finger in the trash can
and then I, and the trash can was full of coffee grounds,
fucking like vegetable shavings,
and she was like, find the piece,
and I tried for like 10 minutes,
just with my finger bleeding,
looking in the trash can for the other part of it.
And then I just gave up and I just wrapped it and went home.
- Went home?
Yeah, I was working, I was doing my nanny job.
Oh, okay. I was like making dinner.
I was making Herrera soup.
Damn. What is that?
It's ginger. Herrera soup?
Yeah, it's ginger, or it's onions.
You saute the onions, you add ginger, a Fresno pepper,
and some garlic.
You saute all that together.
You add spices that are like turmeric,
and cardamom, and cinnamon, and some paprika.
Is it an Indian dish?
I, in my experience, it's from their house.
but originally I've known the Indian they it's it's 60 Indian people yeah and they
live in one year you're taking over for grandpa's kitchen yeah cuz grandpa died
yeah grandpa died and I'm I'm the new grandpa you got a new grandpa now yeah
that's how you start those those vid if you watch those videos yeah just it's
just all right fuck it it's the best just fucking eat this shit you fucking
kids. This is McDonald's. I bought it for you.
Do you ever watch that guy...
Guga?
Not Guga. We've talked about Guga.
I watched a video last night that Guga made where he like took chicken bones and then he made like a creamy
breading and he just made... he called them Heaven's Chicken.
Heaven's Chicken. Ooh.
And it's just a bone. It looks like a... he just looked like he made a...
Cameron, pull it up. He looks like he made cartoon.
I like when he's like, "We're gonna dry age a shoe."
And then they dry age a shoe.
Let's do it.
And then he makes his like stupid, his like nephew, Angel is his name. He'll like set a
shoe in front of Angel.
Is Angel the older guy though?
I don't know.
Angel's the guy that...
What's the young guy?
The young guy is his kid. And then Angel is like his cousin.
Yeah, Angel. All the ones I watch have Angel.
Angel's the best.
He'll set a shoe in front of Angel and he'll be like, "So you want to try, how's it look?"
And Angel will be like, "Man, this is a shoe, man. I can see this is a shoe, man."
And Google will be like, "Well, give it a taste."
And he'll take like two bites of it and be like, "Did you dry age this shoe?"
Yeah, he's like immediately like he loves everything he puts in front of them.
Yeah, unless there was one where he did a...
Oh, the compound butters?
No, no, this is when he took a piece of Wagyu and he put it in like pineapple puree to like
tenderize it for like a week and he gave it to Angel and Angel was like, "Man, you fucked
this thing up, man."
It's really good dude. Guga Foods.
Guga. You are the Guga. You are the Baller of the Week.
You are the Guga of the Week.
You get the Guga of the Week award dog.
You fucking rock.
I've also been watching...
Do you see his channel, Sous Vide Everything?
No, but I want to see that.
He just sous vides everything.
Yeah.
That's the video he made the compound butters.
He took a Big Mac and then blended it down and into like butter.
and then he took like three to four different fast-food brands and then
blended them into like compound butter compound butter sounds like a like
Jinkum style drug from jail yeah yeah my man we were doing compound butter every
single night nuclear bomb just went on outside of it just went on somebody just
turned on a nuclear bomb right outside of Patrick's apartment hope no one
fucking crashed a car or something that just was the big it was a big dumpster
yeah it sounded like the dumpster yeah what was that well that sounded like a
dumpster it sounded like a dumpster being put a
waterfall but it's like it's nine o'clock at night there would be no
nobody's no throw away their trash it would make that sound wouldn't loudly
throw away their trash I'm with you Patrick it makes no sense it came from
that side it did not it came from right there no from the alley I didn't hear it
you didn't hear it I heard it from that side well your brain sideways yeah maybe
yeah they put your brain in upside down mm-hmm yeah oh man I'm fucking like
operation left all day today that's pimp dude yeah I slept like dog shit cuz my
fucking thumb I had to keep it elevated above my head said blood blood wouldn't
just squirt out of my bandage that'd be easy for me one of those liquid band-aid
Yeah, I don't know what that is. I don't know why not
I've heard my mom say I'm gonna I'm gonna have to figure out a way to take a shower
I'm gonna have to like put a condom on my thumb and then put my thumb in my ass
And then take a shower. Yeah. Yeah, it's gonna suck dude. That's why that's why you got your cut thumb
Cut in the monster that lives in my ass took a nibble
Yeah, dude, I got - I got too cocky I went too deep every straight man's ass has a fool
a fool proof second mouth, a set of jaws.
It's like a brown mucinex man.
Yeah, and he will, and if you put something more than an inch and a half in there just
experimenting in the shower with some shampoo.
Hey, what are you doing?
Get out of my hole.
And he'll take a bite.
Hey, you knocked the TV off the wall.
What are you doing?
You're not poop.
You're not food.
And then he'll eat you.
And that's what happened to me.
And then he'll, "You're not food!"
And then he'll eat you.
And that's what happened to me.
I stuck my thumb in my ass.
You can either be poop or food to go into his house.
The ass only understands poop and food.
Unless you're born gay.
Which, yeah, I'll say it.
People are born gay.
It's not a choice.
That's brave of you.
Thank you.
You're born gay, dude.
- Are you born gay?
- No.
- You mean to be born gay?
- Born to be gay.
- ♪ Born to be gay ♪
- That's an on, that would be a sick Rucka Rucka Ali song.
- Yeah.
- Born to be gay.
- ♪ Born to be gay ♪
(mimics guitar)
- That's not that, that's not what it does.
- ♪ Get your boys a suck in ♪
♪ Get your boys a suck in ♪
♪ Riding on the highway ♪
♪ Riding on a big dick ♪
♪ Looking for some gay sex ♪
whatever comes our way that line stays yeah oh baby gonna make it happen and
that also stays pretty much the rest of the song stays except yeah born to be
gay guys burn in there playing over over wild hogs just the John Travolta clips
yeah every time they cut to John Travolta the song splices into that song
and then splices back when they show the rest of the cast they show yeah it's
just John Travolta oh my god dude he's the gayest man on earth yeah man I call
him John revolting because of how gay dude I just I that's what I call him I
can't help it come on man I can't change it now battlefield earth no I feel like
talked about it no aliens yes like John Travolta's passion project yeah
Forrest Whitaker looks like whoopi Goldberg in that movie yeah yeah there's
uh yeah that was like John Travolta's like fucking there John Travolta has had
like two passion projects in his life I would say Greece and no no it's
battlefield earth and a little boy project his second passion is going to
masseuses and trying to get them to jack him off that's his project third passion
project working on it so he I don't remember when it was I think it was like
2012 2013 something like that in the world ended do yeah when the freaking
world ended the world ended because this didn't come out John Travolta was in
in charge of you remember the gummy bear like the Swedish gummy bear like the
song the gummy bear voice the gummy bear no in the 3d animated this is not a joke
he was supposed to he was supposed to add be the voice of the gummy bear him and
his whole family were gonna be in the gummy bear his whole family because his
kids his kids loved the gummy bear so much they were all his wife Kelly
pressed in. They're pretty young. Really? Yeah. He's like 60 something. I remember watching
that video on repeat. Scientology killed him. The Gummy Bear video, the production company
that was in charge of it just embezzled all of their money on like helicopter rides and
shit. Play is shit. Yeah. I like that. So there was supposed to be a Gummy Bear movie starring
John Travolta that never came out because they were just spending money on helicopter
Damn dude, that was a very sexual gummy bear.
Yeah.
I remember being grossed out when he did -
Dude, he shows like half his ass.
He does his butt, yeah.
And I was like, why is he doing that?
Can't he just sing?
And what if his ass is going crazy because he's German?
He has a crazy eye.
Yeah, because he's German people, yeah.
Somebody walked into the art gallery today with the most insane lazy eye I've ever seen.
Yeah.
It was awesome.
I had a math teacher who - I was in like - I had to get extra help for math and my extra
help for math teacher yeah very lazy I and I couldn't pay attention to any of
the problems because I didn't know which it's honestly so hard to be around this
people just until you get used to it yeah I mean like you know I never got used to
it oh well that I showed up every day for getting that she had a lazy eye and
just laughing all over again yeah fuck you yeah fuck that math bitch dude
She's very nice.
She fucking sucks, man.
Math teacher, I've never had good experiences with math teachers.
I told you guys about my crazy 6th grade math teacher, right?
There was this math teacher in my school, my middle school, who was Indian and her name
was Miss Kaushik.
And you can guess how that went.
Yeah.
That was tough.
People used to call her Miss Cowlick.
Yeah.
People used to call her Miss Crazy.
Yeah, Miss K, but with a K.
Miss Crazy with a K.
I also had an Indian math teacher, but I think her name was like Miranda or something.
Oh well, you know what they do with that one.
Yeah.
Mermanda.
I had an assistant Indian, an assistant math teacher who was Indian.
And she saw on the back of my phone case, I found a label maker and I wrote like poop boobs or something on it.
That's fucking awesome.
And I had like stickers that said like 420 and shit and I was like this is hilarious.
And then one day I just had my phone backwards and she was trying to help me with a problem
and then she kept laughing at my phone case.
It's pretty good.
My younger brother, the like really young one, he's like learning how to spell.
Yeah.
Kind of late, but that's a different thing.
He's learning how to spell and he found the label maker and he just started on like everything
in the house.
Like he just writes random shit and puts it on it.
I was looking at this I was like trying to staple something and I looked at the
stapler and it said poop mom poop this crap crap dad yeah yeah minecraft - it's
it's awesome dude it's a paradise it's pretty good I wish somebody would rename
stuff that I wish I had minecraft yeah my house - I think is the microwave the
best game in the house. Minecraft is... Minecraft is sort of a game. It's true. Yeah, it's got
buttons. Yeah, it's got buttons. You put a lizard in there. Somebody told me a story
about someone they knew put their hamster in the microwave but like... Oh, God! But wrapped
it in tinfoil first. So they purposely were like I'm gonna destroy it.
They were like really little and they were just like oh that's what you do when
you put something in the microwave. And then I salted him with gunpowder.
I told you guys about my math teacher, my sixth grade math
teacher right? Is this the same story the third time? No. I feel like you've told
If you start it with, "I've told you this," right?
No, you told us about deluxe hugs. Yeah.
Yeah.
Have I said it on pod? I don't know.
No, I think you just told us that at Ryan's house.
Oh, yeah, that's right. Yeah, I had a math teacher who was clearly like an old pep.
Go on. Go off.
Cameron, take notes.
He used to say, "Fresh slice of paper," and then lick his lips.
We all thought he just had dementia, but it was like you can't just be around kids and have dementia.
Why?
And still not teach, because he had to teach a math class.
So?
Was he bad at it or something?
No, he was really good at math.
Exactly.
That was the problem.
Well, that's the... I feel like he's a great teacher then.
He would say penis M&Ms on purpose and he would lick his lips when he said fresh slice of paper.
Fresh slice of paper thing... you're not building a great case against him as a pedophile, dude.
What? Oh, I told you about the deluxe hugs.
Accusations of pedophile, deluxe, you didn't explain that though.
Oh yeah, that's true.
You just said deluxe hugs.
You know, the deluxe hugs guy.
Oh, so he, well I can't really explain, never mind.
You can't stop explaining.
Yeah, so he would grab kids by the, this was his deluxe hugs, he would grab kids by the shoulder.
And then he would go, like he would put his head on their-
Talk into the microphone.
He would put his head on their right shoulder, then their left shoulder,
then stare at them like in the face and go...
And stick his tongue out.
Do a frog lick?
Hey, do like a frog lick like near their face.
And that's what he gave kids at the end of the school year.
To me, honestly, that is less like kind of weird than just any long hug.
Yeah, that is less pedophile than a hug.
I think he invented the deluxe hug so that he wouldn't actually hug the kids.
Oh, well, I mean, he's not...
So he would keep his temptations down.
Avoid his urges.
Exactly.
Okay.
Yeah, and also, you know, licking his, you know, putting his tongue out of his mouth,
it's not that crazy, he does it when he thinks about paper.
You've already established that.
You know what I mean?
Like it's not, he thinks of these kids, there might as well be paper to him.
Yeah.
You know?
So I don't know, I feel like he's not a pedophile, but maybe just sort of a monster.
A cool guy.
Yeah.
A cool guy to hang out with.
A cool guy.
So you guys wanna, you guys wanna hang out with me?
Yeah.
I want a deluxe hug.
to do a deluxe hug to both of you yeah yeah we could do it at the end of the
podcast we could do some deluxe hugs we gotta teach all the fans how to do deluxe hugs
if you're a patreon member we will post a deluxe hug instructional
yeah we'll do a how-to deluxe hug yeah we're gonna hire an old old man
I'm talking fucking so old he doesn't even know that we're paying him less than
minimum wage yeah and we're gonna make him make this video and guess what we're
gonna get mr. steel your damn cat yeah mr. steel yo damn cat we're gonna deluxe
hug you mr. he's gonna edit it mm-hmm and he's I movie it's crap yo damn cat it's
funnier if it's mr. steel you grab your damn cat grab your damn cat what's why is
he grabbing him cuz he has a grabber that's right and what's he gonna do yeah
it's called a stealer steal the cheez-its from the top shelf with it no yes she
didn't she did with that why is that your checkmate because I'm smart got you mr.
steel yo damn cat is a man on your name grab you mr. grab you shut up two
different guys yeah no oh now that's your damn cat sounds like he's gonna
have his grab he's just wants to it's a catch-and-release yeah
grab it in the grabber exactly shake it around thinks it's funny when he puts a
cat in his thingy yeah but the mr. Stelio damn cat who comes out at night when
he's had a couple too many Sapporos
he has a big Santa sack for the record he's an old Chinese man he did then he
takes your cat some poros yeah Chinese Japanese dirty knees what are these you
know I'm saying it's what he says that's what he says that's how we knew this
Japanese and what are these he doesn't do anything with his eyes yeah so we
understand he says that to every cop yeah he does well we can't book him well
we don't know if he's Chinese or Japanese we have no idea where to start
he distracted us with his dirty knees and he said look at these and we looked
and he ran away. Just doing that to a... I don't do that to a...
A Boston police officer, one of the brave men in blue who are out there fucking...
Stopping the Boston bombing every day.
Yeah, dude. That's... And then, yeah, one slipped through the freaking cracks.
And now we have to disrespect all Boston cops.
People have been trying to do that bomb every day for 30 years.
True.
And two fucking... Two hot sauce named fucking weirdos get it through.
What does that mean?
Doesn't that sound like a, you know, kind of hot sauce?
Jokar Sarnaev does not sound like a hot sauce.
Sarnaev sounds like a sort of like a harissa kind of sauce.
No.
You're an idiot, you're an idiot.
Neither of you know anything about -
Sarnaev sounds more like a -
More like a Boston bomber.
It sounds more like a guy who bombed the Boston mossomer.
The Boston mossomer.
Sounds like the name of the holiday -
The Boston gossamer.
Yeah.
The Boston bossomer.
Whoa.
I'm the Boston bossomer.
I'm the boss of bossomers.
What did you hear?
Did you hear another?
The Grinch's goose.
No.
I heard the Grinch's goose is going to be in Boston.
Are you serious?
For the marathon.
With Grinch eggs.
No.
He's going to leave Grinch eggs on the sidelines.
Grinch eggs are one of the most disgusting things I've ever seen.
They smell so bad.
They smell like stinky piss.
You crack that thing open, green eggs.
eggs and Grinch what do you think the ham is it's oh my god it's Grinch no it's
roast beast that he's stolen from no no the green exit well is the ham green -
no no hams normal okay the ham is always normal it's green eggs and regular ham
actually I don't remember I think it's green ham - yeah it's not hard to make a
green ham though I mean well if it's made out of Grinch meat yeah do shit
this guy fucking dr. Seuss was obsessed with green he was obsessed with the
Grinch and Japanese people yeah those were his Grinch mm-hmm this is funny we
talk it for at least 10 minutes every episode about the great I talk it's such
it like I I mean I have to stop myself more than 10 minutes dude the Grinch is
like all I think about now I my boss caught me the other day in the art
gallery just talking myself saying Grinch stuff she's like you see the
great you have to switch locations you have to go to the other gallery and I was
like yeah sorry I was thinking about the Grinch yeah dude um it's a man I have
Grinch brain dude it's like Epstein brain but like way worse because it's
about the cringe is so much just a much worse thing to do to a kid is steal its
presence exactly yeah I feel like I never I don't know that I'll ever get presents
again mm-hmm you know doesn't that worry you guys live in friggin fear isn't that
a thought that runs in your brain all day every day yeah you I won't get my
present I might not get presents this year this might be the year I finally
stopped getting presents I might just get a bag of items I think I was oh no
Yeah, cuz here's the thing about the Grinch. Uh-huh. This Santa, if you're bad,
he still gives you coal. Yeah, you can fuel your house with that shit.
The Grinch, doesn't matter if you're good or you're bad, you get nothing. That's true.
You get nothing, dude. Nothing. Because he Grinched out in your house. I might get--
He takes the coal. Okay, but I might get like candy or something. Not if the Grinch has
his way I could hide it the great I could hide it from the Grinch you couldn't you
know he has a great vision dude no you're right you cannot 100% more
powerful yeah but I could still hide it no you're gonna Grinch grind what about
a Grinch crime Grinch grind what about what if you were indicted on Grinch
crimes mm-hmm Grinch crimes against the press the
Prince to grind down to 12-steer crap nice yeah doing the grit the Grinch
You should invent a new trick called the Grinch.
Yeah. Did I send you guys that GTA 5 mod with the Grinch?
No.
Do you guys think the Grinch is a spirit or a ghost or something else?
The Grinch is a guy. Let's be clear.
I watched that JayStation video where he downloads a Grinch from the dark web or where he buys
a Grinch.
He calls the Grinch.
The Blue Grinch or the Grinch?
Did you watch the whole video?
No.
apparates Harry Potter style into his living room and steals his girlfriend
in a green cloud of smoke. So that made me reconsider. He might be a spirit. It made
me think he might be a you know he might even be a poltergeist. Yeah. A polter
Grinch. He could be. Might even be a Grinchergeist. Oh man. Yeah. A Grincher
guy. He might be a Grinch Christ. He might be. That's a terrifying argument. Oh my god. Grinch
Christ yeah it's just in green slime but with green slime yeah it's terrifying
that'd be the worst they should crucify the Grinch we will crucify the Grinch
yeah when we find the Grinch and we compromise him to a permanent end he
will be crucified like like they did Jesus Christ what about like they do
you know other people say like eat the rich eat the Grinch oh see I don't think
think the Grinch would have I met the Grinch he's black. I met the Grinch he's green and mean
and he hates presents. Do you think he where does he put the presents is he like
comp is he compost? Oh doesn't he eat them? I don't think the Grinch eats the presents.
I don't think he eats the presents. The Blue Grinch eats the presents. I'll tell you that the Blue Grinch eats the presents.
So the Blue Grinch and the Green Grinch were separated at birth yeah you know and
the blue Grinch - Don't even get me started on the pink Grinch - The pink Grinch is the
girl Grinch and she has humongous pink breasts - It's either the Grinch's - From what I've
learned it's either the Grinch's sister or his girlfriend - It's both - It's both
because in Grinch, in the Grinch's fucked-up brain that's okay - Yeah and it's
actually good - That's how fucked up these Grinches are - That's how messed up these
people and I use people very lightly - Grinch-est - Are - Who? They're who's - They're who's, no the who's
are also not people though because who's are a dog elves that's true they live in
a snowflake they live in a snow yeah so that's the crazy thing though good one
Patrick the Grinch great Patrick that's you're doing great
do all right Caleb yeah so the thing is that's so terrifying about the Grinch is
that he can obviously change sizes. We know that he can be both sort of an
atomic sized Grinch in the tiniest Whoville nucleus of a snowflake, but he
can also be an enormous human sized Grinch because I've seen him. So I guess
what's scary about that is that if he can change that much, we don't know what
the ends of the spectrum are. Maybe he can go quantum like Ant-Man and he can jump
to a time where there were no presents. Well that's how he got here, he's from the
future. He's from the future like Ant-Man. Yeah. And he jumped into a quantum time
loop to stop presents from ever being invented. And he keeps failing. He killed baby Santa.
He went back in time and he killed baby Santa dude. Well it didn't work though. Yeah
because I mean history will rewrite, history will always rewrite itself.
History has its eyes on the Grinch.
That's what quantum theory is.
History is written by the Grinchers.
E=MC2 is about the Grinch.
E is...
Evil.
M stands for man-like green creature.
Man-like creature.
And then 2 is the
numerical number for green.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
Because a green...
We don't need to explain.
it actually mathematically numerical.
- It's hashtag, G-G-G-G-G-G-G-G-G.
- Exactly, which all stands for Grinch.
You think it stands for green, it stands for Grinch.
What came first, the Grinch or the green?
- Probably, probably the green.
- The green, yeah. - Probably the green.
- It was the green.
- It probably was the green.
- It was from the future.
- I think there were things green before the Grinch.
- No, it used to be-- - What about grass?
- Grass used to be--
- Grass is part of the Grinch that fell off and--
- Grass is Grinch hair.
- Yeah, it grew onto the planet.
- Oh my God, that's one of the most terrifying.
- He came back, he's from another planet as well.
- He is very stuffed.
Yeah, he's also from, he's from space Grinch 9.
- Planet Grinch.
- He's from Grinch X.
- Grinch X.
- Yeah, which is a, and it's shaped exactly like his head.
And it just flies through space
at an unimaginable speed towards Earth
and we never know when it's gonna hit.
- Never.
- But we will blink out of existence
in an instant when it does.
- It's gonna steal the, oh my God, oh my God.
he came from the future to steal the present
world
for
uh... that's why i was here that came from the future to steal the present
dude
that we got a whole my got a call about a career-packed all
we do we have to call marjory action
we do have to call marty mcfly is the only guy who can get to the future and
get the grant guys is not answering
uh... all right well i guess i went to the hotel doctor who are you a flyers
been diagnosed with Parkinson's. Come on.
Yeah, that's a real guy man. We're talking about the freaking Grinch right now.
Bringing in this guy who has Parkinson's. Fuck you man.
Do you think if they did make like a Back to the Future 4, do you think that would,
do you think they would write that into Marty Fly's character?
Wow, the future is so shaky. They would put it, it would stabilize him with a video camera.
They would do the video stabilization on him and everything around him would shake.
Whoa, this is an earthquake 24/7 in California in the year 2080.
Yeah, it's time interference Marty.
Yeah, yeah.
Why is everything so shaky?
Well, let me tell you, a little president in the 2015's named Donald J. Trump.
Yeah, that's right, he made the world shaky and now Marty McFly.
With his fat ass.
Yeah, his big fat ass.
He's been walking around the White House so much that he caused a fucking, he caused stalactites
to happen.
(laughing)
Forgot the word for tectonic plates
and I went a different direction.
- Donald Trump put a bunch of stalactites on the ground.
- Donald Trump sat on a stalactite chair.
- In the year 20XX.
- Good thing of stalagmites.
- They're both, no, stalagmite is a bug.
A stalactite.
(laughing)
A stalactite is an evil sword
that runs from the bottom of the ground.
- And sure. - Because water,
here's the thing about stalactites and stalagmites,
they'll make no goddamn sense.
stalagmites, or stalactites I understand.
It's water dripping off of the cave or whatever,
the erosion makes it go.
- Yeah, but the ones that go up.
- But the ones that go, wait,
you tell me water went upstairs?
- What?
- I think-- - It's probably magnet water.
- Oh.
- And the top of the cave is a magnet.
- Yeah, and it's as a, yeah, and it's magnetized water.
- I think it's just because of,
the earth turns around, so.
- Would you drink the water if it had magnets in it?
Yeah.
Discuss.
Yeah, I would.
I would be afraid because I take a lot of lead supplements, I would be afraid that they
would be attracted to the water.
Would you ever eat a magnet?
I would eat a magnet.
Yeah?
Yeah, for like 60 bucks.
I would eat three magnets.
You know like those ones that you--
For free?
Like the rattlesnake magnets where you like put them, you throw them in the air and then
they go and--
Yeah, just like a rattlesnake.
Yeah.
on the inside of your stomach and then put the magnet on the outside.
That would be pretty funny. Yeah. That would be some funny ass bullshit. Okay.
I think people would like it at least. I could probably go to different
like malls and be like check out this magic trick and they'd just be like
oh nice dude you you glued the magnet to your stomach. No but then I would move it up and down.
And they're like oh great you have a sticky magnet. Yeah and I'd be like you've...
I you guys need to believe me I need to get a new job and you can just hold the
magnet that's when you're legs and it'll pull the pull the other one out of your
ass all right nevermind I would pull a magnet out of my ass no problem
what if we get like dermal piercings right yeah I know you learned about
this yeah we get a subdermal implant yeah right here of a magnet of them
Right where it's like a metal stomach. Yeah, and then you put like a
Magnet and then we can get like big magnets you can put them on it
Whoa, what if you got a giant hook on your back so you could hang on to a telephone pole and swing around?
What if you got a light bulb installed in your chest like Iron Man? Mm-hmm, right?
What if I do anything but it looks cool if I go good fly?
What if Cameron could fly?
If Cameron, if you could fly, I would totally send you to the store to get me some French fries.
Yeah.
Right now.
Oh, damn.
Pat threw away his French fries.
You did? What now?
I didn't know. I didn't know when you were gonna get here.
You threw away some fries, man?
Yeah.
Before I got home?
I asked Cameron if he was gonna eat them.
I already ate French fries before I got here.
He said he already ate French fries and then I asked Dominique and well, they were her fries.
And she said she didn't want them, so I offered them to Cameron and Cameron said no.
And you were like, "Those are the two people I know."
Those are the only two people who were here.
Those are the only two people who I'll see tonight.
I couldn't feed them to the cats.
Why?
I don't know.
Yeah.
Cats can have potatoes.
They should put on a little beef anyway.
No, they are, dude.
Look at Yoda.
Yoda's like getting big.
Yeah, has he been going to your cat gym?
No, he's just been feeding them a lot.
Yeah?
What have you been feeding them?
Food.
What kind of food?
Dry food.
Cat food?
Yeah.
Why don't you go wet?
Oh, you got both.
Is it because sometimes they like to change the opposite treat?
We give them wet food for dinner.
Oh, that's what I eat for dinner.
Yeah.
I only eat wet food for dinner.
Dry in the morning, wet at night.
I'm the opposite.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I have wet, I have...
Wet breakfast?
I have wet drinks and dry drinks.
I made my wet breakfast today.
Yeah.
Wet breakfast.
I had wet breakfast this morning.
Oatmeal?
Cereal.
Damn, I want some cereal right now.
Yeah, you know what would come to my house to eat my cereal?
I like healthy people cereal. I like like grape nuts and shit.
I like Raisin Bran. I love Raisin Bran. I like any bran cereal.
I like bran flakes. I like those bran tubes.
I don't like any kind of cereal. No? You wouldn't even fuck with a Lucky Charms?
No, that's the worst. That's my least favorite. Patrick loves Lucky Charms.
I hate Lucky Charms. Pat loves Lucky Charms.
They make fun of my people. You call yourself Irish?
No, that's a mockery. No it's not. It was created by the leprechaun. Lucky the leprechaun.
He beats the kids every single time. Is that so embarrassing? Yeah, Irish people beat up their kids.
They don't beat the kids, he outruns them. It says Irish people are way
are faster than any kid alive. Lucky the leprechaun is the same as Chief Wahoo.
Yeah. Or that picture of that Jewish guy rubbing his hands. Yeah.
Yeah, Lucky the Leprechaun is Aunt John's mascot.
Yeah, the Jewish guy rubbing his hands, Ronald McDonald.
We're living in the Lucky Leprechaun era, said like the Jim Crow era.
Yeah, because they're sort of the same thing.
Yeah, the new Jim Crow is Lucky the Leprechaun.
Yeah, that book's about Lucky.
Yeah.
The whole book is about being a--
The entire thing.
I haven't read it yet.
Just know.
No, but I'm pretty sure it's about Lucky the Leprechaun and how it is an absolute mockery
of the Irish people.
I don't know what else it could be about.
I mean, that green suit, that's just a classic fucking...
Shamrock on his hat, fuck you.
Yeah, fuck you, dude.
It's funny how many Irish people you see with the shamrock tattoo.
Oh yeah, my uncle.
My dad has a shamrock tattoo.
Your dad has one?
God, I'm so glad I'm not Irish.
He's got a shamrock and then he's got his... my dead Nana's initials.
His mom.
Nice, which are?
And then N-A-B.
P-Y-T.
I think, wait.
N-A-B.
Naboo, Naboo. Oh my god, dude, you're Star Wars-ese. No, then I don't know what the NAB stands for cuz it's not my
That's what he said about his mom no, yeah, he said he's got a bit he's got like the barbed wire
Tattoo on his barbed wire. I back barbed wire tats
Humongously, he's that's the uncle who got in that car accident. Oh, no, wait, we weren't
Huh, we weren't friends then. I don't know my first semester at Emerson
he got in like a very bad car accident. Whoa. Yeah. Is he live? Yeah. When? Epic win.
Epic win for sure. I told you. That's a victory royale if I've ever heard one. I think I told you
about this. But I hadn't seen my Nana or my grandma since I was like 14 and then
like I saw her for the first time in this hospital room and she just looked
insane. Uh-huh. And she like they were trying to like tell us like oh like he
like it's gonna be a couple weeks but he's gonna be like good and everything
and then my grandma was like talking to me and she was like have you heard this
Harvey Weinstein stuff I would not let him go near me with his penis that's so
funny dude it's funny how I just weird that case keeps getting yeah just over
he's got a he's got a he's got pussy for balls now he has a pussy ball sack pussy
dude yeah awesome yeah yeah pretty cool no because you know if he had pussy for
balls yeah you know he would have he would have just been he's been going to
town just well he wouldn't even gotten to the point he was making movies yeah
dude if I had a pussy installed next to where my shitty balls are dude I would
have been that would have been just a game I would have never I would have
ever played a video game I would have just done that all day just fuck my just
bend it down you know every time I get a bone it pops out so I have to fuck myself soft
pussy on your thigh and then you put your balls in no see no no no you want
it right underneath because again then you have to you have to bend your penis
and that like a Christian did what yeah that's what I like the new Christian
things he installed a fucking pussy she installed a pussy on her leg no under her
her. Chris Chan cut a hole.
Whoa.
Oh my God.
When I was a kid I saw this episode of House where like somebody has a kid that's intersex
and I looked at my taint and I was like oh my God I'm intersex. That's a vagina.
You think because like all people are.
Did someone just assume your parents didn't like know?
Well no, I thought they knew but the--
They just, every time they changed you,
they looked away like, "Ahh!"
So in the show,
the kid--
Seeing a baby dick is fine,
but a baby vagina...
No, but I--
In the show, the kid is like
13 or whatever and he's having some health
issues and they reveal that
he's intersex but they chose
to make him male by sewing
up the vagina and so I looked at my taint and I was like they sewed, there's a clear line,
they sewed the vagina and my balls were like, I mean it's like a Neapolitan ice cream gradient
and it's my dick, my balls and my pussy.
And turns out it wasn't true though.
I've been a guy since day one, baby.
Neapolitan ice cream, god damn.
Yeah, it was disgusting.
I do have a pink penis and white balls and a big red pussy.
That you're missing the brown. And a black pussy, is what I meant to say.
Black ice cream?
[laughter]
The greatest
Atlanta comedian ever.
I'm black ice cream. You all have a great night. Black ice cream. Yeah there was already a guy
just named ice cream. Yeah and he's like damn I guess I'm black ice cream now.
Remember ice cream shoes? Ice cream is also black. They're both black. Two black guys
but one's black ice cream. Yeah. I black ice cream I think I've had
like a squid ink ice cream or something it could have been that it could it was
something black though what's black what's a liquorice it wasn't licorice
and it wasn't like dark chocolate was like pitch black yeah yeah might have
been a gimmick thing my friend you so no Noah he's working an ice cream shop and
he would just bring me ice cream all the time
father's poop it was father's poop is black vial that falls out of his ass
Yeah, so when you take Pepto-Bismol and you take too much of it and you poop black.
Does Pepto-Bismol make you poop back?
Oh, yeah.
Really?
Because of the bismuth?
I almost...
Oh, I took...
You keep saying bismuth at me, I'm gonna smack your ass.
I don't know what that means, man.
Quit looking at me and saying bismuth and shit.
There was like a week where I just had really bad stomach problems and I was taking Pepto
And then like they stopped but then I like took a shit and it was just like dark black.
Yeah, just an evil shit.
Dark black?
Yeah, it was like a Darth Vader poop.
Vantablack.
I took a nighttime shit.
I took a Vantablack shit and all the light in my bathroom went to my toilet.
It just, it turned off the lights.
It's like, yeah, you just hear the plop and then it's just dark.
Yeah, but I was sitting there.
Where am I?
checked it and then I like Dom was over and I was like Dom I need to go to the
ER right now. She took me to the ER and then they did like a I don't remember
what they did but then they put the shit I think they did I put the shit back in
you maybe you poop it back yeah I didn't have to make a stool sample but they did
tell they asked me like oh have you taken like any Pepto-Bismol and I was like
yeah like a lot and they're like that's what it was that's gonna be $400. Are you a
hypochondriac? Yeah yeah. I thought I was allergic to weed for four years.
You thought that there was a car crash when the garbage can closed. Yeah that's
that's the same. That's the same thing as a hypochondriac. Patrick went to the doctor for the black
shit and they sliced open his butt and they just put vanilla in and then vanilla
ice cream up his ass vanilla syrup I've never had the pod but my brother has a
poop dream whoa he has had a reoccurring poop dream since he was like five years
old where my god he's in like a he's on an operating table and like a like it
looks like the Saw movies uh-huh and like his butt falls off and poop starts
shooting out like a pitching machine.
That's one of the most terrifying dreams I've ever heard.
He told me about it because I guess one night he woke up screaming and my mom
ran into the room and he was like she was like what's going on what's going on he
goes the poop dream!
Like she knew and he was fucking.
God damn. I've been having some of the most amazing shits in my life recently.
Just A+ dude.
Oh, I've had the worst.
Just like a quick, like not too quick, because I used to sit down and it was like a, like
somebody got like a question wrong on Nickelodeon and it was just like slime just falling.
And just out of a big bucket.
Yeah, and it's a really fast worm.
It was exactly, yeah.
No, no, because it was always, it was like a two year span where I shit liquid every
single time. Yeah. And it would just explode like a like fucking bird shot at
my ass. It's terrible dude. My toilets always, I had to like clean the toilet after every shit.
I went to the doctor and she was like, I think you probably like, there's it's like 50/50 chance
you either have like E. coli or stomach cancer. So I need you to like do a stool sample. And she
like gave me the things and then I was like. You sprayed all over the car? No, I was just like,
I don't want to fucking shit in this. So I left. Damn. Yeah. But I'm fine now. You know,
know my shits are pretty yeah what if you when I was on Adderall I was just like I
don't yeah it's fast worm a fast worm yeah they never have any a soft fast
worm I never saw her took like a worm just like zoom a zooming warning us a
zooming snake oh my god I really felt shit's trash the graces body such a
shape of trash but it's brown but he didn't even they even need to eat it's
like a soda can made of shit. Could you imagine the smell of a Grinch shit? Oh my god. I don't want to. It probably
smells good actually. No. Because human shit smell bad. The Grinch smells bad. Yeah but the Grinch
eats trash. So. We eat food. Food smells good. He eats rotten banana peels. Yeah that probably smells good. I saw Jim Carrey do it in the movie. No. He is a rotten banana peel.
Remember that's in the song. So what is the what's the primary Grinch like sort
like canon source. What's like the primary text of The Grinch? Is it the movie?
Book.
You think it's the book but the book doesn't provide enough things.
No, there's not enough world building.
I would say it's a - it ranks like this.
Jim Carrey movie.
Animated movie that has the famous smile.
Yeah.
Book.
And then Halloween is Grinch night.
No, no, no, and then the 3D movie.
What is Halloween is Grinch night?
- You don't know that? - You haven't seen that?
- No. - It's like this like...
- It's one of the craziest. - Yeah.
- It's dude, it will make you feel like you took acid and went to the Grinch party.
- Yeah, which is I would never do that.
- I would never go to the Grinch party in the first place.
- We should...
- Let alone do acid in the...
- We honestly, we should do a smoke weeding watch along of the Grinch.
- That's probably, I mean that makes the most sense for our watch along.
- Me and Cameron hate smoking weed.
- Yeah, I will freak out.
- I will freak out too, but I will freak out.
- I will freak out too.
I will freak out.
I will freak out too, but I'm willing to do it.
I'll do it.
Just because I think in that scenario I would freak out and just be like, I'm just watching
The Grinch right now.
So I think we could do it.
Yeah.
We keep suggesting movies to do watchalongs for.
I think that's the obvious one.
I think Grinch is the obvious one.
Yeah.
And we have to, yeah, because we have big Grinch plans coming.
Oh yeah, we sure do.
We can't tell.
That's still locked up in the vault.
Top secret Grinch information.
Yeah, that is between us and The Grinch and God.
Me, you, God, the Grinch.
The Grinch killed God.
The Grinch climbed up to heaven on a big green ladder and he stabbed God with a green Grinch
sword.
He disemboweled that big white man.
He disemboweled her.
The Grinch killed God and she was black.
Both of them.
Yeah, both of them.
Both of them she was black.
There's two gods.
I just heard that the Grinch drew a picture of the Prophet Muhammad.
Alien vs. Predator vs. Grinch. Who wins?
Grinch.
The thing is, in this version, Alien and Predator
are made out of presents.
Grinch already won. I hope that.
How about Grinch vs.
How about Grinch vs. Evil?
Obviously the answer is going to be Grinch, but Grinch vs. Grouch.
ooh no hold on cuz Oscar the grouch yeah you seen grouch land it's like a Grinch's
paradise and grouch grouch Oscar lives in trash they have to be granted seats
trash Oscar the Grinch it's just we mispronounced it from Sesame Street
people it's people have been think it's Oscar the Grinch but it's really Oscar
the Grinch people just haven't been saying it wrong okay well so he's a
Grinch? Because he's not the Oscar the Grinch. But he's not THE Grinch. Well yeah I mean he's Oscar the Grinch.
The movie's called The Grinch though. Exactly so there's one Grinch. Well there's
the Grinch and there's Oscar the Grinch. That'd be like calling the movie like the Chinese
guy that's like... Yeah or Ip Man. What's that? You don't know Ip Man? It's a movie
about the Ip Man. The guy who invented IP. Yeah he invented, he I-vented, he I-p-vented
Kung Fu. He invented chop suey by system of a down. The bye-bye man invented saying
goodbye. Yeah. That's why he's so scary. Yeah Mr. Meat invented the hamburger.
Mr. Meaty? Mr. Meaty from Nicktoons. Yeah. He invented the hamburger. Mm-hmm. Yeah,
that's true. Well he said in the song, in the theme song, it says all God's
creatures fresh off the grill. What else did he invent? He also, he invented
the he invented the uh... world's biggest toilet
once you take the
when she the biggest hamburger you're gonna want to take the biggest shit and
so it'd be built a big toilet just for that
it's true for you talking about what are you talking about man
nothing mister me
mister mister watch mister meeting you know that that claymation shows no
response
was is it
grew is creepy looking yeah okay uh...
now you're getting a hand
the acting i think the grinch movie we have to do a watch a long present a
permanent only thing i have the other all scary yeah
the only thing what
is that available on streaming
well maybe some
now on you to go to the fuck about mister meeting with a great deal of
interest in but it's a different grinch
i think we could uh... yeah i'll do this on netflix on no that's the benedict
bomb to tell you what i will pay three ninety nine to rent
Well, what I'm thinking about more is just other people.
True.
It's annoying for a watch-along if we're gonna make people.
Well, if we watch, we should upload it to the Patreon.
Pirate the Grinch.
Just the whole movie.
And watermark it with a podcast logo.
And then we could just put the audio on the movie.
If we record ourselves in front of a green screen.
That's actually a really good point.
We could do Grinchery Grinches Theater Grinch 1000.
Grinch tracks.
- Yes.
- Grinch tracks.
- Yeah, 'cause we put us in the corner.
- Let's just watch all the different Grinch movies.
- Okay.
- And do Grinch tracks.
- We'll do a Grinch track for it.
- Is there, yeah, there's a, wait.
- There's three Grinch movies,
plus Halloween is Grinch night.
- I think I've seen part of Halloween is Grinch night
now that I'm thinking about it.
Is there like a lot of yellow in that movie?
(laughing)
- Dude, I don't know why I'm remembering it like a dream.
Yeah, I'm remembering it like a dream.
- Every time anyone brings anything up,
Patrick is like, "Oh, was that the thing with the shapes in it?"
Yeah.
I think I know what you're talking about.
Was that the Super Bowl where she showed her boob?
I remember that vividly.
Me too, because I remember we watched it on TV and then my older brother was like, "You
want to watch that shit again?" and he brought me to the computer and we watched it like
on YouTube or whatever.
Yeah.
Whatever, it wasn't YouTube.
No, it was not.
It was something like that though.
But somebody had uploaded it already.
It was called like MediaDrink.com.
Yeah.
No, no.
It was back in the day when like liquid video every every video had its own website
Yeah, it's a Janet Jackson's boobs calm and you could just go to that and it would just play that video
And there's the only thing on the website. It was like meat spin. Yeah, the same thing happened at the Super Bowl
Yeah, when when they did meat spin it. Yeah
Yeah, and it was and that's that was when that viral moment was born and then she blew off old the audience. Mm-hmm
Yeah, there was I remember that night specific my uncle Kevin as soon as he fucking pulled the thing off my uncle Kevin
Stood up and screamed
That's a titty. Oh
My god nice, yeah, so that's when I learned the word titty. It's my uncle Kevin screaming it man
that's a win is what that is that's a win for guys feel cool Kevin damn uncle Kev
uncle Kev Jumbo uncle Kev my uncle Kev Jumbo we miss yo ass uncle Kev Jumbo you were the
best you're the best on YouTube yeah you were super good on the amazing race you
and your dad your friend I'm not gonna say his name but he made ninja song the
ninja song how to be gangster something Higa uh-huh just said just a horrible
name looking back on it can't believe he has Nigel Higa I I don't know if anybody
I know we're closing up but I don't know if anybody we're closing up the shop I
don't know if anybody listens from the patreon lives in Boston but if you do
come to laugh Boston on the 20th I have I'm roast battling Tom O'Shea this fuck
just happened something fell over my vacuum fell down that's fine I think a
car crashed in Patrick's apartment car crashed in your closet dude yeah me and
Tom O'Shea former guests of the podcast we're gonna be roast battling each other
we're gonna be duking it out he's uh he's taking over he's taking over the
open mic yeah so if you also live in Boston come to the open mic come to
Wednesday's at a burger restaurant in the basement yeah you're gonna love it
But yeah, Caleb used to host it.
That'll be fun. I did use to host it.
I used to host it as of this week.
I'll never host it.
Cameron will never host it.
Ben hosts Mondays.
If you keep asking me to host it, I won't host it.
You guys keep asking me to host it, I won't.
We're gonna ask him again as soon as he presses stop.
I will not host it.
If you pay $50 a month to this Patreon,
you can become the new host of The Open Mic.
Honestly, that's fine with me.
If you live in Boston
If you live in Boston and you are a part of the Patreon and you give us more than $10,
you can become the new host of the Wednesday Mooyah Mike.
Yeah, go for it, man.
Go fucking crazy, dude.
You're going to want to...
You're going to have to fight Tom.
You're going to have to tell Tom that...
Yeah, that's the other part.
You have to duel Tom.
Yeah, he's also a patron.
Old school cowboy style.
I don't know if he'll listen to this episode.
He definitely won't.
No, he supports us out of the love from his heart.
What a great guy.
I love him.
I can't wait to rip him to shreds.
Yeah.
He's gonna get some. Although I don't want to make you do any of your material just in case he listens.
Oh, no, I won't. But let me just tell you something. His dead best friend's making a couple of appearances.
So you might want to come out for that.
Mm-hmm. Bye everybody.
Yeah.