Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
- Premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Okay, so if you just heard the other one,
the other episode. - If you listen to the other,
the last, if you listen to the normal episode just now.
- Yeah, I just got a message from my girlfriend.
She said the DMNFQR trains are delayed
and they're searching those trains.
but listen it's been say that out phonetically
demon fucker
this year in fact this shooter was the demon fucker kinda like he's a constant
teen mhm
i really hope something really horrible happens in the news to a p_s_a_
scumbag
perfect time capsules the uh... you know just full-on like
so one towers been hit kind of thing the uh... you know
it is weird
that
we are back logging all this
we could say anything can happen in the next couple weeks
we could say like we know it's the other way around that we say something that
will have already have a that some things are going to happen
well no that would only be good if we were that we're doing it now that in the
opposite any episode we say something's going to have this is this is the only
episode we can't say that because it will already have happened by the time
d_c_
because we're courting and then release it later time moves because forward yeah
What? Yeah.
You look really confused.
So it's like okay imagine today. Imagine today is April. I'm going to eat a grape
on
August or no.
I mean you can still say that.
No. Trying to predict.
I'm going to eat a grape. No, wait. No.
You could make that come true. I mean we could say we're going to do anything
and then do it. On
- But that's the thing, April--
- It won't have been already happened,
it won't be your turn.
- On April 20th, I'm gonna smoke some weed.
That's my prediction.
- No you won't.
- Damn, that's coming up.
- April 20th?
- Oh my God.
- April 26th?
- You're gonna smoke some weed?
- A week and a day.
- Holy fucking shit.
- On April 26th, I might have to pay a bill.
- Wait, when does this come out?
Hold on.
- Wait, so April 20th, what you're gonna say--
- We have to do a special, if this is a 4/20 episode,
but no.
no the last one we recorded was the 420 episode no no it literally comes out on
420 that's the other shoe dropping fuck dude Wow all right all right well hey you
know we got to make up for lost time I can't believe that this is the 420
episode now I guess you got so high we recorded the fourth we got so fucking
hustled that we messed up our 420 episode we are at we're on story time
Yeah, so what are you stoned on me? I'm on runts. I'm on I'm smoking Red Bull green dragon fruit nice
It's literally this if it's not cold this tastes exactly
Like air freshener, I'm smoking crudders demise. This is what I'm smoking
No, it's just like a fist tastes like I don't care what it's like we're talking about what we're smoking
I don't care what red blood tastes like plus your can is green
What are you doing? Don't pour it on the mic. Why would you do that?
You're not that high. You're only
100 pounds of weed you're not that high
It's really not that much. Oh my god. All right, so that kind of charged me up. I just smoked devil's destruction
Yeah, yeah, you guys ever smoked red weed
You have you guys ever smoked AIDS red weed does the opposite of green weed really?
What does it do makes you on high so if you get too high you can?
I need to smoke some red weed right now, because I am higher than a mofo.
Not me, I'm so high, but I'm going to smoke blue weed that makes the -- that
just changes the effect. It's not like an opposite, it just kind of goes like
side. Well, like if red weed -- if your high level goes up and red weed makes it
go down, blue weed and yellow weed make it go from side to side.
What is your high bar at right now?
About ten perillion.
Yeah, mine's probably around the same.
Sorry, I'm so high, I said a number that wasn't real.
I'm so high, I'm just speaking --
Ten billion, I just made up the number ten billion.
Look how high I am.
Damn.
damn Pat is high as hell wake up wake up buddy got weed to smoke I'm so high just
thought about it what damn I so hold up yo hold on I just smoked too much the
limit I just get so Pikachu is a mouse he's a rat
rat uses what electricity think so yeah well done this room I'm so high I just
can't stop thinking about this wait hold on hold on wait so squirtles a turtle
squirtle squirrel turtle that's a squirrel turtle blur blue
he's squirting he's a squirting turtle hold on does a
twirl even squirt so Charmander's a mander but he's charming wait I'm so I
guess I think about Charizard is a zard how come but he's charring a zard he
can't char that zard don't char that zard charmellon no no cuz I'm here
watermelon. Hold on. Yeah, I got like I'm thinking too much about this
mander because I smoke some Bulbasaur. Yeah. Yep. Pretty much all Pokemon could
be weed. Yeah. Especially grass types. Especially that Mr. Mime.
Mr. Mime. Smoke types. That's who you see. You see Mr. Mime if you smoke too much
weed. Yeah. You see that guy he's like you know that one guy who thinks he's
trapped in a box he smokes one joint. If you smoke if you smoke weed that was in
when your your your your high school dealers back pocket that he sat on all
day while he was feeling his mass,
has a on the you smoke it. That's when you see Mr. My yeah, I found weed on
the ground at a skate park one time and I brought it home and I smoked it and
my eye immediately got itchy. That was dirt and I learned later that if we
looks like it has crystals in it or something that means that it's like
moldy. So I smoked moldy weed. We used to smoke so much K2 and we never even, we
didn't even know. And the reason why was because it was all like pre-ground.
Like it was not real weed. It was like pieces of paper with K2 on them. And the
guy would just sell it to us in a giant Ziploc bag. And it'd be like $10 for like
a pound of it. It was awesome. It was great weed. I never like knew, I would
like to me it's just like oh this it's weed I didn't know there could be
different types of it or it could be bad or good yeah whatever I would just buy
I buy from my friend who got it from his friend who got it from his friend who
got it from his uncle or something yeah yeah I accidentally smoked K I have a
picture of me on it high on K2 because I got scared and I sent my brother a
picture of me I was like 15 I'm looking at the camera like we need to do we need
to smoke salvia that's what we need to do yeah 420 special okay I go
They have Delta 8 at the bodega.
Everything's the same.
Everything's completely normal.
Except everyone hears a fish.
What if you smoked salvia and now this is a bit of a high thought so bear with me.
Smoke salvia, nothing changes.
You live out your whole life.
You're on your deathbed, you're holding your wife's hand, you're holding all your children's
hands.
You have a hundred children.
You die.
The trip ends.
That's happened to me.
Then you're back to where you were starting.
That does happen in salvia.
Yeah, what I know, but it's like a high thought, so it's like crazy. Oh my God
isn't your only high for like five minutes. I mean, I think that for like
ninety seconds that happens in salvia, but in if you would also be like a
wooden barrel or something well, I remember re shafir smoke salvia on a on
a podcast one time and there's a video of it and he smokes like and then he
smokes it just falls asleep and he wakes up. He's like put me back put me
back and apparently he lived a lifetime as a fish. Wow that's what I'm saying you
live a lifetime, but you live a lifetime as like a g mod prop hunt
exactly just like like smoothly sliding along the ground as like like a tv
cabinet yeah yeah just try not to be caught by your friends. I feel like yeah
if you did this, I mean obviously I would probably change your brain forever
in a lot of ways, but if you do salvia and you become a tv cabinet or whatever
go home you look at your TV cabinet you feel like I feel like you just have an
understand you probably gonna make love to it did probably I would probably have
to get rid of it I probably would not want to look at that dude if I I don't
know I would hate to become my penis then I don't think I could smoke it's a
salvia I don't think that I could smoke poison I think I could smoke salvia
anthrax no I would come to like you know I would like come to like I would come
- You can't jump to it.
- Outside.
- You don't move, you can't, no you wouldn't.
- You can't move?
- I mean you can but you--
- Well you can jump out a window but you can't go outside.
- It seems like you have like one good burst of energy
in you when you are on Salvia.
'Cause you don't hear, nobody's like going crazy
and like killing people on Salvia.
- I would.
- Because you just have to--
- You know my ass.
- You're really confused and you get one big,
you can either do a jump, a leap, or a back flip.
And then otherwise I think you're pretty stationary.
- I could do a back flip.
- You could not do a back flip.
I think I could do a flag round back flip.
I think I could. I don't think either of you could. I think I could do one. I think for
me it's all just a mental thing. Pat's getting up, he's going to try and do it. He fell on
the ground. He didn't even fall. He couldn't even fall. He fake fell. I got scared halfway
through. That's what I think. I think anyone can do a backflip. I think it's all just fear.
If you only use 10% of your back. Imagine if you could use 100% of your back. I'd probably
be what I probably be like at least six feet tall. Probably be the hunchback of Notre
Dame. No. I thought with this guy this guy had a big back so we're supposed to be
terrified of this guy and he's a scary monster just because he's different from
us. Yeah. I don't think you're supposed to be scared of him. I think you're supposed
to want to fuck him. You see him and you're supposed to vomit and scream because of how disgusting he looks.
You're supposed to want to fuck that guy. And it's just because he's different slightly different.
It's just because he has a disgusting protruding spine. His grandma was the hunchback of Notre Dame.
My grandma did. Don't say that about Katherine. You were saying it. No, she had, I didn't say
she was the hunchback. I said she had a hunchback, okay? And I used to ask her if I could-- The
hunchback of Caleb's life. I used to ask her if I could hit it really hard and make her
tall. And she said no. Yeah. You should be able to do that. You should be, yeah. It's
like smoothing out a carpet. Say I watch videos of a chiropractor doing that shit to people.
He's just like breaking kids' necks and shit. So funny, dude. I went to a chiropractor when
I went to one too.
That was the best I've ever felt.
I was in chiropractic.
Immediately after that.
You know that like all the time they like rupture people's arteries?
Yeah.
It's like constant.
So funny.
Oh dude, chiropracting.
Chiropractic.
It's chiropracting is not an honest profession.
Anybody who does anything to your body who doesn't have, it doesn't have ologist in their
name you have to kill them.
Definitely.
Yeah.
You can't let them.
You can't have an opologist.
Zoologist.
What?
I want to hear what you're saying about a zoologist.
They could give me elephant ears.
They can't give you elephants.
Have you ever looked at an elephant's teeth?
No.
I didn't even know they had teeth.
So elephants have their incisors or their tusks, but then in the back of their mouth
they have all molars.
I want to be inside them.
And you put food in their mouth.
I saw Myrtle Beach Safari, they throw a peppermint in their mouth.
I want to be inside them.
And you put food in their mouth.
I saw Myrtle Beach Safari, they throw a peppermint in their mouth.
I want to be inside them.
And you put food in their mouth.
I saw Myrtle Beach Safari, they throw a peppermint in their mouth.
I want to be inside them.
they throw a peppermint in uh... the government
i think i forget his name is a normal size peppermint normal size peppermint
they throw it in this elephant's mouth and then he eats it you can hear like
even on a peppermint
you know i have a permit small
what
elephants have to go and other food
even on a peppermint
it's a little story is that the elephant to the issue
elephants have all molars
that is a gap most at most herbivores have all of molars that's the point
given that all molars
yet incisors are you know they have a like nineteen sets of teeth in their
life
i think her peppermints
and and and they'll even if they have a very well if you need some even a
a peppermint even a peppermint has to be actually they're afraid of peanuts and
mice they're not afraid of peanuts they love peanuts they love peanuts oh sorry
Patrick sorry you weren't in on our jinx no I'm trying to find the video that no
Oh you're looking up how to be jealous.
Bubbles.
What idiot would ask if an, of course an elephant has teeth.
There's great big flat teeth.
Awww.
Yeah, great big flat teeth back there.
Yeah, have you ever seen an elephant skull?
Okay, so I'm seeing this but...
He said it.
He didn't even chew.
He just swallowed it whole.
He did not chew at all.
Even a peppermint.
He didn't chew the peppermint!
It's a she.
It swallowed the peppermint.
...teeth back there are used to grind everything up.
Even a peppermint.
You also use...
You can see it swallow it!
I like that you said the exact line from the video.
[laughter]
In your head you were like, "Even a peppermint."
Even a peppermint!
You said it out loud.
Even a peppermint.
you listened and you didn't watch the elephant just fucking swallows it it
grinds it down here it goes. That's him swallowing. He gulps. Here you wanna hear me chewing?
I just chewed a hamburger. Was that a peppermint? No it was a hamburger.
Let me get your teeth checked. Even a peppermint. Even a peppermint.
That was like your closing statement. That was like I'm cinching this.
honor there yeah they're not I can tell I can tell they're not with me even a
pepper even a peppermint has to be chewed by an elephant due to its large amount of
molars in the back of its mouth I learned that I learned that this weekend
you learned that in fucking elephant court yeah what is that that is so for
that I feel time what is it Oh uptime white peach lemonade has other natural
flavors it's basically a mental physical energy drink with natural caffeine and
L-theanine. Let me see what that is. You think you're about to touch this? I want to look at the can.
Why? There's a new energy drink I don't know about I need to see. You haven't had Uptime before? No.
It's bomb. Yeah? They put it with the health drinks instead of the energy drinks. Oh,
that means, yeah. So it's like celsius. Yeah, it's definitely, it's like...
How they put celsius, oh 142 milligrams of caffeine.
It's not intended for children. Nothing. And those sensitive to caffeine. Not intended.
pregnant or nursing women. That's what it says on all those though. Hmm. I don't know. It does.
I don't know. I think it says it twice on all the other ones. It would suck to be pregnant.
We're talking about pregnant. I would hate to be pregnant. Can you smoke weed if you're pregnant?
Yeah. Yeah. Do you drink alcohol? Oh, this says Angelica root extract. Your baby will be born
wearing a damn drug rug though. That's right. Cameron, they have Angelica root extract.
Remember her from college? Oh my gosh, she is. The baby will be like, "Pass the bottle to that left
and side past that bar to do that left and side said a go go go go he'd be
going like
yeah
the three little birds would probably be the ones that are on his mobile yeah
yep he'd probably probably be a rock by baby in the on the palm tree top. You
know he'd be he'd be born. He's he'd be crying like this. Why one
and you know that baby would shoot the sheriff. Yep
And you know he'd make boom boom
Yeah, boom boom oh my god, I don't know my I made but I didn't want to get into what colors and patterns his diaper would
Be uh-huh tell you what that basically be red green and purple
Purple the different colors are strains of weed
The red dragon the green dragon and the purple monster and the baby's name would be smoker. Yeah smoker delightfully
smoky the stoner
That's what happens if you smoke when you're pregnant if they like detect it on it when they're if they detect it
when the baby's being born they take the birth certificate away from me like
sorry this baby has to be named smoker this baby's name is well first time into
the ultrasound well let's take a look well it's got a heartbeat it's got two
legs toque Tatum ma'am he has a joint in his hand yeah everyone's got a joint in
their hands let's go I would have joins every and every view found out that your
baby was gonna be in a stoner would you emergency Lee abort him yes yeah I might
If I found out my kid was gonna be a stoner I'd start drinking.
If he's gonna be a stoner he might as well also be a...
He might as well have schizophrenia.
Yeah, he might as well be a mutant?
If I found out my kid...
What does he do?
If I found out my kid was gonna grow up to do like Jason Mraz guitar music...
Oh my god, I fucking hate guitar music.
I would...
I like it.
Like the...
Yeah, like...
I know you're trying to demonstrate it but you're just like...
- Oh yeah.
(laughing)
- I started hitting my chest like the, yeah.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, my bad.
But you know like the guys that do like the drums
on the guitar?
- Yeah, I know what you mean.
- Yeah, they like make the videos in like the Boston Common.
- You know the guys that make the videos.
- I would probably become a scientist
and I would find the cure for Alzheimer's
so I could put the opposite into their DNA.
- Yeah.
- Like the guys who make those songs,
like the stoner guys who make like the songs
songs that are about like love or whatever but then they sing it like
"Baby I'm at your house, I'm coming to your house and I'm gonna sing to you baby and you're gonna ML"
V-neck t-shirt, V-neck t-shirt, circular hat, circular hat, like a like a neff beanie
but like it's on the back of their head and it looks like a condom reservoir.
It's like falling off.
Oh my god.
"I even love your mama, and your mama nice to me, come on baby come on down to the store with me we're gonna go to the
- Yep.
- Primark at the Boston Common.
- They'd have the V-neck shirt and you can see
their brand of sacrifice on their chest.
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh my God.
- Yep.
- It's fucking disgusting.
- And they take a video.
- Those are the worst kind of guys.
- Yep.
- Worst kind of guys are like Jason, Jason Mraz.
Remember when Jason Mraz, he got caught cheating.
He got caught cheating by his wife.
He was like, no, no baby, I'm too spirited.
- He wasn't really playing the guitar?
(laughing)
- He got caught cheating by his wife
tried to like explain some like like the Native American term for like bisexual
tour. He got caught cheating with a man. I don't know. Or maybe he just thinks
bisexuals two damn girls at the same damn time. That's what he says. Listen brother, no hate.
Remember I remember I found out about Jason Mraz because he was the musical
guest on Mad TV one time. Really? Yeah. I found about it because he had the
pink. He had the big song on the radio. Hey Jason Mraz how about a taste of my ass?
Yeah, dude. Yeah, I think I hate him so much. I hate his music so much, but I like your racial pizazz
You're a white boy swag. Mm-hmm. Yeah
Is a good is a good musician racial pizazz Rachel pizazz, yeah
Gigantic goes Rachel possessed
We should yeah, I wish you big boobs. Yeah. Yeah, two big-ass bongs. Did I just say that?
And no big-ass thongs. Ain't no panties on this bitch
Sorry guys when I smoke weed I get fucking horny as hell I can't even fucking lying
All right, you guys look like two humongous pussies to me. Yeah, I fucking love pussy. I smoke weed
I smoke weed, I just ape. I roll up the weed, I ignite the fire. I wish weed tasted like
puss. I wish weed... Because I love the stink smell of stench. Oh my god, I got the freaking
carpet munchies. I love the stink-stellin-sminch of a stinky puss. Oh sorry did I just high
that up? Yeah because I'm so fucking high. I'm fried like an egg right now. That's right.
that's the and nothing on so i'm seeing nothing on blind that's squelching
squirting wounds not
what is that whole
i love i love all my god
i was sorry what
did i just heard a lot
as a result of my shit that is shopify my words all my god
all crap upgrade that sexy splattering wetness regard split you with his black
blade me up
yeah yeah my god's got the ice my smoke we don't have an in-depth statement of
I'm driving in there like a clown into a swimming pool on circus.
Yeah, I'm climbing a ladder first.
I'm two feet tall.
I need your butt to do green graffiti on my tongue.
All over my mouth.
Green graffiti.
Oh my God.
A little bit of green squelchy belchy.
Yeah.
Nasty.
Just kidding.
Nasty ass tongue.
I like it.
You know what's good to me is actually smoking a bunch of brownies that I have.
Damn, you all think about graffiti and you think of Banksy, I'm thinking of Banksy back
shots.
Yep.
Mm-hmm.
Oh my god that air, I smoked that dude.
Hotboxing the backshot air in a plastic bag.
Ooh.
Wetboxing.
Dude, when that backshot air smells like checkers and rallies, you know I'm checking her backshot
out at a rally and I'm saying this smells rally good.
Yo, I'm blowing O's with her backshot smoke until I blow an O.
Uh huh, yep.
Speedy's big oh my god. Yeah, I'm blowing. Oh, he's all over the place
I'm splotching my
squirmer mm-hmm
I'm sweetly sniffing her. I'm gonna blast plaster mm-hmm on her asser
They gotta like is me and then there's a little guy on top of my shoulders and he calls me blaster blaster plaster
They call me "Blaster Plaster"
They call me "Cooter Shooter the Diaper Sniper"
Yo, I'm fixing to drink a stinky tincture from our sphincter
*laughter*
They call me "Blaster Plaster Blaster" and I'm getting some Thunderdome
Oh my god
When the back shots make your pee fizz like cola
Mhmm
Her brownie looks mad edible to me
When she gave you gonorrhea
*laughter*
for real. Oh damn ain't nothing better than getting chlamydia from a hoe.
Getting chlamydia from Lydia. Oh my god dude.
Gonna get the clap from Scott Stapp.
Getting the clown from Scott Stapp. No. Oh getting the clap from Scott Stapp. Don't be crass.
Sorry. Come on. Hold me now.
My dick seized. Fucking busting my nust.
After smoking that green dust. I wanna fuck a penguin.
yeah when I get so hard their meat is those penguins those penguins heard
that yo those penguins making my mr. popper we really need to make a scene a
sequel to farce of the penguins yeah no I'm gonna be good as shit yeah that's a
high-ass movie to watch oh my god here's some fucking penguins doing this high
Hi, hi is fucking the crib watching Planet Dirt.
(laughing)
You like misclicked the streaming service somehow
and accidentally.
- You're on beef, I'm on beef flicks.
- Beef flicks watching Planet Dirt.
Dude, beef flicks has good movies though.
- Beef flicks is got mad good originals on it though.
- Oh my God.
- They got like Planet Dirt, Planet Squirt, Eating Raul.
- Yep.
got uh they got Jackie change the whole Jackie changes movies yeah I got all of
Jackie changes movie oh my god yo it's crazy he can just change into whoever
did you guys see 20 jump straight with Chang Tatum on there it's a good as hell
and drew new hill Johnny Hill mm-hmm Chang Tatum and Johnny Hill and they're
like huh you know how they be and nice what and nice pube is on it too yeah
dude nice you nice pubes like and I want you to have sex with my daughter mm-hmm
yeah I'm nice pube mm-hmm and then they say and then there and remember that
see where they're like let's all watch planet dirt and they say who has a beef
flicks account I'm still you I still logged into my you know you know when
Can you share in a beef with your see that new name pop up yeah? That's it. Oh
who's who's who's doctor crazy
who's a hacker
you log into netflix says it would you like to be Caleb or doctor
you go to doctor doctor hacker just like how to hack yeah.
documentary continue watching how to hack hacking 101 hackers delight the
crazy world of hacking only watch this if you're a hacker and planet dirt and
planet dirt well that's we should make planet dirt I'm down there's there's
millions of crumbs in this dirt there's billions and billions of billions and
billions of crumbs of turds all over the dirt one million probably you probably
think this is dead. Me too. It's dust. A million turds and a billion thoughts. BBC2 I'm Michael
Pedophile. For BBC2 I'm Michael Pedophile. I'm gonna watch the Jimmy Savile documentary this
week. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah I think I finally. You're gonna get inspired? Yep. What to be famous? Yeah.
Yeah. It's so funny he had a show where it was just like I'm gonna fix all these kids lives. He
He was like pimp my ride with a child's body. Yeah. Yeah, he was doing pimp my ride to like little kids with leukemia
But like he was like, oh you wanna meet Madonna? I can introduce you to Madonna
Mm-hmm as long as you don't tell anybody he was saying me donger. Yeah. Yeah
That's why he don't got such a crazy accent. Yeah
yeah. Oh, meat pop star. Did you guys see the concert they just added to beef?
Meat Donga. Meat Donga live from my square garden.
UB7 was weird sauce though. Yeah. He was kind of normie. He wasn't normie. He was
Chewy as hell.
He, his outfits were mad herby.
Yeah, he was a herb for sure.
Yeah.
Jimmy Savile, you were herb.
He was one of the herbs.
Speaking of herbs.
Oh my god.
Don't even get me started.
I could go for 11 of those and some spices.
That's how high I get sometimes.
I actually eat fried chicken.
Yeah.
I get so damn high.
Fuck dude.
Yeah, I get so high starting chocolate cake off the kitchen counter.
Oh my god, don't you hate it when you get so high and then like you realize you're doing
the Bruce challenge from Matilda.
Bro, I get so high starting in my shoes by accident.
Sometimes I get so high I eat an entire lunch to myself.
Werner Herzog actually ate that shoe because he was high as hell.
Yeah.
Werner Herzog ate a shoe?
I am so hungry right now.
Did you see that movie he made about the- I am so hungry.
I am so hungry.
I have the munchies from smoking pot.
You see that documentary Werner Herzog made about that high guy?
Yeah, the Twizzler man?
You say Werner Herzog?
Yeah, it burns the Herbzog.
Burner herbs off.
Burner herbs sog.
Yeah, I made the damn Twizley man.
The Twizley man has gone.
He's in the bathroom.
Never listen to this tape.
You should never listen to this tape.
I'm so hungry.
Oh God, I need to eat some chicken wings.
Yeah, he's like, the tape is like, "Yo, why are they called Starbucks?
Is it because they make so much bucks?"
Yeah.
Never listen to this tape.
Their bucks can stack to the stars, is that why?
He accidentally recorded over your mixtape.
Wait, I haven't seen Grizzly Man.
Did they put the tape of the guy dying in the--
Yeah.
Really?
He listens to it.
But he says never listen to it?
He tells his wife to never listen to it, the Grizzly Mans.
My mom let me watch that when I was six.
Wait, the Grizz--
Wait, I thought--
My mom showed me Grizzly Man.
He died with his wife.
The Grizzly Man died with his wife.
No, his wife was not a bear.
No, it was him and another lady together.
Nope.
Yeah, I just read about this the other day.
Yeah.
never seen it. I don't know I can't tell you. He doesn't know what he's talking about.
The grizzly man. He picked up his phone to look it up and then he put it back.
My mom thinks that everywhere in New York is my neighborhood. Yeah. So that
fucking train, little train pedophile that shot everybody. Don't start spreading
rumors about the guy. He just killed people and used gas. I thought he did that
because he's angry about being a pedophile. He's a scarecrow. Pedophiles
are not angry about being pedophiles. They like it. They love it. Yeah. That's why it's
pedophile it's a like why don't they just stop yeah what pedophiles like how
hard is that to stop this everybody pedophiles are terrorists yeah both like
chill yeah like how it's easy not you and you're hungry have a Snickers yeah
we got Jimmy Savile of Snickers you wouldn't have done that crap you're
probably started sucking on it yeah he's Willie Jimmy Jimmy Savile each one
Snickers he turns immediately into Arnold Schwarzenegger. He turns and becomes American
immediately. Thank you for giving me that. Yeah well Jimmy Savile that's the thing he should have
moved here they wouldn't have caught him because the cops or whatever they'd be like he's talking
he wants a little willy what does that mean what's that must be some British candy or something.
They don't know what that means. They would hear him say the British word for pants and they'd be
be like oh yeah we yeah we don't like those either yeah well he would be like
he'd be like I like when a child has it's it's his pants on and they think oh
okay he's not a pedophile actually shines that a child is pants on but pants
his underwear in the UK is it pants is underwear trousers his pants so he'd
actually want the child in their underwear they would have no idea and
he'd be like yeah I like I like sucking a child's Willy through the pants and
they'd be like oh that's fine the pants are on and I don't know what you're
saying that you want to eat the candy out of a kid's pocket yeah to the camera
yeah I want to eat the candy out of a kid's pocket Jimmy you crazy you crazy
is he not funny. You're the funniest nonce we know the whitest nonce you
know.
Silent gay yeah yeah.
Kno nce oh my god. I'm gonna get water you guys keep I got I got uh yes.
Oh dry mouth got some cotton man got some cotton mouth.
I can't even fucking lie bro. Yeah the way the future the way the future's going
nowadays it's pretty soon you'll have robots in mouth
while
now
uh... highest fuck
i'm highest fuck i think about robots
a ghost is moving his microphone all my god is mike's moving look at that
well it was just moving it all my god
it stopped when he came out
the microphone what the microphone needed to go to him it's like a jet as
lightsaber you think they'll make a robot slots we can find
from the movie robots
big fat aunt with a big ass. Everyone went in the aunt's ass to sneak around.
Yeah what is up with that movie dude? I was like this beast dude.
Yeah. What if in Robin Williams like suicide note it was just like oh I didn't
want to be in robots they made me be in robots. Robots was actually one of his
his dream projects because he was often called as a child robot Williams because
of his name is it so he was kind of reclaiming the robot name-calling yeah
remember when he says is there's something new on his hand nobody looks in
the camera says there's something new on my hand I love that I love my new hand
yeah I just got a new hand and there's new shit on my hand yep my hand is he
says that's new my head is the new thing I'm looking at my hand be looking like
this mm-hmm remember when in in the wedding ring remember when finding Nemo
when they call that boat they call it a a call off an asshole yeah go finger that
asshole yeah this is you fucking stupid fish it's called a boat you stupid fish
yeah I turn that movie go finger that asshole yeah it was any most dad is like
where's my kid and then Dory says oh yeah your kid is on PP Sherman yeah Wallaby
Way kidney stone kidney stone the ocean is full of pee she says that yeah she
interrupts herself and realizes the ocean is full of pee I'd be pissed off I
was a fish drinking my pee all day I think they like it mm-hmm I think I was
is Dory. I mean the thing is I mean fish if it didn't fish if it doesn't like
its life kill itself really easily, but how well first of all go out of the
water. That's pretty simple. How the hell you get out of the water. There's a
hundred other fish that want to eat you. You just go to one. I mean it's not like
a guy who wants to kill himself in the human world. It's like you go outside
and there's like a there's a giant flying shark. You can walk up to you have
to you there is guys. Maybe these people there is a guy that killed himself with
fish who the crocodile hunter it's not a fish. The manta ray yeah, it's a ray
fish. That's an elasmo brink
yeah, it's an elasmo brink. Okay, it's basically a shark, but that's what I'm
saying like a fish. I mean it doesn't have to be a shark. A fish could go
literally if it's like if you're if you're if you wanted to kill yourself
you could cross the street and your slightly bigger neighbor if you walked
up to me just eat you shark got it easy to if you want to kill yourself just
stop swimming yep fish to probably maybe hold I hold their breath you can't hold
your breath of your fish dude it's all just going up in them gills in them
gizmo the fish I could hold my breath you think some fish be like damn those
gills are fine yeah you know it's like do you do the fishes have a but have a
a
I assume they do because they probably have a slot because I've seen I've seen
some of those fish poop at the aquarium and that shit looks like a bird there.
There was a we had to dissect a shark in high school me to oh you guys are
right.
That would be my a p bio class did that and the whole science part of the
building smelled like fish for like the rest of the year.
I had to leave the room and the lady was like oh just put vicks vapor rub under
your nose so you won't smell it and then I did and I had to leave because it's
like it was menthol and dead shark smell in my mouth.
- I had to, I had to dissect it.
- And I felt like I wanted to puke.
- Really?
- Yeah, they had the eyeballs on it and stuff.
- I did a fetal pig.
- That's cool.
- It was disgusting, dude.
- Yeah.
- I wish they let me dissect the damn teacher.
Gave me so much homework.
- Yep, I would have dissected.
- Let's see what, let me see what makes you tick.
- I would have removed the homework part of the brain.
- Oh, wine, oh, there's lots of wine in here.
- I'm seeing a lot of wine.
- And alphabet cookies.
- I'm seeing some pills in here too.
in alphabet cookies to it and they're in the wrong order. So who's the teacher
now? Look, oh, it's lb it. I see. I see. Yep. I opened up my teacher's stomach
and there's alphabet soup and guess what it's spelled. That's right. Lgbt.
How do you explain that?
Poop my teacher's brain. I want to take alphabet brain. Yeah, so I can learn
how to do the alphabet.
There's a big alarm going on outside. Yeah, I like the sound of that. We're
just getting we're getting just attacked today dude yeah i'm not happy about
they're trying to take down the podcast today the city is working against us
yeah it's us versus new york versus everybody and we're everybody
another car just started going off did you hear that
i can't tell if that's a car alarm or if that is a some kind of like very light
brass band i have no idea well it's still the same day guys so if we are if
we were dead for the last one we're still dead for this one yeah I think it's
closing in definitely the circles getting smaller definitely yeah again
warzone mm-hmm scenario put on my dude did you guys I didn't how do you suppose
as he's Sonic - later I don't know how I fucking miss us but I saw a picture the
other day and it's from 2017 and it's some like Italian Street Festival where
they had a giant Warhammer statue of Trump what have you guys seen that was
- What was it, it was like a God Emperor thing?
- It's like supposed to be a Warhammer guy.
- Well there's a Warhammer guy named the God Emperor,
and I know people call Trump God Emperor.
- Just look it up, I don't have my phone.
- What should I search?
- Search Trump Warhammer statue.
- Trump, dude, it's like 200 feet tall.
- That sounds sick.
- It's so fucking cool. - Sexy naked Trump.
- Naked Trump.
- Whoa, yeah, that's the God Emperor, dude.
- Look at that, bro.
- I can't see it.
- Is that not the coolest shit you, look how big it is.
- As a Warhammer warrior.
- That's the coolest shit I've ever seen.
- Dude, he has a claw hand.
- Dude, I want that in my house so badly, bro.
- Warhammer guys are so cool.
Not the guys who play Warhammer, the guys in Warhammer.
- True.
- (gasps) Which one's Warhammer?
- That's the one where you have the little figurines.
It's a war game.
- You paint it all?
- A Mormon kid I knew in high school
was super into Warhammer, pretty funny.
- Yeah.
- Don't they have different kinds of Warhammer, though?
- There's fantasy and 40K.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, 40K is 40K.
40K in the future.
- 40K is the year 40,000.
- Whoa, okay.
- Yeah.
- It's pretty cool.
It's just like super edgy and dumb.
- We should do podcasts about less 40K.
- Yeah.
- Okay, we're here now.
What, what are you pointing at?
- Oh, nevermind.
I thought there was like four car alarms going off.
- That would just indicate--
- Those are birds.
- Probably a crazy attack.
It's not that big of a deal.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I think today is finally 9/11 too.
- We've been waiting on it.
It is a 10 year anniversary today. Yeah. Of Hitler's birthday, April 20th. Mm-hmm.
Hitler was born on a leap year, that's why he's only 20. If you ask me, he was born
on a creep year, cause that guy gave me the creeps. Yeah. Yeah. No good. No. No. No.
Why is there not a day for different kind of drugs that aren't weed, though?
Valentine's Day for a love drug. Yeah that's true. Yeah. Talk like a pirate day
for gunpowder. Man I'm hungry for grog now. Oh I could you put me in the mood for a
cup of grog so badly. The episode of Bar Rescue with the pirates tavern. Yeah and
they have grog and the grog is like what is it like orange juice and beer? Yeah it's
like the most terrible. Yes the grossest thing and then that was that little shit
Her husband is like this little Italian guy,
I think his name's like Luciano or some shit.
- That doesn't sound Italian.
- Nah, I don't know.
But he's like, he doesn't taste any of his own food
when he cooks it, and he's like,
I'm going to make you a burnt pizza.
And then he cooks it for the chef,
and it's literally just like he pours a whole thing
of habanero hot sauce on the chicken,
and he eats it and throws up.
- Why would you trust an Italian man
with traditional pirate cuisine?
- Yeah.
thing. You have to trust the Portuguese. How's that not appropriation?
Mm-hmm yeah. The Portuguese are the only people who make good pirate cuisine
because they were going around with they had the Nino, the Nino and the Pinto.
They went around there they did all this pirate bullcrap to all these Native
Americans. I don't think those were pirates. They were pirates. Christopher
Columbus was a pirate. I don't think so. And he wasn't Italian he was actually
Spanish. I don't think he was I don't think he had I don't think he was a pirate though.
he's a pirate was he look up a photo of him he's wearing a pirate I think you're
thinking of Captain Jack's yeah I'm gonna say you might be thinking black beard -
yeah that's another one you don't have to bring his the color of his beard into
question well I didn't a statement it was black yeah I think you're the one
who's questioning it right now you wouldn't say no one talks about red
beard no one says yeah they do red beard is fake that's what his name Eric the
red yeah but I'm talking about his beard they tell me a skin I told you about all
of his hair he had a black ass beard I don't know what I Eric the red had a red
hair and beard but yeah the red beard yeah they do they call him Eric the red
calm Eric the red okay so you think we should call black beard black yes okay
we should call beard the black black the pirate okay all right I'll call him
black the pirate yeah you know black the pirates treasure is is is buried in
North Carolina yeah I knew that yeah is it really yep we're gonna go there we
could do a treasure hunt yeah there's like they do treasure hunts there Eric
the red and leaf Erickson what is the topsoil Beach okay that's where it's
tops off beach I'll go there top top sale yeah I had that beach XXX marks the spot
yep oh my god I think we might have a pretty good joke there yeah I think we
might have a good beach on our hands I think we should go do our jokes there
that could be a tagline for a movie called topless pirate beach
topless pirate beach that's so good remember that what's that I want to make one of those
movies where you have 15 different banners on it that say unrated director's cut yeah
not safe for the theater version. Have you seen Pirate Stagnetti's Revenge?
Have you seen? No. No, I haven't. I haven't either. Me neither.
Yeah, me neither. I don't even know what that is. I've never heard of it. It is cool that
there's a lot of movies that just have one shot of boobs in them just for like kids.
Dude, the fucking-- Just for like when you're in middle school to be like,
I'm gonna go watch that movie because it probably has boobs in it based on the cover.
what's that Clark Duke movie? Well I'm thinking of like... What's that Clark Duke
movie that's about like teenagers? I don't know. And it's inappropriate? I don't
know what you're talking about. It's not Road Trip. Sex Drive. Sex Drive. Sex Drive.
That's like why you... Sex Drive Unrated they literally shot like on a different
camera and everything they put like more nudity in it for that reason. Yeah.
there's like your brother to get it from blockbusters yeah there's literally a
scene where it's like Clark Duke is running nude through like a cornfield or
something and then they for no reason cut to just like a great dick running
through a cornfield on a green screen doesn't sound like it's got no reason I
mean he was running through cornfield yeah he's naked yeah what are you gonna
do have him look like a Ken doll down there I don't think so I would hope I
I mean nowadays it probably would.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- But back in the good old days,
just cock and balls is normal to watch.
- Yeah, so nowadays sex drive has transformed
into something more like drive a smart car.
- Yeah, they don't have a sex car anymore,
they took those away.
- Now they have a movie.
- What killed the sex car?
- Nowadays it was called Jexy,
but if it was in 2008 it'd be called Sexy.
- It would've called Sexy Woman.
- Sexy Phone.
- And it'd be about a guy who's using a woman.
And it'd be awesome.
Oh, yeah, I never go to the Mets game. Why are you doing at home? I'm actually having sex
I mean nowadays we get
We get movies like the Avengers
But if it were if they were made way back in the in the heyday of awesome sex movies are probably called TNA Avengers
Yeah, mm-hmm. Yeah, the Avengers xxx. No, we called TNA Avengers. I just said that
Teen Titans.
So you would probably go see that.
The Incredible Hulk and barely legal Teen Titans.
There we go.
That's good.
Barely legal tit and ass.
Yeah, T and A.
Titan ass.
You had it already.
You had it already and you went too far.
Barely legal tit and titans.
Yeah.
Termin.
Teen.
What about teen termites?
Probably in a thousand years we'll have teen termites.
Yeah.
Probably everyone's just going to be a bug.
- Teen termites.
- Yeah.
- Probably everyone's just gonna be a bug
in a thousand years.
- Probably be teen termites by then.
- Yeah, we used to have American Pie,
now it's called Americans Barely Getting By
with Joe Brannon as the president,
as the president and chief of office.
- Yeah, we're barely getting by these days.
- Yeah.
- By, yeah.
- By then.
By then.
- Barely getting-- - By dinner for your kid.
- By then. - And that dinner is bugs.
- By then.
dinner is bugs yeah by then we will be eating bugs by the time keep going guys
the bugs we will eat will be made from protein no meat yep yeah because meat
doesn't have no damn protein in it no no chocolate no chocolate no meat we've
gone beyond me no listen no it's impossible to eat a normal burger
nowadays at Burger King no chocolate no chocolate at the school's smart board
rules yep you used to be able to go down to your favorite restaurant Bob's
burgers and go get yourself a burger and now you got a yeah beyonds burgers and
you have a biop burger yeah yep I said it and it's there mm-hmm no now they
have now jeans the girl and Tina's the boy played by a girl mm-hmm yeah okay so
So this is making what is this world coming to awesome.
Yeah.
So now Dan Vince is used to be on a TV show.
You used to be able to go used to be over a little walk down to
Bob's Burgers and get a perfectly deliciously funny burger named
cheese of war dogs.
Yep.
Yeah nowadays.
Nowadays, what you get beyond a beyond impossible cardboard box.
Yeah used to be able to watch a show called Bob's Burgers.
Now, it's a movie coming this May Bob's Burgers the movie.
Does that mean now?
Fucking so nowadays these fucking burgers.
I mean, if you can even call them burgers.
- Yep.
- They're filled with estrogen.
- And I mean back in the--
- Estrogen, the character.
- Whatever happened to the West I went as a cowboy.
- Yep.
- Yep, nowadays everyone's--
- A strong loner type.
- Everyone wants to put all this estrogen in their body.
When I was a kid we wanted to put X-Men in our body.
I wanted to eat my X-Men toys.
- Yep, estrogen.
- I wanted to eat Maverick and Deadpool and Cyclops.
- Now we have to eat estrogen.
I used to watch Ben of 10.
I mean, I just like, you know, as you used to watch movies,
cowboy movies about the man with no name,
nowadays you got a man with new name,
change the name.
- Nowadays we got the person with new name.
- Yeah, oh my God, don't even get me started
on these people.
I hate people, oh my God.
- Me too, I'm sick of them.
- Nowadays, back then, you'd have to listen
to people's problems.
Nowadays all we care about is Weebles Wobbles,
Yeah, don't fall down.
That's right, they're not even falling down.
People used to fall down out of these damn weebles.
It is up all the damn time.
It used to be a problem when weebles would wobble.
I mean people, hardworking people used to know how to work with their hands.
They'd spend their free time listening to car talk.
Now we got Nar Chalk, the smart boys rule at the school.
Yep, it's just the truth man.
Yeah, got these plastic markers and people are being eaten by fantastic sharkers.
We used to be able to watch Jimmy Neutron, now I'm Slimmy, all the food's gone.
Used to be in your car listening to NPR, now your car has an NPR.
You have to have everybody carpool in your car.
Yep, it's true.
Because there's no room in the damn room.
Oh my god, okay, a carpool used to be something we swam in.
Yeah.
Used to be you chopped a car in half and you filled it with water.
Now all of a sudden you gotta do it at work?
What the hell's going on?
Yeah, I mean, and most of these people don't even go to work.
Their carpool in the damn movie theater, the bar, the strip club, it's depraved.
People are working from home. You know what's at home? The above-ground pool.
You're in your above-ground pool and now, I don't know, coding isn't working.
You said Brokeback Mountain, now what? It's Brokeback Whole Foods, two gay cowboys fucking in the bathroom.
What the fuck is going on?
Strip club used to be a place you partied. Nowadays, people are in there taking notes for their gender studies class.
yeah that's true sure they do out there doing nude male modeling yeah and the
and there should be only women yeah throw hey listen they're not throwing dollars
on the station we're throwing QR codes mm-hmm yeah hey scan this toots yep yep
nowadays all these strippers have to have a QR code on their belly so you
know where to aim your target is a QR code
I go into strip clubs and I just start coming all
I go to the strip club with my dick in my hand just start and I'm wearing yeah
and I'm wearing a big trench and the bouncer says, Are you twenty one? I said
does this I but yeah, this dick belong to a child. I think so I'm coming in
there and I'm not known. Every one of these hard working women, I walk in the
strip club and my wiener flips up like the the penis gun and and from dusk till
gun yeah, but it's not a gun. It's just my wiener. It's my damn cock dude. It is
metal, though it's made out of complete. It's not made of metal. It's made of my
leaders made out of my God metal. It's made of flesh, hot blood and dozens of
white pearls
dozens.
You only have a fine. Oh my God, I'm in your life. I mean I'm shooting, I'm
shooting, I'm shooting balls that come like hadoukens. Yeah, it comes up.
like it's like shooting it's like it's like spray it's like spraying the garden
hose through an oscillating fan
droplets you should be able to watch any
hall now you can't even go to any mall they're all closed yep all the malls are
closed used to watch the movie Manhattan mm-hmm now all these damn hipsters are
living in Brooklyn now now womans are wearing Hattons yeah
hat and pants when did women start wearing hats?
when did women start wearing hats?
now all of a sudden women are allowed to wear hats and pants
that's a german word for hats and pants
this woman is wearing hats and pants hats and pants
yeah and now all these tv shows got hats and pants on them
yeah it used to be called citizen cane now it's probably the citizen app
yeah where you go on and you report that there's a mexican teenager
- Nobody's using their citizen's brain anymore.
It's all out the window.
Oh, and hey, maybe try climbing out
one of these windows nowadays.
Probably a screen, it's probably a LED screen showing,
showing what, where do people go on vacation now?
Afghanistan?
- Yep.
- Where's that, is that where you go?
You go to Afghanistan?
- You think it's beautiful there?
- You go to Syria?
- Oh my God.
- You think that's what's cool now?
- You go to Syria, you used to stay at home, eat cereal.
- Hey pal, you go over there,
you're not gonna see any palm trees,
you're gonna see balm trees and mushroom cloud trees.
Mm-hmm and a Goomba. Yeah
You're gonna see Goomba and you're gonna see the spiky plants there's a literal Goomba in Afghanistan
Hey
I'm gonna say I can't tell you how to I can't tell you how to live your life
But you step into Bowser's Palace. You'll feel Bowser's malice. Mm-hmm. It's true
You want to go to have you really want to go to Afghanistan on vacation?
Oh, no that they have they have Monty moles there. Yeah, I guess what I'm going
(laughing)
I just touched down in a dry, dry desert in Afghanistan.
Yep, and there's a bunch of cactus
with their heads are stacked on top of each other.
- Stactus?
- Mm-hmm, yep.
- Is that what it's called?
I think it's called just spiky.
- And you know there's a big-ass bird
flying around with a star on him?
And I'm getting sucked up in tornadoes and shit.
I'm flying around, god damn.
- Dude, it's the worst when you go to Afghanistan.
My cousin actually was deployed to Afghanistan.
he said the first day he got there thwomp attack.
- Mm-hmm, yep, he saw his best friend get flattened
and walk around flipping his feet up and down.
- He turned around, he heard ooh, and turned around
and his best friend was flattened by a thwomp.
- The thwomps have such a long range in Afghanistan.
I mean, they could be one of the sideways thwomps
that goes to the side.
You could walk--
- Who the fuck is the Kandahar Giant?
- You could hear one from like 20 miles away,
just flying at you.
- The Kandahar Giant was just a thwomp.
It was not a thwomp, it was a giant.
What is the story on the Kandahar giant?
Basically they found bones that proved that Marines fought and killed a giant in a cave
in Kandahar that was about 10 to 12 feet tall.
It had red hair if you're wondering.
It was.
Do you believe in-
It killed six Marines with a spear.
It impaled them.
It killed them.
Really?
And the government's covered it up because they don't want people to know about the giants
in Afghanistan.
weeks drop that I think it was cool stuff on facts cool stuff on facts dot bad
chill yeah chill that's true that happened I heard they also I heard they
found I heard they found Bullwinkle the mooses bones in Afghanistan - really
marines actually had a conflict with him that's crazy mm-hmm they found putt-putt
They found his bones, his car bones.
You know who found all of them was Pajama Sam.
Yeah, Pajama Sam was on a mission.
My mom is still texting me about the shooting and stuff.
You should say you're battling him right now.
Yeah, well she told me I need to hide my kids, hide my wife.
That's funny as hell. She said that?
She said Pat needs to...
Well why, what reason would you do that?
Pat needs to hide his kids, hide his wife.
Because what?
Because what's going on?
shooting everybody out here. I don't know how that was. I don't remember that being in the video.
Yeah. What's it's there hide your kids hide your wife because there's something. Yeah then you say
the next yeah. They say you don't have to call we'll be looking for you we go find you. That's
the next line. And you know Schmoyoho killed that one. Yeah Schmoyoho is the shooter. I don't think
so. He's mad because nobody's. Nobody's out tuning the news these days. Yeah. We so many things from
2008 are coming back already yeah schmoyoho should schmoyoho should come
back yeah should start auto tuning the new red linker bigger than they've ever
been yeah schmoyoho could do they grew well yeah they've been eaten hmm bigger
than they ever been they've been a they've been eaten trust me dude you
don't even want to know what they've been eating they've been eating crap
flavored potato chips every single morning for 40 years
Rhett and Link hit a growth spurt yeah I know them focus tall as hell mm-hmm and
and there's a north carolina. They finally hit puberty. I do respect them because
they're from north carolina. Yeah, yeah, it's cool. They put on for the for the for
the hood. They got cheer wine. They like cheer wine. I told you a place where they
have cheer wine. Yeah, I'm not gonna run. I've had enough. Actually, you know what?
That place where the cheer wine is is like exactly in the area of that
shooting. Oh really? Yeah. Maybe everyone started finding out there's cheer wine there.
Is that far away? You were like you told Caleb you had to go there to get cheer wine? You just take the M to the F.
if two trains to get your wine he would do it you think I'd take the m2f I think
two trains to get a soda is a you thing it's two trains to get a soda but he has
a car it's only a 20-minute drive I'm not gonna take it to drive around trip
to get a soda that I had my entire life but it's you miss it though I don't miss
I mean it's good I don't miss this is it the only soda I like is is could diet
coke no I had a diet Pepsi I heard there's a place in downtown Brooklyn as
Diet Coke. Really? I'll drive over there. There's a place in New Jersey that has
downtown Brooklyn Coke. Diet Coke. Downtown Brooklyn Coke? You mean Fentanyl? Let's go.
Well, I don't... that's so racist, dude. How is that racist? You're a racist.
Really racist. Racist ass. How is that racist? Oh, no wait, no, it's man, it's the
LES stuff. That's where all the chill... that's where all the people are
hanging out and accidentally doing Fentanyl. Really? Yeah. I don't think so.
These people are going to these clubs. They're going to do karaoke.
What are in a good old-fashioned Billy Club when it comes to these druggies?
Yep. We used to have... We used to have normal drugs like weed. Mm-hmm.
Which we're on. And now everyone's doing ketamine and cocaine and they're
overdosing in bathrooms all over Manhattan. Yep. How about you flatten the
curve and stop going out yep mm-hmm yeah we used to have asked Jeeves now wear a
mask please yep that's just the truth it used to be you'd overdose and you killed
seven villagers in the Vietnam War nowadays you overdose you fall asleep at
your house what happened to the youth of today that's right we should be out
there mowing down yeah hundreds of civilians mm-hmm
yep now all the sudden in Vietnam there was a massacre every day now all these
guys are putting on mascara cuz they're gay yep mm-hmm that's right all these
gay guys these days instead of killers instead of instead of cold-blooded
murder yeah who are killing they used to we used to send guys guys 18 to 21 to
war now these 18 to 21 year olds are listening to echo 2k and having sex with
whores yep that's right and they're putting on
on mascara. We could big shoes. We could have ended the Vietnam War with with way
more will a less casual. Yeah, if one per lady one of lady's honor, it would all
they play start doing estrogen peroxide by echo to K. They would play peroxide by
echo to K or one bladey song and then all those male soldiers over there would
be doing estrogen. They're going to go. They're going to tear your ass apart for
saying bladey. I don't care you care. I don't they're going to be up your
asshole dude, lady to your going to be in trouble. You don't want to get you
don't want to fuck with the last boy and that boy digital dude the blade the
blades
they might they might slap you yeah. They might they might be white gloves
did you get yeah? You don't want to you don't want to fuck. I mean blades
blades got blades got scratchers yeah
I got some sharp fingernails. He got biters out here. You called him Blady?
We're about to fly up on you. I just put a curse on you.
I've never listened to a single Blady song. I've been listening to it.
I like classic rock. Curtis Lowe was the finest picker to ever play the blues.
What song I like?
What?
Happy birthday to Cameron.
Really?
It's not my birthday.
It's coming out on his birthday.
Happy birthday to Caleb.
Guys, my birthday is coming out pretty soon.
Yeah.
Oh, we're past your birthday by now.
Oh shit.
Then Cameron, let's sing happy birthday to him right now.
They said I wasn't gonna make it past 25.
You turning 25?
Joke's on you, I'm still alive.
This is gonna be really like darkly ironic when this shooter closes in.
♪ I wasn't gonna make it past 25 ♪
♪ Joke's on you, he's still alive ♪
- You are turning 25, huh?
- Yep.
- He's gonna be in his terrible 25s.
- I'm a hoarder. - Oh my God.
- I'm always on my terribles. - No.
No. - No.
- I'm gonna be running around holding up my underwear.
Nee nee nee nee nee nee nee nee.
- No.
- Be stepping on shit, fighting the dog.
Just like slapping the dog.
(laughing)
- Fighting Phil?
- Yeah.
- Is he getting more attention than you?
- He did it.
- Oh, Jenna, Phil pooped in the--
- Piss all over the fridge.
- He did it.
Phil pooped on the floor in the house.
It was Phil.
- It's like a human poop.
- Yeah.
Phil took a bite out of the TV.
- It looks exactly like a cigar.
- Yeah.
- That's not a human poop.
- Phil does take human-sized poops.
It's frustrating.
- Dude, hold on, let me show you this.
You know how it has the memory things on the phones?
Like it's like, oh, on this day.
Let me show you this.
These phones have memories now. On the on this day photo? That's a turd. That's a
really crazy turd. That's like an MCS picture. Wait let me look at that. That is like a beautiful photo. Oh my god. I have a good eye.
That's amazing. I have a good eye for taking pictures of poops. Alright. This
one, this was like I was skating when I was in LA and I was like I had
nothing I went to like a parking garage to try and skate and I found like I
walked in and immediately saw this human poop. It's an amazing cylindrical turd too. I bet
that guy's butthole is like perfect. Oh yeah. It's crazy. Yeah that is the funniest
poop I've ever seen. It's like a Lego poop. Yeah. Yeah. Alright. Alright. Bye. Do we plug the
tour? Yeah. Go buy tour tickets you're gonna want them. Swagpoop.com/shows.
Swagpoop.com. Don't miss out. We're gonna upload that picture of that poop. That's the swag poop.
Okay, alright, bye!