you're listening to Israel's number one podcast
if you are not a premium subscriber please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately
Patrick is the least annoying
hard to disagree
alright who's the least annoying Caleb? it's me that is an annoying thing to say
that it would be the most annoying thing you could have said that is probably the most annoying answer you could have given
sorry I'm out of breath I just did like a million push-ups in a row that's
annoying oh actually annoying wait annoying to my muscles that's how you
admit it's annoying so you admit you're no I am only really just a minute
cracked my parts of my body so yeah you are annoying you admit you're annoying
so you admit you're not good neck cracks just then we shut up I am yeah some quick
Cameron's diarrhea diarrhea yeah this has been an interesting start we had
- Had to shit.
And then we did a technically a lost episode.
We did 20 seconds.
- No, that was like five seconds.
- I was recording for 21 seconds.
- I think I was recording for maybe six seconds.
- Okay, so one of the lost episodes,
add it to the catalog with the chicken brain one.
- I deleted mine, so.
- We'll tweet.
We'll tweet at us and say release the lost episodes.
Not gonna happen.
- I will release my audio.
- You won't release any of the...
You'll do nothing!
- Damn, I'm watching a video right now
of a kidnapping chase right here on Emu.
- Are you kidding me, dude?
- Okay.
- Fucking one minute in.
- This is the last time we do this over Zoom.
I am, I am--
- You're gonna start driving?
You're gonna start driving to Manchester?
- I'm gonna kidnap Patrick
just so he doesn't look at a fucking screen.
- I can't believe--
- I'm looking at an Emu chasing a child.
- You--
- I can't believe it took you one minute to do that.
(laughing)
- How fa--
I mean it's it's unbelievable this is your job now and you can't for one minute
not look at a fucking YouTube video of an animal that you thought was imaginary
I didn't I never said I thought an emu was imaginary I could see it in your
eyes you thought the child was imaginary I jumped over a dog it was cool
actually send me that video that sounds it's chasing a kid and while it's chasing the
kid the dog gets in the way the dogs fucking chillin yeah I was not helping
at all Patrick sir jumps over I don't see your crazy ass video okay there's this
emu and it's chasing a kid and it jumps over a dog the dog doesn't even care
it's wild guys yes I should do a touch point no we should make a touch point
okay here's what we're gonna do going forward for every premium episode okay
we're gonna have me and Caleb are gonna record an hour-long episode without
Patrick Patrick will record 10 minutes of him describing a video and we'll
release together okay I contribute to the show you'd be a great clip show host
honest oh yeah I would yeah that is your that is your perfect placement it's it's
I was saying that when we did the stream like it's good that Patrick is the one
with face cam because he's you laugh - you laugh hard and you he laughs hard he
holds his nose like a pig he does he like there's always it always seems like
you're about to have something come out of your nose when you laugh mm-hmm
it's because you always have milk in your mouth yeah I don't want the milk to
shoot out yeah so you always like funny little teeth so when you smile it's
really like I don't have really good little teeth and like a really stupid
nose and like really funny eyes I don't have big and fat and so when you laugh
it's like really awesome to look at is what we're saying if I was on face cam
It would just be me staring into the camera without moving my face at all.
Which is why I'm glad that we just sit there just like...
Yeah, we were on a Zoom call the other day and we did not know that Cam was frozen for like 10 minutes.
Yeah, Cam was frozen and he's just sitting there like...
Sometimes he's just still for a long time.
He was so vacant we didn't know what the fuck was going on.
We didn't even notice he didn't blink.
Yeah.
I like to think about what I'm gonna say next you know and I need to sit there you
need to sit there and create 1,000 small worlds in your mind yeah I'm running
simulations destroy them I'm basically like what will happen a hundred years
from now if I say this joke that I'm about to say Cameron I just tried to do
that as a joke to see how long it would take for me you to notice and I like my
hands started to shake I can't wait you tried right in I tried yeah I was trying
to try to sit still for half a second I know my fucking hands started shaking
you might have like ALS I don't have I think you might have ALS you might have
Lou Gehrig's disease no you are never gonna play baseball that would be
Parkinson's if I just started shaking no no that's actually that's called
shivering itis shivering itis yeah it's called the shivering Isle it's called
having it you're a shivering mister yeah yeah yeah he is a shivering mister yeah
ain't that the damn truth yeah you are you're full of energy you're like a
you're like a yeah if I ever got back you're like a car to you're like a
cartoon like cereal mascot just like jumping around the frame of the screen
oh it's shaky the shrew yeah in every every I am the least like a shrew I'd be
more like a boar or something I'd be like every cereal mascot is either either
protecting or trying to get the cereal yeah they're never just so is everybody
in life they're never enjoying the supermarket people are protecting everyone
else is trying to eat the cereal. That's a really good point.
What about Toucan Sam? It's basically Toucan Sam's just an uncle trying to be nice to his kids.
Those are his nephews dude. Yeah I said he was an uncle.
And then you said his kids. Well their parents died and he took them in.
He's a foster father.
They're birds.
Yeah, that's just - he's not the foster father, he's the father who fostered.
Fostered.
He's the father who fostered their youth.
Yeah.
Oh my God, dude.
Week three of growing one of the greatest mustaches the world's ever seen.
Yeah.
Me or you?
What do you think, me?
What do you think?
Why would I be talking about you?
Yeah, Caleb's been keeping track.
Why would I know when the last time -
the last time. - Caleb, you've been out three weeks.
- This is three weeks. - That's three weeks.
- Patrick, Caleb, three extremely powerful--
- This took me three days. - I always thought,
I thought that I was like insecure about how slow
I grew facial hair until I met you, Caleb.
- Yeah, I'm not insecure about it.
I grow it very fast and it's very thick and strong.
- I know, I'm saying you saved me from being,
I didn't say you were insecure.
I said you saved me from being insecure.
- I have an amazing-- - Yeah.
- You, if there's one thing-- - I look at you--
- If there's one thing I know about Caleb,
He's great at growing hair.
Yeah, it's true.
I look at you and it's like, it's like, I'm like an I'm like an
ape.
It's like it's looking at you is like looking into a radioactive
mirror.
You know that's not true.
I do look like I do look like a radioactive mirror that you've
been looking into every day for a year.
I look like white doctor Manhattan.
You look like a porcupine without lopecia.
I don't look like a porcupine.
You look like a porcupine.
Take that back to Caleb.
Caleb looks like a porcupine.
like my uncle with alopecia. I am two eyebrows away from looking like my
alopecia uncle. Damn. Maybe I should just go uncle Matt mode. I should just pop him off, just shave my whole body
every day. Just wake up be like all right dry cereal for breakfast and think about
ghosts I guess that's what I'll do I look like a you it's like a ghost newspaper
yeah he has like a ghost like how does he hold hunters only time does he hold it
if it's ghost come on dude yes would go right through it
the path you have you you suck I'm getting discord notifications to
distracted. It's from your brother. It's not from my brother. Yeah it is. It's from Levi.
No it's not from him. It's from Levi. I got the same ones. No you didn't.
My Uncle Matt has a ghost hunting newspaper that he reads in the mornings.
Pretty cool. You already said that. Yeah I just thought. Can we get a new detail on it?
Yeah it's yellow. What is? It's see-through. It's not see-through. It's not a dead
newspapers go yellow? I basically have a yellow uncle. Your uncle is Matt Groening.
You want to try that last syllable again big guy? Isn't it? Excuse me? Isn't that how you say it?
Oh this is gonna be a fucking Zamas thing. Try it again. No try it again. No go ahead.
No this is way worse than Zamas already. Oh. This is a lot worse than Zamas immediately. Matt Groening.
that's better yeah okay that's a little less I mean it's definitely so far from
what how you say his name which is graining yeah but a graining it's yeah
it's raining it's like Boehner no I've been saying it wrong this whole time
yeah I'm definitely gonna believe our pronunciation of how you said his name
the first time yeah I don't know I don't want it out you want people to have
access to that soundbite I think he does I okay he's trying to explain himself out
of this one watch his ALS brain trying to turn the cogs here just struggling to be like yeah I
didn't mean to I know his name doesn't have the n-word in it I thought okay I
think that that is another more evidence of me having dyslexia Patrick you will
thank me for bleeping that out I guarantee I guarantee you in one day
you'll be so happy that you didn't let me
you'll send a handwritten thank you note
with flowers
if you want I can just clip the pronunciation
and post it directly onto the podcast
account with no caption
you feel like it's worse?
you feel like a bleep is worse?
*laughter*
just that once one half-second clip yeah I don't know I don't know good luck dude
I'm gonna be by your side I want you to know that when they come for you for
that I'm gonna be here it's just me not gonna bad at reading you can't punish me
for having dyslexia. That was Bill Maher's defense too. That was Papa John's defense.
I'm bad at reading. Because the Republicans won't fund the public schools.
The Republicans gave me dyslexia and that's why I said that. Yeah he misread
new rule into the entire sentence I'm a
house new rule that was what he was
trying to say you're right I'm saying
you it said new rule and he said I'm a
house oh gosh he said he's a house yeah
then the other was just that was just a
coincidence he just added that on that
emphasis uh-huh he was just doing like
an ad that wasn't even part of the
misreading yeah yeah Bill Maher would be funny if they um it would be funny if
they like to save like Bill Maher's like ass they like cut that one part out like
him saying the n-word so he's like senator I'm a house what it's just a
joke and everybody and it gets in more trouble for making a joke that makes no
sense. What the fuck is his show even doing anymore? The writers don't care.
It doesn't make sense dude. Is he paying a mortgage on that? People are mad because he's not paying
like taxes on himself being a house. Yeah he's technically a house.
That's how yeah that's how that's the new. Yeah more like Bill Manner am I right?
Oh my god! He is a house, you were right.
Yeah. And Matt Groening is... What is Matt Groening, Patrick?
Come on. I'm just asking, just tell me what he is.
What, what, what, what is great...
He's just struggling now. He's just gasping for air.
- I'm afraid to say any word that ends in -ing from now on.
(laughing)
- Oh, it does end in -ing.
Dude, I do have fucking dyslexia, Jesus Christ.
- You didn't believe us?
- You thought we were joking?
- No, this--
- You thought we were just fucking with you?
- No, this whole time--
- And that his name was the N word?
- This whole time, I didn't know
there was another N in his name.
- Damn, dude.
- Wow.
- At what point, how many--
How many times have I said his name?
That's my question, yeah.
And how many pe- you really gotta think about the company you keep
that nobody ever corrected you on that or Samus.
I've been saying it around you guys!
I'm- Absolutely not.
Listen, listen, Cameron has a- Cameron has like a-
like a bomb-sniffing dog type
like, zero in on that exact syllable.
So I think he would've noticed.
I think he would've smelled that out if you had said it around us.
This is my Mandela effect.
yeah the gray name effect yeah god man this thing on today dude
this is what happens when you come at me for my mustache you immediately fuck up
it's karma yeah and this car this is God this is Yahweh I will alright it is a
very good you doubting me and you do trying to do me it is better than any
mustache you've had in the past that's I'll say that much yeah okay that's
- That's a start. - We're getting somewhere.
Can we take it to another level?
- Absolutely not, no. - Can somebody say that it--
- No, not a chance. - Can somebody say
they wish they could imagine how it feels on their lips?
- I wish I could imagine how it would look behind bars.
- Caleb, I wish I could give you some of that.
- I would look like a pedophile if I was in jail.
- I wish I could give you more of my hair.
- You look like one out of jail too.
- No, I don't.
I look like a child out of jail.
What'd you say?
- I wish I could give you more of my hair, man.
- I wish you could too.
Where would you-- - I got so much.
much. If you could give up hair and give it to me
locks for love donation style. It's so crazy. Where would you take it from?
Um, oh I have like too much chest hair now. That'd be funny if you just had it like
an exact like circle out of your chest that would fit my head like a glove.
Yeah. Just like a circle of hair that is just gone now because it's all on my
head. And it's like it looks exactly like your hair when I met you. Yeah exactly.
My hair looks good.
I have beautiful hair.
There's no weird angles to it.
It grows really thick and full too.
Yeah.
You're full of crap.
Yeah thick and full.
My hair's not full of crap.
It's called fertilizer.
I'm trying to make it grow better.
It's like a chia pet but you have to put something on it.
God, dude, how many fucking times in my life have I been saying it like that?
That's how my brother says it I think.
That's how my family says it.
I think it's a New Hampshire accent thing.
Yeah, the New Hampshire accent is
who does who put the N word into things.
(laughing)
That is, yeah, that is true, yeah.
Yeah.
Damn, dude.
God.
I'm trying to think of what words I've ever said wrong.
I've never said a word wrong.
You know, it's hard because I say everything pretty correct
because I'm very smart, you know?
I realize I say most things wrong.
There's one word I know that you say really funny
every time. Pen.
Pen.
- Pen and Ben.
- Oh, what is it?
- I use-- - Pen?
- No, no, I know that one,
but there's a specific one I'm thinking of.
- Mayim, can I get a pen, bro?
Can I borrow a pen? - Pen?
- Pen. - Pen.
- You say pen. - I don't say pen,
I say pen. - Can I borrow a pen,
bro? - It's all the same.
E and I, in that context, is the same.
- Oh, what am I thinking of?
- There is, I know what you're talking about.
- There's one really funny one.
- Yeah, I don't say anything funny.
Not true.
- Yeah, oh my God.
Somebody in the comments just pointed out,
I'm Caleb's funny word.
Caleb's funny mispronunciation.
Caleb does not have a funny word.
Caleb's funny word.
Cuckoo kangaroo is funny.
First of all, my name is Caleb Michael Pitts.
I'm not Cuckoo kangaroo.
If I were a kangaroo, I would be normal.
I would not be cuckoo.
You are a cuckoo kangaroo.
You're the cereal mascot now.
You're the cuckoo kangaroo.
I've given my title to you. You're a cereal something, all right? And it's a
cereal pedophile cuckoo kangaroo. Patrick is a cereal mascot for but like a
cereal they give you in prison. Like a low sugar, no like a like a no sugar cereal and
you're like the mucinex monster of that world. You're like this is what happens
this is what happens when you eat the sugary cereal. Yeah well you're a cuckoo
kangaroo so I'm not a koo-koo kangaroo you're still a koo-koo kangaroo in a cage pal
no I think Billy Borgen said it best you're crazy you're crazy
grating there you go yeah you're getting this son his son is named Philip Picasso
Nathaniel Philip Picasso beautiful last name is my name's oh is he married
to like Picasso's daughter? To Pablo Picasso?
Wait, he must be married to Pablo Picasso.
Yeah, no, he's related, or she's related to somebody.
She's related to somebody with the last name Picasso.
I think Picasso is her, like, uncle maybe?
Get off Wikipedia. No.
Can't you just hang out with your friends? Yeah. Do you hate us?
single episode by watching TV I care that you won't spend time with me and camera
I'm spending time with you guys not just fact I spend all the amazing so I don't
say names wrong it's amazing that a guy who literally cannot read spend so much
of his job reading shit that doesn't matter I'm trying to learn I mean it's
unbelievable I'm using this time to learn to read I'm gonna buy you one of
those typing games yeah you were gonna get you hooked on phonics I know how to
type yeah we're gonna get we're gonna get Patrick hooked on ebonics he's not gonna
be able to stop there is so many different versions of hooked on phonics
parodies that are out there from like a two-year span where that was yeah yeah
that was that was all there was for two years that was the thing cuz it was like
that it was the mesothelioma commercials mm-hmm the laws of name Sokolov muzzy I
I don't remember Muzzy.
Muzzy was the, it was like Rosetta Stone for kids and it had a big green bear.
No that was your mom.
Yeah that was your imagination.
No that was, your mom and dad were two big green bears.
My mom and dad are two big green bears.
Yeah they are.
You're what happens when a regular dude has sex with a big green bear.
Patrick comes out.
You're what happens when a kangaroo goes cuckoo.
Yeah Caleb, you're what happens when a kangaroo goes cuckoo kangaroo.
I'm not absolutely kangaroo.
Koo koo kangaroo.
I'm not even, I'm gonna stop talking until you guys say I'm Caleb.
Hooked on phonics, more like fooked off the chronic.
Am I right guys?
Am I right?
Am I right koo koo kangaroo?
Caleb's head, he looks like a...
I don't know what.
But he looks like something.
Hey, hey, really good one, Pat.
Yeah, that's funny.
That was a good one.
comedy was. You just go up on stage and you're like...
Women and men are so different. It's sometimes women are uh...
They do something.
You know I can't really think of it right now but it's like there's almost a very funny
difference between the two, you know?
That...
I don't know, you sir, where are you from? What's that, Indiana? Oh man.
They got something there.
There's something funny about this.
There's something hilarious going on there.
They got some funny crap going on there. I can't talk about it right now.
Basically they're saying dirty words you can't say on television and they... and uh...
You know what y'all can come up with them. I don't have to do so Donald Trump is in the news
Something so something or other I don't even know who that guy is, but I'm sure you guys there's probably a joke about it
I was eating lunch the other day, and I can't even I don't remember what happened, but I remember laughing at the time
So this family this family walks into a talent agent's office
No some crap
Something they're like
They do something that guy right there
In the front row he's something I don't know what you know, they would they would have done something
Kramer still gets like
Yeah, I'm video from the laugh factory
Kramer cannot remember his racist rant. As Kramer says the name of the creator of
The Simpsons. Oh come on I'm not gonna fucking live that down ever. No neither did he.
Let me know and I'll bleep it out. That's all I guess. I guess you have to.
If you bleep it out we want you to know not only did Patrick spell out the full N-word.
He said it and he said it get this in a Jamaican accent. So there's different
If it's bleeped out, that's what happened there.
- I think it's so much funnier if it's bleeped out.
- I, why don't we just get a clean take?
- And it's also less incriminating.
- Why don't we get a clean take of me saying it?
- A clean take of me saying that n-word.
- Okay.
- Yeah, go ahead.
- All right, and slate.
- We'll bleep this out.
(laughing)
- We need something to bleep out.
- Yeah.
- Somebody say something that we can bleep
out of the episode, please.
- Uh.
(groaning)
- We're having so much fun.
- I hit my death vape.
I have a Cameron story today.
- You hit it just now?
- No, yesterday.
My first Cameron story ever.
- Wow. - A lot of Cameron stories.
- Yeah, yesterday.
- A few of those are rare.
These are, yeah.
- I have, I had this vape that I got in LA
that every time I hit it, even once,
makes me completely just freak out.
Like I would just, I would hit it every single day in LA,
every night, and I would just lie in bed
and like just be like I'm never gonna be happy again
and just fall asleep.
(laughing)
And so.
- That's the worst, wait, that's the worst
when you smoke so much weed that you think for a second
you're like I've unlocked something wrong in my brain.
- Yeah.
- You get so high that you're like I have just unlocked
a secret thought and knowledge pattern
that will destroy my normal life.
- Yeah, so that would happen to me literally
from one hit from this vape pen.
And I did it every night and then I stopped for like a year
And then I found it again, I found the pen again,
but it had been in my super hot room without AC,
so I thought it was fucked up, I thought it was broken.
So I was trying to get it to work the other night,
and then it wasn't working.
And then yesterday I was just like,
oh, I wonder if it's working, and I just wasn't thinking,
I just assumed it wasn't, and I just took
the biggest fucking hit I've ever taken from it by accident.
'Cause I was just--
- You big milky cloud.
- Yeah, and I just instantly started panicking,
'cause I was like, oh shit, oh fuck.
And I just lay down on my bed--
- That's the worst.
That's the worst when you get accidentally high.
- Yeah, no, that's what made it so bad is because I wasn't expecting, I wasn't prepared.
It was the middle of the day.
I always do it at night because then it's like if I start freaking out, I can just go
to sleep.
But, yeah, I was just lying on my bed looking at the ceiling and just like I started thinking
to myself just like I should be normal.
I should be normal, normal, normal.
I was like, what am I?
I had this moment of clarity where I was like I'm just thinking the word normal to myself
over and over.
I have to put an end to this.
So I was just then I was just listening to the new M.U.R.E. album really loud and lying
on my bed and then I was like I have to turn off this music because I won't be able to
hear if anyone's sneaking up on me.
Dude, I don't I will never understand how people smoke weed.
So yeah.
Then I turned off the music and I just lay down for like an hour or two and then when
I was getting up to leave my room I was like super dizzy because I had just been lying
down and super high and I was like
walking out of my room and the door to
my room slammed shut behind me like I
just let it go in a slam shut right as I
got super dizzy and I was like oh my god
I just got shot
there was a super loud bang behind me and I just instantly felt like I was gonna pass out
what you thought you got shot you are not
that you are smoking fucking
Cameron you can't that's k2 or something
- That is not weed, dude.
- Yeah, you're smoking demon stuff.
- And you think you were shot by a sniper?
- I just think that in general, though.
I would think that normally.
- I would say sometimes I will--
- That was when I wasn't as high anymore,
I'll just add that.
That's just me.
- That's just you normal.
- But if you're just walking around
and you heard a really loud bang,
and then you felt like you're about to fall over,
all of a sudden.
- I do feel like every time I look at somebody
and I have food on my face or something,
and I can tell that they're looking at my face weird,
I do think for a second, like,
I have been shot in the head and I have not noticed yet.
- Yeah, it's a reasonable thought.
- You know, yeah, I feel like it's pretty reasonable.
Just like, you're gonna be like,
wouldn't that be the worst if you're laughing?
- You didn't know. - I mean, it is
the same feeling as having mustard on your face.
If you look at somebody and you have a giant hole
in your head and you're like--
- And your brain's still working.
- Yeah, this person's looking at me so weird
and they don't wanna say anything.
Yeah, that would be, that's a nightmare way to go out.
Fucking, I, I straight up, I smoked weed for like a month.
Straight up. Straight up.
I straight up.
I smoked weed for like three months this year.
Like you guys-- That's pretty sick.
Yeah, I remember it was one of the worst three months
of our friendship. Yeah, yeah.
It's not even close.
I don't, I wasn't even like--
Patrick was coming on the podcast,
just putting up, just laying eggs every single week.
Dude, I didn't even know what the fuck I was doing.
like most of the February episodes I'm just kind of like out of it.
You're asleep yeah.
Yeah I'm like not doing anything.
That was just that wasn't just the episodes too.
That was just how you were.
Right?
You'd be awake for like six hours a day and we had to catch him during that.
We would cancel episodes because he would not be awake when I said we were recording.
Yeah.
It was awesome dude and then he woke up from that and now he can't read anymore.
I yeah.
Yeah.
[laughs]
Dude, I can't fucking read any-
I- losing- losing that vape pen
before
New York kind of saved me.
Oh, yeah, dude.
You would be-
You would be in
Guantanamo Bay right now.
Dude, I would be- I don't even know.
I, like-
Or you would- you might be like a-
like famous if you would come smoking.
Yeah.
Maybe.
Maybe that was it.
You might be like a Brad Pitt-style movie star.
No, you would be like one of those, um,
people on tik-tok that everyone thinks they find and post a post a video to
Twitter of go look at this insane guy I just found but it has like a hundred
thousand views and it's somebody doing something on purpose - yeah oh my god
look at this freak yeah would have been you kissing your cat with your tongue
yeah you would have gotten you'd have gotten to that point where you were
making out with your cat I mean I there have been times when I've smoked weed
and thought that my dog could read my thoughts.
- Yeah? - Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Pretty, I would say every third or fourth time,
I would sit next to my dog and be like,
we are, I can feel you.
- Yeah.
- And then I fuck my dog.
(laughing)
And it's pretty simple.
- Have I told the story of my 18th birthday?
- Yeah, I don't know,
I don't really like smoking weed anymore.
I feel like every time I smoke it, I fuck my dog.
(laughing)
It's just kind of, I don't know.
- No, you just have to try a different--
- I just, I react to weed in a weird way.
sometimes Caleb you just have to try a strain other than dog pussy now it sucks
cuz now I get like brain fog and I get dog on my penis and my neighbor's dog is
coming over now and it's like oh I fuck him yeah it's like well you know yeah
it's hard having to clean the jacuzzi every other night is when I come over
and watch my roommate fuck the dogs in the jacuzzi dude he gets high every night
we have a jacuzzi in our one-bedroom apartment that we share
it's pretty sick dude I heard somebody the other day talking about how
they go jacuzzi-ing which is when they go over to their neighbor's house and
drink two Heineken's and sit in the jacuzzi
They live in Idaho and I was like yeah that's probably that's like a sport over there.
That's a night out.
Yeah that's in the Olympics.
That's like the biggest thing ever.
Yeah.
Dude my 18th my 18th birthday I smoked too much weed.
I was also on Adderall at the time so it was a mix of Adderall weed and just like I chain
smoked cigarettes because I thought like this is gonna make me feel normal.
If I just smoke a whole pack of Camel Blues right now.
When you're like yeah I'm feeling like so high or drunk I'll smoke cigarettes until I
have to vomit.
Yeah.
For some reason fix it.
I smoked a whole pack of Camel Blues because I was like well I'm 18 I can buy these now
and I walked around the beach for like an hour and everyone was like Pat you look like
complete, you look like a ghost.
What is going on?
And I walked away from everybody and they say I fell down and it looked like I got shot
by a sniper.
And I was in front of a family at Hampton Beach and they saw me dig a hole in the ground and
just projectile vomit into the hole and then get up and run away.
with every single every time you guys say you make it you make it clear how normal
it is to think you've been shot by a sniper well I'm thinking now how funny
it would be to just see like a random teenager get shot by a kid just you're
trying to watch the fireworks and then you're like was that a firework yeah and
also like you're on the beach like where could this it's the missing link it's
the fucking the like the creature from the Black Lagoon oh my god he's coming
out he's gonna competition he's gonna yeah he's trying to make it to make it
yeah I didn't look I didn't look like a serial mascot back you do I look nice I
was a you were you were nice I was a handsome kid it's so funny every time
you post a picture of you as a kid as like an 18 year old everybody's like who
the fuck is this guy like my picture tons of hair on my head and all my old
old photos I was like a hundred Phil I was on fucking Adderall I was like a
hundred years old 50 pounds yeah I could get I could get back to looking like
that do it we should we should we should run a run a whole run a marathon
we should run a marathon together we should make a TV series that I should
that's our next thing a web series we're all back once we're all in New York
we're gonna make a web series of Patrick losing all his weight till he's zero
pounds and me and Cameron getting really fat yeah yeah I could change my way
gonna get you guys yeah we could get surgery so that we get parts of you on
us and then we become just like horrible rag dolls of people uh-huh and I and I
I look like a million bucks.
Yeah, not a bad idea.
Yeah, I think if I get any thinner,
then I lose my--
Then you'll just waste away.
Yeah, I'll waste away.
I don't think I can--
You think you lose what?
You think you lose the John Candy thing?
I'll lose my John Candy thing.
Yeah.
It's not funny--
You're such a natural fat guy talent.
It's not funny to see a skinny guy fall down.
Yeah, that's true.
That's very true.
You don't fall down that often though.
I do.
Yeah he does.
That's his whole thing.
He pretends to walk into doors and stuff.
Oh yeah.
That's like his thing.
But no Chevy Chase did that.
Chevy Chase got fat.
Chevy Chase got fucking nothing on me.
I'm funnier than Chevy Chase.
You also, you guys both said the N word on set of a show now.
I did not say, I did not, let me clarify, I did not say the N word.
Yeah, go ahead.
Clarify what you want.
Matt great yeah he don't do anything to avoid an apology yeah no cuz I've been
saying it wrong my say say ginger try saying to try reading ginger and saying
it I'm not that dyslexic no no I think that's I think you have 10 out of 10
dyslexia if you ever think that a word has the n-word in it I think that's
that's how they test this like they show you words they say does this have the
n-word in it and you yeah most words do there's other words I've done that with
- you put the other word in yeah I think yeah crap that's I just remembered what
the funny Caleb mispronunciation is he always says concourse bed for day
Concord name is Concord Conan the barbarian yeah
Concord and Conan they're brothers from another mother it's true those games I
thought it was called Connor cuz those games stuck in my head as a kid cuz I'm
core this quite real that's how cool I thought that they I got con con court
I got concours bad fur day. Just say corky. I got concours bad fur day.
Corky's bad day. As a kid because I thought it was going to be a bad day.
Cuckoo kangaroos. Cuckoo kangaroos? No. We're going to develop a video game called Cuckoo Kangaroos.
You won't develop anything. You don't have any sort of knowledge. Cuckoo kangaroos versus the hungry hamster.
Cuckoo kangaroos versus the hungry hamster. You don't know anything about unity.
Okay let's beat it out. Let's go. Alright. Alright. It starts out.
starts out hungry hamster it's not a nice one he's sitting in his cage okay by
drinking out of his water bottle and he goes damn I was thirsty I'm not anymore
you know what I still am I'm the freaking hungry hamster he busts out of
his cage exterior Australia the crates little voice mod no no absolutely not
do that absolutely not hamsters voice no we'll do that we're saving that for a
very special episode okay where it's only Patrick and he can just do that
alone for an hour I'll do I'll do a whole hungry hamster exterior exterior crazy
Australia's which is where kangaroos from okay
cuckoo kangaroo is sitting on the ground is sitting there in the ground Kris Kost
applesauce he's got a big mixing bowl and you're stirring it and it's full of
poopy diarrhea and Cameron nuts and berries it'd be more crazy for a kangaroo
to be from the south like Caleb is no and then so you keep stirring it and he
takes a big bite and you weren't even gonna you're ready for mixed poop and
diarrhea and berries and nuts like the cocoa for this poopoo I'm cuckoo for
poopoo and then he runs across the ocean like - from the Incredibles
to America. He's crying! He's crying now! Oh come on keep crying. Cry.
Cuckoo kangaroo. No. So then cuckoo kangaroo goes...
kuku kangaroo goes to into the hungry hamsters house and they start fighting
and the hungry hamster rips kuku kangaroos head off and it's just the
game still yes the first cutscene he kills him in the first cutscene then and
then kuku kangaroo jr. why would we have the junior in the first game cuz son so
you would make when was he born he's so beautiful
your cuckoo kangaroo jr. I have a father are you guys done with this can we start
done with the first cutscene no okay okay now you go you test say what the
cutscene should be then the cutscene is me the cutscene is me and I'm at Hardy's
and I'm and I'm saying I'm not a cuckoo kangaroo I don't ever eat poop and crap I
love to eat a hearty stick burger I love to watch the commercials and jack off to
the commercials from Hardee's Wow I you guys have the best commercials here at
Hardee's can I jack off to them I'm Caleb I'm not a kangaroo and the game is
called and again your pouch the game is called cuckoo kangaroo the liar no no
it's called it's a game all about no killing cuckoo kangaroo for his terrible
lies. How about a game called called Patrick's inward adventure and
he plead and it's that and it's a typing game and he's the host of it and I
really got to guess what it is yeah I wonder how many different you have ADHD
and dyslexia at what point do you just say I'm disabled how many different
things I physically I disabilities no I believe in you believe that you believe
in people with learning you believe people with learning disabilities aren't
disabled I wouldn't call myself this we should get you I would call myself
differently and walk around school scooter that we're gonna roll you around
we're gonna give you a little I don't like guys to push me from twisted metal
We're gonna roll you around Urban Outfitters and when people will say stop you're destroying all the dr. Dre chronic
Vinyls, you're destroying all the Japanese office t-shirts. Yeah, you don't understand he has dyslexia
I'm sorry. Oh, you can't read the shirts cuz they're in Japanese. Yeah. Yeah, I have dyslexia
I can't read Japanese
Actually dyslexia means that you read you have a Japanese brain and you can read Japanese perfectly
You can read any sort of kaiju perfectly just that was a
That was the thing in Percy Jackson. You guys have read the Percy Jackson books. They said that I did a Cameron
I've never read a fucking all right well
Then let me talk about it you watch a video for a few minutes
And you just well with the adults talk about reading you just kind of chill out all right
Yeah, get yourself a little a bowl of ice cream. I've read I've read books before you very hard
I read oh if you wanted
- The worst, have you ever read the novelization of Trainspotting?
- No.
- Isn't it, I don't think it's, is it a novelization or was it based on a book?
- It's not, not the novelization.
I, yeah, it was based off the book.
I have a copy.
- You read the novelization though.
You read, they wrote another book that was based on the movie that was based on the book.
- They printed the cover.
- And then a movie and then a book on the book.
- You read the junior novelization of Trainspotting.
- I read the spark notes of Trainspotting.
- You read, it was, you know, like the, that graphic novel, novel Bible.
You read that but for Trainspotting.
I but it's all written in Scottish slang.
So, dude, I had the fucking hardest time.
- That's why you are dyslexic.
It's because you read that and you were like,
this is correct.
- This, all of this makes sense to me.
- You had to move your brain in such a way
that it was accustomed to Scottish slang.
And now English makes no sense to you.
- No, nothing makes, I can't fucking read.
That's all right, dude.
I can't read numbers either.
- You can't read a number?
- No, like if it's higher than like a thousand,
my brain short circuits, it's really hard.
I couldn't read numbers in the hundred thousands
if they didn't have like, if it wasn't like 900,000,
like 99,000.
- Patrick's still telling on himself.
- It's called dyscalculia.
- Oh yeah, I think someone I know has that too.
- Yeah.
- It's you.
- It's me, it's probably me.
- Dude, that was the fucking worst.
I worked at a Clover and I had to have the belt
with all the change in it.
- Yeah, it sucks all their items.
- You hit you with the belt
when you couldn't read the numbers.
- I hit me with the belt 'cause I couldn't read.
- All their menu items are 10 digit numbers.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- That's a huge bummer.
- Yeah, I was like, oh my God.
- I was like, a one billion,
- It's 'cause it's a math.
- 156,346,231.
- It's 'cause it's a math restaurant.
- It's 'cause it's a lab.
- Yeah.
- It's 'cause it's a food lab.
- Can I get that again?
to do an equation to tell you what the meal is.
- Your total is hello.
Oh, I'm sorry, I was reading that upside down, guys.
I have dyscalculia.
(laughing)
- Yeah, your total is boots.
- It's actually 11.34, my bad.
- Hey, that's my bad, bro.
Yeah, but I'm pretty much a math genius
and I've never had any sort of problem in my life, so.
I don't know, maybe I just don't get it.
Yeah, super, super smart.
you don't you'll never understand I think is I'm not cuckoo and I'm actually
really normal kangaroo no I think it's a it's brave of me every day to breathe
I'm brave to be dyslexic it's very brave of you to continue to exist mm-hmm it'd
be funny if you like had it would explain a lot if you had like like a
a Rain Man type ability to like read the ingredients on like the back of a 7-Eleven
sandwich perfectly though. Like everything else you just can't even,
might as well not even try. As soon as you see an Italian job.
It's his abilities knowing all the YouTube videos from 2009.
Just every single thing that was uploaded in that year. He knows all the URLs.
The demonic sex videos.
That's true.
I do have - in high school I used to have a keyboard shortcut that was just the whole
DemoniusXFleshlight video transcribed and every time I would send it to people it would crash
my phone.
It was awesome.
Nice.
Was it an auto fill for like if you type V or something?
It was DemoniusXFleshlight and then I would type that out and it would crash my phone.
It would just fill the entire thing.
Yeah.
I'm gonna have to do that dude.
with the soon to be Patrick transcripts
from this episode that will become famous around the world.
Yeah.
It's gonna be pretty good, dude.
You're gonna have to Teagan up, dude.
You're gonna have to lock up.
Chrissy Teagan, you're gonna have to lock up, block a mill.
That's what she did.
Yeah.
She blocked a millie.
So crazy.
She went little Wayne on that block button.
She, I mean, she's just, she's fucked now.
Everybody's gonna call her a pedophile forever.
doesn't matter what happened once that once that crap get ahold of you to see
you got 13 million followers and that's why I cheat you're so that's why our
cheeks are so big she's stuffing little boys penises and balls in her mouth like
a fucking chipmunk mm-hmm it is but she's allergic to them and she's an
anaphylactic shock yeah that bitch does look like she fucking always got stung
by a bee it's crazy did you see those old tweets that people were posting of
hers there's one that's just like you ever just look at a baby and think this
baby looks like a porn star yeah you've ever been raping a kid and you think his
penis is pretty and so like what is this about yeah she's like you guys are
attacking me and my family is like 10 tweets about toddlers and TRS that are
like I'm so excited watching this little girl do the splits oh that's weird I
mean no no that is worse than that it's like yeah no it's like I'm watching
these little girls do the splits I should be in prison yeah that was one of them
what the fuck is wrong with you lady yeah and then all the other people defending
her were like no she's just making fun jokes about the show toddlers and tiaras
she's saying that the people who make the show should be in prison yeah yeah
it's the it's the Robert Downey jr. Tropic Thunder defense yeah like no you
don't she's a dude playing a dude disguised as another dude exactly that
what she should have said. Once she said I should be in prison she was using the
royal I which means the creators of toddlers and tiaras. The royal I because
she thinks that Prince Andrew should be in prison because he was actually involved.
She's been saying this forever she's on your side. She was ahead of the curve okay and if
you doubt her you're in the CIA mm-hmm she's in the CIA we should just join the
Do you think the CIA would take us as ops?
That would be so cool if it were coming out.
The CIA would take...
Wouldn't it be funny if like, I mean just like right now though.
The CIA would only take Cameron, let's be honest.
They would not take me.
Dude, I don't know, I...
They would not take you, you're too...
Dude, that's why Caleb would be the perfect op, because he's gotten in enough trouble
with them that people wouldn't suspect him.
I think, yeah, I mean...
I think they would take everybody but me.
I don't think I have any talents to give the CIA.
I have a perfect body for Krav Maga.
true I think they would see me and they would see they would see a Spartan 117
They would see your powerful kangaroo leg muscles and go this is the guy who can jump all around everyone
They're gonna turn me into an Israeli Spartan and I think I would do really well as that
My CIA handlers talking to me like Patrick we need you to go over to Yemen
and we need you to keep this this food shortage we need you to keep the famine going
Anything you see, grab it. And no sharing. No sharing. No splitsies. No splitsies. And you're like, not a problem.
Yeah, and you go to the wrong country. You misread Yemen. You don't even know the name of the word. Yeah, you go to Turkey.
I go to Switzerland. I'm in a Swiss chocolate factory the whole time.
Yeah, there's a lot more white people in Yemen than I thought.
Yeah, Yemen's kind of cool.
Yemen's kind of cool, they got a lot of chocolate here.
This place is swag.
This place is cool as hell.
They got a million bank accounts here that have just been walking, that have been going
through.
Nah, dude, I would be an expert CIA op, dude.
I would be incredible.
I'd be a great-
My face and my head, it's like, I already have a bald cap on for like disguises.
I would be a great CIA patsy.
You would be a great CIA honeypot.
Uh-huh.
- Yeah, and I mean that you look like Winnie the Pooh.
(laughing)
That's what I mean.
- I would kinda be the guy they would hire
to go and actually like, you know, kill a lot of people.
Like I'd be like going into a building
and like killing a hundred people in it.
- No, you would be the person that--
- With like their hands and stuff.
- That talks to the people that they capture
at the black sites and you're the one
who puts them through dark experiences.
- Yeah, they basically hire me to go to an office building
and blow it up with--
- They would hire you to go,
they would hire you to go to an office
or like an office building that they have some guy tied up and you're sitting
there and you're going like I'm going to put you through pain until you tell me
that's just reminded me of the book I read and there's impression the book I
read about the inventor of remote viewing my name is puss and boobs it
reminds me of this movie I saw about the inventor of lying
I don't know British the inventor of fuck I don't remember his names Ingo
Swan the creator of remote viewing and he claims he got hired by the CIA to like
to like see what was happening on the other side of the planet and on the moon
with his mind and he said that the way he got recruited was that he saw he saw the
hottest woman ever in a in a supermarket and he got extremely aroused and then
afterwards some agents came up to him and questioned him and we're like did
you know that woman was an alien and he said that's how he got involved with the
CIA. What? There's a lot of crazy like, I mean learning about like, like how MK
Ultra was was basically like a lot of, there's like this whole history of like
crazy CIA psyops, everybody knows that of course, but like the the stuff with like
Helter Skelter is pretty, that's that was that one drove me fully insane. Yeah.
What, the CIA was behind Charles Manson? You should read, yeah, like people think that the
Charles Manson thing is all like a CIA basically like covering up you should
on crazy people you should read this this this book this book penetration the
audio autobiography oh go Swan oh I've seen the moon on I think I've seen a
cut yes every movie in that series actually he has a typo on the cover of
I saw the sequel double, double penetration.
[Laughter]
He talks about how every picture of the moon is fake and there's alien cities up there.
I think there is. I think there's an alien Chicago and they do alien improv and it's actually a really great scene right now.
Yeah.
It's really blowing up.
Yeah, they do, they do, they do yes blorgorborg.
[Laughter]
Yes blogando.
Yes, yes, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Yeah, I'm pretty much an alien expert.
They go, they go, "Si, senor" up there.
Yeah.
Instead of "yes, and."
Yeah, man.
That's where they came from.
Yeah, it's pretty much.
They got aliens speaking Spanish.
That's where the Spanish language came from, is the moon.
Nah, I think white people arrived here in a, in a...
Man, the moon's white.
A giant avocado toast, am I right?
Yeah.
arrived on cross country on cross-country skis yeah white people arrived on some
lonesome shorts and they got here they were wearing chubby shorts and riding
cross-country skis shall be short who does that remind me of Cameron Cameron
now people think no it keeps me up at night that people think that Patrick is
taller than me I mean yes he's not I am he's not he's shorter than me by half an
no I'm not he's he is measured we're the same height no we stood back to back
clearly back and I think Tom it was either time and I was taller it was God
who measured us who's one of us is good at numbers okay I just remember being I
measured you yeah you did no don't disagree with him no I mean I have no
- It was in your bed.
It was in your bedroom.
- It was in Caleb's bed.
- Me and Patrick were already laying.
- You guys were experimenting and exploring each other's,
the entire length of each other's bodies.
- While we're measuring every part of ourselves,
why don't we also measure our length?
- Yeah.
- And then you said, we already did that.
And I said, no, from head to toe.
What if we also had the exact length penis?
- No, I've seen yours.
- Let's say it at the same time.
Let's say it at the same time.
I've seen yours already on Neil's phone.
Let's say our penis at the same time.
Okay.
Penis size.
Alright.
Three.
Two.
You didn't say yours.
[Laughter]
The fuck?
I trusted you.
No, Patrick said two.
[Laughter]
That was good.
Yeah, that was a pretty good one.
That was a really good one.
Yeah, you know, sometimes you just gotta go old school.
That was like a Sammy Davis Jr. joke.
That he would say, "Oh, today..."
Speaking of old school, you know like big time Tommy?
The fat Italian guy, he's like, "Take it ease. Old school. OS for life."
Oh wait, that's... Yeah, yeah, yeah. That's the guy Jesse always says, "I'm gonna be that guy when I'm old."
Yeah.
I got a I got a fucking I was thinking about him today cuz I got a fucking text
from a realtor from a place called round room and he was like hi this is round
room Tommy that rocks dude round this is round room Tommy nicknames suck if
they're not more than like 10 years old uh-huh there's nothing worse than a new
nickname whatever you say kangaroo no no I mean yeah that's a great example it
doesn't make any sense and you guys have to give it up because it's too new
nobody's gonna like it's more catch on it was made by a definitely nobody's
gonna start calling my child kangaroo it's made by a three-year-old the best
nickname to me by three-year-olds yeah I you know what I realize I might to say
poo-poo kangaroo no he meant to say cool cool wow that is a cool cool kangaroo so
you're a kangaroo no I'm at that point he's three years old dude I mean he
thinks a star is a fucking a diamond problem knows what stars are no he
doesn't he thinks you're smart he knows pretty much what everything is I think
no he doesn't know what anything the names of anything he knows your name he
learns all of it from blippy I don't know blip limp is it would be a set
children's show guy who like shat on himself or something or like peed into his own mouth
or something like that.
My sister hates him.
My sister hates him so much because she has to watch -
He did a Harlem Shake video where he pooped into his friend's mouth.
Yeah, it's like Harlem shit or something like that.
But then after that he became a children's YouTuber.
Yeah, and he tried to get it scrubbed from the internet.
You can find it on some Russian site.
I found it on the internet archive and I downloaded it to her computer for her.
Yeah, have him watch this video next.
gonna teach him about what not to do. Check out this new blippy video. What are you
watching Caleb? Nothing I'm watching. So now Caleb's watching videos. I was just checking the news
because of because I'm very smart. Okay so. I check the news all the time on the channel. Turns out I am the
only one who doesn't look at other stuff during recording. I think we understand
now why Caleb. You look at the back of your eyelids sleepy pie. No I don't. There you do.
you're sleeping right don't close my eyes if you're one of the seven doors Cameron
you'd be sleepy you'd be asleep if you were one of the seven dwarves you'd be
asleep right now if you were one of the seven doors you would make it to the
meeting cuz you were too sleeping yeah you're shorter than the seven dwarves
combined all right you're if they were combined they would be very tall that's
seven of them no because also there's no regular humans in that those are all
everybody's the size of an ant so they're even smaller yeah they're all who's yeah
that's a place on a snowflake yeah yeah it's called snow white yeah the clues in
the title yeah who will talk about it reddit theory did you know that snow
white takes place on a snowflake and snow white is a psychopath yeah yeah snow
white just kills all the Goombas yeah but that's just another theory just a
- I think the dwarves are stuck in purgatory
with Ed, Edd, and Eddy.
I think they all were molested.
- Is the hungry hamster a psychopath?
(laughing)
Think about it.
He is so mean to Sullivan the frog about all the nuts.
- What the hungry hamster has
is called intermittent explosive disorder.
(laughing)
- Some viewers think that the hungry hamster
may have an affliction called Mean Hamster Syndrome or MHS.
It's possible.
- Yeah.
- I'm watching it right now
and that's actually kind of possible.
- Does Cuckoo Kangaroo secretly have
borderline personality disorder?
- No!
- He doesn't.
- No.
- How would you know that? - Does Cuckoo Kangaroo
- How would you know that, Caleb?
- Have BPD?
- No, he has chronic fatigue disorder and it's serious
and sometimes it keeps him from eating a balanced breakfast.
So you might want to think about what you say
before you say it and not be so mean.
- Does Cuckoo Kangaroo--
- Interesting touch by the director of Cuckoo Kangaroo.
Cuckoo Kangaroo is never shown eating breakfast
throughout the entire film,
suggesting that the whole film actually takes place
over the course of one day, possibly within a dream.
- Cameron, you are the crazy crocodile
and Patrick, you are the plump pedophile.
I am not any sort of kangaroo.
You're a cuckoo kangaroo.
I am, just make me an animal.
No, they call me crazy normal Caleb.
They call you Caleb the bitch.
They don't.
(meows)
Yo, we can play all we want talking all these animal names,
but don't you dare be calling me a bitch.
Oh, you're a female dog, all right.
Cuckoo the bitch.
I'm gonna come through and I'm gonna hit you with my--
You're gonna hit me with your kangaroo legs.
I'm gonna come through
and I'm gonna kick you twice in the face at the same time.
Yeah, like what animal?
I'm gonna, like a fucking, like a frog.
- Like what kind of animal?
What kind of kooky animal? - Like a jackrabbit.
I'm gonna come at you like a jackrabbit.
I'm gonna jump up both legs, karate kick you.
- You know what a, you know the craziest type of kangaroo
is a jackrabbit?
- You're a pedophile.
(laughing)
Come on, we just said this.
If you can call me a kangaroo,
I'm gonna call you a pedophile.
- It's not an animal. - I might throw
something else in there.
It isn't, oh, you think they're human?
(laughing)
- He's humanizing pedophiles.
- No, dude, they're dirty, you, sorry, not they,
you guys are dirty animals.
- Hey, cuckoo kangaroo, I'm gonna eat your pouch.
- Cuckoo kangaroos say I'm gonna eat your pouch?
- I'm gonna eat your pouch. - Whoa, it seems like you,
oh, you're the cuckoo kangaroo and I'm not!
I just said cuckoo kangaroos say I'm gonna eat your pouch
and you just did. - How would you know
what a cuckoo kangaroo would do?
- Because I've read up on them, because they're cryptids.
- Why did you read up about them?
- 'Cause I'm a huge cryptid enthusiast.
- 'Cause you're a huge cuckoo kangaroo,
You're a huge cryptid?
- I'm not a huge kankaroo.
- Yeah.
- You're the kanker sisters
from fucking Ed, Edd, and Eddy, bitch.
That's what you are.
- You're all three.
- Yeah.
- Cameron kinda, when Cameron had long hair,
he did look like the blonde one.
- I used to have longer hair
than I've ever had before in my life.
- When you had blonde hair.
- I'll say this, when Cameron has long hair,
he looks like any other girl, 'cause he's a girl.
They don't call you Cameron the girl for nothing.
- No.
- We don't call you Cameron Diaz.
Remember Cameron Diaz Cuban man?
Yeah.
I do remember that.
That's so funny.
Man, that was like a year to the day probably.
My name is Cameron Diaz.
It's so good.
Yeah.
I thought about that the other day.
Yeah, it is good.
That's a classic one.
Go listen to that instead of the Cuckoo Kangaroo because that doesn't make any sense.
At least that joke made some sense back in the day.
The Cuckoo Kangaroo is kind of one of those funny Cuckoo Kangaroos.
Back when stuff was normal on this podcast.
It feels like stuff doesn't make sense now on the show.
I know it makes perfect sense come on cuckoo kangaroo hungry hamster everyone
knows we're talking about yeah everyone knows exactly what we're talking about
yeah people love it too I think the best part of hungry hamster is that the
creation of it happened off of the podcast so there's no way to ever find
out right it means it's cuz I was like sick yeah you know like it's insanely
hungover I was insanely hungover sitting on Caleb's bed and I was talking to Noah
Noah and then out of nowhere I was just like man I'm feeling like the Hungry
Hamster right now. I just kept saying that. Yeah guys clip that that's Hungry
Hamster origin. Origin of the Hungry Hamster joke important for all listeners
of podcast about list. Nobody's gonna care. There was someone who DM'd us I think.
Who asked us about the story. Somebody asked is there any history behind the Hungry
Hamster I think. Yeah yeah is there any history around fucking anything of
course there is. The Hungry Hamster actually has roots in white supremacy so
you may want to check yourself. If you think about it the stereotype of the
Hungry Hamster you know you gotta think why is he hungry? Who's denying him food?
I just want you to consider shit like this before you two make make wry jokes
about hamster, hungry hamsters okay? Yeah. Oh my god. Especially coming from you Patrick.
- He's got a long history. - He's still the cuckoo kangaroo.
- Yeah, exactly. - And hungry hamster.
- Oh my... No! - Oh my... No!
- Oh no! - And 1488 snake.
- All of them, dude. They all have... That's what I'm saying. - Oh no!
- We're gonna have to go... We're gonna have to fuckin'...
- Alright, that's the podcast is over. - We're gonna have to end Jemima this, dude.
- It's over. - We're never making another episode.
- We're gonna wipe the entire archive. - Yeah.
replace we're gonna have to replace Patrick with a less offensive stereotype
of a fat Irish guy. We're gonna replace me with Peter Griffin. Yeah. Alright I have to piss so bad.
Yeah. Alright I'll stop recording now. Bye boys. Bye.