You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[laughter]
Nice.
Nice!
Original recipe episode. Are you excited, dude? It's been so long.
I know.
I don't even remember what this is like without Patrick.
I know it's better, but I don't remember what it's like.
what it's like.
- Oh, there's less stories.
- Less stories, less cross talk.
- Less crying.
- It takes up less, the video call takes up less space
on my desktop.
- Yeah, it's just easier to edit.
- Easier to edit, yeah, true.
What else?
Less N-word saying.
- Yeah, that we have to cut out in post.
- That we have to cut out, we do cut a lot of that out.
It takes like me like five hours to edit each episode. We record episodes six weeks in advance
Yeah
Just so that you can do
As many scrubs as you can of the episodes trying to get rid of all the inbox drops
He'll do he'll do this thing where he just whispers in into somebody else's microphone
So yeah, just make sure I can't just mute his his track
Define you have to go he'll hack it'll even when we're like apart for quarantine
He'll somehow find a way to make the zoom call make the audio come from the other channel. Yeah
The we sent we tried to export the work. We tried to add to a to like a firm in China
That does that kind of thing?
But it was so much work that all the workers ended up killing themselves jumping out of the factory fire
They cause a yeah. Yeah, cuz the computer blew up
It was struggling too hard and then they made evil Chucky
Yeah, and then that's when they made evil Chuckie. Yeah, that's actually the backstory. Did you see the new child's play the remake?
No, I'm is it um, it's pretty good. But um
It's not it's not come out. Uh
2019 sometime. I don't know. Um, I saw with Alex and when we saw it some guy
There were two insane things during that movie there in the theater some first there was like this
You know like how they'll do is nothing where it's like a super tense build up to a jump-scare
and then it'll just go like silent for a minute.
Yeah.
Like so it was like, "Doooooo!"
And then there was silence.
And then someone in the back of the theater farted really loud, right?
In the silence.
[Laughter]
Did you guys, was your first thought like, "That's a weird thing to put in the movie"?
I was just laughing for like 10 minutes.
Just like...
That's so funny, dude.
And then also in the second half of the movie, somebody in the back of the theater,
probably the same person, fell asleep and started snoring really loud.
(laughing)
- So there's me and someone going like (snoring)
(snoring)
- Have you ever fallen asleep in a movie?
- No.
- No, never? - I've come close to it.
No, I'm getting banged for my buck, man.
- True.
When I had MoviePass, dude, that was such a bizarre time
in I feel like everybody's life.
- If it was raining out, I would just be like,
"All right, I'm gonna go see a movie
"'cause I don't wanna see the rain."
- I skipped like so many classes that semester
that MoviePass existed.
And I would just go to movies and I would just fall asleep in all the movies.
I would just sit in the very back row and text.
Yeah, that's the best.
It gave you this ability to just watch a movie like you were watching it at your house.
Like it didn't matter.
You didn't care if somebody talked over it or whatever.
So great.
Do you remember when we went and saw Three from Hell?
Yeah.
And we were both just like so freaked out by like all the people in that fucking movie
theater.
people walking around. Yeah, there's like people walking around, there's people with like
big bags and also just like a Rob Zombie movie every like a Rob Zombie movie with
a limited release. Yeah. Everybody in the audience looks like a shooter. Yeah. You
know what I mean? Like that's like his demo. Everybody's there to do the devil's work. Yeah, yeah. And so yeah I
had I kept like going to the bathroom. I feel like I went to the bathroom like six
times. Yeah. Last movie I saw in a theater was Birds of Prey and that's our I've
I've already that was already when I was having like movie theater shooter
anxiety and I was already like man I do not want to go to the theater ever again
but I was like okay I'm gonna go see Birds of Prey with my girlfriend.
Yeah well didn't know it was just like a date night so it's like alright I can
risk it for date night you know and then literally um so partway through the
movie a guy wearing a trench coat and sunglasses came up to oh so me and and
luckily it was just three kids trying to sneak into the movie. Me and Anna were sitting
like somebody had taken our seats and then we got there a little late so the
movie had already started so we didn't want to like ask them to move so we just
like sat in other seats yeah and so yeah and then so like halfway through the
movie some guy comes in with sunglasses and a trench coat on and he he just
stands next to us like he just stands next to us for like 10 minutes just
standing up like and i was just freaking out and then he just go he goes up to the
very back of the theater and sits in the very back and i was like oh yeah we're
gonna die and then like 10 minutes before the end of the movie he walks
down from the back of the theater he walks up to us like stands next to us
again turns to us gives us the middle finger like
points his middle finger right in my fucking face and then turns and like
walks out of the theater and i was like for the rest of that movie i was like oh
i'm gonna like walk out and he's gonna be like waiting at the door yeah
with a machete yeah I'm sure we just like took his seats and he was just like yeah
that would make you a sense maybe but I thought I was gonna die was that at the
AMC yeah in the common yeah yeah that's the most fucked up movie theater in the
world is awful I had one time I was in a I I think I was seeing like I seem like
I Tanya or something and I I was like sitting right near the the exit and some
like old man walked in and then just dropped a bag yeah the exit and then just
left that people do that's all the time at that so yeah just like so weird they
put down and they'll put down like bags of takeout and then like a leaf yeah
exactly yeah what are you doing keeping it hot with the light from the movie
theater yeah just keeping it warm yeah I don't know that I will go to a movie
theater again I don't think I will be theater ever yeah unless they somehow
fix mass shootings. Unless I get to a point I'm like well they took care of it. I mean
that's I'm pretty sure that's what they were trying to do with 5G and it
accidentally caused coronavirus. It accidentally caused coronavirus. They're trying to smooth out the minds of
shooters. Gotcha. They're trying to cure this condition called shooters mind. I
have a shooters mind. Yeah I can't help it I just look around and I see I see the
ducks from duck hunt on it overlaid over everybody's faces. Oh my god. Dude, I'm back to being paranoid
about my Joe Biden video getting me in trouble. Yeah. I feel like I'm immune just because
I can be like, "Your Honor, it was not posted on my account." Yeah, no, yeah. I mean, yeah,
I felt when I got that viral tweet that was like, "I'm gonna vote for Joe Biden in the
head until he wins. I was like I also started to freak out about that, but then
I was just like just not because like I like I just I now would be such a
terrible time for like people to show up at your door. Yeah. Like I'm not like I
don't want to go something you know what I mean? I don't want to take me somewhere
for questioning. Yeah if it was like if it was like in the middle of like finals week in
college oh my god I would I would love to get taken to jail. Yeah well that is I am
I'm kind of in finals, finals month, finals few weeks.
- It sucks.
It's crazy that they're still doing school.
- I can't believe it.
I can't believe I'm supposed to care about this shit, dude.
It's so stupid.
- I just feel like you don't have to.
You can coast so hard.
- I have been, but I still, like the thing is,
I have a fucking paper due this Sunday
that's 25% of my grade in a class.
So it's like, I can only coast to a degree.
- You should be like the Van Wilder of online college.
Just like--
- I don't know who that is.
like from the the national and you're talking about you're thinking of rip van
winkle the guy who fell asleep for a hundred years
that's what i'm thinking of
no you should just be in the zoom calls you should just be in the zoom calls like getting a blowjob
underneath like like right outside of the frame of the video you know
playing flash games and stuff and your professor just keeps going like
van wilder what are you doing
you're like sorry buddy i have just skipped all the zoom calls
uh... yeah i mean because i've only been to like two of them because you can just be like
"Oh, everyone else in my house has to work from home,
"so my Wi-Fi can't handle that many people on meetings."
And then every once in a while,
the teacher will be like,
"Okay, you have to come to this one."
And I'll be like, "Fine."
And then, yeah, I just played Bloons 3 on Cool Math Games.
- Fuck yeah, dude. - Yeah.
It's hell, dude. - I gotta get into Bloons.
That's what my younger brother's been trying to make me do.
- Bloons was all I did in LA.
- That was, um...
(laughing)
- So, I played Bloons in class.
- Oh my God, dude.
- And LA put me in such a flash game hole.
I played so much Bubble Spinner in that fucking class.
- I've been playing Hedgehog Launch 2.
You like that one?
- Oh shit, dude.
- I've been just listening to Longmont Potion Castle
and playing Hedgehog Launch.
That's what I've been doing most nights.
- I should, I've been trying to find good games
for my phone.
- Yeah.
- But there's like no, there's not a single good.
- You can, the good ones are like,
- There are really good like roguelikes,
if you like, which are just like lame though, is the thing.
Like you just have to already be into roguelikes.
- Yeah.
- Or like, there's good like card games too.
- Yeah, I guess I could play Eternal.
I should get back into Eternal.
- Eternal rocks.
- It's a fun game.
- But like Dream Quest, also all the good ones
have just really ugly art 'cause they're just made
by like random programmer guys
who just make them by themselves.
Dream Quest is probably the best iOS game.
If anybody likes card-based roguelikes out there,
that's my that's my recommendation is dream quest i dream and many hours into
that game
very good it's the ugliest game ever though it's like somehow a step below ms
paint graphics
like if you look at dream quest it's it looks like it was a little new
grounds games it's work it's like
the worst graphics i've ever seen in the game
it's worse than pong
it's it's worse than dirt on the ground
has worked on the ground is good that's a great graphics than paper google dream
quest you'll see what i mean search it right now yeah this does look pretty bad
it's like yeah it's like i loved it i love the little they really they really
they obviously like hired some shitty uh some shitty like online artists to do the
little icons for the people yeah it's like because it is not the person who did
the rest of the art like the russian deviant art it's like knockoff deviant
art art yeah it looks like uh like uh chris chan yeah and then like the all the
The icons are just stick figures.
It's great.
- Fuck that rules.
- But it's a great game.
Really, really fun.
- I've just been playing RuneScape.
That's what I found.
Yeah, Krause.
Krause put me onto the mobile RuneScape.
- Shout out to Krause.
They put me on the mobile RuneScape
and I've just been cutting wood, dude.
- Yeah.
- It's so boring.
I don't know how I ever liked it when I was a kid.
- Yeah.
- Like RuneScape, it's only the grinding.
There's no like, like every, every,
like there's no voice acting or like anything interesting
about the game. - I mean the trick with gaming
and stuff like that is you just have to take
like the gaming red pill, which is just like,
games are nothing, games are just numbers
that you watch go up, it doesn't matter what you're doing
and then you'll be happy just like, yeah,
just playing like, press the space bar 100 times.
Like, 'cause then it's just like--
- True, cookie clicker. - Like, well yeah.
- Cookie clicker maybe is like one of the best games ever.
- That is, yeah. - 'Cause as far as like
enjoyment. - Yeah, shit like that.
Once you just realize, oh, I don't need to see a cool monster
and listen to cool music.
I can just click the mouse a bunch of times.
It's just like, it's a fast travel forward in time.
That's all it is.
- Yeah, I've been trying to play more story games, though.
- Yeah.
- Like, I played Firewatch.
I just like all those gay girl games.
- Yeah.
- You know, anything that's like--
- Pregnant Princess Dress Up.
- Pregnant Princess Pussy Press--
- Pussy Pimple Popper.
- Press the Pussy, which is one of the,
sort of like it's a cookie clicker for girls where you just keep pressing the
clit and and trying to make the girl come yeah but it's your own hand yeah but
it's a game called vagina simulator and you just keep trying to make it come but
it's completely impossible and that's the lesson of the game is that you can't
make one orgasm no matter what you do you get it gives you you can literally it's
it's like it's like that game where you fucking draw things or whatever and they
appear it's like that yeah but you but you put anything you want in it and it
won't happen scribble nuts scribble nuts that's what it is I love that yeah I'm
Try a cucumber yeah
Does a very loud
Big red X. It's really loud. It's scary. Yeah, and then the girl falls asleep
And you have to you have to wait
Wait 24 hours
full hours
Yeah, this is the girl is sleeping. Please log back later
Because the other lesson is that girls sleep all the time
Girls will stop sleeping and they're impossible to make come
Recommending movies
Watch Anna Karenina stop trying to make me come and watch Anna Karenina. Yeah, let's go to the store
It takes a week. You have to go to the store and she won't leave the makeup aisle and all
of this you only see from the like you just see the vagina in the store. You just hear
the sounds of a store. And then it comes with it's a and then it's paired with a partner
game called penis simulator and you scroll your cursor over the penis and it comes.
You launch the game and instantly it comes.
It comes right onto the screen.
Yeah.
And then you can never open it again.
It's always a high score.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Yeah, there's a leaderboard with everybody who's ever played it and they all have one
point.
We should design a game.
We're good at this.
Yeah, we should.
What about Monkey Quest?
Alright.
Yeah, you are a monkey.
And you live in the jungle.
You live in the, not only do you live in the jungle, but you have to get bananas.
Oh my god.
You have to get a hundred bananas before a gang of...
Of men with yellow hats.
South American natives eat your brain. Okay. Yeah, out of a bowl. Yeah. They use
your skull like a bowl and they heat your brain up in the microwave. They have
microwaves but they still eat monkey brain. Do you think there's a god that lives in the
jungle? Do you think there are any gods in the jungle? I think there is a god and
he does live in the jungle. And he is a monkey. Yeah. Yeah. He hates
hates TV and modern stuff. That's why he stays in the jungle.
What if Dr. Manhattan was a monkey? Think about that for a minute.
A blue monkey? Yeah. He gets like Dr. Manhattan god powers
and he just makes infinite bananas. He never goes to Mars and he's fine. He's
happy. Yeah.
yeah and the government tries to get him to go to Vietnam and just goes no he
get ya thank you he tip we tell you know he goes to Vietnam and he touches people
and makes him turn into big bananas yeah yeah watch monkeys watch monkeys watch
gonna watch monkey the watch monkeys yeah who watch monkeys the watch which
monkey watch monkeys Roche monkey Roche monkey and it's a Roche test on his face
but it's just yeah and yeah it's just somebody showing him all the tests he's
he's like yeah banana yeah awesome who are the other people in the watch night
owl night monkey night a night monkey ozeman the come the come on is the come
ooh the come on key in yeah who and he throws banana cream pies at people yeah
he doesn't die at the beginning because he it's been so long since I watched since
I watched the Watchmen yeah I want to reread the comics in because I it's so
long I mean I haven't probably read it since middle school where the only reason
I read it was because this kid Paul Winder who is now an Indian alt-right
guy no he he was like yeah you this has nudity in it yeah and it's a comic book
And it's like I love to see naked stuff. Oh, yeah. Yeah, so I borrowed it
Yeah, it's like when you're in like middle school. It's just like oh I wanted a comic book that has that's
Says blood or nudity in this. That's what's cool
And you borrow from your friend and then you give it back with all the pages fused together
Yeah
It must have gone stale yeah
(laughing)
- When did you buy this?
I think it expired while it was in my possession.
'Cause all the pages are stuck together.
- Yeah, I think I used it up.
Yeah, I turned the pages for the last time
and they just, they turned off.
- They just melded into one big page.
- Yeah.
- I wanna do the thing where I need to find a book
big enough that I can glue all the pages together
and then build a compartment in it.
But I don't know what I would keep in the compartment because you don't really smoke weed
And I don't have anything to hide
You know, yeah
You put water in it. What did you put food in?
Some lips, yeah
It's my lunchbox
Yeah
Like somebody finds your chips and that's fine. Yeah, and then I said it with my gun
Yeah, you can keep on my desk put more chips into it. That's a good point
I want to get I just want to be rich enough that I can build one of those secret doors in my house that I move
like, you know, I move a copy of
But I'm like I make the book like a
Something really stupid like a Malcolm Gladwell book. Yeah. Yeah, I make that they move what what the dog saw
Yeah, a secret compartment opens up. Yeah
and it's a more Malcolm Gladwell books it opens up and it's just a sign that says
you have terrible taste in books you are an idiot
psychology you try to take yeah you try to take outliers off the shelf it just
shoots you in the head it's just a string with a gun yeah yeah yeah but if
try to take the official Pokemon strategy guide gives you a cookie. It gives you a
yeah it gives you a cookie falls out of where the book was. Yeah. So that trap is you
just hide a cookie behind the book. The ultimate trap. Yeah but with a Malcolm Gladwell book you put a
venomous cobra behind the book. We found when we were I'm helping Janna
like move Janna's parents move stuff out of their cabin their like storage cabin
and yesterday we we like brought some stuff into like a different like storage
shed that they have with it does not have a door and we walked in and there was I'm
not exactly was the there was the biggest snake I've ever seen in my entire life
just like looking at us and we just threw all the stuff at it like all these boxes
and then ran away and it's probably still in there damn yeah you had like a
- It's what they said, but when I was a kid,
we would catch snakes, and like venomous ones,
like cottonmouths and like copperheads and shit,
'cause they're very common in North Carolina.
And we didn't know what they were though,
so we'd use sticks and me and my older brother
would bring them into our house
and let them like slither around the hallway.
(laughing)
and my mom would be like, "What the fuck are you doing?
"What is this?"
It's our monster that we found.
- Yeah, this is our Pokemon.
- Have I ever told you about the Serpentarium
around town? - Yes, yeah.
- Dude, I drove by it the other day.
It's so sad.
Now, the Serpentarium, I don't know if I've talked about it
on the podcast, maybe I have, but it's basically,
it was a snake museum run by a crazy guy,
and the gift shop was filled with propaganda
about chemtrails.
- Yeah.
- That was like we had to enter and exit through that area.
And also birds, like parrots that were not in cages.
- Is that what Banksy based his movie off of?
- Yeah, yeah, it was actually,
he based it off of the serpentarium
in Wilmington, North Carolina.
But you would walk in and then,
and it would just be like every snake
that the guy who owned it had ever been bitten by,
And then also his fucking, what's that thing called?
The monster.
- The monster?
- What is it called?
The dragon, Komodo dragon.
(laughing)
I wanna have the monster, the Japanese monster.
So he had a Komodo dragon that was like more his pet
than anything else.
- Yeah.
- And he would personally go in and feed all these snakes.
and it never went well.
Like you'd feed them once a day
and every Yelp review for the place,
every single one of them was just like,
yeah, he tried like feeding the alligator,
like the anaconda while I was there
and it got out.
(laughing)
It started chasing like my kid.
And then,
and then it closed because the guy's wife
shot him in the face because he was throwing snakes at her.
- Yeah.
That's awesome dude.
And then Janna's like a family friend of Janna's ended up adopting their baby.
Yeah.
Damn.
But then so anyway it used to be this awesome place and now they took the building and they
turned it into the Museum of the Bazaar.
Ugh.
Which is, oh it sucks.
It's like five dollars of admission.
Those kinds of places are always awful.
They're so terrible.
say um it's it's basically like it's one of those things where they just get like
a like I don't know like a petrified bat or something yeah they'll have like a
Dracula yeah they'll have like a glass case full of like Star Wars Funko Pops
and be like this is these are bizarre memorabilia yeah these were owned by
John Wayne Gacy fans clown no yeah all all those those places my my ghost
Hunter uncle did an investigation of the Museum of the Bizarre. Did we watch that?
I think we did watch that yeah yeah I do remember that. Yeah and he was like
there was like something it was like it was like like a skull. I just remember
him holding like the meter over it and he's like there's definitely something
going on with this skull. Yeah there's something going on with it. We should do a Ghost Hunter
episode that's a good idea that's a really good idea yeah maybe we should
delete what I just said one of my favorite back to snakes one of my
favorite Yelp reviews I've ever seen it somebody posted a screenshot of it I
haven't been able to find it again I don't remember what it was but it was
like a review of um the Hollywood sign and it was just like I tried we tried
hiking near the Hollywood sign and my with like my my baby and like the baby
carriage and the baby got bitten by snakes yeah that's how many stars I was
a one-star review I believe yeah has to be one stars yeah no that sounds like a
three-star to me I mean you did yeah you got to see yeah you got a snake action
posted by the snake appreciator that's five star the snake lover the baby got
bit by snake the baby. Posted by fuck my baby. The snakes are crazy. There's this video of
an anaconda swimming like right after it's eaten so it's just like huge like it just
like it's stomach is all like swollen from it's just eating and it's just like so big
it's crazy snakes are just are they're. Yeah anacondas are crazy. What 20 feet long or some
Yeah, and then so and then like right after they eat they're just like so thick they're just giant they're like
They're crazy
But I could I could fight and kill one. Yeah, I could fold one in half like a piece of paper
Yeah, like ice cube in the movie. Have you seen Anaconda? Yeah, it's a good movie. It rocks, dude
my favorite part of the movie Anaconda is um
the fact that in the
The anaconda whenever it attacks it like it rears up and it's about to and it opens its mouth like it's about to bite
You know and it makes there's a noise that snakes make right?
There's a really obvious snake noise like a snake's hiss, but the anaconda in the movie anaconda goes like
Like does like a velocity
Yeah, it has a dinosaur voice you guys forget what snakes
It was a pretty clear. They have a pretty iconic sound. It's either a hiss or sometimes a rattle.
Yeah, I don't know whose idea it was to make the snake scream. But it's very stupid.
I'll tell you who it was. It was the voice actor who did that thing.
Yeah, like I'm gonna do something different guys.
Yeah, he was like, guys what if we... No, he's one of the writers. He was like, I can do this cool noise that we can put in the movie.
Yeah, it was a producer. It was a guy who just like, yeah.
I'm only funding this movie Ice Cube if I can go, "Reee!"
Yeah, if I can make a pig noise.
Or if the snake sounds like a pig.
I want a pig. I want to do, I want to feed a bunch of pigs something cool.
A human body?
No, not a human body, but like a cow body or something.
Yeah. Did you ever see that movie
where the people, where people are like,
with Danny Trejo, where the people are like half pig,
half zombie or something?
- I don't think so.
- It looks very bad, but it was like,
it's an old, it was like 2011 or something.
- An old movie?
- Yeah, it's old, it's very old.
- It's an old movie.
(laughing)
- Yeah, but it was just like,
like the whole concept is like,
we started breeding, we discovered like,
the way to build like a Master Chief Super Soldier
is
bill is made all that's a big people half people have
pete that's a big conspiracy theory and um...
there's i feel i might have talked about this before but there's the i've started
i found this podcast one time online it was called like exo politics radio or
something
yeah uh... was from a specific state is just one guy calling himself on the
telephone somehow like like
who i think he was like calling
he's like his home phone from another phone and like recording the podcast onto
the answering machine
like some something weird like that like he just wasn't using a computer and he
would just tell stories about like aliens and stuff and yeah one of them was a
scientists are creating pig human hybrids because there's a coming war
and that's like that's the most powerful soldier
is the same guy who said uh... that uh...
uh... there's a virus coming from outer space called the wolf
who named it the wolf uh... that's what it's called
that's like it's cosmic name it was like a virus and or an evil entity
he's like he's like a something bad is coming
and he might meet you know i think i think we might have gotten in with the
world
it
uh... i think
all my god
we might be susuming right now we might be talking shit about the wolf walls
zooming because of the wolf here
only god sucks
yet this is
we need to get out the fucking the
pig human soldiers to fight the war and yet a crime we we we
yes
(laughs)
- From the wolf.
The wolf will fuck them up too, dude.
- Fuck.
I don't, that's, oh my God,
pigs probably can't get it, right?
- Maybe not.
- Maybe that's the key.
Maybe we should splice our DNA with pigs.
- That's not a bad idea.
They're smart, they're pink.
- They're hungry.
- They're, (laughs)
the three best traits.
- And they love mud.
We're trying to create a hybrid species with the intelligence of a human and the adoration
of mud that a pig has and the desire for slop.
Yeah, and the ugliness of a hog.
Yeah, and the friendliness towards spiders of a hog.
The power to grow intensely fat.
To grow huge and giant.
I just want some tusks.
Yeah, oh, now that would be cool.
I want some tusks, but on my, like on my pelvis so when I have sex the girl can ride it like
a motorcycle.
Right, like handlebars.
Yeah, like sitting, or no, you could sit in them like stirrups.
Or no, stirrups are on your feet.
I'm gonna also install, I'm gonna install stirrups on my feet
and sort of do a crab walk
and have the girl get on top. Just installing an entire
like a motorcycle along your front side
so they can sit down, like handlebars on your head
and like pedals down your feet. And the girl sees me at the bar and she's like
I have to fuck that guy. I've always wanted to fuck a motorcycle.
What's your name?
Harley.
Motorcycle.
[laughter]
Motorcycle guy.
Motorcycle.
Harley Motorcycle Guy.
[laughter]
I thought it would be Davidson.
Why?
Why? What are you talking about?
You're racist.
Yeah.
Just 'cause I'm white?
You think my last name's Davidson?
Davidson's a white guy's name?
Is that why?
How the hell do you know I'm Greek?
[laughter]
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm Greek and I have a Greek last name. Motorcycle.
Motorcyclopsilus.
Yeah, Motorcyclopalypse.
[laughter]
If you could be fused with one item, what would it be?
Uh...
Money.
That's not a bad idea, you sexy son of a bitch.
Yeah, perfectly flat.
Oh my god, so flat. Yeah, woven.
People think you're paper, but you're woven upon further inspection.
Yeah, green.
Yeah, when you when you walk out into the light little hundreds start appearing all over you. Yeah
And I could just I could pay for things with myself and then crawl out of the register. Yeah
I'll be paying with my cash creditor yourself
I will be paying with myself. Yeah
You can never eat at sweet green
Yeah, they won't even let you into sweet green. I hate sweet green because of that one experience
Yeah, where you had to pay for me?
Yeah.
In the most embarrassing day of my life?
I just don't understand the cashless thing.
It's uh, it's stupid.
I mean, you're telling me you're a place where you have to pay for the food,
but you don't accept money?
Yeah, no money.
We don't want your money.
What is that?
Does that make any sense?
Yeah, we just like to think about money.
Yeah, we just like, we like points.
We take points here, not money.
They're gamers.
Yeah, I should be able to exchange my RuneScape money for that.
For Sweetgreen?
Yeah. My GP.
We only take RuneScape gold.
Yeah, we only take RuneScape gold.
You can trade. If you have something rare like a party hat,
then we'll cater your house.
Yeah.
My hair hurts.
What other items could you be fused with?
What other items would be good?
One of those fish that sings on the wall.
Credit card.
A credit card would be, you'd get a lot of action.
Yeah.
But if you, the thing is, if you were one of those,
if you were one of those singing bass fish,
you could just have a beautiful voice.
You'd go on American Idol.
One of the most beautiful.
Go on American Idol and be like, okay.
They're like, all right, you go ahead when you're ready.
And you just turn sideways.
Yeah.
(laughing)
yet he starts seeing christian angularism earlier had back it
they have to ask simon calloway press your button rose he can't see it
please
all you know fish what are you have fish no i will pull have plastic fish
yeah my classic fish actually
very very ration of a fish yet
one of those i mean can you come touch my body
Do you guys have a big piece of wood I could sit on?
You guys have a wall?
You're such a diva.
I wanna watch, I might get into some shitty reality TV
while I'm stuck inside.
I'm getting to the point where I'm getting really bored.
Yeah.
Yeah, I got a, my computer's supposed to come tomorrow.
Like Walmart told me that it shipped,
and then I got, I looked at my bank account today
and they refunded me.
- What the fuck? - But they shipped my
computer, so I'm really hoping that that was some accident
and then I just get a free computer.
- That'd be pretty sick.
- That'd be so sick, it was like $800.
- Damn.
- It's like the only money that I had.
- I'm gonna try ordering 100 computers from Walmart
just to see if they'll do it for me too.
- Yeah, well they delayed it like a week,
so I thought that I would maybe get a credit back,
but a full refund doesn't really make any sense.
So it must have been, but I called them
And the lady that I was talking to was like such an idiot.
She had no idea what I was like talking about.
And I like it was a complete miscommunication somehow.
And I left her a great review.
And I'm hoping that maybe she accidentally
hit the refund button or something and got fired.
(laughing)
That'd be awesome.
- In the big red, that was easy, refund button.
- The refund, yeah.
Yeah, when somebody makes no sense to you on the phone,
you just press that.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, sorry Aaliyah.
I'll give you the, I'll split the 800 bucks
with you if you hit me up.
- Yeah.
Oh, now there's a good scam.
You tell them you give them half the money.
- Whoa.
- Genius.
- That's not a bad idea.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I just, I haven't been doing much.
I mean, I have school, so I have that,
I'm not super bored 'cause I just gotta do
all this schoolwork stuff.
- Yeah, I mean, I've been just like walking around,
'cause they have like woods behind their house here,
so I've just been walking through the woods
and just like, just like picking stuff up.
- Yeah, man, I wish I was near like woods or something.
- I feel like I'm nine years old again.
Like I'm just walking around looking at bugs
and picking up sticks.
And then just like coming back to Jana and being like,
hey baby, look at this cool stick I found.
- Yeah, I'm just going on the damn computer.
Yeah, I'm trying to not go on a damn computer as much because it is it is starting to turn
me into a cyborg.
Yeah, I just I really I just watch for a few hours every night.
I just been watching like rare Slipknot interviews.
So it's a how rare can a Slipknot interview be?
Well stuff that was like just on like one VHS in like 1999 or like stuff that like aired
one time and like German TV in like 2001.
They're not a German band are they?
They're from Ohio, right? They're from Iowa.
Oh, why you are. Oh, why you are you? Oh, why you are.
They're from Hawaii, why you? Des Moines. Oh, really?
Hawaiian slipknot. Hawaiian slipknot. There's an idea.
They're pretty cool. They all wear layers. We'll get there.
They all wear tiki masks. Tiki masks and coconut bras?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I was a huacalui before I was a man.
Yeah. Wait and hula. What about that?
Whoa think about that for a minute. Oh my god. Don't blow your mind. Instead of that album Iowa, it's Hawaii.
Whoa. The good thing that makes Slipknot Interviews so great is
they want the like brains behind the bands like the band leader is um clown
who's the guy who wears a clown mask yeah yeah and he's just like he's the biggest
biggest dipshit like he's just like a faux deep like fake philosophy guy. Uh-huh.
So he just always says like just the stupidest shit, but it's so great. It's so
much fun. Like he'll just go and be like yeah you know according to the dark
philosophy of Slipknot we actually we believe that the mask is sort of the
truest form of the face and it's about the dark heart that resides within
humanity and in a way we're kind of all an infection upon just like like this
says all this shit, it's just like, what are you talking about dude?
Like, what does he play, you said?
He's percussion.
He's one of the guys who hits the beer kegs.
But he like designs everything.
He's like a visual artist.
And he's the one who made them all wear masks and shit.
And he goes by Clown?
Clown, yeah.
Sean Clown Crayhan.
They should add Jim Carrey mask to their roster.
They should.
That'd be really-- a lot of energy, I think, it would add.
Yeah, or the or the tiki mask from from crash bandicoot. What's a kuaku? Yeah
He jumps on every time this Jamaican boy, so she had the Justice League dude, yeah, yeah, they said spider-man
Why did you make a man never get a mass they should make a band out of all the superheroes
Oh my god. Oh fuck dude. That's probably what they're gonna do next with the MCU. They're gonna make MCU music
I'm surprised there isn't like a
Like a serialized podcast. Yeah. Yeah, I bet yeah, I will
Yeah, that is weird. I'm right one. I feel like there should yeah, that'll be if it isn't it'll be soon
Yeah, like like it's like a story one. Those are always those always suck dude. Yeah, only good one is branch Berg
I've never listened I don't listen to podcasts. It's it's really good. It's um, I know I know about it
I know absolutely thing. I know I know it. I just never listen to it. Um
They uh, you know, it's really upsetting to think about is you know, how like so much like, um
metal music from like the 90s and shit and earlier - it's just like a bunch of it
It's just like the lyrics of like the lyrics are just like the plots of horror movies like
Like in like 10 years or like 20 years do you think they're just gonna be bands that just like are telling the story of
Infinity War like in their lyrics
Just like yeah, it's this tracks called like like the purple specter and it's about Thanos I
Want them to do like like a horror movie that's like
Eight-legged freaks or a horror song. That's a like it freaks a metal song. I bet there is
- Look at this.
- I love that video.
(laughing)
- Yeah, I'm also reverting.
I'm reverting to just like living the life that I did
when I was like a homeschooled 16 year old.
- Yeah.
- Like I'm just like gaming and just,
I look at the phone a lot.
- I'm so surprised I haven't been gaming.
I just haven't gamed at all.
- No Binding of Isaac?
- Nothing.
I mean, literally just like Hedgehog Launch and like--
- So funny.
- Flash games, that's all.
I mean, I just don't have a, I don't know what it is.
I don't know if it's the attention span or what.
I was, I meant to start playing Death Stranding during this.
I still might, but.
- You have Death Stranding?
- Yeah.
- Oh my God, you gotta get on it.
- Yeah, but I don't feel like it, I don't know.
- Yeah, I mean, the thing is, I also have,
like Flash games and shit have kinda ruined my attention.
Oh, you know, Super Mario Maker
ruined my attention span with games.
- I gotta get back on Super Mario Maker.
- It's the best.
It's like, the thing is, it's like the only game
you ever need.
- It's so good.
- So that's why it sucks,
Like anytime I'm like, "Oh, I should put some time into something like with the, uh, like
I should like replay Uncharted or something."
Yeah.
Instead, I just play Super Mario Maker.
Because I can just be like, "I want to be the fastest guy.
I have to beat all these Korean kids on the leaderboards."
Yeah.
For something called, uh, called, uh, SpongeBob Speed Run 2.
With a 0.0001% completion rate.
Yeah.
(laughs)
- The problem, I'm just not very good at video games,
and so I just, there's always a point when I--
- Hold on, I can't hear you.
- What?
- Where'd you go?
- You can't hear me?
- I can't hear you, you're very, very quiet.
- What the F?
Well, I did nothing changed on my end.
Hello?
- Let me see, maybe I--
- I think your headphones are fucked up.
- Oh, my headphones.
- You're so stupid, dude.
- I'm sorry, continue.
- I'm just not very good at video games,
so just every game I play, there's always a point I get to
where I'm just like, oh, this is too hard for me.
like urges like i'd like i'm at the point where it's not enjoyable to play anymore
because i'm just i uh... i don't know that's just
some gay is like like persona five i want to finish the game so bad but i'm
just like them at the bar is a garment i would just end up using a walk through
unlike the puzzles and shit so it's just like
yeah i always have a high i'd always use walk throughs
like i'd never at when i was growing up i would never ever do like a puzzle
without a walk through absolutely
'Cause I didn't give a fuck about,
I don't care about the puzzle.
Like I just wanted to play,
I wanted to, like in "Nights of the Old Republic",
there's like a couple puzzles where you like have to move,
like on a cube in a way that like everything lights up,
but like every square, one of those puzzles
where like every square lights up some squares
and turns some off,
and you have to like leave with all of them lit up.
- Yeah.
- And I made my grandma do it.
(laughing)
'Cause I couldn't figure it out.
And I was just like, "You have to do this for me."
And she was like, "Okay."
It was like the only video game.
I don't even know if she knew what it was.
She was just like, "Make sure you're not allowed
"to leave this room until all of those squares are lit up."
And she did it.
- Dude, in 10 years, kids are gonna be doing,
are gonna be making their grandmothers
finish Pussy Presser for them.
- Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, little do they know, their grandmothers will die
they finish that fucking game. That's how you get rid of your grandparents. You can say,
you gave them the game. Yeah, you can't leave until, you know, you're not allowed to have
your insulin until you play Pussy Presser and beat it. Yeah. Pussy Presser, well how
hard can that be? Yeah, seems easy. No, wrong. The hardest game ever made. My, I've been
hanging out with my younger brothers nine and
just seeing like all the seem like the media that he
Like the the games and the TV shows and the videos that he watches and stuff the stuff that he consumes
is
so just like
Completely blackmailing me in like the craziest way like what what is he's he'll just watch like he'll watch like a two-hour
video that is like
like all of the like jokes from
like Johnny Test. Dude yeah that shit oh my god. Like it's just and it's just
somebody being like you smell like a total fart and then on to the next one.
It's crazy dude or like or like you like using like throwing slime at my mom. Yeah
like it's it's yeah I mean it's not not to like be like yeah all like lame and
black pill or whatever but like um no we don't know what they would all this
is what computers are gonna do to kids when they grow up.
- Oh my God, dude.
- Nobody is grown. - It's completely
destroying this kid's brain.
- Just like in general, like you go to a restaurant
and you see a kid who's like six years old
and starts crying and their mom just gives them an iPad.
And it's like, that has never been a thing before.
- It's so crazy. - These kids are gonna grow up
and they're just gonna be insane.
They're gonna just be-- - It's like how we,
it's like how I imagine cavemen would've felt
about like if they saw like toys.
- Yeah.
- You know what I mean?
- Like that's how I feel about like--
- That cannot be good.
- Yeah, they're like, you're at a restaurant,
the kid cries, they give them this thing,
they give them a little truck.
They're gonna grow up thinking that you can just
get a truck whenever you want.
- Yeah.
- Like that's how I feel, but it is true.
'Cause just like this, you know,
just and it's like my younger brother,
his entire personality is just like an amalgamation
of Irish YouTubers he's watched play Minecraft.
You know what I mean?
- Yeah, I mean, and also I feel like these kids
are gonna grow up and like at the age of 25,
they're all just gonna spontaneously go blind.
Like-- - Yeah, yeah, exactly.
Just like-- - Yeah, just not be able
to read anymore. - Yeah, there's a limit
to your eyes that we will never hit in our lifetimes.
- Yeah, but they will hit-- - But they already have.
- By the time they turn 13.
- Yeah. - Yeah, exactly.
He definitely has had more screen time in his life than me
at a third of my age or whatever.
- Insane, so scary.
- Yeah, man.
I'm excited to see what that's like.
I'm excited to be an old crotch.
I'm excited for what is like the,
it's like a hack, like stand up bit I feel like,
but what the thing is that it becomes mainstream in society
that our generation is just gonna be like,
nah, we don't want that.
- Yeah, yeah.
- You know?
- Yeah.
- It's like break dancing.
- Yeah, no, it is, 'cause the thing about it is
it's going to be something that we just can't,
like we will not be able to under,
like it is incapable.
- Honestly, I think it'll probably be
people will not eat meat.
I think that's kind of the next thing.
And like a lot of people our age will be like,
no, meat is--
- It's like so important, yeah.
- Yeah, delicious burgers and fries and shakes.
- I bet it's gonna be something that we just like
can't even comp, like it's gonna be,
They're going to start going into the fourth dimension.
I don't even know what this is.
Yeah, exactly.
We're going to be so confused by whatever it is for sure.
Yeah, kids are going to start turning into pure energy.
Kids are going to start duct taping a keyboard to their penis.
And they're going to be like, "See, this is normal.
This is what everybody's doing."
And we'll be like, "Why do you have a penis keyboard?"
And they'll be like, "All my friends have a keyboard penis."
People are gonna start being able to turn into animals people are gonna start
Putting microwaves on their heads. Yeah walking around with yeah, they're gonna have TVs for heads and you can watch
Silverstein like that shell Silverstein poem where the kid watched too much TV. Yeah, he became a TV
Yeah, we're gonna be like you can't you can't just have a TV. You can't just be a TV
Yeah, and they'll get all this
gonna say they're gonna say okay zoomer yeah they'll say okay okay regular head
okay me that's the next big thing people are gonna have different things for
heads oh not just anything how about a crate car for a crazy head is that what
you're crazy yeah okay what if they had a crazy for a head it's not a bad idea
Yeah. Yeah. People are going to start cutting out like removing their noses.
Mmm. Go MJ? Flat face. Flat face? That's what it's going to be called. They're
calling it right now. You know these women they're already doing stuff like that you
know. Absolutely. You just haven't been paying attention to their tyranny. Yeah. I
mean if you follow the trend it's just it's a it's there's a graph of flatness
of size of the of the of the face shape of the face it's going to be it's going
to be a paper. Exactly. That's I'm the scientist who did a study on it and
that's what I had. I think laser beams might be the next big thing. The thing is
people have been saying that for like a hundred years. I think it's gonna catch
on I think it's gonna next few weeks. What is what is the technology where you
officially say like we're in the future? The portal to hell.
before that. Have you played Minecraft? I would say like a laser. They can make a
portal to the other side of the earth and I would say no. That's not the future. Not
until we go to hell. So I think for me it's probably like probably a
laser beam gun. Yeah. I think that that's the point like a stormtrooper type
laser beam coming out of the tip of a gun. Yeah. Well the thing is I bet I think
- I think the reason, the thing about that is
it's always just like, oh, the stuff that we thought of
like as like, oh, this is gonna be the future,
like back in the day, it was always just like,
yeah, like laser beam guns,
it's just like not efficient or whatever.
Like it's gonna end up being something--
- Yeah, it doesn't make any sense.
- Like it's gonna be something even crazier.
Like it's gonna be like a sound gun
that's so loud that it annoys you to death.
- Yeah, a poop gun. - You know, it's like
something that you would just
haven't seen in a movie. - A gun that makes you poop.
- Yeah, exactly, and it kills you, yeah.
- That would be the most devastating.
- 'Cause it drains your body of moisture.
Can you imagine if we could drop a bomb,
like a nuclear bomb that doesn't,
the warhead just hits the ground in the middle of Hiroshima.
We do Hiroshima again, but with this bomb.
It hits the ground and people are like,
"Oh, it's not exploding."
And then, yeah.
God, I have to shit so bad.
And then it's just, everybody shits until they die.
That is what, that'll be the,
when that happens, I'll say, "We're in the future."
Yeah, but not until then.
But not a second before.
Even a portal to hell can't get me to admit
that we're in the future.
I refuse.
Nice burp.
- Thanks.
- Disgusting monkey.
- Not a monkey.
- You should be a monkey.
- But if I was, I would be grateful to be considered one.
So why don't you chew on that for a while?
- I'll chew on it, I'll spit it back at you.
- Chew on you.
I'm chewing your little wee wee.
- Because I've been driving around Jana's car,
I didn't think about this, but all my parking tickets
have been going to her parents' house.
(laughing)
- You're getting a lot of parking tickets?
- Yes, I got here.
And it was just like, I have them all piled here.
They were just like-- - Oh man.
(laughing)
- I got here, and they were just like,
"Hey, do you have like 11 parking tickets?"
I was like, "Shut up!"
(laughing)
Yes. - That's a mistake.
- Yeah, and so now all of it,
The thing is I'll just never pay them.
- No reason to.
- You can kind of just do that.
As far as I know, you know Angela Sawyer?
- Yeah.
- She, her house, nobody knows who would listen to this,
but she's a Boston comic who does shows in her house,
but her entire house is like flyered
with all of her unpaid parking tickets.
- That's sick.
- So that has in my head, I never have to pay this.
But now that I think about it,
I don't think she has a car anymore.
So that might have factored in.
- Yeah.
- On all my late fees.
- Fuck.
It's pretty sick. - God damn.
I hope that doesn't fuck up my probation
and for my speeding ticket.
- I bet it does.
- God, that would suck, 'cause then I would go to jail.
- Yeah.
Right now, too.
- That would be dog shit.
- Yeah.
- And I also haven't paid that fine either.
Dude, I'm a legal genius.
I'm out here, I'm not paying any ticket,
I'm threatening authorities online and public officials.
I'm just, you know, I'm invincible.
- If you go to court with a blindfold on,
they can't send you to jail
'cause they won't be able to see your face.
- That's true, that's called blind justice.
- Exactly.
And it's because if you go in with a blindfold on,
it's always justice prevails.
- Yeah.
- That's that concept.
- Well, if you go in with a blindfold on,
you become the judge.
- Yeah, they make you hold two things and weigh them.
And then if you correctly guess which one is heavier,
they send you home.
- Yeah.
- And the jury's all just like,
"Come on, man, we wanted to decide something."
- Yeah, we were excited.
- Have you ever gotten called for jury duty?
- I've gone, I, just getting called, getting selected,
I've been called but not selected.
- Or you've been summoned or whatever.
- Yeah, summoned, yeah.
- Did you, I got it like three times in North Carolina
and I ignored it every time.
And then at some point I had a warrant for my arrest.
- That's pretty sick.
- But I don't think they were related.
- Yeah.
- I think that was because I was driving without a license
and they caught me.
- Uh-oh, uh-oh.
- Oh no.
- I'm done getting in trouble with the law.
I'm on the straight and narrow from now on.
- Oh yeah?
- What are you gonna do?
- What is a crime you're gonna do?
- I'm gonna play tetherball with a policeman's thingaling.
- Whoa. - Yep.
I'm gonna go, I'm gonna knock down a building.
- Well, I don't know.
No, you won't.
- Yeah, yeah. - No.
- And you're the one who gave me the idea.
- No, I did not give you that idea.
No, no, I said smoke weed with a bullfrog.
And you said I'm gonna knock down a building.
And I said, I heard the secret message you put in there.
No, no, that can't be my fault.
Yeah, I'm going to,
I'm gonna assassinate a Mr. Clean.
You're gonna assassinate Mr. Clean?
Yeah.
You'll need a cartoon gun.
Here, take this.
So you can hand it through the screen.
I've been walking, one of the things that I've been
like helping around doing yard work and shit at the house.
One of the things is they have a carpenter bee infestation.
And these things fuck, they fuck wood up.
- Yeah, yeah. - Let me tell you that.
These guys love wood and there's like holes in everything.
And so what they've been having me do
is they gave me just a tennis racket
and I've just been walking around
and just absolutely smashing these bees to pieces.
- Damn.
- It's like the greatest video game I've ever played.
it's so fun
here is destroying these 'cause they're huge and they don't sting
over really
yet they don't have stingers so i just go around
and i just
whale on
i'd just absolutely
that sounds like a psychopath behavior to me
no
you know no is killing animals in your house they're not animals
there nothing
there nothing to me
that's the others the healthy mind you know no we talk about
- No, it's okay to skin squirrels 'cause they're nothing.
- They're nothing.
(laughing)
The best part is, the best part of it is,
sometimes what I love is,
sometimes I'll accidentally hit 'em
too lightly on purpose, right?
So I'll just incapacitate 'em,
and then I have to destroy their brain with my foot.
- What the fuck?
- Yeah.
(laughing)
Yeah, so I'll just hit it so it's just begging for death.
And sometimes I'll kill it,
sometimes I'll just leave it there.
(laughing)
- Just trying to buzz.
- I just, I'll just put one in a box
and just watch it for days on end.
- Yeah, yeah, just see, say, yeah, you want some,
I'll dangle a piece of wood in front of it.
(laughing)
Make it run on a treadmill.
- I'll push a little splinter into a slot
and then I'll just whisper and I'll go,
you belong to me.
yeah and then i thought the b_e_ yes
yet you know i was there why do you carpet you'll be bitch
and it's the perfect size
the happy i think i'd might might be dick
might be dick size dick finally comes in handy
well these bees locally my ticket shaped exactly like the inside of of bees bodies
it's a new place like i think we're you poor like liquid metal into like um...
an anthill and it like maps out the anthill you know that it's like that but
the inside of a bee that's what it's shaped like my dick is shaped exactly
like the honey nut cheerio bees wand always dripping honey when I was a kid I
wanted to eat that be so bad I wanted to eat that be like a Thanksgiving turkey
Just carve it up. Yeah
Dip it in honey
Bee meat just falling off the stripes. Oh my god succulent bee meat. Mm-hmm
Splitting the thorax in half with my friend like a lobster the bigger part
Yeah
I've never had lobster. Really? Yeah, I can't I've never ever never lobster every night. Oh my god, dude
That's crazy. I didn't know yeah cool. You were I don't really like lobster. It's not I'm just not a big shellfish
He's kind of freaked me out man. They're creepy as fuck. Did you see I sent you that video right of the coconut crabs?
Oh my god, it rocked that video is insane post that video like in the discord or something. So okay see it
It's so good. It's a coconut crab that like it's grabs a crayfish or something
Yeah, just like it snaps it in half with its claw and you're just like it's on like like cobblestones or something
so there's like grooves in the surface
and just like the coconut crab is just huge ass crab
just like picks up this crayfish and goes like
(crunching)
and just pinches it in half
and just the grooves in the ground just fill up
with just like juice.
- Yeah, somebody put like Final Fantasy music
and like UI on that.
- Oh yeah.
- 'Cause I wanna see that 'cause I can't imagine it
but I do wanna see somebody make it.
- Yeah, I wanna see a Dark Souls, you died over that.
- Yeah, actually just make Halo.
How about that?
Make a Halo game.
- Just send me some money.
- Yeah, another thing about it,
I'll do all the heavy lifting.
Just send me some money
and I'll get around to it eventually.
- All right.
- I gotta shit so bad.
- Yeah, I think we're done.
- All right.
- What's going on?
- We'll have some big guests soon, I think.
- Oh yeah, yeah, we're having good big guests.
Please stay tuned.
- Yeah, probably better.
- An original recipe in the books, dude.
It's been too long.
- Yeah.
- Finally got rid of that bitch.
- Oh, and watch the Jollibee documentary.
- Oh yeah, watch the Jollibee documentary.
- We'll be doing a director's commentary
for the $10 tier. - For the $10 tier.
- Yeah. - Soon.
- Soon, whenever we figure out how we're gonna do it.
- Whenever we figure out how to do that.
- Whenever we figure out what is it.
- Yeah.
- What a director's commentary is.
(laughs)
- Yeah, once we figure out what that is,
and find the link to the Jollibee documentary that we lost.
- Yeah.
- If somebody please send us the link,
we don't know where it is!
We lost it! - And we'll make that.
- But yeah, shout out to Nolan.
Nolan did a great job on it. - Nolan's a man, dude.
- Make sure to watch it and follow Nolan
at TooMuchProtein and follow @GrayteenVids.
- Yeah, and follow @Drill.
- Yeah, that guy has some serious issues
going up in his mind.
I think that guy's gonna go active any day now,
just the way that it tweets.
Yeah, pretty soon.
Yeah.
All right, bye.
See you.