You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
Alright, wait, check this out. Ready?
Yeah.
What?
Nothing happened to you.
I turned the- wait, hold on. You'll see- wait.
You just turned the light on?
So that's what you wanted to start the audio episode.
That's the least cool thing you could possibly show us.
I thought you were gonna like play a sound or something.
Nope, that was it.
You weren't doing like a new impression or...
Uh, have this brighter Patrick.
Brighter Patrick?
That's my impression.
Do you guys post, do you guys record the video for Patreon or anything?
No.
No, so you can get naked dude, let's go.
Let's see that thing.
Let's just see that thing.
Let's see the worm.
I think the first dick pic I ever took was, I was like 15,
and I thought that the way that you should take a dick pic
is that you just put it right in front of your penis.
And so it's like looking down the hallway of my dick.
It's like the worst possible angle.
And I was like, "Yeah, she's gonna love that."
Like looking into the meatus?
Like looking straight on?
You're looking into where my pee and my cum comes out of.
Into the hole.
Yeah, the meatus.
Yeah.
Like, if I was meeting your penis at a formal business meeting,
it would be like that.
- Well, I was like, yeah, if you were,
I was like, yeah, that's like what,
that's like how women wanna see the meatus.
- Yeah, that's what women like, they like the hole.
- They wanna look it in the eyes
and give it a firm handshake.
- Women hate the shaft, they love the hole.
- They really dislike the hole.
- What they really like though,
so the two things they like is they like the meatus,
which is the opening around the urethra,
and then they also like the balls.
- You're acting like we don't know the meatus.
I mean, come on.
- I don't know, man.
Sometimes people don't. - I don't know the meatus.
I did.
You do not know the meatus, Caleb?
It's exactly what he just said.
I just literally...
Caleb, open your fucking ears.
I'm so sorry.
Caleb, open your hole and look at it.
Yeah.
Okay, let me look at my meatus.
Caleb, next time you're at your little, uh, your little doctor's office with your pediatrician,
take a look at your penis.
Take a look at your doctor's piece.
Can you look at my dick hole?
I think, I don't know, it's just, I feel like it doesn't look like the other kids.
Can you just look at it just for a minute?
How far into it can you see?
Can you just tell me? Can you drop a pebble in there and see how long it takes to make a splash?
Mine's not very round. Me and Matt both did just actually look at our dicks. I did. I'm very,
very flaccid and then I opened it up and I looked to see how far down I could see.
Yeah, my penis in this moment might be the smallest it's ever been. Yeah. Yeah. I was
looking at that when I looked at mine. I was like, "Pretty bad, dude." I think just when you're around
some bros and you and you look at your cock it's it's always gonna feel a
little bit smaller it's like well it's just further proof that I'm straight you
know besides my gaming PC is that I I'm hanging out with three beautiful beautiful
men and my dick is just softer than ever did yeah it's it's just just completely
it's flabby putty yeah I'm not I'm not I'm not gay but if I was I would have
had an erection in that moment when I pulled it out to look at it in the
presence of three of my friends yeah that would have turned me on that would
have it's a test Mike my penis is like closer to a liquid than it is a solid
right now yeah my penis is not Newtonian yeah I have to slam it pretty hard you
just sit that dump truck ass on my dick cuz that's the only way it gets hard
baby yeah there's otherwise it's gonna be just you have to use the punch to
shit out of my people careful because if you go too slow you're gonna go inside of
it yeah I got a couple rubber bands yeah really tighten that shit until it's
purple that was like all homeschool was when I was homeschooled growing putting
rubber bands around your feet no just make it just mixing my mom thought that
the lesson of non-newtonian fluid is something I needed to learn like 200
times. I was homeschooled yeah. Caleb we're doing oobleck again today. And the thing is I could not get enough of it.
It perplexed me every time. I'm 17 years old I've already seen oobleck. You're gonna see it again kid.
If you don't fucking if you don't punch this oobleck as hard as you fucking can you are not going to college
I'm telling you that right now. Just going through just just fucking tons of fucking cornstarch every year
Yeah, writing it off as a school expense
It's like wheeling the TV in your mom doesn't have like a TV on a cart. So she's got it make oobleck
Yeah, but we did have a fucking TV in my house. Yeah, but you can't wheel it in and it only shows movies
It doesn't have no education. She wheels it in and there's just a video
of Ooblik. An instructional how to make it. What's a non-newtonian fluid? Besides
Ooblik? I don't really know. I don't know of any other. It's like a fluid but if you punch it it's hard.
It's like the phases of matter, it's like between phases of matter or something.
There's a skate shoe that has a non-newtonian insole. The Osirises? No, it's Footprint.
It's called Footprint.
I wish.
I wish they had the non-Newtonian insoles in the Osiris Brocks.
Wouldn't that hurt?
Because when you like jump, it's hard.
I don't know how it works.
Your shoes are solid normally, Caleb.
I've seen videos of it.
No, but they usually have a little bit of cushion.
But they're still solid.
You know what?
I give up on this argument.
No, I hear what Caleb's saying.
I hear what Caleb's saying.
It's like it's soft, but then if you jump and you land hard, it's not going to be soft anymore.
That's a great standing shoe.
It's a terrible jumping shoe.
If you're playing basketball and you come down, it's gonna feel like you just jumped from like a 20 foot ledge.
Yeah, Cameron.
No.
It's two versus one here, man. We win.
I'd have to see a video of it, but...
If you just... if you have to stomp everywhere you go, because if you step normally...
I'm angry a lot of the time!
Your feet just get wet.
It's not a shoe for angry people.
No, no. When I'm huffing and puffing and I'm just mad as hell, again, because my clash of clans is not going well,
and I'm stomping around town, I'm gonna fuck my feet up, dude.
Yeah.
You're gonna fuck your feet when you're mad?
You're gonna hate fuck your foot?
What is wrong with you?
Oh shit!
Oh my god!
You're taking advantage of me because I don't feel well.
I have a stomachache and you're making me sick.
You have a stomachache?
Yeah, I think I might be pregnant.
Hey, does baby need his bottle?
Yeah, I think he does.
Okay, first of all, I think you know I'm not a baby.
Yeah, well...
Second of all, I was breastfed and I never was fed from a bottle.
I found this guy on Twitter the other day who's like a targeted individual type guy who thinks
he's being attacked by the CIA through microwaves and shit.
But he just has schizophrenia.
Yeah, yeah.
But he thinks that the CIA is giving him stomach aches.
And there's a bunch of tweets where he's like, "The CIA has made me constipated and the brutality
of their attack against my intestines makes me grumble for a long time."
one who's like I'm on the bus and and I'm sweating because of how much my stomach
hurts it's because I'm looking at my phone too much and the CIA doesn't like
it those are the best kinds of those guys
where they're like goddamn CIA's making it making the internet go in and out all
day yeah pick one meanwhile it's literally the shittiest fucking internet
exactly yeah like like the dude only eats he eats nothing but like Hungry Man
Dinners and then he's a fucking CIA making making me constipated to that guy eating like frozen chili
chili
Stomach the CIA is making my stomach hurting listen to the popsicle. This is his tweet every stool is hashtag torture
No constipation or hemorrhoids, but a disease with a fatal prognosis within minutes
I run to the bathroom the end of it right wrong
The torture goes on for a while to assure whatever whatever foods left moves into colon and rectum to arrest hashtag digestion
And then he's gonna look through those hashtags and find that and then he says I protect the area with hands
I keep a thick aluminum pad above lower abdomen
Nothing cuts it the hashtag torture goes on with unbelievable hashtag brutality until I run to the bathroom
Then more as times my intestines hashtag rumble long
He's wearing a tinfoil diaper to protect his step up tinfoil hat
That's um
That's why I would hate to have the combination of like extreme schizophrenia and Crohn's disease. Oh, yeah
That's like the worst horrible right there. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Here's the thing though these people like if the CIA was developing technology to give somebody
Stomach pain stomach ache
You know they use that on the terrorists
uh...
and they had to test it they're gonna pick some random do detested on
and the thing is like he could actually be
getting targeted by the c_i_a_ with this shit but
no one would believe
they'd like all this guy's gets a like a of course that yet the c_i_a_'s giving
you stomach aches but like really they actually could be in no one's gonna
believe in which is
which is absolute torture on top of the facts true yeah this the stomach aches
already happening
we should just use the stomach a gun on osama bin laden
yeah i'm trying to think of like what
what use a stomach a gun from the c_i_a_ could have in this imagining like it's
funny yelling at the same
i think that's the thing
the unicity at that for her to be a
because i don't know where they're going to see you in the middle
and the middle of it is going on
all
uh... all
or anything like a drone it like a syrian wedding just to make it a little
far
(laughter)
- Just make all the groomsmen shit their pants.
- That was Obama's legacy.
- Yeah.
- Obama.
- He's like, he's like, on my way out.
He's like, I want to make sure that this, this, this stays.
Obama stayed winning with the, with the,
with the drone strikes that,
that make the men at the Syrian wedding shit themselves.
- Yeah. It was, it was collateral damage for sure.
But they got the guy.
- The whole town, the whole town had stomach aches after that.
just filled with fart gas.
Well the good news is the one guy they were targeting, he did get a stomach ache as well.
Yeah, exactly.
He was out for, you know, 30-45 minutes.
And in that 30-45 minutes, zero terroricity.
He had to lay down in his bed for a good half an hour.
That 30-45 minutes he did not go swimming at all. He had a cramp.
Yeah.
Well he was actually, the stomach ache made him, he wasn't able to eat dinner,
and then the next morning he had a headache so he couldn't fly his plane
over to the US and do that's he did in the day after but yeah I mean that's
unavoidable. They're just using it to fuel the ginger ale industrial complex.
Driving up ginger ale in all these countries. That's a Canadian product.
This guy's deeper than I even thought dude. Jesus Christ. Unless it's Schweppes I don't know I
I don't know who... is Schweppes... I feel like all ginger ale companies...
I don't think ginger ale is just a Canadian thing. Ginger ale is one of those...
No, I know it's not just a Canadian thing.
You don't know anything.
Well, Schweppes is from Switzerland.
Yes, so it's not a Canadian thing, it's a Swiss thing.
But it... Canada Dry...
Patrick was like, "Ginger ale is a Canadian thing." And then a few minutes later he said,
"I know it's not just a Canadian thing." Can we get a fact checker in here, please?
I know I'm just lying all the time because I'm a fucking dumbass.
It's an Irish- let's fucking go dude, it's from Ireland!
Couldn't even finish saying "it's an Irish thing" because you're so excited.
YES!
So excited.
Oh my god.
It's the Irish people that are developing a stomachache.
This is the Hibernian Conspiracy.
He's got a lot of Irish pride.
I do, I'm 100% Irish.
Can you guys just like- I did my 23 in me.
Can Irish people just lose once, dude?
No.
It's annoying how much they win.
I know, I'm so- I was annoyed by it as a kid, but now that I'm older, now that I know that
on the winner. They're just like the least persecuted people in history it feels like.
Why don't you take that back? They're just constantly winning dude. You take that back.
Just non-stop dubs. The opposite side of the coin you've got some of the most persecuted
people you've got the Italians and I don't know if any of you guys are Italian. I, Caleb
is. Are you Italian? Si. You get it. I'm not Italian myself at all. I took the 23andMe
I was like 99.9% British and Irish.
I was 0.1% Ethiopian though.
- Oh, sick.
- See, I had that, I had, I think it was like 5%
broadly Eastern European and then like 0.02%
Sub-Saharan African and then I checked it at Thanksgiving
and it said no, you're 100% Irish.
- The thing is, there's no chance
that you're .01% Ethiopian.
- How do you know?
- 'Cause there's no chance that you have
like a thousand years of relatives
who are just white British people,
and then for some reason a thousand years ago,
your great-great-great-great-great-great-great-great
grandmother was like, yeah, fuck this Ethiopian guy.
- How do you know?
How do you know that didn't happen?
- That's plausible, dude.
That's so plausible.
now wouldn't fucking Ethiopian guy. My grandma now is dead so how do you know
she didn't do it? Oh my god. Dude that's actually Caleb, I'm gonna be honest man that's kind of
that's kind of insensitive because his grandma's dead to make comments about his
grandma having sex. Patrick that percentage is just like one of the
workers at the 23andMe factory had like an eyelash fall into your sample.
You can get a bag that's like 50% Ethiopian.
Yeah, you're 50% cat actually.
We should all get together and we should all mix our spit in one tube and see what it comes
back as.
That's a good idea.
I think they would just say there was too much DNA.
How much is 23andMe?
In vitro fertilized.
23andMe.
I'll tell you it's like 8 bucks.
When I got it, it was like 70 bucks.
Oh, it's $59 right now.
Alright Mr. Moneybags.
That's a video game.
Three years ago when I had student loan refunds.
I do still think of money in terms of video games and think of time in terms of TV episodes.
If something's an hour and a half away, I'm like, that's like fucking...
That's three episodes of Full House, dude.
That's crazy to sit and have an hour and a half and think in episodes and not one movie.
Or it's like two episodes of Breaking Bad without commercial breaks.
Exactly yeah two episodes if I'm if I'm marathoning Breaking Bad or even the Sopranos personally
I tend to think of time like in either minutes or hours, but I guess that's just you're so stupid dude female
Wow Cameron Wow mr.
Mr.
Big brains over here if you come into the 23 and me to been sending in are they gonna?
Like I think they get mad they drink like like sir. That's like are they just gonna deny it if you are they gonna get horny
They might see that and get really really someone gonna use that is there or is it just gonna go to waste
No, they're gonna use it if it's spit. They use all this science if there's a guy
That after they after they detect the like percentages from the spit they just repackaged it into Dasani
If you send in come though, they just have like a guy who takes one step and he's like that guy's Irish
Without a doubt that's a Chinese guys come. Yeah, that's right there. Yeah a hundred percent
It's hidden certain certain nutty notes, it's the guy from the from the
The the dryers like ice cream taste testing video. He keeps smacking his yeah. Yeah. Yeah, it's that guy
he tries the guy tells you that you're
1% sub-saharan Africa and then he's
Yeah
He spits it into an old-timey, but do he's a cowboy now
and then one day one day a lightning bolt struck the spittoon and created a new
race of person mm-hmm that's true that's how we get got Dominic Chinese it's how
the Armenian came to be I wish you guys should sell like pot about this branded
like mud jugs or spittoons that's a good idea yeah I guess we're pretty yeah I
I think old-timey yeah I mean I've been thinking about getting into chewing
tobacco once the holes in my teeth are finally filled up yeah you'd rather
replace them with holes in your gums yeah because then it just looks even at
least I'm just fixing my shit people are just confused if they see your teeth and
then your gums are like fucking worst teeth I've ever seen the most beautiful
gums Jesus Christ those are perfect yeah you gotta fuck them up a little bit
- You gotta fuck 'em up with some dip.
Have you ever dipped before?
- I haven't, my dad did for most of, all of my life.
- My dad's a huge dipper, so I probably will never do it.
'Cause when I was a kid, my dad would,
my dad's a psycho, instead of dipping into like a dip cup,
he would, he was spitting into a dip cup,
he would spit into a Pepsi can.
- I was just about to ask, I was just about to ask,
did he ever accidentally--
- And like two or three times in my life,
I reached for my Pepsi, and it was just my dad's fucking gunk.
- Yeah, my dad and my uncle and my brother.
I've done that more than,
the fucking chances of that happening for me are higher.
- Yeah, it kinda sounds like you wanna do it.
- Yeah, now I do.
- It doesn't really sound like an accident.
- One time's an accident.
- Yeah, exactly.
- But, you know, two times maybe you can still get
the benefit of the doubt, but three times.
- Three times it's a tradition, you gotta keep doing it.
- Yeah.
- That's a choice.
- It's such a cool type of person to be like,
I can pick any way I want to consume tobacco
and I'm gonna pick what I think is the coolest
and then picking the one that's like,
I'm gonna fill my mouth with slime
and then spray it everywhere every once in a while.
- Let me throw a cool cigarette or like a cigar.
You know, there's so many options.
- Let me get a pinch of dirt and throw it in my gum
so I can spit everywhere like a fucking idiot.
- I'm gonna suck on dirt
and it's gonna look like a bee stung my lip.
- Yeah.
- And then I'm just gonna barf everywhere into a cup.
Let me let me spit some dark brown stinky juice all over the place a friend of mine on his 18th birthday
Bought a pack of like the most powerful dip and just shoved like the entire can in his mouth
He worked at a grocery store
And so he was he like bought it on his way out of work
And he puts like the entire can in his mouth starts a driving home, and he passed out
And then and he like me like
Mildly crashed his car like a barrier and then drove home from there like didn't tell anybody or whatever
Walked into his house and just vomited all over his living room
Poisoning is so bad if I saw like crash his car and I walked over and I looked in there was just like black slime
Dripping out of his mouth. I would just go into a bunker in me
The CIA did that one. Yeah, yeah, the CIA was targeting him. I touched that's what the stomach aches lead to
Yeah, the stomach aches make you it's like a pepto-bismol shit
But I was like 19. I was really depressed and I had a pack of American spirits and I was like, oh man
Fuck I'm gonna smoke a cigarette cuz I'm sad and um heard I didn't realize that
I hadn't really experienced like the negative effects of nicotine just like when I liked it's like oh man
this buzz is good.
So I was really sad and I was like, it's like you know when people are sad they drink a lot
of alcohol so I'll smoke a lot of nicotine.
So I took a cigarette and I sucked it down as fast as I could, like maybe the whole thing
in like less than a minute.
And then all of a sudden I just sat down in my car and I just passed out for about 15
minutes.
And I woke up and I had Gatorade all over myself and I had nothing to drink.
I guess I tried to drink it and spilled it on myself.
Miserable though.
And that's the same night I also got cheated on.
So, damn.
That was a fun night.
Which came first?
The cheat, well I was depressed because of the cheating.
Oh, okay.
You were so depressed from being cheated on, you were like, I gotta have one.
Yeah, you're gonna commit suicide.
I gotta have a whole pack.
You're gonna commit suicide with one American spirit.
I gotta speed run a cigarette right now.
Your girlfriend came over and saw you just in the car, passed out, covered in Gatorade
and was like, well, I guess I should go get another guy now.
I should go fuck someone else.
I'm just gonna go fuck a homeless guy right now.
At least he doesn't have Gatorade.
Whatever's happening here.
Dude, I fuckin' in
high school, I forget
when it was the night before prom
and I was like at the skate park.
It was just me there that day, which was fuckin' sick.
But, because no one was there, I
That is sick. There's no one there to watch
you do your tricks though. So what?
I can fuckin', I can do whatever I want.
Maybe I'm just a performer.
I was like, I had nothing to do,
like nobody to like talk to or anything.
So I was like bored as shit.
So I just basically smoked a whole pack of Camel Blues
and I drank these things called high drives,
which were like Gatorade,
but with like 300 milligrams of caffeine,
I drank two of them.
I had, yeah, I was like, hey, dad, you gotta pick me up.
I'm not doing good.
And I got in his car and this is back when I lived
the fucking hotel too so I like tell me about that later okay but I I drove the
whole way home from Londonderry to Manchester with my seat all the way
reclined so I'm just like all the way back in the car just going oh and as
soon as we get into the fucking like the hotel room I run to the bathroom and
just puke up just a chunk of blue gunk.
That was like a whole thing of blue.
- Like a whole flubber.
- A whole blue flubber came out of my mouth
and onto the ground. - Like a non-Newtonian chunk.
- Exactly, exactly. - Some kind of
non-Newtonian fluid.
- It was the grossest vomit I've ever,
like it came out my nose.
- That's the worst.
- Oh, it burned, it burned on the way out.
- Yeah.
- That's how fucking bad it was.
- Yesterday I was at the Super Mega office and--
- You got an office?
- What?
- Ooh, I was at the super mega office.
- Yeah, man, we don't have an office, okay?
I work out of my bathroom.
Is that so wrong?
- Well, Cameron looks like he's in like a shack
in Jamaica right now.
- He was captured two months ago, they let him work.
He's doing some sweat equity now.
- That was very nice of them, yeah.
No, but we were recording some videos,
you know, creating content, and I went in the fridge
and I saw there was a big thing of whole milk,
and I was like, "Oh, fuck, I haven't had milk in like a year."
So I got some chocolate syrup
and I made a big, tall glass of chocolate milk
and I just chugged that sucker down and I really enjoyed it.
And I came back to record and I sat down and I was like,
"Oh man, that doesn't feel too good."
'Cause I guess if you go a long time without drinking milk,
your body just is like, "All right, no more of that ever."
And I proceeded to just projectile vomit
chocolate milk yesterday.
And Ryan heard it.
Ryan walked by the bathroom and heard me puking.
and his reaction is goes, it's not, it's not,
hey man, are you okay?
It's just, yeah, gross.
(laughing)
Just walked off.
- Well, that's 'cause somebody vomiting chocolate milk,
you're like, I know exactly what's happening here.
Like, you're fine as soon as that's out of your body.
- Well, you didn't say--
- You just like did something immoral
and God is punishing you.
- You drank a four year old's drink and it made you sick.
- Exactly, yeah.
- It made me sick, I couldn't handle it.
But the worst part was like, you know when you make
like Nesquik chocolate milk,
the bottom's always more chocolaty.
- Yeah.
- It's the same with the puke.
Like, the more I puked,
the more chocolatey it became until it came out my nose and it was just like
straight chocolate. Just a chocolate bar coming out of your mouth at the end.
That's a bummer. Fully formed, yeah. Yeah, like a vending machine returning a dollar bill.
Just a sheet of chocolate coming out of your disgusting mouth.
Dude, that would legitimately send me into a full-blown panic attack if that happened.
A chocolate bar coming out of your mouth? Like if a perfect chocolate bar came out of my throat.
Low-key that'd freak my shit out.
Like I'd be staring in the toilet, like that shit's floating there and I would pull it out
with my hands and be like, "What?
This is not real."
And I'd probably call 911.
I'd call my attorney because I was gonna be rich.
I was gonna be the greatest fucking act America's Got Talent's ever seen.
If you were able to regurgitate a full like, uh, cocktail bar.
It'd be scarier.
It'd be way scarier if it was a zero bar.
Oh.
Just a whole chunk of white chocolate coming out of ya?
Yeah, I've had white chocolate since like Halloween 2009.
Right.
There's no way that that's just been sitting in me.
Yeah.
What if it was like one of those giant gummy bears?
One of the big like, "Ooh, I'm a gummy bear."
That would be like God telling you you're gay if it's any sort of gummy fruit.
You'd be like, "Oh, this is like an Old Testament miracle telling me I'm gay."
God would be telling you you're gay because you gave birth to a gummy bear out your mouth?
Yeah, dude.
I guess Patrick doesn't get it.
Patrick, gummy bears for centuries have been an icon and a symbol of the gay community.
Oh I didn't know this.
It was like before they had the flags and the letters.
Have you ever heard of the gummy bear song?
Yeah.
Oh, I just...
It's just a gay anthem dude.
Have you never been to a gay club and they turn on the gummy bear song?
I just thought he was German.
Ickbun Gummy Bear? You've never fuckin'
*laughs*
That's like the bottom anthem of all time
The bottom anthem of all time?
The bottom anthem of all time
Patrick knows
Patrick, he's playing coy
He's like "I don't know what the bottom anthem is"
*laughs*
I don't know it
I thought it was Barbie Girl
No dude, that's the top anthem you dumbass
Well, alright, I'm learning!
That's some extreme top energy in that song.
I found the drink, the exact drink that I drank that day and I spit out blue gunk.
The high drive.
I'm gonna sleep with this one.
And it doesn't look like this anymore.
Energy water?
That is so fucked up to market it as energy water.
That looks like something I'd put into my car.
Exactly.
When I'm servicing the engine.
You shouldn't put anything in your body that has a picture of an atom on it.
(laughing)
- You sure you weren't just drinking fucking
anti-freeze or something?
- Honestly, if I was, that would make--
- Probably same effect.
- Yeah, I'd probably feel the same.
- Anything that's caffeinated should taste terrible.
Anything that's that highly caffeinated,
they shouldn't be able to call it water, first of all.
It shouldn't be any kind of water.
It should be like, it should taste like ethanol.
- It's good, it's also, yeah, that's good also
because then you know if you start liking the taste
of a caffeinated drink, you know you'd have to stop.
You have to switch to something else.
- Exactly, yeah.
- You guys remember Vault?
- Yes, dude.
- Yeah.
- Dude, Vault was awesome.
- I knew this kid, so back in sixth grade
was when I got into making YouTube videos.
And I had this rival at school
that was like my YouTube rival named Casey.
And he was a magician.
- Yo!
- That's tough to compete with.
- Yeah, well, actually still, he's still for a living,
he works for a magic card company.
- Do you still hate him?
- Yeah.
(laughing)
He always, he, like we had the biggest war
over like stealing ideas and like views on YouTube
'cause like he'd post a video and get like 20 views
and I'd post one and get like 20 views
and it'd be this whole like,
"I think you stole that joke from me."
No, you took it from, I said it first at lunch.
But I remember every single day he'd come to school,
he was in my first period class
and he would just drink a vault every day
and then for the rest of the class
have his head down with a migraine.
(laughing)
And I remember he would miss he missed like half the school year. He's like I just keep getting these migraines
Dude I for some reason I
Associate vault with the paintball. I don't know why no big time all this drink right there. Yeah ballers drink
Yeah, you know what in the migraines? That's like paintballers version of like coal lung. Yeah
It came with the territory. Yeah. Yeah, you would know you do you fucking I did
- I did play paintball.
I drank a lot of vault.
- Paintball was, I liked it,
but the problem was the paintball course
I went to in Charleston, it was like the only one,
and it was literally like right down the street
from the military base, so like all the guys
that would go there would be these like really pumped up,
like date rapist military guys that would just have to get
all of their energy and like masculinity
out on the paintball field.
So it'd be all these like 21 year old dudes,
and then my 13 year old ass, and they'd run up behind me
just light me up and I'd be screaming and I'd throw my gun on the ground and have
my hands up and they just continue to do it so well yeah that's mainly why I hate
the military. They join the military to kill like 13 year old girls.
They're like we're gonna I'm gonna shoot this kid so many times in the head and
then is it mom here I'd like to shoot her as well yeah yeah. Is there a family in the
building? Yeah I would love to marry this kid's mom. I'm going to shoot this kid's
mom once and then marry her.
Ma'am, ma'am, I just shot, I just pelted your son.
I gave him so many welts.
Will you take my hand in marriage?
Please take my hand in marriage.
Yeah, I basically just fucked your kid up pretty good.
If you wanted to like...
Did you sell those welts on your kid?
Yeah, that was me.
I was doing a good job.
That's right.
And I'll do a lot better than that in the bedroom.
Let me tell you what.
So you want to like see my penis?
You're going to be covered in paint.
- Are you covered in paint?
- Like penis or, yeah, what's up?
I just painted your kid and I'm gonna paint your face next.
- And let me tell you, you're gonna have to wear
a protective vest in the bedroom.
(laughing)
'Cause I go nuts.
- You're gonna have to put one hand up
when you're ready to tap out.
- Yeah, you better not get a Bowflex in the house.
- But that doesn't mean I'm gonna stop shooting.
- Yeah, I'm gonna, yeah.
(laughing)
Yeah.
The paintball field that my brother worked at,
like growing up, which is the only reason I played paintball,
The owner was this guy with like, he had like horrible diabetes.
So he had like no legs and he just vomited blood all the time.
You'd get there and he'd be like, Hey, welcome to blue.
I don't believe you do that. Should you shouldn't be,
you shouldn't be working if he had to work to afford.
Should be in a camp facility.
He has no legs.
They had to have used him as like an example, right?
It'd be like if a kid wasn't wearing like the safety goggles, to be like, "Hey!"
"You'll end up like him!"
For some reason I thought you were going to say they had to have used him in a haunted house.
Because Matt is a perfect haunted house guy.
Oh yeah.
It is, it is.
I love that when like you go to one of those like high budget haunted houses and they hire like a little person.
Yeah.
And it's like, what is, it's just like, that's not any more scary than a normal Jason Voorhees.
This guy has a metal leg.
Yeah, this guy has some genetic defects from the time he was born that he has, you know,
lived in extreme bullying and lack of self-esteem his whole life.
But at least he can go to the haunted house and make minimum wage scaring privileged people.
Yeah, but you're not gonna believe how smooth the space between this guy's lips and noses, okay?
But but also at the same time, you know the Americans with Disabilities Act does
You know fair employment for people
Sending those people to haunted houses
That's how Patrick got on this podcast.
I guess you could be like a tree stump or something.
Exactly. The tree stump.
Yeah, like an evil tree stump.
Just sit there.
I don't know man. Sit there and gurgle.
Yeah, it's either that or you have to like do payroll.
So it's your choice I guess.
Yeah, no one wants to do that.
Painting fences.
Yeah, there was a haunted house in my hometown
that was like
when
having like a cool expensive
Haunted House, it became kind of a trend in like the early 2010s. Yeah. And they
did one. Yeah, there were like, there's like two years where it was like this
this warehouse, they would set it up with like a bunch of rooms and shit and it
cost like 15 bucks and they, it was really popular. And then for the third
year they were like, this year we're one-upping ourselves and
we're going to set a 1 million dollar budget. And then they didn't even make it
Halloween immediately went like so bankrupt and owed all these people money.
Those like haunted houses are so cool like the ones that are like you have to
sign a waiver that's like if the ghost spits in your mouth you can't take
revenge. Isn't there one somewhere that's like the guy if you go if you like can
make it all the way through he pays you like ten thousand dollars. Yeah but then
the waiver is literally like the the people can touch any part of
your body and do whatever they want to you and they can kill you.
You'll get molested in the haunted house.
Like straight up, that's like, there is like a thing in the waiver that's like that.
I remember, I read the waiver of that one I think, if it's the one I'm thinking of.
I don't think waivers can cover that.
Yeah, no, it definitely doesn't, it definitely wouldn't hold up.
No, I mean, hey no dude, that's a legal document.
If I sign a waiver giving Caleb permission to touch me and my meat is, stick his finger
down my meat is and he does it, I can't sue him for putting his finger in my cornhole because
he's, I signed it.
There's literally a clause in that one that's like, "If you die, you can't sue us."
Like, it's like...
It's like, "Duh!"
Yeah, and it's also like, there's like a one that's like, "If we can inject anything into
you with needles."
Like, stuff like that.
It's just like a bunch of stuff like that.
Just inject you with ketamine so you literally just cannot make it to the end of the course.
Like, "I guess you don't get $10,000."
Yeah.
Fucking owned, baby.
Fucking honed.
I can't imagine going to a haunted house.
I can't imagine paying for a haunted house.
You're messing up, dude. They're fun.
I don't think I've ever gone to a haunted house that wasn't just a neighbor's garage or something.
I don't know why I'd ever pay for a haunted house when I can just go stop by Patrick's mom's house.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Matt, lay off him, dude.
Come on.
I thought you were on my side.
I know, but I thought you liked it. I was trying to impress you, Caleb.
to impress you Caleb. I am I am on your side I'm trying to play like good cop bad cop.
Stop. Jesus Christ Matt you're talking I mean this fat piece of shit he goes
through enough. No no I don't. Come on. Oh he doesn't? Oh Matt give him some more. Hey
Patrick have you ever seen Spy Kids? No. Okay never mind then. This is the best way to
shut down like I was gonna compare you to something from Spy Kids you're like no I
haven't seen it's like oh well you look like Junie Cortez man low-key
have you ever seen spy kids no well can you imagine a guy who looks like a hand
but he has a thumb for a head have you ever seen spy kids no well can you
imagine a flugeli can you can you just okay so you know flupe right no you
you haven't seen hold on okay help us save us that's what I'm saying and I think
like I like to roast Patrick over that I'd have to like in person about oh
yeah that's okay hold on I have to pull up a scene and I sit down with my phone
and like one second you have like a sketchpad that just gets to work fine do
you have like any good screenwriting software
I'm just gonna write out a scene for you
Alright, Spy Kids 5
My pencil is out of
my mechanical pencil is out of lead
do you by chance have another?
Sorry I can't do pen, I make too many mistakes
No pencil? Fine
Uh, you're
I guess you're ugly, ah shit
No, that doesn't work
You're very ugly, there it is
Watch Spy Kids and we'll hang out again tomorrow
Have you really not seen Spy Kids Patrick? No, I've seen it
Like that dude he countered you bro. Yep, that's right. You just blocked it like you are to the deal
Hmm. I don't think that's the art of the deal. Yeah. Well, you didn't read it. So yeah, that's what it says
Yeah, I definitely ask someone if they've seen Spy Kids. Yeah
That's how Donald Trump made his millions. He can't someone asks you if you see my kids say no. No, you know, I
Nobody's seen Spy Kids more times than me.
I've never seen Spy Kids.
Nobody's seen Spy Kids more than I have.
I love Spy Kids.
Nobody's seen Spy Kids at all.
Nobody has seen it.
Except me.
I'm the only one who knows what a Floogli is.
Baron appreciates
Alan Cummings
character performance in the movie as
Floop, as Floop with the Floogli's.
Let me tell you folks, he's a mad man.
He's a complete mad man. He's out of control, Floop.
complete man i don't wish
helpless from flu
flip is a madman
help us save us
because it's a status
i'm a lot of president ron strikes the uh... the the flu flu please play yet
anything under a care of your flu
uh... i don't care if you're a flipper flu
you're gonna like your batman you could save them
the
the whole of the israeli clear
the site of the court is a great father did in the in the video game was wrong
but
and it's going on a speech about
all the spies movies
uh... what what what you record as a grandfather's dot
as he's left the
video game into the real world
and
the point is that the
we have got we are we are going to have a nice but i make it
well americans
we've got
i would love to put the toy maker in the fuckin
uh... with those you know
yeah i'd love to just seen his body into the ocean yeah and so long as i had a
copy of the all of his alter egos at the helicopter to
yes
the railing off we need to answer the whole time
yeah president
was in the president i don't remember the bike you know i know he the point
making you fucking idiot but then that the president was working with the toy
maker so that no the president's george clooney
and i a show that i was
fund on to set it was done
you guys are not going for not knowing well i'm not a bush emmy had the island
with animals i thought that was so cool
no one was cool man i thought this was a good news were so sick there's so i
said
there's that fucking quote from spike it's too yet do you think god lives and
God stays in heaven because he lives in fear of what he's created.
That was too fucking heavy for Spy Kids 2.
Not for me, I processed it immediately.
Yeah.
Well that line, no.
Coming from Steve Buscemi.
Yeah, I looked at my mom and I said, "God's not real, Mom."
She immediately burst into tears and then burst into flames.
She immediately started sucking my dick because I was so smart.
What the hell?
You're smart.
Dude, come on.
you guys caught me I was lying yeah you better be lying I don't remember that
part of the movie that's crap I'd be calling the police if you're not I don't
remember if anybody sucked my dick during that I don't remember if that movie even
happened when I was a kid I had a like extreme irrational phobia of vomit and I
remember I was I was I saw holes in theaters and I'm sitting in the back of
the theater I didn't want to sit with my mom cuz I was like an angsty kid so she
I sat in the back by myself.
And then the part when Zero throws up, I just got up and I booked it straight out the theater
because I was just so scared.
Just left.
And my mom had to like follow me out into the, into like the hallway in the theater.
She's like, "Son, son, it's okay."
And then I also, when I saw Cheaper by the Dozen in theaters, or maybe it was Cheaper
the second one or something, there's a scene where a kid throws up and I was in Seattle
with my cousins and I did that I just got up like when he said he was feeling
nauseous in the movie and I just beelined it to the exit. Damn. Damn. You just hated
vomit as a kid? No it just I was I had a rational phobia of it like I wasn't even
grossed out by it just like it's called a metaphobia it's really fucking
terrified. I don't think I've ever walked out of a theater in a movie I feel like I
had to go I saw Elmo and Grouchland in theaters and I was so scared by the bad
guy in that movie that I told my mom like 30 minutes in I was like mom I think I
needed to go take a nap and she just she took me out of the movie and took me
home so yeah do with the big eyebrows dude Mandy Patinkin is scary as shit in
that movie yeah have you got one of the funniest walkouts I've seen in a movie
theater is we saw as I went to see the then like remake of the grudge which is
really really bad the one that came out this year and this couple like just
walked out like the second that the first jump scare happened like 10 minutes
and they just walked in.
It's a horror movie dude.
They thought it was going to be like a family drama.
Yeah, the grudge.
Like the poster.
Thought it was about divorce.
It's a ghost, come on.
I went and saw Moonlight by myself in theaters.
You got so scared you left.
I didn't know what it was about and as soon as I did I said, oh wait, no, that's what
happened though, I sat down in Moonlight, they're my popcorn, and like these two massive,
huge ripped like Turkish dudes come and sit down and the seats in front of me
and they're like sharing a popcorn and I guess they just picked I guess they
didn't know what the movie was about and then like it starts to creep into the
gay territory and I just see it's right in front of me he's like kind of like
scoffing and then the part the part where he looked behind him no he looked behind
him he was just kind of looking around like to check if like the village people
were behind him. And then like some the gay more gay stuff happens and they just be
like and then finally the part happens when he gives him a handjob on the beach
and they're just like like looking around all nervously and they both just get up
and book it out and I enjoyed the movie because they weren't in my in my way
anymore. I love that move of like like something is happening in a movie and
you're just looking around like Rodney Dangerfield. He wants to make sure
everyone else in the theater, they're not focusing on the movie, they're focused on
him right then and they're thinking like yo this guy might be gay because he's
watching this scene yeah and he's like no I'm not gay. The scoff, the audible
scoff is showing that I'm like whoa. It's funny though it's like like if you're in a
before any more movie happens
*laughter*
let me just put this at the record straight
I need to get this off my chest
nothing
this is doing nothing for me
what happened to your pants?
I spilled my soda
about 5 minutes into the movie
and I had to remove my pants
*laughter*
I got the butter from the popcorn
all down my slack
very oily. It's very oily but it's see like that's what the noise is okay I'm
wiping my pants clean very quickly. I've been saying ah geez oh god because I'm
trying to get a stain out. You sound like a Jewish doctor. I'm saying I'm gonna come because I'm using the
the dictation on my phone to tell my girlfriend I'm coming over after the
movie. Yeah I'm gonna come. I'm coming I'm coming. Yeah I'm gonna miss movies dude
they're over oh yeah they're done it is yeah they made two gay movies and it's
done it's finished that's what happened they make call me by your name and
they made moonlight and then they were like all right we need to put a pant we
need to create a virus to make sure no one goes to the movies anymore because
we can't have this keep happening exactly it's very sick that like Christopher
Nolan pushed his movie into theaters and it just like flopped so hard and now we
get to see all the movies on streaming like thank only because like he was
stupid because of that movie because it failed so like it did it just like did
not make enough money because like that's the reason that the HBO Max
thing is going like where they're releasing movies on HBO Max next year
did Chris did Christopher Nolan do interstellar yeah yeah that's a good-ass
movie I still have a nice movie it's too long dude it's long but like I saw that
in theaters and I like bawled my eyes out.
It's a sad movie.
I bawled so hard dude.
Damn I bawled hard as fuck.
I kept bouncing it off the screen.
Every time Matt Damon showed up I'd toss it and try to hit him right in the face.
I don't like space movies bro.
Seriously?
They scare me too much.
I'm so scared of space.
Space is one of my favorite things.
I love space more than anything dude.
Are you making fun of me now?
No, no, I'm serious. I would do any and do you know anyone in space? I?
Don't think he does one time. Oh my yeah, there's no I don't I don't one time my family friends
Like when I was a kid my family started started touching my leg
Just kidding my
my family friends get like gave my family like this like printed out like diary of an astronaut and
And I don't know if it was like a guy that they knew,
that was an astronaut,
or if it was just like something they printed out from online.
But look, it was just like, you know,
like he typed up like,
"Oh, this is what happened when we took off."
And there was just like a whole chapter
about how he had to use a catheter to go to the bathroom.
I was in like fourth grade reading it.
I'm like, "I do not want to go to space anymore."
- I'm starting my astronaut diary.
First off, this is not a diary.
(laughter)
- This is a flight log.
- Yeah.
- Now that'd be a good, it's just him, he's like,
damn bro, I'm in slow motion up here, shit.
God damn, that's cool.
- They make me eat out of a tube.
I'm eating toothpaste up here, this shit sucks.
- Damn, this is the worst steak I ever had.
- But just think about it, like being a kid
wanting to like, go to space and like be an astronaut
and then like read a thing that's like, yeah, okay,
first things first, when you're an astronaut,
You gotta stick a thingy into your pee hole.
- You gotta be surgering your penis every day.
- Are you awake every single day?
- I think so, I think you have to put the catheter
in yourself, you're basically peeing into a bottle.
- So you have to sound yourself.
- You think they just have a guy whose job it is to do that?
- They have the catheter guy on the ship.
- Yeah.
- It could be possible.
- Dude, if I were in this position.
- I'm an astronaut, but I'm not like the explorer-ass
or anything cool, I'm just the bathroom guy.
- I mean, you could argue he's the bigger explorer
right there.
- Whoa, that is a good point.
- That's true, yeah.
He's going through uncharted territory.
Yesterday, we were opening some mail from our PO box and someone sent us a full sounding
kit that had like 20 different sized rods.
It was this big black thing and I unzipped it and I opened it up and it's this really
fancy sounding kit.
Like the thing is leather and it goes up to like 34mm and the biggest sounding bar was
massive.
How the-
Ding dong, massive!
How the fuck?
I, I, that's the one thing I think I-
Unrelated to that, we should get a PO box.
Don't understand.
Yeah.
Oh, it's, it's so worth it.
It's so worth it.
Is that the weirdest thing you've ever gotten in there?
No.
No?
Have you ever gotten the Godlike bombs or anything?
Not yet.
I'm hoping someone does do that.
Like the Bjork thing where I open the package and it sprays hydrochloric acid in my eyes.
We have, you know, we've gotten a lot of-
We've got that coming soon.
We've gotten dead animals, we've gotten hair and human teeth and stuff.
Were they alive when they got sent?
Well we got a big thing.
Someone sent a whole like tank of cockroaches.
Those were dead when they arrived because we didn't check the PO box for like three
months.
Someone sent us like some taxidermy ducklings and stuff.
And we get a lot of hair.
People will just like rip out their hair and mail it.
And then yesterday we got a really well done replication of like two ripped out testicles
wrapped in a paper towel with like blood all over it and I opened it up.
The package said Deez Nuts and we opened it and there were like two very well painted like
well made out of clay nuts like ripped out from the sack.
Wow.
I can't wait until your fans start listening to us and sending us stuff.
When you guys open a PO box, I don't think it's illegal to mail anthrax just to create
it.
Just to open it.
Yeah, you'll go to jail if you open it.
So don't fucking think about it.
You guys should get a PO box though and then part of your podcast, you guys can open some
of the letters and read them.
It is, it's so funny.
Someone would definitely send a poop though.
I know that they do like scans and shit too but it's really funny that when you like mail
a package the guy at the post office just goes like, "Is there anything dangerous in
here and you just go "no" oh yeah you caught me. I'll go put it back. I'm sorry.
Lithium batteries and Fiji's. Yeah, address 1600 Pennsylvania Ave. Now tell me is there anything
dangerous in this? Ah, you got me. I was really hoping you weren't gonna ask me that.
My mother raised me as an honest, you know, never tell a lie.
I cannot tell a lie. I am evil, but I can't tell a lie. I'm sorry.
I'm like a terrorist that has OCD, so like he cannot lie without feeling horribly guilty, so it's just like,
"Sir, is there anything suspicious in this?" Like, "Yeah, it's a bomb."
I was gonna send it to the White House, you got me. Sorry. I'm sorry. I'm just gonna leave. I'll take it with me.
Just, I'm just, I'm gonna leave. Don't worry about it.
Yeah, I've I've only sent like one thing in the mail I think in my entire life really yeah check in the mail
No, it was it. It was a
T-shirt that was like an M&M line. No you said oh my god, dude
Have I sent a pair of pants? I sent a pair of you
I thought I went on your journey with you to send the pair of pants
You kept trying to send. Oh, I sent two things. Yeah, you're right. I forgot about that. Yeah
I remember that very vividly just walking around to different post offices.
It took so long for some reason.
Yeah.
Wait, you had to...
I don't remember why.
I hate the post office.
I had to mail a pair of pants.
I don't even remember why.
I think I sold them.
Oh no, it was somebody left them at my house, I think.
Yeah, I'm a little bit of a player.
Yeah, somewhat.
You know, this girl left her panties at a...
- Patrick, speaking of which, Patrick, by the way,
can you tell your mom to mail me my pants back?
- No.
- And my condom, my YouTube pants.
- I'm wearing them.
- Girl, can you mail me my used condom?
- Hey, I think I left a condom at your house.
- Girl, I left a condom in your toilet.
- Can I get that back?
- Can you send that back, actually?
- Can you send me that condom?
- I'm gonna reuse it.
- There's some stuff in there that I need to put back in me.
I'm doing my 23andMe and I need to... I don't want someone to have that so...
Hey about a year ago I left a condom at your house, could you...
Could you go look for it in your trash?
Yeah I can't afford another one.
Hey I don't know if you remember me, it's Patrick from college.
Um...
I dropped a huge condom.
40 years old.
I took a big shit at your house.
When we meet up for the reunion, could you bring the shit and the condom back?
I know, yeah, I know we didn't have sex but I did leave a condom in the toilet after I
shit.
It fell off.
It fell off on me.
In the future, if I ever end up on a Tinder date, I'm gonna make sure that after sex,
every time I just go take a shit and I don't flush it and I leave.
That's right.
That's like my calling card.
It's just like, wow, that was such good, such good sex.
And then she goes to the bathroom to freshen up her pussy and then she just sees there's
shit in the toilet.
And she's like, "Oh my god, he got me.
He got me."
Yeah.
I think there'd be like a Twitter thread that's like, "Matt Watson left a shit in my toilet."
Content warning poop.
"The sex was just completely normal but there was a crap in my toilet and he forgot to flush."
There's 40 pictures of similar women with similar stories.
It's gonna be like a thread canceling me where it's like, "CW/poop" and then the rest is
like I had sex with Matt Watson in 2019 and he took a he took a poop in my
toilet and just left it yeah he was still there I asked him about her and he said
he didn't know anything about it she has like screenshots of text where it's her
like test be like did you did you shit and not flush it and I'm like I don't
know what you're talking about I mean like it must have been your cat it must
have been you you dumb whore you must have forgot I must have fucked your memory
up when I fucking ate your pussy because you definitely took that shit that was
your that's your poop that's a girl size and that looks like that's what it come
out of it same shape you know like the the play-doh things where it comes out
different shapes I can match it the same way you have a star-shaped asshole and
that poop came out of that thing now it's notably oh yeah I guess if I could
go for any shape I'd go whatever a penis couldn't fit into. Actually a star of
David would be really good for that. You're right that's a good point yeah. I
would never flush I'd go everywhere and just leave that like just a big star of
David shit. You would create a lot of anti-semites. Yeah that's true. Yeah
people just showing up they'd be like because also well the thing is with that
is they would have to take the poop out and look at it. Much like the picture I took of my dick.
And they'd have to look at it like a telescope.
"Hey wait a sec Earl, check this out from this angle.
This looks like that Jewish thing."
"I'm gonna keep it."
Then those guys are gonna go post it on 8chan and be like "Hey I was in the gas station restroom
and I found this Jewish feces."
"I found Jewish poop."
"I found a Jew poop."
How could you tell?
"Well it was shaped exactly like the Star of David.
Sorry."
I want the uh, I gotta say guys, by the way, your merch is fantastic.
Oh, thank you.
I tried ordering some but my card got declined so I should try again.
If we made it ourselves and didn't have like some Chinese company make it, we'd just send
it to you, but we don't have any of it.
We gotta figure that out.
It's all like sitting in Bulgaria.
Yeah.
Wait, what website do you guys use?
We use Teespring.
The only good thing about Teespring is that if you have a YouTube channel you can link
it like underneath the video and we'll show the merch.
Whoa.
Good to know.
But the penis boobs shit one is my favorite.
Oh I have that one.
That one's uh.
It's all good merch.
Thank you very much.
What an amazing plug for Matt Watson.
Hey Matt, why have you never hit me up for a verse on your album?
Do you want it?
Do you want to do it man?
I'm making a rap album right now.
It's it's it's pretty fly for a white guy. So if you want to jump on that, absolutely
I mean, we do a party original shut up. No, don't fuck this up for me
Can I'm the one who spit bars? I'm the one who spit bars cuz most of my homies locked behind him. Oh
Shit, wait, let me show you guys a CD. I got real quick. Okay, I'll be right actually
I gotta take a I gotta take a hot frothy piss. Can I go do that and bring you the CD?
Yeah, that's fine. Just do the normal show for a couple minutes. Okay, read the list. Yeah the list
So what's up with you guys?
Not much, what's up with you?
I miss Matt dude.
Can Matt just come back already?
It's Matt's gone and it's almost over.
I'm just going to go grab my stuff downstairs.
Oh my god dude.
You and Pat can have a nice conversation.
Pat if you leave.
I'm going to stay right here.
Dude what if we just did the podcast you and me?
We could.
Would you be mad?
No.
What would you think about it?
I would think we would betray Gabriel.
It would be funny if they left and you just died immediately.
I just did.
You got pretty close.
I got killed with a sneeze.
I think I'm sick.
I think I might have COVID-19.
You do?
Well, I smoked too many cigarettes today.
Well, there you go.
There's your fucking problem.
No, I don't think it's that.
No, cigarettes would never hurt me.
No, dude, those are good for you.
Dude, I'm disgusted by the smell of my own armpits.
Is that a COVID-19 problem?
No.
What's that?
When did you shower last?
Like 15 days ago.
Okay, well then it's probably, you're probably doing that.
You sound like my mom right now.
I, look, I woke up immediately before this.
I feel like crap.
They got back at the same time.
Wow, that's adorable.
You guys got back at the same time.
Oh my goodness.
Alright, show me this CD.
Show me this fucking CD.
Check it out, dude.
This is Black Dave, Next Stop The Ghetto.
Damn, that's good.
Why is the bus on fire?
A fan sent that yesterday.
I listened to the whole thing today too.
Is it sick?
Yeah, it's really good.
There's this one line, it's all very chill and stuff, but this one line where he just
goes "I'm addicted to crack!"
1998, dude.
It's about honesty, dude.
It's on Spotify, you guys should check it out.
The album's next stop.
- I think I'm gonna add that to my list.
All right, I have to go take a big piss,
but I'm not gonna leave in the middle of the show
'cause I'm a professional, so I think we're gonna end it.
- I'm a professional too, Caleb.
I've done 221 episodes of my podcast.
- I've done 222 of your podcast, so.
(laughing)
- It's not even possible.
- Easy. - I just did 223.
- I just did a 15th one, or 223th one.
- 15? - I just did 15.
Yeah, I just did 15.
- Another easy layup.
Where did these come from?
I don't know.
What episode is this?
This is...
A fucking hundred and something?
Oh god, what is this?
No, this is a premium, so it's fifty something.
Fifty something of the premium?
This is premium?
Oh yeah.
Yeah, if you couldn't tell.
Uh huh.
Is this one going?
We don't bust out the Donald Trump impression on the normal episodes, dude.
That's for the premium listeners.
Hey, in one of my Minecraft Let's Plays, I did a lot of Donald Trump impressions and
the comments were like, "Wow, I've never heard a Donald Trump impression before.
Very funny."
So now I keep them pulled back a little bit.
We can't take that heat, so I hope people are nice to us.
They'll be great to you guys.
You'll get a bunch of nice 16-year-old K-pop stans listening and going, "I can't believe
that Patrick said the N-word."
Well, we're going to cut that out.
But if you're hearing that, it did happen.
That's proof that it happened.
It didn't happen.
No.
It's proof that it happened.
We cut it out.
Yep.
You said it again.
- You gotta get me cut out again, fuck.
- No, I didn't say it.
- All right, thank you Matt.
Thanks for coming on.
- Hey, thanks for having me guys.
Anytime, I love hanging.
Next time after COVID's over,
we'll get all you guys out to LA to come.
- Definitely.
- Yeah, let's make it happen.
- Yeah.
- Bye y'all.
- We can go to Jollibee again.
- Bye bye.
- Bye, I'm gonna stop recording now.