You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[explosion]
Alright.
We're playing Mad Libs with Google Home.
Say repeat.
Repeat thing.
You're gonna have to--
Repeat.
Uh, two guys.
two guys. Patrick get closer to the... Patrick get closer to the... get closer to the...
closer to the... closer to the... so people can hear. Okay.
Sorry, Mad Libs isn't responding right now. No! What?
Try again soon. What?
Mad Libs just cancelled on us. They just fucking...
Mad Libs couldn't take our... Wait, do that...
do that song trick we said earlier.
Oh, okay. Hold the mic next to the Google Home.
Okay, Google.
Play the gayest song of all time.
Alright, playing Village People on Spotify.
[laughs]
Now that's a song trick for sure.
that's the song trick dude we're gonna get taken off of the internet if you play a
song yeah stop playing this hey dogel stop hey dogel hey dogel dogel it also
responds to dogel oh okay dogel okay stop playing that I got him all right we got
dogel out of the picture go gone dogel got killed dogel got assassinated so I
I muted the mic. Okay, thank God. So we can't play with the Google anymore.
That's a good choice. Yeah. I started my job at the art gallery. Yeah. Yeah.
And I started it last night and last night was this big opening for this...
It's... where is it? Nice try, bitch. Yeah, that's not gonna work on Caleb. He's one of the
cleverest art guards of all time. Exactly. I'm not saying because I don't want you to
come steal the art yeah the thing is I could say anything I would never get
fired from this job it's you stand I stand around I look at art but last
night was an opening for an artist's exhibition and the artist is she's deaf
she's dead she's dead she's deaf she's death she's death she's the grim leaper
she's the grim leaper and she's like a frog you expect nobody showed up to that
shit because he was she was the frog well she could see any of them she didn't
know nice yeah she was deaf and so there was a big opening there's like 600
people there and like a big over here and shut the fuck up
your brain. Shut up. Shut up. That's what we laugh on the show now. I'm gonna unmute Dogel.
I'm gonna make Dogel unchained. Dogel unchained? Yeah. I muted it, you can't. I'll unmute Dogel
and unchain him. Try it, try it from here. Unchain Dogel. Unchain Dogel now. Dogel unchained.
Dogel unchained. It's not working. But so there's 600 people who showed up, 300 of which
were deaf and apparently deaf people love to touch art and I have no idea how to
say in sign language don't touch that art so the entire night was just me just
like grabbing deaf people and just being like don't touch the art!
Yeah it was bad dude. It was not good. Why didn't they just put up signs that
say don't touch the for some reason nobody foresaw deaf people showing up to
the deaf artists opening. I don't know why. They had two translators but one of
the translators was for the artist and the other was for random people who were
gonna be there but this so this lady I just had to like run around and try to
get her attention all the time. And she kept doing it? No, she was the translator.
This was the translator. I just had to keep like...
I thought you were saying there's one deaf lady.
If somebody didn't understand what I was trying to tell them...
One deaf lady just like...
Turns out she's the rival artist.
Yeah.
One of the two deaf artists and they hate each other.
She signs like "Ha ha!"
"I have just ruined your priceless art!"
In an evil accent.
Yeah, in a doof and schmertz accent.
She's doing all of it but she's also signing like Sieg Heilig at the same time.
Yeah.
Because it's an evil deaf... that would be the evil deaf voice.
the evil deaf voices because German is the normal voice.
An interesting fact, Hitler was actually deaf and the Seig Heil actually is um it's a
sign language sign that means I am Hitler and people misunderstood it and
they all kind of did it back to him it didn't really make sense.
Yeah because simultaneously it also means stop being me!
No you're not Hitler I am!
He would do it back to them because it's it's poorly designed the German sign
language but it also means stop doing that yeah so he would go stop copying
me and do it right back to them yeah and then they got into this whole
so it's really all he was trying to say was don't I'm it's me I'm Hitler you're
not there's a I'm Hitler and you're not yeah as he gets offstage we were looking
we were looking at an apartment today and like across the street or like next
door to the apartment there was a building and they had like this photo of
like all of them and they're all like reaching their hands out and there's one
guy who's like too far away but he's still trying to reach his hands into the
center like the center circle and it just looks like he's doing like the Z
Kyle. That's sick. Yeah it's across from the Star Market. The Zeke Kyle. Yeah. Wait I have
Zeke Kyle. Zeke Kyle? Oh fuck. Do you remember that picture? It was a picture of the two neo-nazis
and it was like oh seen Kyle? Anybody seen Kyle? He's about this tall. It's a pun. It's
a pun. I miss those old image macros. Yeah. You will shit a brick when you see it. It's
picture of water and under the water, they'll lock this monster. Your ass will explode off
your body when you see it and you will shit yourself.
This image is an optical illusion. Kidnapped? I prefer the term surprise adoption.
Yeah.
Yeah. That picture, there's something where someone moved the Bible into the fiction section
and then that picture of Freddie Mercury, it's a...
Oh, yeah.
And it says like true story or whatever.
You ever heard of Derpina?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
derpina bitch right to watch movies with me I wish yeah and to do that you can do
the troll what would you do if derpina was here right now I would say I would say
me gusta nice I would make that face I would become Yao Ming I would I would I
would sort of motion my wine glass towards her and say true story yeah me
and Caleb went to Olive Garden went to Olive Garden and there was this table
of like guys behind us like what the type of guy they were like
construction worker type guys
were they still in like the the best
yeah yeah they were like the high viz
we're gonna go to fucking Olive Garden after work
you going?
exactly
so we were sitting in there behind us just talking and their conversation was literally
just about like different foods and I was like
it's got noodles it's got cheese it's deep fried what's not to like
hey Strega Nona had a good a fucking idea
I'll tell you that right now
Unlimited spaghetti?
One guy was like, "Listen, I've had macaroni that didn't have enough cheese. I've had macaroni
that was dripping with cheese." That was all he said.
He's talking about cheese all the time.
The best part of that trip was when we walked in, they gave us these, this lady was like,
"Would you guys like to sample our limonada?" And we were like, "Sure." So they gave us
these tiny little cups and put a little bit of strawberry lemonade in them, and we were
kind of drinking them. And then we sat down.
I put mine on the table.
He put his on the table and our waitress comes by and she goes like, "Hey, welcome to Olive
Garden. Can I get you-" What the fuck is that?
Well, no, I started ordering. She said, "What can I-" I said, "Oh, I'll have like the
linguine." And she went, "What the fuck is that?" And I thought she was talking about
what I was ordering.
And he was like, "Linguine?" And she was like, "No, that. Is that methadone?" She thought
that his sample of lemonade was methadone.
What?
And we were like, "No." She's like, "Oh." Because my friend went to the methadone clinic
and it kinda look like that
(laughter)
I'm so sorry, I hope I didn't offend you
I was just like looking at the camera
I was like, yeah if I didn't know you I would have guessed that was methadone too
he came in in that huge jacket
before he shaved
people with methadone are cold
they need big jackets
they need big jackets because they don't have enough
they don't have enough methadone
exactly
never enough
they're always running out
So the fuck yeah, I'll have the
That's
Somebody who's never heard of any italian food working as a waiter in a health garden
I'll have the uh pasta. Ifaggioli. What the fuck you call me?
Yeah, well Caleb did order that and he paused a really long time between the words.
Yeah.
It's faggiole.
Yeah, I know.
Faggiole.
Yeah.
My mom used to pronounce that faggiole.
My mom used to say pasta faggola.
Nice.
Fagula.
Yeah, fagula.
And then we had a teacher.
My mom then turned fagola into the word that she would say instead of like faggot because
she thought it was like the light version.
Yeah.
So then she would like, she called someone like Fagola once and it was their last name.
Whoa.
That's crazy.
Somebody's last name is Fagola?
Somebody's the basketball coach in my middle school.
Fagola?
Yeah.
Damn.
Fagola.
Like gay Dracula.
Yeah, no, I got it.
Listen, I can't stop thinking about it since you said it.
Yeah, it's like I want to suck your dick.
I want to suck your dick.
No.
I want the same rights as everyone else.
Yeah, that's what he says.
I want to go on a big, big beach.
Well, he doesn't matter because he's Transylvanian. He doesn't it doesn't apply to the US.
It's the same thing. It's very similar. That's why he wears a big cape.
Yeah, um, and he can hypnotize people with his eyes. Yeah, just like all gay and turn into a bat
and yeah, uh, gaseous when when a gay guy hypnotizes me with his eyes in the back section.
So annoying. Yeah. Don't use your powers on me. Just take a break for once.
Yeah, just take one night off.
You take one single night off. So it's got to be exhausting for you. You know what I mean?
They should be able to take a night off just play some video games.
Just watch basketball with your dad. Yeah, one of us should become gay.
Not it. Not it. Yeah, camera. Fine. Dude, yes. I'll do it. Got him. We got him. We got him so hard right then.
Oh, what have you guys been doing this week?
Anything fun?
Class.
Yeah.
Yeah, exactly.
Damn, it's Friday.
It feels early in the week.
That Friday feeling.
Yeah, I just have been going to class and to work.
Now imagine if I'm Albert Einstein, ready?
Yeah.
Patrick's making the Albert Einstein face.
Albert Einstein.
Albert.
I stick my tongue out just like the genius.
Yeah.
I've got a genius tongue.
That was a byproduct of how smart he was. He was using all of his brain to think and he couldn't
actually use any brain to close his mouth.
His tongue had a direct connection to his brain.
That was just a little bit of brain poking out of his mouth because he was overflowing with it.
He had too much brain.
Yeah.
When did he die?
Yesterday.
'72.
'72?
I don't know. He was around in the early 1900s.
He was around and that was what time he was active.
Yeah, when did he die?
So when did he die?
He's a rapper, right?
What day of the week did Einstein die?
Hey, Dogel.
Oh, we shut her off.
What day is the 4th?
What day did Einstein die?
Oh, '55.
1955.
April 18th.
What day?
It's kind of late.
Yeah, that's one of my recent searches is "What day is 4-July?"
[Laughter]
I was trying to figure out what day of the week my birthday was on.
What day is 4th Julte.
What day is 4 Julte.
Oh yeah, what are we going to do for your birthday?
My birthday is first. What are we doing for my birthday?
I don't know. Your birthday is the day before or day... 17th?
Yes.
So it's the day after Dom's.
That was one of the most adorable moments of me and Patrick's whole friendship.
What?
He remembered my birthday.
It's after my girlfriend's birthday.
I don't know when Patrick's birthday is.
- I know July 4th.
- That's easy to remember.
- October or something?
- I'm never impressed with someone
who remembers my birthday.
- June.
- No.
- January.
- February.
- No.
- March.
- April.
- No.
- May.
- June.
- No.
- July.
- Yeah.
- July?
- What day?
- I'm not gonna tell you.
- 11th.
- Nope.
- 12th.
- No.
- 13th.
- 14th.
- No.
- 15th.
- First.
- 20th, no, 23rd.
- 23rd. - That's it.
- Yeah, we got it dude, we guessed it so easily dude.
(laughing)
- That was incredibly easy. - That took so long.
I had to, July was like, I feel like we guessed 15 months
before we went to July. - How did you guys know?
We hung out on my birthday I thought.
- Did we? - Yeah, and I was like,
today's July 23rd. - No, we didn't hang out,
no I went to, went to Leo's.
- You went to see what's for my birthday.
- Oh yeah, I was in California.
- Yeah, you were out, he wasn't home.
- Yeah, he was, you know, he was at his door.
- Yeah, what was I doing?
It wasn't I tried you were at the video store video store
Buster I was turning my shit to blockbuster. I was returning all those videos
I'm not even a blockbuster anymore miss sir. Sometimes it feels like the late fees
They blockbuster on roku the late fees are getting bigger and bigger every year. It's cuz you don't return your shit
What if you if you never returned something to blockbuster and then they closed you just own the movie you own the movie
I think they might send their blockbuster assassin. They did. I think somebody
Names like a thousand dollar bill from blockbuster for a copy of freddy got fingered. Whoa, that's cool
Yeah, if they're if you keep their movie, they send josh wick after you
If you keep their if you keep their movie, then they'll make a movie called your name. God. Oh my god, they'll make a movie called
Reputation yeah if people went around saying that I got a finger if you yeah
Caleb and, Caleb, Patrick, and Cameron all got fingered.
Caleb, Patrick, and Tom Green.
All got, all fingered each other.
Yeah.
Where is he?
Tom Green?
No.
Canada.
Is he back in Canada?
I think so.
Do you know he was a rapper before he was a comedian?
Did you know before that he was a baby?
Before that, he was nothing.
Yeah.
He was a sperm in his dad's ass.
No, he actually wasn't.
That's one interesting thing about Tom Green is he skipped that whole stage entirely.
He was just an egg.
He was an egg.
only an egg. That's why he was able to get fingered. Because he didn't have the male
sperm to go into him.
He wasn't Freddy in that movie, his brother was Freddy.
I've never seen that movie, I don't give a fuck.
I'm sure it is, I've heard lots of people say it's good.
If they made that movie about Freddy Krueger, let me tell you what, you wouldn't want to
give finger back. Freddy gives the finger.
Freddy got fingered, I hope it's not by Wolverine. That's my joke about Freddy got fingered.
Who would win in a fight, Freddy Krueger or the Wolverine?
Freddy Krueger has more claws than Wolverine.
That's true.
No, it's not.
Because Wolverine has...
But Wolverine is smaller than Freddy Krueger.
Here's the question.
Freddy Krueger has five and Wolverine has six total.
So Wolverine wins.
Yeah, but Freddy can get you in the dream.
Freddy Krueger would molest Wolverine because he's so short.
He'd be able to... You do what he does to the children.
He thought he was a hairy kid.
He thought he was a hairy kid and he went into his nightmares and had sex with his nightmare.
I bet yeah the Wolverine would he would need to never sleep. Yeah. Like Wall Street. Well,
he doesn't really need to sleep does he? Wolverine? I think everybody needs to sleep Patrick. No,
if you're Wolverine, the metal powers. Yeah. He's a battery power. Yeah, he's made out of a battery.
He's a robot. Yeah, as long as he doesn't, you know, lose his battery juice. He's going to town
on his nuts up there. Can you not talk about Caleb like that? Not me. I wish I could go to town on my
nuts. My the thing is my nuts are long enough, but my my I can't read your neck
only because of the neck brace. Yeah, if I had a long enough, if I if I he's
doing doing that thing that they do where they they put all the gold rings
on the neck. So yeah, yeah. So I have a big long neck. Yeah, but then the rings
get in the way. Yeah, God damn. Once you take the rings off, you can't. It's
pretty funny. You take the rings off and your neck is just floppy. You can't. Oh
If you take the rings off don't don't doesn't your neck break. I think I think it depends on how many rings you have
Yeah, I think they can die. I think you can die if you take your rings off
Well, how do you have sex if you're the ring lady? You don't oh, you don't know. Absolutely not. I'm gonna become one
I'm gonna get the rings. I'm gonna get there, you know, like these bitches Sonic that fucking hedgehog
Mm-hmm
He'd be collecting those rings and snapping their necks like it was fucking
Like it was yeah, and then he'd fall down and all the rings would come out
Yeah, and then they'd be like you killed all our friends for nothing. They'd probably kill him. He'd say got a blast
He said I'm having a brain blast and it would go inside his brain. I'm having a sonic moment
He wouldn't say that dude. That's not in the movie having that awkward. That's not in the movie
It's Sonic moment where you're the bluest guy in your friend group
So annoying it's not a moment when your your dad is dr. Robotnik. Oh fuck
Jim Carrey. Jim Carrey. Jim Carrey. Jim Carrey. They should have made Jim Carrey's
shaped like an egg for a movie. I don't care-y about Jim Carrey's girlfriend. About his girlfriend who he killed.
I don't give a fuck that he forced better prescription drugs. It doesn't mean anything to me. Allegedly.
Allegedly. Dude, he made Yes Man and she said, "Do you want to kill me?"
He said, "I'm a method actor, I gotta do it."
He said, "Alrighty."
He was studying for...
I'm a method actor, so I have to give you this crystal meth to do my acting.
Yeah, exactly.
They were doing a Man on the Moon sequel, and he was doing an Andy Kaufman bit where
he kills a woman.
Because it was like, what if Andy Kaufman hadn't died and had continued with the path
of like wrestling girls?
It's like, oh, well, clearly he'd kill his girlfriend.
And Jim Carrey.
serious Jim and Andy and Kim moment. I don't think Jim ever left Andy. Whoa. Mm-hmm.
I don't think Andy ever left Jim. Yeah. I think they're still married. Yeah. I think
they didn't say till death do us part when they did their vows. Did you guys
watch the Jim and Andy documentary? Yeah. He looks like such a bad person.
He looks, I mean, just a crazy move. Yeah. To put out a movie where you're like,
yeah, I went crazy for like three years. Yeah. And like kind of I'm still crazy.
Yeah, and he sits there, he's sitting there the whole time just like eyes bulging like this is the greatest work of art
I've ever done. I think the Grinch changed him. The Grinch? Yeah.
Because he talks about, he's like, he talks about in that movie
He's like, like every role I've done has like become a part of me and it's like dude you played one of the most
horrific villains in in media history. And he did, he did Andy Kaufman the year before the Grinch.
Imagine what kind of psycho shit. Holy crap.
It's like playing the Hitler and Mussolini back to back. Yeah, yeah exactly. Yeah, and both evil and they yeah
Yeah, it's really bad exactly
Andy Kaufman and Andy Grinch Andy Grinchman Andy Grinchman the scariest person of all time
Grinch Kaufman the Jewish Grinch
That's why he hates Christmas
It's Grinchy Kaufman dude
You didn't have to go there buddy
Yeah I did, I shut up
You're crazy
He's saying some wild shit tonight
guy on the show. You're the Grinch of the show. Who's the most, I think Cameron's the most
evil. I'm the goodest, I'm the best. I'm not the most evil. I think you're the most evil.
You guys are just saying that because I'm wearing all black. No. You're the most evil.
You're definitely the most evil. I've read all. I'm not the most evil. Okay, you're the
most evil. By what metric? I just proved it. I said it. Stats. Stats, yeah, your stats.
You might want to take a look at my stats again. Scroll all the way to the bottom. It
says 100% 100% RBI 300 yeah what's my batting average BMI 3 mm-hmm yeah
batting average like a bat because I'm evil yeah actually you admit it
evil 1,000 point okay guys I just convincing you I was good was part of my
evil scheme I'm at you're right I am I think I'm the goodest one wait well
because your evil scheme of confusing us your good failed that means you're bad
at being evil so you're good Phil. Good Phil? You don't know good Phil. We don't talk about
good Phil. Why not? He's the opposite of the Grinch. He was the third Mike before Patrick.
He didn't talk, he just sat in the room with us. I don't know why I'm bringing this up.
I knew we weren't going to talk about it. I don't know if we were going to talk about
I feel like we should just for the fans.
We should.
Our beloved intern.
Oh my god.
Chris Lucero passed away.
Yeah, Patrick sat on him.
No.
Well, Chris Lucero actually got into a moped accident and then Patrick sat on his body afterward.
And we were like, "Patrick, what are you doing?"
And he was like, "He's already gonna die anyway. I might as well get the kill."
Chris had terminal cancer and his last wish was to ride a moped with me.
And I said, "Chris, there's no way I'm letting you sit behind me on a moped.
It's either going to be you on the moped or me watching you on the moped."
And he, you know, brittle bones, full of cancer.
He shot the moped, he didn't know how to drive it, he went full speed into a mailbox.
And as I was trying to help him up, I did slip on a patch of black ice and snapped on his
head.
That is not true.
Which caused it to explode because his bones were so thin.
You said, "I'm going to see if I can explode this guy's head by sitting on him."
That is not what I said.
Here's what happened.
First of all, Patrick was driving the moped.
I was not trying to involve Chris. The reason Chris died is because I painted a hamburger
on a brick wall and Patrick, he accelerated so hard into the hamburger that Chris exploded
on impact. But Patrick bounced off like a ball.
That's not what happened.
That is what happened. And then you landed on his ass first.
You landed next to him and then you stood up and then you moved over.
- And then you tried to eat the turkey sandwich again.
You ran back into the wall.
- It's a turkey sandwich now?
Your story's not even adding up.
- No, it's a turkey hamburger.
- It was a turkey sandwich.
- It was not a turkey hamburger.
- It is a turkey hamburger.
- You said turkey sandwich.
- It's a turkey burger. - It's on tape.
We have it right here. - It's not.
- It says turkey. - It's not.
- You said turkey. - I will edit that out
and change it to turkey sandwich.
But you, and then you tried to eat the turkey sandwich
and then you died because of the bricks.
- I'm still alive.
- Well, no, you're obviously lying.
- We're talking to Patrick's AI.
- We keep you, we clone you.
- AI self.
- Yeah.
- He's a cloned AI.
- Yeah, you're the Google home.
- No.
- You're Dogel.
- Dogel Doran.
- Well, I'll prove it.
Okay, Dogel, play,
"Don't You Wish Your Girlfriend Was Hot Like Me."
- It's not gonna play.
See, he responded to Dogel.
- It's not gonna play, no.
- He responded to the name Dogel.
- It wouldn't.
♪ Don't you wish your girlfriend was hot ♪
- It's playing, oh my God.
- It's playing out of his mouth.
- It's not playing.
- It's playing out of Patrick's mouth.
wish your girlfriend was a freak. I was trying to update our fans about a beloved member of
the podcast about List family. Okay Dogel, shut up. Okay Dogel, be quiet.
Alright, so yeah, we're going to have a service for Chris. It's going to be inside the Dunkin'
Donuts in Chinatown in Boston. He didn't really like that place but it's, you know, it's fitting.
I didn't give a fuck about that guy. I mean, I feel like we owe it to him to have a service.
we should have something we won't be there so I don't get in trouble we're
gonna take we're gonna take the car we're gonna take his coffin there on a on a
two-wheel dolly and leave it in the doorway at the of the Chinatown Dunkin
Donuts we're gonna say thank you to the staff who doesn't know about this yet
but I'm sure they'll be cooperative and then we're gonna leave we're gonna have
you go into the Dunkin Donuts in Chinatown in Boston you order the Chris
Lucero sandwich Chris Lucero special you and they'll give you one of his teeth
I'm telling you. You can put on a necklace. Yeah. We kept, once the disease got very bad,
we kept all of his teeth in a jar at the Dunkin Donuts. Yeah. And if you go to the Chinese town
Dunkin Donuts, they're kept in a thing of hair gel. Yeah. And they'll put it in your cup like ice.
Yep. You get Chris's teeth covered in hair gel in your coffee. Yeah. And they say that's the Lucero.
Promise. And it's the green club man hair gel from the barber.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's the blue stuff.
Yeah. No, no, not barbicide. It's the blue.
Yeah, it's barbicide.
It's barbicide. You drink it.
You put the barbicide in your white coffee, you're going to have a blue smoothie.
Blue ass coffee.
You're going to have a blue, blue Christmas.
Now, Christmas Lucero.
Yeah, so R.I.P. Chris.
Christmas Tucker Lucero. Rest in peace. August 1st, 1990 to 20 minutes ago.
But yeah, sir, it all happened 20 minutes. Yeah, it actually happened during the episode. Yeah
26 minutes. Okay, so
77 go back go back to the episode listen to six minutes and you're gonna hear a loud crash in the background
And that's what that is
Yeah, it's a real shame. He did he connected us to a lot of people. I think he faked his death like Andy Kaufman
Maybe he did, you know, I think if you're gonna become the new great you could fake your death
how would you do it? Probably how would you... Cut my head off. Rocket jump. Cut your head off and
rocket jump? How would you survive cutting your head off? Would you put a
fake head and just walk around with your body? What? If you're faking your death? I
would cut my head off. Yeah but how would you fake it? How would you fake it? What do you mean?
You cut off your head to fake your death. No I would cut my head off like to fake my
death. Yeah, but then you would die because your head would be gone. No. Why?
No, not... I'll do it. I'll do it special. I'll do it different. There is a way...
Actually, I was reading about this on the Discovery Channel. There is a way that
you can cut your head off and survive. Yeah, that's exactly what I'm talking about.
You have to follow a very specific order of cutting off your head. What is it?
first your head. You start with the neck side of your head and then you cut
down like two inches and then you just cut straight across. And then you go wild.
Yeah and then it's a freestyle. And then you freestyle from there. Yeah.
But yeah I would go crazy. I would do a rocket jump so it's me and I'm
jumping. Freddie Wong. Yeah Freddie Wong style. I'm jumping like Freddie Wong.
doing the Freddy W jump and I'm jumping across a building okay and I shoot the
shoot the rocket down and then I just kind of just kick it away why would you
kick wait how does yeah people just see that you did yeah the way I would fake
my dad's I'd do a backflip I couldn't tell you couldn't couldn't tell you how
I was gonna fake it cuz then you don't know when it's gonna happen I would do
you just do a rocket jump and you die I know you're not now I'm just gonna do
I'm gonna hunt you down and I'm gonna fuck you.
When you faked your death.
Okay, pal!
After you faked your death, where are you going?
Where are you headed off to?
Probably going home.
Probably just gonna go home and sit there.
Go watch TV with my dog.
The next day, do you just go back to work?
Yeah.
Just keep faking your death,
just so the next day, you just go back into work.
No, I'm a different guy.
We saw you fucking jump off of a building yesterday.
yesterday no no I'm Kevin we better now a completely different person yeah oh my
like just with like a Groucho Marx mask I'd like a job here please are you
regretting faking your death I don't know what you're talking about yeah I'd
probably go to the movies and live there dude yeah I'd live there like I'd be the
phantom of the movies yeah but not ugly yeah yeah you'd still wear a mask though
No, and I wouldn't sing either. And I definitely wouldn't have a girlfriend. She'd ruin all the movies.
Why? How?
Because she'd talk about them during the movies.
She'd say, "Hey, who's that?" and I'd say, "UGH!"
Yeah.
That's his name.
We're watching the caveman movie.
That's what I do any time my girlfriend asks me a question during a movie. I just go, "BAAA!"
Yeah, that's the answer to your question.
We're watching the caveman movie.
The fun and annoying answer to say is, "Did you just go..."
you go I don't know I'm watching the same movie as you mm-hmm just be it and that's
fun it's fun your dad says yeah it's my dad's board yeah we should do it okay
grab it okay we're gonna do the Ouija board we're gonna do don't just watch
the it's hung up I'm gonna Google online Ouija board you can use this on the
keyboard we can use the planchette on the keyboard no you can't yeah we can
How? Same deal.
I'm just gonna Google online Ouija board.
I have some questions to ask.
Brainjar.com
Oh wait, we can talk to Chris Lucero.
Will you shut up?
Oh my god. We should talk to Chris Lucero.
Alright, what's our question? We can ask a question.
Chris, are you there?
Chris...
Lucero. We'll type out his full name.
Christmas Tucker.
Christmas Tucker Lucero.
Christmas Tucker...
Lucero are you there question ask and you press ask and then you hold your mouse
what okay okay hold on follow it as your answers what you're not worried about a
demon infecting your computer with a virus oh no I have no I'm a virus I also
have what about a virus from hell that's not what if we talk about a Satan that
be cool talking to Chris Lucero yeah I was asked if it's Satan they'll say no
Do you think he went to heaven or heck?
Who?
Chris.
Oh, definitely hell.
Oh, he went to hell.
Yeah.
Really?
He did some naughty stuff on the pod account.
Yeah.
He messaged some people.
And he said some stuff he shouldn't have said.
He's a nasty woman.
He messaged Brian Regan.
Yeah, and he said he wanted to crawl inside of his asshole.
Yeah.
Are you serious?
I'm dead serious.
Alright, let's talk to him.
Alright, we'll see.
Let's ask him.
Ask.
Alright, now I hold my mouth.
Okay, I follow.
No!
Okay, this is no.
Chris is not there.
Oh, wait.
It's moving again.
again it's going back it went oh it's done so Chris all right let's just do it
again let's ask again keep asking all right Chris there no okay all right okay
one more time again all right wait it has to it has to go back okay we're good
reset it all right ask again are you there ah yes that was we got a lot of
yeah he was praying he loves the rule of threes he's a huge improv comedy guy
ask him now Chris who killed you who killed you we can settle this once and
for all yeah I think I have a pretty strong deal was it Patrick I didn't kill
him and if I was it wasn't on purpose I think you killed you ask Oh P Oh Oh Oh
in on e1 one was that it space oh space f f oh r o okay all right what's what's
happening here one from M one from space okay one from why oh well you're from
why oh I'm not from one from yo mama one from yo mama you one from you Chris
what are you trying to say one from your from your space oh my god it's a
podcast P a maybe be Patrick one from your Patrick s one from your past oh
yeah Patrick and Chris go way back that's no yeah you do yeah back to it's a
school we go back to two months ago that's the past I that's pretty far away
as far as I'm concerned well okay well we that still does not say it's me no me
Me and Caleb have never met, I'm pretty sure that you're the only person who's ever met
Chris ever in Chris's life.
No, that's not true.
You did.
It's not true.
Prove it.
Ask him.
Ask him a question.
Yeah, what are you going to ask him?
Say, have you met Cameron and Caleb?
Okay.
Let's see here.
Have you met Cameron and Caleb?
And I'm just going to add, or let's see here, Cameron and Caleb.
I'm just going to add here, say no at the end.
Just so he knows to say no.
Yeah, just so he knows to say no.
All right, let's ask. He says L.
So far it's the worst spelling I've ever fucking seen.
E. A. I think I know what he's going to say.
Is he going to go to V? Yeah, he goes to V.
Leave. E. Leave Cameron and Caleb out of this.
Oh my God, he says leave Cameron and Caleb out of this.
That's what he said. M. Leave my people I never met, Cameron and
Caleb out of this. Me, leave me a sandwich in the kitchen for when I get home. I think
he's gonna say alone.
He's gonna say alone.
No, leave me at home.
No, Chris, don't. Chris, do not spell that word. Do not.
Okay, he says leave me now.
Oh, now, okay.
Woo!
Alright, bye Chris. Should we just say bye to him?
Yeah, let's just say bye, just see what he says.
Wait, what if it's not Chris?
No, he said leave me. He said it was Chris.
Well, but he said it wasn't Chris twice.
Well, he was joking.
I mean if it was Chris.
Ask if you are the devil.
No I want Mr. Crap.
Ask if this is the Grinch.
Ask if you know the Grinch.
No fuck.
Please do.
Is this the Grinch?
Are you?
Are you yeah.
Are you the Grinch?
Question mark.
Ask.
Please no.
Oh thank god.
Alright it's Chris.
Let's ask him one more time.
Okay.
Whoa.
We have to wait for it to reset.
Oh, some crazy demon.
Oh my god!
He went to yes and no.
It's da blue grinch.
Oh god.
Wait, ask if it's the blue grinch.
Are you the
blue grinch?
Ask.
Oh, no he's not.
No, it's a regular grinch.
It's like the half grinch.
It's Grinch Coffman, dude.
Fuck.
Yeah, this better not be Grinch Coffman.
Half Grinch, half Andy Coffman, the ultimate...
The ultimate evil.
The ultimate enemy.
We need to destroy...
We need to search and destroy the Grinch.
Wait, tell...
Okay.
What?
What are you...
Um...
Just...
I forgot what I was gonna ask.
We should just say bye to him.
I don't know.
If it's the Grinch, we should not be talking to him.
I do not...
What...
I mean, I'm thinking about...
Where are you hiding?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Where...
No, no, no, we should ask him where he's hiding.
Okay, alright.
Where...
Where are you hiding Grinch?
Where are you Grinch?
Just you have to say Grinch though.
So just because it seems like there's multiple people on the line.
Maybe it's a group call.
Yeah just in case it's Chris or like someone else.
Where are you Grinch?
Ask.
He says F.
F.
U C K.
No he doesn't.
F A.
Oh no.
Grinch.
R.
Space.
Oh far.
Oh he's far?
Far A.
Yeah I was going to say far away I think.
Thank God.
Far.
Yeah, W-O.
What you don't want from the Grinch is, "Hey, I'll make him knock on your front door."
Oh my God, he said far away and then he said, "Dot, dot, dot, not."
There's no dots on this.
There's no dots on the board.
I was trying to do a funny joke.
Can you, okay.
He said far away.
Ask if it's, I want to start, this is, you got to ask if it's the devil.
I don't want, you got to ask if it's the devil.
What if it's the Grinch and the devil working together?
I think we should figure that out just in case.
like the Holy Trinity it's the unholy Trinity yeah the devil the Grinch and Andy Kaufman
yeah and they all they all work with each other in hell yeah look Grinch has the
green part of hell yeah also in Inferno the green Inferno yeah he probably Andy
Kaufman just keeps playing pranks on you yeah Andy Kaufman pretends to be Elvis
and you're like oh shit Elvis is down here and he goes not yeah Andy Kaufman
runs the women half of hell he just wrestles yeah either you either get
He's beating up all of our moms.
Yeah.
Stop, stop.
What are you doing?
You're trying to hack the Ouija board, dude.
That's bad juju, man.
I don't want Patrick's fingers to touch my computer.
Why?
We didn't even capitalize demon.
He's our demon.
All right.
Let's see what it says.
It says L.
I bet it just says leave again.
Yeah, A.
Oh, come on, dude.
E.
E, I mean, not A.
A.
I wish this went faster.
Yeah.
Because ghosts are so stupid.
We should have a 100 times faster.
I know.
Ghosts are so stupid.
We should have a 100x speed Ouija board.
Ghosts are so dumb they can't even spell fast.
Ghosts need to spell faster.
Leave space.
The copyright on this website is 1999-2008.
That's pretty cool.
That's a good year.
Yeah.
Those are those great years.
If you guys want to try out the Ouija board and talk to the Grinch or Chris Lucero, it's
brainjar.com/dhtml/ouija.
I still say we get a fucking real Ouija board in here, in this bitch.
Because I think this thing might be phony.
Yeah, I think this might just be a...
This Ouija board is capping.
This might be like a hacker from the internet
just kind of trying to trick us.
He's... there's something feeding it.
Somebody's feeding the meter.
Yeah. Fuckba you.
Alright, Patrick, type fuckba.
He's gonna be so angry.
C. That could be for Caleb.
A. That could be just Caleb.
Or Cameron. N. Canrin.
Can. N again.
Can. Na. O.
O. Cannot. T. Do you think he's just gonna say cannot understand?
Speece. Space. Oh my god. Dude my brain is melting right now. S cannot say. I bet it's
gonna be cannot say. A. And then all the way over to Y. Cannot say. I'm done with this
bullshit dude. Yeah I don't wanna do this anymore. Patrick please stop typing shit in
it's boring and I hate you. Why don't you just X out of the page? You have to say goodbye
or else the demon stays. Yeah, that's true. Let's say bye. Bye, love you. Fuck you. Bye,
love you. Love you, fuck you. Love you and suck you. Love you and I suck you. And I suck
your fuck. Love you. That's disgusting. Bye, love you and I suck you, ask. This is the last
one. C-A- oh my god, I hate this guy. He's gonna say bye. Go away, I'm done with this
demon and it's spelling out cannoli I think c-a-n-n-o we know what he's gonna
yeah we're done can all right we're closing the connection yeah severing the
connection Cameron's computer just got hacked by a demon there's the devil
from tenacious deep pick of destiny on screen and he's laughing at us I'm for
real I think he's laughing cuz he's happy cuz no no he's not he's laughing
because he just got the pick of destiny and he he's gonna beat our asses that's
not true dude he is man he just got he just it went back into his tooth yeah
crap we got a call we got a call we got a call Jables and KG and the
Ghostbusters no the Ghostbusters don't fuck with them. I will never call a woman to do a man's job.
we called the old Ghostbusters they're all dead
Bill Murray is alive and well mm-hmm yeah but the characters are dead no
they're not yeah they are I didn't watch yeah they are did you guys see the girl
Ghostbusters no did you Patrick no I didn't I think Ghostbusters the original
is a really overrated movie. I love it. I think it's pretty bad overall. I like Ghostbusters
2 better just because people hate it. I think the effects in Ghostbusters are great, are
really fun, but I don't think the movie is very good. I don't think it's funny at all.
I think both Ghostbusters are equal. I want to fuck the lady from the fire department
in those movies. I want to fuck the Slimer from the ghost movies. If Slimer had big juicy
slimy titties, I would love to slime on them and get slimed by them. Slimer's wife is the
monster from monsters incorporated that goes Mike Wazowski.
Slommer's wife is a big green BBW and I ain't having no hate on that bitch.
A GGW.
She's a green green woman.
She's a green lean green.
What do you guys think about this?
- Slimer on acid. - Slimer on acid.
- There was a blue slimer. - Oh.
- That wouldn't happen. - I would call the Ghostbusters on the Grinch.
And I would say, "Sick 'em, boys."
- Yeah. - What if you-- Can you--
Did the Ghostbusters guns work on people?
- Yeah, man. They put me in the-- - In the hospital.
They put me in the hospital with that shit, dude.
They shot me in the leg. On regular people, it's just a normal gun.
[laughter]
- It's just a normal electric gun. - Yeah.
of normal electric gun you charge it it shoots electric bullets who's laser
bullet I like this buster I know what y'all talking about I don't dislike it I
just think it's really overrated yeah you're gonna tell me that Sigourney
Weaver looking into her fridge just trying to get a nice late-night snack
and seeing the devil's dog okay but Joker did that better no he didn't yeah
he went in the fridge and he stayed in there meanwhile she came out what he
goes in the fridge and Joker you didn't see Joker what he goes in the fridge
that's one of the things that makes him turn crazy he goes in the fridge and
there's fumes from expired cheese and mushrooms and stuff that make him turn
into the Joker that's it it says that in the movie I haven't seen the movie the
makeup is where's his milk the milk goes on his face and makes it white what from
the fridge you guys I didn't even read the summary no no yeah he's that's why
it's good it's it's like a grocery based take on the story are you serious that's
What?
Yeah, I'm serious.
He goes to the grocery store and he breaks, he opens up the cartons of eggs
and he says, I'm just seeing if there any are broken, but he switches the
cartons so the brown eggs are in the white eggs and the white eggs are in the
brown eggs.
And he says, he goes.
Oh my God.
Oh no, I did see this part where he eats a huge strawberry and it makes his
lips be red.
Yeah, I forgot about that.
There's a part when he goes into the, he finds an old bottle of old glass
bottle of Coca-Cola and he sucks his whole face in and it turns his face into
Cocoa Bottle shape. What? That's one of the climaxes of the movie. The movie has 10 climaxes.
Damn. The perfect movie. Yeah. That's why it's up for so many Oscars. That's one thing
about movies. They talk about structure. One climax. Why wouldn't you just make like a
hundred like climaxes? Uh-huh. Just have like from the beginning like boom boom boom boom
boom one after another. Yeah. Oh my god we're falling off this bridge. Yeah that's like
the best part of the movie. Yeah. You know? Yeah. So I just feel like you know Ghostbusters
for example, the part where you get to see Lady Slimer, like they could have done that
50 more times.
They could have done that at the beginning.
Did they have that?
That's when I climax in the movie.
Did they have a Lady Slimer for Ghostbusters?
I don't know.
2016?
I don't think so.
I think they had a Mr. Slimer.
They had the real guy.
Big Slimer.
And the regular Slimer kind of has some flappers on him too.
Some big sloppy white waps.
Dude, it's not slime, it's milk.
It better be.
better be green milk that's don't worry that's green milk that's that's that's
lettuce flavored milk you know like strawberry milk that's not a milk that's
booger milk you gotta eat the lettuce milk is he a booger is slime or a booger
yeah ghost he does not guy not man he's a ghost dude that is one thing I really
like about Ghostbusters and none of the ghosts are like people there's like
ran it's just like yeah here's a good you know people died I turned into a giant
jogging go giant green that's not a real thing I don't know you're talking about
fuck there's what if he ghost died and turned into a monster what about the
marshmallow man that's not a ghost that was the marshmallow man yeah what about
him what about he was here it goes come on
is it let's hear it I do like one thing I really like about Ghostbusters is the
idea that just like if enough ghosts get out just everything turns kind of weird
Yeah, you know cuz like said like just stuff do you yeah, I do like the idea that you can capture a ghost
Yeah, I do what yeah, and put them on I like how it's like the whole ghost thing is like
Hey, all the pizzas are gone. I like when I like
Yeah, there's actually uh, there's actually an insurgent of Antifa ghosts
Yeah, we're getting the proud ghosts. We're gonna beat the shit out of them.
The proud ghosts? Yeah. Yeah, with our online practice. With our sharp tongues.
We're talking about practice. I'm gonna stick my sharp tongue up that proud ghost urethra,
if you know what I'm talking about. Whoa. My tongue. I'm gonna loosen that shit up so they can get those crystals out of there.
Mm-hmm. My tongue is made out of a crystal. They got a buildup in their urethra, and I'm about to... What?
I'm about to clean that shit out with my pointy pencil-shaped tongue.
[laughter]
And they're gonna like it. Do you guys have long tongues?
No, I don't think so.
Can you touch your damn toes with your tongue?
Yeah.
Do I have a long tongue?
I mean if I put my tongue.
You have a normal tongue I think.
How is that?
Yours is short.
Yeah.
You have a shorter side of the tongue.
It's because I'm not gay.
I heard they're putting a tongue in the Lego movie.
I heard they're putting a tongue on Legos.
They're actually going to make a Lego movie.
I heard I'm going to put my tongue on my Legos later.
They're making a two pronged Lego movie experience where you wear different 3D glasses.
One is blue channel, one is red channel.
Red Channel and if you wear blue channel you watch a boys version if you wear red
channel you get to see a girl's I heard that's what they're doing already
reserved one ticket for the girls for you for you because I love you so much
for you for you oh you love a girl yeah okay you're going to gay jail population
you they should just have two separate McDonald's so you don't have to pick the
toy. Yeah, they should. I always freak out when they ask me which toy I want.
Ah shit, I went to the girls McDonald's. Fuck. Dude, you're legally a girl now and shit bro.
That's the guy who works there. And at the boys McDonald's they have McChicken, the girls
McDonald's salads and water. No dressing, stop asking. The dressing is water. Your dressing
What is your dress that you're wearing?
You have to go to the Boys McDonald's and ask if you can have any dressing, but they won't
let you because no girls allowed.
Yeah.
Also, there's a pin code for the boys.
And it's 1234.
And it's upside down 80085.
The slogan for the Girls McDonald's, still I'm loving it, but the slogan for the Boys
McDonald's is "McDonald's is cool."
I'm a boy.
Yeah.
I'm gaming.
McDonald's is cool and I'm a boy.
I'm playing sports.
I'm boys McDonald's boys don't boy boys don't know about it's McDonald's and then
it's McDenas and make you know is the girl's name yeah McDonald and it's my
friend Donna's and it's Tina McNeil Dina Tina McDena is the girl clown mm-hmm but
she's just a no she's not a clown yeah she's a businesswoman they like that
she's a girl boss she's a girl yeah she's a girl who's trying she's a female
comedian and Ronald McDonald abuses her like Harley Quinn because he's a joker
yeah evil Ronald McDonald, oh gangster Ronald McDonald. Yeah. Oh no. Get it. Oh my god.
That would be so cool. Gangster Ronald McDonald. Yeah. Yeah he'd probably say something like
I'm gonna bust a McChicken in your ass. Yeah. Yeah. I can just visualize the
Twitter account now. Yeah. I'm gonna Google gangster Ronald McDonald right now
just to see if anyone's thought of this because we could make a killing on shirts
shirts of gang no it's definitely shirts of gangster Ronald McDonald I've seen
them in swap meets. 20,000 people for Ronald McDonald to go gangsta it's a
Facebook page. Oh no. It got deleted. It was a petition to make Ronald McDonald.
Whoever wondered what would happen if Ronald McDonald went gangsta?
There's no there's no cute there's no a cashed cached coche. There's no cock on my
Google we just got a way back that yeah look up Ronald McDonald trying to weigh
back the Facebook page what about gangsta McDonald Bugs Bunny gangster
Ronald McDonald what about Oh gangsta Mcgang Ronald make it gangsta yeah yeah
this page does not have nuggets oh my god dude mm-hmm and he sells the ghetto
burger yeah - Ronald from yeah it's called the and it's called the triple
MC Donald on the mic. I'm going to screenshot this entire page and we're just going to post
this with the episode.
What are the comments on it?
Show comments. First comment, like a gansta Ronald. Weird, the last time I checked Ronald
McDonald wasn't Asian.
What?
It probably came from one of the Japanese McDonald's commercials.
Yeah.
He doesn't look Asian, he looks like Ronald.
He looks gangsta.
He's making the gangsta face.
It's the opposite.
McGangsta. Let's see. Oh Ronald McDonald is gangsta by Kierhan on DeviantArt.
Let's see this. Let's see this one. Damn. He does look fresh. He do be looking kinda gangsta here.
I snapped this picture of Ronald McDonald at a parade in St. John's whatever state
M.I. is. Missouri. How did they get this picture? I happened to shoot quite a few shots
rapidly and got him in a gangsta pose. Friggin hilarious. Yeah we'll post this
one too. How did they get Ronald McDonald? Oh that's gangsta Ronald McDonald. Yeah it's
different. Because you never know who's showing up when calling
gangster Ronald McDonald. That's like, speaking of Andy Kaufman, that's like a Tony
Clifton situation. Andy Kaufman was Tony Clifton and he was also Ronald McDonald.
No, Andy Kaufman was gangster Ronald McDonald. There's four comments on this. Check out this
first comment on this gangster Ronald McDonald. He's Michael Jackson trying to
hide his rotting face behind lots of paint and trying to catch some children.
That's from 2010. Here's another comment from 2008. That's wrong, funny, very funny,
but wrong lol as much as that's the funniest thing i've ever heard
seriously messed up gangster ronald you got some freaking screws loose yeah
comment you got a stick you're sticking the head
raffle omg that had to be the best day ever nice shot indeed
ah ha ha ha from cold play and cold play listening to cold play where i live in
hell this has 6k views this picture i think
ronald mcdonald picture on a shirt ronald mcdonald goes to heaven
gangster Ronald McDonald I think we know where he goes yeah damn gangster Ronald
McDonald in the hood goes to Shangri-La let's make the let's make a video
gangster Ronald McDonald in the hood and we'll go to the hood and I'll dress up
like gangster Ronald McDonald I'll say yo yo yo yo it's gangster Ronald McDonald
no I won't say boop you're obsessed with boop buddy yeah I gotta tell you yeah
you're Betty Boop and we know what Boop is and you're a girl named Betty. You're
Betty Boop. No. You're Betty Boobs because you have big boobs. No. Yeah. You're
Caleb Boobs. You're Patrick Vagina. You're Patrick Vagina. And you have a huge
You have a huge boobs and in the middle on your sternum you have a pussy.
You guys are both girl girl. Girl and girl. Your first name is girl and your last name is girl.
Cameron Diaz is a boy, Cameron is a boy's name. Cameron Diaz is a boy.
What were you saying? So girls kiss their vaginas together when they're lesbians?
Mm-hmm. Do they use their tongue? They slam it very hard. They run at each other.
They run at each other and do a scissor kick. Like on a fencing stage. They jump into the air and spread their legs.
Yeah, they kick their legs out and go, "HUH!"
And then you become a lesbian couple when you get fused together that way.
When you get married that way.
You have to be really, if you don't open your legs in time, you could shoot, you could go
inside the other woman's vagina and get trapped in there.
If one woman has a few mongol spousy, then you can get stuck in it.
Yeah, you get sucked in.
Also, yeah, yeah, and if your leg could go in there.
And then the other girl might die.
The other girl, but it would...
And the reason why guys don't do that when they're gay is because your balls would hurt
so bad.
But women have no feeling where their pussy is.
In every movie I watched as a kid, a guy gets kicked in the nuts, he goes "Ugh!" and then
when a girl gets kicked in the nuts she goes "Huh?
I don't even have balls.
I need to go shopping now!"
I need to go shopping!
I think you broke my nails down there.
My down there nails.
Girls should get nails where their vaginas are.
Anything to cover up that whatever it is.
That nasty thingy.
That nasty sarlacc.
No, I just think they're scary.
When I was a kid I hated seeing a woman's vagina.
No, please.
Please, stop.
Stop showing me.
Oh my goodness, I don't want to see it for the millionth time, lady.
Put it outside.
Put it away! Put that thing away!
Put that thing outside where it belongs.
Hey, put that thing back in your pants.
A woman hope with throwing
her vagina out of her pants.
She's just holding it in a hot dog bun.
They should be able to.
Can they not?
They should be able to detach it like a computer part.
Wait, so what's a fleshlight then? I thought a fleshlight came out of a girl.
No. And they removed it.
They sold it. Dude, they would never sell them for that cheap
if that was the case.
So what is it then?
is they have a plastic man stick his penis into a woman's vagina and then they heat
him up until he dies and then they cut off that part of him.
And then they, well, that would be a penis shape. That would be the wrong way.
No, they melt his penis inside of her. And then they use that as a cast.
And then they hollow it out. Okay.
They hollow it out like a chocolate bunny.
They put saran wrap in there and they use plaster.
Yeah, they do. They make a chocolate bunny with the vagina.
Yeah, they put a lot of chocolate in there.
Wait, how do they make, how do they get a chocolate bunny to stay still enough for a chocolate
bunny mold?
I don't know.
My dad makes chocolate bunnies.
That's his like thing for Christmas and Easter.
Your dad makes chocolate bunnies for Christmas?
And Easter, yeah.
Your dad's a psycho.
He's got his holidays all which way?
Well, he makes them pretty much for any holiday he can get away with it.
I'm gonna make some chocolate bunnies after this.
He has these old like vintage chocolate bunny molds and it's like I guess, yeah, he's, I
don't want to get into this.
(laughter)
- Chocolate would go bad if it was old.
- Vintage chocolate.
- Chocolate doesn't go bad.
- First of all, chocolate doesn't go bad.
I ate a chocolate that was a thousand years old yesterday.
I puked a little bit, but it was 'cause I was scared
of the chocolate 'cause of the shape it was in.
- Cameron's daddy poops like that.
- Cameron's gonna poop into the chocolate bunny mold
his dad has.
- His dad won't even realize it 'cause he loves being pooped.
- Dad, go check out your chocolate bunnies.
(laughter)
- Notice anything different about them?
- He's just beat the shit out of them.
(laughter)
He beats the shit out of his adult son
for shitting in his chocolate bunny mold.
- Yeah, I mean, that's fair.
That's a fair reaction.
- If my dad beat me up for shitting in his chocolate bunny,
what's he doing?
- I don't know, being a cat.
- He's trying to go into my boxes.
- He's trying to go into Patrick's box.
- For shitting in his chocolate bunny mold
I'd tell him to grow up.
- Yeah, hey dad, grow up, dude.
- Hey dad, it's a--
- Stop hitting my brother.
dad it's a it's a joke not a dick don't take it so hard whoa hey dad it's a joke
not now your boyfriend stop sucking it off like a gay guy dad I'm just kidding
man no don't take away my Lego no no it's the only Lego I have it's a one by
one yeah just building what'd you build today I built another building I built a
rock I built a micro city and it's just the stud I built the universe I built a
single-celled organism I'm a scientist I should built a Joe mama what's that oh
it's Joe my it's your mama what's up dog I wait what is that don't let the cat go
on the computer or I'll you got some serious up cat you're gonna Hulk what's
up cat yeah what's up nothing much with you just meow once dude please say your
famous catchphrase meow please say meow I hate when he stands like a guy so bad
dude cat won't meow into the microphone please meow please say it say it say it
say it you are such an asshole you fucking suck dude this cat is the worst
fuck out of here man yeah and why I wasn't gonna say anything but you don't
have any hair also whoa all right also one time Oh what putting your please
put a tiny headscarf on your cat will and I've been fighting with Yoda really
yeah never a good idea yeah no yeah that didn't how about well did that work out
general Grievous or Count Dooku. Or Luke Skywalker. No, that was, he didn't fight him.
He fought him when he tried to take the food. Oh yeah, you're right. You are so dumb dude.
He went, I want your food. Yoda loves food. I love crackers and snacks. I need to take a shit.
Yoda's the audience insert. Oh, wait, we have Yoda here with us now. Hey Yoda, how's it going man?
you have to do right now? I need to take a shit.
Whoa, Yoda what do your shits look like? Are they green like you or are they little pellets?
Yes. Oh, I guess they're green pellets maybe.
Yes. Yoda, are you at all related to the Grinch?
That doesn't sound good. That sounds like a knowing laugh.
the fuck out of here man yeah oh he's gone oh he's scurried away Patrick where'd
you go all Yoda you it was like your I went to that I went Patrick was under the
table you find some little green pellets in there no no I found green M&Ms
oh I leave I hope they were green I got some bad news man oh that was Yoda's
little shit he's trying to beckon the cats what's that thing that's next to
water that's the feeder that's a machine is a timed feeder Patrick keeps machines
everything that even the cats can't stop looking at machines and screens yeah
that's one of the problems with modern society everybody's on their machines
all day everybody's either a cat or a human everybody's either a cat a machine
or a human yeah or somewhere in between that's the worst one it's just like
Alanis Morissette said isn't it ironic that your cat could be a machine it's
It's like a cat that's also a machine.
What are you talking about?
A lot of CD games have serious rewrites.
It's like if the Grinch didn't want to steal any presents.
It's like a play from Full House.
It's like an egg that you never eat.
It's like a snack that you don't like.
It's like a mom who never lets you play games. It's like a car. Isn't it ironic?
It's like a car with two wheels. A man went to his house. He sat down and he died
the next day. That is ironic. A guy tried to cook a meal and he looked in the pan
man and it was all a guy got so angry he fell over there was a ground yeah
frog when a frog did it out to school to the pond yeah it went inside and he ate
a bug. A kid went to math class and the math teacher said no class Tuesday. My
jacket, I got ink on my jacket. There were two boys went to school one day.
Is that break out song where someone talks? No. And that was not where you're supposed to take out
guns isn't it ironic? I'd get to take this crazy school shot or mass shooter
there was a video camera with an S and they lost all the files yeah there's a
guy there was a guy who tried to make an order a Taco Bell and he had to wait
like a whole hour that's also true that happened to me and Patrick. Oh yeah that happened to us on
the Friday there were two friends so I tried to type in the top okay it was
there was two friends who love to watch movies together and then one night one
of the friends got in a bad accident is there was a there was a fat guy who was
really thin. The candy store. The fat guy was really thin. But he ate all the candy and then he got thin.
Isn't it ironic? Uh you see the the heater um made the room cold. Cameron's not good at this. I'm on
fire. I'm so good. There was Santa Claus and he was on a motorcycle. And it was awesome.
And it was the Bat-cycle. Batman became the Joker. Isn't that ironic?
Batman is Bruce Wayne but Bruce Wayne has no money and he's married to another guy.
He never got married.
Oh that's why it's ironic.
Superman fought Batman and Batman got beat up so bad he cried.
How hard is that?
Okay, can I try another one?
Yeah, go ahead.
The Wi-Fi password was no Wi-Fi.
No.
No, it's like you type in no Wi-Fi.
My social security number is 9126-43434.
See now that's a good one.
A guy tried to wear some clothes, but all the clothes were a million sizes too big for him.
There was a rubber guy who was made out of erasers and he got married to a pencil.
Isn't it?
Adnan Syed killed Heyman Lee in Baltimore and then they made the podcast serial about him.
It's so easy this bitch got a fucking Oscar for this and Grammy and she got a
granny for this and she got to date the guy from Full House I would kill for a
granny the bathroom has an air freshener but it but it doesn't work and it smells
really bad the toilet smelled so good that I started eating all of my stuff
out of the toilet and drinking my water from the toilet was a bad Hawaiian guy
on us on us which and he lives in cross country name was Israel kamikolaka we
and he died of diabetes you remember him yeah he doesn't what isn't that the guy
that sings yeah somewhere with a rainbow that's a different song though Israel
kamikolaka we yeah okay wait can I align we're thinking of Canada not Hawaii can I
I do one last one.
We got too distracted by this Hawaii stuff.
Can I just do one last one?
I think I got it this time.
Okay.
Okay, don't interrupt me.
Don't interrupt this one, please.
We're already not off to a good start.
No, just don't interrupt because I know you guys have interrupted every single one I've
done so far.
So, I went to the music store, I bought a CD, I got home, it was a DVD, and then I looked
at the DVD closer and I was able to open it up and it had pages like a book inside.
What?
Because it's like that really happened to you. Are you serious? No, no, I mean well kind of I mean happened to him
No, it didn't happen. It didn't happen. It wouldn't happen. I'm you're right
Who's all right? All right. We can we end the episode there sure time. We're waiting. All right. Bye guys
I'm really sad now. There was a party