Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
- Premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Okay, do the thing you were doing.
- Chuck and Larry.
Chuck and Larry.
Chuck, Chuck, Chuck, Chuck.
- You were singing a second ago.
I was thinking the doctor,
when they say open your mouth and say ah,
they should say open your mouth and say,
(chanting)
Just to see if you have a beautiful voice and then maybe you could get on American Idol.
Yeah.
Yeah, well that's because my doctor is Dr. Dre.
No shot, dude.
Is that true?
Do you ever get mad?
Does he spend most of his time when you're in his office usually on the ones and twos?
Yeah, he spends a lot of his time doing like product, like what's that fucking A&R or whatever
the fuck.
A&R.
Not A&R, like inspection of his beats pills.
He does a lot of quality assurance.
what the was. I didn't know he was on the assembly line for those.
It's in his doctor's office. Really? It goes through his doctor's office so
there's like a hole in the wall of the conveyor belt. Yeah, it's like a sushi restaurant. And he has to look at every single one
and inspect it and put a sticker on it. He has to look at every single one and go, "Yeah!"
It says, "Dre approved." He puts the Beats logo
on it. And if one is broken, you get to take it home with you for free?
If he doesn't like one, he slaps it and throws it down a staircase.
case. He doesn't like it. Yeah, because there is a bunch of stairs in his office.
Well yeah, because he's got all these assistants walking around. Where else is he gonna throw people down?
Yeah, Dee Barnes just walks around his office. He tried throwing them off the
chair, but it's just not the same. They should make, I hope they make like a
sequel to the Compton movie, the Stratocompton movie. Yeah. It's just about
Dr. Dre and it's like him every time he has like someone in his life he doesn't
like he like slaps him and throws him down the stairs. He's like I'll have a
I'll have a nice tea sir we're out of tea. Be cool. He carries them to the
stairs. Yeah yeah yeah you want to see my stairs? Yeah yeah you made me mad just
now you're about to see my stairs. He's cool man. Yeah it's cool that he did that when
he was like 30 years old. I actually didn't know what you were talking about. I thought that was
just a thing. D Barnes? No. D Barnes is this like reporter who made I think she
would use she was like talking to him and she was like you don't like women and
you make all your songs about hurting women he's like no I don't.
Threw her down some stairs dude. Jesus. Pretty crazy man. At least he didn't throw her down a
Stairmaster because she would have gone forever. Yeah. On one of those. Oh man.
Yeah.
Get thrown down an escalator.
Oh, yeah.
Fuck.
That'd be scary.
I mean, you can't get off the escalator.
It's just very long.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's not like a Stairmaster where it's going to go indefinitely.
And you just know my white ass would fall exactly the speed that the escalator goes
up, so I'd be stuck in one place.
Oh, dude.
That's what my white ass would be doing.
I'd be rolling like a tumbleweed down that.
And you know my shoelace would get stuck in there.
I don't know how to tie them yet.
I still wear a rope, bro.
You know my flip-flops would get stuck in there, getting fucking grilled cheese.
my flip flops that they're really long in the front and they taper off until
they're as thin as a piece of paper.
And I wear them on the escalator. I hope nothing happens today. I wear them
around like automotive facilities, constructing cars with giant turbines
and shit. Like giant flippers.
Oh, haven't you known?
Yeah, I go scuba. I'm ready to go to the beach. And then I show up at the
beach at the Ford factory.
Yeah. Well, you know, the latest style is that the shoes now, they don't
just they don't have the two ends on the shoelaces there's like ten of them and
they all have tassels and they're 20 feet long. Yeah like a train on a
wedding dress. When did the the curled shoes stop? That was after
Elfin times. Okay yeah. Yeah Elfin. I think maybe we should bring them back.
Curled shoes? Yeah. Well that's one way to... Why do we have steel toed boots? Why not a
curled toe. Yeah. And there's a double layer. Yeah, you have double layer but
inside of the curl. Steel. Yeah, I was gonna say like a steel rod. Yeah, steel.
Yeah, it's like a combo. It can hold the rod. Yeah. It's like a steel combo. You can put a
bundle on it. Oh, you can put a rod into you, you have it curled up. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, and then you put a rod in, you curl it up, and you can carry stuff on
your shoe with the rod. Shit, god damn it, dude. We gotta get on Shark Tank so fucking bad.
They should do a jester shoe skate shoe. Yeah. I feel like you could put that out dude. That might be heat. They kind of did
No, I don't care
Now Dylan Reeder just made these like boots that he skated in yeah, and they were kind of they looked like a foreskin
Oh like a purple. Hell no. Oh, fuck you man. That's disgusting. Rest in peace Dylan.
He's dead. Yeah. Oh he died a couple years ago. Yeah, he died very young.
hard moment in my life. Really? I had a crisis. Really? What was the crisis?
Just like man, oh no, people can die.
That's true man. Yeah. How you guys been? What have you been up to? I kind of beefed my knee
again. You beefed it? You farted on it? Yeah I did. That doesn't make no damn sense. I put my knee under my
butt I went. That's how you fart? You fart like you're cracking your back? I had a
a very bad meal last night. I had a bone for dinner. Yeah. I farted like that. Yeah.
I've been eating those, I had one of those, you know those like hot and spicy
ramen bowls you put in the microwave? Oh yeah. I ate one of those. I woke up this morning.
They put as many things on it as they can to say don't eat this. Yeah.
Yeah. I had the shrimp, the shrimp flavor one and I woke up this morning and
just let out a, it sounded like somebody let a balloon go in my room.
yeah where it got high pitch at the end yeah oh dude it was awful
like just kept happening too and I was like man I gotta stop eating those and I
know I'm gonna get drunk again and buy another one they're fucked up there's so
much sodium and I'm there's so much sodium but it's like the perfect like
sober you up when it makes your farts so awesome that could stop a whale's
heartbeat yeah so much for like it's fucked I'm so fucked when I get older
yeah did you eat my you like every like every like spicy Mexican snack that says
mascalories. You eat all those too. That's like your favorite genre of food.
Los toxicos. Yeah, because like they have to... Cuidado! You can sell all that shit in Mexico. El culo!
Those crossbones! El Diablo. Come el Diablo. Oh man, dude. I haven't eaten them yet but I feel like you put a
thing of blue Takis in front of me I would you gotta try him dude there's a
reason why there's not a lot of blue fruits yeah you know even blueberries I
mean it's purple well blueberries already they covered it yeah most fruits are
berries what about blue cotton candy true that's a fruit I have been one
upped and I have been defeated hmm it happens even the best you think you
think Monsanto has been working on a blue raspberry probably yeah I think
that they thought that they would have it cracked,
so they told all the lollipop companies,
"Yeah, just go ahead,
"we'll have the blue raspberry out in probably six months."
- That's exactly what that would taste like, too.
- Yeah, yeah, they were like,
"Yo, just kind of freestyle it.
"We'll put it out, it'll be like banana,
"it doesn't matter what it actually tastes like."
- It was too good, it was the same with pink lemons, too.
- Yeah. - That's true.
Where that pink lemon at?
- True.
- Is that some kind of fucked up '70s rock euphemism
for a pussy?
- Yes. - A pink lemon?
Uh-huh. It tastes like battery acid.
Because it makes you go like this.
[Laughter]
Yeah. Licking the pussy like a warhead.
Sucking my lips down my throat after.
[Laughter]
Wow!
First it's sour, then you cum.
I had a warhead recently.
Yeah.
One, they're not as sour as I remember.
I think they've dialed it back.
the sorry could be you've like hurtness like burned your taste buds that I was
just about to say yeah maybe in my old age I have yeah I've destroyed my taste
buds and my tongue yeah I think it's less all day so more eating like El fire
sand yeah well you guys seeing this warheads that's all fine and good but
Madonna I'd like to see that horse head on a pike what is it old bitch
you think of that kid is fucking have you heard lucky star that's too great son
bitch never you guys my dad almost killed Madonna with a car he almost
killed Madonna with a car he literally yeah please like on purpose or no he was
fucking he like lived I have to say this is where he's living in California like
I said LA and he like was running a stop sign yeah and Madonna like clipped her
leg on his car and was like freaking out at him and he was like yeah who's this
crazy bitch oh it's Madonna and it's funny cuz I actually also almost killed
Madonna with my mind really yeah I got really close you should try again yeah I
might she probably probably definitely remembers my dad's probably went home
and thought of him when she got fucked by whoever fucked her Sean Penn every guy
in the world fucking old whore what is the matter with energy you're bringing
I mean today, you've been trained to hate Madonna because your dad probably had to
pay so much. I just think she's a stupid
cut it out.
What is going on with you today? I don't know man. I'm twenty twenty one. I
forgot to take my ginseng and I started got my shockers are all fucked up. I'm
turn into a Republican. Yeah, it's fucking bad man.
Madonna is a fucking...
You're dressed up like a bandaid.
Speaking of becoming a gay...
I'm not dressed like a bandaid.
You're dressed up like a bandaid.
You're one red hat away from...
No.
...this Madonna rant sounding evil.
No, I got dressed listening to Luther Vandross.
Oh, okay.
All right, you know what?
Props.
Dude, I'm a 60-year-old black guy today.
Yeah.
They had... I was at the gym today.
They had Fox News.
Fox News on the TV.
Nice.
And you know what they're talking about on there?
Apparently there was an article.
There was an article.
There's an article in some magazine or something that's about apparently now the word Jedi
is offensive.
No.
That's what they said.
See, that's what I'm saying, man.
Isn't that crazy?
That's crazy, man.
That's where I draw the line.
What do you think about that, Caleb?
Jedi?
Yeah.
Dude, Jedi.
Back in my day, you could say Jedi all you wanted to.
just a word. This is a word I'm gonna keep saying it. Yeah. Yeah. Why is it
offensive? I don't know. I mean they don't have sound on the TV so there's no way to tell.
Yeah I saw Fox News on the gym TV and closed his eyes on the treadmill. He put his hands over his eyes and went "Ahh no!"
Even if I did do that I would still be able to run okay. He tripped over his shoes. I can run with my eyes closed.
You're like a shark. Alright try it right now let's see it. Okay well let me step over
these cables here okay yeah that's now run over run back to your chair I can't
run there's not enough look I have to wear this headphone or what your excuses
and excuses that was not a run how am I supposed to run a job three feet I cannot
put the microphone down and go in the land phones to put the headphones down
no you know I I believe you I believe you look this is as far as I can go okay
- Okay, all right, all right, go.
- Put them down.
- No, I'm not gonna put them down.
- He can reach a running speed from this distance.
You need to relax.
- Okay, will you move the chair out of the way?
- Okay, hold on.
- Oh, he gets a little bit on the other end too.
- Yeah, here we go, okay.
All right.
(water gurgling)
(laughing)
- Wow.
- Okay, he did it.
- He actually did it.
- Impressive, right?
- Now imagine that on a treadmill.
- Cameron did fall face first into the treadmill.
- I've been having my left eye has been nonstop watering
for like four days now.
- You probably have conjunctivitis.
What's conjunctivitis? Speaking of poop, dude, did you really come to my house wearing a brown hat that says "P" on it?
Damn!
Well...
What's that stand for?
Poop?
You couldn't pick a different color for your pee hat?
I didn't get this. Mike D gave me this hat.
He got the poop hat!
He got the brown hat that just has a "P" on it!
Oh my god!
I'm gonna continue to wear it. I do think with this hat and the mustache I do look like
The poop salesman?
No, like the poop salesman.
I look like poop Mario.
You do look like poop Mario, bro.
No, Mike gave me this hat.
What's the P supposed to stand for?
Somebody told me, because it's like a...
What's it say on the tag?
poop it's a habits hat and it says P I don't know it doesn't say poop it's a
doesn't stand for anything it's just maybe USA no no it's some like old
baseball team no the first it's I think it might be the it's not fuck did they
say pepper they might have said something pepper the pepper the brown
- How do you spell Ebbets?
- E-B-B-E-T-S.
- E-B-B-B-D-B-D-B-B-B-D?
- Ebbets Field?
- Yeah.
And then, and then they have the hats.
- Hold on, should I just search Ebbets Hat?
- No, that's the hat.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
- What?
- It's the first result.
- What, okay.
We have to shop Father's Day sale.
- Oh, okay, hold on.
Hold on, now, they got deals, though.
- What are, okay, here.
These are, oh.
- Are you plugging your--
- Whoa, hold up, win a free hat?
- Shut up.
Why'd you close out of it?
Fuck you dude, I'm trying to find out what your hat...
Oh fuck dude, we could have won a free...
I'm doing you a huge favor right now by letting your hat not mean poop anymore.
We could have won a free hat.
You want another P?
Here's a brown one with a P.
You want a yellow hat that says P next?
There's five pages, I'm not going to...
Well you could make it spell pussy.
You could.
Yeah.
If you had five heads, that would be so good.
Hold on, go to...
No, no, no, no, you can find the P hat.
No, there's five pages of this!
Sort it by color!
Sort it by boob!
Sit down! Sit down!
I gotta... no.
You are wasting our time.
I'm not wasting anything, I'm figuring this out.
Anyway, my eyes have been bleeding water.
You definitely have some kind of very...
contagious...
I've been constantly crying.
Is it making gunk?
Not really.
Is it ever hard to open?
I'm imagining beautiful paintings all the time too.
The what?
The Paris Red Peppers.
The Poops.
But the hat's brown.
That's what it says, that's the exact hat.
Okay, but it wouldn't be a brown hat for a red pepper.
It says it right there, Paris Red Peppers.
Looks like it says 1946 Vintage Ball Cap, The Poop Patrick Hat.
It does not say the Poop Patrick Hat.
I think it says Patrick the Poop Man.
Oh my god.
This sucks.
It says Poop.
Patrick orders our poop hat.
Poop.
So it would be poof.
Poop hat.
Poof.
Poop.
Poop hat.
You guys enjoy bullying?
Patrick orders our poop hat and this.
That's right.
Yes sir.
And when it under and this it has a picture of poop.
Yeah.
Under this.
Because it came with a free poop gift.
It's the Paris Red Peppers.
You guys are jealous because you don't understand Parisian culture.
Yeah.
This is a very Parisian hat.
They would.
Don't get Kaled started on Parisian culture today.
That's right, dude.
I might bust out some fucked up evil.
Yeah.
Yeah, I might go fucking-- what's that guy's name?
Luther Vandross.
I might go Luther Vandross on Paris real quick.
Yeah.
I might go crazy.
heard you heard a glow of love it's a song he was a featured on you and I have a
some poop in your gloves when you're playing for the Poop Pirates or whatever
I'm trying to give you a do you remember the poop glove you remember that was a
genius plan someone had what was the poop glove you put your hand in poop and your
hand is like a poop glove. I think it's probably one of us. I think it could have been one of us.
Hey, if it's someone else, I'm sorry for stealing your idea.
Something about arm wrestling is like people say it's all, it's all like...
It's all in the arms.
Yeah, it's not. It's not. It's not in the arms.
No, it's in the mind.
It's in the table.
It's like the technique, but there needs to be a new, a third dimension to arm wrestling
where you're trying to do fucking like, you know, getting their heads.
Zero gravity table.
And also to see who can have a nastier hand.
Yeah.
You don't want to touch it, right?
Mm-hmm.
Like you should have to like, it should be like pee hand versus poop hand almost every
single time.
Yeah.
Because you also can't copy your opponent's hand.
No.
It would stink.
And then you come in with throw up hand and everyone's just like, "Oh, too far."
Well, then it's like, well, if you can't copy then it's like, well, who gets to decide first?
You have to arm wrestle to decide who gets to decide first.
You have to rock, paper, scissors to decide.
Right.
How do you decide who gets the, you know, the poop hand and rock, paper, scissors?
Okay, you play rock, paper, poop hand.
And whoever gets poop hand wins or loses?
Yeah, rock, paper, poop hand.
Hold on, wait, wait, hold on, hold on, wait, wait, because you're trying to get your poop
hand ready.
You're trying to get it fully coated.
Keep your poop hand strong.
I was supposed to go to the Met today.
It ended up getting canceled.
Got ice cream instead.
You got canceled so you couldn't go to the Met?
Oh, I was in the fucking...
Who's Shawn Mendes?
Is that guy famous?
Yeah, that's a singer.
He was...
He was in Central Park all day, just like singing to like, doing like a rehearsal.
So I pretty much got the most amazing concert ever.
Wow.
Did you get to meet him?
Did you see Camilla Cabello there too?
He's married to Camilla Cabello?
I think he's dating her.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
I love her dad's hunting store.
Oh yeah.
He's insanely good at it.
Oh my god dude, we gotta make a run there.
Yeah.
Camilla Cabello's great hunt.
hunt tell you what that's a bell I bet she's got a Cabela's good a great you
got a great you know what hunt what hunt Camilla Cabela huh Camilla Cabela
Cinderella Amelia Bedelia use your words carefully Cinderella she's got a great
Cinderella now what what did you say what no say what you can say it about
the body part not about a woman's face that's like the whole rule I don't think
that's the yeah you can say it about you just can't call like Ellen that like
anything they call a girl's thing that what do you want me to say what do you
want me to say her thingy yeah you read me say that yeah she's got a great
thingy that's weird that's not weird you're supposed to say like yeah now
there's the one you say like oh she's got a fantastic area it's like what yeah
now it is everything's still PC they were they want to say yeah her her
thingy whatever is really good hmm yeah you're what they would they would yeah
the freaking PC culture wants to say her her hoo-ha makes me he happy yeah yeah
her joy box makes me laugh like a clown so I saw that I went hip-hip hooray see
that's what they're trying to censor guy talk now you can't say girl has a nice
pair of now now you have to say my weasel popped all around her mulberry
bush what the hell is that about yeah yeah it's fucked up yeah it's just I
I'd ring around her Rosie. That's what you have to say now. That's a bit you know
that's a song about the Black Plague. Yes. So can you like not talk about that?
It's a bit of a sore subject. Yeah. There's a there's a you can you just
remember the American heroes who died in the Black Plague? Yeah to stop the Black
Plague? There's a brewing company called Black Plague Brewing Company. Tell you
what I'm not gonna drink there. Yeah. Right? Isn't that a fight like? Tell you
here's a here's why I'd be afraid I would get the black plague mm-hmm and their
logo is a it's a what's the a nose big nose
big nose doctor no it's I know yeah no I know exactly what other jobs it does
guys have this is the pg-13 f yes right that's my bad I'm PG 13 yeah if you're
13 put down the iPod touch but yeah why would you like the black plague still
exists some places why would you name your brewing complex oh you drink this
shit you'll get the plague they should call it there should be an HIV
just a sickness just a disease. No they shouldn't. What am I even saying? It's the worst idea
of all time. There should be an HIV thrift store. There actually is. What? What's it
called? It's called, no it's called, oh it's called Out the Closet. That's what it's
called in LA. What? Yeah I have them here too. Really? Yeah. I see that. If I was a
gay guy with AIDS I'd see that and I'd say that's not cool man. Yeah. They have them
Ohio too. I went to one in Ohio. I would just feel like they were profiting off my
image. Yeah. Yeah, because you walk in there, it's just a normal thrift store.
Right. You can get AIDS tested there. I know. I told you guys about the time when
I was there and a guy came in and was like, "Where's the AIDS test?" I was
like trying to buy a shirt. I was like, "This is not a fun place to be." Yeah, and you said, "Right here,
buddy," and you pointed to your open mouth. Okay. Okay, you realize AIDS kills like
billions of people every day. But it keeps Magic Johnson alive every year. That's not
true. What? He's making things up. Magic Johnson. You were hoping it would power
you up like that. He's making it up. Yeah. You think Magic Johnson, the most pussy
getter of all time, would ever get AIDS? No, he's got... He uses his magic to keep it away.
He doesn't have magic, dude. This is the stupidest conversation I've ever had. Okay, you've seen him on the court, though.
The Comedy Central roasts paid him to pretend to have AIDS 15 years before they
started so that they could do awesome jokes about how his Johnson was magic in
2001. Right. So anyway. Which roast was he on? I don't think he was in any of the roasts.
Oh. So anyway Caleb was buying a trench coat and he said that about the AIDS test
because he wanted to become like Wesker from Resident Evil because he thought
that the T-virus was real. No. What's that T stand for? The virus. The AIDS.
That virus? The AIDS virus. That virus. Yeah. That boy got that virus. That boy got that
virus yeah and these I forgot about these shoes secondhand they're starting to
blow out in the back yeah I'm starting it I wish you would blow it in the back
that's right bumping mics he got mad at us for bumping mics on cuz you didn't do
it the right way it's like this we did do it we did do it the right way no it's
like this today we did it two days ago and we were before we were done with D&D
or during D&D we bumped mics and he said don't do that you know you shouldn't
- That's what I was telling you guys.
It damages the mics if you hit them into each other.
And the reason--
- You're just mad at what Jeffrey Ross said to you
at the roast.
- No, the reason that they bump mics on TV
is 'cause they're so rich
they can afford a new mic every night.
We can't, you know?
We just got our first new mic in two years, today.
- One year.
- Three years.
- That's right.
New business bank account.
- Things are looking up for us, man.
- Account number.
- Account number one.
- Two. - Two.
- Okay, we can't do it again. - Three.
- Three. - Three.
- All right, but we can't do another one.
- Four. - Don't, all right.
But don't say, we all know what it is,
don't say the next one. - Five.
- Are you serious?
Are you fucking serious? - Okay, stop.
Wait, seriously stop.
No, seriously stop.
- But we will say the routing number.
- Seriously stop.
- Nine. - Nine.
(laughing)
- Eight. - Eight.
- 10. - 10.
- Oh.
(laughing)
- Trying to throw him off.
- 11.
- Dude, if we get robbed for all we're worth,
I'm gonna fucking, whatever, it's insured.
It's like a bank robbery.
It doesn't matter.
Is that true?
You're free to rob us.
Wait, is that true?
Yeah.
You're allowed to rob us.
Whoa, dude, I think I might have a plan brewing.
It's all FDIC insured, dude.
God damn.
Fuck dick.
Fuck dick insured.
Mm-hmm.
That's what--
For dick.
I bet that's huge at the FDIC office.
Yeah.
What's this-- what do we work at?
Fuck dick?
Remember that production company?
They did like the--
Deek.
They did a bunch of like Inspector Gadget, Heathcliff.
Heathcliff.
Yeah.
They did Heathcliff.
Dude, I've been watching Mike Tyson videos.
Yeah.
Because he just is like, there's a YouTube wormhole you can get into that is just every time Mike Tyson has done an interview.
That dude is awesome.
Yeah.
I'll fuck you till you love me. He said a lot of really weird shit. FFFF. He said he was
gonna eat a guy's kids. Yeah. He's like I want your heart I want to eat your
children. Awesome. So cool. He said that he was like trying to talk like Muhammad
Ali but like the whole thing about Mike Tyson is he literally has like an 85 IQ.
Yeah he was like homeless and then he like fed pigeons. Yeah no he's like one
of the like stupidest people of all time. I don't think that's stupid.
To get a pigeon to trust you, you gotta be some kind of intelligent.
Yeah, but Muhammad Ali was like a genius and Mike Tyson is like
the stupidest guy of all time. He's like, "I'm gonna be like him." So he just tries to talk.
He tried to talk like him all the time. He would get confused and say things wrong.
And it was just so cool, man. And now I've been watching the videos of him recently where he says
he smokes like 10 pounds of weed a day and he's like,
There's a demon inside me. I used to be a demon. He wants to come out. I'm not gonna let him. It's so cool, man
He's like I want to hang out with him so bad. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, it's not gonna be happy
Yeah, I'm gonna he knows he's fucking stupid. That's his whole thing. I'm gonna go with this recording
I'm gonna show him I'm gonna say Mike. He said this about you. He did your voice. Yeah, I didn't I wasn't even doing his voice
Yeah, you were not dude. Please don't tell Mike Tyson that I don't telling him. He's like insanely strong. You know that please
I'm gonna show his tiger that could clip too. The tiger's gonna get mad at you.
He doesn't have the tiger anymore. Plus he had a TV show and
you're never gonna guest star. He told the story of why he had a tiger and
apparently he was trying to buy a car and the guy was like, the guy selling the
car was like, "Yeah, you know, like I think we'll have a new Maserati in in like a
a month. In the meantime, I have a bunch of tigers." And he wasn't even looking to buy
a tiger. Someone just was like, "Do you want a tiger?" And he was like, "Yeah."
That's sick.
That's so cool, man.
Yeah. I would not buy a tiger.
No?
Let me just put it out on the record. I would never.
I do not support that industry, so I would buy the tiger. I would throw it away.
I'd buy a tiger.
Because that's one less tiger on the market.
I would never buy a tiger.
- Hey, I'll say it, I'd buy a tiger.
Yeah, if I owned a zoo.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- Yeah, if I owned a zoo, I'd buy a tiger.
And guess what?
Put the tiger in the zoo.
All of a sudden, I'm a millionaire.
What do I do with the million dollars?
A million more tigers.
- I pay to keep the tigers sick.
- Yeah, that's right.
Keep 'em, dude, there is a horrible zoo.
- That is what they do at the zoo.
- Bro, when you guys come to North Carolina,
which by the way, boys trip, coming up.
prepared pack your trunks remind me about remind me about trunks after I'm done
okay yeah mm-hmm tree gimbal animal park Wilmington NC the most fucked up demonic
zoo of all time all the animals want to kill themselves they're like literally
you see it's every zoo though no but dude this one is like there's a protest in
front of it every single day shit and ever and like they've been trying to shut
it down for years I don't know if I want to go to this you have to go I would
love to go chimps are like crossing their days on like the side of the walls
and shit it's horrible they have all these they like alligators with no legs
it's they have at least souvenirs they have one of those those crank machines
where you put in 51 cents look yes they do when it gives you a penny with a sad
monkey on it oh okay well you know as long as I mean I'll go see like a like
an otter get hit with a cattle prod as long as I get to buy a shirt yeah I don't
even they don't even turn on the cattle prod you know row it out yeah javelin
You know what the great thing about when liberals protest the damn zoo is is that's free food for the animals. Mm-hmm. That's right
That's right. And you know what some of the some of the employees have to wrangle them back in that's right
Those Dan's animals those liberals. It's been oh my god. Don't even get me started
Yeah, somebody out there with a big net and catches speaking of trunks. All these women are so hairy
And there's the best thing about going to the gym regularly is there's a beautiful cast of characters, uh-huh
Yeah, of course. New favorite, okay? Okay. Mr. Trunks. Really young, like mid-20s
Indian dude. Walks in, he goes every single day, white polo shirt, swim trunks
that have a picture of the beach on them, picks up a one-pound dumbbell and does
this. While he's on the phone the entire time. He's moving his arm left to right. He moves his arm left to
- Right, and then he goes to-- - Same arm?
- One arm, and then he goes over to a,
he mostly just walks around,
and then he wipes stuff down that he didn't use.
(laughing)
And then he goes over to the cable pull machine,
and just goes like,
(laughing)
like, really the smallest movement I've ever seen.
- He's just inspecting it.
- He might be, dude. - Yeah, that's the inspector.
- He works there.
- He does feel like, it does feel like
I'm an undercover boss when he's there.
- Yeah. - Yeah, I'm like,
this guy, this guy, I mean, I just wanna,
I want so badly to just like,
and everybody in the gym, when he walks by,
just like watches him because he's so entertaining to watch. He's like walking
up to like fucking like the squat rack and like he'll I saw him do this the other
day instead of squatting the bar he walked up to one side of it and held it
like this and just
it's it's exactly how does he like ripped no he's in like horrible shape yeah yeah
yeah does he look like he's like probably five five and like a hundred and
50 pounds of just like pure just pudge.
Yeah.
And he just walks around in the same swim trunks every single time.
A polo shirt.
I wish that was me.
That's sick.
Dude, he's like completely alpha-dogging everybody there.
I don't know if this is a thing that people actually do, so you know, you can make fun
of me if it is, but I saw a guy at the gym running backwards on the treadmill a few,
like a week ago.
Damn.
Yeah.
He's getting ready for that.
Really fast.
Was he in good shape?
Yeah.
No, it was crazy.
If someone's in good shape, you just assume.
to like, yeah, he was, well, he was like sprinting on it forward for like a really long time and
then he turned around and was running backwards.
He's like, "Come on, man, like, you see me right here."
Yeah.
That's what I hate about the gym is all the damn showboats.
Yeah, wait until I leave to do that.
The best guy that I have at my gym besides that dude is like the biggest guy there.
Huge like, like Bose over the ear headphones.
That's right.
That is a mirror.
Getting huge.
Big over the ear headphones.
Fuck.
Sits there.
That backfired.
Eminem songs while like these listen to while he works out sick he's like sitting
there curling and he's like everybody's just trying to like work out it's so I
have a gym membership that I have not canceled for it's got to be about four
years now to wear planet yeah yeah PF I have the gap the of the the membership
that lets you use the, it's like a waterbed thing
that like massages your back.
- That's gotta be expensive.
- Yeah, dude, it's like 21 bucks a month.
- What, for four years?
- Yeah, I just forgot to-- - What the fuck
is wrong with you, man?
- I forgot to shut it off.
- You, this is the worst part.
You've told me about that probably three times
in the past year, and not once did you say,
"I'm gonna log on to PF."
- You can just do that?
I thought you had to cancel it in person.
- Still!
- Who cares, you live--
- I thought you had to cancel it--
- You live six blocks away from one.
- I thought you had to cancel it at the one
that you got the membership in.
- No, why would you assume that?
- Someone told me that.
- That's the craziest thing I've ever heard.
- You never tried?
You were just like, oh well, okay.
I figured I'd go to the gym at some point.
- I'd rather pay $300.
- You could also go on your credit card
and flag that as like, I don't wanna pay this,
and they'll just decline it,
and then they will cancel your membership.
- Yeah, I could do that.
But what if I wanna go use the massage jet?
- That's actually a really strong point.
that's actually an insanely good point. Yeah. Yeah, I guess that's true.
You know what, you guys could use my membership too.
You guys could... I can't use your membership. What are you talking about?
You can put on a wig. I already have a gym membership.
You can put on a wig, put on my face.
They have a photo of me in it.
Look me in the eyes and tell me exactly how you think I could put your face on me.
Mask.
You want me to pay to have a custom Patrick mask made?
No reason why.
You want me to put it on my face like Mission Impossible 2 and you want me to walk into
a Planet Fitness and say, "Can I have a glass of water, dude?"
You want me to do that?
Yeah.
You would get a massage out of it.
It would be really awkward when they threw you a party.
They're like, "You're the guy who's paid the longest and come the least."
Yeah, he set a record like Google's one billion search.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like confetti falls from the ceiling.
They're like, "Yeah."
Like people had bets on whether you would ever show up or not.
We all thought you were dead, man.
like oh this guy this guy was saying your first visit would be 10 years in but if
you could go use you get a massage out of this I don't care about massages dude
well massages are evil that's why you're so to miss every other person who goes
and gets a massage the person touches their butthole I don't want that smoke
where your bottle in between your cheek yeah on your butthole you're fucking like
- Like the--
- Where is this massage place
where people are getting their buttholes touched?
- Around.
- Dr. Butts?
In this neighborhood?
- Yeah.
- What street?
- They're around.
- I don't think this is true.
- It's true, man.
People get--
- And you don't have like a phone number for it?
- Yeah, I do.
It's my phone number.
If you want me to touch your butthole, man,
just be a man about it.
Just ask me.
I'll do the Kim Possible the
If you want to beat me yeah, I want to beep her what I want to beep hell no
What's up? That's a teenage girl. No, that's the whole thing about her
She's 21 years old she's not
She goes to prom call me a beat me if you want to reach me. Yeah, I want to beep you Kim possible. What's good?
Stop that's a child. I'm gonna be it's not a child. He's cartoon. She's 21 years old
Like 21 Jump Street, she's a spy she's in she's undercover man. No dude. She's
16 call me beep me
beep me Caleb call me and beep me
(laughing)
I'm on it.
- Yeah, dude, you're the naked mole rat.
You look like that.
- Nah, dude.
- You look like that.
- Oh, true.
- I'm Ron Pussible.
- God damn it, dude.
- I'm Ron Pussible when I'm in that.
Bang.
(laughing)
(laughter)
- She Go crazy.
- What's the bad guy's name, Mojo Jojo?
- Mojo Jojo, what?
- It's She Go.
- No, She Go is the girl, the green girl.
And then her dad is the blue monkey.
- There's a blue monkey, I never watched that show.
- And She Go is part monkey.
- She Go's part monkey?
I have to erase some searches for my circuitry.
Yeah, I went part monkey on her, though. Yeah, I went Charla Nash. I went Charla Nash on the pussy.
That's right. You know what it do.
Alright, so I um
Today we're doing weekend update. Okay, what? Yep. I brought some he has a Mario Party minigame for us
I brought some headlines from
Some headlines that have been ripped doing the headline. Did we decide we're gonna write new jokes for it
You guys are gonna you guys are gonna riff on me. Oh, all right
Christian Charleston just requested $10 for me co-pay for MRI parentheses will increase amount if tumor positive
Do you think that's a scam?
No earthly clue and then I immediately got a text from my mom which is scary will
Let's see is this a real guy
This is probably just a good. I guess everyone in the world has my phone number. I should expect things like that
Yeah, well Charles
Kudos to you and well done
It's pretty good, man
All right
So I yeah, I
I got these headlines from one of my favorite news sources,
which is fascinatingthings.net.
(laughing)
- Okay, that's good news.
- So these are big in the news lately,
and I want you guys to kind of just riff on them
politically, like we can update,
'cause it is the weekend when this comes out.
- The hardest part about this is,
this is not like a video episode.
- Right, if you guys are doing any mugging or anything.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Well, that's okay.
like i mean if you guys are going to do great if we're doing joe's rules then
like you're not going to see my funny face a big part of my delivery is my
eyes
yeah he's making a face like he just ate a warhead
yeah all right okay i have a bunch of headlines here from fascinating things
dot net okay so we're going to kind of workshop some jokes for these yeah or
you know if you could just say a joke instantly and not waste my time that
would be good let me go first okay
Alright, the first headline here is, "This bear lost all her fur after being used in a
circus for 20 years."
Yeah, and that bear is not fur sale no more.
Oh, there's the face.
Oh, there's the eyes.
Yeah, you have to wait for the eyes for the pop.
Yeah.
Okay, good morning.
I mean, good evening.
Good morning.
morning good morning there
but you gotta you gotta get a new bears name Oh Hillary Clinton you could do
like the Bears name like Caleb Pitts - maybe yeah that could be what well if
you are all your fur said her yeah yeah I'm doing like a Dennis Miller thing and
yeah the bear is yet the bear is Hillary Clinton after meeting up with Nabokov
and Herman Melville at the Benghazi Convention.
- The Benghazi Convention,
that's actually a really good idea.
- Yeah.
- I honestly think that she probably
was responsible for all that.
- Yeah, she was solely responsible.
She was the person who went there
and killed all those guys.
- Yeah, I think if I remember correctly,
she accidentally dropped a big turd out of a plane.
- From her butt.
- And it collateraled all six of them, like in Halo.
- Yeah.
All right, you want this one?
Here.
OK, I guess.
Here's the second headline.
Take a look to a Canadian moose refreshing
in an inflatable pool.
That moose's name is Hillary Clinton.
That's pretty good.
That sucked.
No, that was pretty-- OK, you do one then.
You do a better one.
Well--
Here, I'll say the headline again for you.
What's funny?
Take a look to a Canadian moose refreshing
in an inflatable pool.
That moose's name, Hillary Clinton.
Fuck dude, this is so hard.
Yeah.
Wait, wait, say it again.
Take a look to a Canadian moose refreshing in an inflatable pool.
He's just making a face.
No.
That's all he's doing is making a face.
I don't know.
Let's do an Mr. Bean thing.
Well, maybe we should have just done a Mr. Bean thing instead of a Weekend Update thing.
Oh, he's pretending to drink! Oh my god!
Oh, he doesn't like the tea! Oh, he's pretending it's his wiener!
Oh my god!
Minion he turned into.
Well, you have to... I'm trying to get a laugh here, okay? Alright, here, try this one.
Give me the worst shit in the world. Give me a good one.
between a cow and a goat that hides in fear of humans they also found a hybrid
between a gay guy and a car it's called a Prius that was pretty good it's pretty
good that was not bad it worked yeah I wouldn't actually I'm gonna write that
down what's next a hybrid of
friggin sucky shit all right here get this one this is comedy gold right here
okay you guys hop right on this one I mean once you hear it you mean just
throw a punch line out immediately okay
lost dog daily gets on the bus looking for his owner his watery eyes cry out
for help what is this Futurama come on there's a lost dog paddywhack give the
dog a bone I think this dog is riding the bus home there's a lost dog in the
back of the bus alone, I think he might be taking it home.
Try this one out, okay? Okay.
Faithful puppy cannot bear sadness and crosses the rainbow
15 minutes after his owner dies.
(laughter)
It's weakening up. You're not supposed to pause that long.
That is one hungry dog.
(laughing)
- He's after, fuck.
He's after the Lucky Charms.
'Cause he's hungry.
You could've put that in there.
- You don't get to try to add to my joke, man.
I'm like fucking--
- I thought we were riffing together.
I thought we were fucking--
- No, we're battling like Tina Fey
and fucking yellow hair.
We're battling.
- No, they uplifted each other
- It was a battle. - The power of femininity.
- But we're two guys and we hate each other
so much on the show, so.
- What?
- This is the Weekend Update life
and you're basically about to get fired by me.
- Ah, shit.
- I'm the head writer.
- I think maybe I should come in
and do a character for the Weekend Update.
- I can do anything I want to.
- I think I'm a desk piece guy.
I don't think I'm a host.
- You're being a baby right now.
- You're a hot piece at my desk.
Now sit down and shut up and look pretty.
All right, 'cause I'm doing work.
- All right, here.
- Yeah, this one's a change of pace here.
I know the last one was kind of heavy, so.
- I'm not trying to goose you.
- I'm Caleb's secretary and he's trying to goose me.
- I'm trying to find your gander here.
- This one, I think this is nice.
A duck and a monkey proved their loyalty to the death,
leaving millions heartbroken.
- I don't even, they were in love?
- No, they fought to the death.
- Oh, they fought to the death.
All right, well, my bananas
are on the monkey.
Okay, maybe we give these weekend update guys a hard time.
They have a difficult job. I mean, they're pulling their stories from the
source fascinating news.com yeah fascinating things dot net things dot
net oh fuck how is your version these guys are these guys are quackers that's
pretty good hey I could see Josie saying that yeah
justy yeah just alone oh fuck could you imagine that crap hold up let me get up
with maybe let me pull out my Photoshop real quick cuz that would make me go
nuts yeah this one gets a little political so I'm sorry but sweet dog
with a heart-shaped nose that catches everyone's attention with its sweetness
yeah and and liberals want to abort him that's right
yep yeah I'm my favorite Nirvana song there's a dog with a heart-shaped nose
and he's sweet like a rose like a rose what do you think that was good that
gonna be good for like a maybe if he maybe a Kurt Cobain wrote about dogs and
with heart-shaped noses yeah they could do this story and we can update and then
have like that's the thing if Kena Thompson playing Kurt Cobain didn't
insist on writing all his songs about fucking snakes and spiders maybe he'd be
still alive still yeah yeah there's an idea
Madonna that whores been singing about fucking bikinis and the beach for 45
years and she won't fucking die no matter how many times my dad tries so
well yeah speaking of that here's the next one um the miraculous
transformation of the pregnant dog after it came back from the dead 17 times oh
yeah what is this the freaking octo mom come on now yeah come on now it's the
dog go mom yeah what is this the dog octo mom eight babies coming out of its
dog pussy yeah what's this the stinky pussy dog pussy with stinky little dog
babies just shooting out of a pussy like a cannon yeah just plopping out like
evil Knievel is fucking what's this the stink pussy dog let's taste your pussy
see if it stinks this is the stinky pussy dog and I'm gonna eat that pussy why
you're not doing a joke for weekend update me why you can't get mad at me
that's true that's a good point the fucking the guys on weekend up yeah no
no you wait no you went mad TV every week no I did not go mad TV every week
they do a weekend update and one of them says some joke about 9/11 yeah and they
have to apologize right to Pete Davidson to Pete Davidson is right next to them
yeah right he's under the desk he's under the desk he's servicing God knows
what yep heroin probably yeah yeah yeah I mean his second favorite needle after
the damn tattoo needle am i right yep you can say that again
second favorite needle after the damn tattoo needle this guy got so many
tattoos he's getting them all move - it's like what do you think that what do
you think the tattoo needle is a heroin needle or something? He might be so
stupid that he thinks that actually he sees black tar heroin he hears that he
sees the little black ink in the in the tattoo needle he says well that's got to
be that thing yeah he takes he says this actually hurts instead of feels like
amazing good this hurts and it draws a picture this is even better than heroin
it's actually a really strong point by us do you have another all right yeah I
I was the last one so you guys have to make this one count
His name is Frederick the great and he is the most handsome horse in the world
Yeah, and I fucked him
except for
Tom Hanks the horse
Who's a handsome guy
Brad Pitt the horse
Adrian Brody the horse. Adrian Brody looks like shit. Looks like a damn plague doctor.
You can't say that about him. What?
He's a proud Jamaican man. That's true. I forget that.
Proud white Jamaican. Yeah, like snow. Yeah.
Infarmer.
Snow.
Is Snow the Canadian rapper? Yeah. Okay. Yeah.
- Oh.
- So who do you guys think won Weekend Update?
- I think I gave up pretty quick.
- I think Caleb won.
- I'm sorry that I have a perfect brain
for writing jokes in fortune cookies.
- Well you guys, hey, you listeners, comment below.
Comment who won.
- Yeah, see who won.
- Just like on SNL.
- Can we do a fortune cookie context now?
Context?
- Yeah, be careful with the accent you choose.
- That's a really good fortune cookie.
(laughing)
careful with the accent you choose.
- That is like perfect, yeah.
- Yeah.
There's always a little bit more soda in the can.
Don't you guys feel like that's true?
Every time you think you're done with the soda,
you pick up the soda can, you shake it around.
You hear, what's this, a rain stick?
Did I get a rain stick installed in my--
- Yeah, and then you go to Tricky,
you go, oh, it's the tab, and I was shredding my throat.
- I had a Dr. Pepper for the first time in a while today.
I've been obsessed with that DC guy video.
Yeah?
The guy's like, "As soon as you start your day with a DC,
"it's all downhill from there."
I mean, come on, it's a fucking DC.
I've never seen it.
You've never seen that?
No. Dude, it's so good.
It's a guy with no chin, sitting in his car,
drinking a Diet Coke, and just talking about
how awesome a Diet Coke is, it calls it a DC.
It's really good.
You had a Dr. Pepper though, I'm sorry to interrupt.
Yeah, well, Dr. Pepper, it's really good.
You know that motherfucker got 23 flavors in it?
- It's also got some ingredient called,
it starts with a P-H.
- Fentanyl.
- Fent, final nucleides or something.
- No shot.
They got nucleides in that?
- Phyto, is that what gives it its flavor?
- Final nucleus.
- They have the final nucleus in that?
- Favorite flavor?
Is it pepper?
- I think that could be.
- Flavor bubble?
- I never thought I would like a pepper flavored soda water.
but damn if Dr. Pepper doesn't hit the spot.
- It's true.
- I never thought I'd like a drink in a cold can,
but oh, what the hell.
- You know what, it does taste better in a can.
- What the fuck are you talking about?
- Dr. Pepper tastes better in a can.
I got it in a plastic bottle.
- I can not believe what you're saying.
- That's a good fortune cookie.
If it was in a fortune cookie flavored soda can.
- They should just do like the--
- Fortune cookie flavored soda,
and it's got a fortune in it.
- Holy shit, dude.
- Why is there not fortune cookie flavored shit?
- That makes no, you're right,
'cause fortune cookie's like vanilla and lemon, right?
Vanilla, lemon, soda would be so good.
- Yeah, well they have that.
- But they don't call it fortune cookie soda.
- Great, just ruin everything for me, all the time.
Just fucking destroy every idea I have.
You say, they already exist.
I said, what about shoes that make you jump?
- This would also, also, if we have,
say we have fortune cookie flavored soda,
they print the fortune on the inside of the can,
People are gonna stop throwing their cans out.
They're gonna save them to look at the fortunes.
And finally, these freaking homeless guys
will stay out of the grocery store.
- That's right.
- Get out!
That machine's not yours.
You're too close to the red box.
- Fortune cookie soda.
- You have to leave.
- The only soda.
- You're stinking up the produce.
- The only soda that keeps the homeless people out of the store.
- I put my apples in that plastic bag.
I see a green cloud when I tie the plastic bag closed inside there.
Come on man, I gotta eat those later!
That's right.
What the fuck's going on bro?
I would do anything to be able to eat an apple.
Yeah, you should try being a homeless freak piece of shit.
At least dress like Aladdin.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think that'll solve the homeless problem.
If we put them all in suits and like costumes and put them in Times Square and you can take
a photo with them.
Here's my thing, if you're homeless, right?
Okay, you're homeless.
What do most of these homeless guys do?
out with a bunch of other homeless guys. Listen buddy, your network is your net
worth. Yeah. If you're homeless you need to be hanging out with CEOs. Yep. And
richest, rich hot girls. Yeah. And then maybe, just maybe, if you work, play your cards
right, one of them will give you a job. We dress up a bunch of homeless guys like
priests and the Pope and we throw them in Dimesquare and then they hang out
with all these rich Red Scare girls and... Who all day hang out in Timesquare.
Dime Square.
What's that?
This guy's in another world though.
Yeah, I don't know what this means.
We don't have any.
He's in this weird world where that is a place.
It's a place.
Tell you what's a real place.
Citi Field.
Mets play there.
You know that?
Oh wait, we could dress them all up like Mr. Met and then it's like Mr. Met's like, we
have like a big like family, Mr. Met family reunion.
It would ruin the costumes.
Fuck, you're right.
Okay, well we dress them up.
They stink it up, smell like a fucking Nintendo cartridge.
- During the seventh inning, during the seventh inning stretch,
we put them all in chains and put them out in the field
and make them fight.
- You got a seven in you stretched.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
- I got seven in me?
- You put a seven in you and stretched you.
- Yeah.
What stretches?
- I don't know.
(laughing)
I don't know.
- You tell me.
- Could be any part of your body, buddy.
I don't know, you tell me.
- I'm just a little girl.
- Wait, what? - You're a little girl?
- What?
- Just run that shit back.
Run that shit back.
What did you just say?
- I'm a little boy.
I don't-- - No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- I just played the hate back.
- That's not what you said.
That's not what you, stop reversing.
Stop reversing. - I'm a normal guy.
I'm a normal guy.
- Oh, he's stuck.
- Oh, shit. - I'm a normal guy.
I'm a normal guy.
- How do we fix him?
- I'm a little girl.
- What?
(imitates a guitar)
DJ Funk Flex.
- Do you remember the
- I still have my headphones on.
- DaBaby's, I was talking about this the other day,
DaBaby's, during his rant where it's like,
you're not sucking dick in the parking lot,
put your phone up,
- Yeah.
- And that, what are you saying,
like something like,
oh, you're not getting AIDS or whatever.
As soon as he says AIDS,
- Well, I mean, he doesn't--
- The DJ does a drop that's like,
(imitates gunshot)
(laughter)
- Gunshot, yeah.
- Two gunshots, then he says,
these people don't know!
I don't know man.
I mean he does.
It's so good.
He doesn't, it's not that he's homophobic.
He really and this is, it's admirable.
He respects the sanctity of a parking lot.
I don't want to walk out there and see, you know, I have no problem with them but I don't
want to see a demon or devil doing its business out there.
I don't want to go out there and see, you know, whatever it is, a man tricking another
man.
I don't want to see that when I'm walking out of the parking lot, you know.
And that's fine.
And it's nothing, it's just not, don't do it in the parking lot.
Yeah, if you want to punch your ticket to hell in the sanctity of your own cave, do that,
but not in the parking lot.
Hey, how about you do it at freaking Whole Foods or at a liberal shop?
Yeah, Whole Foods, because a lot of these liberal things think eating a whole is food
to them.
Yeah, absolutely.
Because they're so gay.
And they don't even eat steak.
They don't eat steak.
And they don't even eat a whole steak.
- They don't even eat a whole steak.
- They think chicken is a cow, basically.
- They think chicken is a cow,
and that salmon is real food, which it's not.
- They think a Beyond Burger,
yeah, it's gonna send you beyond heaven,
past it, back all the way around to hell,
where you'll probably live forever.
- Absolutely.
- Yeah.
- Oh, and the Impossible Burger?
It's impossible for you to get into heaven
after you eat that.
It's red, but it never died.
If something is red and never died,
that is one of the most evil things of all time.
You know what else is red?
- You know what's living inside your belly.
- What else is red?
- The demons, baby.
- The magma in the heart, the hoary depths of hell,
where the devil lives and he pokes you.
- That's right, tell 'em.
And you know what?
These people, they're eating soy products.
Well, guess what?
Yo soy devil, and I'm--
- Mm-hmm, talk that talk.
- Welcome you into El Hel.
- That's right, yeah.
- Yes, sir.
- You're eating kale.
You going to hell, boy.
You'll be going straight to hell.
You'll be killed.
And go to hell.
Oh, you like Swiss chard?
You're gonna be charred and burned to death by the way.
Just like the Swiss.
And your Swiss dog.
Already going to hell.
That's right.
You're gonna get killed by the volcano in hell.
Yeah.
Yeah, 'cause your flag's a cross.
Yeah, you're taking a ginger shot.
Hey, I got a thing.
Your things are shot.
That's right.
I'm gonna shoot your thing.
hell will see thee pretty soon.
(laughing)
God dammit dude.
That was...
You're talking about food.
I don't think that. I just thought it was a funny rhyme.
I don't think that though.
You're talking about food though. You're supposed to talk about food.
Alright, how about just bee though.
The bees are going to hell.
Yes. Anyone else?
You will be...
Tortured eternally.
You will be in hell very soon.
Yeah, okay. Well, there's eight set seven seconds six seconds five seconds
This is the Patriots right to the twitch and your site. Alright, bye everybody