Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
- Premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Oh!
- That's the sound I made earlier when I hurt my back
and none of you called me.
- You didn't tell us that you hurt your back.
- He did tell us actually, I just didn't.
- I can barely get a full breath in.
- You didn't tell us until it happened
and we were all busy.
- I didn't tell him until it happened.
I didn't say before it happened that I hurt my back.
That is a fucking amazing point.
You should have told me.
That is an amazing point.
You should have told me before I'm going to hurt my back today.
I would not know whether to tell you that or not.
Okay, I'm going to hurt my back tomorrow.
I'm just going to start telling you that every day.
I'm going to pass away.
Don't joke about that.
Yeah, that's not funny.
I'm going to pass away tonight.
That's funny.
Cooper just, Dio just died.
Yeah, a famous TikToker just died and we're kind of broken up about it.
apparently and I read this and I read this I'm and I this is breaking news
about this tick-tock my god he will apparently never be forgotten they're
not going to forget him that was not going to forget that Cooper do you
something I think it's Cooper Dio Cooper Cooper rodeo Cooper the name like rodeo
what do you folks Cooper he's they're not gonna forget him listen you will
live on in the hearts of his family, friends and fans. Nobody
will forget him. There's videos of him a winking to an a con
sign his family. I won't forget him. It was that you see I
didn't see I saw a picture of him. I like the Twitter
trending tab and I clicked on it and like it was like
somebody posted like his last his last tick tock video that he
posted was like damn you ever feel like you be dying young and
shit. You ever feel like you're about to die young and then he
it or let me read what it was. It was so funny. I thought that I was going to die
wasn't a suicide. I hope I when I hope that nobody forgets about this guy.
Yep, when I picked up the heavy box today that I picked up and I hurt my
back. I thought that I was going to die young. I was like this is the moment.
Yeah, dude is a box of t-shirts. I went to the I went to the post office. I
received two packages who else be thinking they gun die young af and then
emoji with the sweat drop oh that's the
funniest part of the whole thing that's
the only funny part of it the rest of it
is touching and that is crazy though
it's so brutal when somebody actually
it's absolutely brutal when a tick-tocker
leaves this mortal coil it's honestly
horrible when somebody moves on to the
other world fuck shit now I'm next thing
I was trying to make light of it but now
I'm kind of pensive we should deliver a
or a flag to his house. Yeah, a folded triangle flag. Yeah, I we should hold a
funeral for him here right now.
Let's go for yeah dial up his we have gathered here dearly beloved. How do you
start a funeral? I know to start a a well dearly beloved hello.
Hello,
so it was telling me so it was telling me yesterday about this video of trump
where he's at somebody's getting married at Mar-a-Lago and like he walks by and
he walks into the wedding and he like grabs a microphone and he just he's
like the beautiful couple. They look so happy. What we're doing with China is
absolutely terrible in the middle of their wedding. It's so funny. That's so
sick. Did you did you guys see somebody posted? He was the first guy. You know
how people online will say like we do a little trolling or we do a little
something. He was the guy who said that first. What did you say? He said we do a
little trolling. Wow. Yeah, that's where it came from. Yeah, I didn't know that.
Yeah, you know, he also invented saying you're fired. Just like that. He said
Felicia hired he did that first he didn't do by Felicia did by Felicia
fires fired by the 90s yeah you're canceled listen you're canceled sister
yeah you're canceled sis not and so not my hair waving in the wind not my orange
ass with my go fee fee haircut it's coffee to haircut he doesn't look good I
could go for a bowl of coffee for you guys right here something I came up with
with to be able to drive over here right then when my back was hurting so bad?
Yeah.
I'm not yeller. No, fuck it.
You don't say it now.
I'm not yellow. I'm Homer.
I don't get it at all.
I'm not black. I'm OJ.
What?
You never heard OJ say that?
I thought that was supposed to mean...
I don't listen to a word that that scoundrel says.
Yeah.
Scoundrel's a little heavy of a word for OJ Simpson.
Yeah, I think you need to dial it back.
In what way is he a fucking scoundrel?
innocent proven innocent by a court of law I thought that that was supposed he was
driving way under the speed limit first of all and you don't need a court to
tell you that you can see a plain as day second of all tailgating on the fucking
highway yeah second of all Jamuk he totally I don't feel like you can say
why second time he's got Matt Jamuk that's what Hulk Hogan was saying yeah
Hulk Hogan was also saying a very good point yeah second of all he acted too
funny in the naked gun uh-huh yep that's why Kareem Abdul-Jabbar is fine cuz he
confused me by being funny in the naked gun then I see him on TV and it's not a
laughing matter anymore I see him and he's a different guy he's completely
playing him yep and how violent TV what kind of violent menace actually plays
professional NFL football the most violent sport this guy's a fucking
violent maniac okay I didn't say a violent maniac I think it was down girl
I think that that's that's fine for me. I thought I'm not yellow, I'm Homer is supposed to be a play on I'm not little, I'm fun size.
You ever heard story OJ by Jay Z too? No.
The chorus is I'm not black, I'm OJ. He goes okay. So he could go I'm not yellow, I'm Homer,
okurr. Something like that. That sounds good. Yeah. Oh me and Matt, me and my uncle Matt came
up with another joke. What was it? Okay. This is gonna, this is a bit of a thinker, okay? Okay,
I'm ready to think. There's a thinker. I'm ready to think. Me and Matt, we collaborated on a haunted
joke let me think oh well wait hold on okay don't tell it yeah don't tell you
we go outside tell us spirits it's the joke is a hon it's about fucking haunted
shit okay so it's a it's a joke on a joke of I don't know if it makes any sense I
will see just say something about haunted life jackets that are so
foreboding oh I just got it it's pretty good right yeah that's pretty good Matt
collabed on that yeah yeah cuz they're so scary
because of the good haunted lights orbit foreboding or boat and but it's also so
- It's scary. - Yeah, it's foreboding.
- Yeah, they're foreboding. - Yeah, it's scary.
- I don't get it. - Yeah, it's foreboding
'cause it's scary. - Yeah.
- And it's so haunted. - 'Cause you also use it on a boat.
- Yeah, 'cause it's like a ghost ship.
Yeah, it's foreboding. - Yeah.
- It's haunted. - Well, it's, okay.
There's something about a ghost ship--
- It's like you don't wanna go near it.
- There's something about a ghost ship
that's so hauntingly beautiful.
(laughing)
- I don't think I agree with you.
- There's something about a haunted painting
that's so hauntingly beautiful.
- Depends on the painting.
There's something so haunted.
There's something about a zombie Mona Lisa that's so decomposingly gorgeous.
Oh my god, dude.
A zombie Mona Lisa would go so fucking hard in 2009.
You could get that in a museum for sure.
I think you could get, I'll say, I think you could get any Mona Lisa in a museum.
Nope.
I think that's where they belong.
Listen, listen.
I'm not gonna, listen.
I don't wanna, again, I don't wanna get political.
I don't wanna get divisive about society and about men and women.
Don't even get me started.
Mona Lisa was a man she would not be in the museum.
- You're right, she'd be the president.
Woo hoo!
(laughing)
- Yes!
- Yay!
- You think that you could get any Mona Lisa
into a museum, but trust me, it's hard.
- It's hard as fuck.
- I have a lot of Mona Lisas I've done Photoshop to.
- And it's a hell of a lot harder to get them out.
- They don't go in the museum.
- Well, you know the Mona Lisa that's in the museum,
that's like probably the 200th or 300th Mona Lisa.
- I made her--
- The Mr. Bean Mona Lisa was before that one.
I put I made Mona Lisa Latina. I made her do a duck face selfie. I made her do I
mean there's one of her and it's modern. Don't tell me that. And this is you ever
do a Darth Vader mask? Yep none of them in the MoMA. Yeah. No museum is touching
these things. They're going in my MoMA's house. It was my drawing and she puts
them all on the fridge. The gift shops. Yeah they go well that does that barely
accounts of being in a museum though. I think I might open up the Museum of
Mona Lisa. And then maybe all these Mona Lisa, all these different Mona
Lisas that aren't making it to the museums could find a home, a forever home.
I know that you can't say publicly that you're gonna like assassinate somebody
or do something. Going to assassinate Mona Lisa. I'm going to smear cream on Mona Lisa.
Can't you publicly say like I'm going to steal the Mona Lisa? Yeah. You can say that and you won't get in trouble.
you won't you can say you can say all of that stuff unless it's about a specific
person we were talking these days the employees at the Louvre there said it's
if somebody tries to steal the Mona Lisa they're not supposed to stop them really
just let them go yeah because it's insured yeah I mean look at last week
somebody I haven't looked up this store I would like to get it get a quick update
on the Mona Lisa cream stir that cream stir that's what I'm calling I'm what's
that's what I'm calling him. Somebody cream pied the Mona Lisa, so they cream
of a man cremulated that's a lucky man. Let me see if I can order to
eventually by the Mona Lisa, the real Mona Lisa yeah. Why do you think how do
you think she stood so damn still she's so full of fucking come glue. No well
come yeah she's glued to her her chair with come. I was trying to see like I
want to know if like this guy went to jail or something the first
36 year old man disguised as an elderly woman in a wheelchair tried to smear a
cake-like substance on the Mona Lisa on Sunday in an apparent climate-related
protest at the Louvre in Paris. He has since been referred to a police
psychiatric unit. Whoa, they have police psychiatric units?
A joker interrogated him. Why'd you do it? Why'd you smear the Mona Lisa in cream?
I found a video here I looked up Mona Lisa. Wait, this isn't our suspect. This is just an old woman.
I don't know if this is similar. I looked up Mona Lisa cream pie and I saw a video
Mona Lisa gets all three holes filled. Holy shit. Oh my god. Did you guys know
Mona Lisa has actually been attacked several times not just by cream. Really?
What's one of the other horrifying incidents? 1956 two separate incidents in
1956 Holy Shit Acid Whoa that's way more more than cream and a rock a whole
rock a rock a rock
is
a plan. You're like I'm going to van vandalize the Mona Lisa this year. I'm
going to I'm going to do it. Here's my plan. I'm going to hit it with a rock
and then the right before you do it. Some God throws
throw the rock. The rock's already in my hand. I already have. I already bought the rock.
You could also play that off as like, look I slipped I was trying to throw a rock at
the guy throwing the acid. I was playing rock and I missed. The goal. 2009 the Mona Lisa
was attacked with a ceramic cup. Whoa. Attacked is a strong word. It says attacked. You can't
can attack as a woman attacked it with the ceramic cup. She did she was not
doing that. I do think when I was at a museum, I was at the gardener when we
were in Boston and I you can just touch paintings. You're not supposed to. You
can't yeah, they'll walk over but like they want you to touch him like there's
not you get oils from your fingers could degrade to but like why would you not
put every painting in a with a yeah, why is it only like the Mona Lisa just put
it in like a giant black box? Yeah, I don't you shouldn't be able to get so
close to them. That's what I think that hey, that's just Caleb's two cents in
Caleb's corner of this week. He then proceeds to smear cream on the glass and
throws roses everywhere before being tackled by security on the class. He
threw roses. This guy should be in jail. I'm obsessed with this guy. Someone
smashed a cake on Mona Lisa.
And that's not as good as smeared cream. This guy's is an elderly woman. I
smeared cream
left unharmed but smeared in cream.
(laughing)
- I'm also seeing here,
she also, she gets all three of her holes filled.
- We, with cream?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, we already talked about that.
He creamed her.
- It looks like she's gonna have
a difficult time walking after this.
- Oh really?
You know, I think that's a myth.
I don't think any women have had sex
so good that they can't walk.
- They probably already couldn't walk.
- Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, maybe you pulled a muscle, but it wasn't any wasn't the guy's fault. I
know that much. Yeah, I don't think any man has ever done that. No, nobody and
also nobody has a big a big penis either. No, nobody has and if they do they
should be in the circus. Yeah, you're a freak. You basically are close to close
to an elephant than a human. Okay, I promise this is the last one I'm gonna
read. Okay, but here's a line from the Al Jazeera article. I trust Al Jazeera.
The cake attack left a conspicuous white creamy smear
on what but the famous work by Leonardo da Vinci was not damaged. Oh my God,
the cake attack left a conspicuous white creamy. So you guys know about
that painting that is supposedly like a da Vinci painting of Jesus or something
and but it's not really but like a some
fucking what's his name the prince of of no, I don't the Saudi Prince guy. He
bought it for like 400 million dollars. It's just a fake painting. That's pretty cool.
Yeah, I mean, have you seen this? It doesn't really... That's just two balls hanging out
of a fat guy's poofer. I think that's not Da Vinci. That is the furthest thing from
Da Vinci. Yeah, absolutely not Da Vinci. I showed this to Cameron earlier, but I didn't
notice that his penis is inside of his fat fold. Oh, I see balls and no dick. I thought
it was a balls no dick guy, because I know that exists. And guys who just pee out of
- Nolo. - Nolo?
- That's what it is. - Nolo.
- They're calling them Nolos. - It's called Nolos.
- It might be Nolos. - They're called Nolos.
They get their penises surgically removed.
- There's just a little, just a little.
- A little hole. - A little dot.
A dot for them to pee from.
- They pee from a dot?
- Yeah. - They pee from a dot
on their body.
- That's actually sick. - Folks, they pee from a dot.
- Folks. - They pee from one little dot.
- They don't want you to pee from a dot.
- I don't know. - They want you
to get rid of your penis and just leave a dot.
- It's unbelievable.
If I had a dot, I'd probably have four dots.
[laughter]
I'd have four little dots.
I'd probably have four or five dots, I don't know.
Four little dots over the unit square.
They're saying I have the most dots of any NOLO.
Guys, I think it's been three weeks. I think I'll never stop doing this voice.
It won't stop.
I think I ruined my life.
I think it's gonna keep happening.
There was a point where we kept talking about serious things in this voice.
It was so funny to me.
So funny, but it was very cathartic. It was very weird. I don't like that word. Don't ever
Say that again he broke
Nope, a bee flew flew a bee went into the studio and in
B was in here get that be out of here get that to be out of here get that be out of here
We don't like we don't like that. No, I like the bees buzzing. He's yellow and black. It's beautiful
Actually, I was only joking you get the beer
you can collapse the colony. Everybody go on YouTube right now type in
Donald Trump get that baby out of here. That's the best Trump video that
nobody talks about. Honestly going forward that's like required
viewing for this to make any sense. I think so yeah. I think that's the key.
It's a founding text. That's the video that we watched on tour that mutated our
brains forever. Well the first one I think in terms of Trump video top
Number one is get the baby out of here. Number two is Obama chewing gum.
Yeah, and then turn the lights off. Those are the top. I wouldn't put them in any order,
but those are my top three. I'm going to have to go with the get the baby out of here,
turn the lights off. I would say I'm going to probably have to go with this time the pee tape.
Nah. Nah, nah, nah. Actually, somebody showed it to me. My favorite footage is him leaving the
White House on January 20th. And him actually leaving the White House on January 6th was
actually very cathartic. Do you guys remember when he looked at the eclipse?
Yeah. And he took, they gave everyone special glasses to look at the eclipse and he took his off.
And like, it's just like so fucking sick. I've been smoking weed again and watching every single Trump video.
I took an edible when I was back at home. What's wrong with us? The worst thing I've ever done.
It was the, literally I took that and then I re-evaluated a lot of things in my
life and I think I can no longer do the show.
Whoa! That's dope!
That's huge!
That's great for you! I'm happy for you!
I smoked so much weed that I thought that there was maybe
or I was told there was a ghost in my house
and then I was up looking
for the ghost. I got really
really really scared and then I laid down and I
kind of started
feeling more like a video game character and then
I was able to go to sleep. I tried to learn
chess. I smoked too little weed and I
read a thousand books and became a genius.
I took half of an edible, she had these little fruit gummies, I took half of it and I was like, I don't feel anything.
And then...
Story as old as time!
I don't... dude, stop right there, I know what's coming next.
I am fucking high as hell!
I am crazy, I am from my edible!
Edible let me guess
Let me act this out so maybe this is what my handle be the weed, okay?
He just hate it
Man this edible ain't shit. Yep our one hour later
Brah I am high as hell. Well this edible
I'm so fucking high. I am high bot. OMG. I got so damn high. Oh, no. I'm wait
I thought the edible wasn't shit, but I'm not as high as hell, but I'm high as some kind of high bot. Holy crap
So I am very scared
You're grabbing some go whoa, what's this? Oh my god. Yeah when the edible hits too hard and you're scared
Mm-hmm, well, it's too hard and you start thinking everything's a slice of pizza. Yeah, damn that shit is bullshit
I looked at my computer
When I was growing up weed was bullshit weed was
I mean when I was when I I don't know about you guys when I was growing up weed was something
I had to get rid of in the yard with the damn push mower now
It's something that's what I'm after I'm thinking it ain't shit. Mm-hmm. What the hell is going fucking on these days?
What the heck are they putting in weed? Seriously? I look at I go into the tree. I see a blue
Strain I say what the heff. Mm-hmm. Wait, they got a fucking yellow green. Now. It's the problem. No
Putting purple in it
- I mean, they're making jelly beans.
- So we used to smoke as kids, that shit was black.
- Yep.
- Black as night.
- It was black and you would get it--
- And it came in a pill.
- Yeah.
- Yep.
- You'd get it in a pill and it--
- And it was called Sex with a Grudge.
- And it smelled.
- Yep, it smelled.
- Oh, it's so bad.
- It wasn't even really a pill.
- It smelled groovy.
- It smelled like mint.
But it was like potent mint.
- And I mean, we would smoke that shit
and we would just be doing wheelies on our Razor scooters.
- And then one of us has the crazy idea,
like I'm gonna put baseball cards in my spokes.
- Damn, and one homie hit the rip stick.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yep.
- We used to smoke weed and then just do
the family guy vomit in my living room.
- One guy hits the rip stick and he's going--
- Oh my God, he goes down the hill to--
- What is he, he's training for snowboarding?
- He's going too fast on the rip stick.
- I used to fucking destroy rip stick, dude.
I hated them.
- I could go super speed.
- I was too scared to go on the rip stick.
- I'm good at them now, but I couldn't do them then.
- They're fun, dude.
- Yeah.
fun. I'm gonna learn how to ollie on a ripstick this year. You know what I was
good at? My shit was riding my bike at the park. God damn. I had a... There's this
fucking kid who every every morning I'm having... dude, every morning I have to go
to the park with Phil. I go to the dog park, right? And it's right next to this
other park and my neighborhood is all Polish people and there's this little
Polish kid on a three-wheel scooter that every time he sees Phil he like starts
like doing chicken with him with his fucking scooter and he tries to like
get as close in as possible without hitting him and then runs away and then
I'll just be I'll be like what are you doing you can't do you later he'll just
hope I'll see my peripheral in one ear at the other
kids do be doing to be needing three wheels on their scooters though you
don't you need to do a lot about Polish people having a dog they hate dogs yeah
You need to put your dog in lapel
Kids on scooters in general are those were the worst kids. Yeah. Yeah all the time. Yeah, don't get me started
360 yeah
Scooters at the skate park are actually the best ones. Yeah, they actually get it all the way and they snake
I mean cuz those are those are those are those are
Respectable citizens who are can hold themselves upright on two wheels that don't need
government assistance and extra two wheels yep to keep them to keep them up
or or welfare cuz they're skaters yeah welfare yeah what is it like being a
welfare King Patrick I actually went to the welfare office in my limousine yeah
I bet you did and then you parked your limousine out back and it turns out
because I was a that's the company of the escape yeah and then it struck
midnight as a pumpkin yeah yeah yep what also the guy at the welfare office
Guess who it is.
Who?
What?
Don't.
Joe Brandon?
Bernie Sanders.
God, I fucking hate that piece of shit.
I hate that slob.
I hate that slut.
He's a slut, let's be real.
He's a fucking slut.
Let's be real.
Let's talk about this.
It's unbelievable.
He's a slut.
He's a hoe.
He's a...
That's unbelievable.
I'm Jerry Seinfeld.
Nope.
Hey.
Shut up.
Nope. Funny I Trump my friends. Stop. Funny I Trump my friends. Funny I Trump my friends.
You better knock that off. That's a great show. I'm literally gonna fucking stick my-
Funny I Trump the kids. I'm gonna finger your butt like a bowling ball. I'm gonna turn you
into a lamp. Yep, I'm gonna use you like a lamp. You're smaller than an apple. I'm gonna
throw you like one. He's as little as an apple. He's as big as an apple. Wow. Wow.
doesn't make any sense. How did you get this scar? Can you explain this?
Oh yeah, he was jumping.
He has a giant, disgusting arm scar that looks like you got like liposuction on one arm.
So we went to a wedding this weekend and they had a trampoline with a basketball hoop,
but it was an in-ground trampoline, so it was probably like six feet deep that they dug so
so you could get really high jumps and I fucked up the jump really bad here. I
don't have a video of him getting of him getting cut, but a video I took like
after where you can just see the giant all the blood on his arm. That's so
funny. Okay, so there's like the camera wouldn't focus. Okay, there's like dust
in front of it. Look at this.
Oh my God. Yeah. Did you know that you had gotten scraped? No, so you didn't.
So you so carefree I didn't notice it dude. I was my God. Yeah, I did not
notice it till he like he's so I it's a crazy video. So I jumped and I
there's blood fucking I had the basketball in my hand because I was like
the way I was pretty drunk and I was like
tonight's the night I dunk for the first time. Yep, and I jumped but I
I think I timed it wrong and I fell into the hoop.
- Yeah, I did a similar thing.
- Oh, I have a really good video of you doing that.
- There's a very good video, Caleb.
- Yeah, that trampoline was kind of a death trap.
I hurt my toe pretty bad on that.
- There shouldn't be any, weddings need to--
- The owner of that house looked at me and said,
I put, four kids lived at this house,
they all went through college
without a single trampoline accident.
- They sound like fucking losers.
- I should've said, your kids are pussies.
they were not going on. Yeah, they probably never try to back. That was
the thing. It was like it was like a an in ground trampoline. It was like
there who kept it was going crazy with the back flips. They were so yeah,
that was nuts. It was front flips, but it was it was not so crazy flip on
a because it's flush with the ground. Yeah, it's ground level and there's
like a pit under it and there's like gap. There's like gaps. Yeah, right
when you get to the hoop, there's gaps. There's gaps on all sides. So
So people were like somebody, I think, dropped their phone or something down in
there, too, and they were like trying to find it, but like it's literally yeah.
If you jump
to the side by accident a little bit, you will your leg will go down to a pit.
You shouldn't there should not be activities at a wedding. This is this was
just because I guess it was at the venue already, but there should you shouldn't
put physical activities after like a wedding reception, because I'm getting so
fucked up at this wedding and I'm going to do whatever it is. Yep, I will. There's
way that I'm I changed out of trampoline I changed out of all of my wedding clothes
yeah and I immediately put on shorts and a shirt yeah I mean I was I was doing
cartwheels and shit yep yeah that is Peter Griffin outfit on he was going he
was going crazy and then he took it off no it wasn't a Peter you weren't wearing
the Peter Griffin one because the pants weren't green oh you're right yeah he
has worn a Peter Griffin thing before yep one time to a funeral no no where
did you wear the Peter Griffin thing I don't remember - I wore the Peter
Griffin to the live show I dressed up like Peter Griffin for that oh yeah
you're right I don't remember another time you were getting ready for
something else and you came out and you're wearing a white button-down
shirt green pants and glasses and he said do I look like Peter yeah you know
he said do I look too much like Peter and I said yeah and you got changed mm-hmm
is a smart choice
yeah
uh... look like peter griffin
all day to quit chris
i don't think it
to what that's the
but it's not just like so but he dressed up exactly like chris griffin
because you wouldn't notice we had a good idea of the uh... it's it's like
it's
it's the most or no we don't know what it is is if you have the hell way of it
but specifically somebody somebody
somebody dressed exactly like homer
what is a white shirt white shirt blue pants
i'm not yellow i'm homer
you know yeah
okur they could say that okur
yeah just
no i think it's also their name was chris griffith
what the fuck you talking about
you're saying it would be funny if there was a real life rin and stimpy too
that'd be really funny
it'd be super funny if there was a uh... an actual sponge named spongebob that wore
there is you know what the fuck they did on him talking about right now does he
wear square pants with a little tie yes does he actually have a nemesis nor is
no they fictionalized that part oh really the TV is really normal why the
thing is octopus octopi don't there's any of the sponges squids is there an
octopus in spinoza squid wait no squidwards an octopus he's a squid he's
a squid he doesn't have the pointy head he's got a little fucking ball head dumb
as fuck you sound dumb as fuck y'all don't know shit about octopuses no
doctor pie he's a squid he's not actually as good squid have arms and
octopi don't see that he's making shit up putting me squirted up no arms don't
what none of them out they all have tentacles no I think I think it looks
like I think it's on wids have eight arms and two tentacles or something my
hat there's something where there's a there's a difference between our only has
has only a six well squid where it's not a squid because he doesn't have a well
he doesn't have a beak well octopi have beaks to though well but squidward has a
beak well he's also squidward does have a be just a gray guy yeah he's a blob
yeah just fucking gray it's fine as a beak you guys know that octopi are
actually from another planet yeah you know that their other DNA is alien it's
a completely alien they came from another planet came on a comet and they
evolved alongside it's so cool have you have you if you have you ever seen those
those like articles that are that are like from those like disclosure
websites and stuff and they're like trying to say like scientists
confirm that octopi have alien dna and then you click on like their source
and it's always like the scientists are being like octopi are such weird
animals. They're so alien to life on land and then there it is. It's it's
pretty funny. I'm pretty much fully adjusted to civilian life again. Yeah,
yep we should we should go back on tour I know we should do it yeah I'd be down I
honestly I think that I've a dad like I had a my like my Amtrak to and from
Boston both times it felt like nothing I was like just I literally I was ended
too soon no did you take a regional baby that's some good deals on the cellos I
I I fucking yeah well I get nervous on the Amtrak now because the Amtrak like
broke down for three hours one time I was on it so now I think it's happen gonna
happen every time yeah that's scary I was like it was scary
it just sucked TJ Miller I just don't like I don't like Amtrak's like it's
just between a bus and a plane and it's so expensive I just don't like them it's
really I'd rather really pretty to look out the window no I like I like the
train better than flying I love the trains you can walk to the the cafe car
flying on your toes man I've had some fucking rough flights where I really
thought I was gonna die that's a bad I like it it's good
there's a cargo flight where they landed too hard oh yeah we hit yeah the guy
next to me flew up and hit his head on the fucking like a bounce we got that it
was so and I was like listen buddy buck your damn seatbelt over here okay why
you know buckled your seatbelt but he was a thug with no fingers he was a thug he
he's a thug with no fingers. How do you know he's a thug? Because he was like
very weirdly, like loudly talking to me about how he was coming, or not to me,
but like on the phone as we were before we took off on the tarmac, about how he
was going to New York to sell drugs. And you think that makes someone a thug?
Yeah, he's a thug. He's probably a pharmacist.
That's a thuggish behavior. I think that the entire pharmaceutical industry is
a bunch of thugs. Okay, you got me there. Okay, but also he did have no fingers.
He had no fingers and I didn't notice till halfway through the flight.
he's a Yakuza. He was not a Yakuza. Yeah, like a John Wick. Yakuza's lose their
pinky. No, he was a no finger. He might have been a Yakuza ten different times
maybe. Yeah. He had no fingers at all and also he may he he had no fingers at
all. Not a single finger. Not a single finger. How was he on his phone and
stuff? He literally was using like a like a part of his hand where it looked
like maybe there was a knuckle. So, but there was no fingernail. A part of his
hand where it looked like he was a knuckle. But it was like it was like this.
It was like his thumb knuckle is all he I know what you mean, but you also
described a finger yeah, okay, you're you're being a bitch. So he was using
that on his phone. Yeah, yeah, sounds to me like you had ten for you didn't know,
but he made me sit and he made me sit between him and his wife.
He was like I was like because I traded seats with somebody so that they could
sit next to their wife did the same thing and then I did that and so clear
see was between these two people and I was like they say that's so crazy.
So great. I think there was a wife swap trip. Well this lady this lady
This lady was a wife swap happening on the plane. They all joined the mile-high club the whole time
Are you fucking for real this guy couldn't even finger he didn't have any finger. No he
Toes people he doesn't need to finger. He's got all of that. He can put it. He's not the palm
Really bad for that guy. Yeah. Yeah, cuz I was like this guy. He has no fingers. He's
he doesn't he has no that's why you didn't buckle a seatbelt I'm just
remembering he didn't have any fucking fingers and he didn't ask me to help him
and I almost like four different times asked him if he needed help with
something because I was something such a good guy but he never did I I love he
was completely real I when I wish I'd taken a picture of him but I was in
yeah no I he asked me if I worked at Waffle House is where my Waffle House at
that when I got I was in do you work at Waffle House no I'm sorry can I take
your picture I was in Boston and I was um downtown and I was like got off the
the Park Street stop yeah and there's this like old lady with those kind of
like arm crutches that she's using to like help herself walk and she was just
kind of standing outside of the Park Street station she was asking everybody
like do you know where the movie theater is and nobody was answering her so I like
went up to her and I was like oh yeah the movie theater like it's right down
there like it's straight down this street it's on the left a couple blocks
down you can't miss it just that way and she's like oh thank you so much and she
like started walking and she was walking very slowly and I went like I was going
to the comment to sit in the common to like read and I was like sitting and I
could like see the movie theater I could see her like walking towards it and she
like sitting and watching her walk really slowly towards it and then at one
of those like you know those like huge apartment buildings that are along the
away. There's your evolving door and she just turned left and went into that
revolving door and just went all the way around like three
yeah. I was like I probably should have like I don't know. I mean she's
leaning to go home or something fucking things is a good and find the movie
fishing a bit of red flag yeah, very I think you let
really bad situation. I think you let a woman with dementia just like... Yeah just run free.
Yeah I felt kind of bad after I saw her do that. Let's get these hospital wristbands
off. These must be weighing you down. Yeah. Can you take these off please? No problem.
Whatever you need. Yeah she's in a straight jacket. You're getting me up. My sweater's
too warm yeah no problem yeah.
I made it myself into the sweater.
I can't get out.
What happens old women just don't even worry about it yeah I'll let you out of it.
Yeah the part that made me feel the part where I felt like maybe I was in like a like yeah
what would you do or like a fable or something was what because like when I I was saying
that I was like I think I had like oh it's not that far I guess I could like also I could
like offer to walk I could be like oh like and I was like oh no it's fine it's just a
straight line yeah that's weird yeah and then like leaving and seeing her do that
I was like oh my god all of a sudden she's fucking I'm a bad lady from yes
man gumming your penis you can't have that oh yeah you don't want that right
feel good do you know that if I actually did that it was all for the movie they
actually did that he's like a Tom Cruise style do his own stunts guy and he
actually got dome from the gold lady with no teeth it's like a brown but they
should have released the brown boney cut yeah they really should have so mighty
he yeah it's a final woman. Yeah, it wasn't Bruce Almighty though. Oh right,
yes, yes, yes, yes,
and they would never do anything sexual like that. They should add that into
more. It's so cool that Bruce Almighty is like like have God is Morgan Freeman
and it's funny and like God,
Christianity and then Evan Almighty is like God's a hundred percent real and
this is like all about how God is good. That's such a cool way to do the second
movie. Yeah, because they ditched a Jim Carrey piece of shit liberal Jim Carrey
and they got Michael Scott. They got Michael Scott who's actually Catholic.
Every good director knows if you want to do a sequel you have to you have to
change the stakes you have to change it a bit you know alien to aliens. Yep.
Right there's two aliens. Yeah Batman Begins the Dark Knight you got to add a
Joker. Yeah. You're and Dark Knight to Devil May Rise. You got to take this shit
seriously. You're right dude when it comes to filmmaking you do have to take
seriously if you want to make a brilliant it's a crap it's a craft if you
don't think it's movie people people think it's they don't even think the
playing around can you believe that people still think talkies aren't art
what are talkies talkies talkies like oh like the snack no like when movies have
all those - though I saw an ad for talkies before the movie what movie the
movie with no the movie with no sound the movie no time movie no talk it's
just movie no talking. Picture only movie. Picture only movie.
Accordion player. Organ player. It's an organ not an accordion. Well there's an
accordion at this one. Really? Yeah. Wow. In between the movies. There's two movies.
No talkie both? No talkie both. Wow. In between you got to do the chicken dance.
I fucking love that dance. Yep. I'm always looking for places I can do the chicken
dance. They started phasing it out.
They don't do it at weddings anymore, I learned.
I did it at a wedding.
They probably do the non-binary gender dance now.
Yeah.
Probably, yeah.
They probably put your blue hair in.
Put your wage gap out.
Chicken dance is probably, chick, eh, dance, because nowadays they're not chicks.
Not even chicks anymore.
They're some, whatever.
You have to call them Samantha.
Yep.
You have to call them Brianna and you have to call them Ashley.
And you have to call them...
Instead of chick.
Instead of, "Hey you dumb broad."
I would never say that.
That's a little much.
That's a little mouthy.
I don't think you ever could say that.
And you have to call them Myrtle and you have to call them Moysha.
What the fuck are you on about?
Mate, what are you even on about?
Mabel.
What the hell?
I think the edible just snapped into my head like Thanos' finger.
I thought my beer wasn't shit and then I'm on my ass.
This Bud Light Lime ain't shit.
Bro I am drunk as hell.
OMG I'm the drunk bot.
Wow I could seriously have no more beers.
I have 100 beers.
The IPA was too strong.
Yeah this beer ain't shit.
Bro this White Claw ain't shit.
Three hours later, me watching Scooby-Doo Cyberchase on my bed crying.
Yep, I got the beer munchies.
OMG.
Oh my god, I need Taco Bell.
This beer ain't shit.
Oh my god, this Taco Bell ain't shit.
Three hours later, me shitting my ass out on the toilet.
OMG, I am a shit bot.
Oh my god, fire from my asshole.
I am a food bot.
The smell of this poop ain't shit.
Three hours later, my whole bathroom smells like poop.
I forgot to flush my poop.
(laughing)
- This poop is gross.
- This poop ain't shit.
- Yo, this poop ain't shit.
Three hours later, this poop is disgusting.
- This poop is seriously shit.
- It's too gross.
- Who put this on my floor?
Who put the poop on my floor?
It was me, oopsie.
- Oh, while we were in Boston, I didn't tell you guys this.
The last night that we had at the hotel,
we took Phil to Boston.
and I took him downstairs to go poop outside. He didn't poop and then we
walked back in and it was like it was like three or four in the morning and
there was nobody working there and he just like pooped all in the middle of
the hotel,
the floor of the hotel and I didn't have a bag or any paper towels, so I just I
just left it there.
That's horrible.
I felt really bad you staying at the Ritz Carlton. No, I was staying at the Sheraton in there is it
There is like a Ritz something. I think it is a
There's a Ritz in in downtown Boston Boston when I was looking at hotel Arlington $8,000 a night. I was like, what the fuck is that?
I think I think I stayed there one time. I think I've stayed there maybe 365 days. Yeah in a row probably
Let your ass state at the Tipton
Boy bro, you know that ain't no real hotel, you know, that's some actual I think the beer just hit me
Yeah, bro, these cartoons ain't shit. Oh my god. I'm living in cartoon world
I'm inside the cartoons
Yeah, this roller coaster a crew oh my god, it's going down oh my god
It's going in a loop. I'm having so much fun. My adrenaline is pumping
These arcade games ain't shit. Oh my god. I got a hundred tickets. Wow. I'm gonna get my favorite surprise
I'm gonna buy myself. I'm gonna buy an atomic fireball. Oh my god, bro. This prize ain't shit this Chinese finger trap ain't shit
Oh my god. Oh my god. My fingers are actually
Cushion ain't shit. Oh my god. It actually made a fart. Oh my god. I think my friend farted. Oh wait. Oh wait
It was the prank. It was the cushion man. This laser tag ain't shit. Oh my god 100 points Wow. Oh my god 200 points
Wow so many points. Oh, I lost this age shit. Oh my god 100 more points
Power up power up. Oh my god. I got a power up. Oh my god. I'm invincible. Oh my god. My name is lovely snake
Or the names that we did
You did laser
Destroyer obliterator and like wizard. Yeah, yeah, yeah, you know that I was a blitter
I think I got like the I got the shit and you got the one that they made for girls
Basically, cuz some girls actually do play laser tag. Yeah, and you they basically gave you the girl I got I got a Madison
Yeah, yeah
I
Was I watched the new the new Top Gun?
Movie and you know how they all call they all have like they have great call signs
They all call each other like like the man miles and his own call sign
rooster miles teller it's rooster nope it's rooster
that was my most i was a brand x
i don't know
uh... but i think that i don't know if they let you pick your own but i think
that if i was in
the top gun academy michael's i would probably be like ultimate destroyer
attacker of
destruction money patrick the plane roger roger
to actually had a guy who's called site his name is bob as close i was bob and
as comedic in the movie so they wouldn't laugh too hard a little joke since it's
basically are doing my name would be patrick the plane out of a detail of
mind face i think that my name would be bowser
that was actually a really good idea roger maverick to bowser
yeah i'm a robot display nature of my god i'm actually i don't know how to
get a lot of stuff
well
uh...
and getting shut down by the enemy and shit
all my god actually i'm dying home i got all you have a side by president
stockham my god they're actually doing torture to me
yeah man this kamikaze oh my god pearl harbor oh my god the plane literally
flew into the building whoa i would hate if my day if i was tried to join the uh
navy or the uh top gun academy and because my dad's call sign was goose
they're like you have to be a rooster just because my dad picked a terrible
name i should get to be so because the movie was actually made this year in
2002 volcano was it called something was it called something
black hole.
What's up was it called something instead of top gun was it called maybe
bottoms bottom fun nowadays. That's what they call it. I actually called
Top Gun Maverick though. Okay, bottom bottoms have fun when they have dick.
What do you think? I think
Maverick is a funny name. Would that be the new version of it? That is it.
Yeah, that's definitely what they call it. I think
because the guys because maverick the one that's the one on john cody
because maverick is just the main characters name it'll be like if they
called the new matrix like the matrix neo they sure like they should have i
think that they should call most new movies things he's hardly in the movie
though yeah that's why they're calling star wars they're calling in star wars
yoda yeah
dude you know they're you jest but i think there are things going down the
R2D2 a robots tail. Yeah, they're going to have a tail. I think with a robots
parts, he lost it. I think within the next two years, every character in the
original movie will have a TV series. Not the puddler. The puddler will. No,
cause he doesn't. Actually, that's already in the words. He won't have a
movie, cause he doesn't even exist. The puddler does exist in it. The puddler,
yeah. He's a force sensitive rhodian from. They put the puddler into one of
the remasters and they took him out of the next one, but he was in there. The
puddler was a four sensitive rhodium, but he didn't know he was four sensitive
until one day he made a puddle. I'm having a suspicious face. I'm not sure
that either of these three things and the road and he was a rhodium, you know,
like Greedo yeah and he would go like you don't want your what the fuck hey
Caleb Caleb. It says it says gullible on the inside of your wallet and I need to
read it. It says gullible on my ceiling at home. Do you need to read it really?
you need to read or you need to read it. So you need to take every it's on the
bottom or under everything like to see all the money moving aside. No it's
behind that it's actually on each of the money. I don't have any. I have a
bunch of receipts. Oh, they doesn't say it in me that so I can erase them. I
race it go ahead, okay,
okay, it actually also says gullible. Where does it say go? It's got to be my
favorite word to read. It's probably in your bank account. It's in my bank
bank account yeah, so you'll need to all right. I'll just go to the bank after
this, okay, and I need to come with you because I need to read.
I guess I need to read it okay, the gullible yeah, you just want to look at
my bank account. That's all you want to do yeah to see if the gullible is
written as gullible yeah, that's not a problem for me yeah. I don't know why
that would be an issue yeah. I mean yeah, that weird I don't yeah. Patrick
is is your gullible written on all my cards because you're taking a picture of
That's why I have to take a picture of every single one of your cards.
Oh, okay.
I'm taking a picture of a few people's credit cards as a joke, like in front of them.
Yeah.
But, like, I do feel like I'm gonna lose my phone someday, and like a bunch of people's identities are gonna get stolen or something.
Patrick's gonna get fappeninged, and somebody's gonna get my fucking card.
Oh my god.
Well, good luck to you.
You can actually lower the exposure and completely make it out.
Have fun, Jordan.
I didn't even realize that's how pretty it is.
Did you hear that?
He sounded, he just did a cartoon underwater bubble talk noise.
Really?
He went, "Brrrrr."
Look at that.
Wow, that's too bright.
It's too bright a picture.
Do you guys think that the podcast is big enough now that we could be subject to the
fat-putting?
I hope not.
No, because I've never sent a nude, never taken one, and I've never taken my clothes
off.
What really never never my life. I would honestly I'm serious. I would rather
fucking die than be naked in front of anybody. Yeah. Yeah. I think I would
rather I would rather be fucking executed. I probably would rather be
dead than anybody seeing take no not even the well the fappening fappening
the fapping you always pretend. It's not your body. You know I'd rather my
entire fucking family die, but I would also rather I would also rather my
entire family and I survive than the fapping their money than the fapping
not happen again to more celebrities.
Like who?
Celebrities I want to see naked.
Wait.
What?
That's what the fappening was?
What did you think it was?
Kind of like a flash mob.
You thought it was a flash mob of just a bunch of men?
Well they were all flashing everybody with their nudes.
That is true.
That's what I'm complaining.
No one, hey ScarJo, ain't nobody want to see that girl.
Uh huh.
- Girl, ain't nobody wanna see that bullshit.
Put that thing back in your pants.
- That needs to stay in the movies.
- Put away your green eggs and ham.
- Put that thing away.
Save it for the silver screen, okay?
I don't wanna see it on my tiny ass phone.
- Put it in your, put it in the--
- Is a movie is a silver screen?
Is a TV a bronze screen?
- TV is-- - What's the gold screen?
- TV is the tubular--
- That's a little thing I've been workshopping
that I might be trying out.
- I don't think that you should continue trying that out.
I think that might be one of the worst ideas I've ever heard.
- So silver screen's in movies?
- Yep, okay, wait.
He's actually doing a stand up cadence now.
Okay, hold on, wait.
And I'll, wait, so if the, so the silver screen's movies.
Yep.
And the silver screen is Shell.
And then what, well, okay, wait.
So the silver screen's movies.
Yeah.
Well, okay, at least good movies.
A bad movie, that's a black screen, 'cause I turn it off.
Yep.
Holy shit.
And the silver and-
Oh, and if it's a black screen and little, and green mysterious symbols show up, that's
a movie too.
And the Silverman is saved, 'cause that's the movie I'm putting on, saving Silverman.
I would like to save Sarah Silverman.
From what?
save from herself. She's in a downward spiral folks. I saw her one time at a
place in our life. Her life is falling apart. You guys should see her
documentary television show. It's fucked up. She's from Bedford, New Hampshire, right?
Yep, and my friend's mom in high school saw her at Walmart. I saw her in
Los Angeles. Yep, just more evidence that her life is falling apart. She's fucking,
She's a dumpster fire. I mean, I think probably one of the only ways I could keep her safe from
this terrible tragedy that's befalling her and kind of the way that she's kind of losing her shit
is I might have to, um, I think that she wouldn't be able to, you know, continue devastating herself
if she was in a dog cage.
Yep. I think you're right. Protect her from herself.
We need her protected.
Maybe in a dog cage in my garage.
Yeah, there was...
It's musty as fuck in there.
There's a dog cage out back.
Yeah, oh, and I should specify, Chihuahua dog cage.
Small.
She ain't gonna fit in that playboy.
Well, that's the point.
I mean, if she works on herself, she'll fit into something like that.
We're gonna grow her into a square like a Japanese watermelon.
That's what we're gonna do to her.
She's gonna be a cube.
We're growing Sarah Silverman into a cube.
She's gonna be a complete cube.
Like a Japanese watermelon.
That's what she's gonna be.
She's gonna be stuck in a cube. I have, but it's a cage so she's gonna have little
it's gonna she'll have parts that are sticking out between the bars. Yeah. I
think she's kind of like a bumpy cube. I don't care that she's 95 years old. I
don't care what she's doing to the people around her. I brother I think that
was probably my first ever middle school Mr. Skin Search Sarah Silverman. Wow.
Wow.
Yeah.
She, you know what?
Wow.
Yeah.
She was a Bedford Bulldog and for that, she can fuck off.
We don't fuck with that?
I don't, yeah.
Uh-uh.
Nope.
Those are your, wait, Patrick.
Lancers, baby.
Are those your ops?
Those are my ops.
Really?
I fucking hate my ops.
Don't even get me started on the Pinkerton Astros.
I honestly fucking hate my ops.
Yeah, my ops ain't shit.
Oh my God, I hate my ops.
Oh my God, I actually hate my ops.
I actually hate my ops.
actually hate my ops. I hate my ops, though I hate my did you know that
goofy is actually Mickey's on my house would probably my ops would be the like
legions of hell or the Nazis. Yeah, my ops would definitely have to be white
supremacist yeah yeah, those are my ops and I'm right and I'm sliding party. I'm
going to slide on my on the Nazi Party. Yeah, yeah,
I'm spinning on the club and the Nazi Party have serious be
Yeah, like a one and a half million view YouTube video.
The history of the beef between the Nazi party and the rolling Caleb.
RappTV.com, it's just like a picture of you and at the bottom it says like Caleb Pitts
declares he will slide on the Nazi party.
I'm honestly going to fucking slide Hitler's jaw so fucking soon.
That's right.
By the way, my crew is called the Gangsta Velociraptors.
And I don't fucking, I don't throw punches, okay?
I don't do that.
Yeah, I'm gonna pull up on Hitler and I'm gonna have the stick with me
Do you see that video in the car? I'm gonna pop my trunk right on it. Pull it pulling up on Hitler
do you see the video of the
The Rangers fan knocking that guy out. Nope, but you drew a photo of Hitler in pull-ups
Yeah, I did. Yeah, you did. Yeah, I
Drew a photo of Hitler in pull-ups, but it was not sexual. Yeah
demeaning it's it's supposed to be did he squirted soft soap on it listen not
everybody's gonna pull up on Hitler with a gun some you know for some people
weapon the only weapon they can use against something so evil is art it's
crazy he was his own worst enemy Hitler yep I would say his worst enemy was
probably Allied powers yeah or me his worst his own enemy was himself because
he killed himself I'm actually worst fucking nightmare Hitler Hitler buddy
listen Hitler I don't care how old you are okay
Hitler, you're a poop face.
- I'm literally-- - You're a fucking pussy, dude.
- I'm about to-- - You're a fucking poop face,
- Hitler. - Listen, fool.
I'm gonna slide on your block.
I'm gonna spin on you, okay?
I'm coming through.
- You are such a poop face.
- I have a heater, okay? - Yeah.
- I have a heater with me. - You eat poop.
- A heater, yeah.
- I'm gonna hit you with that fire, okay?
I'm gonna hit you with that dragon, okay?
It's gonna go fa, fa, fa, fa, fa, okay?
And it's gonna slide into your jaw, all right?
And then when you're done,
I'm literally going to do the woo dance at your funeral
because i'm also part of the world gang
and i'm here in new york city and i'm one of the world's
was a helluva can fuck with me
are you going to do whatever that we do whatever the fuck you want to me
but i think it but the second you you uh... you do a genocide that's it's over
and i read your fuck i'm so sad night and day
i'm and i'm taking care of it and i think your business it was a very
difficult to decide the second i come up with any of my jews
uh... info to me but what but when i'm with my jews
don't you dare fuck with me. Okay? Because I'll slide on you. I'll slide on you like
I'm sliding for my chosen people. Okay? You understand me? I'm actually going to roll up on you.
80 fucking five foot five Jewish guys.
I'm sliding. It's going to be me. It's going to be Moisha. Yep. Me and all my Ashkenazi brothers.
Yep. We're pulling up on you. That's right. That's right. Rachel. Don't get me started on
Rachel Rachel's the craziest one. And don't you even think about
trying to run away across the Red Sea. Yep, because I'm gonna have that fire and
they're all gonna have probably probably softballs in their hands. They're gonna throw
them at you. Yep. Okay. You think you think me and my Jewish friends are not gonna
slide on you? Wait till you see Dr. Rosenblatt. Yep. Wait till you see him.
Yeah. He's a therapist and he knows how to turn on being crazy.
He knows what makes people tick and he knows what makes people stop ticking.
My guy Dr. Silverstein, he actually did time for medical malpractice.
So yeah, you don't want to fuck with him.
He's been in the pit.
You know what the worst part was? It was dental.
And they were calling him Jailbird. Listen to him sing.
It was dental malpractice. It was medical malpractice.
He was in the temple choir.
He put too many teeth in my mouth.
That's right. He gave me extra teeth, which means I said I wanted it. I'm gonna slide on you with my yeah
I'm gonna teeth like a shark. I'm gonna shave off that dumbass mustache. Mm-hmm
Oh hell no, you're gonna look like a little boy. You're just gonna look like some random fucking guy
Mm-hmm. Nobody's gonna know who you are. It's gonna think you're a damn emo with that haircut. Yep. Oh this guy listens to MCR
Listen Hitler, you might actually think that you could you could escape me
You can maybe disguise yourself by shaving the mustache you could disappear into the crowd. I won't I won't get confused
I want to know you are guess what I got a photographic memory damn and all I have
to do is use Photoshop in my brain and erase the mustache.
I don't know exactly what you look like.
Yep, you got him and I got a coming after you and I got a phonographic memory
to I got a song playing in this bar right now is Imagine Dragons.
I got a pornographic memory and I'm imagining you doing gay shit and I'm
memorizing it and I'm memorizing it and I want to save it for later.
Everyone's gonna think you're just some emo twink.
You're just gonna think you like sunny day.
That's right, you're an emo twink.
That's right Hitler.
Everyone thinks you're an emo twink because you shaved that mustache off.
Hitler, my friend, you are cringe.
Uh huh.
Mm-hmm.
Got his ass.
And Jews are the most based people in the world.
Based out of the holy land.
What are you laughing about?
Not laughing.
Why do you laugh when he said Jews are the most based people in the world?
Why are you smiling?
Don't make that face.
You're like doing a silent laugh.
If you're going to blink, you blink with both eyes, okay?
not the time to be to be blinking like that uh-huh no I was laughing because I
was remembering remember the atrocities the drawing I made of the drawing I made
of Hitler's a native Hitler no the drawing I made of Hitler native Hitler
was in those Jojo rabbit yeah oh yeah drawing that the drawing that I made of
Hitler where he's a sucking up wiener why would you want to see that what's
funny looking at it it's funny it's funny anime hearts all over his head no
it's funny that he looks like this. He's blushing so much. Wait Patrick that's your tattoo in the
fucking... is he sucking your dick in this fucking picture? Yeah because I made my op suck my dick.
Whoa really? Yep. You're making someone suck your dick?
That's what you're saying? No. Even Hitler that's wrong.
That's just wrong dude. Yeah that shouldn't be... we should keep that out of it. Yeah don't
fucking make it about come on bro yeah it's not a little much demeaning you
know it's you're no better than Hitler yeah making him such your dick wrong
with you oh Patrick just got a worrying text message yeah I got a very worrying
text message it says Sony wide conversion lens X 0.6 VCL 0 6 3 7 H made
in Japan from eBay is in transit I'm so hungry
Whoa.
And it will be arriving in three days.
What are you guys going to eat tonight?
I just hit, I had a Reuben.
I think I'm going to have a slice of pizza.
Nice.
I haven't been eating all that much.
Have you seen that picture somebody posted it one time?
It is a picture, it's somebody taking a selfie and it's like, "We made the ops suck our dick."
No.
Oh, it's crazy.
Now he's pretending it was a reference instead of him threatening to do sexual assault to
Hitler.
Don't see a problem.
It's not right.
Okay.
bad dude but people you can't that I mean that's that's never okay that's
something that's never a jammer that's something nobody ever okay to do I mean
no I know he was a user and listen Pat he's a rough-and-tumble customer but
that doesn't mean you could take away as humanity he's a serious right to
consent yeah he was a fucking asshole he's a scoundrel but he's no less human
than you know yeah I mean I mean what you're doing you're perpetrating is not
a crime unto Hitler but a crime to the dignity of the human race yeah and it's
also quite gay
gay as fuck
i didn't realize i'd be gay if i did this
this yo this is a
this is a close up from hitler and shit
oh my god it's actually gay as fuck
gay as fuck
ok bye