You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[laughter]
3, 2, 1, record.
You're not supposed to say it at the same time.
We all have to say it.
Why don't we all say it?
It doesn't make any sense to do that.
That's why Cam is the boss.
Oh, so you just said I'm the boss?
I'm the boss.
You just admitted it?
I'll admit it, dude.
the-
Yeah Thomas is not so you don't give up immediately Jake
That's why it's me. No. Here's the thing
It's me
He pays for the buzzsprout so that's why the boss but if
So he has the eight bucks a month or whatever. Yeah. Yeah
Jake doesn't know this, but he pays half of the bus route, which we have worked out
Financially he but he's like I guess I got a covert again. No, I'm splitting in half
Every time you try and give me like an extra, you know, $24 or whatever and I'm like you don't have to pay the full thing
Yeah, that's doesn't sound like a boss to me. Yeah. Yeah, sounds like an assistant
Yeah, yeah, it's it's a co-op. It's a working cooperative here and they have time we
We're gonna make a $10 patreon we're gonna start making jams together. Oh, yeah, beautiful
Artisanal jams, they don't Oh jams like that like jams like like food and jelly's not no
We're not gonna do a hip-hop def jam
I've been trying to get these guys to do to do music with me
The problem is Pat is way more deaf than us.
Patrick, I've told you so many times, "Hey Patrick, send me a funny little bass line."
You never do it.
Never.
I don't have the equipment to record yet.
I would say there's upwards of four hours of you playing the bass on the podcast.
It's true.
Just while we're talking about something else.
Should I just put my microphone up to my amp?
I don't know.
Why don't you figure it out?
I don't know anything about this.
I want to just have you get the microphone.
They're complaining about that we never do music stuff with you and then I say, "Oh,
do you want to do music stuff?" and you say, "I don't know what an amp is."
No.
And I don't have any wires.
I know.
Do you think Elvis had a microphone?
No.
Not at all.
He didn't.
He shouted.
He just screamed.
He cupped his hands.
He was really loud.
He was screaming into the radio.
He had an old-timey megaphone, not like the ones that have the electric--
Just the big brass horn?
Yeah.
He would just go like, "You ain't nothing but a holler!"
That's what Elvis did.
That's what he was so famous for.
That podcasting in 1898 was just like six guys in a room, each had their own big brass horn.
And he's going, "Ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh,
ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh,
ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh,
nobody able to talk because they've smoked too much.
Yeah, I want to return to the other and just like the most powerful like tobacco.
It's you high.
Yeah, smoking out of a pipe return to tradition before they knew how to like record audio
too.
So they were trying to like trap the audio and it's like a ghost of your soul.
Like if we hold if we hold this gemstone under the sunlight for 10 hours, it'll start to
absorb the soul of our audio.
So we'll be able to distribute that pretty well.
If we like just speak while we're exhaling smoke
and we cup the smoke, maybe then.
Let's eat a bunch of lead dust
so that it gives our voices gravity
and then we can hold our voices and give it to people.
If you were in World War I
and you wanted to yell at your wife,
you'd scream on a boat in the middle of the fucking ocean
and then mail it to her, and about seven months later,
she would open it and call her the C word.
Damn, that's some Harry Potter shit
were doing it yeah I'm 145 years old now you don't even have to talk to her true
you can just put on your your valve index and just lose your wife putting on
an oculus rift and just playing a VR game where everything is exactly the same in
my life except for the fact I don't have a wife yeah my wife is Riley Reed in VR
porn. I'm like, "Babe, can you give me a blowjob for like 11 minutes and 27 seconds?"
She's made out of like four polygons, like worse than Nintendo 64 graphics.
Yeah, so I'm combining Oculus Rift, wife is Riley Reid, and I have exactly 40 more dollars
than I do in real life. Yeah, just buying Lucy's. Just buying
illegal tobacco products. Just spending an extra 45 minutes at the
bar every night.
Yeah, yeah.
Getting to stay up an hour past my bedtime.
Yeah, you're asleep in real life, but I'm still awake.
In the VR too, they just have like a fuckin' another VR headset that you can use to do
this plan.
You get another two hours.
Yeah, your VR reality is just, you got a new skin for the headset itself.
It's like a gold decal.
At this point you're $16,000 deep in this VR setup for two extra hours of bed time.
You're not able to rent an apartment or own a home ever because you have $45,000 worth of different VR skins.
Buying a second VR headset and putting it on to my wife while she's asleep so she wakes up and thinks she's in prison.
just give me just like making her like the shittiest food ever
hey tough shit bitch you're in prison
she's in the war zone gulag
I'm making her fight Riley Reid
for your handy marriage
whoever wins redeploys in the apartment
yeah redeploys in your actual bed in real life
yeah good luck
I gave Riley Reid a fucking 50 cal sniper
Cal Sniper and you have a toothpick, bitch.
(laughing)
Oh my God, good luck.
Didn't she make a rap song where she said the N word?
- Yeah, yeah, she said run that shit back, friend.
That was the line.
- Wow.
- I think she said the N word a ton in that act.
- Yeah, yeah, I think she just started like,
like it was one of those things where she couldn't rhyme
the word with anything else.
So she just kept--
- The thing is--
- Let's look up the, I'll look up the lyrics.
- I did that also.
Hey Patrick, can you sing it for us acapella?
Yeah, yeah, I got you, I got you, don't worry.
You can't cancel a porn star because they already have the worst job in the world.
Right.
Like you can't go down from porn star.
Really worse than being a teacher.
Way worse. Teachers have it so cushy and good. Teachers are pussies.
We've been over this a thousand times.
Yeah.
It says triple stack bitch think we got a hundred packs.
Imagine trying to get like a porn star cancel for saying the n-word
we're in like walking into like the the porn producers office and he's just like
an like a fantasy ogre with one
just dripping swamp slime. He's got a big glowing club and he's like
he has like a woman's leg sticking out of his mouth he's in the middle of eating her as you
walk in. He's like "oh I had no idea that she was saying slurs in a rap song"
entertainment kid. My name's Luke Tarr. Welcome to Vixen, how may I help you?
Yeah that's why the kink mansion looks like that. It's where he lives, it's like
where he keeps all his midnight snacks. Like entire ham hocks and like 45,000 pounds of
brisket. But yes I think she's she's probably in the clear. I think the
The biggest thing she has to worry about is turning 35.
I don't know that it's necessarily saying the right word.
She's said it seven times.
I think at that point...
Is she 35?
I don't know.
I just mean if it's coming up, that's a tough milestone for a porn star.
The other one being 13.
That's got to be the worst age to get started in the industry.
Yeah.
No, they'll eat you up, dude.
Most of them are done by then.
- I was at work approaching Riley Reed in seventh grade
and he's like, "You gotta be tough
"to work in this industry."
(laughing)
- Yeah, dude, it's all, I mean,
the industry's about rejection, you know.
There's a lot of 13-year-olds moving to Hollywood
trying to make it in porn.
- I do-- - Washing dishes
in the back of restaurants.
- Scrubbing out used condoms and reusing them on set.
(laughing)
- No. - No.
- Oh my God. - For Christ's sake.
- Come on, you guys.
kids were talking about what the fuck is wrong with you no cancel
uh but yeah we're here with pendejo time how you guys doing
yeah that's a cold open we're here with our our uh our favorite new podcasters jake and thomas
just such amazing setups you guys have yeah yeah thomas has thomas has like a seemingly a
race car chair. Yeah, is that a GTX racer? Or is that like the Walmart one?
The thing is I got it at like an office store but I they wouldn't help me get it
off the top shelf so I had to drop it like 15 feet down and it kind of it's
kind of warps. You just kicked it off the shelf? I just slid it off
the shelf and hit the ground. But I had to like climb up there because it
wouldn't help me. What's the worst that you would get it? Office Max. Office Max Extreme?
I went up to the front desk and I said, or like where the cashier was. Did somebody like
belay you up to the top shelf? I was like, I was gonna get the red gaming chair back there.
Do you want me to just, you know, I didn't know if there's someone who brings it up to
front and she was like nope and I was like all right cool I'll climb up there.
Absolutely not like this is OSHA violation day.
No well there was a blue one on the ground floor but the blue one
I didn't want I wanted the red one.
Did you use a ladder to climb up there or like?
I say that like it was like a cliff. I was I had to climb up like not that
far I don't know it was probably 12 to 15 feet. That's pretty far. I would say anything above
three feet is high in office mats. That's like a small cliff. That's like the smallest cliff you can have.
So you free climbed your way up to a gaming chair because you really like the color of it?
And then you kicked it off. I like the red color of it. It was like a NASCAR chair that I'm sitting.
the
Yes, it's true. So I'm guessing that you are on the floor then.
No, I'm on a futon.
That is a tall chair friend.
Yeah. It's a bar stool. Yeah.
Oh, that makes sense.
I'm in the, I'm in the, uh, my girlfriend's dad's music room.
It's wall to ceiling, uh, Eddie from iron maiden.
Damn, that's a beast.
Yeah. Yeah. And, uh, so this is how like I have to record it.
Cause the futons may be like half a foot off the ground and I'm not,
I guess two feet five inches tall.
Maybe you got to shrink.
Maybe that's ideal.
Podcaster height, like a jockey.
Yeah.
They all have to be five, four.
That's you guys all five for two is LA five, nine.
Yeah, that's a nice setup you have there.
Did you throw that chair off a cliff at some point?
No, I think it belongs downstairs in the dining room, but it's up here right now.
For how about you bring it back?
yeah
i got the fucking back to your seat
not
it might go for a little bit
right now
having second thoughts about having you on the show the shows open day no time
it's not called nice
the time it's not called it's not called thief time either so i don't know what
to expect a lot of no one can do anything
the about the gun
well it's the end either do i
positive not our signature
probably should just google it before we yeah yeah it's i think it's an ancient
incan word for yeah huge penis cool guy i'm the cool guy i don't really know
what it means i think it means like like okay best friend because the guy at the
bodega yells it when i ask for extra mayo after he hands me my sandwich
okay handsome guy with lots of money well thank you friend
Now how about that mayo chop? Chopped. Chopped mayo? Chopped mayo, yeah. I get that from Ak.
Yeah. I love Ak. Oh man, Ak. Ak is the man, dude. I love my Ak at my bodega. My Ak is my,
he might be my best friend in the world, dude. Yeah, I am so scared of him all the time. He has
piercing red eyes. What's the... Spiraling ram's horns. Can you fill me in on this guy? What is
his job occupation at the bodega? What does he do?
Ok is the guy is just what you call the guy who makes your sandwiches.
Oh, okay. Yeah, I think it means like it means like brother or something.
It's probably racist. It's based on Dr. Octopus because Spider-Man is New York.
Mm-hmm. Oh, nice. Call those guys Daryls down here.
Daryls? Daryls. We don't have...
So like obviously, obviously, I've been to New York, alright?
so i know what it would be is uh... but i don't uh...
oh yeah
but we don't have a good taxes you just have like uh...
obviously you have like the corn dog rollers in the tiki doors but every now
and then you'll have like a half-assed tacos and it's like where the mop bucket
is also
yeah i guess just
this is this is back there and you're like this is really delicious but i i'm
assuming that there's also like vomit
and they're telling you that that's like the uh... hot dog rollers at the uh...
What was it the 7-eleven near our college like people just saw rats in there all the time?
That was the best I'd get hot dogs from there every day there was a
so when the comedy club in Austin that recently closed down RIP cap city comedy club
I was doing the funniest person in Austin competition there one year and
This guy's up on stage and he's just bombing and it's just like quiet crickets
Nothing and I guess he thought he was gonna save his set by pointing out the fact that for the last 10 minutes or so
There was a fucking rat in the rafters and this place serves food
so
Like I see the manager back there that got owner to the guy and who he was kind of a hard-ass and the guys like
Man, hope you all guys didn't get chicken tenders because there's a big fucking rat out there
And I just want I know we're not no no one's watching this on video
But I see the manager's face just go white as a fucking sheet
And people do like laugh, but it's like almost like a oh, you know right
Cuz and like he gets offstage and he comes back to where the comics are sitting and I'm like no one wants to say it
But that guy never did that club again, but he came
Back and he was like man that was tough at the beginning, but I feel like I really brought it together
other team. And we were all like, yeah, man, you probably are Comedy Central's, they're
parked outside now. Are you that rat guy? You noticed a rat? We want you to do a show
on Comedy Central where you do that exact bit over and over again. It's every single
week. Listen, man, we're giving you a show. It's called Rat Hunters. We're going to take
you out to the woods and we're not going to bring a camera or a microphone. We're going
drive away we're gonna come back and you tell us if you saw a rat over the weekend.
You had a bag full of rats at the end of the weekend and we count them on TV.
For every rat you get, you're gonna get a thousand dollars.
This is gonna be the biggest show on Spike TV.
Spike TV's last ditch effort to
stay alive. Before they changed it to the Paramount
Network. Before Spike TV
was acquired by the criterion channel.
(laughing)
I always thought it was fun, like when I was a kid,
it was very much like 13 or 14 year old,
Deadliest Warrior,
the whole channel was like,
are you horny and do you want to watch stuff blow up?
You have absolutely come to the right place.
- Yeah. - Oh, dude, it rocked.
Dude, the thousand ways to die
then fucking Manser's block.
- Yeah. - That was tight.
- That was a good line-up. - Deadliest Warrior
was like, obviously it's fucking entertainment,
entertainment, but even as a kid I was like, when would a
pirate ever encounter the IRA?
You have a guy who is mostly a myth.
There were guys who were--
but you have Blackbeard versus the guys that killed Osama bin
Laden, like Seal Team 6.
It's like, well, the pirate, he's going to be drunk.
And so he's got a high pain tolerance.
And he's got a big sword he stole off of an Arab merchant.
and then you have to have grew as uh... machine guns and they know you can see
so that we're on this a thousand times in a simulation and yeah that while i we
didn't expect this you'll team six wins a thousand times
do the rifle
it was always funny when they had like fucking uh...
it's just like
different races like it would be a like a like maury versus like shall in month
Yeah, it's like a guy from Philadelphia versus a guy from Chicago.
We could watch any of those online at any time it feels.
Maybe not Chalin Monk versus Maori guy.
Yeah, but we can set it up.
The funniest thing I remember from there was the Mafia episode.
They would bring in like doctors and like trauma specialists and
then they would be like like the Mafia guy was like, yeah, so one
of our weapons is a bat and the doctor would be like, yeah, the
bats can do serious damage and there's a big Italian guy,
like powerlifter looking dude.
And he's like, if I swing this at you,
it's going to crack your ribs.
Intuitive, right?
Obvious.
And the doctor's like,
but he's just there to provide, I guess, authority.
And he's like, that was a hard swing.
Let's take a look at this pig's ribs.
And they're all fucking mangled.
(laughing)
- They got the pigs and they got like the jelly guys,
that like the clear jelly guy that bleeds on the inside.
- Yeah.
- This is what would happen
if you shot a guy made out of jelly.
(laughing)
Samurai versus Jellyman. One of the biggest mysteries in modern warfare is what a 50 cal
bullet does at point blank range. So we're going to need to bring in 25 doctors and a
bunch of ER trauma doctors as well to ascertain what kind of damage can be done by a 50 cal.
I miss like the last 3 or 4 years that Spike TV was on. They switched to like, it was all
Deadliest Warrior until like 5 p.m. and then it was these like creepy dating
shows where they would be like how to rape with Vince Champ and it would be
like yeah like an hour and a half of like some guy talking about the game and
shit. Oh yeah then every Sunday all they all they played was fucking Bar Rescue
because it was like their most valuable property. I think it those dating shows
It was like all of the worst parts about like 1999 Pickup Artist guys and then like UFC 2010 Affliction guys and then blended into one just like the ultimate villain.
The ultimate sports bar villain. The guy you have to encounter on the way to your car.
The final boss of Buffalo Wild West.
You have a marble of light, if you don't I'm going to knock you the fuck out of here.
Yeah.
Dude, may Spike TV rest easy, dude.
Dude, that'd be a great Deadliest Warriors.
The guy who thinks you're looking at his girl versus the guy you won't give a cigarette to.
See who gets that.
Their measurements are on the blue corner, 5'5", 387 pounds, and in the red corner you're
gonna have one of those 6'1" but also 110 soaking wet guys.
The guy who thinks you're looking at his girl versus his girl.
This girl is like, yeah, 5'4", 400 pages.
He's got a fucking Tweety Bird, like, muumuu on and he's like,
"This is my beautiful wife and you're looking at her like that?"
And they do, like,
the loadouts and it's like, "In her purse, she has pepper spray, a gun,
twix bar kit kat melted
happy pin expired birth control
yeah just the last week of birth control just the sugar pills the sugar pills yeah yeah yeah
they've got like that blue lint on them that you get in your jeans pocket
yeah it's a denim purse
i like the idea that it's not a denim purse but it still has that on it somehow
it's denim inside
Yeah, denim lined purse. It's leather, it's pleather on the outside, denim on the inside.
Yeah, just the least durable thing of all time.
It's a purse designed to be stolen.
Yeah, designed to have shit spilled in.
It's one of those things when you walk into 7-Eleven and it's got like,
like a now defunct sports team coffee mug from '88 on sale,
like next to CBD and kratom and like Chinese sawdust as nootropics.
I do like that they're bringing back the gas stations now like they sell CBD and I do remember
the fake weed era when you could go to like the stripes and you could buy something called
like joker's dust.
Oh yeah.
And smoke it and you'd go to hell for like three days.
Yeah and it claimed that it was like a sponge.
Yeah.
Yeah they could only legally sell it.
This is legally a TV.
Under no circumstances.
I'm not saying you should or can, but if you light it on fire and breathe near it, you'll
get schizophrenia for like 17 hours.
This will unlock a dark soul in your mind.
Do not smoke.
The coolest shit to me is the fucking workout shit that's called "I am a psycho murderer."
yeah that shit rocks dude
oh dude the best pill i've ever seen at a 7-eleven was uh these things called swag pills
that are called they're they're swag swag is an acronym for sex with a grudge
yeah i've seen those too
yeah it's like having sex with an enemy
isn't there a drawing patrick there's a rendering of like a girl with like
a stick figure girl and like her ass is in pain or something
Yeah, yeah, it's uh, it's...
I'm looking at it right now, it's Swag 6 with a grudge.
It's two pills, one of them's like a tiny black, like, ball bearing,
and the other one's just like a white pill.
It says "One to hurt it, two to kill it."
And it's two stick figures, and one of them has smoke,
and then the other one just has fire on the pussy.
On the stick figure.
Wow, dude.
Oh my god.
I- I can't admit, like, the fucking, the marketing team for Swag Pill--
Oh, it says no headache, so that's good.
(laughter)
I'm glad I can't get a headache from this thing.
It does involve some sort of pain and then death shortly thereafter.
(laughter)
But I need to have a clear mind.
I'm so excited to try out this new knife penis ointment that I just got.
(laughter)
Have you guys ever tried dick pills? For real? Like, gas station ones?
No. I never have.
I have a perfectly 60% penis, so...
(laughter)
You gotta get on that shit, man. They got one called, like, Rhino Power.
I see the rhino pills. I got offered one recently, but I decided not to take it.
They're pretty good as like pre-workout.
Yeah.
You do? Just working out with a fucking huge stick?
You just take one of those, you run like nine miles.
Well, the-
Good work.
The reason those probably say no headache is like you do, so basically what the gas station ones do is they get your blood pressure to like, I don't know, John Madden levels. All right?
Yeah.
Just your liver turns into cheese.
but it's not the same as a little hot blood pumping to your body that it
naturally just goes to the two between your legs
and uh... it makes it gives you a pre hypertension headache like a strike a
headache you get before you stroke the fuck out and like
you lose the ability to walk normally
so if it says no headache on i'm pretty sure that they've done lots of science
to get this is the uh... this is the ingredients for swag bills are
caterpillar fungus
something act knows
fuckin act knows the panics
at the g_m_
wolfberry fruit ginseng
chinese
was it's a chinese
daughter
jackie
the chinese do d_d_r_
studies daughter is not a good ingredient is
i don't know what the extras being ground up to do with the what the state
kills the
i don't know if you're going to go to bills
yeah i need to honor a proprietary blend of essential amino acids like this
like the baby chicks like the male chicks
*laughter*
that's a bad ingredient dude
oh man
I gotta look up what chinese daughter is now
jesus christ
I don't wanna know
it's just caffeine
oh chinese daughter seed
that's not any better than what you said
*laughter*
I just googled swag pills
just the swag pills
the first result is
public notification swag contains hidden drug ingredient and it says do not take
it
the second one which is from two years or three years later says public
notification swag to contains
so they tried to go straight and obey the laws and they just fucked it up with swag too
the fourth result is swag pill directions pediatrics in los angeles
pediatrics
for the swag pill? Yeah dude it's like a foot doctor. I'm stupid I'm dumber than hell.
No wait. It's not a foot doctor. It's a pediatrist. That's right. I don't know how to read. What
is the ingredient in swag pills? I'm trying to look at this FDA thing. It says Chinese
daughters Chinese daughter there is my idea is sildenafil the active
ingredient in the FDA approved prescription drug Viagra. Oh okay.
So it's just Viagra but with a funny name. Yeah it's just Viagra with like other
stuff in it. But it also does say consumers should stop using this product
immediately and throw it away. Well that was that was why I didn't take that
rhino pill that I saw was because on the back it said what said last up to five
hours and then on the back it said do not take more than one every two weeks
that can't be good nothing that you can only do once every two weeks is good
the best thing that I've seen though I've talked about this on the pod before
but was in a gas station was called add all XR yeah oh yeah yeah - a LL which is
That's just so, that's brave dude.
- I got an ad for something on Facebook called Dadderall.
It was like a, it was literally just,
I don't know why I got an ad for it
because I'm not an older guy.
But it was called Dadderall, spelled normally,
and it was like white powder in a little,
it just looked like something you'd cut Coke with.
I don't know.
(laughs)
And it was like, the description was like,
having trouble focusing on your wife
and like your family and shit.
And I was like, dude, if you're having those kind of problems,
You do not need to be taking like half-assed nootropics from--
you need to go to therapy or something.
Like this caffeine ginseng Chinese daughter mixture is not going to make you love your wife again.
You don't know that. You don't know that it won't work.
Try teaching your son a talent. Maybe you'll care about him more.
Yeah, yeah.
Teach your kid guitar or something.
Exactly, then you can listen to him play.
Patrick, you're learning guitar, right?
Yeah, I'm kind of learning. I'm doing all right.
He's playing on it.
Nice.
you're in the tent in the dark
uh... no i have not written any signs are not there and still learn scales
now you know i i don't know what the you know you know that basically just
you're gonna wanna dislike uh...
when my power chords and just like
start yelling
nobody at all day
i think our courts pretty guy you know it is it's a my my fingers i get it get
better it
holding the notes down
yeah no say that's why i i always whenever i try to learn guitar i'd like
small fingers so it's so hard to play the bar chords and I just give up.
My fingers are fucking huge. My hand's like big.
I got stubby fingers compared to my height.
I have huge hands with pleasure hooks on the end.
It's impossible to play any sort of string instrument.
I have a full rib cage inside each of my fingers.
I have webbed feet like a duck, I don't know why that's relevant but...
Oh shit. I do not play any instrument. I played, I tried, I pretended to play the banjo.
Yeah for like one minute and then uh... I was like this is too hard.
Yeah, your banjo... I'm gonna play
video games. That thing's broken too. You broke it.
I didn't break it. You broke it. I did not break that. You did drop it.
Patrick's not gonna do it. No, no, it was broken from the day I met you. You broke the
the nut on it. You broke the nut on the fifth string.
Patrick met Caleb and he's like, "I'm gonna make a note in my head that this guy's banjo
is broken."
Because he's gonna blame it on a podcast.
I can break it as many times as possible between now and when I bring it up in a few years.
And then be like, "Well it was broken when I fucking saw it."
He saw one string was messed up and he just snipped all the other ones.
I don't know, maybe I'll get back into it. The thing is a banjo is like, it's in a tricky
spot as an instrument because it's like not immediately cool and I think if you
try to make it cool you're like the worst guy ever. With the banjo? Yeah.
You had a window of time like... Maybe 2013 I could have played. Yeah, Mumford and Sons, Loomis, Stomp Clap bullshit.
You could just get like the six string banjo though like the one where it's
just like... A guitar? Yeah the one where it's just a guitar for guys who just
don't know how to play the banjo. What if I just get a speaker and I just listen to
music. You should get, Caleb, you should get turntables. That's what you should do.
Yo! You should go to the Times Square. In New York, there is definitely like a shit ton
of returned turntables in New York City. I used to play a saxophone when I was a
kid. I played the saxophone. Yeah, and I would, my dad lived downtown. I played it
in like band in school. Downtown Caleb Pitts. Dude, I was fucking, I was Zatarand out downtown Wilmington, bro.
I was like, I sat on the corner of my dad's block with my saxophone case open and I just
played Hot Cross Buns for like two hours for tourists to throw change in.
I'm very surprised that you weren't like, yeah, people either weren't, they thought
you were like a sickly, you know, failed Make-A-Wish kid type deal or they just didn't throw rocks
at you at mock speeds.
I lived in a very, you know, they were nice southern blokes, you know?
People with big hats and white suits.
Like Thomas and me?
Yeah, exactly, like you guys.
That's why I like you guys. You remind me of Colonel Sanders a lot.
I used to play the violin.
That is a huge curveball. Continue.
Yeah, keep going with that. No, it was when I was little. I was in like an orchestra and stuff.
It wasn't like,
It wasn't like fiddle though, it was like classical
Violin, which damn yeah, I used to be an opera singer
That was a pretty spot on thomas impression every second it's not even that's not even how I talk
They talk like that the key to thomas impression is just pretend you're trying to not wake your dad up every single time
Yeah, even though it's 4 30 p.m.
It's still like this.
Yeah, it's like 19 Miller Miller light cans in front of him in a
full one in his hand still cold and he's been asleep.
Yeah, I used to play violin dad Thomas's dad just barging into
the room slamming the door open.
Do you tell him you played violin?
Yeah, I always phrase it like like I'm going to get beaten or
something. I'm just trying to be nice. No, and then I'm trying to play guitar right
now but the way I'm learning is I'll practice for like an hour every like
three weeks so it really sticks with you if you do that. I think I know three
chords. I know a few. I got, it really helps like, I know, fuck off. You don't know any. Sing one right now Pat.
That was a note.
That was a note, dumbass.
And you don't even know which one.
It's gonna double.
That was a G.
That was like the clown school.
I was singing a G.
I'm sorry.
Hold on, wait a minute.
I'm just going in on his ass.
What note is it?
G.
Tell him what note it is, pussy.
You don't sing the letter.
G.
That doesn't make any fucking sense, dude.
No, it makes sense.
No.
You're capitalist.
Like dollars.
You ain't no musician.
You a fool.
What was it?
What was it what we're doing for everybody got on the Amy Teresa
Red Bull with the straw in it did
iconic look
I'm really glad to be here with some of the best nephews. I got this right here. God's green. That's pretty cool
I've been repairing it. Hey, you know, she had you to it. He smash it on stage. Yeah my dad
- Your dad is Eric Clapton.
- Dad's Eric Clapton because I fell out my window.
- That's why he's like that.
- Yeah.
- That's why I talk like this.
- A lot of people don't know, Clapton actually pushed two suns out the window.
And Pat's the survivor.
- One of them landed in a ship container filled with marshmallows.
- The wrong one died.
- And ate his way out.
- And broke his fall.
I just got one in the mail I posted about it today.
Oh yeah, a guitar?
Yeah, new Telecaster. It's pretty nice.
Yeah, that's the, uh, it's like one of the hollow ones, right?
Semi-hollow.
A guitar Thomas?
Yeah, semi-hollow.
The guy from Jimmy World designed it or whatever.
Ah.
Or whatever.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't even know that fact. I'm just saying it.
Yeah, that's...
I don't care so much.
Yeah, I'm probably the coolest guy on Pandaylo Time.
of time if Thomas is the boss I'm the cool guy.
Dude, that's a good dynamic to have.
Thomas is kind of...
You think everything's about being cool?
Everything's about making money, dude.
That's all I do.
That's why he's the boss, dude.
He's got money on the mind.
You're the money man.
You're Mr. Business and I'm Mr. Party.
I can make 80 bucks any day I want.
How would you do that?
You could just go to work.
That's strong.
Dude, honestly, I can't argue with you there at all.
See, I would have never thought about that.
I'm trying to think of like an Instagram fake it till you make it, like doing poses in front
of a rented BMW guy and he's like, "You want the secret to 80 bucks a day?
Easy.
You're going to want to clock in at your job."
You want to kind of go home and you're going to want to do that for 40 hours a week, that's
probably like $2,200 a month.
Jake's trying to sell-
I make 300 bucks a year just on tax refunds because I work so much.
(laughs)
- Jake's trying to sell weight loss wraps to his mom,
and Thomas is just fucking digging a hole.
- We both get together outside of the podcast,
he's like, "What kind of revenue streams are you running?"
And I'm like, "I'm trying to sell tummy tea to my own mom."
And then, "What are you doing, you still digging holes?"
Yeah, yeah, that's pretty much what we got going on for us.
Now, and the Patreon, and you know, the podcast career.
- But the Patreon--
- It's a good thing I'm stealing all the money.
- Sponsors the tummy tea.
Thomas spends all the money on bigger shovels to dig bigger holes.
He's digging holes to bury his earnings.
He doesn't want his dad to go.
I think it's like burying gold.
I don't like doing anything to protect the cash.
So I just put like individual hundred dollar bills in like six foot holes.
And never, never, they just disintegrate.
that's really smart man that's smart money tactics yeah
people don't know this but Pablo Escobar used to bury 20 bucks at a time
every field
the savings account dude
yeah
that's why he was a genius
I don't know my savings account I'm
I think I'm just gonna let them close it
close it. I think it's overdrafted like $20 because they charge you a fee at Bank of America.
At some point, I'm just never going to lose the $20 to put money in that.
No. I'll tell people, especially when I was in college, I'd be like, "Hey man, I'm broke
this week." They'd be like, "Oh, okay. We're going out. Do you want to come get food?"
I don't know what broke means to you. Some people who are good with money, broke means
like I have a thousand dollars in the bank. Yeah. And to me it means I am
overdrafted in my checking account by like four hundred and fifty dollars.
I used to have Cameron buy me McDonald's like three times a week because we just
worked together and I would be like, "Hey Cam, I'm hungry. You buy me a french fry?"
Yeah. Yeah. It's pretty awesome. Good times, dude. Yeah. Wow. I miss those
Just constant piercing headaches and sodium headaches.
Drinking the worst coffee in the world out of K-cups that were somehow shipped from the
other side of the world and went sour somehow before you get them.
I only drank coffee at work because I didn't want to buy coffee at home.
Before I left for work on some days, I'd put four K-cups in a row and then fill up a big
container of coffee and then just drink it at home.
of my old roommates with blueberry flavored wait blueberry coffee it's
fucked up dude is it bad it's really gross good what smells like berries it
smells horrible it was like I used to drink four cups of a day worst thing in
the fucking world it's free dude I can it was all is my only option did the a
guy I lived with we did he would leave for where he is a delivery driver and he
he would leave for work and he would take boiling coffee out of the pot and he would pour it
into an Ozarka water bottle and you would see the plastic melting.
That guy just has like a BPA deposit in his brain.
That's what I'm saying.
And so apparently, so one day I'm in the kitchen, I'm about to leave for work, I guess I just
never noticed it and he kind of has this like, he's from like near Austin but he has this
like rollerblader from SoCal type voice he does.
It's how he talks.
He's like, "Yeah, man, I've been pouring boiling hot water and coffee and stuff into water bottles
like my whole life."
That's how he started talking like that.
The roommates, we were like, "What do you mean your whole life?
Is this a college thing and you're exaggerating?"
He's like, "No, no, no.
Before high school, it's just sometimes you just don't have time.
You're late, so you don't get a coffee cup, like a real one, so you just pour it in an
empty water bottle."
I would hold the water bottle up to the light and you could see little bits of melted plastic
floating in coffee.
It's kind of dripping out of the bottom too because it's starting to partially melt the
whole bottle.
I was like, "Dude, you're drinking...
Cancer's not contagious, but you're...
This is like being like, "I don't want to go get AIDS," and then just drinking from the
Ganges for six weeks straight.
I like that move.
He's doing the dolphin diet.
get enough like plastic in your stomach that you're not hungry for anything else.
Yeah.
He also, he was the same guy who, we bought electric flyswatters because we had a bad
fly problem because we were gross like college idiots.
We just rotted food everywhere, cups everywhere, it just spilled shit, floor's sticky.
And so we got an electric flyswatter, two of them, and I hear him, he's in the shower,
I hear, "Zzzz, uh."
(laughing)
"Zzzz."
And these are the, not the shitty ones you buy at Walmart.
These are like the shop that, I don't know how much voltage they were putting out.
But I was like, "Hey Sam, I have a question for you, real important.
Are you in the shower with an electric flash water?"
(laughing)
He's like, "Yeah, yeah, there's a lot of them in here.
I think they're attracted to the drain 'cause of the water."
And I was like, "I don't think you're wrong in that assessment,
but I do think you're, as a gross miscalculation,
I don't know if it's 50 volts, probably not even that much, but I don't want you to find
out what happens when water hits that thing.
Those things are fucking crazy too.
It's just like a whole like...
It's a taser paddle.
Yeah, exactly.
It's just like electricity going through like a fence in your hand.
So cool.
My granddad has one of those, you know those shotguns that shoot salt?
Oh yeah.
I had one of those too.
For flies?
Yeah, you kill flies with them. They're pretty fucking awesome.
Yeah, the green one.
It's like a little one, right?
Yeah, it's a tiny little, it just shoots like a salt blast.
Your granddad's shooting a fucking 12-gauge buckshot.
Every time he sees a fly.
Cuckoo!
In the North Carolina summer.
Yeah, yeah. You go to visit him at his house and just pop markers, holes everywhere.
I remember he just like shot me one time when I was like, he shot me with that when I was like
like mowing his lawn with my shirt off or something when I was a kid and then I
went home and I had this like giant splotch of red on my lawn. My mom was like what the
fuck happened? I was like, "Ah, Granddad shot me with salt again." It happens. I was out there doing slave labor and Grandpa was firing a buckshot at me.
Yeah, he's paying me a dime to do two hours of lawn work and he also shot me with salt.
Pretty awesome dude. I guess I wasn't mowing hard enough.
I can't wait to be the grandpa that's like
42 Miller High Life's Deep.
Saturday 2pm my grandson's out there mowing the lawn and I'm like, "Huh,
is this the salt gun for the fly or is this the Remington 870?"
I can't see from this angle.
Lately I've been getting it right because the police ain't showing up.
Both right next to my lazy boy.
Yeah.
One on each side.
Still doesn't help.
I have lost 90% of my vision, so mostly God's hand is just guiding me.
Yeah, dude, I'm ready to be old as shit.
Yeah.
Just fucking, just, when are you guys just gonna give up on like, trying not to get insanely fat?
What age?
Uh, 26.
Yeah.
I get insanely fat every two years and then I lose it in like a four month span.
But I think what I'm most excited about is getting like no return fat.
Not like oh diet, exercise, but I'm talking like a solid 350, 400.
Yeah, like the people who like, like the older people who lose a bunch of weight from like
walking somehow and then they're still fat as shit.
Yeah, because it's just like, yeah, it's just skin and like gravity and just terror.
I don't know, like, I want to, this is going to sound bad, I just want to be able to, if
I am feeling in the mood, to be the age where being racist like isn't, no one cares.
True, yeah.
It's like maybe 70, 74, like around, a little after retirement, let's be honest, but where
you can just say the most outlandish shit in a Walmart and like maybe somebody steps
to you but more than likely everyone's like, yeah that guy probably has poop in his pants.
*laughter*
Yeah.
Like, you're just hearing a racist comment and just turning around and just seeing the Mancubus from Doom.
*laughter*
Like, alright, I'll leave this one alone.
It's- it's- it's definitely- you have to be a certain type of old.
You really- it has to be- you have to be, like, demon old.
Like, big, like-
Demonically old?
Like a hundred and ninety.
Like, you have to look like a fucking- like, the drawing from, like-
You have to look like a drawing that they do in a horror role-playing game for the art.
You know what I mean? When they're like, "Oh, this is the demon that represents hunger."
Yeah.
That's what you have to look like.
You're the guy on the back of the Megadeth album who's just like, "That's me."
I have an aunt like that who is... I can't believe I've never talked about this before.
Her first name is actually Satan.
I swear to God, her name is S-A-I-T-A-N.
Is it supposed to mean something else?
It's some Italian word but she pronounces it Satan.
It's Satan. She's my aunt Satan.
And she's just exactly, she's just evil dude. I want you to know you just doxxed your own aunt
because there's probably two women in the whole building.
(laughter)
- She's gonna get whipped.
Patrick's gonna be sitting here suspicious files.
- There's two people and one of them is the devil.
- Yeah, yeah.
- She's fine.
- You just described, yeah, it's like,
can you guys stop doxing my aunt?
It is kind of my fault because she's the only
Italian woman named Satan on planet Earth
that's ever existed.
- The fans trying to find pictures of your Aunt Satan
and accidentally like finding the devil's Facebook
for eternity. Would you add him as a friend? No, I would not add the devil. No way. Fuck
no, that's bad news. I would poke him. Just to see his profile for you. Yeah, to see what
happens. I just know he wouldn't poke you back, dude. He'd be one of those. Imagine
the terror of logging on one day onto your Facebook and getting a notification, Satan
has poked you. Satan has poked you. Or all of your friends that you've been building
since you've had it in middle school or gone on your own, you have one friend requesting
it's from Satan.
Yeah.
Satan has poked you and you are now locked out of your Oculus Quest forever.
You've lost all of your goats in photo.
Satan tagged you in a photo.
You open the photo, it's just hell.
It's just welcome home.
Caleb's aunt is there.
Oh my god.
I can't believe I have an aunt named Satan.
Yeah, I don't know why you're talking about that.
The only thing that would make that funnier if Patrick was like, "You just reminded me of an uncle named God."
Yeah.
Yeah, that's my uncle.
We will not be putting them together, dude.
They're a natural enemy.
Yeah.
Yeah, they wouldn't like each other one bit.
What did you say to me, Thomas? It was to all of us in a different group chat.
You said, "We're the nephews of the uncles you couldn't burn."
Yeah.
[laughter]
That's nice.
I thought about that this morning, as I couldn't fall asleep, and I was like, "Yeah."
yeah they tried to burn my uncle he's a volunteer firefighter that's why you
follow you you know you volunteer as a fireman so that they can test out new
fire equipment on you yeah we're gonna we're gonna give this this guy this
uncle we're gonna give him the gasoline hose we're gonna see if it works they
They have a gasoline hose for the houses they want to burn down.
This has been giving us some trouble, it keeps getting on fire.
So we're just going to burn it down.
That would be the ultimate prank, kind of like the shotgun thing where you're like,
you're just kind of a wild and crazy fireman and you're like, alright, I'm going to replace
the water in this tank with pure diesel.
Just one time, dude.
Can I just help the fire one time?
It's the perfect crime.
Why do I always have to fight this shit?
Statistically aren't like a lot of arson cases done by firemen.
That's true.
You know what, I don't care if that's true to me.
Yeah, none of them are done by me.
[Laughter]
I think I heard that on a show.
Statistically zero are done by Thomas.
Statistically zero percent of fires are started by me.
You ever see firemen and Thomas in the same room?
[Laughter]
I guess it would make sense, because they need work, you know.
if there's no fires. Yeah. I think there's some that you know they get a kick out of it.
Right. Yeah. There's some fire and they think, "Oh this is really my cup of tea." Right. Like you go
into like your first big fire and you're just like, "Man, this is actually not that bad. I can live
here." I'm imagining like a, they think he's like a pyromaniac but he explains it and he's like, "I
just, I get cold." You know. You've set fire to like 16 buildings across town. Yeah, I know.
I didn't know how to turn the thermostat on.
Of course, heat doesn't work, so I have to stop at places.
This happened, by the way, like two or three, I was probably 23 or 24, but a friend of mine
is a firefighter in a small survey Houston.
I was like, "Hey, do you guys have like the big pole and they're like chilly all day?"
And he was like, "What?"
He goes, "The fuck is you?"
I was like, "Yeah, man, so fireman, like before you get in the big truck," like I'm talking
him like I'm an eight-year-old boy who thinks he's the coolest guy I've ever met.
But he's an old friend of mine.
I was like, "You guys have the pole, right?"
He's like, "Yeah, but we don't use it.
It's like the pole that was there in 19..."
We don't use it.
We take the stairs.
I was like, "Yeah, but y'all eat the chili, right?"
He's like, "We don't...
What?"
I was like, "Yeah, you don't..."
You guys got a Dalmatian, right?
Y'all got horns, right?
Y'all got horns under them hats.
That's why you wear them, right?
You guys know lowly worm, right?
That was a good one.
I'm going to go back to the next one.
You guys know lowly worm right?
I was like yeah you guys sit around in the truck after work and you eat really spicy
chili together and he's like dude I hate to let you down but it's like a job where you
go there you clock in you say like hey what's up and you put some fires out but there's
no chili and we don't light up and down the fire poles all day.
I do imagine firefighters just doing like Charlie Chaplin shit under the way of the fire.
I know it's a very important job and it's a very dangerous job,
but because as a kid I watched so many cartoons,
I feel like they're followed by a cloud of dust with fish scales,
like cartoon trash.
[LAUGHTER]
Like the smoke makes its way to the station,
kind of like the pie gag in Looney Tunes.
The thing is, it's one of those jobs that we're losing to automation,
but instead of robots, it's prisoners.
So I don't know why you would ever go into that field.
As long as we're still locking up kids for selling,
accidentally selling weed, then I think we're fine with firefighters.
I think it's funny that like, they still, even after like,
how much of a PR nightmare the prisoners fighting fires is,
there's always at least one outlet who I guess didn't get the memo and they're like,
"Wanting to make a difference, these former, these prisoners spend 17 hours a day for $1.50
putting out fires that are killing them at 25% increments.
A quarter of them will die as they walk into the woods.
Yeah.
These brave souls lick the fire off the walls of children's hospitals.
[Laughter]
Even if they were violent criminals, it wouldn't be okay.
But a lot of them are caught up in the private prison fiasco.
So they're like, "Yeah, I sold some weed in 1988.
I've been in jail for about 33 years.
I'm 58 years old and I'm super excited to go die in a California fire.
I want to die in a woods fire.
That's my thing.
So HuffPost can tell me that my death is everything.
I ate five pounds of asbestos and I'm going to walk into Chrissy Teigen's house and just
extinguish the fire just by standing in there.
Did she still...
It's just Kamala Harris just sacrificing prisoners to the great fire in Bakersfield, California.
it is a big speed pieces slate just putting some poor kid
a big rebel rousing speech late
sacrifices need to be made and and and and and you're late
irrational person that brings like
talking about like guys
yeah that's like lies it but you know
they the political machine is like no it's true they they're in jail so they're
kind of like
let they're not people for kinda like a little bugs
and i was in a few hours and if they were
if they were in their spitting on fires in millionaires houses they would be
you know chilling at home in prison breaking giant rocks in half with big
access where it is a good way to get the board at a moment i think a little
straight pat make out a big ball to get there
the final of the long-sought orders
yeah
do you think they like making license plates do you think that's what they
wanted to get me to come up with all the numbers
they want to go through a bucket of water
at a redwood that's on fire
the area
they want to go they want to go stare down a fucking grizzly bear that knows
it's about to get fucking cooked alive and just like this is the moment this is my moment
i'm gonna set this fire out so good they're gonna release me from jail
yeah just just being a prisoner who's like sent to fight a fire and like
pulling Paris Hilton's chihuahua out of the the house like like ten seconds too
late and just be like aww fuck i'm never getting out of here now but it's Paris Hilton so you do the
little chin grab like lip bite thing to her you're like ah the dog is a little
*laughter*
I tried, I tried to save the dog
What's up?
*laughter*
Oh boy
Oh man, a load-bearing pole fell on your dog
But what's up?
You yourself have second degree burns over 98% of your body
in your life
*laughter*
Just screaming, just because you're touching your chin
and sloughing off.
I heard she used to party with Chad Muska!
Eating the burnt chihuahua like a turkey leg of the steak and everything.
This is the most evil fireman of all time.
Alright, I'm trying my best.
Yeah, that's why he likes it, dude. He wants to murder the fire.
That's how they motivate him.
Just fucking, just try and murder the fire.
(laughter)
- Yeah, you used to do all those murders on people.
Just pretend the fire was a person.
- Pretend the fire hose is a Glock 40
and the fire is your dad.
(laughter)
- That's what you did, right Richard?
- Oh, God.
- They should make him do different jobs.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, they should make him work at CVS.
- They should.
- I want my mailman to be like a convicted murderer.
- I think mine probably is.
He's like a mailman with a dangly earring and I'm like you should not be holding anything
I own ever.
I want the guy who pours the icing on my Cinnabon to be a fucking cereal rabid.
That's how you get that extra icing.
Yeah, there we go.
I want a massage from a guy who's wearing a Hannibal Lecter mask.
I think you could go on Craigslist or something.
(laughter)
- Easy, you can make that happen.
- That guy's up there for sure.
- You can make that happen.
- Yeah.
- Probably 450 bucks, I don't know.
- The magician that you hire for your kid's
fifth birthday party is like the leader
of the Aryan Brotherhood.
He's on a work release program.
- Well, he works for cigarettes, so.
- I'm gonna set this cross on fire!
(laughter)
- Holy magic!
that's it
it is a separate bring it up for it
is a a brilliant from the it's not no men volunteers just a lady okay i think
i'm gonna make something disappear wrote real fast to the
report it's a
the
no this is uh...
it
not yet
yet
and vomit
let's just make the prisoners cops
yeah
right
the other day i find a guy who got the mind of the criminal
it was that way
the biggest
prison is
uh... being outside of it you know
you know
that's the fact that promises to report yes
yes
he's telling me
that the best thing about
is i know exactly what guy you're talking about who
you're sitting in a shitty lawn chair on like a chipped glass table at a house
party like three in the morning
and the guy's like hitting you with truth knowledge
he's the only other guy awake at the party
he's like yeah you know sometimes when you're outside of it
that's kinda like when you're
on the inside of it you know and you have to say yeah i get it or he'll knock you
unconsciously
you know the self the mind can be a prison at times
flicking ash in your eye
he's thinking of like a way you can leave in fifteen minutes he's like
you know you got to wings of the government
not right
that's doing shit
one bird
all he needs to stones brother
and that's what you know what it is there any six times
near the guy uh... so i i i had a through a house show a bunch of bands
like
sector itself but much base played in the afterwards i got a couple times
So my band played, a bunch of like, like punk bands, hardcore bands played, and then after
we would have a house party, and I would just like play music on my phone or whatever, like,
or somebody would DJ, like Spotify DJ.
Anyway, like, you know, fucking Return of the Mac stops playing or whatever, whatever
the fuck's on.
And I just hear this tone, it's like a "Ooooooooh" and everyone also, you hear the noise of like,
like 50 or 60 angry partygoers, and I walk back inside and I'm like, "What the fuck?"
There's a guy next to the fucking speaker and he's got his head right up to it and he's like this is a
48,000 gigahertz tone it's supposed to like
Just drug everyone at the park
Take their wallets well, they're all
Yeah, and I'm trying to like I'm like hey man no
You can't and he's like dude
Just leave it off cuz like it really like you're supposed to peek on like three and I'm just afraid it was gonna work Jake
Afraid of what you'd see what the fucking the elves would tell you yeah, yeah, I was afraid
Yeah, I was afraid that he would like put me out of business
selling drugs
You can't be playing
DMT beats
It's also weird to go from like an emo house show to like just a tone like
You just have like like a really like heavy screamo band followed by like a beatdown power violence band and then you just have
like a hundred
Yeah that rocks
also, he was like
He was being really defensive with the aux cord. He was like
This is my house. Yeah
I didn't want to use "dude, it's my house" card, but I was like, "dude, I live here and I'm just calling at the end to the Binaural Beats party hour."
He's like, "I don't understand you."
Did he just have the aux cord on his hand or something? Is that who he was making the sound? Or was he playing it on something?
He just got it on his tongue.
Yeah.
Like, "Wah-wah."
He had it hooked up to his phone, I guess.
Was this his music that he made?
made? No, it was like, I, I, so I, you, it's funny that you asked that question. I got a
chance to glimpse at the screen and it was literally one of those like, uh, 14,000 megahertz
or whatever, 488 hertz for nine hours, YouTube videos with one of the fractal brain guys.
It's one of those tones that keep your dog inside. Yeah. 10 hour, 10 hour sine wave brain
tickler yes
yet
anyway as they can see
he was a guy we all got so uh...
the rest and now
uh... it was uh... it is such a powerful trip to actually still this is a real
i'm actually yeah
uh... we've got a little time
the area
Alright boys, thank you guys for coming on man, this was a lot of fun.
I'm watching the Galvanino time on Patreon, I'm Nick the Millionaire.
Yeah, yeah, subscribe, check it out, it's out everywhere, Apple, Spotify, all 9.
You guys add a new service that it's on every week.
I'm getting it taken down, see, I've applied to like everywhere, and I think there's only
like one or two we've been turned down from.
Aren't you guys on iHeartRadio?
Yeah, we are.
The only one I haven't gotten us on is Pandora,
'cause you have to explain all the downloads and all that.
I'm not doing that, so.
Anyway, we're up pretty much everywhere, if you all.
- Nice.
- Check them out on iHeartRadio.
- Thanks guys, check these guys out.
- Check us out on Stitcher, please.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- All right, bye boys.
- All right, bye.