you're listening to Israel's number one pod
this is premium content
if you are not a premium subscriber
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately
*laughter*
Patrick is playing Angry Birds all night
look it records?
oh my god
Angry Birds is already established as Caleb's favorite game
I don't like it that much
you love that game
no the pigs make me mad
they piss me off dude
gotten yeah yeah that hole in your ass yeah I've been sure I didn't even notice
how big that's gotten dude yeah wait can we see it again oh dude there's a marble
in there there's actually marble and a jawbreaker and a paperclip and all kinds
of things yeah yeah I'm still thinking of Phil Hoffman Borat in the car we
I should have recorded the car ride.
Yeah.
That was amazing.
Maybe some stuff to cut out, but definitely.
Yeah, a couple of oopsies, but on the whole.
All Cameron.
On the whole, pretty safe report minus the camera was there.
Barely me.
I'm glad we didn't have video on because what Cameron was doing with his arm.
It's part of his arm.
Yeah.
Guys, it's literally okay to tickle yourself.
Okay
Sorry my my bird clock is going right now. That's the fucking bird clock. Yeah, it's really shocking late at night
It's supposed to turn off at night, but it doesn't
Philip Seymour Hoffman bore at oh, yeah, what was it? Yeah?
What's the idea of my wife?
My wife. Yeah
Kazakh has has extended as many problem economic social and Jewish if Jewish problems
Yeah, I'll be reading for Mario in the Super Mario Brothers movie alongside John Legaslamo.
It's a me and Mario. You have any heroin? Oh, sorry. That's the role of myself in my life. Luigi, I need help.
I need help, Luigi. Straight up, Luigi. That sounds more like Sam Elliot.
Well, well, I'll be reading for, well. Do you have any heroin? I'm gonna jump on you.
Listen, listen, Gooba. Gooba, it's nothing personal.
But I'm gonna jump on you. It's gonna go one of two ways mr. Goomba
I was driving Jana crazy on the way up to Boston doing Tim Dillon Joker
You wanna know where I got these scars, okay, they're called stretch marks Google. Okay, they have Google where you live in Tulsa
Don't know where I got these scars. I tried to eat a really big hamburger
Okay
Have a small mouth. He does have a small mouth. He does have a small no disrespect
Makeups about just cuz I sound like a mechanic doesn't mean I'm not gay still
Listen Bruce Wayne, he's not your friend. Okay. He was on the flight logs. This guy likes playing boys penises like a gameboy
All right
She didn't like me very much
Impression. Yeah. Yeah, this is a
Impression of somebody you guys this is mr. Cinnamon
I love you, Donald!
I love being part of Applejacks!
I love Donald Trump!
Oh boy, I love being the Applejacks guy!
It's great!
Oh my god!
I'm the cinnamon guy!
I'm from Jamaica!
I'm from Jamaica, that's why I sound like this!
Is there cinnamon in Jamaica?
I don't know.
don't make it there. No. They only make it, they have to make it from the challenge.
Cinnamon comes from the store. Yeah, they make it in the back of the store in the room
I'm not allowed to go in. When I try to go in the room they yell at me, I know it's because
they're making cinnamon back there. They want me to think it comes from Jamaica. Is cinnamon
grown on a tree? Yeah. Is it a Christmas tree? You get cinnamon from the Christmas tree.
That's true. Cinnamon is what happens when it snows in the desert and when it touches
the ground it turns into cinnamon. It is kind of it does make sense that he's
Jamaican because he does it cinnamon looks like a... Well because he's Cinnamon.
Let's be honest. Yeah that's what I was trying to... I knew the reason why he was Jamaican.
I was like no it can't be that. No dude, Cinnamon is Jamaican. The apple is...
Cinnamon is the Winnemon. He's a goblin. That's what he said. He's a... the apple is just a
little evil... The apple goblin. The apple demon. The apple demon genes. It's scary dude. I think that
apple was a little coated yeah we all know the truth the apple yeah the evil
demon yeah lucky the leprechaun is problematically coated yeah let's cause
clearly let's
obsessed with gold oh he's trying to keep away some kids from stealing his shit
Yeah, I know what's going on here guys. Oh, and he's trying to find some kind of promised land at the end of a rainbow
Yeah, all right, yeah, you can fucking dress it up all you on this Irish bullshit
We know what you're saying and look at look Oh a shooting star what shape is that star that's right
think about it Wow Wow
where they add a bunch of shapes to the lucky rainbow for globalization
rainbow wasn't already one
yeah no really I'm just going to the balloon wasn't there was a little
unicorn was a unicorn one and I was an Irish about a unicorn maybe the least
no I unicorns there's there's like a lick that's like British or gala
Something you'd love to look you're gay like yeah, I am fuck you're the one
I was forgetting about you and I remember and I just feel my name is bad. You don't look Irish
You don't look Irish. You look very green look Indian
Every time I put myself through one of those like, you know, like the celebrity like oh, which celebrity do you look like?
I always get J chan to see car, dude. I put tendency car
I don't know. I put I put it I went for it.
Yeah, I actually got Jason.
I put my I put my myself through that celebrity thing and I got I
keep I got I got Tyler Ninja Blevins. Nice and Priyanka
Chopra. Yeah, I maybe it's because there's so many Indian
people in the world. It's like you're gonna look like one of
them. It could be it might be a good you know, like everybody
definitely has an Indian doppelganger. Like half the world is from India. There's definitely
like a guy, an Indian Sam Jackson somewhere.
There's an Indian Kanye, isn't there?
Yeah, it's you.
Yeah, it's me. Yeah, I'm the old Kanye.
I miss the old, I miss the Indian Kanye.
I miss the Indian Kanye. I miss the Welsh Kanye. I miss the German and the Italian and
the Polish Kanye.
How is it, how is it beginning of a pretty good song?
Yeah, keep going.
I've lost all the steam I had. Can I get another beer? Yeah. No. Here wait let me
yeah we're all in New York. Yeah. What are you guys gonna do while you're here?
Walk around. We should take down the mafia. We should go to the Times Square Jollibee. You wanna do that? We gotta go.
Hold on. Look at dude he's on the mic in the fridge. Nobody's ever. God damn.
We're breaking barriers here. I know. Dude this is Orson Welles shit. I just fucking opened the
fridge and got a beer for Patrick while recording. Yeah. Oh my god. This is why I told
This is why I wanted us to sit here.
This is, yeah.
I'm the genius of mic placements on the show.
This would be a good trip.
This is a...
Yeah.
Because we were just talking about how we're...
We don't all get COVID.
I mean, if fucking Trump got it.
We'll try.
I mean, yeah, it doesn't...
But it is funny that just all of the world will change so much by the time we record
another episode.
Oh, yeah.
We're about to backlog like eight episodes while the president is dying.
Yeah, right?
We're not going to record another one until after the election.
I know.
It's so fucked.
The president will be dead.
What else is going to happen between now and then?
Joe Biden. Joe Biden will breakdance on Oprah.
Joe Biden's going to go on Oprah and he's going to jump on her couch like Tom Cruise.
It's so crazy how can you get excited about what's coming up.
Like the whole set up.
Christmas. Oh, fuck.
I forgot about that. Come on. What are you talking about, dude?
If Trump wins, we're definitely going to have a white Christmas.
"Let's go!"
Now that I'm in New York, I gotta go try this.
Say "Orange Christmas."
No, because he's a white supremacist.
Or we're gonna have a white Christmas.
Or an orange Christmas.
Get me to the fucking pit right now.
I'm doing their open mic.
We're taking him down.
Do we know where the Babylon B headquarters are?
Can we get Patrick Shift in there?
Let's get me into the Babylon.
We just gotta get him in a meeting. He'll kill.
him in front of someone. He's a sergeant of sarcasm first class. I'd be very good as a
very bad New York comedian. The best part of him. I can tell because you keep tossling your hair.
That's true. Yeah you got a messy mop top. Yeah. Yeah this mullet's not been working out as great.
It looks good. I think it looks good dude. My cousin, I saw, I ran into my cousin at Walmart.
Such a great start to a story. Ran into my cousin at Walmart, my six foot five cousin,
And he was like, "I don't want to brag, don't want to brag. The other one that was there was 6'8".
Whoa. I have one 6'5 cousin and one 6'8 cousin. You got the wrong parents.
Yeah. Yeah. No, dude, your stork picked the wrong family. He got swapped out at the hospital.
Oh man, I don't want to be that tall. Can you imagine if Patrick was 6'8"?
Right? Current body type too.
You would honestly, you would make a good tall guy.
You'd be fucking unstoppable, dude.
It's true.
If I was tall, like...
You'd be just dominating.
Oh yeah.
You'd be like a fucking Uruk-hai, dude.
You would just be...
Yeah, that too.
That's true.
I do have a tall guy personality, I guess.
Is that what you think?
I have the personality of a tall man.
It is funny.
It is funny that tall guys just get like a bonus.
Right.
They just wake up and they're like, "Damn, I'm tall as fuck."
Oh, but I saw my cousins and then my taller cousin,
or the least tall one, the 6'5" one,
looked at me and said, "Oh, did you do that yourself?"
I was like, "Yeah, I did."
And he was like, "Oh yeah, I couldn't tell.
"I mean, one side's higher than the other."
And I was like, "No!
"No!
"Why did you do that to me?"
You should've told him noticing--
Hey man, I can see your penis from right here.
Hey man, hey man.
I see your penis, it's in my mouth.
Yeah, it's eye level.
It is fine.
Hey man, how come your penis is shorter
than the rest of you.
- I've never ever noticed anybody's haircut.
- Yeah? - No.
That's how straight I am.
- Yeah? - Yeah.
I have no ability to, I mean--
- I would look at--
- You could have came in with like a Madagascar 3
fucking colorful afro and I would not have blinked an eye.
- Okay. - I would have been like,
it's kind of offensive, but it's cool.
To clowns. - Oh, you think it's--
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah, why do clowns pick the afro?
- I wonder.
I wonder what, you know, what comedy tradition had to do with putting makeup all over your
face and acting crazy on stage.
I don't know what you're alluding to.
We're taking down clowns now.
Yeah, is clowns just like, did people just become Irish?
Yeah, no, clowns grew out.
It's like a mix of Irish and minstrel shit.
Yeah.
That makes sense.
That's why their faces are white.
Yeah, that's why they do like the red lips and shit, dude.
Their penises are pitch black.
Oh my god, now I hate clowns.
Now I have a reason to hate clowns.
Yeah.
That's why they always have that clown bit where they're dunking, dude.
The dunking clown.
That's what they do with the dunk tank.
Do you guys remember like ten years ago there was this like...
There was a scary clown.
There was a really scary clown in my room.
You guys remember that?
Yeah.
His name was Evil Bobo.
And let me tell you...
Let me tell you. Good Bobo hated him.
[Laughter]
No, there was like this thing where actors were doing like clowning.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You remember that shit? Yeah, like Sasha Baron Cohen.
Dude, prestige clowning. Yeah.
It's the most embarrassing thing I can think of.
People still fucking do it out of like...
When I was working at UCB... People will go to fucking NYU and then graduate and become a clown.
It's so funny. I got invited by someone I worked with at UCB.
She was like, "You should come watch my clown show. You'll really like it."
I was like, what is it? She's like, basically we just like find ourselves on stage.
Yeah.
I'm like, that's not what a clown does.
The only clown I respect is a clown who has the...
Bitch, you better be finding yourself in a small ass car.
[Laughter]
Real shit.
You ain't no goddamn clown.
You're a clown in the metaphorical sense for sure.
A modern clown who has the balls to like abduct and kill children in today's climate, you know?
I mean, that's beast mode.
When clowns are already being hated on all the time.
Dude, Johnathan is going to get it.
I had such a primal...
I had a primal fear.
Pogo the Clown?
Isn't that John Gacy?
Yeah.
Why did he get the middle name privilege?
Why does everybody hit him with the middle name?
Every serial killer gets a middle name.
Jeffrey Elizabeth Dahmer.
His middle name's Elizabeth?
That explains a lot I guess.
Yeah.
Well he was, you know.
He was.
Yeah.
The middle name turned him gay.
Your honor, my client was a girl during all of those murders.
That's the Psycho movie.
The psychiatrist looks at his name and goes, "Oh!"
guys guys he has a split personality it's just a girl just fucking he's just don't
worry about it he's half girl who gives a crap I think you might be a
where girl and nighty turns to a girl and kills boys because he's jealous have
you guys ever seen Jennifer's body it's kind of like that have I seen Jennifer's
body I've done a lot more than seen it yes I've jacked off to the movie that
was a boat it's a disappointing movie oh yeah the whole thing was like Megan Fox
is gonna she's gonna get fucked in this movie and you're gonna see well no the
marketing for the movie got fucked up it was like each I named it Jennifer's I
yeah I don't want to get into no no let no let's get into it yeah no I don't
know I like learning it I like learning stuff please professor Patrick teach me
no this is the no I honestly want to know what happened it was a
miscommunication between the marketing team and the producers yeah it's
supposed to be like a feminist movie right about like about like taking
control of your sexuality yeah and then so I didn't watch that shit yeah take
control my sexuality I'd rather jump in front of a bus yeah I'm gonna take
control my sexuality on the bus I'm gonna take control of your sexuality and
guess what I'm gonna go to jail I guess what I'm gonna do in there
do it again. Do it again. And then where are you gonna fucking put me, you coward?
Oh, you're gonna put me in a hole in the ground? Oh, no. Free audience. Okay. Sorry, did I jerk off in jail?
Oh my bad, yeah. Yeah, execute me in front of all those people. You know what I'm gonna do when those
bolts of electricity course through my body. Do you think any, you know what I'm gonna do with that
last that last Frankenstein volt that moves my muscles up and down.
That's right.
I'm gonna blow.
You fucking guessed it dude.
I'm gonna come in my mouth.
Do you think any subway masturbators...
Can you imagine a guy in the electric chair getting zapped and he just spontaneously comes
into his mouth as he dies?
And it saves him?
His final reflex is just fucking posting a load into his own mouth.
He just has a wry smile.
I'm still alive, bitch.
His last words, "You asked for this, America."
His last words, "I'm gonna come in my own mouth."
Yeah, we didn't believe him and it happened.
It's a Christmas miracle.
Anyway, I went home that night and shot myself in the foot.
(laughing)
Just to feel something after that.
- Imagine a guy who tries to commit suicide
by shooting himself once in the foot.
He's like, "I thought that's where my brain was.
"I must be really stupid."
- I wanted to see if it would hurt before I did it.
- I remember, yeah, my mom telling me
that people who are decapitated,
They have like a couple thoughts before they actually die.
Yeah, I still live in fear of that.
Oh, I just remembered this stupid fucking thing.
But I when I was like, I got decapitated when I was 10.
I did. It took them a long time to put it back on.
No, when I was like 10, my mom told me there was like, you know, when you like put like paint on like the side of your hand and then you like put it on like a surface and then like make it look like a footprint, like a baby footprint.
Yeah.
So somebody did that at this like campground.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know how to fucking explain it.
I saw him doing the thing on the wall.
Okay, I understand what you're saying, but to preface that with like, "You know when you..."
It's like, what?
I thought it was a normal thing.
No.
Oh, well I guess... Alright, well somebody did that at this...
Some guy did that.
Some fucking freakazoid.
Some guy framed a baby for walking on the wall.
Yeah.
That's... Okay, so somebody like put like a fake baby footprint and then my mom told us that a baby got their head cut off
and ran up the wall she told us it was like she was trying to like freak us out
like she was trying to like tell us like it was like we're camping so she's trying
to tell us a ghost story that's what she told us I didn't have the fucking like
the thought to be like that wouldn't work
you were camping we were camping so where's the wall it was no wall no we
were camping at a well I mean we were like camping but it was like just my my
uncle's like a veteran so he goes to like this VFW campground.
"My uncle's a veteran!"
"He's a red eye!"
Was it like a cabin?
We didn't have a cabin.
So where was the wall?
There was like the showers.
They put baby footprints in the showers?
On the front door.
So my mom told me that a baby got its head cut off.
Sounds like Passover.
A baby got its head cut off.
My mom told me a baby got its head cut off.
She explained, she was like, you know how when a chicken gets its head cut off, the body can still run around?
Sure.
Yeah.
I have heard that, yeah.
But a baby is far from a chicken.
I was fucking ten years old.
I was ten years old.
You were ten?
I was ten. She told me that.
She told me it, saying she was like,
"This is the only time it has ever happened in existence."
And I was like, "I have to believe you. You're my mom."
A baby got its head cut off.
He got his head cut off and ran up the wall.
(laughter)
- So we were so freaked out,
we were so freaked out by that,
that we were like,
well obviously we're gonna tell,
she was like, don't tell any of the younger kids.
Obviously we're gonna immediately tell the younger kids.
- 'Cause they're gonna try it.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, 'cause the younger kids are gonna try it.
- The kids are gonna cut their heads off.
- Can a baby run?
(laughter)
- That's the truth, that's the whole thing.
That's how he got her, dude.
She made sure...
Ma'am, I posit one question to you.
Can a baby run?
No, but a teen can.
It ran because its head fell off
and it lost all the weight of its head.
[laughter]
It seems like she really
thought this out.
Well, of course, the baby's head
is what's keeping it from running.
Running up the wall, Neo style.
Matrix.
Once it loses its head, it's weightless enough it can just run up a wall like a bug.
No clip right through the fucking wall.
Also it was standing in paint when it got its head cut off.
No, the paint on the wall was red so she told us that was the baby's blood.
Oh my gosh.
And they never washed it off.
They never washed it off.
I think you have a bad mom.
She just wanted to scare us.
She didn't call me a lying piece of shit.
She did, yeah.
When she dropped me off.
scare me he would just wait around a corner and then go really loud
that wouldn't scare me he would like you would like to start he would hiss or
like yell he would startle me my mom would just show me a spoon she'd be
like you know what this means I'm gonna play spoons on your head she yeah my mom
she broke four wooden spoons on my ass and then if you if you bring that up to
her she's like why do you why are you a liar I love that thing that parents do
were there just like nothing bad ever happened to you when you were a kid
everything was swag oh yeah you you had this most cool childhood of all time we
went to Disney World even though we never did we did this new world it
wasn't the backyard no no that was Disney World yeah also a baby got its
head up the wall a couple things about your childhood the baby actually did get
his head cut off but he did not run up the wall up the wall they painted the
footprints on later. And he scared your dad away. And he never came back because
that baby. So if you're gonna blame somebody, blame that baby. I feel like I've talked about this before on the podcast, but my mom also
scared me out of drinking blueberry pomegranate juice. No. She scared me out
of drinking more than one cup a day. It was, she did this as a precautionary
measure because she wanted to keep her juice to herself. She was like, you can
I mean drink like half of a cup of this because you drink more than that.
There's so many antioxidants in it.
Your blood will be oxidized.
That's bullshit.
I don't remember saying it like it was like science.
That's fucked up.
My mom told me that spiders lived in bananas and like every third banana had a spider in
it.
So you wouldn't eat too many bananas.
I still can't eat the bottom of a banana.
my brain won't let me eat the bottom because my mom said that, you know, the little like
the little tip, the uncircumcised penis tip of a banana at the very bottom?
Yeah.
She was like, that's where the spiders live.
The clit.
Yeah, like banana clit.
The banana's clit.
Yeah.
So like still to this day, I throw away the last bite of a banana.
I can't eat it.
I mean, I know that it's not in there, but I kind of don't.
I don't drink juice as much as I did.
It's funny to hear you talk about this Pat, because you do the exact same thing to your
nephews.
Oh yeah.
Every day you go up to your nephews and say, "Hey, you know if you put that Spider-Man
mask on it could pull your head off."
I mean it is the truth that like the only fun part of having kids is abusing them mentally.
You know what I mean?
Tricking them into playing mind games.
It's like the fucking mind games.
Yeah.
I remember one time my younger brother when he was like four, because he's like 15 years
younger than me or whatever, he spilled a glass of orange juice or
something. I was like, "Well, gotta call the police." And he was like, "No! Don't call the police!"
I was like, "Listen, buddy. The deed is done. They're on their way." And then I had my
other brother go outside and knock on the door. It's like, "It's the police! Open up!"
Now he's 10 and he brings it up all the time. Every time I see him, he's like,
Remember when you told me that the police were coming because I spilled the juice
Shut up
Yeah, I can't wait till like in like can't wait three or four years old in one year yeah, yeah
But my nephews are like old enough, and I'm look they're like oh yeah, you told me you're going to see spider-man in New York
Yeah, and you said you told me if you told me if you open the fridge after 10 p.m.
And or comes out and eats you. Oh, I told I told uh, I told one of them the other day
That if they open up the air fryer
If they touch the air fryer at all, the food will turn to ice while it's cooking
That's scary. Yeah, I thought a pressure cooker could blow my head off
Little did I know?
good
We have to give more.
We can say that we're getting beers.
You want to call my buddies?
We're trying to keep it from the listeners.
We're not drinking beer.
No.
The listeners would hate it if we drank beer.
In New York it's illegal to drink beer and record a podcast.
Back to drinking beer is pretty awesome.
Yeah.
Man, I fucking, beginning of the month
when you, I'm just gonna show you anyways.
Yeah, when your uncle died in 9/11.
Yeah, when my uncle died in 9/11
at the beginning of this month.
Yeah.
That was bad.
I drank, I bought, what's that?
Clown shoes space something IPA.
You just putting words together brother.
I mean that's what they do to make the IPAs.
They take a dart board that just has every word that someone posted on Reddit in 2009
and they just throw a dart at it.
Bacon.
And then they hire the worst.
Bacon plucker Will Wheaton.
Yeah.
Double IPA.
They hire a guy who makes Calvin and Hobbes fan comics to draw the art for it.
And it's like a dinosaur in a spaceship.
And you drink one and you pass out immediately.
You drink one and you don't have to eat for three days.
I drank four 9ABV Tallboys.
- 39 ABV?
- I drank four of them in a row because I was bored.
- Dude, you got a fly in your house right now,
a little fly creature.
- I've had a couple of fruit flies recently.
- I've had a couple of fruit flies.
- They love fruit, so Cameron, watch out.
- They love fruit?
- I don't get it.
Could you explain?
- You wear women's cologne.
- Cameron does wear women's deodorant.
- I straight up don't wear any cologne.
kind of gangster to admit that.
Cushby is Cologne.
That's true dude.
Hey Patrick.
Who sings that?
Who's Cushby?
It's me.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Hey Patrick.
Cushby my Cologne.
If you heard the most beautiful song in the world would you cry?
Yeah.
And you know what that song is?
It's Hero by Enrique Iglesias.
Hey Caleb.
What's up?
If you heard the most beautiful song in the world would you cry?
A hundred times.
Would you cry if I broke your heart?
I would cry if you did anything to me.
Would you cry right now?
I would cry.
If you saw me on the train and you saw me standing on the platform and I was waving goodbye,
would you cry?
If you saw me on the train crying?
Yo, if you saw me on the Hogwarts Express, would you cry?
Because you know you wasn't going to see me for a school year.
What would you do if I went to boarding school right now?
Would you sign my paper to go to Hogsmeade?
Would you cry if they made me go to Mars to colonize it and you never saw me again?
Are you guys going to go off planet when it happens?
Yeah, dude.
I'm gonna go to Neptune.
Wow.
I'm gonna go to the alien planet.
I have to decide.
You have to pick a planet right now.
That's a binding decision.
Yeah.
You have to pick a planet right now.
Which planet, Patrick?
I would do Mercury because then I could live to be like...
You're gonna die.
Alright, Caleb.
What's it?
Shut up.
You shut up.
You listen to me.
If we colonize Mercury, Mercury travels around the sun like I think 88 days is...
How many days, Patrick?
Wow.
I think it's 88, one year on Mercury is 88 days on Earth.
So I could live to be 300.
Wow.
If I do it right.
If you do it right.
And how is doing it right?
Maybe start doing a keto, do what my grandpa did.
If you could do keto on Mercury you'd live forever.
No, a keto.
Oh.
A keto and keto.
Uh huh.
I'll go with keto.
Well, he went, my grandpa went completely vegan.
Wow.
I had to clean out his shit from my closet.
I had to clean that shit out of his ass when he turned vegan.
I had to clean out the shit out of his, like, closet.
Do you have an avant-garde vegan cookbook?
I have had that, but it's not my thing.
[laughter]
I saw that guy one time in Boston.
Yeah, he was filming his videos.
Well, I saw him and I was like, "Is, like, Drake around?
Is this, like, one of, like, Drake's friends?"
One of Drake's, like, white dude friends?
So he's like, "You're gonna be black from now on, and I'm gonna give you a black guy haircut."
Dude, he's so Welsh, too.
Yeah.
I love making Welsh food.
I do love, Drake has 50 guys in his crew, all white dudes with cuts in their hairline.
Yeah, yeah, with the line.
And he's like, "I'm gonna make sure that you never go bald.
If you go bald, I just replace you with another white dude."
But I found, I was cleaning out my grandpa's shit in his closet and I found the Chinese
health chimes.
Chimes you say?
Oh yeah, yeah.
There were two balls, like two silver balls.
I think those might have been your grandpa's.
There were two balls in my grandpa's.
They got him silvered, dude.
They got his balls put in silver.
Oh, he put his real balls.
Honestly, that, I kind of want to have my penis.
I kind of want to have my penis pickled like.
Like kimchi.
Oh, yeah, you know, yeah, cuz also like I want people makes it bigger like think about a well no cucumber
I know yeah, it makes it much smaller. Well, and that's even more impressive how big his dick is and that fucking brine
Yeah, yeah, he's got like a Jerry feels the rest are got it. No rest. Putin was packing. That's being was hanging that thing
Yeah, he was long dong and on the that's what Rasputin translates to in American
Yeah, strong penis.
Strongest penis on earth.
Yeah, Putin means penis.
If you think about that, in relation to our fearless leader Donald Trump,
Some woman came into work today and was like,
What the hell?
Did you hear the news about our fearless leader?
Fingers crossed, I'm sorry if you're a Republican.
Republican that's like damn you had that rehearsed lady. You're buying like vodka. What are you come on now?
Let me buy all the vodka in the store
Fuck I bet she bought a flavored vodka. Yeah, I can't remember what she bought to be honest
She bought a mojito. I think she might have bought gin actually now that I think about it. It's a man's drink
That's even better New Amsterdam something cheap
Not New Amsterdam. My dad when my dad visited me in Boston
He bought like the largest thing of New Amsterdam gin that they had at the store
like when he first got there.
They just polished it off by the time he left.
Every night, just down in gin and tonics.
Oh, dude, a fucked up order we got today on the delivery thing.
Somebody ordered a liter of Diet Pepsi and a liter and a half of Fireball.
Ugh, oh, fuck.
Were they 10 years old?
Right.
Isn't that sick, dude?
I'll pay.
I need to pick up my order.
Hello.
Thank you.
you thank you thank you that's going in that's going to different direction
can we run that back hello I would like to buy okay yeah we played the dub that
time yeah I was doing a child's voice a child what you'll voice yeah and old
- Old, wait, an old chai, what is it?
What do you say?
Chai old, old, chai what?
- Old, dirty bastard, alive and uncut.
- You think he was cut?
- What, old, dirty, I don't know.
There's probably a photo of his penis somewhere.
- You know he was uncut
'cause he was old and dirty down there.
- I don't care how many fucking aborted babies it takes.
I'm regrowing my shit.
- You're regrowing your foreskin?
- Yeah, dude.
- I got mine, I don't need--
- I know you got yours, dude.
- You guys are jealous of me.
- I am jealous.
That's sick.
would love to have a surprise tip yeah that I have to hunt for you got a you
got it just like a wash it you got to claim the souls do you want to do you
well I wash it because I have to you like washing I mean I guess you ever
just put like you ever like just squirt shampoo in there and just shake it up
here's put your mouth on as a joke you know what can I feel the inside of it I
I do just like wanna feel that.
No, I never did.
You definitely did.
How much extra is there?
What? For me?
Yeah.
There's not a lot extra.
Do you have a little like, you have a little spout at the end?
I don't.
You have to pull it back to pee?
Does it look like a rhinoceros horn?
Can you draw a smiley face on it and make it talk like a puppet?
[Laughter]
Can you do some Ace Ventura shit with it?
Yeah, can you make it like the Pops commercials with the upside down mouths?
Yeah, I could.
That's kind of cool.
Yeah.
I could put googly eyes on it.
I don't know, I just...
It would look like the mushroom guys. It would look like the truffles from Kingdom Hearts.
Really?
If I put googly eyes on it.
I just want something actually.
You just want something special.
I just want to be special.
I just want to be able to make it look like a character from Kingdom Hearts.
It is funny that we just cut...
What if you got an experimental treatment to restore your foreskin and it put a foreskin over your head?
Okay.
What would you do then?
I would pull it down.
interesting yeah I would leave it up no I would look good with a foreskin though
yeah yeah I mean look at me I mean I look like a penis a little dude I mean
you know dude come on you're stunning oh my god you know you know can you grab a
a sharpie and draw just a line down the middle of Kayla's head.
No, dude, no, you don't know I would like to have a face for
skin. Yeah, yeah.
Face for skin like a yeah, no, that's a built in COVID mask
right there.
In those hoodies from like 2014.
Oh, a bay putty.
Oh, yeah, the sweaters with the fucking the cowls. Oh, yeah.
Remember ninja guys? Remember guys you dress like ninjas?
Remember the Shogunite?
Y'all remember Genghis Khan?
Y'all remember that shit?
That was wild dude.
No, that was crazy.
There was a minute where I was like, "This might be the dude."
[Laughter]
"This might be that dude."
"This might be it, dude."
Nah, but he had swag.
He had mad swag, dude.
Yeah.
You don't go around calling yourself Khan if you don't have swag, right?
That's right.
How else was William Shatner gonna yell out his name?
Yeah.
RIP.
I don't think he was talking about him.
Is William Shatner dead?
RIP William Shatner.
He's dead to me.
Rick James dead Rick James is dead it's funny that Rick James and Charlie Murphy
are both dead mm-hmm I watched that video last night hold on
is he dead Charlie Murphy is dead is Charlie Murphy's definitely which is
is Rick James dead Rick James better known yeah he died in 2004 I mean I
Party like that guy you're gonna die in 2004. Yeah, no matter what
That's that was the year dude that was the year when partiers died
Yeah, dude, what was it like two weeks ago people found like people remembered that Eddie Murphy made party all the time
How do you forget that song that sounds amazing I've never heard that song you've never heard party all the time
No, I do that Eddie Murphy's Eddie Murphy saying it Rick James produced it
It's about his girlfriend partying all the time. I hate that. No, dude. It's it's a I'll show you it after no
I hate with my girlfriend parties. Oh, okay. Well, then you're gonna love this song
Might be I finally might have a favorite song. Yeah, I've been waiting so long
Yeah, no listening to somebody to saying like do you remember like somebody I used to know by go to you and you'd be like
Oh, yeah, that's the first song I ever heard
(laughing)
- It's actually the first song, now that I think about it,
I think that's the first song I ever heard maybe?
- No, not even having to think about it,
oh yeah, no, that's the first song I heard.
- I remember, yeah, my dad showed me that song.
It's the first song I ever heard.
- Yeah, in 2009.
- No, I'll never forget that, yeah.
- You remember--
- I'll never forget where I was, the couch.
(laughing)
- Listening to somebody that I used to know.
- 9/11, I'll never forget where I was.
- Never forget that.
When I heard Collide by Howie Day,
man I fucking oh my god did you and I we collide I remember listening to Let It
Rock and thinking wow yeah this is the first song I'm gonna remember what I am
during this for the rest of my life I remember a guy who remembers where he
was every time he heard Let It Rock I remember a specific time when I heard
Let It Rock. I have very I have very specific memories of Let It Rock.
It was jacking off. I mean the worst song PMV. I talked about this on the stream but
yeah I mean I fucked Eminem yeah accidentally but besides that I'm trying
to think of what's a worse one time I fucked off a space my first time what I
lost my virginity to office space no way yeah like middle of the movie no like
damn it feels good to be a gangster that I that part I don't like
know, he's he's around the scene.
It was around the it was around the
day. Yeah, he's like, yeah,
don't stop was when we started like the beginning of the movie.
Yeah, she didn't want to watch it.
I honestly I wanted to watch office space, but that bitch was
hungry.
Did I hate when I'm trying to watch office space, but my bitch
hungry? Don't you hate that?
Yeah, imagine. Can we just get to the first stapler line?
Imagine having sex and hearing, "My stapler."
I don't, I mean... That was my first time.
What movie have I fucked to that was bad?
I feel like I've maybe fucked to the pianist. Oh wait, I gotta go. To what did you say?
The pianist.
Jesus. I made out to uh, Taken.
No, yeah, dude. Taken two was my first date with the same girl.
Baby, if you were taken, I'd do this.
Yeah, if I was if I was those Ukrainian criminals, this is what I
would be doing. Yeah, taken two. That was my that was my first date
with the girl. I lost my virginity to office space to
memories, do memories, man. Oh, my God, bro. Damn. Yeah. I think
- You sound so fucking lame.
- I think I lost my virginity to, I think like,
honestly I think SpongeBob is on me in the background.
- I think I lost my virginity to a girl.
I'm pretty sure.
- Maybe my hand.
- I lost my virginity on,
on my family all lived in a two bedroom apartment.
- I lost my virginity to my family.
(laughing)
- Yeah, we keep it in the family.
- Yeah, we went into this producer's office
and he was like, "Okay, what is your act?"
And we just went to town.
- There was five of us living in a two bedroom apartment.
And I was like, I knew that we had like 30 minutes
before my mom got home.
I just made it happen, dude.
- Let's do it.
- I came at 29, dude.
29 and 20 seconds. - All I needed was two.
- A family photographer who was like,
"Okay, for this next photo,
can we get your dick in her ass, please?"
- How about a sexy one?
- Okay.
daughter yeah you know your dad the family photographer is Gilbert Gottfried
and he needed all right go ahead do it need a material do it
you can't miss you the Gilbert it's close okay what you need to do mm-hmm
you start fucking her ass yeah the dog gets involved if I remember mm-hmm
you know what they called
i did it
thank you finally have done it on the part of the only did you
finally a one trip on the yeah
took long as i was not even a good gilbert godfrey to get it to get a pretty
good deal but i was yeah i would say it's a very good way i don't see what
that's a very good gilbert got honestly say you're gilbert
that i really think about it all of them
are you know i was go berg got freed at on taller than a
dinner but i don't know man told in a diet
gober got freed spawned inside a ring of much for
s
we pause real quickly to be you know my gut
yeah
i mean so far it's pretty good it's it's a great song
is there any lyrics
there's lyrics is eddie murphy said eddie murphy sings the whole song
what year did this came out
eighty
uh... or alright that makes sense
but it's just
so hot
richie's died in two thousand four but it came out in the producer from the great
yeah i was noticed that i well
it
why you want to have me
it's a great voice is funny like this comes out the same morning
truck types
was a any and then every size kind of fire yeah i don't know it's great
honestly it's a
more one of the top songs for me
where a political there's no way
i think it's a good i don't have amazing songs
lately for it
the homophobic at any point now
it's about his girl partying all the time
but i think it is a answer
i'm leaving it on
please turn it off
while he's trying to tell you anything that's not even a it's not even a
little bit or anything
object
listen baby i'll do anything for you to turn that's all
they didn't use the word song i've ever heard
hey patrick it may have had tricking
if you saw me on the side of the street walking home would you have sex with me
You pick me up like Eddie Murphy did that if you drop me off and I asked you to come upstairs, would you?
Yeah, yeah you would I'll try and get a nut off man, that's right. Hey, I'm trying to get nut off we should fuck this weekend
That would be so funny, so this is just the plot of the movie. Imagine just posting a video to Twitter
(laughing)
- Hey guys, we're gonna fuck.
- We didn't even put it on the Patreon.
- Yeah, just on Twitter.
- We're just gonna fuck each other.
We're just gonna fuck each other raw in my apartment.
- Eddie Murphy style.
- Yeah, wife in the next room, door locked.
- Mm-hmm.
- I got a door, I got a door to the bedroom,
locked in the outside.
Put the wife in the refrigerator.
I don't give a fuck if you're cold, bitch, bring a towel.
(laughing)
towel. I don't know. Oh boy. I guess we should mention Caleb left the oven on all day. Oh
yeah. That's why we've been in a gas leak. We're sitting in a gas chamber. Let's cut
that out. I'm not cutting that out. Why would you cut that out dude? I'm not cutting that
out because I want to. Those holocaust survivors are going to be so mad at you. All of our
Holocaust survivors will listen to this.
Oh my god, they're gonna be pissed off, dude.
"Hey Patrick said what?"
Don't do the voice.
That's not even what they sounded like.
We should join the voice. We should audition.
For the voice? You know Neil auditioned for the voice?
What? No!
Oh, maybe I shouldn't say that.
It's okay, it's okay.
I just wanna say from here on out, for the last 15 minutes of the episode,
I'm not gonna edit anything out
because I don't want to.
I don't feel like editing anything tonight.
Well, I didn't say anything bad before.
Just keep that in mind with whatever you say going forward.
Now do your famous accent, Caleb.
Yeah, Chinese Mr. Bean.
Hello, I'm Mr. Bean.
Nah, I'm kidding. Chinese people don't say "wa."
What am I even saying?
That's the Mr. Bean part, you don't understand.
You don't understand, he's Mr. Bean.
That's the Mr. Bean part.
The only difference- Mr. Bean transcends race and culture, okay?
He does, that's why there's so many different- He's Mr. Bean no matter where he is.
Listen, you can't hear the difference in the impression, okay?
But if you could see me right now, you would be able to tell the Chinese part of Mr. Bean.
You would be ripping some tape off my eyes.
God damn it, dude.
No.
No!
We don't even have any tape!
Caleb doesn't have eyes.
Nah, I'm kidding.
Oh man, imagine him...
I don't have eyes!
Smooth head and no eyes.
Oh my god, dude.
I would love to be an eyepatch guy.
Yeah? You wanna go Dan Crenshaw mode?
No, I wanna go like Slick Rick.
Oh, okay.
You wanna be one of the most fire MCs of all time.
I mean, I basically wanna spit
more than anything, so if the eyepatch
helps, I guess I'll do that.
I also memorized all the lyrics
to Children's Story when I was 13.
Nice, I've I didn't realize how much I drank. You realize how much you drank?
Yeah, I talked about losing my virginity on here. I don't talk about
We have a really nasty lately someone said
Apologize a Kimster 61 on Apple podcast app. Sorry for talking about fingering dogs and fucking so
It's funny, yeah. I literally didn't even think, like, when you tell a story about a child putting
a fist up a dog's ass, it doesn't register in my head like, "Oh, that's disgusting."
It registers in my head like, "Oh, that's very funny."
Yeah, I mean, it is more funny than anything. I mean, just like imagine coming home and being
like, "What do you think?"
"Ah, shit, we gotta put the dog down."
"Which one do you get rid of?"
Yeah, that's true.
You know, you send a kid to a job...
It is fucked up that the dog got punished for that.
Yeah.
It's the kid who tried to fuck the dog.
I wasn't even trying to fuck him.
He was trying to fuck the dog.
I would put my kid first up exploring my kid in veterinary
school and I claim that my dog's gay.
I mean, they're all two birds one bone two birds one fist in
the dog's ass.
I don't know that it was a fist.
It could have been you know, how like the monkey video and
porn they always say monkey video do that's one of my
favorite one loves to claim fisting.
There's no fist, dude. Come on. You're making a temple with your fingers.
Yeah.
Come on, man.
You can't punch into a man.
We were just complaining. We were just talking about how people were complaining about us getting nasty,
and now you're talking about the temple.
It's not a... Okay. Temple's the wrong word.
It's a point. You're making a point.
You make a teardrop shape with your hand.
It's like a...
You reach in there. You form a fist in there.
Oh.
You pull it out. Your hand's full of poop.
That's true. That's a good point.
It's yeah, I mean it's like Tony Soprano getting mad.
It's that. It's that hand.
It's not disgusting because some people medically need that to remove poop from their ass, okay?
Some people do.
Some people need that.
And if you're calling that disgusting, that's ableist.
If you had C. diff, would you drink a poop milkshake?
If I had what?
What's C. diff?
C. diff, it's what Tig Notaro had.
I think that's what you had.
Yeah.
Excuse me?
Well, once you tweet from her account, you get it.
I tried to donate poop to the C. diff thing, yeah.
- Is that like a fecal transplant thing?
- Yeah.
- But you know how it works?
They don't like cut you open and put new poop in you.
You have to drink a poop smoothie.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- What?
- I swear to God, dude.
- You didn't know that?
- You have to drink a man's, it has to be a man.
(laughing)
You have to drink a man's poop smoothie.
- Ugh.
- Yeah, you're telling me, dude.
- Oh, oh, oh.
- Yucky.
- I thought about giving poop,
or I tried to give poop and they said that I had bad poop.
Yeah, no you have to have perfect poop to get into the smoothie.
My poop is insanely bad.
Yeah.
Okay, we're getting nasty.
Sorry.
We have already been talking about fucking drinking poop smoothies.
What can we talk about that's not nasty?
Okay.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, people have to drink those sometimes because they like the taste.
What can we talk about that's not gross?
I don't know.
Let's go back to the whatever how many fucking episodes we've done of this show.
Think about the not least nasty thing we've talked about.
We've always been nasty.
We aren't good.
were okay we are we are getting more nasty but that's just because because
we're so excited to see each other first times are a change I'll say that this is
a nasty era Donald Trump is in the hospital for having bad poop okay this is
a thing that we ate some black that's gonna have some died on the toilet yeah
yeah he Elvis Elvis dude it was funny if Trump survives COVID and walks out of
the hospital and gets like hit by a bus but it's like the end of a movie
meet Joe Black. Yeah, meet Joe Black.
Yeah.
It's just like, ah man.
And while, before he goes out and gets hit by all the cars,
he also does the other scene.
The president getting hit by a bus.
He also does.
President Trump today died when he was hit by a bus.
He does that scene
from Meet Joe Black. Yeah.
And then he does the other scene from Meet Joe Black
before, the second before he
leaves the hospital. Or like it's the end of
Drag Me to Hell. Yeah.
He just gets pulled to hell at the train station.
Yeah, there's a talking goat.
Nah, I'm just kidding.
He's going to heaven.
Come on, dude.
He's beautiful.
They put beautiful people in heaven.
They put ugly people in hell.
I want to fuck him.
They want--
Yeah.
Everybody's so mad at Donald Trump.
Does he just want to fuck him?
Rachel Maddow's mad because he's turning him straight.
Oh, what?
Yeah, you're jealous of his hair?
Come on, guys.
God, Rachel Maddow.
So transparent.
That's a beautiful guy.
I love Lin-Manuel. I love Lin-Manuel. What if you, okay, imagine craziest threesome of all
time Lin-Manuel Miranda, you, Rachel Maddow. Could you tell when they started? I can't even
choose which one to spit on, dude. Oh my god. That's hard. God, we're nasty again. I've had
too many beers. Yeah. What's the nastiest thing you can think of? Okay, now opposite. Yeah,
What's the nastiest thing you think of?
Fuck.
Uh, like a normal poop.
It's a normal kind of a normal emoji poop.
You know, that's kind of gross.
Yeah, fake poop.
Fake poop.
You buy it five below.
Yeah, fake poop.
Where you soak a toilet paper roll in water.
I can think of is you're probably be having sex in a toilet getting
pranked by a stick of gum.
I remember I may have talked about this before.
a stick of gum that zaps you.
- I remember my mom, no I've talked about this before.
My mom was like--
- We're at a point where we're like,
all the best stories have been said.
- We've run out of stuff, dude.
- Can somebody do something horrible to me?
Just so I have something to talk about.
I don't care what it is.
- It's hard to do it now with COVID and everything.
You can't go out and experience shit.
- Trying to think what's happened recently.
- Well no, I have the story job now.
- Yeah, you do.
- Now I'm gonna be the one with the stories.
- I need to get a job for stories.
I have zero stories but I tell the most.
I didn't tell it on the pod but a guy came in and he was talking about the tech bubble
to me and I was like oh I know the tech bubble and I was just like talking to him about that
and he just started talking about like the future and shit and he's like does that know
where he started going yeah and in fucking five years we're all gonna have heads this
big and tiny bodies we're gonna use mind control and teleport everywhere.
Just so you know, listener, Cameron just mimed a yard long head.
How big is a yard?
It's three feet.
Somebody hates football in America.
I do.
Yeah.
And somebody never went to first grade.
And he came in, he came in, I thought a yard was metric for like a really long time.
He did, yeah.
He talked to me.
I did tilt just now.
He talked to me for fucking like 10 minutes.
This big.
I never, I only think of things in like feet and inches.
Yeah.
Actually no, 'cause millimeters,
like if you, like skateboard wheels are all in millimeters.
I think a millimeter is how big a millipede is.
Yeah.
I don't know how big a millimeter is,
I just know there's a difference between--
A millimeter is a million meters.
50 millimeters and 60 millimeters, big difference.
That's true.
Yeah.
I know that.
else about metric. Yeah let's get let's do some math and measurement content right
now. You want me to do math? Let's do okay Patrick what is 5 times 3? 5 times 3 is
15. Okay what's... You did this thing where you delay by saying the problem back to you. 5 times 3 well I know that I
definitely know that one. It's 15. Okay give me another one. What's 15 times 5? Fuck off.
15 times 5, okay? That's easy. Come on.
Shut up.
15 times 5.
Uh-uh.
This is literally Beetlejuice on our story.
We're just doing that, dude.
Alright, what's 100 plus 100?
100 plus 100 is 200.
7 times 7 is 49.
Okay, I didn't ask you that one, so it doesn't count.
You just lost points.
Ah, shit.
All right, what's 7 times 8? 7 times 8 is 56 because 5 6 7 8
What?
56 5 6
7 8. All right. What's 13 times 13? 13 times 13 is 111
No
What? No, no, no, that's 11 times 11. That can't be true.
144 okay, so it's okay. All right, let's do it.
144 so the one after that. I wish I could cut your brain open and see what's happening right now.
Which go going here teen times is that 156? No, he's having a push out. It's 169
You guys I fuck I have dyscalculia you can't do
Math shit at me. I only better has time Patrick has dysmorphia. So we can't do math
It's true, and this is a message to all the fans out there. We're allowed to make fun of Patrick for this you're not that's right
You're not best friends with him. You leave him alone
Yeah, you stop going in the discord and you stop saying things like I wish Patrick would get hit by a bus I
Don't you're making me sound like a bitch wrong. Yeah, actually do it. I can't
Try to kill me try to kill me you can't you can't find me. Yeah, I can't even get to his heart
It's very easy to find Patrick. It's no
Here's a new challenge. Find Patrick and break his heart.
I dare you. Find Patrick and make him cry.
Whichever person does that first
gets a guess on an episode.
Whoever finds Patrick and breaks his heart
to pieces, they get to come on the podcast.
It has to be to pieces. It won't happen. He has to be in shambles.
That's a long time.
It doesn't matter if you're
breaking my heart.
I'll do it right now.
OK, I love you.
Not.
What?
You heard me, you heard me.
Are you serious?
Chambles, guess who gets a guest
on the next episode?
Me.
Hey, Patrick.
What?
Would it break your heart if I
played your favorite song?
That's fucking--
- I can't stop.
- That's up to the first one,
would you cry, what would you do if I cried right now?
(laughing)
- Asking your manager what would you do if I cried at work.
My manager that.
- What would you do if I cried at work?
- That was how I was entertaining myself
for just like an hour.
Like there was just a point where I was just like
walking up and down the aisles where I just like have to--
- When you have like stupid jobs like that,
you have to entertain yourself.
- Yeah, it's just like retailers.
It's just like, yeah.
(laughing)
I just imagine going up to my manager and be like,
what would you do if I started crying?
And I did ask him and he started laughing
And then he said, "I would tell you to toughen up."
Which is, I think, a fair answer.
- That's beast, honestly.
- Yeah.
- Fucking bird clock, dude.
- I hate that bird clock warning.
- Can we break it?
- We got a minute and a half left, dude.
- I think, yeah, the funniest version of that
is like in a boardroom.
- Yeah, great meeting.
- Just real quick, one last thing before we leave.
What would you guys do if I just started crying?
Just right now in the boardroom.
- Yeah, so I'm just gonna--
- Would anybody else start crying?
just gonna give you a warning but right now I just want to know what would you do
if I cried right now just so you know I was thinking about crying the context
that I asked my manager was I asked if I could take my lunch break and she said
no like jokingly he was like no and I was like yeah and what would you do if I
just burst into tears right now
I it's better just no yeah no no context is a lot of straight-up manager what do
you have us right I don't remember your name is that part of being of working
here then fire me I don't care yeah just asking him over and over to just every
hour okay what would you do if I cried now would you would it be worse if I
cried in the morning or at the end of my shift if I cry at 3:30 would you be mad
if I picked you up from school and I was crying would you assume the worst?
Did you just pop a tooth out of your mouth?
no I have a really big cavity. Let me see it. You can't just put your finger over it.
Oh I can actually oh my god. My filling fell out and I haven't gotten it replaced. Did you swallow it?
No I spit it out thankfully but. Did it taste good? I feel like I have an iron
deficiency so it did taste good. Was it gold? I had a silver filling. My dentist Robert Christ.
There's no way. That was his name. I've talked about this before. We've talked about Robert Christ.
My dentist growing up was Sandra Miles, S Miles. What was your dentist name? Dr. Haruyama.
Haruyama? Isn't that a Pokemon? Like the fucking end of a Captain Underpants book?
Harry I was a pokey no hiriyama not harium. Okay, come on. Shut your mouth
Patrick thinks all Japanese stuff is the same. No, I don't he literally just said it you literally like that did I?
Just wrote it down on the table. You're gonna have to wipe that off, dude
I don't know why you wrote it on the table great now. You're dropping the fucking marker. Come on. That's
My jewel yeah, you're for people listening. Yeah, you're jewel marker
Stop that banjo. Damn it. I'm just kidding
I'm sitting on Cameron side. Why on his lap?
Yeah, I would be jealous a little bit. Would you fall in love with me if I let you sit on my lap?
Yo, Santa Santa straight up. Would you fall in love with me if I asked for your heart for Christmas?
Would you give me your heart make it real or let's forget about it
I think the only thing that makes those questions funny to me is just looking
Patrick in the face when I ask him and just watching him try not to laugh.
Just when I start with... He's trying not to cry dude. Yeah, I'm trying not to fall.
If I asked you if you would cry, would you cry? Would you dance? No. If I asked you to dance?
I would not. I would dance with either of you if you asked. I think that's the thing that's making me
laugh the most about it is I'm imagining it as like lines from Hero by Enrique Iglesias.
yeah I am baby if I if I bought you a Valentine heart would you write me a
poem it's not a bad idea what are we doing for Valentine's Day let's have a
boys party for Valentine's Day we need to have a Valentine's bow wow let's do
another hour do we got a finger some stuff out mm-hmm all right Cameron's
but come on you can try dude I got spikes in there you have no defense I got a
tail dude you'd never seen it I got a tail that covers up tail doesn't cover
it up you know dogs will put their tail down when they're scared they cover
their butt with their tail that's what I do but it's a demon's tail and it's got
spikes they should get a tail he's got Bowser's tail I got Bowser's tail yeah
Cameron's part Bowser I'm gonna have to hear myself with it when I'm trying to
sleep keep me up I'm gonna have to hear that all night yeah true he has a better
sleep in my living room yeah we're gonna whisper to each other and giggle you're
gonna tell scary stories yeah tell Cameron scary story put a campfire in my
room do you think it ghost could be beautiful if you imagined a beautiful
ghost right now, would it make you cry?
- What if, okay, so you see the ghost's bed sheet, right?
- Yeah. - And then you look,
you look over-- - If you saw the lady
in black, could you make her good?
(laughing)
- You look at the ghost's bed sheet,
and you see some big ol', big ol' bolt-ons
poking throughout the sheet. - Take that thang off, girl.
(laughing)
- There it goes. - Take my sheet off.
- You ain't fooling nobody, I know what you hiding.
Let me get a piece of that.
- You was at the club.
(laughing)
- All right, we're done.
- We'll do 15 more of these this weekend.
- Bye.
- Bye everybody.