Come here, come here, come here, let me see your butt.
(upbeat music)
(explosion)
- Naruto, poster, sorry.
- Have you watched the rehearsal?
- Thank you, thank you.
- Yeah, I have.
- Blew my mind.
- It's, yeah, I mean, it's pretty great.
- The shit when he's like--
- Have you guys seen the show about the show?
People know about that?
Do you know the show about the show?
Is it called the show about the show?
- It's a guy, this insane, I think he's a narcissist,
but he seems very talented.
Old guy, like kind of cult director in New York
made this show about making the show,
and each episode is about the previous,
making the previous episode.
- Whoa. - Whoa.
- What's the first episode about?
- It's about what he's about to do.
- Oh.
- And apparently John Wilson showed that to Nathan Fielder,
and I think that probably, is this, are we recording?
We have started recording.
Oh, God.
This is depressing.
No, it's good.
I don't think that guy's a narcissist.
I think he's great and if he ever wants me to help him out or--
We started recording right after he said the narcissist thing, so now it seems like he's
dead.
That's awesome.
I do think he's a narcissist then.
I'm tripling down.
Triple down?
That's a double negative.
You cancel it out.
That's right.
Double jeopardy.
Yeah.
Welcome to Podcasts About List.
Hey, guys.
What up?
Caleb, Cameron, Patrick.
Yup.
I'm Caleb.
And Cameron at the helm and we always announce our names because we're the famous three amigos. Yep, which everyone calls us
Yes, and I the leader. Mm-hmm. Okay
Um for now for the leader I with the crown atop my I'm pretty sure Patrick's the leader of the I'm the leader of the
Three amigos, I'm pretty sure that Cameron I think Cameron maybe although he's not the most vocal all the time
Speaking in the third person, of course, right? Right, which we do every once in a while every now and then you gotta yeah
Yeah, absolutely.
I think that I--
Caleb agrees.
I think I am the glue that really bonds us
as both friends and as business partners.
That's really beautiful.
That's interesting.
I would agree, I would agree.
I think I'm like the wild card sexual thriller guy.
The wild sexual thriller guy.
The wild sexual--
Yeah, I'm sort of like the goofball.
Yeah.
So like a lot of time people will be like.
(laughing)
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm like, "Ugh, you're so funny, man."
- Yeah.
- Dude, what's up?
- What's so great is that at the end of the day,
we're all goofballs.
- That's true.
- And we are bonded by our goofiness
and we're bonded by our love for one another.
- Yeah.
There's a lot of love in this room.
- There's a lot of love in this room.
- A lot of love.
- You best believe post-recording.
- Oh my God.
- We're gonna show that physically.
- Holy shit.
- I'm ready.
- I'm ready too.
I was ready before we started recording.
I'm ready while we're recording.
- What's great about this desk is you can't see below.
That's right. So we're all just popping boners. Yeah, I'm rock hard. Yeah, all two and a half right now
Just just hanging out. Yeah, if only my arms were a little longer. Ah, I could jerk you guys off
Yeah, I came your arms are so long - that's one of my favorite things actually about you
I think I do have a longer torso and arm set than legs. Mm-hmm as a tall person. Yeah, it's sort of a Polish thing
Yeah, I think so. Yeah, I'm pretty I'm
You know me
Five seven.
I'm like very compact.
Yeah.
I'm very...
I'm built like a fucking tank.
But like a tank.
Dude, you can barely fit through the office door now.
I know.
I'm so like stocky and wide.
Do you guys know that Caleb's been going to the gym every fucking day?
It shows.
I know, bro.
I mean like how could you not know?
Thank you for noticing.
You see when Caleb pops off his shirt, you're like...
Yeah.
And he's always has his shirt off, which is so awesome for all of us here.
You charmers.
He's got that he's got that 50s strong man built kind of right like right you
Yeah, what is that like like?
Like I try to run into him do people love that sound on the mic
That works yeah, I'm not gonna do that that reads that's awesome, but yeah, so this weekend I
My brother got married
Patrick's brother. Congratulations. Yeah. Thank you. Yeah, your brother. Yeah. No, it was a lot of fun. And where was it it was
somewhere in New Hampshire
What's the exact address sure it was one two three. You're about to say it on the podcast
Yeah, no is what it was in New Hampshire though it was really fun
Yeah, I like highlight number one
Honestly, the DJ was like really great. He was this sort of like
Like a really annoying Italian guy, but he was so friendly and handsy with all the women there. That's cool
Yeah, did he like runs? That sounds like a nightmare. Yeah. No, it was really great. No all the everyone
like
What do you think handsy means? I think he's grabbing the girls, but no no
He's like leading them around he's like showing them where he's high-fiving them. He's using his hands. That's what hands
I feel like he's doing ASL hands. He has a very different association than no, but New Hampshire means something different waving your hands around
Yeah, no, he just was very handsy like waving his hands around
Your coastal elitism is showing right now jazz hands. Mmm. Yeah, you know left to right hands, right?
Hey, oh
He was catching a lot of stuff - have you guys have you guys been to a wedding yet?
I'm gearing up for a wedding this weekend. No kidding. Where you going?
Upstate New York, that's very nice. I'm best man. No kidding. I got a cam. It's amazing. It's amazing
And what's crazy is that I do not know the guy that's awesome. Cameron does not have you ever met him
Yeah, all I mean sort of like it sounds kind of like it's kind of like a magical like thing, you know
Yeah, it's gonna be kind of like I appear in a portal right I jump out after a little spell
I did a runescape chalk draw sir. Okay. Yeah, and I hop out. I forgot how much cam plays runescape. It was great
Yeah, it was a great game. Did you play 2007 or do you play like the new one?
You stumped me. There's two there's two there's two editions of runescape that are out right now. There's one being maintained
I'm getting I'm getting the somebody's giving me the waving me off signal
What is runescape? I don't know. You ever played runescape? It was like a free-to-play MMO that was around
Oh, is that where you're like an ear? So Patrick's a lot older than you guys
I played runescape hard. Yeah, yeah. I've heard of it. I went to the trading grounds. Mm-hmm
That place I got I would trade my mind
materials
For weaponry. I mean that's like I feel like that's like real life though and Romeo and Juliet were weirdly a part of it. Whoa
Okay, I'm in yeah always the Alex what did you?
I just forgot
I love that guy. That's a blow dude. Yes. Yeah, Caleb. What did you what are you?
Are you going to wedding this weekend? Also? No, I went to a wedding
Huh, this dude does not know. Oh, I don't know what you don't know the people getting married. Oh, yeah
I've never met them either. Yeah, you're going this weekend or you're not going no, I'm not I
Caleb doesn't know the people getting married. Well small wedding - yeah, no small wedding. That's nice 50
Oh, yeah, that's great. Hey Patrick. How big was your buddy?
patches his wedding
Yeah, it was about a hundred and
50 ish people or that's big. It was pretty big. I mean we had kids there
So they had kids there so like kind of you were there - yeah, I was there - I cut my whole arm
on that and I still have a scar and patches patches uh keeps telling me it
looks cool but he actually just feels really bad that I hurt myself. It's scary
that your wound hasn't healed yet. It is scary. Your roommate Alex is kind of
concerned. Yeah no yeah no I've been talking to Alex about that and patches
has also been like a little bit concerned but like doesn't know how to
express it. It's not really their the way that they're you know they love each
other but it's not how they're friends. Maybe when you come back from your trip
you'll it'll be healed. Oh yeah I can't wait to see my girlfriend. Yeah it's pretty
exciting you must be having fun right now. Yeah I'm having a lot of fun. Where
are you guys? We're in modern technology bro. We can be anywhere.
Bro. Yeah this I am I remember doing like like when there was Skype and then Skype
Skype stopped being a thing. I don't know how that happened.
Yeah, Skype got fucked.
What happened? Do you guys know?
Skype? Zoom, bro.
I think Zoom took over, yeah.
Was it really just Zoom? That's not how shit... Shit doesn't just happen like that.
The pandemic. Zoom got the... 'Cause Skype, I don't think, had the... Skype didn't have
the big conference capabilities.
Oh.
So Zoom took it and just fucked it up.
What was the other one?
I think someone owned Skype, too.
Like a company?
I think it's like a Facebook kind of...
Billy's Skype.
- Get someone.
(laughing)
A guy.
- Skippy Skype.
- Skippy Skype, yeah.
- Jeff on Zoom.
- Jeff, yeah, Jeffy.
- Man's a freak.
- Yeah, but what are you,
wait, I was, sorry, what are you doing this,
what'd you do last weekend?
Or what are you doing this weekend?
That was the question.
- This weekend?
What is Caleb doing this weekend?
What's today, Tuesday?
Wednesday.
- Tuesday, Tuesday, Tuesday, Tuesday, Tuesday.
- I don't know what I'm doing this weekend.
Might hang out.
- I feel like you haven't seen yourself
like two weeks. Yeah I don't know. I don't know what the fuck is happening. I don't know.
I don't know what I'm doing. My friend from high school just moved to New York. Oh that's
awesome. I'll probably do something with him. Is he cool or? Can we say names? Yeah I think
we can drop the yeah a little bit drop the with yeah yeah absolutely who cares I
meant like other people's names you say they usually say my friend Eric just
moved here so probably nice that's awesome yeah no I feel like anyone who's
like still listening like no like doesn't got the drop off rate is just
enjoy yeah it's just enjoying us talking for some yeah you open up the podcast
yeah hey what's going on five minutes of strangers talking yeah you're still here
thanks for sticking around. You're a real fan. Yeah, we are gonna do a list if you
like, if like, while you listen to this is lists. No we're not. We're saving it for the end.
We're saving it for the end. We're absolutely, I want. We're gonna get five minutes left and we're gonna pound it out super fast. Oh yeah, no it's gonna be great.
But yeah, that's awesome. Why did Eric move here? Is he in trouble? I don't know. I
hope not. He, I think he wanted to move here for a while and then just did it.
Everyone wants to move to New York these days and it did not help that the deal went bad. Yeah, and all the deal went bad
Yeah
Antonio is after him. No kidding. And you know how Antonio gets you do not want to get on his bad side
Oh my god, Antonio
The thing about Antonio is you don't want to get on his bad side, but even on his good side
He's like also kind of like yeah, you know what I mean?
It's like it's like ah like stop like, you know player cards wrong. You're gonna get fucked, right?
It's like you feel like you feel like he's keeping a mental ledger of everything that's going on. Yeah, so it's like well
What is the good side always calculating? Yeah, he's always running the numbers. It's always buying me drinks
He's getting me lap dances, but I'm like, okay, but when am I gonna like look at you wrong?
Yeah, then I'm gonna have to like hear about it late or like when am I gonna touch like your girl?
Like you didn't tell me that this was your girl, right? Yeah, exactly
Yeah, it's like and like and that's and that's annoying because he has so many girls
Yeah, when we go to pumps you expect to have some freebies, you know exactly but he's like he's like no, that's my girl
That's my girl. That's my girl and it's like all right. It's like you can't just call dibs on every fucking whore in this club. Yeah
It's not cool
It's not and he does and I get why he does that because of like the thing that happened with his mom and like yes
Her knees very
It's pretty brutal. Have you ever been to a strip club?
Patrick I don't know
Patrick, yes. Me, no way. I've never been, no. I would just get way too horny, so I can't
go to the strip club. Yeah, it's fair. I have such a big, fat penis that it would just burst
out and then I would get in trouble. Mine's small and shit, but I wouldn't, it's not for
me. I think it would still burst out though. Yeah, it would still burst out though. No,
I've never been, I don't think I've had any, I would go to like meet people maybe. Sort
like hang out yeah otherwise I mean I would give I don't know like I don't
want to be like I want to be like it's weird to do this like I think the strip
clubs kind of an all-or-nothing I don't want to go there and then be like oh I'm
I'm a nice guy I don't want to fucking do that you could maybe do that if you
went to one in like Atlanta where that's like a big club you know the food is
renowned yeah exactly yeah like that would be kind of use no bed as the food
is so what was I supposed to go one other restaurant 1000 wing stops or
naked what what what and I suppose so eat these with my clothes on but yeah
it's like you know how you feel bad after watching porn something like you
like that when you finish. No, I feel good. I do feel bad. I'm not gonna lie to you and
tell you I feel good. I was raised Catholic. I could not imagine the shame of like leaving
a strip club just after like an hour and a half. I don't know. Maybe. I know it's like
it's one of those things where it's like I don't know like what the right opinion is
to have kind of thing but like I don't really care. You know I'm not I'm not even gonna
focus on what's right and what's wrong. Yeah. I just think it's hot. Right, wrong, who gives
As long as I'm getting off. I wanna see some pussy. I do want to see pussy
Hmm, I would like to see pussy. What is like the minute though like when you're at a strip club
What do you think that second minute or when when you're like?
Yeah
You should keep going I'm just like when you're just like let's go like oh, yeah, this is it
Oh, yeah, I'm gonna be clear
I feel like if I was in a strip club like it would take like I think it would be like a minute
I'd be like oh geez and like
and then like
I don't know if I could simply continue to wear a wedding rose.
I'm gonna be on the bed.
I don't know.
But yeah, then after a minute of that kind of thing, I think I'd be like, yeah!
I think I would just immediately, I think I'd be, 'cause it's like, what are you, again,
like, what are you gonna do, like, go there and be like, oh, I don't, I don't know if this is for me.
Yeah, fuck you.
I think the only thing worse, like, fuck you.
The only thing worse than going to a strip club is being a guy at a strip club who's like,
like I don't actually agree with yeah right please go yeah fuck you man I'm
exactly that's what I mean it's get away from my wife yeah get away from my get
away look at my wife get away from my wife bro his wife chased him in there
you shouldn't get away that's the most fun GTA game when you go in the strip
when you go to the strip club and you try to touch her boobs and then the
bouncer like looks in every five seconds and then you have to stop. It's pretty fun.
I never did that. You never did that? I've only played GTA. So growing up, growing up we're very strict on like my my my dad was an
extremely unfortunately very thoughtful about like you can play M games like
God of War because it's fantasy and like it's not real. You can't play COD
Because like that looks scary like it's recruiting you. Yeah, and so he's a fucking nerd and so like GTA
He was like, I do not want you to play
and so like I
Had that and so I only played it at like friends houses
Yeah
and so I never experience I didn't experience that like that moment where like
Cuz I was like when you steal a car for the first
I definitely feel I don't feel I don't feel robbed. I'm okay, but I do feel like like oh man
That sounds that sounds first of all hysterical. It was pretty lit. You know I mean also it is kind of it's a weird thing
I mean especially the age that I am mmM. It was the first 37 yeah
It was the first when I was like when I was like 28. It was the first time I ever like saw
Pretty sick. Do that's like so young to see boobs though. That's amazing. Yeah, I mean
They are incredible.
Mad Fientist Yeah, I saw boobs when I was a zero dude.
Justin: First time I saw boobs I was...
Mad Fientist Really?
Justin: I think I was like...
Mad Fientist I've never seen my mom's boobs.
That's weird.
Mad Fientist Wow, I feel bad for you dude.
Justin Why?
Mad Fientist First time I saw boobs was at the Museum of
Modern Art.
Like in person.
Justin Oh, that's a great place.
In person?
Mad Fientist Yeah.
Justin Who?
What happened?
Mad Fientist They were doing...
It was like a performance art thing and you had to walk into...
Justin Sex!
Mad Fientist To walk into the exhibit.
There were two people...
Justin It's too like...
- Like, do you know how most people fucking?
Oh son, it's just performance art.
- Yeah, my dad--
- We're gonna go.
- My dad left me outside the museum.
I saw a bum fucking another bum.
Oh my god, his boobs!
It's just a fat bum.
(laughing)
It was awesome.
- But yeah, it was like a performance art thing,
and that's--
- And you had to walk through a doorway,
and it was really skinny,
'cause two naked people were on either side.
- Ugh.
- Oh my god.
- I was like, "Yeah, this is cool."
(laughing)
I was like, "No problem."
time I saw like nudity in person was my my grandparents accidentally took took me
and my brother to a nude beach oh okay and it's kind of cool when you open with
grandmother I thought that you're snow that's nightmare that's worse case
I've done that. You have? Done it! Next! Give me my aunt.
Give me my aunt. Dad I love your family. But yeah that was that was like it was
mostly like just kind of I mean like I don't know if I had like the the
framework to call it this but it was surreal in that I was like I've never
like looking at like a dick flopping around you're just like like you know
there's no way to like you're like five there's no way in the real like
interpreting that like in any normal way like in any like like I'm not aghast a
A soft dick is not that.
Okay, you're not gay.
Cool.
We get it.
A soft penis is pretty inoffensive, I feel like.
A soft dick?
Yeah.
Like, I feel like if I'm in a room full of just a bunch of soft penises, I'm like, not
that worried about it.
Right, yeah.
Me too.
Alex, I mean, whatever.
Are you ever worried about being in a, like, if you were in a room full of soft penises,
would you be like me and Joe and not be worried about it?
Well, it depends on the context, of course.
Locker room, I don't think so, but yeah, I think it'd be fun if I woke up in the middle of night
What if those your friends though, yeah, I was all your friends yeah, and they said happy birthday, all right, then that would be cool
Yeah, you're also all right. And then then that's my god. I've been sleeping buck. You said that though
They said it's interesting recently. I don't have an AC. How is it? It's great. I've got nervous
About what? I don't know. I think I've accepted that like if someone in a window across from me is gonna see me naked
They're gonna see me naked. I'm not that oh, it's not even that it's like a it's like a
Supernatural concern that makes no sense. I'd never lived alone before and I think
You wouldn't understand I see things I go ghost I
Get that though, you know, but but I think that's probably very comfortable though. It's incredibly comfortable just a fan on me, too
Just get a little oscillation going. Yeah
Feel every inch from my toes to my head. I don't usually sleep naked, but when I have done it I it is very comfortable
I'm like, oh, this is great. I just love my pajamas. I don't know
I love in comfy clothes and like settling in but the thing I don't like about a pajamas
You put them on and then you sweat yeah
I don't want my like the butt of my pajamas to be sweaty because then I'm just gonna be trapped in like a little
Little swamp blanket. Yeah, I guess that's true - I like to sleep cold though. Well. You don't have an AC
That's what that's what's happening. That's rough man. I just might do you have a yeah
Do you put one in your window or anything?
No, I need to I need to like procure one really do but it is scorched or the supper
Yeah, I want to get the you have you seen the you sorry the you yeah
Yeah, you close the window down on the middle of it.
The letter?
Did you see the letter U?
It's really cool.
No, wait, what do you mean?
So it's like a...
You shut your window and the box is...
It has a U, so there's a small sliver at the bottom.
So the control panel goes down, you shut the window down on the whole thing, so you're
not like...
Oh!
That's nice.
It's pretty sick.
Yeah, because I have a lot of shitty memories of being in this stupid city and like trying
to like get one in the window and it falling out.
Whoa, that's happened to you? It's fallen out of the window?
Yeah, but it was on the first floor.
Oh, that's still crazy though.
Did it hit like a small person?
It hit like a small cat.
It hit a bug. Did it break when that happened?
No, it didn't, which I was very concerned about.
AC is pretty sturdy.
AC is very sturdy and my wife does not know about that.
And so she'll never listen to this though, so we'll be okay.
She doesn't know that they're sturdy.
No, I dropped the AC once.
Oh, you still use it?
She also has no idea that the AC is hurting.
And we're going to keep that between us, okay?
All right, boys.
Please cut that out, bro.
Yeah, yeah, please.
I really don't want that knowledge getting out there.
It is a weird thing. Like, I didn't notice until I moved into the place I live now.
Yeah.
And then this guy put my AC in for me.
Oh, that's nice.
By the way.
No problem.
But I did that happen and then I just was thinking about ACs a lot.
Why just cuz it was a big ordeal and also my girlfriend at the time
I put her AC into like the same week and then I helped Neil put his AC in so it's like a big AC week
Wow, I just was walking around looking and it's crazy that uh
Just they don't fall out of windows more and kill. Yeah. I know cuz you look at that everywhere
You're thinking like structurally this doesn't make sense. I did not do a good job putting in Neil or
My girlfriend's one and say her name
Say her name
Cameron Diaz. Oh my God.
You hit that bro? Yes, I did.
This dude's dick got her out of retirement, bro.
All right. I think it's time for the list.
Sure.
If these guys have made it through this.
That's crazy.
Oh yeah, they deserve a list.
Just talking about A/Cs.
Yeah, we're just hanging out.
Okay.
Sorry, sorry, sorry to the boys. We tried.
Yeah.
We're not lost yet. No, I don't think so. I guess. Nah, nah. We're screwed. So yeah,
you're the cam. So, okay. Okay, list time. We got this list from the top 10s, our favorite website.
And the list is top 10 worst things to be magically turned into. Okay. You know,
kind of surprised that this list hasn't been hit yet. Maybe it has. And we don't know that.
Oh, yeah shit. I mean we're doing um
But I feel like I think you guys will like that though. Yeah, this is gonna be a fresh take on this list
Before this is a by Fremantle Dockers with a profile
Heart he's
classified top-secret Australia from
Australia. Here's his TBH, I'm not going to be active here. The winner of the best
music genre tournament is rock and roll. Favorite artist, this is all in his bio.
Oh wow. Alphabetically and songs from each. And he goes on the list upwards of.
That's cool for someone to not be active. And there's a giant Yoshi image. This is for Yoshi
dude. If you want a copy, go ahead. This guy's very, this guy seems very sweet. He's a cool guy.
I'm very excited to see his list. The idea of magic is totally awesome, but the idea of magic being used against you
It's totally not awesome. Correct. One prime example slash stereotype of magic is the power of turning an object into something else
Which again may sound very awesome, but you wouldn't want that power being used against you
Mm-hmm. So without further ado, here's some of the very worst objects that you could ever turn into. Okay
This guy's favorite Michael Jackson song is beat it
That seems standard. That's his favorite song his favorite Michael Jackson song beat it. I think it's a great song. What would you pick? I
Wouldn't pick beat it either I'm picking ABC
Well, but that's like is that that's Jackson 5 though. That's pre-corruption though. Yeah, it is white freaker
Before I went to the light side bro. Mm-hmm. I would pick
Yes, yes, all right number one on the list is
Toilet would not want to be a toilet the toilet not only you have to grab
You know what and forced to be sat by people it'll be very boring standing in the bathroom restroom all day
I think that's the probably the problem with any
Stationary object you can't move around can't move around you have to grab. You know what's though. I don't know how toilets are really doing
It would be it wouldn't be bad being like a toilet in like a cool like have you seen those like
Things like and a millionaires like crazy thing where it's like the toilet is like moving
You get rich enough right? Yeah, you know what I mean? Like I feel like I know like so far
I don't like a bidet toilet. No, like I saw someone on Instagram
I know posted like a thing where they're sitting in a bathroom in the window. There was a window in front of it
That one so you're saying a toilet with a view not so bad. Yeah, you got toilet
I mean if you had to be a toilet, I would want to be a toilet with the view. Mm-hmm
Yeah, don't think that's crazy. It's a great comment number two. Yuck. I would not appreciate people rubbing their butt on me. Thank you
Ginger for PS I would vote poop too, but I don't have enough votes
- Thanks for letting us know.
- I didn't even know you could live in on boats.
- Did not know that was a limited resource.
Yeah, I mean, I think the real downside of the toilet
is piss and shit. - Poopy.
- And butts.
- Oh my gosh. - Dirty butts.
- Butts I think is the least of my worries.
Butts, I guess, is very good. - The shit is the worst part.
- And I guess you're eating it too.
- Are you eating it?
- Well, so the image-- - Why are you assuming
that's your mouth?
I guess I'm-- - I think that--
- Is that the mouth? - I think out of anything
to be the mouth, I would assume that is.
- I mean, I guess like any drawing I've seen
of a toilet-- - It's your asshole.
- A toilet with eyes on it?
- It's the mouth and then you have to talk, yeah.
- That makes sense to me.
- Honestly, if I'm a toilet that can talk
and look around and stuff, I'm probably--
- Please don't shit in me.
- Hey, stop it.
(laughing)
- Hey, knock it off, pal.
- Right?
- That's how a toilet would talk, right?
- Really, you're only wiping twice?
Come on, dude, sit down more.
Wipe more, bro.
- You're a freak.
- Shit in me.
- I mean, honestly, if I was a toilet,
I'd probably be into it at a certain point.
- You kind of have to.
- You have to be, right?
- You pass the breaking point.
- Yeah, that's sort of--
(laughing)
- Yes!
- Hey, buddy!
- Woo!
- But Marge, I don't wanna be a toilet.
Please, I don't wanna pee and poop in me
from someone else's body,
especially if they smear it all over me.
Yeah, I mean, people--
- Do you guys ever put down,
do you guys put down the toilet paper
when you go to a public toilet or no?
- I almost never see these public toilets.
- Oh, really?
- Not for poop.
- That's pretty nice.
I'm of the belief that my butt,
the butt that sits on the toilet seat is not that dirty.
- Yeah, I'm in your camp.
- So I'm not really that worried.
- Like other people's butts aren't that dirty?
- I don't think that the thing
that the toilet ring sits on is that dirty.
Because I don't consider my piece, my ass and stuff,
like my surrounding ass. - Your ass piece.
- My little ass piece.
I don't consider that to be filthy dirty.
- I don't even know if it's a dirty thing.
Like I just don't want it to be like touching somewhere where someone else's but yeah, I'll give it a read
You know, I'm very much like in the belief of like people
I mean, I and I keep my my shit very very clean
but I also do believe in but I do believe that like things are more sanitary than we
Act like they are at least in the United States. It's like most shit is like
Pretty clean relatively speaking a gas station. I'll throw it like a shitty gas station. I'll throw down some paper
Do you guys wash your hands when you use like bathrooms at like bars?
Well, I got the of you like a dirty bar or a dirty gas station if you pee do you wash your hand?
Yes, every time I almost never if I'm not like a bar and I'm going in the covert era
You're not washing your hands after using I just don't I try I'll roll up the sleeves or something and just try not to touch
As a little as possible. I just feel like my touching your penis though
Well, my penis is cleaner than whatever that been touching those faucets. You know, I mean, okay, that's what you mean
door knob um generally I just touch this because you know what you touch the
fucking thing and you wash your hands and I guess you're touching it off do it
after you wash your hands to turn it off I think about that and then you opening
the door again I think I have like gangrene or something everything's a
read get yourself checked out if the sink is nice enough I'm gonna wash in
the sink mm-hmm full body yeah number two is pinata pinata is based on llamas
- May look cute, but if someone tried beating you up
with a weapon in a game,
that would have been extremely painful.
- Clearly this guy has never been to battle.
- Ow, ouch, stop hitting me with that.
That's what you'd be thinking as your insides spill out
and you take your last look at the world.
It would be last breath, but well,
I don't think pinatas can breathe.
- So this one brings up a very good thing,
which is if you are being transformed into a new object,
you probably want to go out pretty quick.
That is true.
And I think the pinata is kind of giving you that quick out.
The question is here too, I guess in this case we're assuming you have nerve endings,
like you're feeling all this stuff, right?
And once your body breaks open, you're probably dead.
Okay, yeah.
Right?
I mean it doesn't make sense.
Or it's a slow death and you're just on the ground like...
Yeah, you're ripped in half like a chicken.
Yeah.
It's like if you turn into a pinata, just imagine all these kids beating you with sharp
objects such as baseball bats until they finally slice you in half for candy.
Pinata there's some joy involved though and maybe the factory you're in all the
other pinatas are also sentient. You're giving joy to people. Yeah. I'm thinking about a Viva
pinata. Were they scared that they were pinatas or were they like was that game
trying them trying to... I have no idea what that is. I didn't play the game but... You know what I'm
talking about. I know exactly what you're talking about. Viva pinata. You ever play Viva pinata for
Xbox no I'm pretty much pretty much I think it's a flea yeah sports video
games oh really never really got into this shit where it is a sport you're
waiting Madden or FIFA or what MLB the show NBA 2k no shit pretty good
showing did you play NFL 2k5 I played NFL 2k2 I got in the bargain no kidding
game stop when I was a kid k5 was unbelievable I've made the I made the
like convicts and the police guards from the longest yard I custom made all the
different players oh that's right I would just play as Nelly and cheeseburger Eddie
and I would beat the guards is anybody else falling asleep I think some people
would relate to that I think anybody who's still listening would relate to
that I feel like once we got to the list I'm feeling people can people came back
We'll start it off in the list. Yeah. All right. Number three, food. You get chewed on
by someone, go into their body, come out as you know what, and then get flushed
down the toilet. Sorry, this is gross, but that's what would happen if you were a
Super Mario fan. I would love to be food. Yeah. Are you kidding me? Again, it depends on the food. I would
like it if I could be like a pig and I could live the life of being a pig and
- That's a different thing.
- And then dying and turned into food.
- That's a pig though, that's not food.
- Well pigs can be our food sometimes, you know?
- I guess, yeah, it depends on your definition.
- But if I'm like, that's a bunch of bags of chips,
I wouldn't wanna be a bag of chips.
- Well people are not--
- Especially around this guy.
- I love chips.
- Oh, he does love chips. - Just devour some chips.
- Dude, honestly, that would be fucking terrifying.
Like to be a tiny little bag of chips
and you're like, crushing.
(laughing)
I'd be like, you would not wanna be
buttered popcorn around me, I'll tell you that right now.
- I don't even wanna be around you
you're eating butter pop. Peanut says hmm I'm not sure if I would like this or not.
So the jury's out for him. Yeah I think he's probably not given one of his
precious votes up to this one then. At least he would smell good. Imagine being
eaten by a hot girl. Hmm. That's what somebody said. Be a banana. Oh my god I
I would love that. Your last moments. Peanut. That's such a good username. Peanut. Let's take a trip down
Peanut's road. Yeah, go to Peanut. Hi, I'm Peanut, currently on a hiatus right now.
His favorite song is Summer of 69 by Bryan Adams. Great song. And his favorite movie is the
Spongebob Squarepants movie. His favorite actor is Tom Kenny. His favorite cartoon
character is Spongebob Squarepants his favorite TV show is Spongebob
Squarepants it's a cartoon a sponge bus current Squarepants his favorite food is
french fries his favorite youtubers mr. beast mr. B's pretty cool guy I like
this guy yeah he's and his favorite actress of course Ellen DeGeneres so
he's an ally pretty cool guy just really fucking dig Spongebob you know it doesn't
number nine is tampon oh I don't know and Yoshi Yoshi dude who we heard about
earlier on the profile Yoshi dude Wow asked what is a tampon oh and then
discord one responds with you don't want to know clearly wants to know okay I
don't know either though yeah it's nasty you don't want to know
- There's four people that don't know what a tampon is.
- People really are not into the idea of a tampon.
I feel like no one's even having the fun in--
- God no!
How is this not number one?
I'd rather be turned into a toilet than a tampon.
Yuck, yuck, yuck, yuck, yuck, yuck.
- That's five capital yucks.
Yuck, yuck, yuck.
This should be number one for those who left a comment
saying what it is.
You do not, or who's saying--
- Yeah, no, you read that right, unfortunately.
- Okay, there we go.
You do not want to know.
Because when you think about being turned into what a tampon is, eww, how is it not in the
top ten?
I would hate that.
I'd rather be turned into a toilet.
Seriously, how is it not number one?
I would not be.
These people are so dramatic.
I feel like tampon, there's the funny thing of like, well, at least you're going to a
pussy.
Right, at least you're going to a hoo-ha.
That's right.
I mean, I wouldn't love it because that shit is stinky.
I wouldn't love it because yuck, yuck, yuck, yuck.
Eww, God, no.
But being in a pussy is pretty cool.
What if you were that tampon that uh...
A toilet?
That sucks.
You're just getting poop in your...
Yeah, that'd be a tampon.
What if you were the tampon that that girl ate?
You remember that video?
The girl like sucks the blood off her tampon?
No, I don't watch.
What is that?
That was like in high school.
Is that a life time?
No, it was um...
I feel like that's not that crazy.
I can't remember.
It was like a viral video.
But yeah, it was like a girl just like has her tampon and then like...
She eats it or like sucks it or something?
I would hope she just sucks it.
Some shit.
I don't know.
It's awesome number four is bubble which I think is pretty cute. I'd be a bubble
This is one of the only items on this list on
This rather not very funny list. I'm willing to vote
There is certain way bathroom whom humor can be executed and the other entries are how you don't
Fucking inscrutable just absolutely
I was waiting for it to make sense
This is one of the only items on this rather not very funny list. I'm willing to vote. Okay, kind of clear
Yeah, there is a certain way bathroom humor can be executed and the other entries are how you don't do it
Oh, I do get it now. Okay, it's very clear. I might read your read blue my mind
I think on this website you kind of anticipate
Yeah, fucked up Graham. I think it's yeah
I was there's there's there is a lot of like sort of pop last thing I see is a kid's finger
You will die very quickly you will die in eight seconds Liam coaster fan
Should we take a trip down Liam coaster fan? Yeah, absolutely do it. Oh
My god, this message is super important. Please do not ignore this message and read it the whole way through
Do not take this message lightly. Please don't bully me for this
I'm trying to help you by saying this long message God and Jesus are real
For our sins and rose from the dead true. There's bad news and good news
Okay, what's a good news? I'm not gonna read the whole thing. Oh, hey guys, I'm Liam an elevator enthusiast
You may think this is an odd interest, but I have had it since I was a kid
I film in elevators and post the videos on YouTube. I joined the site in 2020. I think it's pretty nice
People really like to put their favorite songs
Music is awesome. Dude. Tell me you don't like music
Okay, bubble pretty good one pretty guy be bubble. I'd be bubble
Any second of the day you're with a bunch of other bubbles, and then you're just done no bubble
I mean, I guess bubble on the quick death line. Yes, pretty smooth. Yeah, but bubble on the
Existence thing because you only are your your life is very short and well
That's cool, too
If you're a bubble that doesn't get popped and you get float up, but that gets popped eventually yeah
But then you get a nice little view I guess that could be terrifying -
you. I mean maybe you won't be alive long enough to really know, because it's the
minute the wizard turns you out, you're a bubble, and you're gone. The wizard
turns you out.
He fucks you, then he turns you to a minute fucks you're done. Yeah, the
many fucks you like you're going to be a bubble
spell on you. Your ass is going to be a bubble Frodo. That's pretty sick. This
So fucking twisted I'm about to make you a bubble boy dark. We like the wizard scrolling this list to figure out what to do
Punching bag punching bag is a stupid one. That is stupid. So you can hit it's like yeah, but you're you're putting your blue
You're indestructible. Yeah, it's not a problem. It feels good probably and people are wearing boxing gloves
139 is a thong which is the dumbest thing I've ever heard. Of course you want to be a thong
deodorant.
Oh, toilet paper, that's pretty rough.
Deodorant.
No, no, no.
I don't want to rub off my skin onto some smelly kid's armpits.
That does suck.
That's a slow death.
Just a little off the top.
But you could be, I feel like I have a couple sticks of Dio that are kind of lost to time.
You know, they just kind of roll to the bottom of the bag.
Oh, I didn't even think about that.
Maybe you get a-
So you can just kind of hang out.
You get a nice little Toy Story life.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, we didn't even think about that.
These guys like Toy Story guys.
Are they, are we, are you alive and moving around?
- That's what I'm saying, like do you have friends?
Like do you have like an inner life?
Like do you have, like if you're a toilet,
which we all agree on this list, it's number one, right?
- Yeah.
- I think toilet paper is worse than toilet.
- Toilet paper is definitely worse than toilet.
- 'Cause you get flushed down,
but you get to meet new people that way.
- I think being,
I guess that's true.
I'm not someone who typically wants to die.
Like I don't have that at all.
- No, me neither, I love life.
So I would like to be a solid object that stands.
Yeah, I would love to be...
The test of time.
Yeah.
So a toilet is better than...
I'd love to be a diamond.
A diamond would be pretty sick.
So the wizard, if he's really trying to, like, fuck you up, he's probably not gonna let Toy
Story rules apply.
I see.
Is he just trying to fuck you up or is he trying to teach you a lesson?
Is this a wizard?
I think that the whole conceit of it is magic.
Oh, right.
The idea of magic is totally awesome.
But is it like a funny, like, thing?
I forgot.
Of course the idea of magic is totally awesome, but I'm gonna not is it okay funny thing
So this is a way to get a funny is it a wizard like you know
It's just like a light-hearted romp or is it like a scary?
Who is this wizard if the idea of magic being used against you is the cut right?
But sometimes that happens to teach you a lesson Joe is assuming if there's an agent using magic against you in this case
It's a wizard. I'm just trying to get my yeah
I mean, I don't know where the magic is coming from if there isn't some sort of a wizard. Yes, okay fine
So the what are we who do we who is this?
So this wizard is trying to fuck with us is well
Is there a way to turn yourself back into a part like let's say what if it's like an uh?
Quest like a nine lives with Kevin Spacey situation
Yeah
You're into a cat turn to a cat and he has to get back to Christopher Walken
So he turns him he could turn into a human
Yeah, so he can be back in time to make the deal exactly with the Japanese. Yeah, is it like that?
Well does he make a deal with the Japanese in that movie?
I think he's probably a businessman who needs to shake a hand at the end of the movie, but
I know but it's crazy that like it was still the Japanese in like 2009. I'll level with
you. I have not seen the movie. I believe it's a Japanese though. I do believe. I feel
like a lot of people were stuck with thinking that you're gonna make business deals with
the Japanese. It was a very strange time for sure. It was very much. What's that in? That's
in click yes to do that right? I think click yes, I think it's a Japanese also. Yeah and
definitely a lot of jokes just on the level of like these guys don't have a clue what's
actually going on. It's just like being like, "Yes, of course."
Yeah, just thinking it's a regular business deal.
Yeah, because that's how it goes.
That's a funny joke in some movie where it's like that and then they're just like, "We
can speak English." It's funny.
Is that it from a movie?
I think it's got to be. If it's not...
That's a funny joke from a movie.
It's probably in a movie.
That's facts. But I think of a wizard... I feel like if I were a wizard, I would feel
feel very bad about turning people into stuff. I think I would. But I think the
kind of eternal being thing, maybe you just need to do some stuff to. So this is
an eternal wizard. This is like the third assumption you've made. So wizards also
live forever. I'll put the story together in my head. Yeah. If you're a wizard, the
first spell you're casting is an invincibility spell. Right. As far as I'm
concerned. It's eternal life and eternal youth. Because there's that Greek myth
about that guy who had eternal life but he didn't have eternal youth. And he
decomposed. Well then you get the other the twist side of the kid who became
eternal or whatever as a kid and then all his friends die and he's still a
little boy. And he sits in the chair. Fuck that shit! You get to live forever! Who cares?
You make new fucking friends! Yeah but I mean. You have the capacity to love so many
people. I feel like I'd also maybe turn some people into eternal beings or are
you so poisoned by the fact that you have to live this eternal life you think
bit as a curse. So the idea of turning the love of your life into an eternal being
as well is the cruelest act you could possibly do. So you turn her into a
toilet instead. So you turn her into a toilet and shit in her. Which will be destroyed soon.
You turn into a bubble and you pop her. Yeah I'd love to pop a woman. I'll be honest I
got I got lost in there. We're just setting up the backstory.
Okay so we are now operating under the assumption that this is a
a wizard and we are in the love of his life and this is him trying to not have
us exist right no no he's trying to okay so is he so it's a he so we know if it's
a wizard it's a boy and a girl it's true that's facts I'm stupid it's a warlock
Warlock is also a boy.
I'm just kidding.
It's a gay wizard, he's right.
I do the D&D stuff.
Warlock, what is warlock properly?
A warlock is like an evil
like wizard.
In D&D it's a warlock
consorts with a
patron. But I don't know
what a technical warlock is
outside of the Forgotten Realms.
So all warlocks
are wizards but not all wizards are warlocks.
potentially. Let me look this up. In my head a warlock is like a wizard troll.
So Miriam Webster says a man practicing the black arts.
Oh, that's so... The black arts. Yeah, that's a little... I don't know Miriam Webster.
So like Basquiat. Yeah, Jean-Michel Basquiat, the OG warlock. A warlock is a
male practice. It's of witchcraft specifically. So wizardry is using magic,
right? Witchcraft is using like devil's magic. Huh. And a warlock is a guy who
does devil magic. So I would assume that someone doing this is probably ranging
on the territory of dark arts. No, dark arts is like, uh, like you're a devil guy.
You don't think that turning someone into a fart is a dark art? Polymorphing isn't
Necessarily a dark art. Yeah, it's like it's polymorphing. I thought that was when it's yourself not other stuff
No, you can polymorph other people when I think like turning someone into something
I think like a like Disney like zap and then right baby. Bobby boo. Yeah
Turning someone into anything is always gonna be on the magic side of stuff
Feels like a slippery slope depends on the thing. Yeah a good point
I'd say most of this stuff pretty is basically how Nazi Germany happened, right? It was like something like this
this. I don't know. Farts. It was with first start with farts. Yeah,
I think if you first it came for the farts, then they came for
it. No, I think it's a good point that like maybe we should
like sort of take a step back and see is this guy a warlock
and not a wizard. Yeah, I think if we need to do anything we
need to take another step back as far as possible really. Yeah,
fart is another one is far another one. What does it say?
It doesn't say anything. That's a newcomer really, but I'm going
vote for it. I would say fart would be like nine votes remaining. Oh, wait,
there's a vote limit. Yeah. Okay. Just like the USA ash. Imagine being turned
into imagine being about to be turned into a beauty or a unicorn or any animal
or object of your choice. But the magic trick fails and you get cremated.
Justin Bieber. That's great. Justin. Justin Bieber is like, I would love to
be just to be there. I wish I was just a neighbor right now. I'm married to a
Baldwin that sounds fucking lit as fuck drums
That's kind of fair. It depends on the drum set if I'm if I'm you know
Frickin the killers drums, right? I think that'd be pretty cool
I'm the big so much condoms a booger you would be stuck in someone's nose and then sometimes eaten homework
Homework is cool, but then homework you get the camaraderie of a classroom adora DVD
That's interesting I think this list was made like like last year.
Mmm Kenny from South Park. That would be bad. That would be cool you get to come
back. Oh he does come back right. And you get to live in the magical town of South
Park. Donald Trump. As much as I love Kenny McCormick from South Park I really
wouldn't want to turn into him. Plus the idea of dying all the time would be
extremely painful. A Barney DVD. Give it up guys.
a Katy Perry ended 11 years ago and you are still complaining a Katy Perry album
would rather die depends on the album from person one two three four president
too much responsibility says McDonald's whoa
Donald says being president would be too much responsibility
Patrice Wilson a Nigerian American musician who is best known for being the
writer and producer of Rebecca Black's infamous song Friday. Oh,
that guy would want to be that guy that came drawing on I would
love to be Kim Jong. Are you fucking kidding me? I am Kim
Jong.
Dildo
Adolf Hitler porno magazine. Cockroach. Amber heard. That's
not funny. Once once you get into the sorry, sorry, sorry.
Once you get into the people, ooh, a Justin Bieber doll.
I guess Varg Vikernes I wouldn't want to be. P.
Who is Varg Vikernes?
He's a, well he's sort of one of the um
Oh my god you guys went so far.
Varg is one of the founders of Black Metal. He's part of the band um
Oh god what's that band called?
They had this singer Death and Varg would kill the guy and he's worse than this.
Burzum?
No it wasn't Burzum.
It was um. Oh he's a convicted murderer in our case.
Yeah he's a murderer.
Mayhem, Mayhem, Mayhem is the band.
And so he was in that band and it's part of the Norwegian black metal movement.
Everyone was burning churches.
Is that the one with the album cover was the picture of the dead guy?
Yes.
Pretty hardcore though.
Yeah, it's extremely hardcore.
Justin Timberlake.
I think any...
I would love to be Justin Timberlake.
Any person, pretty sick.
Isn't he married to Jessica Biel?
What is wrong with people?
A goomba.
A deer.
I don't know pac-man mud you really I can't fucking believe that it goes down
at 200 Sanjay from Sanjay and Craig by Craig I'm gonna give my votes to Sanjay
and Craig I would not want to be those guys gasoline glasses chef peepee
is
it's on
explain
he looks like the swedish chef but different
loses gay
will go to chef p p
and last on the list a criminal
while says something
really says something everyone wants to be a criminal no one wants to be a
toilet squidward's pretty low on the list
I feel like Squidward, I mean, any time that you're being asserted...
I would definitely not want to be Squidward.
I think actually Squidward...
Bro, the living, wicked bottom, bro?
Just me, I would honestly, I would be Squidward, I would step into the world and I would say,
"Hey, SpongeBob, we may have had our differences in the past, but I'm willing to look past
them."
That's a good point.
How many bubble in your damn face...
I wouldn't want to be Squidward if I had Squidward's personality.
But you're right, if I just became Squidward, I would patch things up with all the guys.
Yeah, I would look around and be like, "Wow, look at this beautiful town."
Look how lucky I am.
said than done you try working a shift at the Krusty Krab see if you don't want
to blow your brains out. That's true because Mr. Krabs is kind of a freaking jerk.
But if I'm able to afford A) a beautiful stone house. That's true. B) I'm able to take
my time and play my music and C) I'm able to do whatever else I do like bike
around on my little bike. He fucks kids. He forgot that he does that dude.
You did peanut you peanut probably pretty upset about this. Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry peanut
No, I don't know. I don't know cuz like I feel like Squidward is
Like definitely one of the most attractive characters
They have the entire South Park cast on this list I wouldn't want to be any of those kids
I think kidding me those kids have so much fucking fun. I think that's maybe to counteract the
The toilet humor they're saying like oh you think that's all funny. Well, I wouldn't want to be your favorite cartoon character
But I was sum it up. You know, I think I'm happy being myself
Caleb Michael Pitts
There's no name. I think Michael Pitts is an actor - right? I
Don't know Kyle Pitts is a football player. I think Michael Pitts is an actor or it's a Michael Michael Michael
Michael, then you're thinking of Brad Pitt. No, there's Michael Pitt Sean Penn not the game of Sean Penn. I never thought about Sean Penn
Chris Michael Pitt is an actor
PIT it's PITT
Drop the ID B. He was in that um Kurt Cobain
Thing I remember the montage of heck no
Documentary but last days last days
Gus Van Sant's last days
Haven't seen it. He was in funny games to remake. Oh
Is that the dude from boardwalk Empire? Yes. Yeah
He looks like a me Dharma D. He's like a young Leo kind of guy. Yeah
kind of like unfortunately like was
Around during that time and you know
Be he was good on
I remember watching all of Boardwalk Empire. This is a spoiler, but I stopped watching after his character died. No shit
You liked him that much. I just was like I didn't I wasn't I didn't love the show and I was just like I never watched
It I can't I get like kind of like turned off by like the the like
Dude, Scorsese, bro. I know but it's really good. I'm like, I don't want to do this again
It's a lot of another shit thing about people being like criminals. Yeah, it's like the Sopranos but like not as fun
Yes, I know like she's amazing which is you know, there's no real like levity to boardwalk
I'm really just kind of also I stopped watching it the soundtrack pretty good though. I've got some soundtrack saved
I feel like it's all like Eddie Cantor like they get like new artists to do old songs. No, really? Yeah
Got a couple saved like Beyonce does like um
Does ragtime?
Hello, my baby
is Michigan J frog. I'm a baby. I'm a honey. We sick you hear that new
Michigan J frog album. It's the same thing as looney tunes, but they just
say it's bouncing.
She does it at the super ball,
but I don't phone. I'll be sick
a queen bee. I don't do you think we should do? We should spare everybody
five minutes. I just I I have no conscious way of knowing how like I don't know
why. I think it was just us talking. Yeah I don't think there is a whole lot of. I
would not listen to this episode. I wouldn't listen. I probably would have
turned it off and I think we've had this conversation a few times. I think only
one other time on record. Yeah I mean like what were we gonna do? You know what I mean?
I mean we can you know we have ten minutes that might not be released. Should this be
the reflection the last five minutes. Yeah, this is us reflecting. We can go over the five
minutes too, because I'm like, let's do three hours. I mean, let's get real. So, you know,
they couldn't, they were having trouble coordinating their schedule because a lot of them, the three
guys are going to go away. You know, you guys know them, Caleb, Cameron, Patrick, and we
just thought we'd fill in. Actually, they thought we would fill in. Yeah. That's not.
Glad to do it. I think they... Yeah, absolutely. We love doing it. We love the fans. And we're
We're gonna be back every week. We're not going anywhere, guys.
I think this was just us hanging out. I'd be like, "Why would we?"
'Cause it's hard to try to do this. We can't be them.
We're not gonna pretend to be them. Yeah, no. We're just gonna be three guys.
I don't wanna be them. I'm happy as me.
On this list, who I wouldn't wanna be turned into?
Caleb, Cameron, Patrick. Honestly, I wouldn't want any of us to be
anyone but ourselves. That's right. Me too, man.
What's the lesson we learned from doing this?
Number 217 is giant hogweeds.
What is a hogweed?
I don't know.
I'm gonna look that up right now.
I know what hogwarts is.
I don't know what hogwarts is, man.
Come on.
You don't know what hogwarts is?
I'm just fucking kidding.
Okay, I almost lost my shit.
But yeah, no, I think I'd rather be a giant hogweed is a monocarpic perennial herbaceous
flowering plant in the carrot family Appia.
In the carrot family?
Appia...
I love carrots.
No cap.
Yeah, you know, I mean...
I had that bomb made.
I know, it looked really good.
I can't believe you didn't even give me a piece.
I ordered it.
What was that?
APACIORE.
There's no way that's how that's pronounced.
What is that?
Is that hogweed?
A P I A C E A E.
Okay, let me see.
Patches, what's your social security number?
Uh, 2 2 1 2 2 2 1 2 2 baby.
Do you guys have yours memorized?
I do have mine memorized.
I have mine memorized.
Of course.
Makes forms so much easier.
Yeah.
I got a pretty good one too.
I'm not going to say it, but it's a good one.
I think I have the numbers in my head, but they're out of order.
Mine is regular.
I got a couple repeated numbers in it.
Oh, that's very useful.
Yeah.
I'm going to go ahead and get my phone.
It's a good one.
I think I have the numbers in my head, but they're out of order.
I got a couple repeated numbers in it.
Oh, that's very useful.
Yeah.
Which narrows it down pretty good.
I don't.
You don't know your social.
I think I do.
I don't know my debit card.
If I put a gun to your head, you will not know your social.
I'm going to kill you.
I can probably.
What's the most damage you could do with someone's social?
Open a credit card, right?
Yeah, pretty much.
Yeah.
sign something. Yeah, I mean there's a lot of stuff you could do with this. Oh, for sure.
I mean, I would never give. I would never give. No, I would never give somebody my social...
that's a good point, Joe. I wouldn't do that. Where's my list, bro? I mean, if I fill in
a W-9, I'll have to, but other than that... Anytime I... because I do like freelance stuff.
Anytime I do that, I feel really like stupid. Oh, yeah, it's crazy. You're sending it over
email. You feel like a fucking chump. I'll take a screenshot of the number and send it
to someone. Oh, yeah. No, I have it not written down. It's not written down anywhere. My phone
or anything. I hate having to send it when we got our apartment just having to send that
to a guy. Yeah you feel fucking weird man. It's like a weird thing that like we all,
cause you hear all, I mean I don't know it's a little bit of boogeyman kind of shit. I
mean like I guess it's probably pretty bad to get your identity stolen but like I imagine
you could figure it out. Did you see the, there's like an ad that someone did, like
- Like it was like a protection company,
like we protect your shit or whatever.
- Okay.
- That's the whole thing.
So you pay them a monthly fee and they do it.
And the ad that they did was the CEO of the company.
And he was like, "This is my social security number."
And they gave out his actual social security number.
And like 10 people committed identity fraud against it.
Like the product did not work to stop it.
- That's crazy.
What was that product?
- Oh my God, what is that, Easy Bake Oven?
- Yeah, it was a strip club.
(laughing)
Identity theft company.
- It was like a--
- CEO.
- It was a guy, like the CEO of the general.
Just something that was--
(laughing)
- LifeLock.
- No shit.
- Oh, I've heard of that.
- Richard Todd Davis, also known as Todd Davis,
is the co-founder of LifeLock,
an American identity theft protection company
based in Tempe, Arizona.
I think this is him. Maybe it's not. What does he look like?
I would say
long skinny head.
Honestly he looks freaking freaky.
Long skinny.
He kind of looks like a combo.
He looks like a cop.
he does look like a cop
uh... now you know it's these people it i_d_ theft c_e_o_ you like you talk
about this good because i'm trying to crack and contract the story
uh...
weird
the uh... yes is blue
something
uh...
- He's crazy.
- Go see the pod guys on tour.
- Yes, please do.
- Subscribe to their Patreon and listen to Patches do D&D.
- Yeah, thank you.
Listen, go check out Home Planet.
If you haven't yet, you're an idiot
'cause they're very, very funny and we love them.
- Very cool.
And give us all love.
Suck our penis, love each other.
- Yeah, do that too.
- March 2018, I hit a man with my Honda Civic
and I was driving.
- All right, goodbye.
(laughing)