Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
- Premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- So we're deciding on what kind of episode
we want to do today.
- We've decided on one thing.
- We're gonna narrow it down.
- I'm gonna narrow it down
because I got something in my teeth.
- What was it that you said?
- Dental.
- Dental, okay, that's a veto from me.
I'm using my one veto immediately.
- Really, you're doing your bit,
you're doing your America's Got Talent X.
- Yeah.
- Or X Factor X.
I know not a dental on the X Factor do you use the X to get the person off the show
yeah and then you use the factor to get them on but wait don't they have an axe
on America's Got Talent? They have a golden buzzer. But what is the X where's the wait which show has
the X's where you X people X men that's America's Got Talent right or is that
the X Factor? The X Factor it's good if you get an X. But there's X's on
America's Got Talent too where if you get three X's that you stop the performance.
That's why it's important to know which show you're on when you're performing.
Have you seen that one?
I've seen that one actually.
It's pretty good.
Oh my God.
Have you seen that America's Got Talent clip where it's like a grandma goes up and she's
trying to do stand up and she goes like, "How's everybody doing?
Are you all right?"
And she says, everyone's like, "Yeah."
And then she goes, "No, you are all left."
And they all buzz so quick.
it's like the fastest anyone's ever been buzzed on the show that's awesome so I
want I feel like we're getting distracted though because I had two pitches all
right what are you my first pitch is a duck face Christmas well we said that we
wanted to do a Christmas okay we said we might want to make it kind of musical
okay a duck face Christmas yeah pitch for a Christmas yeah and then my other
pitch that I just came up with is a fascinating slash peculiar Christmas
which is kind of like a curious curiosity mixed with Christmas peculiar yeah yeah
the most peculiar day of the year we can call it peculiarity is is the same thing
as as some fascinating i mean if you if you have enough curiosity it is no i
think like an extra eye on an animal is peculiar but it's not you would not be
fascinated by an extra i can also be fascinated by how a clock might work
that's and yeah but that's that's not very peculiar it's a rectangle and
square type thing there's shapes of it's the shape of the clock and there's
something peculiar yeah how Santa's sleigh yes and exactly how does it fly
reindeer right I remembered and that's peculiar it is kind of peculiar
peculiar Christmas I guess who I guess the entire holiday is a bit or why did
he decide on why wouldn't he decide on something with wings to fly him away why
Why not like a duck? Yeah, maybe like a maybe Santa could make a face similar to a duck.
A dove or a swan. Or a partridge. I feel like it should have been partridges. Yeah. Or flying
reindeer you completely lose me. Yeah, exactly. Like, listen, all right, there's a fat guy.
He's up in the mountains of the north. Yeah, he's already that's already sounding a little
bit anomalous and atypical. Yeah, and he's got some shorties. He's got mad shorties and
and one and they're all making different kinds of Xbox games and that's all
that's all good and gravy with me, but it's also kind of incongruous and
dubious. I think it's a bit in in Congress, but until you get to the
reindeer part, I'm pretty much believing it. Well, the reindeer part is
totally eccentric and back ass words. Yeah, then that's basically what I was
thinking and that's where it felt the whole story falls apart for me there.
You know if they said yeah, Santa does Santa does all that shit, but he's got
flying reindeer sounds to me a little freaky or kinky yeah that's almost like
I think that's kinky it says I mean I'm just I'm looking at synonyms for
peculiar okay kinky kinky kinky is a wacko for peculiar dilly I guess I guess
my I guess getting fucked in the ass is a little bit peculiar or remarkable how
How remarkable how remarkable is it that
chained up and fucked in the
be a bit it's a bit airity off center yeah,
but I wouldn't call you're going to be walking a bit off center. I yeah, but I
would not call it. I mean I'm just reading the list of synonyms here, but
these are synonyms. I would not choose deviant. I might not say that I might
use that one or it says yeah queer well well no depends on who's doing it I was
think it would be better it would be funnier if the instead of queer they
said were peculiar yeah that'd be a little bit of a better word I think yeah
yeah and they could talk about different shows but they're making that show
so peculiar yet the white lemony snicket is one of the most peculiar shows
peculiar has been the funniest word to me. It's a funny word yeah the past few
days yeah how peculiar the peculiar community is really good to that's that
that would be a great a great name for like a children's book that's for kids
who like Tim Burton. You know what's so so and so in the peculiar community. I'm
gonna add that to the list of really good things to like just things to say
when your card declines.
Is just be like, "That's peculiar."
(laughing)
- Buyin' one pack of cigarettes.
- Your card has declined.
That's actually peculiar.
- Yeah, huh. - Fascinating.
- We'll have to look into this.
- Yeah.
You ever do the thing where you say,
"I'm gonna come back later and pay for that?"
- Yeah, you don't do it.
- I mean, I haven't not done it yet,
but every time I think about it,
I'm like, "Maybe this is the time."
- I've never actually done that.
I've always just like figured out a way.
I've always, you know, if they have an ATM or something.
- Figured out a way?
- I think that they-- - You figured out a way, yeah.
- I've always figured out a way--
- That sounds peculiar.
- I've figured out a way to pay them no matter what.
- That's what you're saying?
- Sounds like he's doing some peculiar stuff.
- I'm popping this thing, I'm done with it.
- Do not pop that thing in your mouth.
- What are you doing?
- Don't, stop. - Oh my God, you're gonna
give me a weird thing on my neck if you do that.
- I need to get it, like, I need to go to the doctor.
- A weird thing, a weird feeling on my neck?
affecting how I say words. You do look like you got punched in the face.
This is the second time in a year that you've had a crazy like mouth. I look like I got punched
in the face like on my lip. Yeah, your lip looks a little bit busted right now. It's a bit peculiar.
Have you talked about this on the podcast yet? Do you have a ball in your mouth? Yeah.
Oh, okay. Yeah, the ball. I think so. I think I talked about it on stream or something, but yeah,
I'm totally convinced this is a benign or very malignant tumor in my mouth. And I'm not going
to the doctor because I'm too afraid. Should we cut it out and do a biopsy? That would
actually be great. Yeah. I think they need to get rid of these stupid terms benign
and malignant and call them what they are good and evil. Yeah I do mix up benign and
malignant pretty often where someone will say somebody will say your cousin
got cancer. Yeah somebody will say that. And it's malignant and I'll say thank God. Yeah. And they'll go no that's bad.
That's the bad one. And I'll say okay. They should literally call them good and evil
tumors yeah way simpler you have an evil and bad I think if it's to be words it's
way too confusing easier to mix them up very good but bad and very good okay
yeah that could work or very good and very berry your husband has tutti-frutti
cancer yeah well that's a good that it also could be salty and sweet
yeah okay maybe there are five types and it's salty sweet sour umami spicy spicy
and spit sweet salt fat acid heat then that's one of the greatest books fire
air water air wind earth are getting earth I forgot earth Larry Moe curly
me curly Joe and Curly Joe, Chris Ed and Eddie yeah yeah or another Ed no,
we could just have a know we could do it. I saw why they should have had the
third edge should have been an Ed with three DS and the hell and Ed and Ed did
yeah did yeah how the hell on Blue's Clues salt and pepper have a have a kid
named paprika boy. I think I think Pepper was cheating on her husband. I
that she got in I think she maybe hooked up with Tony Sachery.
And you think that's how they got paprika?
That's how they got paprika.
I don't know any.
Salt and pepper does not make paprika.
Do you remember there being other dogs besides Blue and the Pink one?
Well Salt and Pepper weren't dogs.
Those weren't dogs.
They were salt and pepper.
They were spices.
Oh I don't remember that.
They were in the kitchen.
They were salt and pepper in the kitchen.
Is that one of the later seasons?
Yeah that's not until like season five.
Is that after Steve is gone?
Because I only remember Steve.
was there. Steve was there. Who was this guy after Steve? Joe. Joe what? Mama. You want
to take that back? You want to try that one again? Okay, pick up the mic. Alright, so
who came after Steve? Joe. Go ahead, ask. And what, hold on, hold on. And what was Joe's
last name? Mama. This is his real name. See you guys are making me put my phone
away. I can't look it up. He can't do the IMDB thing. Oh my god this is perfect. You
know why? Because me and him always think he's wrong about something and then he's
always right. So since he's making me put my phone away to sabotage me.
He can't ever be right about anything. We just say no that's not right.
Oh my god, we're Machiavellian geniuses.
Yeah, you guys are trying to say like, "Oh, he gets distracted too easy.
He has a medical brain condition that makes him get distracted too easy."
No, it's so that you guys can tower over me like some kind of giant.
You're right. You have a medical condition.
Yeah, that's what I usually...
The doctor looked at your mom and said, "Unfortunately, he has a medical condition
condition where he can be distracted by a telephone.
Yep, that's what they said the medical could so anyway. What about what about a
space alien Christmas? You think that's what we might be able to do or an
astronaut Christmas? Hi Joe
Joe Mama Joe Mama got him. Oh my God astronaut Christmas. I don't like
Christmas alien because there's no winter. There could be winter on a
different planet. If they go to another planet or time
I don't know how you're doing you how are you finding another way to do your
phone with a spoon you're playing angry birds you're angry birds with a with a
spoon and a something you're supposed to talk and think
Jesus not can you please weigh in on a space alien Christmas
don't you what if I was like silent like harpo marks. I don't think that would
work on a podcast. I think it's a bad idea.
That's really funny.
you. Yeah, but I am wondering what you think of space a space alien Christmas.
I still just think that I think it just needs to be musical. Well, yeah, I can
be musical. I'm just I'm pitching the you see my for the musical.
Yeah, you like to eat it. You're in your clothes in your eye. You can look like
you stub your toe. Yeah,
you would have made just a great pirate. I think yeah, I think you would have
been like an all timer of a pirate. Yeah, you would be a great smith. Yes, I
would be a good you would look so good with a parrot on your shoulder and
missing an eye and we I swear to God we've said this before that you would be
a good pirate yeah that just means it's more true yeah you have dark or I'm just
like or I had a dream about this not a dream last night that I had a dream I
escaped an invasion yeah it's so kind of a body snatchers no no no it's basically
basically some kind of like I mean I you have to assume come some kind of like
republicans that are basically invading this like beautiful like island that i
was on
and they were basically doing a lot of different gun violence and
i just dodged them and kinda running away
and maybe doing some double crossing convincing them i was on their side and
i was actually not on their side and i escaped at the end
but they did kill millions of people and i was sitting there and i did
pretty much nothing about it. Did i tell you about my vampire kidnapping escape dream?
Is that after the show? The live show?
I think it well I don't think it was right after but it was after where you were
Dracula infected his brain with yeah yeah I was so scared that dreams that I was
well it was one of the it was a dream so I feel like actually you know what maybe
if this is an episode where we come up with movies because I think that that
could be a movie first of all the dream you just said there's nothing it's called
uh a low January 6 yeah oh that's good but here's my this movie okay this dream
I feel like a perfect movie. Yeah, that's the tagline. Yeah, the movie's called Caleb
is
I in the dream. It's the dream starts. I'm already kidnapped. I'm locked in a room with a vampire with a Dracula. He's not fair
Yeah, I know I don't get a chance to do anything stop yourself the room. It's the the the room
It's and I'm in locked in like a school or something - okay
The vampire has me in a school and basically the dream is that I go out of the door that the vampire has me and I
I run down the hallway and I run down the stairs and then there's a there's doors
and they have a they have like a they have a number punch keypad combination
lock to open it from the inside yeah and in the dream I type in I type in the
number. I just type in a random number and it works immediately. I go well,
thank God, if I had to do even one more number, he probably would have got me
and then I go outside and his daytime and like oh, thank God, it's daytime. He
can't follow me and then I woke up. That's like just there's almost no
tension in that yeah I ran downstairs and like just put it but it could be a
really short movie it could be a short film. I had a dream the other night
that I was attempting like a cartwheel and I woke up. Is this a dream episode or a
movie episode? Well this could be a movie. Okay all right then that's why I continue. I had a
dream that I was attempting a cartwheel and I woke up and I had both of my arms
like this and I flung myself forward you just did a cartwheel in the dream and
then you're in you called Patrick's cartwheel the movie it's actually not a
bad idea yeah that might be even better instead of a movie even as a gif yeah an
animated what's it like what if what about like an oak lakes with oceans 11
Ocean's 12 thing but with 12 years of slave and you have like 13 years of slave.
That's the sequel? Yeah. They add a year? Just do one more year. It's just one more
year? Does he have to do 13 more years or just one more year? I think it's a different...
I never saw that movie. Wait, so is it a heist movie? Is that where the Ocean's thing comes in?
Well the naming scheme is where the Ocean's thing comes in but maybe he gets
okay maybe he gets the whole gang back together and he's like I gotta do one more year.
more. Why are you saying gang? Like everybody that he that like
this the guy who is I've never seen the movie I'm guessing the bad guys and
there's good guys and he's gets everybody together and he's like we got
to do you remember when I was a slave for 12 years we have to do one more year
until cuz maybe somebody you know what it is somebody comes to him and says
I'll give you a million dollars if you do one more year as a slave he says ah
Ah, they're right as I was out, they're pulling me right back in.
But if he gets a million dollars to be a slave, then he's not a slave.
Oh, that's actually, that's one of the philosophical conundrums at the heart of
the film. Yeah, it's kind of like, it's a, it's a retreat box.
If you get a slave for one million dollars, is that like a good...
Yeah. For one year.
And the, and the subtitle, it's, it's called, it's called, it's called
"13 Years a Slave, a Peculiar Quandary." Would you do this?
And it's a philosophical movie.
I think, I don't think I would be a slave for a year for a million bucks. That's pretty tough.
Yeah. Yeah. I guess it depends what I would be doing.
Like do you get a stipend every day?
No, I think that you have to go full slave.
Yeah, you're fully.
We both went for full slave.
We both moved our hands like this and said full slave.
Like we were wiping a car window. Full slave.
Full slave.
Yeah.
One year.
Full slave, university in Florida.
Yeah, but I yeah, I don't tell you I almost went to full sail. I don't think
you told me that, but I knew that. Yeah, yeah, I'm sure that you were you did
that when you did DeVry, you're doing all that. I almost went to full sail.
Well, I'd like to make it was a for-profit. I'd like to make a third
person shooter. Yeah, I think I think the coolest thing that people go to full
sale and those types of things for is like 3d modeling and they just make
their they just put stuff on deviantART. I think that's awesome. I think that's so
cool. I saw this picture on Facebook. Oh it was like I think I showed you. Oh my god.
Yeah it's like the snake. It was a college in like the Philippines or
something where they do like they do like 3d modeling classes and they like
post the like college itself posted on their official Facebook page like one of
the like final projects and it's like a snake that's like smiling. It's like a
What about a movie about a 3D artist, right?
Oh, the 3D artist.
The 3D artist and a client comes in and he says, "Here is, here's all the dimensions for the character that I need for my movie, right?
And here's all the dimensions, so plug it into your computer program and I want that. You got to model this thing."
You got to print it.
So he does all the dimensions right and it starts to look familiar and he
finishes it and it looks exactly like his dead brother. Whoa right and then
the guy says and also i'll give you one million dollars to be a slave for
higher here. That's the cinematic universe that we're working on. Yeah,
I think that'd be really good. You could call it the disaster artist.
That's good because it's a complete disaster to be put in this life. Yeah,
that's true.
Remember that movie?
Oh I found it.
Come check this out.
It's slipping up my speech.
Spit it out.
Look at this snake with vampire teeth.
Oh my god it's a complete ball.
I can't turn my laptop.
Damn he looks dope.
Doesn't that look sick?
I might enroll in this school.
Can we make this a cover for this episode?
Yeah I think so.
profile picture. We should just make that the new cover for the podcast. Yeah.
Yeah that's so good. Well we'd have to pay the guy. That's fine. I'll pay him. Let's see if I
don't know if it says he did it. Okay here's the plan. I'm gonna reach out to...
It's for the snake. Okay. We give him, we send him an email say like hey we are
are three guys who host a podcast we love your snake with a smile guys I have
horrible news what every post on this on this Facebook page has a little
subtitle under under the the name that says the here it says satire page we got
played it's a satirical it's a satirical 3d snake what serious I'm completely
serious I didn't know that Facebook could do that so if it's satirical that
means that they must be making fun of what our satire pages. They're a way for
people to share social commentary by using humor, exaggeration, and absurdity to
make a point. Why are they labeled as satire pages? Posts from satire pages can
appear very similar to posts from public figures or conventional news sources.
Pages can label themselves as satire pages to help avoid this confusion. Is that real?
That's something that Facebook does? That's what it says when you click on this. That is so funny dude.
So like if you go to the Onion it says satire on you? I would imagine it does. I never, I don't really go to the
the on that's so I'm going to check it right now. I wonder if the onion put out
any heat lately.
No dude, this doesn't even say satire page. It's his media slash news
company. Let's check up on the audience. Who can I hate? I do I am. I think I'm
really passionate about fake news. Now that I got tricked by that three D
snake, I think I'm really. I think we really have to crack down on social
media and what we're allowed to post. I agree. I think that these these trolls
online and these are gone too far this time too far. It's just they made me
believe that in the Philippines you can take a class on making a 3d snake. I
feel like a total bozo. I think that these Russian bot farms basically we
need to go to a complete nuclear war. We need to go to Russia. Just kill every
one of I agree. I think that Russia should just be completely wiped off the
mouth. Yeah, I'm I'm completely pro Ukraine. Now I was on the fence before
I've said this from the beginning wipe them both out. Yeah, just flatten them.
Oh, I just found a new funny onion headline. What does it say? CEOs warn
against the dangers of artificial intelligence. That could be a movie. The
CEO opening scene, the CEO, he's sitting in his office, right? We are up from the
little bronze nameplate that says, says Derek awesome, the CEO, the CEO, and then
it's a pans up and he says, what did he say? What's up? What did he say about AI?
Oh, he's, uh, they, let me scroll back up here, they warn against the dangers of it.
There's gonna be dangers in regards to artificial intelligence, right?
Yeah.
So that could be like the opening scene, and that could be what they call an inciting incident
in the movie.
So now we need a rising action, so maybe he says that and then the person across from
him who's clearly half robot but he doesn't realize it goes like, "No, there's not any
dangers to it."
Before we go any further, I just wanted to say, I thought, this whole time I thought artificial intelligence was what they called Fox News.
Ohhhhh.
Are you fucking for real?
Did you really think that?
That's like so stupid.
I just thought of that.
You just thought of what you thought?
Mmhmm.
What?
You really thought that?
This whole time I thought artificial intelligence is what they labeled Fox News.
I'm reporting this fake satire Philippines page.
I think that they should put...
For false information.
I think that I would actually find Fox News a little bit humorous if they put that little
satire button on the bottom of that, right?
Yep.
Because then I would find their outrageous...
Yeah, they should put artificial intelligence at the bottom of it because when you read
it you become stupid and it's not real.
Well, they should put lack of intelligence.
And they should call it fake news.
I think that they should...
Fake...
Fox should stand for fake all over...
over it may be pronounced Fox News but it's spelled FAUX yeah oh like foe yeah
but it's pronounced Fox hmm what about pH Oh news I would read it and eat read it
read it read it and eat that could be a good movie name news there is a food
news and weep no no this movie is called KK Panabaker X what's it about me
reading the last three Harry Potter books? Tearjerkers. Oh yeah. Waterworks.
I don't know. Bye-bye Dobby. Dobby, did he die? Oh yeah, he died in the
one, yeah. In my brain, Dobby died the second he was introduced. He should have. He's too
weak and sickly a creature to sustain. Dobby had a brother named Creature. Yeah, I
don't even know if he's-- I don't think he's a brother, I think he's the
same species I think we said is insanely racist full-on speaking of slavery full
on slavery complete slavery yeah it's really and it's and it's like and Dobby
just is as intelligent as any other being the entire thing they're like
everybody's fine with it yep but he doesn't have the right clothes on he's a
slave yeah if you give him a sock he's free yeah kind of fucking shit is that
it's a stupid it really works it's one of the worst book series in the world
it's so funny that like you, you just see people complaining about jk
rolling like all the time and you're like okay, people are like there are
this many complaints like whatever people all online always like blow the
shit out of proportion like people are knowing about this kind of stuff and
then you like like remember stuff about harry potter's like oh yeah, the
only chinese character was named cho chang and there was there was a there
was a there was a there was a yeah and there was a they have a black guy
whose name is Kingsley Shacklebolts. No, thank you
it's insane. It's like so crazy yeah, it's so funny. This use is like a
homeless lady like writing that it like coffee shops or whatever and now she's a
billionaire because he wrote the most fucking stupid books ever. It's also
it's so funny that the whole like conflict of that thing of that those
books is like the evil guys want to do genocide, but the good guys they don't
want to genocide, but they still don't like the people they're going to get
like that. They're trying to kill yeah the muggles are there still there. Hey,
there's literally like a homeless lady who had like a like was writing it on
library computers just being like and then there's a slave name. Don't be
yeah, don't be going to be a complete slave, but he's a friendly one and then
The mean ones called creature right?
Yeah
The mean ones is brother too
They're all brothers
All slaves are related
And he's got some kind of mark
And you give him a sock
Yeah
And he gets off the slavery
And he's completely done with being a slave
And there's a blonde boy
And he's a complete villain
He's mixed with a snake
What's he? He's a...
Oh Dobby's an elf?
House elf
*laughter*
Oh my fucking god
Yeah, and his house!
Ah, oh, frog!
At this point it's so hacked to be like, man,
Harry Potter was weird, but yeah
It's fucking crazy.
It is fucked up.
It's really, it's like wrong.
I always hated Harry Potter because of who it was.
Me too, I did not like it.
I read it all and then I thought,
I was like, why did I do that?
This sucks.
Yeah, someone is, she's writing the bank scene
and gives it to someone and they're like,
Is this doesn't seem kind of like anti-semitic.
She's like, no, it's not supposed to be Jews expecting me
midgets, right?
It's supposed to be midget Jews, not normal Jews.
And they got also slaves working for them, right?
Yeah.
Oh my God.
I remember I rewatched all those movies recently in the past
like two years because my girlfriend wanted to and the first
like in the first movie when they go to Gringotts and they
see all the goblins.
It's fucking crazy.
the first thing that the Hagrid says when they walk into that bank is like he
turns to her and it's like you have to stay close to me. You can't trust any of
these goblins for a single second.
It's so funny that you now you could go to you can go pay a hundred and eighty
dollars to go see them at Universal Studios. So sick and it's really fun
dude. I part of Harry Potter. I like is the amusement park bro. I love
amusement park so fucking much when I was in California. I was trying to get I
I was trying to beg my family like please, please can we go to
Disneyland so I can go to the Star Wars ride.
Please. I want to see that thing so bad. I want to get in that
ride and just be flown all the way around. We gotta go to Orlando.
I need to go to Florida.
I've never been.
Dude, I went to the Universal in whichever Disney is in
Orlando. Disney World.
World.
Yeah, the Star Wars ride, whatever that crazy Star Wars ride
is at the World. Rise of the Republic.
Is it Rise of the Republic?
rise of the no no it's not i mean i i went on it so i don't know okay i've
never been that right is crazy or land it's so cool i've been at universal
though and let me tell you universal yo the velocity coaster is next is next
freaking level i really literally want i want i want to go on the et ride i want
i want there to be ones where they're where king kong picks you up and rips
you in half the king kong ride at universal i would honestly love so it's
really bad but does he jump up no you're in a car they're screwed the one cool
part of it is they have a giant uh animatronic um kong head at the end of it that's what i want is a
giant the hulk ride is sick the hulk ride i i like i almost passed out on the hulk ride the hulk ride
is so fucking he has nothing to do with hulk it's a gamma chamber some shit it's a gamma chamber what
the hell is that what's the that's the that's the story of the ride oh yeah i thought you're saying
that's like a kind of roller coaster
chamber. The Velocicoaster is like incredible though. That was our
pre-show reel for a little bit. Well you've made us watch the ET ride thing
probably 30 times. It's so good. Well it's the video just doesn't do it justice.
It's one of the best rides in the world because it's one of the worst rides. Wow.
So good. It's so bad. It's good. Wow like Trolls 2. You should do an MST 3K for that. You
should yeah I would actually be great at that when ET says thank you Patrick I
get you get chills I guess so he knows my name how you know you sitting in my name
isn't Patrick he says you're gonna have to say thank you Caleb really what if
you have a name that nobody else has yeah what do they plug in have they
recorded ET saying he's saying a bunch of names but if I don't know what if my
name is like what if my name is like water bottle. I don't think they have that.
Thank you water bottle. He can say water bottle? Yeah. Holy crap. I guess that's just water
and bottle so they probably already recorded names for people named water and people named
bottle. Thank you Mohammed. Your mic keeps going crazy whenever you move it around. There
might be something wrong with that cable. That's okay by me. Yeah. Yeah that's not really
my problem. It's gonna have to be okay with everyone listening. Sorry. Is there any kind
of Nickelodeon rides or the I think I got rid of all the Nickelodeon stuff I
won't there's dr. Seuss they're building for years they've been building the
Nintendo Lynch part what oh yeah the Nintendo and look so sick they took out
they took out some unless the haggard unless the twin dragons is still there I
was a good ride I think that dueling dragons is gone maybe yeah I think the
dueling dragons is gone and then they replace that with Nintendo world
Nintendo World, yeah, is still, but the Hagrid motorcycle ride was sick. Did you
ride that one? I did. That one is tight. I went on the, when they go to, you go to
the big Hogwarts. Yeah. That one's sick. The one, the dark ride, when you, when you
go and... We should just, we should just plan. We really need to go. We should just
plan an amusement park. We should just plan an amusement park trip. We should go.
No, an amusement park. First, the best time to go is like the three days after
thanksgiving this guy watch that German tour that's I think exactly when I read
a long video about roller coaster day that last year I went to Universal three
days I think also maybe we could go in tonight we can go tonight I we really
need to plan a big Universal trip I know okay we plan a trip where we go we do one
night at Universal then we do one night in Las Vegas and then we go back to
to Universal and we go back to Las Vegas and then back to Universal and then we go
home. Yes we can do that. Okay yeah that's what you want to do we could definitely
do that. I think it should be one day. Different mindsets. One day each, one day each.
Can we go to Cuba? Yes. Different mindsets. I think if you go to if you go to
Universal then Vegas then you if you go to Vegas and you lose your money you
won't have enough money to get funny photos. Well I think well okay but I
think that if you go if you alternate days between those that is not something
that people I don't think I would say that maybe we could be the first people
ever to do four days of alternating Vegas and universal isn't like a like a.
Oh, this is like I'm going to go have the time of my life. Vegas is like a job
like you're on the clock. I think that we could create a completely new brain
mindset by doing that. I don't think anybody in history has ever done that. I
think it would nobody's right. I think something would happen to Vegas every
like to Vegas, then to universe and that's like the only world you knew for
days. I think you would actually like you
transcend. Yeah, you're right. Something would happen. That would be so
fucking insane. I don't think it would necessarily be good, but I think that
that would be like a new type of brain experiment. Yeah, that nobody's done. It's
like, oh my god, I'm leaving universe. The feeling of leaving vacation and then
touching down in Las Vegas, that's so crazy. And then knowing that
you have to go back to the universe. Yeah, and then you gamble, you stay up all
all night you gamble, you lose all your money and then you have that kind of
like hangover feeling where you're leaving a casino. You don't want to go
on a you don't want to go on a roll and you're like you're like oh my God, my
life, what the fuck I don't want to get to this point, okay and the flight
non stop flight between Orlando and Las Vegas is only five hours. So that's not
that bad. No yeah, so if you go, I mean you just do red eyes, you're going to
see to maximize the time yeah. So you do read every time you would be sleeping
you you go on the plane. Well, you try to sleep on the plane. I guess yeah,
- Well, I mean, that's what I mean.
Like, every time you'll be sleeping in a bed.
- Yeah.
- Different hotels every time, too.
- Look, if we can make this mindset happen, I--
- Oh my God, oh my God.
I just figured out the high roller coaster mindset.
- This is the--
- High roller, roller coaster.
- Oh my God.
- You could also, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
'Cause you could do it in, you could do Disney--
- This is the movie.
You could do Disney Land-- - Leaving Las Vegas
and going to Orlando and then leaving Orlando
and going to Las Vegas.
- If we're trying to maximize time here,
you could go Disneyland. I'm not trying to maximize any time I'm trying to create a
new brain experiment. Yeah we're trying to actually induce psychosis.
I thought that you wanted to, but if you keep taking flights from Las Vegas to LA
back and forth, because if you're trying to induce psychosis,
one ride back to LAX. He just sat up in his chair, he's got some serious points. One
One ride back to LAX, Vegas airport, gamble for like three hours, back to the airport,
back to LAX, universal, two rides, back to Vegas.
But here's my-
Wait, are you saying go to Florida and then Vegas and then LA and then Vegas and then
Florida?
Because that's actually crazy.
I was thinking about now about-
I was saying LA, but if you do that-
That's crazy.
But LA to Las Vegas is only an hour and 15 minutes flight.
Well, that's what I mean.
It would completely warp your perception of time if you were going to Disneyland
and Disney World which are almost identical.
Okay, but here's the thing I have to...
But you're only seeing an hour difference between Vegas and Disneyland
and a five-hour difference between Vegas and Disney World.
So you're seeing the same thing. You're like,
"Am I time-traveling when I go to Disney World?"
If only both Disney parks had an airport.
If they had a landing strip, that'd be huge.
That might tip the mindset, though, into being too much about amusement
and you might need to add a second a second las vegas style stop in there but
here at top show
like maybe like you go to like a business summit
but you're doing it every other time anyway for both of them so really as
long as you start with a guess you could have in with the same thing is i just
want to do it will do a patient
yeah i just want to learn all time you're on blow
yeah i don't think the drug should be involved i think it's a pure is it
really good drinking as a drinking is insanely involved drinking you're
drinking the entire time. We're trying to, because it is, you're trying to like,
What if you just need like a just a bump to keep you awake at Vegas? I think you're really
trying to hurt whoever you are subjecting this to. Okay, here's my new pitch.
Okay. This is like that movie The Game. Uh-huh. This is kind of what you're doing.
It's called The Park. Yeah, the Michael Douglas movie. Yeah, yeah. It's like that.
You're doing it to somebody. I think it's Disney World to Las
Vegas, Las Vegas to Disneyland, Disneyland to a zero-gravity space flight
where you go up out of the atmosphere you hang in so you get that zero gravity
thrill yeah and then you're back down also your bones separate a little bit so
every day you're getting like an inch shorter yeah this is like that movie
phone booth where the guy is like if you don't do this I'll fucking kill like mm-hmm
so you tell you're you're doing like a phone booth style thing this guy's got a
Bluetooth headset on you're actually is a razor headset yeah so you're calling him
you call him and say like if you don't go to Disney World Orlando right now yeah
I'm fucking killed I will fucking kill the president's daughter or whatever that
movie was well he's in love with the president that's another part of me this
guy's in love with the president's daughter or maybe he's going on a date
with it's the guy from my day with the president's daughter or it's maybe it's
the guy from Resident Evil 4 who's trying to rescue the president's
daughter or maybe it's Jon Favreau and he's saying I will I will become a big
show I will become an even better chef than you if you don't go
Orlando, then Las Vegas, then Universal Hollywood, then Zero Gravity Flight.
There's no need to kill any president's daughter or anything.
This is just, you ask somebody, you say, "Okay, I'm going to give you a million dollars to
be a slave for a year."
They agree.
This is what you force them to do.
Holy shit.
They are a pleasure and business slave.
They literally just brought it completely back to that.
Well, that's it.
We can end the episode now.
Well, that's the thing about if you do-
Just play 30 minutes of an album.
in the episode here play fucking play Dark Side of the Moon synced up with I feel
like this is the last 10 minutes has been some of the densest this podcast has ever
been as far as like just pure ideas yeah I think that is like one of our
smartest more time yeah speaking of fascinating high roller coaster slave
well the thing is I would that is that if someone says I'll give you a million
dollars bf2 my my slave for an entire year you expect to be working you don't
don't know what kind of slave you could be yeah. You know you to be my high
roller coaster slave who goes from Disney land to Disney world to Las Vegas
to space and then back for a year. Then you say yes, I think yeah because that
will do so much psychic damage to you. Can you imagine even going to Disney
world every day for a month? How fucking insane your life would be? Oh my God,
can you imagine the the movies and art that we would get if we did that to
hundreds of thousands of young men in this country? Absolutely like just like
just like a generational trauma. I feel like we could get better stuff than
Vietnam movies. Definitely, yeah. We don't have a war right now. Yeah. It's at all
interesting, right? There's no kind of like mass like violent movement for everybody to rally behind.
This is not, this is a movie idea, what we've come up with. It's not an idea for a movie.
It is an idea for a way to make movies be great. Yeah, which is that we take a
bunch of people who are like, you know, kind of their brains are like right on
the edge of development, early 20s, like late teens.
- 18 to 22.
- Yeah, and we're sending them--
- Mail.
- In droves.
- Drove.
- To--
- We are chartering flights that's just full
of only these people.
- Exactly.
- And they are not allowed to talk to each other.
- Well, we time it perfectly, so as soon as one leaves,
another arrives to each location.
- Yeah.
- Oh my God.
- And they have a circuit that they have to follow.
- And the Disney parks will pay for it,
'cause we're driving so much traffic to their parks.
- Exactly, 'cause they do have to pay for their own food.
yes and their own drinks because you know what there's and they have a for photos
with with Mickey and sting goofy and sully because they have to prove that
they went every single time yeah they have a punch card yeah exactly they put
they tape a photo yeah of them with and also we give them a virus that kills
them in 24 hours if they don't get the antidote yeah and the antidote it's like
a what's the antidote it's in space it's maybe it's under 24 hours they do go to
space. Maybe it's at the core of the earth. That's too hard to get to. Yeah, space is easier
to get to. In Florida, space is easy to get to. That's true. Yeah, because it's hanging
off of the earth. Yeah, that's a good point. I am trying to think of how we can involve
the center of the earth though. Maybe that's where we hang out. We can't go to the center
of the earth. I think we just need to buy a new XLR. Should we replace it right now? Yeah.
Yeah, I'm gonna do that. Okay, wow. It's serious, but I think okay so back to what we were saying before
I think maybe that our control center is at the center of the earth
hmm
Like our command center where we're watching everyone on screens
I just think you're getting so caught up on this whole like center of the earth thing and I feel like being in the
Controlling aspect of it. Yeah, why do you mostly about control of a Nathan Fielder type this one? Yeah?
I'm not anything like neurodivergent. Oh, I'm gonna be like the famous fucking
manipulator Nathan Fielder. Okay, first of all, he's not that famous. He's mad.
He's pretty fucking famous. No, but he's an alt comedian. Okay, if he was, if he was,
if he was famous, he'd be called a mainstream comedian. That's true. I don't
think, I think he's pretty fucking like Brad Pitt level famous at this point.
Every woman wants to have sex with that guy. Brad Pitt is not that famous. I think every woman who has it.
is really not fit that famous at all really yeah he's fair fame just dropped.
I did see a picture of Brad Pitt the other day and I could not believe that
he's like 55 years old. He's one of the hottest people I know it looks damn good.
Yeah yeah he has such a good actor - I can't believe if you should be that good
at that good girlfriend ever said that she would have sex with Nathan Fielder.
No no she has insurance insurance she's not like us like one of these scumbags
with no insurance talking about yeah I'll fuck Nathan Fielder I'll do anything for
insurance yeah yeah health insurance oh that's a weird you know everyone
complains about that everyone's like oh why does why do women think he's hot and
then it's like who complains about that other men and it's like well if you're
a man you know he's the most normal-looking guy so if you look if you
look anywhere near that guy I feel like I don't know I feel like people
shouldn't be complaining about it I feel like people should be celebrating I
I don't think that I think that women are more attracted to his sarcastic mind
than anything else. Exactly. Not really his physical body. Yeah. Yeah.
They're looking at him they're like okay this guy's fucking next level at
sarcasm let's try to learn let's try to learn from the best. That's the
point I was trying to make. I've talked to plenty of women, tons of women and they're all like I'm sarcastic.
There's also a thing of like you know your girlfriend was watching a movie and
there's like a slime monster in it and she's like that is the hottest guy I've
ever seen and you're like well that's like the hottest guy ever seen then what
the fuck am I what what's going on here yeah I don't really something about me
I'm like I'm like I'm I'm not slime monster enough yeah yeah if that's the
hottest one yeah the slime everyone has the slime monster experience isn't it
great to feel inadequate yeah but I'll never feel inadequate again once I have
millions no one's like my young man I'm gonna talk about us getting tendrils
tendrils the I don't want tendrils youngness of the men under my control
though facts you don't want tendrils anymore I didn't want tendrils from the
beginning bro tendrils he said he wants to tendrils are you saying like for
dinner like at a Jamaican restaurant. No like on my head like on my head I'm gonna get a
series of tendrils. Tendrils. I don't even set I don't think that you can buy those anymore.
Yeah I was talking to Patrick I think I might get black veneers completely black. Yeah completely
black teeth. Yeah I was talking to him last night about shiny. We were talking to each
other last night. Yeah you missed you missed our walk. You completely missed out. You went
- You walked home.
- We had a sleepover.
- Yeah, you walked home and then we--
- Talked about our teeths.
- We talked about some ideas.
- Yeah.
- I was telling him about my uncle.
My uncle like went to--
- Too far.
- My uncle went too far.
No, my uncle, my mom told me my uncle
like had to stay in our living room
because he just got like a really bad,
like big surgery.
And she was like--
- Really bad or big?
- Like big surgery, like oh he's gonna be like
out of commission for--
a couple days. They made it? No, no, no, no. Well, I'm getting there. Okay. He's like,
"Oh, he's got like a big surgery. I'm gonna set up a bed for him in the
living room so he can like recover," because he was like living with us at the
time. And then I found out later he just got fucking veneers. What? My uncle got
veneers and my mom was like... You have to recover from veneers? He needs to
recover. Yeah, you need to rest. Really? It's gonna reflect light into your eyes and
hurt you. Yeah, you have to let him get around for a couple days. Yeah, exactly. Don't they just pop him on top?
I don't know, but he was acting like he got like giant leg surgery or something
trying to get surgery yeah yeah no you just why do you keep saying my big and
giant in regards to the surgery he's taller than me and big sir yeah my uncle
just got had to get a bunch of rabies shots because he picked up a raccoon
soaked in urine yeah while he had a woman an open wound on his wound he of
wreck a raccoon soaked in urine was the rabies is honestly exact reason I was
funniest things like seeing I saw video of a guy with rabies. It is so funny.
Can you imagine if my uncle died from rabies and the like lead up to that was I
got a text and said hey your uncle picked up a raccoon soaked in urine and
then I just had that was like a part of my like psyche that was like shattered
forever. Yeah. Does he seem like a kind of a wild card this uncle or does he
has he ever been cursed with bad luck? No that's my dad's cousin. Okay. That
that guys. I don't even know what he's up to. So he's not the most people in my
family. I don't know what what's going on. They're kind of just doing their
crazy. I know what every single actually never mind never mind. No, I don't know.
I was thinking about that and then I was like I have no fucking idea. I have I
have coming for the mind my close family. Obviously, I know what's up, but
like you know my like some of my cousins and stuff. I'm like I was families. I
grew up next to all of my cousins.
- Yeah. - I have cousins that I knew,
that I met, I saw a lot growing up.
Like, they're like second cousins.
And I saw them a lot growing up,
and we were pretty close,
and our families had like kind of a falling out.
And I haven't seen them in a little while,
and I asked my grandmother about them.
And that's when I learned, at 25 years old,
I learned that my cousins were twins.
- Whoa. - I had no idea.
I didn't even know as a kid they were twins.
- That's crazy. - Which was a real,
of an atom bomb. Yeah. Right on my brain. Yeah. Yeah. My mom told me I have like
medical mesh in my stomach or something like that because I got umbilical
hernia surgery when I was a kid. You had a hernia? I had an umbilical hernia. You
have mesh in your stomach because you tried to chew through a net when you're
in the ocean? Yeah. No. You were trying to get... I could see you dying with a six-pack ring on
your neck. Yeah. Yeah. You can see right around there there's a scar. Why are you showing me
your belly button because I had an umbilical hernia. You're so big dude
because yeah cuz I look how big his belly button is. It's so deep. I got surgery on it.
Stick your finger in there and then smell your finger right now live. It
smells like dr. Bronner's. Really? Wow. Mine is bad if I do that. Yeah. And also like it
smells like I wash the shit out of it. I know that. Yeah you probably have to. I know most of my holes
on my body smell. I hate a belly button gives me like body horror. Yeah I don't
I fucking hate it.
Well you should have seen my, because my
I don't want to see it.
An umbilical hernia is when part of your intestine pokes out of your fucking belly button.
Yeah I know, that's why belly buttons scare me.
So I'd walk around with a little fucking like penis on my stomach.
That's exactly what
I know there's a penis on your stomach.
When you put your finger in your belly button it feels like you're touching your stuff.
What stuff?
The inside.
The skin is so thin.
I don't really know what a belly button is and I really don't care.
Do you not?
That's where the umbilical is.
Can I see your belly button?
The umbilical cord.
No.
Are you an outie or an innie?
many who's in who's an out. I know it can you imagine if you said out. I think
they thought I had an out and then they realize it's
an out belly button like a like an anime belly, but that's like a really big one
that has like the like bandages over it like that one did you mon
and how do you battle like any adults have? I think you're an out e belly
button because you won't show it. I'm not an out, but I'm not he's literally
he has an out e belly. Now I really don't know. I'm very protective over my
delightful little white body. Can I see it? I showed you my, I showed everybody my belly
button. My alabaster torso will never be shown to you guys. You will not see my belly button.
Let me see your belly button. There's so much hair inside of my belly button. Well then
let's just get it out of there. It's so crazy. Let's get that hair out. It's so crazy that
I look like a. Get that hair out of here. I wore like an undershirt the other day. Just
out and like I sweat a little bit and then all you could see was just like my chest hair
pattern like said under showers you said undershirt undershirt that's right I said
it oh and I fucking said it bro we all said undershirt dude stop saying it
you're doodoo I just said doodoo shit god damn it dude there should be I almost
just said do Kyle XY not have a belly button yeah that's how they knew he was
an alien yeah this guy's such a freak that he didn't have in a belly button he
He wasn't an alien, right? He was born an alien.
What would you do if you saw someone without a belly button?
Make one.
I guess that would probably get...
Draw one on them.
Do you know sometimes when you see someone without eyebrows
and you can't really tell what's wrong with their face at first?
Yes.
Like you can't and then you go, "Oh, of course, it's the eyebrows."
Why do people shave their eyebrows and bleach their eyebrows?
Sometimes it looks good.
It depends on who it is.
If strange females nowadays had the option,
they would shave their belly button to make it disappear.
Probably true because I want to be like the strangeness of the other day.
We're sick from sick of X. Oh yeah, Mia goth. She's got no eyebrows. She has no
belly button either. Really camera. We're talking the other day about how to feed
her hands. Me and him saw who has no feet or hands or a hair. It's got him
removed. No hair or feet or hands or belly button or eyebrows. I'm sick of
Alternative O types do I know and her at the hair and her scalp is blue because
she doesn't have hair so she colors her scalp blue that sounds for the movie
they had to CGI Bushwick 10 I saw a guy I saw a guy the other day he had
freckles all over his body fucking disgusting I got covered in freckles do
you guys I get you said you and came we're talking about we saw an
alternative O type walking across the street very slowly the other day well we
were in a car oh yeah I do remember this poor this poor bastard was just walking
he had tattered jeans on. He walked towards the car as if he wanted to get in. Yeah,
and his clothes were completely tattered and he's walking across the street and
just looking like and he had piercings on he had two piercings both on his ears.
He had a beard like a ruffian. Yeah, and he was wearing some kind of rock and roll tee
and he had no sleeves on. We locked the doors. Really? Yeah, we locked the doors and I
also put the I put the sunscreen on on on my front windshield because I was like I
don't I don't want this guy to see me. I want him to think that maybe we're
we're sleeping in this car and then me and him started rocking the car back
and forth to make him think we were having sex in the car, so he wouldn't
come knock on it. If my Ford Focus is okay and then I and then I was and then
I was like and then the reason I knew he was coming when we're in the car is
because I was like looking at like the Starbucks you had in the car and I was
like oh this pink the pink whipped cream drink that we have yeah, it's me it's
like in Jurassic Park and there's ripples going through it because he's
walking because that's what it would make a best part is this this fucking
piece of shit probably works at a starbucks or another kind of indie
coffee roastery and he's too busy making some kind of fucking
something with a ristretto shot yeah to read a ristretto. What is it? What I
don't know what you're making an Aleppo shot ever at starbucks yeah and he's
probably doing a mobile order also probably on an iphone instead of an
android yeah or maybe on an apple watch, which I recently bought one by the way
to he's making and then you go up and you're like can I get a large like
sorry, we don't call it that here. We call it a boloco. It's like what are you
talking about? Yeah, yeah, I can yeah shit. And then I'm like pants. I'm like
okay, fine. I don't want a large than give me just a small and they're like a
small we call that a cheapotle. Yep. Yep. Yep. I hate you go ahead and just
guess what the giant size is called. It's called a Qdoba. When you go to the
when you go to the indie coffee shop, you say let me get a large. I say sorry,
we don't call that a large. We call it a super size me. Yeah, okay, fine. Then I
small and they say we don't call it a small we call it a kids meal and all of a
sudden you're eating two nuggets so that's pretty interesting. It's funny they
sell those in twos. Have you seen the tiny fries? I can probably imagine what they look
like. Yeah. Yeah. Just imagine. Yeah when I'm watching Futurama on my phone I see
tiny fries. Yeah on my iPod video. My iPod phone. I've been thinking about getting an iPod.
iPod phono. Like an old iPod? I already said I wanted to get an iPod shuffle like a
while ago you're copying me an iPod video so I can watch my movies you can watch
your movies it's funny I feel like I maybe maybe not you guys I feel like
most people have like one movie that they bought in 2009 on I iPod that's
just like they just have permanently or like a music video or something I have I
have a I have a censored version of shootouts by Jadakiss and Stiles P on my
iTunes and then I have five premium episodes of WTF with Mark Maron I know I
I know I have a movie on there, but I can't remember what it is. I haven't opened iTunes
in so long. I'm going to see what it is.
I think I have... Oh, you know what I have? It's on my mom's iTunes, though. I have...
Come on, you got this.
Yeah, come on.
What it is is like...
You don't remember.
I bought three of the... because I already downloaded a bunch of that fucking Ariel Pink
album. I have three Ariel Pink songs on my mom's iTunes.
That's pretty tight.
That's dope as fuck.
They changed the name of iTunes on my computer to "Music."
Yeah.
They're trying to get rid of iTunes.
What the hell?
Just like they did Napstar.
They're making this all PC.
It's all PC.
It's like, you can't call it iTunes anymore.
It's Weetunes.
When they were trying to, like when LimeWire and they were cracking down on all the torrenting
stuff, you used to be able to buy the LimeWire software at Best Buy for like 20 bucks.
Yeah.
crazy that they would sell LimeWire on a disc.
They need to do it again.
They need to bring it back.
I think you can still download LimeWire.
I don't think there's probably all that much good stuff on there though.
I have some good stuff on my iTunes.
What do you have?
Got some Tyler the Creator, got some Korn, some Wimp Bizkit, some Symphony X.
That is ill.
That is seriously the soundtrack of the summer.
That is ballin' folks.
Some Five Finger Death Punch, some Green Day.
Oh wow.
Damn, Green Day.
Some Jonathan Colton.
Green Day.
hell yeah dude. One Jonathan Coulton song still alive. We're going on the, we're
going on the, got some fallout boy. They might be giants. Disturbed. What's it
called the cruise ship they do? Oh my god I would love to. We're doing that. That's
funny that they do a cruise ship. That have cardiacs on it. Yeah they do a cruise, we should do a cruise ship. All American
rejects, we should do a cruise ship. That is a genius idea. Let's do it. I feel like.
Do you think we could hop along on some cruise ship tour? What do you mean? Hop
hop along. I feel like our audience doesn't overlap with hop along. Yeah, I
don't think so. We could do a personal cruise ship trip. We could do yeah, a
cruise ship. It's like a small, just a small boat. I don't think so. I think I
would hate it. When my parents first got divorced, my dad was like, "Merry Christmas, we're going on a
cruise ship," and it was the worst. It was one of the worst week or weekend. Yeah, I
think I would absolutely hate being on a cruise ship. Yeah, it was really, really
I wasn't old enough to do any of the gambling. I was vegan so I had to eat the worst
I'd eat just salad the entire time. I couldn't smoke a cigarette.
Isn't it just for like weird people to fuck in the water?
Yeah.
Huh?
Isn't it just for oldies?
It's for swingers. Every cruise ship is for old swingers.
No, the bedrooms are too small for that.
No, that's not true.
We had four bunk beds that were like...
Yeah, you had four bunk beds because you were a kid.
No, we had like, me, my dad, my brothers.
dad my brother's yeah I don't think your dad was paying for the swingers package
well he was doing it though but we only had four bunk beds your dad was swinging
single swinger one man swinging team was jacking off in the same room as you on
to a woman and her brother that's a true story I think that's how crazy Jamaica
America is that's a true story. Yep, my dad jacked off on a woman and her brother
and we'll just say yeah me too. I was there he jacked off on to me okay and my
two brothers. My girlfriend's watching this video series of this Australian
family who just goes on a bunch of cruise ships and it makes videos of like
this cruise ship is amazing and it's they always it's fun. Just the thing I
you always see on cruise ship is the big water slide that goes all around the
like top of the ship. I think it'd be so funny if they like installed it wrong
and this everybody like just the first day everybody gets in the water so they
all just shoot off the side of the ship.
They just launch into the ocean. See we did. They just lose half the passengers
immediately. I remember when my dad showed us the video for the cruise ship.
It was like the video was like he just a video he found on YouTube of like a
trailer for a cruise ship and he was like look at this and there's people doing
like this the like surf surfboard simulator and stuff. Yeah, yeah. It was
like a thing. There wasn't even a pool on this cruise. It was it was a top deck
that had like a shuffleboard and that was about it. I would get terrified that
the cruise ship would leave me behind on stops like I already get scared of that
when I'm going on the bus from like Boston, New York. I get in Burger King
and I'm there for one minute. I can see the bus yeah, but if they're letting me
off in Italy and I'm going to like I'm climbing a mountain and eating at a
restaurant. Yeah, you have a lot of big plans. Well, we don't have so many big
playing climbing a mountain eating at a restaurant and then I have to like I'm
starting a company and opening my factory. I'm worried that they might leave
me behind too much stuff you're gonna miss your cruise. I might be too far
exactly I might miss it and I'm afraid of that and it's like I mean I have to
train these employees. Don't go there then. I have to there's a lot of
fabrication and like machines I have to assemble. You have enough money if you're
opening a factory. I don't have enough money because I spent it all on the
cruise ship. You bought the cruise ship or the the the ticket was really expensive
and the only way building a factory and hiring employees. Well, I offset the cost
of the of the factory by selling my room on the cruise ship. That was funny when
like pandemic first started and like we all over factories. Everybody opened up a
factory. Remember we all had to shut our factories down. Yeah, my god, the fact is
for a couple weeks and then you know it started right back up. You guys remember
this
seems like almost at the beginning of the covid pandemic that a lot of people are actually
making sourdough bread yeah
yeah the pandemic first i was and meanwhile at the beginning of covid to each other that
was cool beginning of the um of the pandemic i was making sour doo doo in my head bad thoughts
i was making it in the toilet yeah that too the head oh the head like the toilet on that
sound cool go back to the cruise ship you can we're doing kind of like dense references
to the loopback. Yeah it sounds interesting. It sounds like there's an effect. So in the
end. Okay. It doesn't even matter. It doesn't even matter. There's been a guy going around
Maria Hernandez Park with a big Puerto Rican flag speaker and he's just blasting Lincoln
Park. It's been so sick. Good taste. That's dope. I'll go there just to listen for free.
Yeah. It's cheaper than a title subscription. Yep. Yep. And you know what's cheaper than
a title subscription tickets to our shows in the Pacific Northwest which actually has a
lot of big shows.
Seattle!
Portland.
And then two shows in Seattle.
Yep, two shows.
We have so much insane.
We have a special guest.
We have so much insanity planned for the rest of this year.
Adrian Brody will be at our Portland show.
That's just the truth.
We have so many insane things that we're doing before the end of the year.
This is probably going to be the last time we're going to be doing any kind of tour show
for a while.
So just come on out, man.
your friends, no parents allowed. And it's not a podcast live show, we do an actual
show. And three girls to every guy. Yeah. Yeah. We gotta keep that ratio.
This will be our last live show ever. Huh? Last live show ever. Yeah, let's just say that.
It's gonna be the last live show we ever do. It's an actual fun-ass fuck show.
It's a fun-as-fuck show and we're gonna break up on stage. Yep. Okay, we're
gonna have a complete fight. Yeah. We're gonna fight so hard and if you don't go
to the show I'm going to kill myself and we're doing like I'll blame the venues
and that'll be that'll be great cuz we can see them blame I'll blame the
crocodile room is that one of the places we're doing croc I think it's called
hereafter at the croc and the other one is Mississippi Studios Mississippi
Studios in Oregon because it's on Mississippi Street excuse me I think I
I don't know.
Merry Christmas from the podcast about Lisp.
I forgot this was supposed to be a Christmas episode.
All right.
Bye.