You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
Frying zucchinis backstage.
Yeah, my mom's backstage frying zucchinis.
She backstage frying zucchinis.
Why do you bring your mom to every single show, Sebastian?
How hungry is this man for zucchinis?
Can you imagine frying zu- Why are we talking about this?
Sebastian?
his mom's fried zucchini snacks dude.
His VMA hosting like a year and a half ago.
I can't, I can't fucking burn that bridge dude.
He might be big for me later.
I've never seen him or heard him talk in any format and whatsoever.
He looks like a monkey.
I mean I know actually I've seen pictures of him but I've never seen a video or heard
him talk.
You've seen a video, have you seen the Irishman?
That's a video of him.
Yeah, he's in the Irishman as the lawyer.
Wow.
He's not the law-
Yeah, Sebastian Maniscalco, he's like, "Oh, I can get you a..."
He's like, "Yeah, the Irishman's frying zucchinis backstage."
That's the only thing they can get him to say.
"I can help you with your case, Robert De Niro, but it's..."
"But I gotta go help my mom. She's backstage frying zucchinis."
"My wife Deborah's in Queens."
You know Sebastian Maniscalco? He's like, "Oh, Deborah, why?"
yeah I miss him my brother Brad Garrett yep I remember that and then he's also
in in the big sick with nor with normal face Kumail yep yeah yeah that's a
bizarre movie to watch him yeah yeah it's fucked up I mean they should do
that what they do to the man they should do that to Ray Romano next they should
good dude I mean he once I feel like you either get that treatment when you're
famous in your 20s and you turn 30 or you're famous in your 40s and you turn 60
yep then they make a last-ditch effort to put fucking like mud in your head
until you look like a balloon yeah yeah I'm hoping I I'm hoping if we hit it big
I mean what kind of mods should I do that's a big that's a big question Marty
Marty maxing out my job I've been over that I want to I want a chin that goes
to like a point like one foot away from my face but I don't want any other changes to
the shape of my face just a line.
Like a pharaoh?
Exactly.
Tiny penis.
A pharaoh chin.
Tiny penis, big balls.
Well they won't have to do much work on that first part.
Yeah.
I know.
They'll have to upgrade it a little bit I think.
I think maybe I have to go bigger than smaller.
You need to go to small and not from microscopic.
It's gonna be a pretty big leap.
We don't have a lot to work with down here if I'm being honest.
Yeah.
Yeah well listen we could extend it to be like.
I want an inverted penis. We could get it like two inches longer but we'd have to take two
inches off of your legs in order to get the material we need. It's mostly going to be
foot and femur bone and we're going to build you a new penis. What if I get, what if you
get like a bone installed in your penis? I think you can, right? I mean you can get anything
kind of installed anywhere, right? I could get a TV in my back but I don't want to. No
reverse Teletubby. He could. I could get a TV in Janice's back. Oh come on don't do that to your wife.
Do it to my... I'd be doing it for me dude. Then you got to get a satellite and everything.
For me. To carry a satellite around. Put a satellite on her head, hide it in her hair,
TV in her back. Hey baby do you want to go look out of the window for two hours?
I believe it's Monday Night Football. But I think there's some birds out there.
there. Yeah, I just fire crop tops all the time. Yeah, I know it's a timber, but I just
think you look great in crop tops. Yeah, yeah, little TV, like PSP sized. You know, actually
just a PSP. Yeah. Yeah, maybe instead of getting any kind of body mods at all, I get a PSP.
Maybe I just get a PSP. Might be actually a way cheaper move. Or a TV. Yeah, maybe I'm
I'm thinking of maybe getting like a PSP,
something that's easy to homebrew
and just kind of like load it up,
like load it up with like old games.
- You're some sort of hacker.
I want you to know, if you hack something
or download a game, I will report you.
Yeah, I will be reporting you to the NYPD
and they're gonna kick down your door.
- That would be so funny.
- That's right, and they're gonna take all your games.
Actually, they don't even take the games,
they just delete the saves.
- Yeah.
- Oh, that's worse, they take my memory cards?
Oh, they know it's worse.
Yeah, they fucking know.
That's why they do it.
God.
Yeah.
They're going to catch you fucking on Jedi, whatever, Jedi Academy games on PSP.
You're going to be like one level off the boss, dude.
They're going to fucking snatch that shit, delete it, give it back to you.
I'm going to be on the Hoth mission.
Yeah.
They're going to...
Do you ever have a saved game like just super deleted by a sibling?
Yeah.
I had a save, yeah, my fucking Kingdom Hearts.
Kingdom Hearts 1.
It was my brother's birthday and I don't know what happened, but we were we had just beat Riku
We were about to beat the game and then somebody deleted the save we don't know who
But it was like some agent. We I don't know if it was like my cousin or my brother
I think I think we talked about this before yeah, we definitely have
Because this was sense this was a fucking nightmare
This was like one of the worst things that happened because we didn't know how to beat Riku
We didn't know why we beat him. We didn't we didn't understand like oh you have to use this thing and like this armor or whatever and
It was just like a fucking like
You fucking did it. No you did it. Why did you do it?
I didn't fucking do it like just going back and forth screaming at each other
And then we were like well, I guess we just have to beat it again
I think you maybe had an agent of chaos and on the premises.
Yeah, it could have been.
It could have been.
Maybe my mom deleted it.
Oh, my dad.
So you're your mom that your mom saw you and your and your brothers were getting too close
and we're gonna overthrow her.
She was like, I need it was my sister.
My sister beat it.
So it was like a like a thing where it was like all of us were getting along.
You can't let them.
Yeah, you can't let them reach across the aisle like that.
If they all get along, they won't need me.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- That's excellent.
They'll start cooking and cleaning
and making food for each other.
That's a bad sight for a mom.
- That is what happened when my sister left.
- Moms hate harmony so much.
Moms despise harmony.
- They wanna sow some discord.
- They love discord.
They hate harmony.
- Disorder, disorder, disorder, I don't know.
- My dad's fucked up my Mewtwo unlock on Melee
'cause he had to like leave the GameCube on
for like a long time or something.
Like you had to be playing the game for so many hours.
- Yeah, it's like 200 hours or 20 hours.
- Yeah, so I just left my GameCube on for like a couple days
and I came in after a couple days
and the GameCube had been off
and I was like, "What the fuck happened?"
And my dad, I asked my dad and he was like,
"Oh yeah, I had to turn the breaker off to work on a light."
And I've like never hated somebody so much.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I wish that he had just gotten electrocuted
working on it instead of fucking up my YouTube shit.
Oh man, when you're a kid, that's the most devastating fucking thing.
He's the only character in the game who does a backflip.
Yeah.
And my dad's worried about a fucking light in the kitchen.
Suck my dick, David.
My aunt Kathy ran over one of my skateboards.
Ugh!
And I, yeah, when I was like in fourth grade, and it was a...
It was like one of the most devastating.
Like, I was so pissed.
Like, I remember, like, my brother had just gotten another skateboard,
and that was like an older one that we had, that like a neighbor gave us.
And uh, she like, it was, I mean, it was pretty much already on the way out, but just the fact that she ran it over, I never forgave her.
That's tough. Can you imagine how much worse that is if you have like a- I still don't.
Like, do you know anybody who whose parents like ran over their kid on your car?
No. That's gotta be tough. Yeah, that I mean- They're talking about save games. That's fucked up.
That's not good. Yeah, the kid's gonna be so mad. I knew one kid and he was like,
I went to school with this kid and his mom was like our art teacher or something and they
talked about-- it was a Christian like homeschool thing and they were-- they told us like you
have to get together and have these like Christian conversations about shit and I can't remember
what they call it but like the reason why they became a Christian, they tell that story
and this lady told the story about running over her son with her car and she was like
yeah that's when I started believing in God because I like cracked his head open
and his brains are everywhere. And I didn't even notice for seven hours.
But like here he is he's still okay and this kid was not okay. God through all that
made him so normal and this kid was like he was fucking weird. He was like at
recess he would just try to get on top of whatever like every part of the
playground like he would like climb on top to the very top of the like slide
gym thing and he would just sit there by himself. It's like that like ant
parasite that makes ants climb up to a high place and then their head explodes
and shits up the sports. Yeah but his head exploded first and then he started climbing to the top of shit.
Yeah when his head was cracked open some an ant parasite crawled in from the
ground yeah dude I miss climbing dude we can hit a rock yeah you could go climb
I can't fucking do anything right now oh yeah I gotta go get vexed I gotta go get
my second appointment tomorrow I gotta walk to this fucking place no yeah it
sucks we get it I'll get like a crutch or dirt an uber or get Caleb to drive you
I'll get you a scooter well it is down that it's like they moved my appointment
place so it is closer but I still get a walk downhill and that's gonna suck I
I think walking uphill would be worse.
Just roll in a ball.
Like Sonic.
I could become a Droidica.
I could roll.
You don't have time to build all that armor right now.
I don't have time to build a shield generator.
Just buy it second hand, dude.
You just roll up like a roly-poly.
Yeah.
I'm ready to get my vaccine.
I have a question.
I'm gonna go to the vaccine and have like a
obviously like huge bulge of
prosthetic skin over the vaccine. And as you can see, there's like a jar
side.
Just right in there, that'll be perfect. Shoot it right there.
A lab coat that just says like Chinese government.
Yeah.
Yep. A little higher. No, right there. You see this up? I have a
Flight to catch.
You see the little nozzle right there on my arm?
Just right in the nozzle, please.
Yeah, you just have a valve that stops it.
And I also have a vaccine for you as well, if you don't mind, while I'm here.
Try this out.
Why don't I give you one?
You might be very, very tired.
Man, I'm dreading that.
I don't want to feel any more tired than I already do.
You should do some drugs.
Yeah.
Or go to sleep.
Yeah, man.
No.
The second dose was not that bad.
Which one did you get?
Pfizer or Moderna?
Pfizer.
Oh, I heard Moderna's second is bad.
I felt like shit, but I did not feel like shit.
I still went places and stuff.
The first dose, the day after, I was like, "Knock the fuck out."
Nope, I've not heard that at all from anyone about the first dose.
I think you might have an issue.
I think, yeah, maybe I'm a...
Did you stay up until 4am that night?
Yeah, probably.
He slept for 20 minutes that night.
He's like, "Oh, something about that vaccine knocked me out, man."
I don't know.
Maybe the second one will knock you out, though.
It didn't mind.
I just felt really shitty the day I got it, and then the next two days I just had like
a headache and was tired, but like it never...
I tell you what, if you actually get the vaccine, I'm going to knock you out.
Putting that poison in your body.
You get it.
No, I stood at an angle where she thought that she put the needle into my arm, but it
just went behind my arm.
And then it squirted on the ground and she noticed and I said, "That was me.
I squirted that."
That was my, that's my juice.
It comes out sometimes.
Yeah.
Yeah, no, no, that's my stuff.
No, that's my stuff and I'm going to take it also.
It should be on my allergy card.
I squirt stuff when I'm sick.
Any allergies?
I'm sick right now with COVID-19.
Any allergies at all?
Yeah, just, just, just I squirt.
I'm a squirter.
When there's too much pollen, I squirt.
I'm a bleeder and I'm a squirter.
So be prepared.
I'm a squeter.
I'm a squirter.
I'm a jurdle.
I'm a midnight squirter.
Squirting my stuff on the nerves.
Squirting the meat to fall on your bum.
How about that?
That's gotta be one of the worst songs ever made.
Really? You don't like the Joker?
No. You know what I like? Guitar Hero 3.
okay
guitar hero
man i've been saying it for
a year now i need to buy
rock band
i miss playing
i've said it to somebody
to who?
i think to will, i think maybe i talked about rock band and guitar hero
with will
well here's the thing about
i think guitar hero is like
music that I know is probably from Guitar Hero. Yeah. Like Guitar Hero has a
huge grasp on my mind. Remember that guy with that big-ass chin? Uh-huh. That ain't a
guy, that ain't fooling nobody. That ain't no person. Which one was that? Was that uh...
It's a male. Axl Steel, I think was his name. That's a great name. Yeah and then Johnny
Napalm and Judy Nails and uh... fucking Lars Umlott, that's a fun name. He's the
black
character you could design your own guitar in all the other games and they
like it so much I gotta get guitar here all right you know what Kim I'm gonna
get guitar here three today and I'm gonna try and find you I want to design
my guitar it's really easy so if you can't it's kind of pathetic did you guys
know anybody when that those games were out who were like guitar hero it's not
even like playing real guitar like that's always a stupidest shit dude yeah
I remember uh...
What, Forza 4?
I'm actually a real race car driver.
And that's not like driving a real race car.
You don't- you use a wheel, not a controller.
Oh, Tony Hawk?
Yeah, alright, go outside, fuckin' try that shit.
Yeah, just spam A and B all day on your skateboard.
Nothing's gonna happen, you're gonna do-
Yeah, people would say that shit about like Call of Duty and it's like you're 12 years
old.
Yeah.
This would never happen in a real war.
Yeah, trust me, I know war.
Yeah.
I'm actually a master chief and the energy sword. It's not it's not even that good in real life
You can't make a hammer that has gravity. Yeah, sorry you can't put gravity in something cars aren't called warthogs in space
They're just called cars. Why would he have a new name for them?
Warthog still exist I remember I was playing guitar here with my cousins once and
We were doing like the slash battle
And I think one of my cousins was like man slash must be so good at guitar here
I just remember this thing like, "Well, no, like, I don't think so. It's just pressing
buttons." He's like, "Yeah, but the hand-eye coordination."
I think the best part about those is that like, with like rock band and shit, is that
all of them are just like pressing stupid buttons or whatever and you can, people who
play those instruments can be like, "Yeah, whatever. It's not like that." Except for
the drums is just playing the drums.
Yeah.
It's just exactly like the drums.
You have to know how to play the drums to play those.
you have to be a drum a drummer to play that game well like there's probably
some people who have learned the drums through rock I'm sure there's a huge
amount of people I think I know people learn to dance people learn drums from
like electric drums I think because you can't you know I never considered it
like like looking at it like electric drums cuz it's like I look at that and
I'm like oh that's just a toy yeah well drums are a toy most instruments are
DJ Hero.
That's the thing, musicians need to grow, they act like it's art, it's, you know, you're
playing.
Yeah.
It's called playing music.
It's not, it's, exactly.
You're saying that because you don't play any instruments.
I play a lot of instruments.
Yeah?
Name them.
My mind and my soul.
Uh, well, one instrument would be the, like, writing a song is one thing that I'm sure.
I play my computer really well.
You have written a lot more songs than anyone else here.
You know, the notes.
notes I tend to play different notes. You know I was trying to get on your shit but I think
you know I went too far. The keys uh-huh the black keys. Damn really you play those? I can
only play the black part of the piano. Yeah yeah just a bunch of just sharp notes. My fingers are
too small and weak to play the giant white keys. I can only play the I can only push down on the
on the thin black parts. Oh I'm sorry I'd love to play piano in your band but I can only play
the pedals. I don't even know how to play the keys yet. Yeah I'd probably be really good
at driving a car. If you want to get like a really big piano and you stand on the upper
level and play the keys and I can stand underneath because I can't do the pedals with my hands
either. I can't like crutch down under a normal sized piano. You sit on my lap and you play
the piano. And I'll do the, I'll fuck up the pedals. I mean you don't have to worry about
it. Those notes are going to be sustained. Yeah I'm going to sustain every last one of
If you want to sit on my lap when you play guitar too, I can do that too.
I mean I can do the pedals for the piano while you're doing that.
It won't make any noise but it might be fun.
I can do some pedals for the guitar too.
Hey, why not?
Why not?
I think that they should add more pedals to the piano.
Yeah?
Well you could.
You could get an electric piano, plug like a...
They should add one that just drives around the piano a little bit, pretty slowly, like
five miles an hour.
Oh dude, I would hate to get one of those.
A piano where they mixed up the pedals at the pedal factory and they gave it car pedals
instead.
Yeah, from like a Lamborghini. It's the fastest fucking piano.
So she sits down to play her piano for the first time and it just shoots into the wall.
Yeah, that would be a big mistake, dude.
And you take it to the shop and they're like, "Yeah, see, the gear shift should have tipped you off right away."
Yeah.
It was very obvious.
You just have a whole car in your house, you think it's a piano?
It's got pedals.
I thought it was a piano.
Look, the fucking, the key's here.
There's a key.
- Yeah, there is a key.
- Whoa.
- A single key, wow.
- Cars and pianos both have a key,
pedals and a chair.
- Yeah. - Hold on.
And they have a sound that they make.
- And you can open up the hood to see
what Tom and Jerry play in.
- Yep, I think a lot of people don't realize--
- What Tom and Jerry play in?
(laughing)
What they playing in there?
I hear some Tom and Jerry shit.
- Walking into a dueling piano bar in New Orleans.
- Y'all do some Tom and Jerry shit in here.
Oh, now I'm out, man.
- Every time I play the piano,
I get really, really scared and I triple check the piano
to see if Tom and Jerry are inside,
if they're gonna pull any shit.
'Cause I do not wanna get hit in the face
with one of those hammer things from inside.
That shit would suck.
- I mean, one of those self-playing pianos,
tell me that, I don't know how those work.
It has to be Tom and Jerry, dude.
There's no way it's anything else.
Because you can't make a computer, we know this, a computer can't play music, that's
the Turing test.
Exactly.
So it's Tom and Jerry in there and they're fucking punching those keys dude.
And you gotta wonder, you're like, well not only is this weird to have a Tom and Jerry
in there, but it's also immoral because you know one of them is playing it with the other's
body.
Exactly.
That's how the Chuck E. Cheese animatronic bands work too, they got Tom and Jerry and
the guitars and stuff.
Just battling.
Don't even get me started on the xylophone, you know that's one of their rib bones.
it's their teeth uh-huh it's their teeth - it's either rib bones or teeth either
way this is not vegan to me uh-huh yeah it is not vegan to play any of these
instruments cuz Tom and Jerry or maybe maybe could be loony tunes yeah remember
Jerry's French cousin the little gray mouse it's like you guys like nibbles
the orphan is that his name I don't know if I don't think nibbles the orphan was
French the orphan who comes and he's even hungrier than Jerry and he eats all the
food and makes Jerry mad that he was I posted I posted about my thing and
somebody message requested me and said um you know his name is it nibbles the
orphan it's toughy the mouse right what I think one second was it toughy nibbles
also known as toughy yeah all right so you're both right fuck this guy yeah
shut up this guy fucking pussy you know what I'm gonna do I'm gonna chop you a
Way better name, I'll say.
I'm gonna chop you in half,
and then I'm gonna push out the eye of the ribeye steak
that happens when I cut you in half.
That's not gonna happen.
I'm gonna push it out with my big claw.
How come Tom never got an orphan to hang out with?
Quacker, Quacker Jeff Duck.
That's just lazy.
Tom and Jerry Loki, one of the best cartoons of all time.
Yep.
Remember when he went to heaven,
and then he went to hell?
Remember how racist it was?
Yeah.
I had a cartoon about a cat and mouse fighting and they still found a way to like...
They still made it racist.
Well yeah, you run out of ideas at some point, right?
It's like, ah, the cat and the mouse are chasing each other.
I guess we'll make it a racist thing now? At least they had that cartoon thing where they
didn't show the people's faces so when they had like Aunt Jemima walk in
at least you know they were gonna do some really fucked up shit.
that was a good move by them. When you when was the when was the day that you
realized Aunt Jemima was racist? What? For me? You know what I'm saying? Aunt Jemima's a
racist depiction. When was the day you realized that? I have yet to realize it.
Yeah? Yeah. I think she's pretty cool. I mean she seems like a sweet lady. I
didn't I didn't know about like this the like the stereotypes or anything
surrounding it and then like I think when I was in high school I was like I guess
that is a little fucked up huh yeah I heard they're changing auntie mama
because they find out that found out she was racist against whites yeah yeah
that's what I meant when I said that they're changing the logo to some really
messed up stuff yeah yeah switching it to a she said she said white people
listened to Radiohead and and they actually take a fucking made her lose
her job they fired her for that yeah it's pretty fucked up yeah she's
actually that size and they use her real body as a mold for the the syrup bottles
didn't just do like a doc didn't take out a book from the dr. Seuss yeah
something like that it was the one where it was like a Japanese is a Japanese.
They stopped publishing it. Yeah I think that you sent it to us forever ago.
It's like yeah these are two Japanese people. Well he did way worse stuff than
that. Yeah I know that's why it's so funny for that to be the thing that they
take. Yeah that one's like one panel in a book but he yeah he did some stuff.
Yeah you see how this guy talks about who's? Not kindly. Have you seen his
- It's so funny that-- - There's depictions of you, of who's--
- Of who's? - Their noses don't look like that!
- He has the whole thing of the sneeches,
where it's just like, "Oh, racism is bad,"
but you go like, you just look at any,
like all the cartoons he drew, like World War II,
it's like, man.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, he only thinks racism is bad
when it's like a bird-turtle hybrid.
- Who's more racist, Dr. Seuss for drawing a Japanese guy,
or my great-grandfather for shooting one in the head?
(laughing)
In World War II, which one is worse, you think?
probably doctor seuss you think so
i'm just kidding
woo i'm in the clear sounds good
maybe doctor seuss
i don't know
i think it's worse to kill somebody than it is to draw something racist about them
well well
uh
i don't know i think that's a no brainer
my history teacher told me it was all justified
in high school so
i think he's in the clear
yeah dude they were being mean or something
yeah they were all being mean
Yeah, they were being so rude about dr. Seuss's cartoons. Yeah ruined it. They ruined somebody's surf surfing lessons in Hawaii
So we obliterated two cities. Uh-huh. Yeah, somebody's fucking
Margarita got the umbrella blown out of it in Hawaii. Yeah by some wind
The hotel from forgetting Sarah Marshall had to close
Japan just dropped a fart on Hawaii. We have to obliterate it with a laser now
Mm-hmm, and I guess it worked kind of
What works?
Well, you know
It worked we what do you mean it weren't we won
World War two we won it right. I don't remember actually who won. I think yeah, I think we won, right
Maybe you know might have won are any of us Japanese or
Hitler no, we won't true. Yeah
It's cool how we won every war it is pretty cool. You got you start to wonder like man
Maybe maybe we're just the best. Yeah, maybe everyone's jealous of us. Yeah, maybe maybe that's why the war started in the first place
Mm-hmm
The u.s. Is so fucking swag
This sucks. We should fight each other for three years first and then see if they get involved. They're trying to bait us
Yeah, they were in on it the whole time. Yeah. No, we're doing some fucked up shit
Also, World War II, they were like, "The US is gonna want to get in on this so fucking
badly.
Let's just fucking fight each other forever and then just see, I mean at some point they're
gonna cave."
And we were just like, we were all in the US just like biting our knuckles, just like,
"Oh fuck.
Oh, I wanna go there so bad and kill some people, dude.
Please, please, just let me.
Let me go over there."
Yeah, they started doing the holocaust and everyone in America is just like, "Oh no, that's fine."
The what now? Sorry, no clue what you're talking about.
That word's too big for me.
Yeah, the holler what now? Oh, Hollaback Girl, Gwen Stefani, great song.
Yeah, and then Japan, fucking...
No, no, no, we're not talking about Hollaback Girl.
There's something very... there's something going very wrong here.
We're doing some messed up stuff over here that... see if you even fucking care.
Yeah. I think we need a World War III like insanely soon also. Yeah. Yeah. That stuff's getting too
good, dude. I mean, a world where we, us three, can be like kind of successful needs the biggest
war of all time to happen. Exactly. Agreed. We need something to just level the planet.
Just take it down, dude. We need every ice cap to melt. We need a meteor. A meteor. Giant meteor
2021 we need like cloudy with a chance of meatballs level like
Devastation. Yeah. Yeah. We need a giant pizza to fall on me and I go
Mmm, that's my favorite book as a kid. Did you guys ever read that book? Yeah, it was so awesome
I had to read that in first grade and then we had to write our own
Cloudy with a chance of meatballs story where it's like with the day that that happened to us
Whoa
I thought it was so cool and you know this should have been an early sign from my
parents to you know that something maybe was going on with my brain. My favorite
part of that book is I was like they have a part where they have like street
sweepers but they have like plates and forks and knives instead of the
sweeping. I was like that's the coolest thing ever. They need to make machines
like this. Yeah I remember in my thing in the first grade I wrote mine about how I
skateboarded on a sausage that's sick dude yeah that's actually I was in the
halfpipe similar personality revealer yeah yeah I never had an experience with
that book oh really yeah it's pretty guessing it out check it out at h24 I
think I might have to know yeah yeah you should cloudy cloudy with a chance of my
balls I knew you're gonna be in my pants from my balls cuz it's so hot out it's
getting damn cloudy sweating down there cloudy with a chance I got a storm
system leaving a stain yep yep okay let's keep going all right
clawing clawing at my balls cuz I'm a cat cloudy with a chance of swag balls
that's pretty good yeah you could I think you could probably sell that - you could
get like a Instagram TV that's like a soft that is like a swag balls that's
what would fall from the sky that's like a pet like swag what's the fucking a
hand's called no the the bags of weed that have like the name or like the
parody names there's just barely we've been oh I know you mean the ones that
have like like cartoons on them. Aren't they called runts? I don't know what they are. I've
just seen pictures of the ones that are like the Flintstones. Yeah. Like that kind of thing.
Stongebob, stony pants, weed pants. Yeah. I think runts is a type of weed. I think I'm
very wrong about runts. Well, runts would be called blunts. I bought fake white runts this
YouTube video. Let's see. What? I don't want to watch that. I don't want you to watch it
it is a gaming video. It's somebody playing Call of Duty and telling the story.
Playing with my runts.
Oh yeah, because there's, yeah, if you look up Obama runts, there's like a, yeah.
Did you guys ever hang out with any, with the runts of the litter when you were growing up?
Mm-hmm. Pretty much I was the runt. I was the one everybody doubted. And then look at me now.
I'm on top. Yeah. You're a big runt. And I can fight anybody now.
yeah all my brothers are seven feet tall and I used to know the little one but
now I'm now I'm the king of the damn castle yeah in New York they started
they started having because recreational weed is legal now so people have started
selling it out of trucks and so you'll just be walking by someplace and there
will be the like the most insane like twisted metal fucking like weed oh yeah
somebody just screaming out of I saw a weed truck in Times Square yeah they'd be
like do you wanna get high do you wanna get high and then like homeless guys will
walk up and be like fo sho it's you have to pay yeah do you have the
square app yeah yeah and they're always playing just like the worst like music
they're just like playing beamer Benzer Bentley yeah just on repeat yeah dude
it's a it's a it's a brave new brave new weed here in New York City
yeah I'm gonna just like old like songs that you would hear out of like a weed
car like that I've been listening to move that dope by future a lot oh yeah
when that song came out that was do that was like one of the best yeah cuz I
I miss that.
And then Pharrell talks about his big hat.
Yeah.
And you're like, "Oh my God, dude, this guy knew his hat was big."
He realized it all along.
I always thought that this was some sort of accident.
Maybe his hat had fallen into an enlarging ray, but it turns out that he bought a big
hat.
Before he got to the Grammys, somebody took a leaf blower to his hat.
Yeah.
Or maybe he got shrunk, but he left his hat.
I mean, Pharrell, I've always trusted Pharrell's choices like that, but that hat was too damn
much I mean that hat was huge uh-huh that was a big ass hat. Has anyone really talked about this hat?
That must be the size of Texas. Oh my god hey Arby's Pharrell has that your logo yeah wait a second
that that hat must be the size of the whole United States. Do you think that reached other countries?
That was like a big enough news story there was like an anchor in Mexico who's like a Pharrell hat
un grande. Caleb's been learning Spanish he wants to show off. I said grande. Yeah.
Everything else English but if you say it in that voice it sounds like Spanish. You said es un.
Which I think means is a so I said Pharrell's hat is a march. Yep I've been on my
Duolingo shit you know. Yeah. Kind of just when I'm walking around I'll be doing
Duolingo you know. Yeah. Sometimes you have to. I did that for a bit. Duolingo? I did well I
would like walk and do Duolingo. They just teach you the stupidest shit. Yeah, it's so
it's I don't learn Klingon and German. I have a small cat. Duolingo is it's it's
uh it's a trap. Yeah, I need to know. It's the same it's like it's the exact same
thing as one of those phone games it's like you need to buy more energy to play
Spongebob run. Yeah, I need a Duolingo that tells me how to like ask a Dominican
guy if he has car insurance because I just like rear-ended him that is like
the kind of Duolingo I don't need to know like that I have a big glass of milk
exactly the cat is a woman yeah like that's not gonna help me when I'm trying
to green that owl do a little go yeah kind of nice kind of nice with it though
he's manipulative as hell dude that's the owl from the lollipop tootsie pop
commercials you and he got he got throat game dude he's shy Steve his throat
games crazy dude okay imagine him going to town on your shit he's down there it
only takes three licks that's right shit goes crazy yeah it takes three licks to
get to your tootsie roll. He licked me like a lollipop. Goddamn, just imagine just like
that the tootsie roll owl like licks your penis three times and you immediately start pooping
at him. I've been busted in so long that all the nut is just coagulated and brown like
yeah dude looks like earwax it shoots out like out of a potato gun and he just
chomps it just faces the whole thing yeah yeah he's trying to teach you
Spanish - yeah do you get those emails from Duolingo that's like I miss you
yeah dude why when did fuck I just unsubscribe from like every email today
every like I know newsletter because they're fucking they're horny as fuck
yeah I unsubscribe from so many newsletters and they just keep sending
me like I unsubscribe them like three times and it just doesn't work like so
many of them just don't unsubscribe now it's so easy it's literally impossible to
use my email I love the ones that you get for like donating to Bernie that are
like, like, I'm, I'm on the ledge. Yeah, the title, and then you
open it and it's some poll from Quinnipiac. Yeah, it's like,
we're I am going to kill myself if you do not open this email.
Yeah, dude, that's a I think that should be outlawed. Yeah,
absolutely. Nobody should be able to send you emails. There
should be a do not call list for emails, but there I guess there
isn't, you should be able to just say nobody can ever email
me unless I ask you to. I guess that's what a spam filter is. Mine doesn't work though.
And then you forget to unsubscribe. You know what I found out the other day? I've been
a member at fucking Magic Mountain Six Flags for like two years, paying fucking ten bucks
a month. Is that the LA one? Yeah, it's in fucking Los Angeles. I knew I shouldn't have
got that fucking thing. You were like, no dude, if we go like twenty times then it's
worth it and then I dude and then I tried I went three times and then I tried to
cancel I think I'm actually still up because I only went three times and it's
ten bucks a month I think cuz it's 60 bucks per visit so I mean I'm still
winning obviously but the I tried to cancel it and the website when I press
cancel just broke yes wouldn't load anymore they love doing that shit yeah
- It's crazy, there's definitely something wrong.
- I have to go out there, and here's what they do.
They make it so you have to fly all the way out
to Los Angeles to cancel your membership,
and then you get there and you're like,
well hell, while I'm here,
might as well fucking hit a couple rides for old time--
- That Superman ride is calling me.
- Might as well hit Superman Return to Krypton real quick.
Oh my God, I'm coming again.
I'm re-upping my membership, wow.
That was incredible, I got so high.
- That's the same thing they do with Planet Fitness.
- Last time I went, I went with Joe,
and Joe was like about to vomit the entire time
and he ended up vomiting,
and I just walked into one of the kitchens that they had
and I stole an onion and two bags of tortillas
and I just walked around the whole park.
- I remember that.
- With like, and then every ride they'd be like--
- I think that might have been the onion that Patrick ate.
- Oh, it might have been actually.
- That is not it.
- I think it might have been.
- That was way earlier,
'cause there was a bag of onions in the hallway.
- I walked around all the--
- Isn't that the one that Caleb took?
- No.
- Could have been.
- No, 'cause that, when you didn't go to sit,
That was like when you first got to LA.
- No, you came when we were right about to leave LA.
- I went a bunch of times, bro.
- You were in LA, that was like a week before we left.
- That was not the same onion.
I can tell you that right now, it was not the same onion.
- I don't think it matters.
- It matters.
- It doesn't.
- It was the same onion.
- Every ride I went to, I'd have to put the onion
and the tortilla in the cubbies
where you're supposed to put backpacks.
And the person would be like, I'll take your backpack.
And I'd be like, can you just take these things?
(laughing)
I brought the onion on a roller coaster and it just flies out and kills somebody.
Well, because I was thinking at the time I was like I'm paying ten bucks a month for
this if I can get groceries every time I come to Magic Mountain I'm up so much
because there's no security on the restaurants you can just walk in there's
piles of food everywhere it's mostly tortillas and onions from what I've found.
And you can just carry them around with you dude. But and then on my way out there was
like there was like like they had a sheriff like a sheriff's department like
right outside of Magic Mountain and they were loading up like fucking m16s and
shit into the sheriff's department and Joe was like some it's an onion and he
thought that somebody called the cops cuz I stole that's pretty cool dude yeah
they were bringing like an m16 to fucking threaten you they're gonna kill
- Yeah. - Oh, they did.
- They were gonna do the thing from Good Time
where they pour all the acid sprite into your mouth.
- Yeah.
- And then leave you in one of the rides.
- I didn't see Good Time,
but which character are you insinuating I am?
- Security guard.
- All right.
I'm fine with that one.
- Why, what?
- Anything but that one guy.
- What one guy?
- From Good Time.
- Oh, the sassy brother?
- Yeah. - Oh, okay.
as long as I'm any character in that movie but him I'm pretty happy with that
comparison. You do a lot of stuff that Robert Pattinson did in that movie. Yeah.
Yeah. I've seen it. Yeah. Yeah. Can you get you to sign off on that? Can you say it? Yeah dude.
Fuck yeah. I'm Robert Pattinson in that movie. I do everything he does.
Oh no. What does he do?
He probably just helps us. He rubs a bank. He makes out with a sixteen year old I think too.
Yeah. Okay.
Can I be the one with the no brain, please?
Can I switch?
It's just deaf.
I think-
Can I switch sides?
All it is is he's deaf, right?
I don't think so.
That's not how I've had that movie described to me by comedians.
I don't think that's true.
No.
No, I think he looks deaf, but there's more going on.
How does somebody look deaf?
How many times do I have to explain this to you?
No, but yeah, no, this-
If you walk around and you see somebody and their face is a little bit wrong and you can't quite
tell what it is and then you notice that their eyes are really really big.
You notice that they're sound waves that are going into kind of like they can see.
Like they're kind of like watching sound waves maybe.
Yeah that person is deaf.
They sniff really loudly before they cross the street.
I don't want any of our deaf listeners to get angry. That's fair. All right. That's fair.
You know what's worse than being deaf is having super hearing. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Like tinnitus.
That's what super hearing. That's super. Is it? What? Really? No. No, that's it's tinnitus is
bad hearing. Tinnitus is like you fucking hear the earth's vibration. That's what that sounds.
Tinnitus is like also everybody has tinnitus is like I saw Brockhampton and I was it was too loud
and now I have tinnitus. Tinnitus sucks dude. Shut up. It's so evil. Yeah. I have very slight tinnitus.
Really? It's gonna get, dude by age 30 it's gonna be over for me. That's what Cameron gets for
listening to all those, that loud rock. All that damn rock and roll music. Honestly probably what
it was. Yeah. Probably just from listening to my iPod too loud. Cameron put on like,
yeah, Cameron put on like Psychosocial by Slipknot. Putting on Psychosocial, yeah,
walking to school and turning it up really loud so everyone could tell I'm listening to Psychosocial.
Sick. That was a power move, dude.
Yeah, yeah.
It's like, I'm suffering right now just to fucking, just so you know how cool this is.
I still turn music up way too. It's nicer loud, dude. That's what, it helps you get in touch with yourself, you know?
Yeah, I like to touch myself loudly.
Mm-hmm.
My, uh, this is a stupid fucking story from my youth.
My, uh, I think one of us said, like, "I want an eye touch for Christmas," and my Uncle Kevin turned to us and was like, "Hmm, I want an eye touch myself."
- That's clever. - That's pretty good.
- I think about that a lot.
- Dude, my uncles have had some bangers over the years.
- Yeah, I mean, the advent of Apple has to be
like the number one best thing to ever happen to uncles.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah.
- iPod, iMac, whatever happened to I have a job?
- Yeah. - You know?
- iPod, iPad, I paid.
- Yeah, iPod, iPad, I don't give a crap, honestly.
- Mm-hmm. - Yeah.
yeah I poop that's yeah I poop my damn pants like a neon shirt with like a
silhouette of a guy on a toilet and it says I poop you ever see those people
wear like an like a shirt with an Apple logo on it mm-hmm what the fuck yeah I
mean Pierce is taking like pictures oh yeah
on their cars this shit is so funny yeah it's such a fucking so many people
sticker yeah so many people put the Apple logo on their fucking cars yeah
insane I have an iPhone the sticker that comes with the phone yeah makes you go
the worst sticker ever made I think yeah the big joke is like putting it on your
like Windows PC or whatever and yeah like of a Mac I would know I would never do
something so controversial I don't yeah I would not do that I would I would put a
sticker the sticker that comes when I buy an assault rifle and I will put it
on my phone that would and that would be kind of a bait like a bait and switch
thing like it also be a bit of a commentary like which one of these is
killing me first exactly yeah yeah probably EMF radiation I mean the the
pen is mightier than the I mean the phone is mightier than they are 15 Wow
that was you know that was a moment of wow yeah that was I'm having clarity
right now yeah maybe the first time in my life I listen to the iPad iPod I just
thought. Wow and if you know and when you're on one of those damn things
you're not thinking. Absolutely. Yeah. Screen time, whatever happened to brain
time, excuse me, your brain. Screen time, whatever happened to scream time, I need
sometimes I just got to let it out. Sometimes you got to yell into that
pillow. Uh-huh. Yeah. And now what you yell into your phone? Mm-hmm. I don't think so.
You can't do that. Yeah. Apps used to be something that you would get at TGI
Fridays you know nowadays it's how you how you fuck a gay man as fast as
humanly possible yeah you know there's so many things and hey it's like they
always say there's an app for that mm-hmm yeah there's an app for everything
you know how everyone's still saying that except for meditation oh wait is
there there's an app for that a message a message used to used to say well now
it's on your phone uh-huh yeah preach you said notes used to be a musical in them
you had it in music I I remember when notes used to be sticky yeah I remember
that too oh my god I was thinking the other day how funny it is that people
who are like they pay like 200 bucks a year to use headspace and then they
think they're doing the same thing that like starving monks are doing yeah
Because they're doing it like on a subway train on the way to where we work.
What's Headspace?
It's like one of those guided meditation apps where like a British guy tells you
like just try not thinking for a couple minutes.
Yeah.
And those people are like I'm pretty much gonna like a monk right now.
I'm basically the same as like...
If you watch, I have to give you a secret right now.
You don't have to spend a dollar.
If you want to learn to meditate, all you have to do, you watch all three extended edition
Lord of the Rings movies back to back.
It's going to change your life and the way you think about things.
You get really into listening to very boring music.
You're going to be sitting on the couch all night thinking, "Damn, you know, the world
really is beautiful."
And you know what?
Some things come to you, you never thought of before.
You know, Pokemon really is ingenious.
That's true.
Stuff like that.
It'd do be crazy how cars go.
- How'd that work?
- That's how I think about everything.
- I don't know.
- That is genuinely how I think about everything nowadays.
- Yeah.
- That's how I've always thought about things.
- If I'm up past 10 o'clock, I sit there and I go,
damn, it's crazy they invented the hole in the hat
so it goes on the head.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- I remember having a moment where I was--
- You guys ever think about how we're like meat sacks
floating on a rock in space?
- Wow, yeah.
I'm gonna pop you.
(laughing)
I'm gonna pop you, I'm gonna squirt you like a balloon.
Yeah.
I did one time have a, recently I was like on a plane and I was like, how the fuck does
this work?
And then I realized, I don't know.
Every time, every time I'm on a plane.
I don't know how a paper airplane works.
Why am I trying to understand how this thing works?
I don't know.
Yeah, no, how you truly transcend is what, yeah, when you start having those dumb guy
thoughts that are so dumb that there's not even like yeah like it's like like
every every dumb guy is like oh we're just we're just meet sex on a spinning
rock oh like how does an airplane work but not every dumb guy can get to like
damn the computer keys are crazy yeah that's a way of saying yeah that's how
meditation gets you yeah that's it truly puts you in tune it's because you you
were make actively making yourself stupid or meditating yeah you're trying
- Trying to atrophy that brain.
- You're literally, you're emptying your brain.
That's what do you think is gonna happen?
- Yeah, dude.
What do you, I mean, yeah.
'Cause also like--
- I think if I think less, I'll be smarter.
- 'Cause also, like monks aren't sitting there like,
oh, I hope this meditation makes me better at running.
- Right.
- Or my job.
They're like, I'm trying to die.
- That's just what Buddhism is.
They sit around, they go, damn, it's so crazy
that a fish could be a bird.
- Yeah, and they're wrong.
Shut up dude, I'm doing mathematics.
Yeah.
One plus one plus one plus one, four.
Dude, it's so stupid to fucking try to be smart.
Just chill.
Yeah.
You know?
Just fucking watch TV, drink some beer, eat some pretzels.
How hard is that?
That's like literally the happiest you can possibly be.
Here's my impression of someone who meditates who would try to do that.
I can't drink beer and pretzels at the same time because that's too many thoughts for
me.
Or even this.
What is beer?
Because they can't remember because they emptied their brain.
How does beer work?
Yeah.
Pat, he's completely frozen.
I didn't even notice.
Sorry, I was meditating.
Wow!
Oh my god.
Wow, dude.
You're like the most zen guy in the world.
Did you come to any conclusions?
You're like Gary Shandling.
I did.
I did come to a conclusion.
What'd you conclude?
You're gay.
Woo!
[Laughter]
You ever think about how they make this, they can make, they have long sleeve and short sleeve shirts so they don't have that for pants?
Yep.
They do.
Not sleeves.
Yeah, pants don't have sleeves, they have legs, Caleb. Get with it.
Is that?
You guys ever consider...
Who named the key...
[Laughter]
Yep.
What kind of name is that?
probably some New Zealand guy Apple makes sense you guys ever think about there
was no you know there was no there's no difference between cats and dogs until
society changed it that's true yeah the society put the society came up with the
names you know cats and dogs used to the names used to be switched there a social
construct until until you call a lobby to switch them that's the fucking way our
world works until the Civil War the cats and dogs were opposite yeah have you
- Have you ever seen the caracal cats?
Like the hybrid caracal house cats?
- Yeah.
- Just thinking about that, that's crazy.
- What does that mean?
- You ever think about how a cat's ears
can hear the same as a human's?
Even though it's full of fur?
- What the fuck is this cat?
- Caracal cat?
You've never seen one?
- No.
- Oh dude, these are like the best cats in the world.
- They're cool.
- Yeah, the little floppas.
What the fuck is this?
It's the one that uh...
It's carnivorous, no thank you.
Dude, I wanna get one of the...
My goal in life is to move to Russia
and just own one of these
and just wait for it to kill me.
Why do you wanna go to Russia, dude?
'Cause it's where you can own this.
Yeah, they have cool shit in Russia.
Oh, dude, you can own so many fucking cool animals over there.
Alright, slave master.
I'm not a slave master.
You want a bunch of slaves.
I don't want slaves, I just want a caracal.
Yeah, you want to own it though slave guy. How is that a slave it won't do anything for me?
You're the slave you're the slave guy
duh
Yeah, you ever realize like really I was slaves to the to the animals
No, humans are slaves to their phones. Oh
Serious
I'm busy right now. I'm looking at a picture of a caracal cat eating a drinking a bottle. I
Don't like that shit. I don't like when people like fucking feed a skunk milk out of a bottle
Yeah, just relax dude. Well. What if its mom died?
Yeah, I don't care and he needs to be fed. I will I I don't care
What if why don't you care a skunk if I was a skunk? I'd probably fucking
The thing about Caleb is he loves to pretend to hate animals
I don't hate animals, but I'm not gonna fucking speed a skunk out of a bottle
I would do that and then it's you would you feed a fish a soda?
I remember when I was first when I was first getting I was first getting to know Caleb
I showed him a picture of my dog, and he's like I don't care about anyone else's dog. I don't want to see this picture
That's true
Anybody else's dog is not my concern
Yeah, and then fucking twice a week. You're like. Yo, you know my dog's name was crash bandicoot
That's not true. Yeah, it is. I've heard that so many times. You've definitely
talked about that. What other people like about that dog? I don't know anything about Patrick's pets, that's all I'll say.
I know all of your pets names because you love them too much.
Name all my pets. The one, Kiryum Abdul Jabbark? That's not mine. That's yours.
No, that's my brother's dog. Okay, so it's another person's pet that you like that you talk
about
for a hundred bucks and shut the fuck up right now.
Never looked at an ocelot before really.
They're cool.
Yeah those are cool.
Is that an alien?
You know what's an insane looking animal that I was- that me and Leo were talking about?
Look up the bulldog pat.
It looks like an alien.
Like for real- like it has the most insane mouth I've ever seen.
Oh my god!
It's so crazy looking.
Fucking christ.
It looks like a xenomorph or a predator or something.
Yeah that thing's terrifying.
I think it should be in jail.
Mm-hmm
You're going to normal human jail for that mm-hmm
Unleashing a bat in a prison
Every bats body plan looks like God designed them to just look like a flasher body plan like like look
They all have they all have their foot. I've never heard. I've never heard it described as body plan. That's what it's called
they all have when they're like put their wings out they all are like standing out
like this with like a big coat on their arms and then they're they're fucking
penis is just poking up oh yeah have you ever seen the picture of the bad penis is
a lot of animals to be a lot more modest if you ask me absolutely let me find it
yeah that's what I like when people put their dogs in bikinis something you see
lot in New York City. Have you seen this picture? It's a bat. It's a bat with a giant penis.
What? Let me see it. Google bat penis. No. It's the first one if I Google bat penis. This
can't be that ubiquitous of a photo. It is. Oh, yeah, I've seen this. Yeah. Not just big
penis, big ass balls. Oh, yeah, wow. It looks like it's got a disease. It looks like it
shouldn't look like that it looks like it had a it looks like dad and but just got
the penis it looks like they did like a photo realistic like edit of like a
middle schoolers drawing of a penis wait there's a bunch of them dude dude that's
a fucking hard dick yeah what that that that's ready that's looking for a mate
This bat's gonna lay some pipe, dude.
What the fuck?
What did I just find here?
I don't know.
Okay, never mind. Bulls penis bat soup and foigua. Foigua? Is that how you say it?
Foigua.
Disgusting food museum puts new spin on delicacies.
Three new bat species identified by their penis bones.
Damn that would feel I'd be so embarrassed if they discover me based on my penis bone
Like I don't think we have bones in our penises, huh? No, I think only I think where they might be the only mammals that don't
Have them not yet. I get that surgery true put a bone in your thing back you learn
The baculum dig. Yeah, we don't have it but like girls and the way she's have it and bang it with my baculum
I'm gonna get a Draculam. Yeah, yeah
Installed some fangs on there. Yep, but it's gonna hang on so bad put a fang on my thing. I put a fang on my fang
Mm-hmm ain't no thing up. Yo, but a fang on my wang
the first recorded
Explain the lack of baculum and humans might be more than 2,000 years old the biblical rib that was taken from Adam may actually have been
the baculum
Yo
his penis bone out and made it to Eve. Do you guys know that that Kane is actually Bigfoot?
Really? I thought it was Chewbacca. It's confirmed.
No Bigfoot is a rat. Nope Bigfoot is Kane and he's cursed to walk the earth after killing his brother.
So he got and also he got really hairy at some point. He fell into a glue truck
and then he fell into a hair truck and then he had to walk the earth for the
rest of his days. Damn. Yeah. Pretty crazy. Those are the coolest
Bigfoot truthers are the people who turn into like
you know make a bible or like he's a ghost or something
yeah instead of just like he's a big monster. They try to make everything the
bible. There's five or six times they've
found a like a mountain that has like a line
on it and people will be like this is Noah's
arc yeah yeah this is Noah's Ark and it got turned into a mountain to hide it
from us the people who think that they're used to the the Nephilim and
shit you know my absolute favorite like thing like that is is the well people
think that Marines in Kandahar fought and killed like a giant yeah that's my
that's my absolutely so good fuck that search just search giant Kandahar it'll
probably come up. How do you spell Kandahar? K-A-N-D-A-H-R-A-D-H-A-H-A. I think it's
norm supposed to be giant of Kandahar. Yeah here it is.
Oh it's one of those things where I don't think that's how it's actually
spelled but that's out of the type of people who think that a giant was there
would spell it. Do you think it's just like a big guy? I mean I think it was an
occurrence. I think classified by US government in his popular radio show
coast to coast. Oh, okay. So it was on, yeah. He was 12 to 15 feet tall, had six fingers
on each hand. Well, that's how you know it's inhuman. It has one more finger. Dude, the
giant of Kandahar should have hooped. He was tall as hell. Yeah. It's so fucking sick, dude.
I think it really happened. It has to have, right? Yeah. I don't doubt that it did. This
is the guy who talks about it a lot. It's L.A. Marzulli, who's that guy that I'd sent
the video before a bunch where he's like drinking a thing of water ball and he
goes like Osama bin Laden he's the guy hold on let me get my slurp here and then
he goes bin Laden he's the guy he rocks yeah I'll post that video with the
episode because that's all right that's time to spin in the rest of the day
checking out this giant thing yeah you should watch some la mars always videos
he's very knowledgeable on this type of thing.
The Kandahar giant.
He's got, he has some documentaries about Nephilim and stuff.
I think I might be a descendant of a Kandahar.
Here's a comment on the crypted, on the crypted uh, wiki.
I thought it was a giant.
No.
Nephilim are the giants.
There's a comment from DavinGaming903 on that wiki article about the giant of Kandahar.
"Imagine if this happened in World War II. You were a German soldier in the Russian
cold fields. Suddenly your squad tank gets smashed down by a monster. Then your squad
fired bullets and anti-tank shells to that creature. It died."
Real quick, I would like to point out, if it has nothing to do with what side you're
on and you're just imagining if you were in World War II and you start, "Imagine you're
a German soldier, okay?" That would be a bad sign.
That guy's a born storyteller too. I mean you can really see that happening in your mind's eye,
the way you described it. Painting a picture with words.
He's a master. All right, time to research. Bye.
Bye.