You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content!
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately!
*laughter*
*explosion*
I'm gonna suck Caleb's Jolly Rancher.
I'm thinking about sucking on Caleb's Jolly Rancher.
Okay, you guys talk while I finish my Jolly Rancher, because according to Cameron, I'm the most disgusting fucking piece of shit who's ever lived.
That's some true shit.
Yeah, Caleb's got a disgusting blue thing in his mouth and it's not...
A blue penis.
A blue penis this time.
What is it then?
A Jolly Rancher we just talked...
No it's not.
What is it then?
It's a chocolate egg.
It's my tongue.
It's a blue chocolate egg.
Yeah.
That's Hungry Hamster combo number four.
Hungry Hamster combo number four.
From the hotel.
From the Hungry Hamster hotel.
The Hungry Hamster hotel is one of the best hotels in the nation.
You can also, they have rates by the hour.
Yeah.
Yes, you can go in there you have sex in the hungry hamster hotel with a process ex hamster style. Yeah
Which is when you're both?
Hamster style. Yeah. Yeah
You go in it in and out. Yeah, can I get this shit hamster style?
And they go absolutely and they lead you into a back room and they fuck your ass
Hungry well feeding feeding you a burger. Yeah, what is the plot of the hungry hamster? We don't know yet. It's not out
It's not out. The trailer just dropped a few days ago. You should watch the trailer.
If you had to guess from the trailer.
Probably about the hungry hamster.
I know his enemy is in it.
What's his enemy?
The candy hamster.
The candy hamster?
Yeah.
Why? What?
I mean, just like, is there other animals too?
The snail with the tail.
Snail with the tail is in it.
Michael the crawler.
I heard Michael the crawler is going to make a cameo.
The crapping crocodile.
That's in the adult remake. They remade it for adults.
Yeah, you know I think they should do that with more movies where they put out
one for the kids, one for the parents. They should have done that with the live action Scooby-Doo.
And we can see Velma's beautiful nipples when she turns into Shaggy. What? Yeah.
She turns into Shaggy? Remember when they body switch and then Shaggy's like
feeling Velma's tits with his hands. No. You don't remember that? No. They put
Shaggy's stoner weed brain into Velma's hot girl body and he's... They created the
ultimate organism. Yeah. The highest life form. The highest level life form. He starts
grabbing his pussy and his boobies and he goes like, "I like this. Yeah, this is my
favorite thing. That's what Shaggy sounds like. He's like yeah. That's not what Shaggy sounds like.
Shaggy sounds a little something like this. Hey guys I'm Shaggy. I'm Norval. Imagine I'm doing
the voice. Man I don't want to go to the airport. Don't go to the airport. Yeah this is our last,
this is this will be our last episode hopefully ever recorded in the city of Los Angeles.
Yeah. Pretty excited. Yeah. Pretty cool. Pack a vest for your Jimmy in the city of sex. What is
that from? It's from California Love. Oh. That's why I've been saying it. California Girls by...
By the Beaching Boys. By Katy Perry. By the Beaching Boys. Okay, my finish... I haven't
finished it. It's actually stuck in my teeth. I'm pretty close to finishing my Jolly Rancher,
so then the podcast will start. Yeah. Yeah. We haven't started yet. No, we've just been
laying out our pitch for The Hungry Hamster. Yeah, so basically The Hungry Hamster
finds out that the candy hamster has stolen his family. The Hungry Hamster sounds like a movie
like when you would go to Woody Allen's IMDb page and just scroll all the way to the bottom,
one of those ones from the 60s that just nobody's seen. Yeah. You know, The Hungry Hamster. Well,
it's from 2020. Yeah, it's from 2020. Yeah, it's coming out next year. What the fuck? What? I
I thought it was a re-release. No. No? It's based on a book. I thought it was like
unfound or unfound. And then they made a game out of the book. Yeah. What was that
game called? The Hungry Hamster. And Nintendo DS. The Hungry Hamster and
Nintendo DS for Nintendo Wii. Yeah, they had a couple of games. They had
Hungry Hamster Ride Da Pony. Ride Da Pony, Hungry Hamster Off Da Wheel. Yeah.
They also made a spin-off for 3DS that was Candy Hamster. It was kind of like Shadow
the Hedgehog where you can play as Candy Hamster and be sort of the anti-hero type character.
It was the exact plot of Shadow the Hedgehog but with the Candy Hamster.
It was more like a fan-made mod.
But it did get an official release.
Yeah, they did the mod and then they actually got the people who made the mod to come onto
of the official hungry hamster team and those people actually made hungry
hamster guardians yeah yeah the MOBA yeah the League of Legends style yeah
hamster game where you can place all the different characters every hamster in
the game yeah it's hamsters versus crocodiles yeah and versus crocodiles
and snails yeah yeah yeah use your faction at the beginning yeah yeah
Hamsters are crocodiles and snails.
Yeah, yeah, and then there's play mode.
There's, yeah.
There's a, there's, you get to, there's the game, but then there's a bonus game section
where you can play.
Unlock different toys.
Yeah.
Yeah, like.
Different hamster style toys.
Or, if you're playing as snail and crocodiles, there, you don't play, because you just.
Because snails and crocodiles.
You do, yeah, they don't work.
Yeah, snails and crocodiles just do jobs.
They have work, work, work mode.
Exactly.
Yeah, you can unlock different pencils.
say that if you play crocodile mode it is actually harder because you're playing, I mean, you
don't have all of the other abilities.
That's true.
Yeah.
So it's a more challenging experience.
You really do.
Crocodiles can only move in a straight line.
Yeah.
Which makes it really hard on the MOBA.
Because you can't ever turn, you just can walk on a straight line through the map.
Yeah.
really easy to be killed by the by the falling rocks that are in the center of
the stage. And the crocodile traps yeah that are everywhere. Yeah the
poison the crocodile poison. And crocodile dung. It's disguised to look
like a leg of chicken. Yeah. Which crocodiles love. Crocodiles adore chicken. It's
interesting because there aren't any real legs of chicken in the game they're all
poisoned so you would think the players would learn but since the crocodile can
only walk in a straight line if there is one in your path there's no possible way
to avoid it and you end up just eating it because the eat button is the same as
the walk button. Yeah well it's only played with one button it's a joystick
game. Yeah stop doing that Patrick. How did that sound? Just sounds like you quiet. Yeah.
It just is muffled. He has his microphone in his ass. Yeah. No. Yeah it's in his ass and he's
sick. He's saying I don't know what just I just got so tired all of a sudden. Yeah
Come here. What? No. Come here. I'm not letting you do that. Letting me do what? I don't know.
Come here. No. Come here. Go to him. Come here. Go to him. No. Dude, there's candy over here.
It's okay. I'm serious. I have a candy. Look at it. Look. There's no candy. It's right behind my
hand. I can see. Oh my god. It's golden. It's the most amazing candy you've ever seen. It's
the golden candy. I can't. Show me your hand. I have bad mobility with my arms. Just come and
look at it turn it's right here look it's right here I'm serious I look at it why
are you you won't be able to see the candy if you put that I tried to hit
him in the face with the camera wake you up no fuck I'm away no I hit myself to
sleep hit yourself again he instantly fell asleep is that your slapping
technique no for the way that all all fingers now you stink it's lapping
yourself that was hit the microphone there you know yeah I'm always like why
do the microphone so shitty why do they keep stopping working and it's because
Patrick tries to hit every microphone every time we record and it's kind of
his hobby you suck dude I'm glad you're leaving you hear that that was the noise
of all Patrick's teeth falling out. Yeah. Because he got so sad. Yeah. I just gave up on him.
Oh, the day that I was very hungover here, I don't know what happened. Like, I think
something was stuck in like, you know, I have the cracked teeth in the back. You got
the cracked teeth. I got the cracked teeth, but something was stuck in the back of my tooth
and I just like, it just hurt all day. Like, it felt like I was having like nerve pain.
No, it felt more like a migraine. I don't know. I was very hungover. I think you were having a migraine
And then I ate Cameron's salad. Yeah, I gave Patrick my salad salad. When's the last time you had a salad?
I used to get salads at work. That's true. So answer the question. So like a week ago
I don't eat salads. I almost never eat salads. Yeah, I eat I eat walgreens salad because I have that walgreens gift card
Oh, yeah, true
The thing is about making a salad is that you have to buy like 50 ingredients to make a good salad.
And then you have spent $50 for one salad and then you have to throw everything away.
I was at work, I probably said this on the pod before, but this guy ordered all the
protein additions to the salad, like the tofu, like the falafel and stuff. He added everything
to a Caesar salad and it ended up being $21.
God damn!
Wow.
A $21 salad, to me that's nothing.
That sounds delicious.
I spent more on a salad in my dream.
Yeah.
Yeah. And in my dream, I have no money.
Yeah. I'm famously poor in my dreams.
I famously only have $100, which is one of the poorest things you can be.
I mean, speaking from our perspective, at least.
Because we only have $90 on the Patreon right now.
Yeah.
Everybody get - everybody tell two friends to subscribe to the Patreon,
and we can get to $200 by midnight.
Yeah.
And we can finally buy - here's what we'll do.
We'll buy 16 tickets to The Hungry Hamster and we will raffle them off.
We won't buy out a whole theater.
Here, honestly, I'm not, okay, breaking it for a minute, we will make The Hungry Hamster.
I'm serious. We will make The Hungry Hamster, we'll make all the video games, we'll design
the lunchbox and produce it, we'll do like an AliExpress, or an Alibaba like order for all
that shit. We'll make merch for The Hungry Hamster and we will do a full-length movie.
What if we just make merch for The Hungry Hamster?
Yeah, I'm not going to make a Hungry Hamster movie. Because I mean, there's already one coming out in
2020. There's already a movie coming out.
But what if we beat them to the market?
No, no, we should make the merch.
Just the merch for the Hungry Hamster?
Yeah, we should just bootleg some Hungry Hamster merch.
Do you think we would make more money than on the movie?
Yes, absolutely.
Because I already have, I'm already casting this movie in my head.
Okay, who plays who?
They've already casted it in Hollywood.
Who plays the Hungry Hamster in Hollywood?
They haven't released that information yet.
Oh, well, then they haven't cast it.
No, they have. They've cast everyone else.
Lupita Nyong'o plays Hungry Hamster.
go play as Hungry Hamster in my version. No, no. That's terrible casting. Why is that terrible
casting? Because Hungry Hamster's a guy. So? It's a voice acting thing. No, girls don't
voice boys ever. Oh really? That's never happened. What about Barf Simpson? That's not a real
character. Barf Simpson? Yeah. What are you talking about? That's not on the show. Barf
Simpson. Who is that? That's the son. No, no, you're thinking of the son of the dad.
You're thinking of the son of the dad Simpson. Oh. The son of the dad Simpson. The son of
the dead. Yeah. I don't know. My personal fan theory is they're gonna get Tom
Holland's to voice the hungry hamster. Yeah. Why? Well, you know. He's Spider-Man. Yeah.
And you know those characters have a classic history with each other. He's popular right now. Yeah. I think they
would probably be better with like... Adam Driver. Adam Driver. Yeah. Or... I think
Adam Driver is playing the candy hamster. Yeah. You think so? I mean yeah.
He's Kylo Ren. Based on the trailer. He can... I mean also he's proven he can
can fulfill that kind of role in a movie. As a monster. A big ugly fucking dope.
You did that with Marriage Story. Yeah. Yeah the Marriage Story video game was really
good though. Yeah. That was really good. I liked, I really liked all the
quick time events. Yeah. That they put in there. Cheat code where you can see Adam
Driver's penis. Yeah. It was fun. They modeled it specifically for the cheat
code. Yeah. What are you doing? What's that face? I'm cracking my knuckles. Okay.
I think they should get Michael J Fox to voice the hungry hamster.
I think they should get Michael Scott to voice the hungry hamster. I think he'd be pretty funny.
Well, you know he's in the movie, right?
What?
Yeah, he's live action.
But you can do...
Oh, are they doing full CGI or full 3D animation or are they doing like a Who Framed Roger Rabbit style?
They're augmenting a real hamster with CGI facial features.
Oh, like in the...
With cartoon eyes.
Like Homeward Bound.
a big red kissy lips. Sullivan the frog is in it too but I don't know what they're doing
with Sullivan the frog. Yeah it might just be like a small role. Like a cameo just for
fan service? Yeah. Miranda Cosgrove is playing Sullivan the frog. Really? Yeah. I heard that
Michael the crawler doesn't have a voice. He speaks in spider-ese. That's how Michael the
crawler speaks he goes yeah he's kind of like that he's like he's like if hungry
hamster was a spider hmm which um which hungry hamster universe that which which
earth are they doing earth 3.0 earth 3.0 yeah gotcha so the cyborg atrons aren't
part of it okay yeah that was an earth 4.5 and what about hamster the girl is
she in it yeah she's the love interest on this one I think she's actually the
Susan. Oh, really? The mother love interest. Yeah. Mother love interest? Of Candy Hamster.
That's why he's so evil. Oh, because he wants to fuck his mom. Which is one of the most evil
things you can do for a hamster. I forgot about that plot in the comics. Yeah. Of the
Hungry Hamster comics. Yeah, I think Kevin Smith did a really good job with the Hungry Hamster
comics. Hamster comics 52 where you first see the Hungry Hamster. Yeah. Yeah, it's really good.
It blows your mind. It does blow your mind. You think, you never think of hamsters as all that
hungry I feel like. Absolutely. I see them as more, they're more concerned about
their wheel. Yeah, yeah. Really a revolutionary character. When I was a
kid I buried, I've talked about this, I feel like I buried a hamster that was
alive that I didn't realize was alive and then it died in the ground. I didn't
know that. That's pretty common I guess because hamsters have like, they will
like stiffen up sometimes but they're not actually dead. They're just pretending.
Yeah. So how did you find out the hamster was alive? You know I just kind of
guessed. So it could have been dead? But I'd like just gotten it. It was like I
guess like oh I think it was because their bodies don't like go stiff when
they die really. Not in the same way. This thing was like he was like stiff. Yeah.
And I guess he was like in shock. Oh, and I just put him in the kill.
Instantly. I would never do that to my hamsters. Yeah. Suffocate him with the earth. Mm-hmm. I kind of put the entire earth on him.
Yeah, kind of when you think about it. Kind of to drop the world. Yeah, I dropped the world on that bitch. Yeah, Kevin Rudolph style.
Yeah, I might drop the world if I change hands. Yeah, if I change hamsters. If I change hamsters. If I change hams.
If I change it, I wonder if hamsters are named after the ham
Yeah
They used to be the guys who would sell ham. Yeah, they called them hamsters and then they lost consciousness
They lost they lost their body. Yeah, they lost their bodies and became small little little little peanuts little penises
Little penises little furred penis a furred penis furred penis
My name is furred penis
Need my name's hurt penis need help refinancing my car
Yeah, third penis works at H&R Block. Mm-hmm
And he can't get his shit together. He's
Messing up. He's spilling water. He's fucking putting
He keeps giving Finn Dom's money. Yeah, absolutely
Stop it for penis for penis. You got to stop giving Finn Dom's your money. You're listening right now
You have three kids for Ferdpenis. This is a reality check. You have three kids and 20 hamsters
And you need to start providing for them. You got a whole series of hamster tubes in your house
And you're spending that shit on Fendoms?
Come on, man. You gotta buy hamster food, Ferdpenis. Playa, you fucking up. You gotta buy candy for your hamsters.
Mm-hmm. Hamsters love candy. Hamsters love eating dark chocolate. Yeah. Give them a bark-
Give them dark chocolate bark right now. Mm-hmm. Give them a hamster a butter finger and watch that shit gets stuck in its teeth
Yeah, now that's some funny shit. Do you guys brush your hamsters teeth? Never? I don't have I don't have I don't have a toothbrush
It's small enough. They don't make them. That's fair. You can use a regular toothbrush
You'll need the front of the you can use a regular toothbrush if your hamster is six feet tall
My hamster is pretty big not a big hamster. It wouldn't my hamster is like three feet tall
That's pretty big. I told you yeah, but still a regular toothbrush is to use a half-size toothbrush
They don't make even half size. I made it you made it from what is it to bark made out of dick and grass sticking grass
It's not a toothbrush. That's gonna make your that's gonna make your hamsters teeth even more. He's just gonna eat the grass
Yeah, that's why he likes it
Terrible terrible way to brush. Oh, he wouldn't he wouldn't let me brush his teeth if I used what what do you use a knife?
That's awful. No what I do you know what I do you listen
I don't brush his teeth, and so you just want his teeth to rot out, and he's gonna die like Patrick's gonna die
Yeah, I'm probably gonna die from some dental shit now that I think about it
You think you're gonna die from dental shit
I think that there's I'm gonna get an infection in one of my teeth
And it's gonna spread to my brain, and it's gonna brought my brain out well
In my eyes Patrick's brain is gonna suck his teeth inside. I'm gonna die of cancer
We had that too probably mouth cancer. I'll probably die of all
Everything everything at the same time probably I don't see why not
Yeah, that's a really good point. I don't really see why not either. I can't really you there's a 50% chance of anything
That's true. It's actually a 75% chance 75% chance of anything. There's actually a 100% chance of anything. Oh
My yeah, whoa. Yeah, you just changed the game. Yeah, that was my shower thought last night
R/showerthoughts. Don't you hate when you have a shower thought? I hate when I have a shower
thought. I should go to school tomorrow with my dad's AR-15. Shower thought. Shower thought.
I should go to school tomorrow in the shower. Yeah. I should start a school inside this
shower. I should go naked style to my jorb. Tomorrow. Yeah. I should probably use the
soap on my body yeah that's a show right there how'd you how are you guys I'm
tired you won't care you have a job to do buddy be so tired you wouldn't be so
tired if you didn't keep saying you were tired that's true I'm manifesting I'm
extremely awake that's the noise of an awake man yeah an awakened an awakened
guy. Awakened spirit. What if we did a watch-along of the Irishman? You want to do a three-hour show?
That'd be pretty good. No, because I need to... no. Why don't we do a watch-along of...
When I went fishing the other day, I was like, "Yeah, you know, I could never watch the
Irishman. It's like three hours long." And they were like, "We just went fishing for three hours."
That's funny. Was Robert De Niro there?
The fishing joint? Yeah. That fishing joint?
Oh, did you? I sent you the...
Spike Lee Fishing Joint.
I sent you guys that place I found, right?
Yeah, what was it called?
The Poetry Studio.
That's sick.
Did you go there?
No.
Why not?
I went to the Supreme store today.
How was your solo campaign today in the name of Los Angeles?
It was... So I ran into somebody that I like a...
like somebody that I'm like mutuals with on Twitter but like
you ran into them?
they were um
crossing the street at um
I think it was like towards the tender greens
they're crossing the street there or
might have been closer might have been by united but
they're crossing the street they waved to me I waved back and then I was like
what the who the fuck was that and I turned around
and then they were waving again I went like I waved again and then I got a DM
from them they were like they were like oh yeah that was me I was like oh shit
okay I've never been noticed before who was it this is guy Reggie Reggie Fils-Aimé
Redman yeah from Wu-Tang Clan from Wu-Tang holy shit it was Wu-Tang Ted
Wu-Tang Ted oh my god but you didn't tell us that Wu-Tang Ted's been walking
around no walk around waving at people oh my god waving at motherfuckers but so
then from there I just kept skating down and then I think I think I got to the
Sunset Strip or whatever is that is the whole Sunset Strip is yeah is this whole
thing called Sunset Strip and not really Sunset Strip is like when when sunset
stops becoming just like a straight line uh-huh and it starts like that's where
the comedy store is and stuff oh I didn't get that far yeah that's like
just like four or five. I went to, I like skated by the big Guitar Center and like
I was skating and I accidentally skated through a little patch of glass and then
a very fat guy holding a guitar stared at me out the window of the Guitar Center.
Nice. And then I like... How could you tell he was fat? Yeah. His penis. Yeah.
Yeah it was a very, it was very foggy glass. There was only a space.
No, no, he was coming out of the store.
And then you could see his penis.
Yeah, he was so fat that he took up every inch of the store.
And so you looked in and you were like, oh, they have like skin-tinted windows.
But then you saw a face.
And a penis.
A face and a penis right next to each other, coming off of this amorphous blob.
And you said, oh, it's just a very fat man.
And then you saw a guitar in his mouth.
Yeah, Douglas Banila.
Yeah, it was Douglas Banila who occupied.
They haven't been able to open the door to that guitar center for 20 years
because he's been stuck in there. You have to play the magic song. And he just keeps getting bigger and bigger.
Eddie Van Halen's guitar but it's a problem because Eddie Van Halen's guitar is in glass in the front of this door.
Exactly. They're selling his guitar. So I got towards the... so I skated past
the Guitar Center. I just kept going and like I just I had like the urge to just
ask people like hey where the fuck am I right now? Yeah. Because I was just in
West Hollywood I didn't know what the fuck to do and then I like realized I
was on like the intersection where Fairfax is and then I just went down
Fairfax Street and that is just the worst place on earth yeah yeah Fairfax
like there's like the the Hasidic part was nice but then like the hype beast
part is just like I hate them both yeah I'm being honest no I can't say what I
was gonna say which is that you should nuke the Supreme Store yeah no the
the supreme store so it's all just yeah the whole thing that you walked by the
faze clan store oh no no I didn't know you have a store
I think they had a store in arcade oh shit pretty awesome I did see it we
should go yeah let's go right now fuck the podcast yeah fuck you guys fuck it
no I went to the golf Wang store cuz I wanted to cuz I was gonna get something
for Dom's brother nice cuz you were like oh my two favorite things mm-hmm
golf and wang. But I went in or I was at the door and I was like how the fuck do you get in here?
And it's like a slight it's like an automatic door right? But they have it so the sensor is
on the inside and the employee has to come up to the door and let you in. That's odd.
You have to convince them you're cool enough to get into the store.
And then they tell you you can't use your phone and you're basically not allowed to touch anything
on the racks. Like they have signs on everything. They're like, "Hey, do not touch this."
That's a genius idea for a store. The store that doesn't sell anything.
It sucked, dude. It was so bad.
Sounds cool to me. I would have enjoyed it. I would have made the best of it. Just saying.
I make the best of most situations, which is something I guess Patrick,
it's a skill that he doesn't really have anymore.
You guys know you would not like that.
I would have loved that.
I love not touching things.
Break the thing.
I would have walked in and said, "Yeah, I'd like to...
You guys, let's do a stand-up comedy show in this store.
I'm gonna get all of my favorite comedians who are my friends, and we're gonna come in
here and we're gonna do stand-up comedy improv everywhere."
And they would have said, "You know what, buddy?
We could try to stop you, but we're not going to."
Yeah, and we'll have beer.
And we'll have...
And you know what?
We'll bring the beer, you bring the comedians, we'll bring the beer, we bring the music, you
You bring the fun.
- And we bring the beer.
And they would have said yes,
because I was, it would have charmed them.
- They would not have said that.
- No, they would have said yes.
You know what I would have said?
I would have walked in and said,
"Can I touch the clothes?"
And they would have said,
"For you, Caleb, you can touch anything."
And then the guy would have showed me--
- I would have gone out to the door
and it would have opened without the employee coming.
- No, it would--
- I have the remote in my pocket.
I have the remote in my pocket.
- You actually have to have a specific facial structure.
- Yeah.
- And it scans to see if you have it when you walk up.
It's based on your haplo group.
It does not let Irish people in.
That's true.
That's why it didn't open.
Yeah, but for me and Cameron, since we weren't cursed, we would have been let in.
Yeah, I don't know. I was very mad about this.
Yeah?
Yeah.
You still mad?
A little bit.
Are you madder now that you know that me and Cameron would have easily
entered, penetrated this door?
I am hopping mad.
Yeah?
Did they put lasers?
That reminds me of Sullivan the Frog's famous catchphrase.
I saw Sullivan the Frog on top of the Jim Henson Studios today.
Is it a Jim Henson production?
Is that who's doing it?
Sullivan the Frog is on top.
Dude, they put Sullivan up there?
Sullivan, he's got a big top hat.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
That was actually, that was really nice to just run into.
This the Jim Henson Studios?
Yeah, like I went down, I forget what way I went, but I was like down, I had to walk
up so I could skate that way and then I just kept going down I think it might
have been I was on Santa Monica and then I went somewhere else and then I ended
up near Kat Von D's tattoo studio and across the street there was like this
really good like ledge that I was skating and then like an old man was about to
yell at me so I had to leave. He went "I'm about to yell at you!" I'm getting so close!
charging up. He did. He lifted his bags at me. He went like...
I owned. I was like I'm not dealing with that. Seeing like the Jim Henson studio and stuff
my I would say the predominant feeling of like walking around Hollywood and like
most of Los Angeles is like how am I allowed to be this close to stuff? Yeah
no they had the gate wide open I was gonna walk in. But there's like just like
everywhere you go there will be like something that you remember from like
you being a kid and you're just like I didn't know that this actually ever
existed. Yeah. It was just like a fake thing in my brain. There's a lot of
strip clubs out here too, I didn't know that. Yeah and those are the
ones that I'm talking about. How do I, how do you let me this close to women? You
know? I saw just like a homeless guy just sitting in front of a strip
club and he was just like looking at the pictures and rocking back and forth. He
might have been jacking off. Yeah just jacking off. I like the smell. I like that guy. Yeah.
Have you had any good homeless encounters? No. No? Not that I can think of.
You're missing out. We're gonna get you one tonight. I'm gonna pay for that.
Mm-hmm. Yeah. I'm gonna get sucked off by the homeless guy. I think I said it, did I
already say it on the pod? The guy that attacked the skateboarders? Yeah. Yeah I did.
Yeah. Yeah I saw that guy. You saw the clown woman? Yeah the clown lady who
times. Who eats Blaze Pizza. Yeah, eats Blaze Pizza and cigarettes. Mm-hmm. Yum. You're
allowed to smoke in the in in the seats outside of restaurants? You can smoke wherever
the fuck you want. Really? Yeah. That's crazy. There was a lot of people just
like in restaurant like patios just just smoking. You can smoke in the hospital.
You can smoke inside your baby's room. Los Angeles is a smokers
paradise. That's true. In every way. Yeah, they'll let you smoke inside your own
shirt. Yeah. You can blow the smoke down into your shirt. You're not allowed to
smoke in one of the forest fires though. Because then they don't know which
smoke to put out. Yeah. It confuses the prisoners who were fighting the fires.
Yeah. Whoa, whoa, Caleb. Yeah. No, no, I think it's good. I was walking, I forgot
that LA is like this, but I saw like a... I think Ryan made this comment about like
we saw a sign on us that said like a something something a woke Japanese game
show and he was like oh that's like the first time I've seen woke not used in
like a derogatory context. Woke Japanese game show is super funny. Yeah. I like
that term. What is it? Woke Japanese Game Show. What do you think you do on it? You
just don't like molest women on it? You don't put women in a plastic cube. Like a
squid costume where the boobies are cut out? Yeah and you don't put it you don't
put them in a plastic cube. And then you drop them down a 100-foot hole. Yeah. You don't cover
them in you don't cover them in sashimi and make a Komodo dragon lick it off.
Yeah I would do that. I think that's a thing. I think that's a real clip. There's
Ripley's Believe It or Not episode where they show you about or they show you
like the sushi that you eat off of a human body. Yeah. And he said jack my
fucking raw dick to that shit when I was a kid. Yeah. You're skinless. A guy's body.
Skinless fucking bone. It was a girl's body dude. It was a girl's body dude.
No no no. On a guy there would be no place to put the sushi. What do you mean?
Caleb jacked off to a guy, a naked guy swimming in an aquarium. No, that's not true.
And he said, wow, this is just like, this is, this is like if a girl was covered in sushi.
Do they, do they actually put sushi on nude women? Yeah. Really? I do.
I don't. Do they actually drop women down holes? Yeah. Okay.
You never know. I've seen a woman in a hole. Yeah, what hole?
The whole damn country.
The whole damn enchilada.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
So Patrick, what's your top five?
Do a little
list. Top five things I've eaten here.
Top five restaurants here.
Okay. So the castle
was pretty good, but it doesn't make the list.
The castle? What's the castle?
The Korean barbecue place we went today.
I was telling him they made such a
mistake designing the place by putting the troughs of marinating meat that you
eat like the beef bulgogi and shit was just like brown shitty meat they put it
in giant bins like next to the entrance of the store so it's the first thing you
see when you come in but then you get it then your heart tummy gets hungry for
that meat but then you get a little hungry also when you walk by it and you
go can I have can I give me the whole can I give me the whole trash can yeah but
But it was pretty, it was alright.
Yeah, they just had like very weird rules there, like, oh, the kids 1 to 2 eat free.
Children 3 to 10 get 10% off.
That's so funny.
10% off.
That's so strange, like are they gonna check?
Yeah, let me see your kid's ID.
I am 1.
Yeah.
Yeah, you could, I mean you could go in with your one year old kid and be like, yeah, my
son would like everything on the menu.
Yeah.
anything but my kids really hungry yeah oh it says that they charge you per
person it doesn't matter if they're eating or not yeah that is and then any
meat that you don't eat you pay for by the pound what yeah so we six bucks a
pound for the so Caleb and I like realize that midway through the meal and
then had to eat everything we fucking guy yeah we got probably a pound each so
it's more expensive if you don't finish if you don't yeah yeah what the heck can
you can't like take it home? No, no it's a Korean barbecue place. Well I mean you
could cook it and then cook it yourself. Oh okay. But they also don't let you take
stuff home. I see what you're saying. Yeah, yeah I gotcha.
Yeah so if you if you can't finish it you're fucked. You gotta go there very hungry.
You're totally fucked if you can't finish it. Okay so the castle doesn't make the list.
Doesn't make the list. We're gonna do top five right? We're gonna do top five I guess.
In-N-Out the burger was good but the fries weren't. So in and out, okay.
But the peppers were good. And the milk. Let me let me figure out, okay, where do we go?
In-N-Out, Del Taco, Roscoe's. Roscoe's is number one. Yeah? Roscoe's was good.
Roscoe's is... Jollibee. I think it might have been just because I woke up and I
was still very drunk. We're eating the Roscoe's in that state. The waffle was
really good. Oh my god. The best waffle I've ever had. I think Jollibee chicken was
better than Roscoe's chicken. Yeah, that's... if you get... here's the meal. Yeah.
Here's the meal. Here's the meal. Here's the da meal. Da meal. You go to Jollibee
Drive-Thru, you get two chicken... Spicy. You get the spicy chicken. Yum. It's called
Spicy chicken yum. Spicy chicken yum. You get two of those. You get two drumsticks.
Isn't it chicken joy? Chicken joy. You get two chicken joys.
Drums only. Yeah. Then you go to Roscoe's you get one waffle. Okay. With a side of
syrup. Yeah. And then you go home. Then you go to In-N-Out and you get those peppers.
And you go to In-N-Out you get the peppers. Then you go to the
grocery store get some milk. Then you go to Castle Korean BBQ. You fill up there
so you don't have to eat what you just got.
- Mm-hmm.
- It's true.
- And you can put it in the fridge for tomorrow.
- Put it in the fridge for tomorrow.
Then you go to Del Taco, you get the beans.
- Mm-hmm.
And you spread them all the way down your hallway
and you use them like a slip and slide.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Okay, so Roscoe's number one.
Jollibee is number three.
- That's an interesting way of--
- The chicken was good,
but I don't think the pasta was very good.
- You didn't like the Paul Bak surprise.
- The shrimp dissolved in my mouth.
That's such a good thing to say about meat.
Yeah.
That means that it's good.
Actually, you know, if it didn't have the shrimp on there, I like the, if it was spicier,
if it was spicier, it would have been very good.
Number two, or in and out is number four.
Okay.
And I can't, where else did we go?
We went to Del Taco.
Millie's.
Millie's Cafe.
Oh.
The Hawaiian place.
Oh yeah, the Hawaiian place.
Got some shrimp.
Hawaiian place? Oh yeah, the Hawaiian place got some spam. Yeah, the Hawaiian place was
good, but I don't think they make the list. Where else do we go? Anywhere? It's funny
that you... Oh, Chick-fil-A is number five. Chick-fil-A is number five, so you have an
empty spot at number two. Yeah. Okay. So we could figure this out later when we go get
food. I guess we could. Yeah, we have to find a place that is really good, but it's not
- It's not as good as Roscoe's.
- Better than Roscoe's.
- But it is better than--
- So if anybody has any suggestions,
while we're recording this right now,
in the past for you,
send it to Patrick, text him right now.
I'm gonna let three seconds pass
to see if anyone texts any time travelers.
- Wouldn't I go anywhere by myself again?
- You went to that one,
that place where you got the hot chicken
that made you fart.
- Oh, Crawford's.
- Oh, Crawford's was good.
- And you filled my room with your farts.
- Yeah.
- The Nashville hot.
- Okay, I think--
- The Nashville fart.
Crawfords is number five and then you push everything else up one
Okay, okay, so now we don't have to eat dinner. Yeah, yeah, you don't gotta eat now
I finally don't you can skip dinner again. Yeah, I love to skip dinner now. This is my top five places
I've eaten since you've been here
It's pretty much the same list I would say except instead of Crawfords is a ramen place I had yesterday. Yeah
Yeah
What about you?
I don't know.
Cameron doesn't like food.
That's smart.
Yeah, I will like, I like a lot of the food we ate.
I like eating peanuts.
I like picking the corn out of the poop I find in public toilets.
Yeah.
Poop you found on the street.
On Sunset.
And I put it into my, and I grind up the corn and make it into a tortilla and I eat the
tortilla plain.
Tortilla.
I feel like that could be like a food trend.
Like pooped corn.
- Or pooped corn that you pick out and turn into,
you wash it really well.
- Yeah.
- But like, I feel like it has changed it a little bit.
- That's what good coffee is like,
has been digested by some kind of animal, right?
- You're saying the best coffee beans?
- I don't know.
- People, yeah, that's what they do for like fancy coffee.
They have animals eat it and shit it out.
I'm pretty sure. - What the fuck?
- I'm pretty sure.
You have your favorite--
- I don't disbelieve you.
- Yeah, I don't remember what animal it is.
I'm gonna look it up.
- You guys keep talking about pooped corn.
- Yeah.
- I just feel like pooped corn,
make like a cheese corn what what about it we could have got it today oh we
could have got some elote we can go we can still get some of the
get some elote yeah I don't know of a restaurant that sells it around here we
would have to probably go to a street but we would need cash
kopi luwak it's a spur it's a specific it's the world's most expensive coffee
but I think it's I guess it's like a tourist trap yeah and it's been digested
buy a civet which is kind of like a raccoon type animal.
Interesting.
Yeah.
Could I sell this?
In the west, Kopi Luwak has become known as cat poop coffee.
Oh, okay.
So, if you've ever had any cat poop coffee, that's what it is.
Yeah.
I don't think I've ever ordered a cat poop coffee.
I try to order every time at Starbucks and every time they say, "Sir, please scowl."
I think I got it as a prank.
Yeah, I pranked myself by drinking cat poop coffee.
You smell my hat.
I feel like this is going to suck because I see the grease on your hair.
You look like Neil Hamburger.
Yeah.
Is it gross?
What did it smell like?
It smelled like hair sweat.
It smells like Hat Ultimo.
Yeah.
The ultimate hat.
Dude, I don't think I've washed this.
I don't think I've washed this.
I'm feeling sick to my stomach now.
I've had this hat since 2013.
Stop talking when you don't have the microphone.
Oh, I've had this hat since 2013.
I've had this hat since 2013.
uh...
hope thirteen stop talking when you don't have the micro i've had this had
since twenty thirteen
and uh...
well no i watched it
i watched it like
the week before i came here
yes i just accumulated all i know we have some of the only one in what
grease
if you know i want it in pooping p
uh... even with even worse why would that be worse it's probably better
something that i have a list of things stink
now like cameron
like me karen's a big stinky larvae i'll be sticking to our vote and i can't wait
to keep it
but you would like to keep it and you know it loves to be a little bit on the
air comes to the camera doesn't think you can't raise fucking because the
short-term ready to keep a team in a few paid into a chrysalis
unit all of you wish a a fucking way you would have a really good you paid a
different hands you see your vision
chris will not let you keep it into a chris hates you
I'm going to pupate into a chrysalis and then I'm going to turn into a big fly.
No, he's not going to turn into a big fly.
No, he's not.
No.
You're going to turn into a gay butterfly.
Yeah.
He admits it.
Fuck you.
I'm going to turn into a big insect.
Why?
I've just been thinking about it.
If you think about something enough, you turn into it.
um all right we don't you guys know about girls
ow caleb got the ouch penis i got the ouchy penis
no i don't caleb got the ouchy penis i would love to be a transformer who just
turns into a baby yeah it would help so much you would get
if oh okay you go to the okay so you're a transformer who can turn into a
baby yeah you show up with your friends to the castle yeah you transform into a
baby yeah it's a three-year-old baby that you transform into and then you know
it's a no it's a two-year-old baby transformers transformers can't be
younger than three years old that's one of the rules I don't special I kind of
feel like that's maybe true what I think you can't you the transformers have to
at least three. Otherwise they wouldn't have names yet. Actually you know what I
just realized the castle charges you by the letter. By the letter?
Yeah by A, B, or C. Oh yeah there's three different letters that you can eat.
Yeah that's true there's menu A, menu B, menu C. Menu A is $13.99 and menu C is $18.99.
yeah that's insane imagine menu B doesn't exist imagine imagine oh god
menu menu a was pretty pretty bare-bones yeah that's a I just look you know what
I think it must have been I don't know what the other tables got but they
walked up to their tables and then just immediately threw a bunch of meat on the
thing yeah I think they said please oh my god we didn't say please we didn't say
please for anything. What is that white gooey thing you get at Korean BBQ?
White gooey thing? Yeah remember that it was like the little like...
Oh that was some sort of... no not cum. Hush the Korean adults are talking.
Listen we got it's like a weird it's like a tortilla. It's a tortilla. It's not a
tortilla. It's not cum, it's a tortilla. It's some sort of like doughy thing though.
Yeah. It's probably a rice. Some sort of white goo. Oh maybe it's just like they boil some rice paper.
Maybe those were napkins that we ate.
Yeah, we ate the napkins.
Yeah, it was alright.
I liked the bean sprouts there were really good.
And the sweet pickles.
I could have gone five things with those pickles.
Five rounds of those.
I didn't even think of that shit.
You know what? I was focused on the meat.
Arby's style.
Caleb got the meat.
Castle Arby's.
Nope.
I'm gonna move into Castle Arby's.
you'd be the king because you view cuz you cuz I'm the king thank you no yeah
you know I'm the king of Arby's no no no no I'm the king of our baby the king of
roast beef because your pussy look cuz your pussy got roast beef flip-flaps
that's pretty cool I could eat my own pussy no you can't eat your own pussy
cuz also you're not flexible in this scenario I got straw you get it you're
you get you got a rib added yeah they give you extra ribs so you can't suck
your own dick ever. Actually they just make your penis a rib. They take your dick off,
they put a rib there.
Ronald McDonald got the McRib removed so he could suck his own menu.
What the fuck?
That doesn't make any sense.
I saw it on Twitter.
That's my MKUltra activation phrase.
What else did you see on Twitter?
I saw...
Did you see that hot bitch mom?
Oh my god. Oh my god no.
Oh my god.
God stop on the podcast. I'm thinking about the woman you're gonna be turning into a hot mom. No, no
The thing is about
Sure, she doesn't speak in that video. Yeah, and then that's why oh no, I'm gonna
I'm going on a date with that woman. You are? Yeah, man. I'm serious. I don't think you are. Dude, I'm serious, man
I'll show you a picture. Uh-uh. A picture of what? You don't know that
That proves we're going on a date. Yeah, dude
Why else would I have a photo of a woman if I wasn't going on a date with her?
What if it's- You're so stupid dude. You're in 1th grade, man. Yeah
Dumbass. You're a 1th grader. You're a 1th grader, and you'll never go to sunken grade
I'll never go to what grade? Sunken grade. Seeking
Seeking grade I don't even know what that is cuz I'm too young. Yeah, cuz you're in 1th grade
Yeah, you learn about seeking grade when you in stunking grade. Mm-hmm. Yeah, and then you go to fourth then just regular fourth grade
Right. Yeah. Yeah, and then you go to sixth grade and then you go back to fifth grade
So you learn how to be in sixth grade?
And then you go to college and then you go to college get more knowledge
And if you're a girl you go to stupider to get more you more stupider get more Jupiter. No
drops of Jupiter
Drops of Jupiter. If you're a girl you go to the plastic surgeon
Yeah to learn how to make your face look all fucking beautiful for the boys when they get out of college
Yeah, they spend a week in college. You go to bring them and then you go to bring them to work
University you look for a husband you look for a husband there. Wait what?
That's what?
What? That's what Mormons do. No. Mormon women. Mormons never. No, no Mormon women. Oh my god
Thank you for saying women. I was going on a... my brain was in the gutter.
Mormon women go to Brigham Young to find their husbands there and then they get married once
the men graduate and they drop out. Yeah. That's what a Mormon girl I went to high school with.
That's what most, I would say most like religious women, I think that's what
my girlfriend's parents did. Yeah? Yeah.
That's what your girlfriend's gonna do. Yeah. She's gonna do that too.
Yeah. She's gonna... I'm gonna do that.
Yeah. I'm gonna do it too.
What was it again?
When, okay, so what we're saying is you get, you're gonna go to jail.
You go to Jupiter to get more stupid.
I go to, I could go to jail. I would, I probably do really well.
I probably will. I probably do really well in jail. I feel like I would be able to make
friends with most of the people in there. Cause I'm just like kind of a charming guy
and I, you know, I can just kind of like talk to people.
Charming.
They really get me. Yeah, I could tell them about like all the different games I've played
and like, kind of like I could explain to them sort of the differences between
Pokemon Ruby and Omega Ruby. I feel like they would really like, I mean just a lot
of them I feel like I've never like looked at Pokemon in the way that I have.
They could use, you know what, I bet they would love to you basically say every
action that's happening in a Pokemon game that you're playing in your brain
and they control it with your penis and your balls are the two buttons. Yeah
that'd be fun. So you would be like, they would crank it left and
you would be like left, left, left, encounter. You have come across a coughing.
Yeah. And then like what attack would you like to use? And I would teach
them all the different attacks. I feel like I could also you know kind of
bring them together and maybe like I bet like I could teach them like a few songs.
Everybody in prison is so, they're so nice. They're really angry all
the time I think and I feel like I could probably just calm them down just by you
know being like hey guys you know what why don't we just make the best of this?
this is I mean why don't we just have the best summer of our lives? I mean I
don't know how long you guys are here, but I'm here for the summer camp.
I'm here for the summer camp.
I'm doing more of the work.
And he doesn't want to take care of me. He doesn't want to. So he put me in
jail for the summer. And I feel like we could just have a good time. And you
know I'm I know I'm a lot longer than you guys, but I feel like you know we
can we can connect on kind of like a deeper level than just across like you
know it's like it's like it what's your favorite guy what's your guys favorite
comic book that's what I would do first thing I do when I get into prison guys
we don't have to fight and be racist well who's it was everyone's favorite movie
yeah you know I bet my life that it's a matrix do you guys see the new Funko
drop yeah you guys see the new Funko drop you know we're all in jail I see
the new hungry hamster trailer just like you guys see the new hungry hamster in
here they do they show you it on the TV okay you know what that's it that's the
last straw I am cannot believe how terrible the way these these guards do
not let the inmates watch the hungry hamster trailer when it drops it's
fucked up man you know I was okay when they were forcing the prisoners to do
labor and you know letting them kill each other wherever but this this is the
last straw this is where it is I bet most of these people don't even know who
Michael the crawler is and how he sounds and for the record he sounds like this
it's fucked cuz he's a spider who's hungry mm-hmm is every character hungry
no some candy hamsters not hungry I'm in jail and I'm just twiddling my thumbs
just waiting for Jeff Ross to come roast me yeah you know yeah yeah you're in
jail I have a heart attack and that's how you get out of jail help him having a
heart attack I need to be let out of jail and sent home. We're in this this is a real
prisoners dilemma. We either keep him in jail or we bring him to the hospital. Can I go
home and grab my medication? Yeah. Can I go home and grab my switch? Do you guys
have an HDMI cable? No. Well then I guess I'm gonna have to go to Best Buy. Can I go
home again? I gotta go to Best Buy right now. Yeah. Guys I really have to go to Best Buy.
I don't know why I just. I'm sick can I go home? Can I go to Best Buy? I'm really
sick. I think I have a cold. Can I go to Best Buy? I love how it smells in there. I just
love candy beans. Candy beans? Like Boston baked beans? Like Arrested Development. I
don't know. They say candy beans on it. Patrick sing the song that you wrote yesterday. It
was a protest chant. Yeah sing it. I forget it. I want candy, I want food, I want to be
in the Christmas mood where are you protesting front of Sears yeah Sears
that doesn't exist anymore oh wait we think we drove past one there's like a
very big Sears over like very big this means nothing to me it was huge I don't
care what are the biggest doors I've seen and it's gone and does that make
you profoundly sad no I think he learned about death I wanted to go inside of it
yeah but it's dead mm-hmm I wanted to get yelled at that is sad to think about I
bet if I went to jail I'd have like ten boyfriends because of how like sexy I am
that's true yeah I feel I feel like everyone want to fuck you just cuz I'm
like so yellow jumpsuit into a bikini yeah cuz I'm just like hot and yeah
would like really want you sure we should do is you should draw even I feel
like yeah even the guy t-shirt on your yeah I'm just saying they should allow
women to be in men jail so that everybody can have sex with each other
because then the guys won't have sex with each other. Yeah. Right? I feel yeah I
just I feel like you know people just don't know how to be in jail and I can
like kind of just turn it around and start a new era. They should install
pussies in the walls that you could fuck. Yeah. Right? Because then nobody's
gonna have you know nobody's gonna. Nobody's gonna yeah exactly it's like
and it's like that's the most obvious fucking thing and these stupid people in
charge who isn't even in charge the what is it president president Jordan the
Jordan Jordan Michael Jordan Michael Jordan Michael Jordan Bob Michael Jordan
doesn't even care about these inmates you know it's like I care more than I
care probably more than even the average person care about eating dinner I'm the
ultimate activist in the way that I go into prisons and let every single man
there fuck me in the ass that they won't fuck each other in the ass yeah right
and then I needs to stop and then I leave and then I have one gnarly white shit
this has to end yeah yeah I'm have a big flag yeah guy fucking my butt and I'm
saying this yeah put pussies in the wall I'll be the last one yeah so and you
guys promise after I leave you're not gonna have sex with each other anymore
right but what it we but what did they cross their fingers well that's yeah
Yeah, that is another thing in prison. They should probably be put tape around
everyone's fingers and they can't cross. Yeah, because the thing is if somebody
crosses their fingers in jail, you have to make an example out of them and be
like this is why you were here in the first place. Yeah.
Somebody, that's what the warden does. He shoots. He shoots. What does he shoot?
The inmates. Oh, that's really kind of not cool. I feel like if I was in jail,
I'd just become the warden. I'd be the warden, but I'd be the chill warden and
I let everybody smoke weed. I let everyone watch The Longest Yard and be like I would never do this to you
But we can play football. Every warden started off as an inmate. It's like because you work your way to the top of the company
It's like the mailroom. Exactly. Start as a mailroom, start as a dishwasher, start as an inmate and then eventually you're the warden
You're the CEO, you know. Yeah, so basically what you want to do if you want to become the warden of prison is commit a terrible
Crime so you're in there as long as possible. Give yourself the best possible chance
Yeah, and you want to just go around and start canvassing. Yeah
Yeah, meet me the warden me for warden me for warden me for warden me me
Yeah, I want food. I want to be in the Christmas mood and I like you elect me as warden
I'll put a Christmas tree
I'll be in the machine in the vending machine and I'll put water on the floor so you can play in
Mm-hmm Caleb for warden my ass is on the menu
That's what I would say. Yeah, my tag
We can watch every movie trailer that comes out, but I don't want to spend money on the movie Caleb for warden
I'll be your boyfriend forever. Yeah. And I can have multiple boyfriends, but you can't.
Solved. Problem solved. Problem solved. I just Vox explained solving prison. Solving problems.
Vox explains. Vox solves problems. Cameron for Warden, I'll put a CD switcher in the bathroom.
Yeah. I'll put a subwoofer in the toilet. I'll put a subwoofer in the toilet so your shit jumps.
I'll put, yeah. And make your shit jump after you shit. Why don't they just sell drugs? Make that
- I think that shit jumps out.
- That's what I would actually do.
I would probably sell drugs.
- Yeah.
- In all realistic honesty.
- I'll put fish on the ceiling.
- Yeah.
- That just makes no sense.
- I would put--
- You can look at them when you're trying to go to sleep.
- He's the crazy warden with a K.
- No, like aquarium ceilings.
Like you know those tunnels?
You know like a tunnel where--
- You'd make all of the ceilings.
- But what if they got a hold of the fish
and used its bones as a weapon?
- That's fine.
I mean in my jail people wouldn't be fighting.
They would all be too occupied
thinking about all the Pokemon assignments I give them.
I would install video games because then they would not have any time to do to
work out. Yeah. Then they would never be able to do a violent revolt. Yeah. I
probably replace the bars with bigger bars. Honestly I would, I'm not kidding
though, I would probably forget to lock the door a couple times. Yeah, I'd forget
to throw away the key. People would walk in. You have to throw away the key every
day or else the inmate... People would walk out and just leave, you know, and I would just
be like... That's your prerogative I guess. Yeah. That's what I would say. Does the
warden, is the warden like God and they can just decide who lives and dies?
Pretty much. He's like Bob God. Bob God salad? Bob God salad. Yeah. Oh. And yeah I'd
probably just be the god of the place then. And also I'd create new versions of
me. Yeah. And then I'd have... You'd have two? I'd actually let all the prisoners free and
create a bunch of little me's and then create a little society of myselves and
we would all we'd all have we would we all share one bathroom though which would
be that'd be a nightmare yeah I probably tried and capture grew and bring him in
to the prison to increase morality that's a funny that's a big get I was
the warden the first move I'd make is I put the Grinch in jail you know that the
cops have been trying to get the Grinch for so long if I dude if I got my
fucking hands on the Grinch. I would grab him, I would push my thumbs into his fucking
into his fucking butthole and I would rip him in half from the bottom. I would grab his
hairy finger, I would swing him around and slam him against the wall so hard he turns
into a flat paper. The thing is, the Grinch is so fucked up in his brain that if you grabbed
his finger he'd probably fart as a prank to you. He'd let out a big Grinch gasp. He'd
Grinch get you with his big gun. You don't even want to know what I would do if I was
in the same room as the Grinch. Yeah. You'd have to kill me. Yeah. Because if I'm mad at
the Grinch. Two bullets. One in the Grinch's head and one in the wall because I missed.
Yeah. I would probably grab the Grinch by his fur and shake him around until all his
bones came out. Yeah. And then I'd take his skin and I'd wear it as pants. As a Grinch
shirt I would take the the Grinch right uh-huh and then I would pluck all of his
hairs out one by one oh my god you should be the saw moving then I would
keep all of the hair what the fuck I would make my own Grinch suit and then
now I'm the Grinch I would take I'm a good Grinch no you there's no such
things a good Grinch he's green you'd have to be blue you could be the smart
out of blue Grinch no he's good
a blue grinch. Have you seen the trailer for the blue grinch? No. What happened?
There's a there's a video. It's just the reverse story. There's a video of somebody watching the blue
grinch trailer and something very bad happened. Really? Yeah. What happened?
Look up the blue grinch trailer. Okay. Oh my god his heart is so big. Something
really bad happened. Something really bad happened. I react to the blue grinch trailer.
the blue Grinch they do they together you got a blue Grinch something terrible is
happening to the blue Grinch and you the only way to stop it is by watching the
video okay watching the blue Grinch movie at 3 a.m. he came to my house he
came to his house yeah what okay
(video playing)
Do you hear the thing?
What? No, just play, keep going, you can hear it.
(video playing)
He's going to be watching the Blue Grinch.
We hit the like button for me.
I already have.
I wonder if it happens.
So he comes to his house.
skip to the good stuff i wanna see the blue grinch
so what we're looking at here is he's got it overexposed
he's gonna, there we go
he has three shrimp
a whole plate of white rice
and a carton of orange juice yeah it looks like about two cups of jasmine rice
and then three extremely dark shrimp
since fried shrimp to
so he's eating those well he watches the blue grinch
how hot only
the blue grins is drinking a couple of years
and then
and then was a blue grinch come to tell
so he gets a call
He's eating his shrimp and his food.
Hold up.
Oh fuck.
Oh, yeah.
This guy better be fucking careful.
(Distorted voice)
That is really really weird y'all
Could it be the blue Grinch knocking on the door?
(Laughter)
Could it be the blue Grinch?
Oh no
It can't be the blue Grinch right?
It's gonna be the blue Grinch
Nobody's there.
This is scary.
So apparently the door is not supposed to be closed in this hallway.
a
left his apartment door open. That's a big thing right there.
He goes back into his apartment? Yeah.
And... some shit is about to happen. Something bad happened here.
So what we're saying is please do not watch the Blue Grinch trailer.
Otherwise this will happen to you.
Oh my god.
It's the blue green the blue Grinch is in the in the building
You don't play with toys who is this sucker
And he's shaking he's shaking the camera - in fear yeah
What the fuck turn this off turn this on this guy's a fucking heat I hate oh my god with toys
You guys hear about the new present drop. Yeah, they're coming out with a new one. Yeah, there's putting stripes on the wrapping paper
Yeah, they're putting stripes on a wrapping paper and also it's gonna be it's gonna be like it's gonna look like a gift wrapped bike
Yeah, it's like not in a box anymore. I heard that they're never making presents again. What's who told you that?
Blue Grinch. Oh my god. We have to fuck him
It's gonna happen, okay
All right. All right. Enjoy your gifts. Yeah, watch the hungry hamster trailer. Let us know what you think in the comments, please
I'll post the the blue Grinch video link yeah the patreon blue watch the blue
Grinch don't watch the bear don't watch the blue Grinch do if you watch the
hungry hamster the hungry hamster does not come to your house unfortunately he
does not want to take your gifts yeah and I remember your food play hard and
play harder do we have any new patreon oh no this is a page on this we do say
that shout out I will say that the dummy of the week is the blue Grinch yep yep I
I think it was supposed to be Freak of the Week.
Freak of the Week is the Blue Grinch.
Freak of the Week is the Blue Grinch. Dummy of the Week is Cameron.
Is me.
Because I don't even know.
That's how dumb I am.
That's how stupid he is.
Alright, bye.