You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[LAUGHTER]
Episode three.
Episode three of the same three.
Episode three of the podcast.
Of the marathon.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, the--
We were in--
The podcast about list COVID--
COVID list.
COVIDtacular.
It is a festival that we're having.
Yeah, yeah, no phones Patrick.
No, it's a premium, I can be on my phone.
No you can't.
No you cannot.
That's the one you can't.
I'm reading the news.
Put your phone back under the couch.
US considering cash stimulus as global cases pass.
You ain't got cash, you can't get cash on the internet.
Cameron, we might be getting a cash stimulus, I'm telling you.
I'm gonna cash stimuli your fucking asshole if you don't put that phone away.
Yeah, yeah, with dollars.
Yeah, with dollars.
JG Wentworth is trending.
Easy.
I'm gonna put sharpened coins up into you.
Yeah, this is the one where we give all of our thoughts on this thing.
"Exit the Gungeon" is Trenjin.
Trenjin?
"Exit the Gungeon"?
Yeah, what?
Is that a new one?
That's, yeah, they just announced the sequel.
Oh.
Oh, so you guys want me to put my phone away?
Shut up!
Yeah, put your phone away.
You want me to put my phone away right now?
I did not know that you were going to talk about games.
Yeah.
If you're talking about games, you can do whatever you want.
Don't tell him that.
I was going to talk about games the whole time.
If you turn on G4, we will just watch TV right now.
Mm-hmm.
We could do a watch-along too.
I honestly feel like 15 years ago we could have had a show on G4 pretty easy.
Don't turn the TV on.
We could do a watch along to Combat Tai Chi.
Combat Tai Chi with Richard Clear.
I thought Tai Chi was like a thing fat people do in white clothes.
Don't open the DVD.
Look what you did.
You told him you could watch stuff.
No, he can't watch it.
He can show us.
Look at this fucked up DVD.
Whoa.
Somebody's riding the hog outside.
That's the Mad Max starting.
might be the guy on the hog who listens to Steve Miller band all the time that's
a cool combo oh it's a couple DVDs if you're on a motorcycle especially Harley
Davidson I don't care what you're listening to I will suck you and fuck you
but I just imagine that you're listening to like a like a like a LimeWire
playlist that's just highway to hell over and over again. I'm not gonna smell a DVD.
literally Patrick is the weird kid really is dude smell it he doesn't wear shoes he
says he brings me things in my face and says smell it no dude you should be in
detention right now dude you fucking smell that thing I'm not oh that smells
like it would kill the Chinese child smell the little Chinese factory work I
believe you I'm not gonna smell the DVD it no just say more just say more funny
things about what it smells like and don't make us smell it yeah keep
smelling it yourself it smells like bean boozled dude that's straight up that
smells like a bean boozled you're gonna smell it one more time DVD yeah I mean
boozled flavor that's one is DVD and the other is stinky DVD which one is it
which all right I smell it yeah come on okay I smell it it smells like how a
switch cartridge tastes all right that's not a bad dude it smells like I feel like
I mean okay to be fair this is my first time ever smelling a DVD.
They could open another DVD.
Let me open up Krav Maga the Israeli connection.
Open Krav Maga it doesn't smell bad it smells like rubber.
It doesn't smell like a tire.
Oh yeah it just smells like industrial.
It just smells like a weird plastic thing.
But this is not unreasonable for like a shitty DVD to smell like that.
Do you know?
I've never smelled a deal. So yet I feel like the is really crumb. I got
connection is not a fair control group. I think this is also going to smell
crazy. This one smells normal. What do you mean normal?
It's like strawberry was like a normal DVD. No, this smells exactly the
same. What are you talking about? Smell exactly the same. It's not as
strong. It's the same smell. Yeah, it's not open. It is the same. Open a
different DVD, a non combat art. This is this is exactly how the virus
started.
sniffing DVDs and caught something. No smell, no smell at all. What DVD is this?
What DVD is this? This is Brass Eye. This is Brass Eye. This is from the UK. Yeah,
they have different smells over there. It's a completely different smell. I
wouldn't say there's no smell. It's definitely a different smell. Let me see
it.
That's all I'm saying.
This one's, yeah, it smells different, I guess. It smells like... I don't know, can
you get a normal DVD? It smells normal. My head is hurting.
I think I'm I think I'm high.
This one's checking out with Dr. Sleepy.
You're going to smell all of Patrick's DVDs.
No smell.
No smell at all.
Let me smell this.
Yeah, this one has the least smell so far, I think.
Okay, I think I've discovered what it is.
It has to do...
I can like taste that in my mouth.
Maybe it's the sooner you open it.
It's the new DVD smell.
I think that is a new DVD smell.
Which is older, Brass Eye or Steve Rule?
Steve Ruhle. I knew it and Steve Ruhle smells the least. Yeah. It's yeah it's new DVD
it's new DVD smell. You know what that could be that could be but no because this one was
unsealed and we opened it and it smelled less bad as this one which was open. You keep saying
unsealed when you mean sealed. Ah fuck off. This one didn't smell as bad. Exactly and
we just opened that one and it smelled. It's no I mean this one smelled worse this one
didn't smell. Wait, okay, give me these two. Okay. And when did you open Combat Tai Chi?
Never opened it. That one came, like, that came unsealed. Yeah, but I bet nobody had ever
opened the box before. No, my grandpa John did. Well, he did that to that. He did something
to that DVD. That's what I'm saying! He did something to the DVD! I think they smell pretty
equally bad. I think Combat Tai Chi is a bit stronger. No, smell them both again back to
Okay, hold on. Will you hold this like a boom mic so you can get my reaction?
Yeah. Okay, I'm opening. Oh, we should do a blind test. Okay.
Okay, wait, wait, wait. Hold the mic and close your eyes. No, don't pause it. Just close your eyes.
I'm going to shuffle. Well, now he knows which ones which. No, no, no. He's closing his eyes.
My eyes are closed. Okay, let's see if I can tell which one is Combat Tai Chi. All right.
Okay, I'm going to make it. Now, keep your eyes closed. Don't say it. Don't say it.
Cameron is giving him a DVD right now. The first DVD. Smell.
Okay, you smelled it? Alright, are you ready for the other DVD? Yeah. Alright, we're
giving him the other DVD. Smell. Okay, now which do you think is Combat Tai Chi? The
first one. You're right. Yeah, see? It has a fucking distinct smell and it has a
weird... Alright, alright, let's try. Let's do this with... Now you have to do it,
Cameron because I know that Patrick will pass. All right yeah I don't know I think
I have a pretty weak sense of smell in general but I'll try it. All right close
your eyes. My eyes are closed. All right I'm gonna give you one DVD now. Okay all right
okay he's giving him the DVD. Smell. Okay. Okay now the second DVD. Okay now? Yeah.
can I open my eyes I think the second one is combat Tai Chi you are right see it
has a fucking distinct smell I'm not wrong about but it's the same so I could
tell it was combat Tai Chi because it was a stronger smell but it's it is the same
same smell but it's just different it's a matter of magnitude yeah okay so I
admit it might not be new DVD smoke is cuz I touchy is older but smells
stronger yeah it's kind of the uglier the guy on the on the thing is the stinkier
the DVD is. Post pictures of these DVDs. It's funny that what I love about this one is like
if you just showed me the picture and there was no text this is exactly what...
It looks like a video, it looks like a PS4 character.
If you showed me just the picture of this guy and said name this DVD I would have called
it Krav Maga the Israeli Connection just based on his general...
Which is exactly what it's called. His general face and look and the fact that
there's spikes behind him. Yeah.
Spikes behind him. Yeah.
All I'm saying is that that DVD has a very harsh plastic smell and it's strange.
Yeah.
Yes.
Yeah, but I also don't think, it also isn't necessarily like a bad smell to me.
I hate that smell.
I don't like it.
I feel sick.
I think if you breathe that in for more than one sniff.
If that smell was in your room, you would not stay in your room.
They're from the same company?
Imagine the smell of the DVD of the company.
Yeah, imagine what the CEO would smell like.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
He, yeah, he, he kisses every single DVD.
Imagine the smell of the factory where they're making the plastic.
The factory where they're making the plastic, man.
It's gotta be fucked up, dude.
Yeah, that's all I'm saying.
Let's try a video game.
Yeah, wait, get out a, get a, now a Switch game we already know that's gonna smell fucked
up, so get the non-Switch game.
Do Switch games smell fucked up?
They taste fucked up, so I'd assume they'd smell fucked up.
see there's no there's a copy of skate to with the avatar in it okay so this is not
that's corrupted yeah this is a sample that's a DVD inside a video game case we
gotta be scientific about yeah that's gonna no matter what smell like shit I
don't know what just pick up yeah that should use an unsealed copy of Paul
Blart mall cop okay so yeah we can see if this smell one yeah so okay old is
because this is see is it the new dvd smell is a new dvd smell is what we'll
figure out or is it just the martial art dvd smell every martial. We should
every episode that we record today is just going to get more and more on like
this
just doing things yeah.
Oh my God,
no, this is a new smell.
his eyes open so wide. You look like a meerkat who saw a lion.
Yeah, you look like you just like you. Okay, now we got to test this. You look
like you acquired dark knowledge. You look like an H.P. Lovecraft. That's a
different smell.
I can't smell it.
I don't know if I smell anything on this one.
All right, I'm going in. Yeah, do it.
That one smells darker.
It smells darker.
Darker.
This is like a...
What year did this movie come out?
I don't know.
2008.
No, yeah, 2008 because my uncle saw them filming it at the Burlington Mall and my grandpa was
dying in the hospital.
This smells like 2008.
Let me try it again.
It has such a...
It smells like a new Golden Corral.
Oh, okay.
I can't smell this one.
You don't smell that?
I don't smell anything on this one.
Okay, here I have some...
This is the Yanny versus Laurel of smells.
There is a...
I can't smell it.
thing on this one. This is the Yanny vs. Laurel of smells. I will say, there's a twist to this
one. You turn it around, eco-friendly packaging. Oh my god. Plastic case uses 20% less material,
30% post-consumer waste paper. So that doesn't count. This is an outlier. It smells like
a new vegetable like a vegetable dr. Seuss would invent yeah that's what it's like
a needle yeah yeah it smells like a clumble yeah a clumble earth needle yeah
you get another DVD get another DVD this is always what I wanted the patreon
episodes to be like yeah yeah there's a Cosmopolis what that that's a Greek
guy's last name that's the last name of the character he plays in yeah that's my
down my downstairs neighbor who's a pro soccer player his name George Cosmopolis
Georgie but his real name is Eleftherios but he goes by George okay I can't tell
that one all right I smell then was this one new or not no that's not new I've
watched it already a very slight I think it has a very slight weird plastic smell
I think you can smell that we can I think I just I don't have a good sense of
smell I will say that. The Tai Chi one left an aftertaste. Oh that has a smell.
Yeah it's kind of similar smell to the Tai Chi one. I would say this is like a sour.
This is like the DVD is old. This is David Cronenberg put his slime into this
one that's why it smells like that. This is actually the least...
This does smell a little sour. It smells a little sour. You just did Griffin McElroy
voice dude. It's a pretty good movie. I haven't seen it yet. Along with the smell it's a pretty
good movie. Yeah this one's yeah this one definitely has a smell. Paul Giamatti's in it.
Let's smell the plastic wrapping from the DVD. Yeah that's true we got to do that too. Smells.
Just I want somebody yeah I want the Toronto star called Cosmopolis a blockbuster of the mind.
More like a blockbuster of the nose. It has some stank on it. Should start a movie review show
show you just smell them okay. I got it that is such a good idea. I have a real
curve ball about the third a blue ray of the shape of water. This is going to
smell like fish. They put a real fish smell into it.
I just smelled like my hand.
What does your hand smell like? I don't know. I think they got rid of smells
during that when they made blue. That was one of the advances. This one has a
DVD and a blue ray. This is a DVD plus blue ray copy. I think that's what you're
nothing that's like wine and cheese. This one smells sterile. This one actively
smells like nothing. This smells like they tried to remove a smell. Right.
Here's my idea. Yeah. The reason why DVD Blu-ray copies exist like a combo disc
or a combo package is because there is a DVD smell and there's a Blu-ray smell
and they can't. Okay. All right. This is the smell that Caleb has to close his
for. All right close your eyes. I'll pass it over. Okay all right take it open it up.
Do I have to guess what movie this is?
Oh wait this is a really good activity. Okay all right wait wait wait let me pass it to Caleb
before you smell it. I have to guess what movie this is. And you have to open your eyes mid-smell.
Don't open your eyes no just smell. Smell and then guess. Guess what it is. Just based on that?
yeah sleepless in Seattle final answer my mic take a look
exactly like Matt Besser's mustache yeah doesn't even have a mustache there no
but no you know now that you said it I'm looking at the case of a mustache I'm
looking at the case now and you said that comment about his arms yeah he's
got some freakish he's got like that sir looks like a fucked-up monkey he looks
like he looks like he escaped the zoo this is the DVD discovered makeup this
there's a very there's a sketch on this DVD where they do a live show and Amy
Poehler plays a Japanese person and she ends a sentence by going she just goes
why not just not did you get have you guys seen the I'm sure it's on that DVD
the like live ass cat no with this no but you know the one I'm talking about
where they do like a lot they do like a taped ass cat and it has like the fat
guy what's that on it ask cat is like they're like version of improv with like
a monologue and stuff oh yeah it's funny cuz it's from like 2003 or something but
all of the scenes are like I'm a pedophile rapist and you're like a
little Chinese kid it's like stuff that at the UCB they would never do now yeah
it's so funny sick I think I ran out of DVDs well here let's get all the DVDs
who smelled so far close your eyes shuffle them up and try to figure out which is which.
Okay. Oh my god. This is this is like the Super Bowl for us. This is a which DVD is the stinkiest
we know which DVD is the stinkiest. Yeah it's Tai Chi. It's Tai Chi. Yeah I don't think we
need to do any more than. Well we I want to find I want to find a ranking. Okay well okay
ranking Taichi and then Robert is a smelly as Robert got here - I would say
Cosmopolis is number number three yeah I agree and then Paul Blart and yeah I
mean water is water water nothing shape water to these are many UCB where you're
the only one who's going to be oh yeah you guys should smell it's already gone
now I smelled it it didn't smell I would say it has it does have paper on it so
it smells like paper but this paper smell yeah times yeah I think paper is
on the paper. Well let's get some paper. Okay. Okay. Let's get, wait, does shit smell?
Well like an old book can smell. Oh it can smell. An old anything can smell. Yeah but a
book, like a old book's got like a smell. Hold on. Hold on, right there, copy of Cat's Cradle.
It's like a, yeah that's a very old book. Be careful with it, it's that old.
I'm interested to see if this is the same smell as a DVD. Okay, we're testing to see
of Kurt Vonnegut's Cat's Cradle book smells like a DVD.
But you know what I'm saying? Like a book smell? Like an old book smell?
Yeah, of course. Yeah.
It smells like yellow paper.
I don't know if it's because my nasal pathways have been corrupted by the Israeli connection,
but this doesn't smell like anything to me.
Let me smell it. Let me smell it.
This looks like the lead singer of the Mighty Mighty Boss Tones.
No, this smells like a book. This has book smell.
The guy on the cover of the Israeli Connection looks like the lead singer of Mighty Mighty
Boss Tones. He looks like he's about to sing a ska song.
He looks like a Bond villain.
A little bit. A little bit.
I think he looks more like...
In like a Bollywood version of James Bond.
He looks... Can you put that back up there? He looks more like... He looks like the guy
from Mighty... He looks like he's about to sing Never Had to Knock on Wood.
Yeah.
But I know someone who had.
you know i'm not i'm not wondering about the boss towns boston's their trombone
player with emerson
you know i don't care their townies baby and i mean you never know how to name
i've definitely said it but my uncle uh... pay like a thousand dollars to go
see them open for dropkick murphy's and then left
yeah that's not bad actually dropkick murphy's is doing a live uh... a live
stream today
yeah we should want to do it did i hate the dropkick murphy's so they saw
They're, it's like punk rock for cops.
Yeah.
It's like punk rock for cops and like just the most racist man in the world named Bob Shaughnessy.
What's the name of the like better version of them?
The Pokes.
No, I'm thinking...
Flogging Molly.
That's what I'm thinking of, yeah.
They're like, do the same thing but they're not like Blue Eyes Matter.
But the Dropkick Murphys are like, they had that song for the Red Sox.
Yeah.
They had Tessie.
Sweet Caroline.
No.
Yeah, they made Sweet Caroline.
Tessie and then they named the girl mascot.
goes oh yeah they made that yeah the game so they made it from Boston
don't don't if they aren't that's fucked I have to be from Boston we really
funny they aren't I would like I would like them way more whenever I find out
like a band is like posers and they're making up their background I like them
so I like them so much more yeah honestly like a house of pain they're
from Los Angeles and like Celtic Jersey. I think I remember okay this my dad was
really into the front bottoms for a little while and he told me he was
listening to like yeah dude it's great dad is yeah he um no wonder he was
listening to one of their album commentaries like where they talk about
the meanings of the songs and they have a song that's about like the guy's
girlfriend getting an abortion and it's like everyone's like this is so deep and
great and on like the comment they like talk about like what how why they wrote
the songs and stuff and the guy's just like, "Yeah, I don't know. I don't know
anyone who's gotten an abortion. I just thought it was rock and roll." And I was like, "Oh, I
like you guys now. That's awesome." They're like, "Yeah, none of
these stories are true. We just thought it sounded cool." The only example I can
think of that is Blink-182, how they like wrote all of their songs about being 15
when they were like 32. Yeah, so great. So sick. So funny to do that. I love it.
And all those songs are like, "I fucked a 17 year old.
"Josie, you are 14 and I'm 20."
(laughing)
- Dude, they rock.
- Yeah.
- Dude, Blink-182 is a great band.
- Dude, I unashamedly love Blink-182.
- Yeah, I've been getting back into it.
There's just been so much shit that I just like--
- Are you listening to the new stuff?
- No, I would never listen to Blink-182,
the album that they put out when I was in the eighth grade.
- It's not bad.
- That fucking, what was that album?
The fucking worst album cover?
It just looks like a--
bunch of like Nicki Nora's Infinite Playlist. Yeah, them and I feel like Weezer is another
band. I've been listening to a bunch of Sum 41. Sum 41 rocks dude. So good. My favorite
thing to do is just get drunk and then just listen to just early 90s or late 90s pop punk.
I get drunk and I get sad and then I watch the music videos in a row for Sum 41 Fat Lip.
Greatest music video of all time. Every time I die map change. I don't get sad I just get
too excited and I'm like why don't people why isn't anyone else excited?
Patrick's jumping up and down watching Fatlib. I've done that we did that at
Noah's that one time. Dude I think with you two I've seen that that music
video like 15 times. I love that music video so much it's so good.
Definitely the best ever. There's a third sad music video that I watch or like a wistful
you know yeah I like drunk alone like. Pretending you're like 16. Yeah exactly
Sugar Ray every morning. Sugar were going down swinging by Fall Out Boy.
That one? Swing swing by All American Rejects. Growing up I thought that Fall Out Boy, All
American Rejects, I thought they were gay. Yeah I did too. And OK Go, like all that
stuff. That was my favorite. When I was like 8?
Oh my god. No, No, No, All American Rejects was my favorite band. I loved All
American Rejects. Yeah. See I liked like I was in. Because they had that bionicle
commercial. I was in a Blink-182, Sum 41, Newfound Glory, Set Your Goals, 4-Year Strong.
But you listened to like vegan hardcore shit. Yeah, I was also listening to like Earth Crisis.
I was listening to like, I had a scoff phase when I was 12. Earth Crisis was my favorite
band as a kid. I had like a really bad scoff phase. That sucks man. Dude, I loved Sublime
when I was 12 for like 3 months. I was super into Five Finger Death Punch. Damn. Like super
into them. They were like my favorite band for a really long time. I liked Slipknot a
lot when I was in the sixth grade. But in seventh grade I got into Sublime.
-Burzum. -I got into Sublime and then immediately I realized
just like, "Oh, all these songs just sound the same." -I was also super into
symphonic metal, like the kind where they play the keyboards. -I got into chip
tunes, dude. I just made YouTube poop music videos. That's all I fucking did.
all I'd listen to was like Mega Man music and Block Party for some reason.
Yeah.
One of the... you mentioned your dad getting into front bottoms. The biggest curveball of my life
one time was my dad was like... which it makes sense, but it was just so weird to me. I came
home one day and my dad was like, "I have to show you two of my favorite artists." And he played a
Girl Talk like remix. And then he was... I was like, "That's weird." And he was like, "Yeah,
but like this is my favorite shit right now and also this and then he played Florence and the Machine
and my dad is like my dad is like such a weird like he's such like old school like cigar smoking guy
and just hearing him listening to him or thinking about him like sitting on his front porch listening
to like a Kanye Rolling Stones like yeah yeah remix he's just so weird my yeah my dad all my
dad listens to is like U2 and stuff yeah my dad is like like old punk and then like like mod
Yeah, yeah, and then yeah, and then like folk punk. I don't know what my dad my dad
My dad definitely has like weird like shit my dad. No, my dad was also very into Scott
My dad loved like the English beat. Yeah
I tried to show my dad like some hardcore band like Cro-Mags or something and he
Said he my dad would always say about like punk and hardcore that it sounded like diarrhea. Yeah my dad
I listened to odd future tape volume two in the car. I bought it and then my dad would just say the
it. Whenever they would say it, he would look at me and go like...
It's a crazy dad move.
Yeah, well he was just making fun of how often they said it, but then he was just saying
it.
That's sick dude.
My dad's awesome.
Your dad will live forever.
I've never seen what your dad looks like.
Yeah, I remember I played...
He kind of looks like Morrissey.
I was playing Young Thug...
This guy is weird.
What's the fucking song?
The song is...
Pull Up On A Kid?
No.
Danny Glover.
Also, that's a funny title for a song.
Pull Up On A Kid?
Yeah.
With Them.
The song, when he goes on, when he says, "Give me a head on the plane, I just call it Airhead,"
or something like that, you know that line?
What is it?
Cameron's dad said that to him.
But I was playing that in the car, my mom, and she was like, "Turn that off.
What did he just say?"
Yeah.
I still get it if like if a rap song comes on the radio
I'm in the car with either my parents. I get shut I get like a heat on the back of my yeah
Yeah, I feel like I'm in trouble. Yeah. Yeah, dude my
It's not my dad listens to like he he just has like the music he listens to my mom jumps all over the fucking place
You know remember that frog? Oh my dad also loves
Harmony, but a con my mom reason my mom loves
hypnotized by notorious BIG
Well, that's yeah, that's like a 90s. Yeah, she loves that and then remember monsters calling home. No, oh they were I
Hated them, but my mom fucking loved that band. They were like, um, I don't know
They were kind of like that was that band?
There's the of monsters and men but it was not that there were two bands that came out at the same time that had the name
Monsters in their title and of monsters and men scary monsters and nice spread. Yeah, my mom loves Skrillex
No, she like she loved that
so that band Monsters Calling Home and I think they changed their band name
because of Monsters and Men. Patrick's Calling Home.
Mm-hmm yeah. Angels and Airwaves. Patrick Calling Cookie Monster. See I was so into Blink-22 that I was an
Angels and Airwaves fan. Yeah. You didn't like Boxcar Racer? No. Oh man my little
brother by the sixth grade my little brother started dating a girl and then
she broke up with him day one.
- Nice.
- And I remember hearing him downstairs in our room,
'cause I was on the computer doing homework,
and then I like really loud hear him listening to
There Is by Fox Car Executive.
(laughing)
And he was just like crying,
and all I hear is like,
♪ I hate all the stillin' lives hung on the radio ♪
- Dude, the worst thing about being like a pop punk fan
was when you were like, oh, that's a cool song,
buy the album you buy the album three songs and one of the songs is about God
yeah right like that was what sucked about like under oath yeah I was like I
was like under oath is sick and then someone's like they are like a Christian
band first metal band I liked was demon hunter which is like Christian hunter is
the is like the gateway metal band I mean they started hunter demon hunter
their first albums fucking sick it's just like new metal it's just like it
sounds like Slipknot um and then they just turned into like weird like like I
I don't even know, like just like generic. I was into their album The World is a Thorn. I remember
the first metal song I heard and I was like, "Damn, this is sick." It was a song, "Tie This
Around Your Neck" by Demon Hunter about people getting freaking hanged. I've never heard of
Demon Hunter. Really? The first metal, I mean, I played like all the Tony Hawk games, so I just
had like a really like, like my introduction to like metal music was like Whiplash by Metallica
and like yeah storm the gates of hell by demon hunter what was that song so sick
dude yeah dude just be it's on the it's on Tony Hawk's Underground 2 it's so sick
to be into God Oh Lamb of God I was like seven give it a job for a cowboy no
Lannis singer for Lamb of God like killed a guy really right Randy I don't know I
don't fucking know I think that's Lamb of God they he like stabbed a guy and
went to jail for a while and now he's out. Yeah, Lamb of God, there's that Lamb of
God song. Oh, that ministry? Oh dude, ministry rocks. Dude, ministry, stigmata,
and then ministry. There's that ministry song where they open it with the
George W. Bush intro. That taught me, when I was a little kid, that taught me not to
trust George W. Bush. Like, I was like, my mom was like, my mom and my grandpa were
like, after 9/11, were like super into George W. Bush, but I heard that
ministry song, and I was like, "Do you not hear?"
Dude, I've been watching a lot of old George W. Bush.
It's funny that people pretend like Trump is the only president who was just a fucking
idiot, but every president ever, they're just guys.
They're just guys who are just kind of hanging out.
They don't do a lot.
They play a lot of golf.
The thing where George W. Bush, the video where he's talking to the camera, and he's like,
"And we have to stop the violence in the Middle East.
Now watch this drive."
and then he hit dude that that video fucking rules it's like i like i watch that and and people are
always like how did he how did he beat gore and carry it's like because he's fucking awesome
i would have voted for him i would have voted for him 60 more times yeah he deserved that you just
got i mean like you just gotta be the funniest coolest guy that is whoever is the funniest wins
it was like until we had until up to a certain point in history the tallest person running for
president always won. It's true, yeah, Lincoln. And then after that it's just the funniest
guy. Yeah. It's whoever, whoever was the best. Whoever can get stuck in a bathtub. Yeah, whoever
was the best at like roasting. Yeah, whoever. If Patrisse O'Neil had run for president.
Oh that would be awesome. He would have made, he would have been the president forever.
Yeah. He could have fucking run. Greg Giraldo. Greg Giraldo. Imagine, imagine a Greg Giraldo
imagine a great Colin Mockrey Ryan Stiles honestly Colin it would have to be Ryan
Stiles call no they fight over who's no because Colin Mockrey's president he's
Canadian oh yeah that's true yeah this it doesn't make sense yeah right it
wouldn't work no no he could still be VP no no no no no Ryan's really no Brad and
and Wayne for president. And we get two singing presidents. What about Moe, Larry, Curly?
The first one. And Shemp is the vice president. That would have been good, man.
Shemp was the, you know, Curly was not actually related to the other. No, no, no, no, no. Larry
wasn't related. Did you know they actually hated each other in real life and murdered
each other yesterday? Yeah, that's actually true. I just saw that in the news.
No, Shemp, Moe and Curly were related.
- Shemp, Smay, I got recommended a YouTube video
called the Three Stooges Getting Hurt in Real Life.
- Yeah, oh I watched that one.
Dude, there's a scene, there's a scene,
the Moe like almost beat the shit
out of the director of the short,
'cause there's a scene where Larry got stabbed
in the head with a fountain pen.
- Oh my God. - And it's real.
Like he just sits there and he's like,
has a reaction, but it's a real reaction
of him freaking the fuck out.
I love that. I love old comedy. We should bring that back.
What, like just beating the shit out of performers?
If we ever make a movie, we should just...
I mean, that is what Jackass is.
Yeah, if we ever make a movie, we should do that to each other.
It should be like the Johnny Knoxville movie with the water park.
We'll call it the Three Cool Stooges.
Huh?
Point Break?
Yeah, Point Break.
Have you guys seen the previews for that new Eric Andre movie that's like pranks combined with a movie?
No.
It's like he does like street bits, but it's also in a plot.
Uh-uh.
Like it's about some crazy road travel.
Yeah, they just did a Dirty Grandpa thing.
Yeah, it looks fun.
bad grandpa. Dirty Grandpa is the one where Robert Edmurs is the N word.
Yeah. The ultimate stunt. White Grandpa.
Yeah. White Grandpa the movie.
I'm Robert De Niro.
I'm Robert De Niro, this is Jackass. The Junior Novelist Nation.
And I'm going to be saying the N word.
I'm still on White Grandpa. White Grandpa.
What would that movie be about? Sexy Grandpa. White Grandpa?
It should be about you. Fat Grandpa.
old grandpa yeah damn that'd be a great
movie now we should we should write a
movie that's just like I think we should
put a screenplay on it right now it's
just us Patrick's the only one who gets
hurt in the entire thing yeah it's just
us making Patrick do stunts. I'm good at stunts dude.
he is a stunt man I'm good at stunts I
know how to fall. You're probably the best at
stunts. You're absolutely the best at stunts.
you can skateboard. You're only saying
this so I could you're gonna make me do more stunts.
No dude you're like the
king of snots man. You could probably jump off the house right now you could jump off of it.
You could survive if I shot you in the head. No you would jump and you would survive.
Patrick's evil knishes. Fucking fat bitch. I'm kidding. I know how to bread fall though.
I used to. I can't believe we've only done half of the episode. I feel like we've done
like ten years of content in this one episode. We've only done three. This is the second
wind one yeah this is yeah I want to smell DVDs. I had a cup of coffee, I had a half a cigarette and I got to
smell all sorts of smells from around the world yeah do you guys remember wait okay
figure out where the DVDs were made that's how we create it. That is how we source it. We know how DVDs smell from
different countries yeah between like Malaysia and China. They're all China. No
they're not. One of them was Israel. The fighting style is from Israel. Yeah and so
they made the DVD there too. No. Yeah. Yeah. They don't make DVDs in Israel. Oh they do
brother and you do not want to see what they put on there. They make WMDs. Yeah.
Whoa. Weapons of... My demise. Misa doo doo. Weed marijuana. Weapons of Misa and big doo doo now.
Weapons of Moyshe Dershowitz. That's pretty good. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's what a WMD is.
Yeah. Weapons of Moyshe Dershowitz. Websites of Moyshe Dershowitz.
I have to make a website. Yeah. My boss. Caleb.com.
No, my, well, I do have to make a website. Oh, man.
My boss. He bought this domain. My boss fired me and then was like, not really, but I'm on leave
from the museum. And she was like, but I need, I have this other thing that I need you to make a
like if you know how to make a website I need you to make a website for it and I
just lied and said I know how to make a website so now I have to figure out how
to do that. Just use Wix. Yeah but I think she probably wants me to like not
have make her pay for like a subscription to something. Oh then no I
mean you have to pay. You can't just make a website and not pay for anything you
need hosting and shit anyway. Well she has host she already has a website she wants me to
update it. Oh I just have to like find. You shouldn't have said you could do that. Dude you should put a crazy cursor on it.
Yeah, you should I think I might put like a chest cursor. Yeah. Yeah, I should put the mind
I know
My face with a little triangle on the top left a jump scare every three seconds. Yeah. Yeah that children's theater is gonna get fucking owned
Yeah, yeah, sounds good. I don't know. I feel like I can learn it can't be that hard or I can I guess
Yeah, somebody has a code that I can just throw on there and it's probably one of the random shit
The easiest coding is to make a web. I know how to do like some like like I know to change the color
Yeah, I know how to do some HTML stuff.
Yeah, you just need to know, you just need to have an idea of what you want to look like.
You have an idea of what a pretty website looks like and then just look up how to do things,
like how to make sidebar stick to the side and stuff like that.
Yeah, I'll figure it out. I'll play it by ear.
Dude, it's so crazy how many people like...
It's so crazy.
It's so crazy how many people, like Neopets guilds,
like so many kids were just learning how to make websites through Neopets and they didn't...
like my sister like all she used to do like was just code like Neopets shit and
I don't even think she remembers how to do it. You could hack a Neopet? No it's like the Neopets guilds.
What in the Samian are you talking about? What in tarnation are you talking about?
I just remember my sister... What in tarnation are you talking about? My sister would go
Oh Neopets and MySpace you'd have to code your MySpace to like get like cursors
I do remember but yeah but that was something you just copy and paste. Yeah I know but
But then there was other stuff that you had to do?
I don't know.
We should just do a Three Stooges style movie.
Yeah.
Like I'm talking old school.
Yeah, black and white.
Black and white, we hit each other with bricks.
We're always tripping each other.
We're all trying to fuck the same girl.
Some beautiful dame.
Actually some ugly white bitch from the 40s.
Wait, who's who?
I think it's obvious.
Yeah, say it then.
We're all Groucho.
Groucho Stooges.
I'm probably like mostly the I'm probably like I don't know much about him.
Pat's curly I think Caleb's mo because he's a short and I'm Larry.
He's Jewish.
No we're all groucho.
I think Caleb's mo because he's short and Jewish.
I'm not Jewish.
Yeah.
Larry.
I am Jewish.
Sometimes I think what if I just started telling people I was Jewish how would my life change?
I tried to do that in middle school.
Really?
like I'm half Jewish yeah and everyone just said shut the fuck up no you're not
the teacher brings you into it my Jewish secret secret door you get secret lunch
we sit on a throne
yeah you have to yeah you just start getting called you start getting A's on
all of your homework teacher winks at you and she hands you your homework oh there I did have
have a we had a teacher named Mrs. Douche Arm. Mrs. Douche? That's what kid that was
the joke. I feel like all your teachers had a pretty easily lampoonable name.
They did yeah most of them Mr. Denno. Yeah. Mr. Asshole. Mr.
Gaping Asshole. Mr. Cream Pie. Actually Mrs. Ballsack got it the worst.
Mrs. Douche Arm was the only I think she was the only Jewish teacher at the school and
she was like our seventh like my seventh grade teacher because we had like the
pod system and then like a year before my brother's friends were in the class and
they learned how to say go shit in the ocean in Hebrew but they didn't know
that she was Jewish and they said it I guess one of them like told because
their their friend Dave was Jewish and then one of them said it to Dave and
then he said something back and then she said something back to them in Hebrew and
then one of them looked up at her and went you speak Jew yeah I mean that's
pretty fair to say I think as a middle schooler. Yeah, my youngest brother, my
half-brother, he's Jewish and not like in the technical, not because his mom
is not, but his dad is. And the way that we found out, because he, my
stepdad didn't even know that he was Jewish because he was raised Christian.
Yeah. But he's like half Jewish. So he's like a quarter Jewish? So yeah, my
brother's a quarter Jewish. So the way that we learned was his mom saw his one
day who's like this like saw his penis and it was circumcised. So she's like this
goofy like old southern lady. She saw him like he like put like a like a sock on
his head or something when he was like a kid started running around and she was
like he looks like a little Jew boy and my mom was like you can't say that and
she was like oh no I'm a hundred percent Jewish and my stepdad was just like what
the fuck then she yeah they just like never yeah they just never is just
something that she he never knew about himself damn yeah well that's crazy
it's like if Patrick didn't know that he was half woman yeah but luckily he
doesn't know clearly does mm-hmm yeah figured that out pretty quick it's hard
to miss mm-hmm yeah yeah cuz it's under my armpit what's it my pussy my pussy on
my armpit mm-hmm that's a that's Daniel Tosh joke
pussy on my armpit yeah he's sorry I wouldn't listen to that fucking white
bastard white Daniel Tosh you white bastard yeah yeah I knew somebody whose
boyfriend knew somebody who wrote for that show I wished it who wrote for that
show and he said that working in that office is a nightmare yeah because
they're always trying to like prank the people who work there like that's part
the job because like you have that lips where people where he'll just like put
like spaghetti on your head or something while you're right at your computer and
he was like yeah it's just like complete hell like everybody hates it yeah I feel
like I'd survive there they should hire you would love it yeah yeah just people
like yeah they just serve you fucking it's pretty you watch YouTube videos
you just watch that you did there's like okay today you have to watch every video
of a midget that's online and you have to find the funniest one that sounds like
perfect job for me. It's paradise but every once in a while we're gonna make
you smell something funny. Yeah. Yeah we're gonna put it... What did I just do at the
beginning of the episode? That's literally what Patrick's... Patrick's apartment is
indistinguishable from the Tosh.0 offices. The office on that show, that
office looked very nice. It is nice. Yeah, they get a lot of money man. Yeah. I think
yeah. It's still running. Tosh.0 is still running. It'll never end. Yeah. It's one of the...
like he doesn't even do stand-up really anymore, he just does it.
There was a, in my high school, we couldn't have Class Clown as the superlative.
So you guys had Tosh, who's the Daniel Tosh?
We did, so 2013.
Oh my god.
So I, my year, it was Next Will Ferrell, which I won, thank you.
Nice dude.
Whoa.
That's huge.
Nice.
You should put that on your resume.
Yeah, two years before was Next Tosh.0.
They thought his name was Tosh.0?
I thought his name was Tosh.0.
Next Homer Simpson.
Yeah.
I didn't win any superlatives.
Me and all my boys won superlatives.
You were the popular kid, dude.
No, I just won Next Will Ferrell.
My friend won.
Ugliest goblet.
My friend Alex won Takes the Most Selfies, which he was not excited for.
That's getting flamed right there.
But then we pulled a prank because you'd get like three comments from your friends and
we pulled the prank and we put a kid who didn't go to the school anymore.
So we were like, "Oh this would be funny, they won't use it." So then he, next
semester, he came back to the school and it's in the yearbook. It says like, "Wow, he
really does take the most selfies with that kid's name." And then he saw it in
the yearbook and then like tried to complain to them and he's like, "That's a
misprint. I don't..." The high school like co-op homeschool thing I went to,
you. They did a yearbook, but by the time I was graduating, I was the only person in the
senior class because everybody else had dropped out.
And so I got like two pages on the yearbook and it was just like a bunch of pictures of
me.
Nice.
And the girl who made the yearbook, she was like, "What do you want as a quote there?"
And it was like right after Harris Whittles died. And so I was like, I want my quote to
be his wheat thicks joke. And so I sent it to her and it's like, "Wheat thins call me
when their wheat thicks, give me that wheat is the joke. And she just typed, she just,
I like, I remember getting the yearbook and opening it and it just said, "Give me wheat
thicks."
That's a whole new quote.
Give me wheat thicks. And oh, and it didn't, he didn't, she didn't attribute it to Harris
Little. It just said, "Give me wheat thicks, Caleb Pence."
My senior quote was Homer Simpson's senior quote, which was just, "I can't believe I ate
the whole thing."
Nice.
Yeah.
senior quote was "What's the big idea?" That's pretty good, right? My friend's senior
quote was just "Skrrt" for like five lines. I'm really surprised they let him do it.
It's definitely much better to just do like gibberish. Yeah, it's so much
funnier. But I did, yeah. I was doing a tribute to my friend.
They mixed up... They're twins at my school named Connor and Patrick
and so they did like... That's your guys' name. They did a quote, their quote was
like some is this the Krusty Krab and the other one was no this is Patrick.
They fucked that up.
And they fucked, but the yearbook fucked it up and switched them.
Damn that's awesome.
Yeah so it was like in the wrong order and on the wrong people.
That rocks dude.
Great it's so funny.
Fuck man.
Yeah.
I used to take my older brother's yearbooks and just I loved going through them and just
like scribbling.
Write a drawing on them.
Just scribbling on people who I never knew.
I used to do it with my sister's yearbook.
I did it with her 8th grade yearbook and there was a kid.
Just because I saw that on like the intro to some like Nickelodeon show probably.
Yeah, I had that idea.
No, no, it's in the bathroom
Good look through a podcast where it looked through or my yearbook. Oh my god. Why?
Because that'd be cool. That shit would be funny as hell. Mm-hmm. I
Could just tell you which kids shit their pants me. Why don't you tell us right now?
Say the first names of everyone who shit their pants
Pissed his pants. I think I told this on the pot already, but the kid who?
What my gym teacher who had like a cleft lip in the second grade?
Only in the second grade he got a cured
They cured it he used to write he was like legally blind
But he would ride a bike to school and he had like a little caddy that he put his kids in
Yeah, dude, this guy should not have been teaching at a school
He had a he looked like this like he had like a cross doing nothing
Just make his normal face
He had like a cross eye like his I was part of the lazy eye that looked at his nose permanently a good left lip
he always wore a windbreaker tracksuit. You know like the tracksuits that are like, it's like a
green and purple? Yeah, like the 90s tracksuits. Yeah, he wore like a tracksuit that he's owned
since he was in college and he one day, he taught a whole unit to us on how to juggle scarves.
What the fuck? Can you imagine going to any European country and just talking about your
high school for 10 minutes right yeah maybe like that's we did not have a
gymnasium yeah but fucking hit so we had this after-school program for like kids
whose mom worked yeah like we it was called it was called like it's called
poor kids school poor kids games and we played this game called sharks and
minnows Oh love sharks yeah I wish we I was classic wish it was a structure to
play sharks yeah let's play it you could play it right now no but we before we
played Sharks and Windows he was explaining the rules to us and Ian was
raising his hand I think I told this but he was like he did the can I go to the
bathroom I don't know can you yeah can I go to the bathroom and he came back with
just gray sweatpants piss soaked down to the leg and his twin brother stood up
and went
the worst part is getting Nelson'd by your own blood you're by someone who
looks exactly like you. Yeah, by a mirror. Yeah, his brother stood up. His brother was
the only one who laughed. We all felt bad. We all were just like, "Oh, Ian." Oh my god,
dude. How old? It was second grade? Yeah. You said? Alright. That's one of like just
the defining moments. Just I knew from that day on, I knew I had to ask, "May I go to
the bathroom?" Yeah, you know, and man. Yeah. I was just thinking, I've been thinking so
much recently about, I texted you guys about this, but the kid in my like
homeschool co-op who had some condition where if he laughed too hard, there's
this kid, his name is Noah, and we found out like my like junior year that
if he started having this thing where if he laughed too hard, he would just
have a seizure and like pass out and just for like, like until I graduated,
we just thought it was so funny and I would go I would just like every day as
soon as I got there I would immediately make a beeline to him and just try to
get him to pass out and everybody thought it was so funny and I was like
and someone he always he had this one friend who as soon as I walked towards
him his friend would stand behind him just fell backwards he could catch him
and it got to the point where the like the principal of the place was like yeah
you guys if I see you in the same room as him you're banned from the school
forever and yeah I got and then I guess he got treatment for it at some point
but recently I found like like a like an Instagram that was like run by like a
collection of the kids like a high school like meme page for the school or
whatever and there was like all these all these like pictures of him just like
asleep, just like having fallen over because I made him laugh and he's just
like slumped over like in his chair in class or whatever and just all of the
captions are just like, "Ah, Noah's bitch-ass fell asleep again!"
Cause Caleb made him laugh.
Dude, it was fuckin' - I miss it, man. I miss that dude.
And then I hosted his graduation and -
You said a joke in the speech?
No, I wish. No, I hosted his graduation and I was like, "Graduating is Noah and he's a
really smart kid," and he started crying and hugging me.
Aww.
And I was like, "I thought that-- Do you not realize that I probably ruined your life?"
I'm probably the reason why you won't be able to fucking pass the--
This is Noah McGee.
No, I wish it was Noah McGee. No, Noah McGee is stupid for other reasons.
Damn, shout out Noah.
Shout out to Noah, baby.
He's headed back to the East Coast.
Oh, hell yeah.
Yeah, I'll probably see him on home.
Yeah, once this corona shit's done, bring him up here.
I will.
I will, in tow when I come back up.
Drag him by the middle.
By the string.
Yeah, I'm gonna drag him by the...
Well, I did install a string on it.
Noah, we're gonna grab your string.
I'm gonna grab your string and I'm gonna pull it.
Pull your string all the way to Boston.
It makes you say your catchphrase.
Yeah.
You're gonna say something.
We should put a catchphrase box in Patrick, in his back.
What would his catchphrase be?
I'm hungry.
I just pull it.
mmm toasting yeah no it would be yeah oh do that yeah which we're yeah yeah that
one no no tire pitched it's a thing that you don't know that you do the but we
know yeah oh yeah do it that's somebody when somebody when somebody says
something like mentions like like if I say like yeah I was watching the Rugrats
movie the other day and you also know the Rugrats movie you pointed me go yeah
yeah yeah I finally known Patrick long enough that I can I didn't it's so hard
to with people that you really know it's hard to identify like impressionable
stuff yeah you know I mean like the only person and people that I know that I can
do I don't have a distinct voice but I know you and you and Neil hmm yeah Neil
is just you know just has like a hand thing that Neil you talk with your hands
yeah that's it but like anybody else like the same me doing an impression of
Patrick is the same as doing an impression of Joshua de Farina it's
literally the same movement of the yes yes we just watch those videos and just
picked up that yeah the frown yeah and the raised eyebrows
They're roommates!
I love him, dude.
Yeah, me too.
We should have him on.
Yeah, we should.
I would love to have him on.
He follows a bunch of people we know on Twitter.
Yeah, because we all follow him.
He's the best.
Shout out to that kid.
Shout out Josh.
If he started a Patreon, I'd subscribe.
Absolutely.
Let's get him some money.
Yeah.
They'll buy street signs.
Oh, that'd be great for him.
That would be great for him.
That would be huge for him.
That would.
No, it would.
Also just if they make like a new Alvin and the Chipmunks, they're definitely stealing some of his ideas. He'll get royalties
Yeah, you know I mean, so yeah, I heard he's going on the writing staff. Yeah, I've talked point. Oh, yeah
He's gonna he's gonna write for touch point
And he's pitching jokes
So what if we get a video with Elmo and he went to the store?
That's not bad Josh
I knew we would get there one day. Yeah, we got there. It's the quarantine. Yeah, it's making us be mean
Tell you that
Squibbder web redemption. We're gonna have Sullivan the frog on for a web redemption
How'd I feel bad saying that I feel bad laughing at it no dude he he's our he's our cousin and our buddy and we love
Him yeah, no. I just feel like uh he's our friend
I don't know we make fun of our friends. Yeah. Yeah, dude. He's our best. What are you talking about?
He's our best friend. It's our homie man. He lives with Patrick. Yeah
He's Patrick's roommate. He's here man. He was doing all those voices not me mm-hmm. Yeah, I
I love him.
Alright for the love of...
We have to talk about something else for the last five minutes.
Yeah.
We can talk about how much I have to pee.
Alright.
I'm glad, you know...
Caleb's gonna pee pee in peace.
I honestly, I think this is not a horrible way to do episodes.
I got a notification from Domino's.
Cool man.
Hey Domino's.
Hey man, that's huge.
Hey, you guys wanna order a Domino's?
Should we do another one after this?
Yeah, I got...
I'll do one more.
Yeah, I got a...
I'm gonna go blast a hot one.
Caleb's gonna blast sticky hot ropes of piss.
I'm gonna pee. Yeah, busting. He's gonna be piss busting.
Busted nice with pee in the pants. Dude, I'm gonna pee out fist sized globs of
yellow gunk. It's crazy.
I'm gonna, they're gonna stick to your bathroom wall forever.
Yeah, dude. I'm gonna do the dumb and dumber scene but it's gonna be white chocolate and
you're gonna go, what the heck is this? That's dumb and dumber.
Whatever. Have you ever seen the Amazon Prime description
of that movie? No.
Say it. Say it verbatim.
I don't know it. Say it.
Are you just asking? Well, I don't know it.
I don't know if they did it on purpose because of the title of the movie.
Did they keep going "er, er"?
No, but it's like, it literally makes no sense.
Let's read it.
I posted it somewhere.
Yeah, I bet you did.
You posted it.
I posted it to Cameron's stream.
You posted your pussy.
No, it's got to be on the streaming service.
It's got to be like the...
Oh yeah, the one on the TV.
Yeah.
Alright.
Yeah, we won't see it then.
Alright, find it dude.
Okay.
Find it now.
I'll find it for you.
Find it for me, dude.
Finding for Cameron.
That's my new movie, coming out soon.
Do you think when girls have sex for the first time, they...
Oh, here it is.
...complain that they can't find the penis?
Alright, here's the description for "Dumb and Dumber" when Harry met Lloyd.
"Two mentally challenged teenagers dream an impossible dream to get out of the
special needs. The adventures was so dynamic duo as the two possibly dumbest
boys become lifelong." Damn that's good. It's written by them. Yeah. They wrote it.
Yeah, they let Harry... The thing is they're not that stupid. No. You know like you know
they look stupid. They got a bowl cut? Jim Carrey, the thing is even even Jim Carrey
in that movie his character could have just been Jim Carrey like if he had
tried hard if he had gone to like if he'd gone to an open casting people have been
like damn you're good you make some of the funniest faces around dumb you
straight up you look like Jim Carrey right you look like dude you seriously
have Jim Carrey face right now you you straight up you'd be looking like
Truman you us three we're like here we're like I'm Jim you're Andy Patrick's
the Grinch we're like the three the three versions the Trinity of Jim Carrey huh
Jim Andy and the Grinch yeah and oh I thought you were talking about yeah I
thought you meant Jim Halpert Andy Bernard in the Grinch that would be so
sick could you imagine if the Grinch went to Dunder Mifflin for an internship
yeah you have green paper yeah actually just save all the shreds of the paper
yeah that's my life I'm gonna eat him in the break room he'd be honestly if you
replaced Creed Bratton he was good grinch nothing changes imagine if they were
friends the Grinch would think Michael Scott is the best boss ever and that he
treats women well buddy cop movie Creed Bratton and the Grinch right and they
have to go save they have to go save the trash Creed and Grinch versus trash how
about a mung bean together what if they go to what if what about what about a
got a an eat prey love style movie where it's the Grinch on a spiritual journey
to the trash island in the middle of the Pacific Ocean. Okay, that might be the
movie we make. We're gonna write something while we're in quarantine.
We should write a gritty reboot of the Grinch. Yeah, we should do a Grinch reboot.
Oh man, with all the Grinch. Wait, oh wait, I have a piece of Grinch lore to
submit. I thought of this over the weekend. Okay, let me know what you guys
think of this. The Grinch's penis, it looks exactly like a Christmas tree and
that's part of why he hates Christmas is because he thinks everyone's making fun
of this weird shape of his penis when they see he sees the trees. You gotta save his
skull for the movie buddy. His penis is darker than the rest of his body. Yeah. Yeah. So what do you guys think of the Grinch
lore? Comment down below and let me know if you like my Grinch lore. Comment below my feet.
Yeah, crawl underneath my feet and comment and lick the bottom of my feet
while you comment. Yeah look up under the dress that I'm wearing. Which I do. I
guess I'll peek through my toes at my junk. What kind of pose should I do
for my sexy dress photo? A sexy woman pose? Duh. I don't even know what that is. Why is he
even asking yeah you don't know what a sexy woman looks like because you never
look at one you look at a sexy man mm-hmm I'm gonna eat you imagine okay so
imagine like Jonah in the whale I'm gonna bite off your butthole I'm gonna get you
you remember the I'm gonna put my sharp ass thumb in your butt dude rip you up
from the inside I'm gonna put a pencil in your button it's gonna come out sharp
Yeah. Okay, I have to shit and piss so bad. Oh wait, we have 30 seconds. Do
you remember that VeggieTales movie with Jonah and the whale and there's a
worm in it for no reason? We will talk about VeggieTales in the next episode.
This is a little teaser. I got some thoughts on Larry the cucumber. Larry the
cucumber hung out with a blue worm in that movie. The blue worm? No. Janna one
time told me that when she was growing up a girl told her that every night she
would go home and stick an entire French cucumber in her pussy. What? Damn. Yeah and I was like
"girls are so disgusting." "Girls are so cool." "I hate girls." Dom told me that uh when she went to
summer camp there was like a very religious girl who handed out Bibles to everybody on the first
day but she was also obsessed with the WWE Divas. What? She was like she's gay. Yeah she's a gay
woman but she was very like she didn't understand. That's such a funny like thing to put your gayness