You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
Wow, alright, we're recording now.
Say it again, Patrick.
Watch Mojo's Top 10 Crazy-Ass MF White Boy Moments.
Okay, and now say the next thing that you were gonna say.
I wasn't gonna say anything.
You said... No, you said something about...
thing there's someone someone in one of my classes was like yeah I watched like
every watch mojo video that's just so cool that's insane that's like psychotic
behavior that's no yeah that's like a hundred thousand hours of and most of
them are just like the craziest looking birds that you can see in Boston 10
weird chairs I sat on today yeah yeah the 12 craziest movies to exist 17
greatest 9/11 hijackers. They only go up to 10. Shut up dude. They're not called
10 Mojo. Yeah. I refuse. A watch goes up to 12. Mmm or 60. Yeah depending on the watch.
Yeah. Or one. If you have like a shitty... I don't watch this as day or night.
Just divided in the middle. Yeah. That'd be kind of cool. Yeah. Welcome to the first
patreon episode yeah paying money to stop hitting the camera damn going crazy
dog yeah crazy crazy white boy shit so number one crazy white boy moment that's
happened recently I think belongs to Caleb okay right I got a hand tat last
Yeah, yeah. Last time I thought I went to my brother's house and I was like, all right,
we're gonna chill gonna play pool and that'll be it. And then I and I was on like a ton of Dayquil.
And then I started drinking which you're not supposed to do with Dayquil. It's very bad for
you. And it can compound the effect that alcohol has on you. And cut to like six in the morning,
I'm getting a hand tattoo of just a dot.
And also another guy, one of his roommates,
was doing a tattoo of the word Satan on my leg.
And then my brother, I was really fucked up.
I kept as I was sitting there, I kept showing everybody my dick.
And there was like a bunch of people there who I didn't know at all.
There's like this guy's girlfriend was there and she's like,
it's like his new girlfriend.
And I was just showing everybody my dick.
Which they later, they told me today, they were like, I had three of them tell me,
"Caleb, you have an incredibly pink penis."
They were like, "Your penis was shockingly pink."
And so I guess I have like a, I guess I have like a clit, like just a little pink bulb.
And another, another, a different crazy MF White Boy moment.
Uh, you took Neil's phone at the TAM and then you took a photo of your, of your pinky.
I did.
I'm realizing I'm like, I'm in, I'm like a drunk, uh, when I get drunk,
I just show my dick to people, which is not good to admit.
Not good.
No.
It's behind a paywall.
And it's true.
Yeah.
I did for like a minute make that Neal's Tinder picture.
That's so funny.
And then I found out today Jana is like doing like,
she's like is developing like some older photos and one of them is just like,
has my wiener in it.
And she might like take it to like one of her like critiques and just,
I'll just have like 15 photo students just like, like critiquing my penis.
So I'm looking forward to that, but they changed the S into a flower.
So it's not Satan anymore, it's a flower.
Yeah, which is the opposite of Satan.
I was kind of bummed that I didn't get-- Satan would have been a funny--
Satan would have been sick, dude.
--a funny sticking poke to get.
Yeah, that would have been fun.
And then I did a bone on him, but it looks like a wrench.
It's like the worst bone of all time.
It's like a bone that doesn't exist.
Damn, the worst bone of all time?
That's you having sex.
That's my tiny pink penis that everybody saw.
Yeah.
But apparently the girl today, her boyfriend, asked her, "Hey, sorry you had to see that
guy's penis."
And she was like, "Oh, he had a very small penis."
She was like, "I didn't see much of his small penis."
It's pretty cool, man.
Hell yeah, brother.
Yeah dude it was one for the ages, one for the history books.
What have you guys been up to this week?
First off, if you're listening to this, thank you for becoming a patron.
We have one of the patrons made it out live to be sitting on the episode.
First live Patreon I guess.
Yeah, this is our first live podcast.
They flew me out here.
Fuck a fan challenge.
Yeah, that's why you're here.
You're here to get railed by me and Cam.
That means that Patrick is just gonna jerk off and...
Yeah, he's gonna watch.
I'm gonna sit here in my bed and put the talkie powder on my peepee.
This is kind of like a cuckold thing then.
Yeah.
Patrick's my husband. I'm the wife.
Yeah, you're gonna have to pay more if you want to talk this much, Noah.
Yeah, I've been trying to shut the fuck up the whole time.
I've been taking a lot of self-control, so I'll go back to shutting the fuck up.
Um, yeah, we got a lot of fun stuff planned for the Patreon.
What are you talking about? Oh yeah, we do.
He's stupid. He's so dumb.
We do, actually. I thought you meant for this episode.
Yeah, that's because you're stupid. Yeah, I know.
Cameron's just tired. Stop hitting the camera with the axe.
see this. I'm so fucking tired I just got no good sleep the past few days and I've
just been like laughing at just the stupidest shit like it was like cracking
up like I was at work and I was just dying laughing because I saw on Facebook
like one of those you know those like Facebook app games I saw one called
Santa Claus plays Japanese crossword and I was just laughing for like 10 minutes.
I've been getting phrases stuck in my head so much today it was um it was I
I it's just thinking about Wiz Khalifa saying I'm smoking a thingy of weed just
calling a joint a thingy yeah I packed my thingy full of weed push start the car
Pat you can't just like put your hand on the microphone like that he's
It's gonna sound awful.
It's gonna sound normal.
It's gonna sound terrible.
But people paid for this.
People paid for this episode.
Yeah, so you shouldn't palm the microphone.
They want to hear the raw shit.
This is like the Peel Sessions.
This is real rap.
This is Eminem's smile right now.
This is probably Peel Sessions.
It's true.
I hope I didn't leave it on the cam.
I just ate fucking so many tortilla chips.
Fuck.
You didn't do that.
I ate two rice cakes.
Nice.
Cool, dude.
Yeah.
I don't care.
It's exciting.
Anybody else get a hand tat?
No.
That now it's so loud.
It was?
What are you doing with the mic?
No, you're just, can you just like, be normal?
All right, I'll put it back.
Okay, there we go.
It's gonna sound so terrible.
It's okay.
This is gonna be great.
I, did you, Pat, did you see the message that apparently has been going out to all the patrons
when they signed up. Oh yeah, it's just this "fuck you". It's just this "fuck you". I forgot
about that until Cameron told me yesterday. Yeah, apparently. I think, Pat, did you do
that? No, you did that. I did not do that. You did that. No, I remember because we were
on Skype and you typed it in. I don't remember typing that. Fuck you. That was you. So we're
really sorry guys when you gave us money. No, stand by it. Fuck you. No, I don't remember
doing it I don't have to stand by it all right I did it fuck you okay I'm tell
tell what fuck you know that's so funny really like that the fact we had just no
content up on the pager and people are paying $5 nothing except a message like
there's your personalized thank you notice is good checking the patreon
every day and getting madder every day.
(laughing)
And say nothing.
Hey buddy, fuck you.
Yeah.
Idiot.
Man, what else did I do today?
Oh, I laughed at a car horn today.
I woke up at eight o'clock 'cause I had work.
Nice.
And then, I got up too early.
I don't need to get up that early,
but I keep getting up that early.
Yeah.
And I went to bed at like three.
But I--
Awesome.
Just like there was a car--
somebody honked at somebody on my way to work.
And the sound of the horn was so funny to me
that I stopped and started laughing.
And I just looked like a fucking psycho.
No, no, it was just a normal horn.
It was just like a, "Ha."
That's not normal.
That's a funny horn.
That's a pretty funny horn.
That sounds like Peter Griffin laughing.
Yeah.
[LAUGHTER]
Ha.
Today I watched The Equalizer.
What's that noise?
What noise?
Ah, nevermind, it's probably something only I hear.
I hear something.
Kill, kill.
(laughing)
I watched The Equalizer today.
Great, great movie. What's that?
Is that a movie about a guy
who fucking does math or something?
Kind of. Sounds lame as shit, dude.
He's a guy who he uses math to kill white people.
Okay.
Which is kind of my perfect movie.
It's Denzel Washington and he's in Boston.
It's a Boston movie.
Yeah, hell yeah.
Where does it take place?
He has like OCD or some shit and he loves to move things on tables and make sure that there's
two of things and he's very particular about shit and he works at Home Depot.
And then like 35 minutes into the movie, yeah Boston's famous Home Depot.
And he works-
The one in Somerville next to the Circuit City.
I think it's actually South.
I think he lives in Dorchester.
Oh, OK.
Have you have you heard of Southie?
Yeah, yeah.
It's a great, great movie title.
Southie, the most dangerous neighborhood in America.
Uh-huh.
Tom O'Shea's told you about it for sure.
Yeah.
Yeah, of course.
He's a he loves any Boston movie.
Yeah.
He was like, he was screaming his fucking head.
There was a Celtics game on.
Nice.
He was the only person in the bar paying attention.
And he was just screaming like, "Let's go, baby! Let's go!"
Yeah, Tom's not doing great.
Famously not doing awesome right now.
So let's make fun of him on the podcast.
He'll never hear it. He won't.
I will never. I will never make fun of Tom.
He's too pussy to throw down five dollars.
Me too. I love him too much.
Yeah.
But in the movie, he starts, he's so good at math.
You assume he's good at math because he is neat.
and then he, which I don't know why that makes sense to me, but then somebody tries to have
sex with a kid or something or no, he tries to, no.
He tries to have sex with a kid.
So, Chloe Moretz is like a teen prostitute who gets beat up and then he's like, I want
to buy her.
When did this movie come out?
2014.
Oh, okay.
But he goes up to the Russian guy and he's like, I want to buy that little girl and,
because I want to protect her or whatever.
And the Russian guy's like, I don't care.
You can't have her, buddy.
and then he kills, he kills in like the coolest way.
And he times everything.
Before he kills people, he's like,
bet myself this is gonna take 15 seconds.
- Yeah.
- It's like, and then, yeah, and then he does it.
- And it's like, it took 15 seconds.
- Yeah, but I, or he doesn't time it.
He forgets to time it. - He counts out loud.
- Well, he does, he goes like, one 1,000, two 1,000.
And he's like fucking putting, grabbing people's dicks
and putting them in their mouths.
And he's just like, three 1,000, four 1,000,
it's really cool.
- Yeah.
you would be if you were a killer. No. Yeah. No. That's probably true. I can't count to
ten. Drew, I can't count past nine. Well, that's why you'd be so good. Cause you'd
be killing. Everything takes nine seconds. The nine second killer. One, two, three, four,
five, five, five, five, five. I guess it took five seconds. Wow, dude. I'm the king of killing.
Dude, I'm the best murderer ever
Shit today. I was laughing really hard
imagining
Going like being at it. I was at a deli and I my brother ordered something with
Or something with no onions and they just loaded it up with onions
and I thought about
Going up to the counter and being like listen, buddy. I like a good prank as much as the next guy
But this makes no sense. Listen. Yes. Was it funny? Of course it was funny. Yes. I'm fucking dying laughing
But I did pay for no onions
Seriously not cool. That happened at work today. I went I was running food and uh, yeah a woman asked specifically for no avocado
And you pranked her with avocado? No, no somebody at the counter gave her double avocado in her order
So she just had like two like piles of avocado on her salad and she was like I'm saying it is a good
It's a good prank and it's like it has plausible deniability to when you're like, oh you said no
I thought you said please give me extra. Yeah
You might press the mo avocado
Shit yeah, yeah. Yeah, let me sorry. Let me delete that off the order. I have to press the she it but
(laughing)
- Mo'avocado subtract she.
How's working at a restaurant, you loving it?
- No.
I literally, you know who came in today?
- Yo mama.
- No, what?
- Yo mama came in.
- No.
John Mugar, the producer of Awesome Show
and like Tom Goes to the Mayor and stuff.
- Oh. - Damn.
- And I was just like-- - Did you get his number?
- What?
- You get his number?
No, because I didn't take his order.
I like saw him and I was like,
"Damn, I should time this just right so I take his order so it can be like,
'Oh, you're John Mugar, can I have an internship?'"
And then, uh, someone else took his order.
That would've worked.
Yeah.
What?
That would've worked.
That would've worked, yeah.
Did you see how good I made you salad?
Look at how good I put this order in.
Now imagine that every day.
Just fucking up every part of the order.
By the way, Tom Goes to the Mayor was great.
And I just like, type in poop.
Yeah.
[LAUGHTER]
But then I just started--
You ordered the poop salad, right?
Oh, I did an intern's prank.
Yeah, sorry.
Sorry, I was--
You have to give me the internship if you laugh.
That's a little taste of what it's
going to be like when I'm around the office.
I'm a bit of an office clown.
You ordered the poop salad, right?
One poop salad!
One poop salad, hold the capers.
Yeah. Mo poop.
Oh, I hit the mo poop button.
Shit.
I hit the mo poop button.
Every order you put in, you have to hit no poop.
Everything comes with poop default.
Oh, fuck, I'm so sorry. I forgot to press hold the poop.
To be fair, you did not ask for no poop.
You didn't ask, I'm sorry.
(laughing)
I keep thinking, 'cause it's like a vegan restaurant,
I keep thinking of like, oh, it would be funny
if I wrote on the modification button extra chicken
or something just so the chefs will like me.
And then-- The chefs will go crazy.
And then it never happens.
Yeah?
Yeah, 'cause I'm like, oh--
Do the people working--
They're literally all mad at me
because I fucked up so many things today.
Well, the chefs are notorious grumps.
Yeah.
I have one of the chef, like the head chef or whatever,
he keeps doing that, like,
oh, you have like blood on your shirt
and then flicking my nose.
I love that prank.
It's good.
He's trying to be your uncle.
Yeah.
I'm kinda like the uncle at the restaurant.
He's a real uncle figure to me.
Yeah.
Yeah, growing up I didn't have an uncle, so.
You know, I was raised by my mother and father.
Yeah.
I didn't even--
I didn't even have an uncle to--
Didn't even have an uncle to horse around with.
Yeah, I didn't have an uncle to show me nasty websites.
Yeah.
So now my boss does it.
(laughing)
Hey, come in here.
Don't tell your parents about this.
(laughing)
I'm 23 years old.
But you got parents, don't you?
And they would not like to hear about this.
Hey, your dad would never show you that.
Yeah, they're watching like King Kong.
This shit is scary.
It's King Kong.
They just zooms in on the, he pauses it and just zooms in on King Kong's like crotch.
Now check that out.
How's that gonna fit in that little woman?
He is entirely smooth there.
time you hear someone say I have a gorilla dick yeah think about that think about
this King Kong would have a giant floppy penis huh yeah but it would be small for
even though monkeys gorillas have the smallest dick size proportional to body
size mm-hmm really yeah it's true yeah give them a really small that's
reassuring yeah I mean it's the stereotype of like they're compensating
for something. The thing is you like yeah you're compensating for your tiny dick by being a gorilla.
I feel like in this in the grand scheme of things though I'd much rather be like an unkillable
gorilla than have a big dick. I mean did you see King Kong though? They killed him he was
like the biggest one. Damn. It's true he's the biggest ape. That is bullshit how did they kill
him? Gorillas have thick skulls. It was a plane. Oh okay. They flew a plane into him. Yeah but like
They flew a plane into the tower.
'Twas beauty that killed the beast.
Yeah.
Yeah, a beautiful plane.
The most beautiful plane you'll ever fucking see.
God, it was gorgeous.
A really hot plane.
Yeah, it's so good.
I really like that, the, uh, Peter Jackson King Kong.
Really?
I like it a lot, yeah.
Did you ever play the video game?
To me, Jack Black is so charmingly funny, you know?
And I loved all those parody songs in the middle.
Yeah, all the things where he went like,
(imitating King Kong)
- That's me playing bass with King Kong.
- That's how they killed him.
- Yeah.
- They showed him Les Claypool when he lost his mind.
- His head blew up.
- Yeah.
They showed him Wynonna's big brown beaver
and his head fucking exploded.
- His monkey brain can't handle rock and roll.
- Yeah.
- And that's the truth.
You can't handle new metal.
He wasn't built for it, you know.
It's so funny that Les Claypool just became a steampunk guy.
Did he?
That's awesome.
Yeah, he plays like Dobros and stuff.
Like a Dobro bass.
That's sick.
Yeah, it looks really cool, but he just looks like the fucking worst.
Yeah, he's not looking good.
How's Tom Morello doing?
Tom Morello looks the same, pretty much, just like older.
But less playable.
- What's his profits of rage now, right?
- He has that weird super group.
- Yeah, it's like,
isn't it Rage Against the Machine and Cypress Hill?
- I think it's just Tom Morello.
I don't think it's a super group with just Tom Morello.
- So it's just Tom Morello.
- No, no, I mean, I don't think all of Rage Against,
I don't think like Zack De La Roca's in it, I'm pretty sure.
- Yeah, yeah, Zack De La Roca's not in it.
Yeah.
Hold on, this is what Les Claypool looks like now.
All right, let's...
That's me.
That's me in camera.
Damn, that's sick.
Wow, that's great, dude.
Dude, he looks fucking awesome, dude.
He just looks like a coffee shop writer.
Yeah, pretty much.
He looks like a pedophile to me.
Yeah, a coffee shop writer.
Yeah, yes, you're right.
Yeah.
It's the same.
What are you writing?
I'm writing Lolita 2.
Fucking Brooklyn hipsters appropriated their look from pedophiles.
Yeah, yeah, I hate Brooklyn hipsters. I freaking hate I freaking hate when I go
into a coffee shop. Yeah and there's always hipsters everywhere. Can I just get a
freaking cup of coffee? Yeah. And they're like, "uh sorry we only have uh venti
turn you trans." Yeah, yeah, you mean a non-binary macchiato? Is that what you want?
you fucking scum get the fuck out of our coffee shop you mean hipsters I mean
they do that you mean a double shot at HRT wait seriously you want a black guy
drink that's what you want I just want a cup of coffee no all right
no you don't get mad say black lives matter black lives matter I won't give
okay you want a black coffee you say black lives matter I don't give it to
And you can't put your name in as MAGA
or else we're gonna write Chelsea Manning on it.
(laughing)
Yeah, here's your two dads latte, buddy.
That's all you're getting, it's the best you're getting
out of us. It's so cool
Dennis Leary was able to coast on that until like 2012.
What, oh, just hating-- Just doing that.
Hating gay people.
Yeah, just being like, oh, coffee's gay now.
Yeah.
I wasn't expecting coffee to be gay.
Yeah, I thought everything else would be gay,
but coffee was our last respite.
(laughing)
The straight man's last hope.
Coffee.
- Oh yeah, that's so funny, like coffee.
- It's funny to make coffee into a tough guy thing.
- Yeah.
- Of like, yeah, I'd wake up,
I have my fucking cup of black coffee.
- Yeah.
- Everybody drinks that shitty drink.
- Yeah, I have to drink this drink
or else I get a splitting headache.
- Yeah, I'm pretty tough.
- Or else I get a seizure.
- Sometimes I--
(laughing)
- I see it's in my bathroom.
I get a frickin seizure.
And I fall into the toilet.
I hit my head on the tub and I wake up thinking I'm another person.
And then I go to work and they ask me to say "Hey John" and I'm like "Who the fuck is that?"
I'm Magga.
I'm John, cause the frickin Starbucks guy can't get my name correct.
He fucked up my name again.
I'm pretty sure that's how Johnny Sun came up with his book.
He dictated it all to the Starbucks barista and they wrote it all out.
He hit his head on the tub so many times that he just wrote the fucking book.
He developed a brain disease that like...
That makes you write stupid poetry?
Yeah, it's like, uh, the sky is actually the ocean of the clouds.
Yeah, the clowns.
Yeah, clowns.
I fucking, oh dude if I ever see him in real life.
Whoever, who cares.
Fuckin' on, dude.
I told you guys he came into my work, right?
right? Yeah. Yeah, he called nutritional yeast "nooch." That's awesome. Yeah, real cool guy
move. Yeah. Yeah, great job Johnny's son. He was asking for pussy in his smoothie. Yeah.
Can you put some frickin' pussy in there? Can you put a little nooch in that thing,
if you know what I mean? Yeah. You're like, "Alright, let me get some nooch juice." Yeah,
I'm here to, listen buddy, I'm here to pick up some nooch. And you're like, "You want
smoothie with the flakes in it? Okay. No. No. I'm Johnny Sun. I'm here to get 15 year old pussy.
No, I'm here to go to the back of the restaurant, if you know what I mean.
Oh, I need to actually talk to my manager first. Yeah, you work at Comet Pizza or
Comet Ping Pong. Mm-hmm. Comet Pizza. I mean, Comet Ping Pong and Pizza. They sell pizza.
That's the name of the pizza place in Toy Story. Fuck. That would actually,
Actually, that'd be a funny shirt idea.
Is the Pizza Planet logo, but it says Comet Ping Pong?
That's a good idea.
Why don't you write that down?
Yeah, mock that up.
Yeah, write that down.
Bleep, we're gonna bleep this part
so that nobody steals our idea.
No, I'm not.
I'm not gonna do that. We're bleeping it.
We're gonna bleep it. Do you want me to?
I'll write down the time if you want me to.
No. All right.
Unless somebody listening wants to make the shirt
and then pay us for the rights.
- Yeah.
- And we get--
- Okay, we'll start the bidding at $100 trillion.
- And it's a 70/30 split.
And it starts at $1 trillion.
- We get 70 and we get 30.
Fuck you.
(laughing)
Yeah, you bitch.
- That would be cool.
- We should come up with some shirts.
- Yeah.
- We could come up with some shirts.
How about, all right, what about Patrick?
- I already like this.
head on a steak and it says... I don't think I like it anymore. But it's like a it's like a
steak like a piece of beef yeah and it says I'm gonna eat this later cuz I'm a
fan. Okay now I like it. Now that's a good shirt. Now I like it. That's a pretty good
shirt. Yeah. What about like Hillary Clinton eating... eating pussy. Yeah eating
eating Princess Leia's pussy. Yeah that'd be kind of good. Hillary Clinton as Yoda would be good.
Just make her green and put her face on him.
Yeah.
And the caption would say "Hillary Yoda" like it's supposed to be a pun.
Does not even try.
That's good.
We should fuck the podcast, let's just do shirts now.
Yeah, we'll just do shirts till the end until one of them blows up on like some meme page
or whatever and then we only sell that and then that shirt gets stolen and then we never
or make another profit.
- Look, we should sell just a shirt
that is your Yoda tweet,
and we should sell it for like $500.
- Yeah, that'd be pretty funny.
- And we'd only make one of them.
- Fuck Jerry would buy it, dude.
- Yeah, they would buy it.
And they'd say, "This is our shirt.
"You guys like that?
"Did you guys like that?"
I got 'em for, 'cause they take things, I don't know.
- Yeah.
Nice, man.
- Yeah, thanks, man.
Was that somebody talking in the other room?
That just echoed so much on my end.
That was so weird.
Cool, man.
Great.
That was our first Patreon gift.
It sounded like the Smash Brothers announcer.
Yeah, it was the Smash Brothers announcer.
He's actually standing outside my room right now announcing this podcast.
Luigi!
Yeah, he's...
Yeah, yeah.
Patrick!
Patrick is gay!
not what he says. When you pick, when you go, he's going putting down like the the like
little coin thing on all the it's like "Caleb! Cameron! GAY!" I made a I made a
sound clip in high school I gotta find it because it says I don't know if it
sounds enough like Mario vs. Isis but it's a it's Smash Brothers on Gamecube
and it's saying Mario vs. Isis.
Nice.
Yeah.
It's cool.
I can imagine that.
Who would win?
Mario vs. Isis?
Yeah.
Uh...
They have to behead him twice.
Well yeah.
Because he only loses the mushroom the first time.
What if Isis gets the fire flower?
Then what?
Damn, Isis wit the fire flower?
That's a scary thought.
Ah, shit.
Shit, Isis got da fire flower.
Fuck.
It's over.
Wrap it up boys, they won.
damn what's the metal Isis oh god dude that sucks so bad that would suck shit
ice has got the blue shell Isis is um are they still even around
Isis? No, they all went home.
Yeah, they quit. They're hanging out, yeah.
They're retired. I haven't heard much from them.
It's just not worth it anymore. Yeah.
I feel like I could talk them out of it.
What, you could talk Isis out of doing Isis shit?
Yeah. I don't think so.
I feel like I could just be like,
like we could just get you,
like, this divergent, like,
Just you, just like, on Skype with Isis,
and you're like,
"Look, we're gonna get ya."
We're gonna get you.
[laughter]
I hope you know, we could kill you so easy.
I don't know why we don't.
I'm gonna get you.
We have computers that we only make those computers to kill you and your friends.
[laughter]
That's how serious it is.
We have a big computer in the sky.
We have a big gun that we wrote ISIS on the bullet and we're gonna shoot it in the air and it's gonna kill all of you.
It's gonna ricochet around and kill everyone of you.
It's an actual special...
them that and they'd believe it because every day just like they'll just be like walking down the
street and somebody their friend will explode and just like an American flag will pop out of the
top of his head and I'll be like oh that's magic how do they do that I feel like we could tell
them that we have any weapon and they'd be like yeah it's probably not probably not worth it.
It'd be funny if you told them. I'll tell them. That's what this that's what this agreement was
that you have to tell them. Yeah, I can tell them. I just feel like I could convince them.
I need to learn the language. Is ISIS on Duolingo? Yeah.
Yeah. I think it's like Esperanto.
Speak Esperanto. They all speak Esperanto, yeah.
It'd be funny if ISIS broke up like a band and they're like, "We've been doing ISIS for 20
years and we've had some great times, but we feel like we've reached the height of it and we want to
quit war ahead like we're gonna do one final tour and then yeah hang on we're
not telling you where yeah look yeah yeah yeah we'll tweet out the location
and stay away from that location yeah Isis was a project that I started with
my friends in high school it actually started in a garage never started in a
garage in Orange, New Jersey. Look. And look where we are now, you know. Fucking
incredible, dude. Only 1,000 people bought a copy of Al-Qaeda, but
those 1,000 people went and started their own terrorist organizations of their own.
Remember, you guys remember when Osama died and Fox News tried to call him
"Oo-sama" with a "U"? What's up with that? Yeah, serious what's up with that moment.
Yeah, seriously, look at my face. I'm doing Kenan Thompson face, because what's up with that?
Well, stop doing Kenan Thompson face right now!
[Laughter]
Please stop!
Take it off!
[Laughter]
Dude, SNL sucks.
SNL's so trash now, dude.
I'm in that writing for TV class. I keep having to watch SNL clips.
Dude, wow. That's my own personal hell.
Hell is actually watching the Hillary Clinton "Hallelujah" clip on a loop.
That's the only good thing they've ever done.
That's their last good sketch.
So funny as fuck, dude. I busted a damn gut watching that.
I laughed so hard.
Yeah. It would have been funny if it was Chris Farley doing it. That's true.
If they didn't have... if right after... yeah, if a fat Chris Farley had shittily sung "Hallelujah"
as Hillary Clinton, that shit would be so...
That would have been really good. Now that I'm thinking about it, that would have been great.
So they got Chris Farley's bloated corpse and they...
Yeah.
They prop it up.
Yeah, and they work it like a puppet.
Yeah.
They make him sing "Hallelujah".
They kept Chris Farley's corpse intact like they did with Lenin in Russia.
Yeah, they just shove a fucking Beats pill down his throat.
Pipe hallelujah.
Adam Sandler's singing voice coming out of the Beats pill in his body.
I was at a pool hall the other day and they played Adam's song by Blink-182.
And it's just like a bar. They played Adam's Song by Blink-182 and then the Hanukkah Song by Adam Sandler back-to-back.
It's so fucking weird. It's the weirdest...
Nobody was like adding songs on the jukebox. That's just what the soundtrack of the place was.
Pretty good. Fucking bizarre. They were getting it in early.
Yeah, it was like 11 o'clock. Like people were... people were gonna soon leave to have sex.
And they were playing the Hanukkah song. That might be like a good like get the fuck out of here tactic. Oh
Yeah, yeah, I guess so
That's actually I mean if any song to play that's probably the song
Now dude, I would stay for even longer. Yes, I would be like I want to hear Hanukkah song part one two and three
And the fourth one he's gonna put out. Yeah, how many parts of the Hanukkah song are there?
How many days of Hanukkah are there? There's eight. One. Crazy nights.
Yeah, there's no days. It's just eight crazy crazy nights.
Yeah, so that's how many parts there are. Oh, there is a part four.
I think eight crazy nights was maybe the first time in my life I was like aware of Judaism.
Yeah, no, honestly me too. I don't think I knew what that was until I saw that movie. You didn't know what Judaism was?
Yeah, I was young and there's no Jewish people in North Carolina.
Yeah.
It's very, very uncommon.
Adam Sandler released a Hanukkah song in 2015.
Oh shit.
Play that joint.
So the first two people that Adam Sandler mentions in Hanukkah Song Part 4 are Jesus
and then Olaf from Frozen.
Nice. Both killed by Jews.
But he mentions Josh Gad.
Nice.
Ron?
I'm dropping Jesus in the Hanukkah song. That's a bold move.
Yeah.
It's an extremely bold move.
Queen Elsa from Frozen.
She's Jewish?
Yeah. Oh, this is pretty funny.
He mentioned Jared Fogle and said,
"God damn it, a Jew."
I like that.
yeah yeah that's nice yet when I say that exact thing on stage people get pissed
off I'm talking about Jared vocal okay it's no it's fine
he's weird wait he was he was fucking out of his mind weird he was weird Jared
was weird fuck dude come on you're telling me you're on his side now all
that guy was utterly bizarre he's a serious weirdo he was like something out of a Tim
Burton movie yeah yeah he's the mayor he's the mayor from Nightmare Before Christmas
He turns around to his child fucking face.
He flips his head.
That's good.
I want to smoke a cigarette.
Yeah? Really?
Yeah. Probably after this.
Nice baby.
Is that cool?
Yeah. I mean not in here, but yeah.
No, I would never imagine.
I mean just the way you asked is that cool made me worried about that.
I was like what?
I'm going to smoke a cigarette in your room.
Yeah, what?
Why else would you ask if it was okay?
I don't remember the last time I smoked a cigarette inside.
That's such a foreign thought.
Uh, yeah, I don't know that I ever have.
I remember we used to go to Golden Corral after like church on Sundays and they had
a smoking section.
Yeah, maybe.
And it re- and like the doors were broken.
Yeah.
On the smoking section so the whole place was just a smoking section then.
That's awesome, dude.
would piss off my mom but I kind of like the smell cuz I was kind of a weird kid.
Yeah you'd kind of run and go into the section and go... I ran towards it. Yeah. Are y'all smoking pot in
here or what? I'm six years old and I want to smoke some pot. Come on pass it to the
left player. That's what I did at the Golden Corral. All the fat people smoking cigarettes. I'm
reading I'm still reading the Wikipedia section. Here's yeah here's a list for
the show list of the list of Jewish people mentioned in the Adam Sandler
Hanukkah songs. It says okay so the list has it's this is this is the this is the
run it goes Jack Black whose dad converted his mom was Jewish. But you're doing a list on a no list episode.
This is podcast without lists. Oh all right well anyway he says he says
I cannot say anything that's even close.
Deuce Bigelow is Jewish?
Deuce Bigelow is Jewish and then it says "See note below"
That's such an odd
Wikipedia list.
And then there's like a whole fucking like this big fucking paragraph
The size you held up
with your fingers is very small
when you said this big.
Well it's big on a computer screen.
That's one Caleb penis.
One Caleb penis big.
One tiny red penis.
I have like a perfect plaster cast of Caleb's penis
to measure things because I know it's exactly one millimeter long.
Yeah.
It's true man, I have a small little red penis.
And you said it was pink. You're a liar.
Fact check.
They caught me. I have a huge black.
Yeah, Caleb, Caleb, you just heard three Pinocchios.
Shit dude, you guys fucking caught me in a big lie. Damn.
All right, fine, I don't have a little penis.
Joe Biden getting fact checked on stage because he says he has a pink penis and
and I was like actually it's red like a dog. I love him. Yeah this senile old guy
forgot what color his penis was. I stan that bitch. I stan that bitch for life.
Yeah I stan him like I'm gonna kill some my pregnant girlfriend cuz I love him so
much yeah yeah dear Joe I wrote you but you still ain't calling just just like
just like ripping all your hair out and forgetting things all the time to try
and be like him yeah yeah you gotta go get you gotta get fucked up 90s plugs
yeah just injecting fucking cancer blood into your infant side come on that's
That's what happened to Beau!
I gotta be like Joe!
You gotta be like Beau Biden!
Come on!
Yeah.
And didn't his whole wife- his whole wife died?
His entire wife?
Man, his whole damn wife died.
Damn dude.
The whole damn wife.
The whole damn wife?
Damn, he lost a whole damn wife!
Shit dude, that sucks.
There's not even a little left.
None of your wife left, dude? None of your wife is alive?
She all died? You couldn't keep good stuff?
Come on. Couldn't keep just a little bit?
Break me off a piece of that wife.
Break me off a little wife piece.
His whole wife. His whole wife.
Whole wife, dead. Second wife?
Half. Half dead. Half dead.
And you know what half's alive
My man, and then Joe high-fives me. Yeah
No, he's not gonna high-five you he goes in for the high-five, but then you just go straight for the shoulder. Yeah
He's not a pedophile
He's not so he's an inappropriate shoulder toucher
No, I think he didn't care. He's fine. That's still weird. Yeah, I mean, yeah
I mean like I look at that guy. It's weird a girl shoulders and I'll be like
like no it's weird I mean as I just don't you don't know a little girl and you're
an old-ass man like you just can't like it like I know maybe it's not like it's
nice he's definitely not like a pedophile or whatever but it's like you can't just
go around doing that like yeah I have at least a little self-awareness you know
what I'm doing that's very common actually and yeah he's actually more
cultured than us yeah I mean so I feel like I'm gonna take your upside on this
like when it's Italian people on the cheeks I kiss my dad on the mouth until
like yesterday like 11 yeah till yesterday yeah till 11 p.m. so one hour
ago that's why you were late too busy smooching my dad
Every day 10 to 11, that's dad time.
Yeah, but you're out in LA now, you can't kiss your dad at home.
He's got long lips.
Your dad takes a flight every day at 6 a.m.
Then he lands and then you kiss him until 11 p.m.
Then he does, he starts to cycle over.
Yeah, and then he flies back and touches down and gets ready for the flight.
Unpacks everything, packs it back up.
Yeah
Yeah, yeah, he's just goes through the revolving door walks back in is like yep
She's back again. What's your is a suitcase full of a pelican case full of Burt's bees?
Didn't expect to see you so soon. He's like, yep. I'm going to kiss my son
You should expect me. I do this every day. You fucking airhead, bitch
Can I have a kiss? No! Save them! I've saved them from so many!
Yeah, we do one long hour-long kiss. Yeah.
Until our lips kind of fuse together because of our saliva. Yeah.
And then we have to peel each other off with a spackling knife. Yeah.
And then he leaves. Play catch. Uh, that's not normal.
Let's get closer and closer. I'm just gonna say it. That's not normal.
No, it's normal. That's not normal. You guys aren't from the South, man.
Is Caleb's dad Tom Brady or something?
Yeah, my dad's Tom Brady.
Hey!
I'm a little kid.
New England.
Hey!
What is your dad, Tom Brady or something?
Yeah.
Tom Brady, if you're listening to this, man, we just want you to know you fucking suck,
dude.
You're the fucking worst guy in the world.
Stop kissing your son.
Caleb hates his dad.
Have you...
Tom Brady's not my dad, okay?
Have you seen the Tom Brady store on Boylston?
Yeah, man, I opened it.
That's where T.L. works.
Yeah, I do work there.
I'm the manager.
You kiss the fathers.
I kiss everybody who comes in, that's why I got the job.
Oh, okay.
I said, "Can I kiss everybody?"
It's like a Walmart door greeter.
Yeah.
Well, hello there.
Open mouth kiss.
Va va voom.
Just to my son who walks in.
Whoa.
Where do you think you're taking that thing?
What's the Tom Brady store?
What do they sell Tom Brady merch?
It's called the TB12 store and it sells like diet supplements and like
Nice workout equipment and shit. Nice, dude. He's one of the most famous
Work at gym rats of all time. Yeah, this guy's just the dumbest Midwestern guy. I like him
It's got a trillion dollars got some fucking tall woman. They married. Yeah best friends with the president
The reason why he kisses his son is because it reminds him of his beautiful wife. His wife is so beautiful
Yeah, it's like he's like create when mommy's away
Daddy's got to get a little action
Come on. Come here, baby
And that's just for the patreon listeners, yeah, yeah, that's right we can say anything here
My mom will never listen to this. That's true. Yeah, she doesn't know what this is
Hey mom if you're listening I
Love you
Wow, dude, I love you mom. Shut up. Did I love my mom shut up and she'll never fucking know
She'll never know she'll never find out stupid bitch
How long should the patreon episodes be
Left seeing you we didn't specify it. I think it'd be kind of yeah to do less in our yeah, great. Yeah
- Yeah.
- And yeah, I don't know what day these will come out
on normally, maybe Thursday.
- Today, this one will come out tonight, right?
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I'll edit it when we're done.
I also watched that movie "Crawl" today.
- What's that about? - Dude, I liked that movie
a lot, I did not, I thought it was terrible.
- You thought it was terrible?
- You told me, there were certain things I liked.
I liked that it--
- Is that the alligator movie?
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I liked that it was like, they weren't in the house.
I liked like the crawl space stuff, that was cool.
- Yeah.
and I liked the end, kinda.
But the alligators just like,
I thought were poorly done, generally.
They were really slow.
- I love the way their eyes looked.
- The eyes were, yeah, I guess.
- They shined.
- That was incredible to you.
- Pretty cool.
I was like, this reminds me of my favorite movie,
The Shining.
- This reminds me of Diamonds, which I love to look at.
This reminds me of shiny, shiny little marbles.
- Yeah, this reminds me of the top
of Caleb's shiny bald head.
- I actually have hair.
I actually have tons of hair.
Sure.
I do.
Okay.
Okay, dude.
Alright, tons of hair and a tiny, tiny pink penis.
Sure thing.
Yeah, this reminds me of Caleb's shiny pink penis.
Yeah.
Don't fucking do that in front of the mic.
What are you doing?
What?
No, it's smart.
It's so loud.
I'm not doing anything.
Stop beatboxing.
Yeah.
It's really, it sounds really good, yeah, but stop beatboxing, please.
Please.
But I, I, I liked the part where the guy's leg or arm got bitten off.
Yeah, um, spoiler alert for Crawl. Wait, thanks. I'm gonna, the end originally, what they're gonna do for the end is they get on the helicopter and an alligator just jumps up and eats them.
Like at the last second. I always liked that more. That would be way better. No horror movie should have like a good ending. Yeah. No, I disagree with that, but. I don't. I agree with what I just said.
Yeah, because Cameron likes horror movies like, he thinks the freaking Wiggles are scary.
Yeah, no, you like Hotel Transylvania.
Yeah.
That shit is terrifying.
That's your favorite scary movie.
What are you talking, a hotel where Dracula lives?
Wow, that is pretty scary.
He's not even staying there temporarily, he literally owns that place.
And he rents it out to all his scary friends?
And you're telling me you would stay in a hotel called Hotel Transylvania?
No way.
And there are three of them?
No.
Three scary hotels.
I think I know one hotel that's not gonna get a good review.
Yeah, which one?
Trip Advisor, three stars.
Great, great.
Transylvania.
I was expecting two stars because Dracula sucked my blood and killed me.
Two stars, Dracula killed my whole family.
One of those stars, amazing, amazing, and I cannot stress this enough, Jacuzzi and workout
room.
Yeah.
It's rare for them to have free weights, but Dracula don't care.
He, honestly, he's made all that money. He's honestly a really down-to-earth guy.
Honestly, after he killed my family and I was just kind of talking to him as a small business owner to a small business owner,
we kind of have a similar idea of how you should run a business.
We kind of clicked.
And so in that way, I'm gonna give him two stars.
Because that bitch earned that shit.
Also, the Continental Breakfast was fire.
Yeah.
On another level.
yeah didn't touch the blood
yeah
yet but they had the waffle iron
uh... okay but hormones of happy endings i mean like every slasher
no does that it was at the end so
no are any money-making career
freddie krueger
uh... make you cougar
the uh... but like that's that that's i guess that was a twist at the end but
yeah i mean like you know it's a twisted ending it's fucked up
it follows
what i don't even remember it oh they kill him in the bathtub
in the pool
is that what happens? there's a lot of good horror movies with happy endings
uh...
yeah yeah just saying you're dumb
you're stupid
uh... you're stupid friday the thirteenth not happy yeah ugly ugly kid
Yeah, but it's a dream sequence.
Yeah, that kid has to live the rest of his life as Ollie.
It's literally a dream sequence.
You finally get the second one as a fucking dream sequence.
I disagree.
Idiot.
Fucking stupid asshole.
So you think it's an unhappy ending until you have to wait to see the second movie,
then it's an unhappy ending.
No.
It's also happy because Jason's cute.
You do get to see...
No.
You are happy because they've been talking about this guy the whole fucking movie, and
now you finally get to see him.
Yeah, finally get to meet him.
That is true.
Yeah.
Alright, you know I've turned around.
- Yeah, I'm with you. - Good to see an ugly kid.
- Mm-hmm. - At the end of a movie,
that's sort of the happiest.
- Yeah. - I'll be,
"The kid isn't dead after all, he didn't drown."
(both laughing)
- Oh, he's still alive. - Yeah.
(Josh laughing)
- Was it-- - "Jason, I thought
you drowned," you're looking at the screen.
(both laughing)
- Was it, it's Freddy versus Jason, right?
Where he like, they go inside of his dreams.
- Jason's dreams, yeah, and he's just like,
"Mommy! Mommy!" and he's just, there's water and he's really afraid of water.
They, uh, they, yeah, they made him a bitch in that movie, dude.
Yeah.
They, they bitched him up.
They did the same thing with Alien vs. Predator, man.
Yeah, they did that in, uh...
They ate the alien big juicy tits.
Yeah.
Yeah, and made her cry.
Yeah, she cried.
Yeah.
She was like, "Can you help me open this pickle jar, Predator?"
You stupid bitch.
Yeah.
And he's like, that's one of my favorite characters.
And he just turned into a...
It is so funny when people get really mad that like their favorite characters get like,
like defanged or whatever.
Like, it's just, it's such a like...
Dracula defanged.
Yeah, baby.
That's just a guy.
It's just so funny.
Like, it's just so funny to care that much.
That's just a sex pest.
That's just an old guy.
That's an old guy who looks at you funny.
It's an extremely old guy.
It's an extremely old guy who loves sex.
It's weird.
Yeah.
He sleeps in a coffin. He's just kind of weird now. Ever since Dracula got his teeth taken
out, he's just like, just not the same. He's just kind of a weird guy. He honestly got weirder.
Yeah. Yeah. He's like a eunuch. Like he just, he doesn't, he's personality changes. Very
like calm all the time. Yeah, beautiful singing voice. Yeah, very high pitched. "I want to
"I'm gonna suck your blood!"
Alvin and the Chipmunks voice.
That's how Alvin and the Chipmunks sound like, you know?
The voice actors, they all...
They were all...
They were required to cut off their balls.
Actually, everyone involved in the movie, David Cross, had to get castrated.
David Cross did, Jason Lee...
Yeah.
He had to cut off his balls to join Scientology, though.
Jason Lee.
Is Jason Lee a Scientologist?
He was. He went clear in 2017, I think.
I think and then he said I'm out yeah you said he yeah that's what going clear is
in Scientology going clear is when you're removed of all your thetans yeah yeah so
but he's so he's but you still are a sign no wait no never mind wait then why is
it called going clear with the Leah Remini that's just the name of the
documentary shit yeah now go still stuck in that I thought I just quit one last
job John Travolta we need you to go to one last massage parlor John Travolta. Come on dude I can't
they're taking Pelham one two three. Aren't you the bad guy in that movie? Not anymore. No we're
remaking it so I'm the good guy. Yeah he has a he has an Occupy Wall Street motive now. Yeah. He's
He's like Bane from Dark Knight Rises now.
If I was a really rich celebrity, I would pay to make reshoots of all my favorite movies
where I'm the hero.
Yeah.
That's a good idea.
I would do like Back to the Future.
Yeah.
You know?
And I would do like Toy Story.
And I'd just be like a...
A toy.
You're the toy.
No, you get to be Andy.
And you get to play with all the toys.
I get to be...
Because they sort of have different...
know between Woody and Buzz and then now the new I didn't see the new one but I
think isn't Bo Peep the hero? Bo Burnham yeah. Bo Burnham's the hero.
I would just have them edit me into that role in every single one. Yeah you know that
video of like like this dad who's a genius with CGI like made it put his
little kid in all these like adventure situations that kid must like I don't
know I feel like that that kids gonna grow up fucked up. It's gonna have like a
- Something about that. - A sense of reality.
- Something about your dad,
like using after effects to make it look like
you're jumping over a volcano.
I just feel like you can't turn into a normal guy
after that, you know what I mean?
- That's true. - I don't know what it is.
It'd be funny if-- - I think it's like
the same thing as most child actors though.
- Yeah, yeah, it's the same as being a child actor.
It's the same way they're hooked up.
- 'Cause it's like they're put on a pedestal.
If your dad tells you you can jump over a volcano,
You're gonna grow up believing it.
And you're gonna try it.
And you're gonna try it for sure.
It'd be funny if like, uh...
You just can't take him to Hawaii.
You can do whatever you want.
Yeah, my fucking kid thinks he can jump over a volcano.
Maui trip's fucking ruined.
Fucking cancelled.
The big island's not for us.
I wanted to learn how to surf.
Before I turned 49.
Yeah.
I was gonna put myself in with Moana.
And now I can't.
Now I can't even get fucking shots of me surfing.
Yeah.
The dad just like puts the kid into like, scenes in their like DVDs without telling him.
Like he puts him, so he's getting like curb stomped in American History.
He's like, "What the fuck is going on?"
He's gaslighting your kid.
The kid like goes through the DVD collection one day and pops in Monster's Ball and sees his dad fucking Halle Berry.
*laughter*
Why's my dad bad Santa?
That was an odd choice.
Uh, kinda weird, my dad made me everyone in Schindler's List.
*laughter*
Brilliant CGI artist,
bringing son's fantasy to life.
*laughter*
Playing in the holocaust.
yeah just like everybody like even the Nazis yes and then all of their home
movies he just edits in he replaces the kid with Macaulay Culkin now yeah yeah
tech startup Macaulay Culkin yeah damn dude pizza pizza underground Macaulay
Culkin that's the best one that yet that dad must be fucking insufferable like a
belly kill for sure it's wedding video like him and his wife's wedding video he
just like puts in like explosions and shit is it can you not oh my god I
I forgot Master Chief was there.
*laughter*
Master Chief was the ring bearer!
Oh my god, do you remember?
Master Chief was the best man!
And then he shows his wife
He's just playing!
He shows his wife, he's like
"Sit down, I need to show you something."
And then shows a sex tape of them
but he has himself replaced with Banjo Kazooie
*laughter*
He's like "What the fuck is this?"
"I've had my suspicions for a while."
for a while. He just like, it's like his kid's graduation, he just like, he's like
this stay puffed guy from Ghostbusters. Yeah he's like, he's like check this out,
check this out and the kids like can we just like watch the normal one? He's like
deleted it. Yeah, I don't have it anymore. You're gonna have to. He just he just
replaces the graduation video with the entirety of Ghostbusters. Yeah. Ghostbusters 2.
I did CGI magic dude. I replaced all the footage. I replaced all the footage with an episode of Mansers.
Yeah. Like dad just say you taped over it by accident. I won't be mad. Just please
Please stop saying you're a CGI mastermind.
(laughter)
Dad, you didn't do shit.
Dad, stop editing episodes of Dexter to make it look like you're killing me over and over again.
(laughter)
Please stop. Please stop. This is really fucking me up. I'm 8 years old, man. Come on.
Goddammit, Dad.
Son, this is my art, okay?
Since I left your mom for being a cheating bitch,
this is the only thing I have.
I have. Editing his ex-wife into everyone in Shindra's list. She got what she deserved.
I don't know what to tell you. Yeah, that's what happened to your mom. I know you can't
see her. Don't cross me. Yeah, mom's gone. Yeah, thousands, thousands of your mom were
murdered literally hundreds of the millions. Mom's gone go ahead look I have the video
it's spider-man one she's Peter Parker's uncle and she's dead okay she's dead
he's modding his ex-wife into Mortal Kombat he just mods an entire map of his
like in whole home into battlefront 2. Into that episode of call of duty where you shoot up the airport. Yeah, no Russian. No mother.
It's him and his son are the shooters walking through an airport killing thousands of his mom. He's like dad, dad first off this is incredible.
This is the best level of any video game ever but I saw mom at her job at Best Buy yesterday.
She's dating Yuka and Lele now.
broke up with Concord because he was abusive. Is that a plot point in that game? I don't
remember it. Concord's bad fur day? Yeah I know Conker's like a misogynist. Why do you
keep saying Concord? Yeah what the fuck? Flight of the Conkers or something? I was gonna let
it just happen. That's a cooler way to say it. Straight up. Concord. Doesn't it sound
Yeah.
The Conqueror's bad for a day?
He thinks his name's The Conqueror.
I'm The Conqueror.
Yeah.
Alright.
That was an hour or two.
Yeah.
That's an hour or two.
Who cares?
Thanks for subscribing to the Patreon.
I gotta work tomorrow.
Yeah, thank you for subscribing.
Shut up!
Not if we get enough fucking Patreon patrons.
That's true.
I will never have to work again.
If we can get a thousand people between now and tomorrow, Patrick can officially not go
to work tomorrow.
Yep.
so how about that show my boss the balls in your court mm-hmm patrons and
ball in your sack we have some fun surprise content yeah soon work yeah and
hopefully next couple weeks hopefully a video before too long and then a special
file and a special developing we're developing a new format we're giving you
a new format. Dot Patrick. Yeah. WinRAR is not gonna know what to do with this.
It's gonna break your computer. It's gonna be too big for most computers. Hey,
patrons, if you're listening to this, I know a way to make your computer be able
to read the dot Patrick file. Go into file explorer and delete system 32. Uh-oh.
Yeah, I'm serious. That'll free up enough space. Yeah, it frees up enough space because the dot
Patrick file it's a million gigabytes it's a million pure Patrick. They've
uploaded me to the computer. It's his entire genome and also his
consciousness yeah we're speaking to him right now and you had no idea that's how
good it is that's how accurate it is to the real Patrick. I know I'm not even
here I'm in bed I'm sleeping. Yeah we couldn't stand to split the Patreon
money three ways so me and Cameron we put him to sleep don't worry about where he went
he's in a better place and you're talking to dot Patrick now.
Patrick dot Patrick.
I'm in the computer.
He's fully playable.
You can change his outfits.
You can do like a Barbie dress up game and just like take all the clothes off and not
put any on and just look at his little wiener.
You can noclip and look at his wiener from inside.
You can go in there and look at how he doesn't have a brain because he has no thoughts.
You go into console commands, you type in help us ob and then the number one and then
you can type in all the commands. It's just like it's it's exactly like Jedi
Knight Jedi Academy. Mm-hmm it's true. And if you do the Konami code, you can get a mod to put
weird Al in it just like Jedi Knight Jedi Academy. And also we're playing
big-head mode Patrick. Yeah. Yeah and if you do the Konami code you can turn him
into a girl. Yep. Yep. He turns into Pam Anderson if you do the Konami code into
his onto his 3d model. He has a keypad on his stomach and if you press the
Konami code in guess what beautiful Pam Anderson beautiful titties beautiful
ass if you mess it up spider-man yeah if you fuck it up guess what that's all
right spider-man's cool - yeah you're not gonna want to have sex with him you can
swing on my web maybe yeah you can use Patrick spider-man and you can go all
the way to New York City and you become a movie star spider-man yeah so please
subscribe to the patreon tell everybody this was good and then tell people it
- It was worth it. - Word of mouth.
- Yeah.
- And then also, for people who are doing
the $10 Master Chief tier--
- November, we'll schedule a Master Chief call.
- We will schedule a Master Chief call for November.
I'll send an email on November 1st.
Remember, it is five minutes.
Also, just so you know, you don't have to cash it in
if you don't want to.
(laughing)
Don't feel like you have to, you know what I mean?
That's all I'm saying.
It's not, you can still pay the $10
and just not do it.
You can support us super much.
You can, but you don't have to.
You know what I mean?
So I just want to put that out there.
Yeah. Alright.
Thanks guys.
Bye.