Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
(laughing)
- Oh my god.
(imitating gunfire)
- Scare all the audience at the up top.
- You did that, that was the last episode.
You can't do that anymore.
- Oh yeah, true, yeah, but I'm scaring the audience,
not Caleb.
- Joke's on you guys, I had fucking 15 cigarettes
on the way over here.
(burps)
central nervous system is completely blocked.
- Well I do have 15 cigarettes on the way over here.
- So you guys can't scare me.
- I wasn't gonna scare you.
- I'm dead now.
I'm barely alive.
You're gonna need to do one more thing again.
- I'm doing force lightning, Caleb.
- My heart isn't even beating right now.
My heart is slowly rotating like this.
- I'm in poor condition today.
- I can tell 'cause I see the bottom of your foot.
(laughing)
- What, what's wrong with that?
- I just don't--
- It's yellow with slime.
- Yeah.
- What's wrong with the bottom of your foot?
You don't have an arch on your foot at all.
You're excluded.
I have fucked up feet.
You have a completely flat foot.
Who has the flatter foot?
Me or Cam?
Might be a bit of a tarsup.
Hold on, let me take my sock off.
No, I don't want to see your foot.
Can we just fucking move on?
There's some people who would want to hear about my feet.
Who?
You can hear about them, I don't want to see them.
Yeah, I don't want to see.
Do you want to see the picture I took of Neil's foot?
Oh yeah.
We were waiting.
He had his foot on his foot.
He had his foot on the table in the living room.
He was just...
Oh my fucking god.
How is that possible?
Does it have a bruise on it?
I think so.
What?
Oh god, that's awful.
Feet are disgusting.
They're really nasty.
Yeah.
I love how this picture is like blurry too.
It looks like it's attacking me.
Yeah.
That looks crazy.
I just couldn't hold my hand steady when I was taking it.
It was so funny because he had his foot on the table.
We were all sitting around just talking and Cam just pulled his phone out and put it right
up to his foot and took the picture.
I bet he was mad.
Yeah, maybe.
No, he thought it was funny actually.
Really?
Yeah.
Wow.
I'd be mad if he took a photo of my foot.
My feet are all kinds of fucked up.
All my toes have these permanent scratches on them.
I've got like a, I don't know if it's a bunion or a wart.
No, they're on the toenail.
Sorry.
know, has permanent scratches. I've had it since I was like 13 years old.
I've got some kind of bump on one of my toes.
That's nice.
Yeah, it's called your toe.
I don't know if it's a plant or wart.
A plant or wart?
Yeah, I could be growing a plant out of there.
You probably could.
I have a little sprout that's growing out of my pinky toe.
You have a fertilizer because you step in your own dookie all day.
I'm turning into poison ivy.
You like, you literally have dookie on the floor of your room.
No, I don't.
You do.
I saw a little perfect poopy pile on the ploar of your plume.
The ploar of my plume?
I-pod.
I saw a dollop of dookie in your doon.
Is there a fucking gas leak in here?
What's going on?
Me me me me me me me me.
What did he say?
Fuck you.
He said like, "ploar the plume" and then said "i-pod."
I didn't say "i-pod."
Who said "i-pod?"
I-pod.
You're having...
Caleb's having a stroke.
I didn't say "i-pod."
Oh my god, it hurts my stomach to laugh today.
I'm so I'm suffering. He walked around.
He said I walked.
Okay, first of all, that's not what I literally said.
I walked around.
Yes, I'm much I sprinted for like an hour for the video.
We're making with Joan.
Alec.
Yeah, I did when I'm not in shape.
I'm not like I don't like do stuff.
So sprinting for an hour is me up.
He's lying.
Now.
It's crazy that it the hierarchy is like of most in shape is probably like
Caleb me Cameron. Yeah, I go the other way or it should I should not be second. Yeah, but then I did it's messed up
And then I just had to I just had to do it even look like I'm a shit
And then I got a migraine like as I was going to bed and I woke up with it still going
Okay, so I'm I'm I'm suffering today. That's I'm telling you guys and you guys are laughing all over me
Well, I got in a car accident, you don't hear me complaining yeah, I flew out of the window
Yeah, this side you crashed your RC car. Nope. I don't drive an RC car. Not that small you drive an RC car
Okay, we riddle me guys
I might my Hot Wheels car flipped all the way over in the loop the loop guys
So I'm having a really stressful day Caleb and Stuart little share a parking garage little
You know me this in New York City you Riddler Jokers if I was as small as a
Thing that could be driving in our seat car. You're not talking into the megaphone. Yeah, I can't hear you
I was small enough to be driving an RC car, how would I hold the controls?
Just for the listeners to know, I've been pitch shifting Caleb's audio down like three octaves
for every episode.
Usually he sounds like a hummingbird.
I don't go like...
Okay, so the pitch shift malfunctioned for just a second there.
No, it didn't malfunction.
You don't have a giant reverse helium box.
645 Caleb.
That's how tall I am, 6 feet and 45 inches.
Six millimeters, four millimeters, five millimeters.
I don't, that seems pretty tall.
That's like 15 millimeters.
To you, that's like really tall.
Yeah, that's a million meters, so that's the most tall.
That is pretty tall.
15 millimeters, like that's like probably, that's really tall.
I think it might be.
I feel like if you jumped off that height, you'd die.
15 millimeters?
Yeah.
I'm going to keep a stack with you.
I don't know how much a millimeter is.
I do.
How much is 15 millimeters roughly?
It's about 15 millimeters.
If you could do it with your fingers.
That's probably like, it's probably close to like .015 centimeters.
Oh, okay.
So it's smaller than a centimeter.
Is that correct?
I don't know.
It is smaller than a centimeter.
Can we get millimeters to centimeters on the clock?
I think it's 10 in a centimeter.
I'm pretty sure.
Oh, okay.
half an inch that's point six inches 15 millimeters point six inches that's
average i was pretty close i hear that's average wait wait change it from inches
to centimeters why i was gonna say it's gonna say point one or 1.5 i think yeah
1.5 i was i was way way wrong yeah all you knew is that it's base 10 and so it
was you just knew it was small which is that's the idea that's pretty much all i
think you guys have to give me credit for it i am giving you credit at least
- Just knowing math a little bit.
- You know it's smaller than a centimeter.
- How is that you knowing math?
- It doesn't matter beyond that.
- 'Cause you knew that metric is all just
in multiples of 10, you think that's you knowing math?
I don't think so.
- You didn't know what a millimeter was either.
- I knew it's a metric unit, so I knew that it was--
- But he did too.
- Yeah, but I'm saying it's not a--
- I think you didn't even have a guess.
You couldn't even think of a number.
- I have Caleb Beat here.
- Nope.
- You literally couldn't think of a number that entire time.
- You guys know I have less neurons
because of my small brain, and it's impressive that I can even form a single sentence.
But I don't have a small brain because I'm small.
It's small in comparison to my big body.
And I didn't come here rowing a leaf.
No, of course not. It was a bottle cap.
It wasn't a bottle cap.
[Laughter]
Very funny. No, I didn't.
I know you weren't rowing anything. It wasn't raining when you came here.
with a hawk and I didn't turn myself into a pickle. It was a sparrow. There's a
there's been a hawk at the park recently. Have you guys seen this hawk? No. No you
should try to catch him. I want to dude I keep seeing it he swoops like pretty
close to my head with a mouse in his like claws. What? Every time? Yeah I've seen it like
twice this week. Twice this week I've seen this hawk go up to this
lamppost with a mouse in his claws. I'm like damn I'm gonna try and like swing my
skateboard at the hawk. Save the mouse.
Yeah.
In like a bowling park.
Just truck smacking a hawk.
That would be kind of cool actually.
That would be funny to see.
But I would get in so much trouble.
Yeah. You should shoot him.
I would just get arrested on the spot.
I hate being in those situations.
where you have to swing a skateboard at a hawk to save a mouse.
Where I want to do something so bad but I know that somebody would like videotape it.
Yeah. And then I would get in a lot of trouble.
Like public urination?
Yeah, like shitting in public.
Dude, I almost got... I didn't almost get caught or anything,
but I did get caught on Halloween by a guy in a Mario costume.
While you was peeing?
While I was peeing in between like...
His butt?
Cheeks.
well as the player i was in the middle of a mario and a lowly g_e_
yet there's a there's a guy in a mario costume the walked by some my full dong
peing well as just like men
is this is a serious night of my life
mario's not that that outfit near your neighborhood of the in
in a mario game i know yeah
yeah chris never seen you don't say it's rats on my
some i think there's a great ronin loser shop it is chris pratt and was really
Are you serious it was Chris Pratt? Can I see a photo of Chris Pratt? Yeah. Wow, that's a good photo.
Go to Google and look up Chris Pratt. I'm looking him up. This is a hot guy.
Yeah. I hope he's not a Christian. Oh, I hope he doesn't love God.
I hope he's only one inch tall. You're gonna be sorely disappointed.
Chris Pratt, can you please autograph this postage stamp? No, I don't. I'm such a huge fan.
Well, not a huge fan, but I'm a...
I'm your littlest fan.
I'm the tiniest fan you have.
Chris Pratt.
@ChrisPratt.
I'm a fellow Christian and your littlest fan.
Your number point one fan.
Yeah, no, I'm not small though, like actually.
Like I fit on my couch normal and I barely fall between the cushions.
Your couch is a crumb.
That's what you thought of?
My couch is a crumb?
Yep.
You didn't have to think of it.
It doesn't even look...
We've been to your apartment.
You can't just say anything I use.
And notice I said we've been to your apartment, not in it.
You can't say...
Because we can't fit in your apartment.
That doesn't make any sense though.
It needs to generally have the shape of something.
Like you can't say...
Crumbs can be any shape.
Oh, the plate you eat off of is a piece of dust.
Your bathtub is a peanut shell.
That one makes some sense.
Because it's true.
It's not true.
And you bathe in peanut water.
If you, okay, if I'm so small, why can't I sit on one of your shoulders and I can just
walk around maybe sit in your pocket?
What are you talking about?
We do that like all the time.
How do you think you get-
But it's been a while.
How do you think you get on the train?
Yeah, your train is a crumb.
Look I'm trying to-
Yeah, basically your computer is a crumb.
You're so small.
You're so small that your shoes are crumbs, your clothes are crumbs.
You're basically, they call you crumbleb.
You're basically a small guy who also-
Crumbleb pits.
small you also have a lot of bread or crumbs around.
Hmm.
Yeah, I leave trails for myself.
Small stuff loves crumbs though.
I won't admit to being small.
I will say I do leave a breadcrumb trail everywhere I go.
Yeah.
Just to make sure I can get home.
That's how I get places too.
Yeah.
Well, Pat follows me and eats all the breadcrumbs as I go.
I'm just glad.
And then I get lost.
I'm just glad I can follow the breadcrumb trail to get back to my apartment.
That's how we met actually.
Yeah.
I was leaving a breadcrumb trail and uh...
I want to try that one time.
picking them up and doing that one. I want to try to leave a breadcrumb
trail see if I can get a home that way. I could see that as like one of those like
when you like when you like when you like open YouTube without an account it
shows you like a city to find your house it's all it's all it shows like like a
like it shows the like the the vloggers that no one's ever heard of and they're
like I like did I but that would be a really good one of those videos like
- Yeah, I followed a breadcrumb trail from New York City to my house.
- It'd be cool to follow a bread-- I mean, the thing is, there are breadcrumb trails here.
There's breadcrumbs. I probably passed seven loaves of bread worth of crumbs on the way here.
- I followed a few glass shard trails, but they usually just take me from, like, one line on the sidewalk to the next,
so they're not very interesting to follow.
One really good trail is-- there's really good train station trails.
- That's true. Train track trails?
- Yeah. Those are good.
- Those will take you--
- Yeah, building trails, too.
You ever look and like see like the lights on in one of them?
In one of what? In a building? Yes.
In a train? In a train? Yes.
I've seen the lights on in a train. In a train tunnel.
There's like lights on in a train tunnel? In a train station? Yes.
I've seen lights on. Usually when I cross the street,
I leave myself a trail of white dashes on the ground.
And also I build a sign with a picture of me. Yeah.
I was on an R train. With a picture of my big red hand.
I was on an R train and I looked, it was like middle of the tunnel.
Yeah, you were. And I saw like the lights on
in the train. I was like, "Damn, if I could live in there, live in the train tunnel."
Wait, you saw the train.
You saw the train.
You persisted.
I saw the train tunnel with the lights on.
And you said...
"Damn, what if I could live in there?"
What if I could live...
In the train.
We did see some elves fixing the train. Do you remember that?
Oh, yeah.
And they disappeared.
Dude, this was so fucking freaky. We were coming back from Six Flags. It was like 3,
four in the morning we're sitting at some that's how late you guys got back yeah
we're sitting at we're sitting at World Trade Center one of those like train
stations well those are the you know no we were in we were in the elves that
stayed home we were what that is true no elves died in but there was like we have
to go. Yeah we heard like some like some like clanging and voices from the tunnel
and I thought maybe there were like devils sabotaging the tracks or something.
We looked and there was there was two little green I think they were green
gnomes or elves. They were either green or skin colored. No they were green and they
were they were going away with little little squeaky hammers. And my mic just
stopped working for a second. So scary but they're singing a song. Did you
actually see elves? I don't remember there were elves but then the train came. There were
little elves working down there and the train came and I was like those guys need to get
out of there. They're going to fucking die. They're going to get killed. And they didn't
come out and I was like we're going to watch these little elves get killed and then the
train came and right as they were coming I looked and they were gone. And then they came
back when the train left. Yeah. It was fucking terrifying. Yeah we called the person who
was still waiting at the train station after we got on the train and they said they were
Alright, I believe this. I believe that there were elves.
It's true.
There are subway elves in New York. That's one of the big things about this city.
Well isn't there like bronzed little subway elves in the 14th street station?
Those are the elves that died in service.
By getting hit by the train.
Yeah, and they bronze them after. That's why all the bronzed elves are so grotesque and
their viscera is...
- They look like the little green guys from Fraggle Rock.
- The Fraggles.
- No, no the little guys.
- Oh, the green Fraggles, yeah.
- No.
- The little Fraggles.
- No, not the Fraggles.
- Right, oh the Rocks.
- They're not the Rocks.
The little green guys, I forget their names.
- I think they were Rock Fraggles.
- No.
- I think you're gonna grabble my cock.
- There's red, and red was the main Fraggle.
- Knock it off, quit grabbling my cock.
There's the purple fraggle with the blue hair.
- Grapple cock.
- Grapple a cop, is that what you said?
- No, I said grapple cock.
That's a good, that's a fun phrase to say.
- There should be an MTV--
- There's a big guy who says,
"Look, mom, I found a fraggle."
- UFC show where they get like a--
- There's a little green guy and they do work.
- Yeah.
- You know?
- Like it's like a Deadliest Warrior thing,
but it's the same matchup every--
- But it's real.
- It's just different cops and different guys.
- It's just like literally just an octagon style UFC fight
between like guy who volunteers and a cop.
you know and they should make uh...
they should be forced in fire but they're making guns there's a new season
did you hear what i said
that's a good idea yeah
but there's a new season of force of our government acted by my own brain
i'm pretty excited
i really hope they make a career sort of something out of damascus steel uh...
they love them asked if they don't ask i was at the time as a steel and like
elementary school 'cause i got this like kids magazine that would have
uh... was a called
Damascus steel samples?
- Muse. - The Doozers.
- Muse, okay.
Muse, you remember, my mom signed me up for Muse,
I think it was called Muse Magazine.
Those are Fraggle Rockers.
- Those are the Doozers.
- Those are called Rockers.
- They're the Doozers.
- And there was one article in there
just about Damascus steel, and I thought it was so cool,
even though it was a boring article, it was like--
- It's cool as fuck, dude.
- It's not cool when it's written down, though.
- But it looks cool.
- It looks cool on a video.
- It looks cool. - Damascus steel?
- Yeah.
I could live with it or without it, I don't care.
Damascus steel?
Yeah.
What are the things you couldn't live without in this world, Patrick?
My friends.
Mm-hmm.
People aren't allowed.
I said things.
Okay.
It shows what you fucking think of us.
He thinks his friends are things.
Probably.
You think I'm just a sex object?
Well, first off, my 700 slaves.
I would bring them to my desert island, no question.
Well, yeah, how else am I gonna get around this thing?
And for my desert island album, I would have to say the magical song that commands my slaves
to do my bidding.
Yep, the one that makes your eyes completely white and makes you build me a house.
And the movie would be that swirly thing I put on the TV screen that makes them follow
my every command.
And I would play it on, basically they would arrange themselves in a kind of cheerleader
position and each would play one pixel of the movie and run around and show me a movie.
I'd have to say too my Desert Island book would probably be 101 fun activities to do
with your slaves on an island.
Pat Rick actually does have slaves that he uses like nanobots.
Yeah.
And he, they sometimes are a roller coaster.
And uh...
Oh my god.
Well, okay.
Don't act like, don't act like you guys don't have fun on that roller coaster.
It's so much fun.
Yeah.
It's, they've, yeah, well one of the slaves, his face is like the exact reverse contour of my, of like my ass.
Yeah, so.
Yeah.
It's a good seat.
Yeah, it's a great seat.
It's pretty much, they're basically like the doozers.
They just fart on them.
Yeah.
Not dead.
I like the slave who draws a picture of us what we looked like on the big drop
after we ride it. Yeah that's right and he gets really white for a second.
He does that. And he has a beautiful painting of us
with our arms up and one of us is clapping because we love the ride so
much. I always show my tits. Show my tits on the ride. Show my tits on the stretcher.
I always like basically just like glue down like monopoly pieces to a board
and it's like a pretty funny joke every time. Yeah it's like funny as hell.
that was
uh...
one of the worst things you've ever done
there were so many of those there's so many of those monopoly pieces that like
as you've been use a lot of glue
radio and that guy when my slaves i
oh yeah well that was on purpose
well because you know the little die cast metal dog
well yeah it's pretty easy to fall off the bar me you know you don't
you didn't know i had a i had a pellet gun
Oh yeah. I had a custom pellet gun. So you were just telling me that it was the
the the little die-cast dog from Monopoly. I didn't know. Oh it was the die-cast dog.
Oh you put a pellet gun you put the dog in the pellet gun. Yeah.
Oh and you shot. You shot at my slave with a dog. Yeah this is becoming more clear. Yeah. Okay.
Kind of a clue situation. Clue? Now that's a good board game.
true yeah yeah Patrick with five hundred getting so excited to like glue do the
glue down pieces thing and you the only board game you have is Scrabble and you
but you just like do just a bunch of random letters. There's no doesn't spell
any words. They're like not in the right spaces. Those were the thing is about
those like yes, those are played out, but if I went if I got off of a roller
coaster and I saw that I'd be I'd laugh my ass off. Yeah, I would laugh my
ass all year i'd last are a thorough my i feel like
yeah
it'll be funny though to get little
to get a little turkey somehow yeah and for life from a six flags as you try to
smuggle in a chessboard yeah well you know what you're doing immediately
yeah i know that you're not sitting at the dip in dot if you're going to get
a hand for life at least bring in like
think i'm gonna get really good at something else
yeah i think i i think i'm gonna get really good at chess i think i have a
perfect mind for it
right
It takes you a long time to move the pieces though.
I'm sick of games.
Uh, well I ride the pieces.
Yeah.
I'm tired of games.
And that's how I dictate to somebody bigger than me.
You're tired of games, including chess?
Yeah.
I'm tired of these games, man.
Man, it's not real.
I'd rather get into checkers.
I think I could be really good at checkers.
Okay, how about this?
Tomorrow, 3pm, my chess pieces versus your checkers.
Are you serious?
You're busy?
Yeah.
Well then, you lose by default.
I win by default.
Good game, my fellow foes.
I just rescheduled the game to yesterday.
It seems like you didn't show up.
I feel like he's doing some Bobby Fischer type move.
I just rescheduled my...
This is...
You can't reschedule.
Pay attention, kid.
This is mental chess.
Okay.
Huh?
I already won.
You can't reschedule it.
Stupid says what?
Who?
Wow.
What'd you say?
I said what?
He got me.
What was Bobby Fischer's deal?
He was like a little freak.
He was Hank Hill's son.
Okay.
In the show.
I think he, I believe he was the, you know, Autismo Chess Master kind of thing, right?
I don't know.
Wasn't he?
Well, I know that he like, I don't know who he is.
He just like exhausted a guy into like making him lose a game.
By just like not showing up.
He exhausted a guy?
he just kept like not showing up to the match. He exhausted the guy. Yeah he exhausted him.
How did he exhaust him? What did he do to him? Like draining him like the dark crystal.
Yeah. And begin.
The essence. God. Is it my turn yet? Is it my turn yet? Hey is it my turn yet? Is it my turn
go can I go can I go can I go and then taking 200 minutes on his turn. Why is chess the
only board game where there's like a flourishing yeah yeah a competitive scene.
You can be very good at clue. You can be very good at shooting. You know what's more
impressive? If you're very good at clue because it's all stuck in it is all
shit in an envelope. Exactly. Can you imagine you sit down for the Bobby
Fisher of chess and you sit down that you put the cards in the envelope
immediately he guesses it. He's just like yeah, Mr. Mrs. Violet in the study with
the candlestick, you open up the clue, the clue, you open up the clue. The top secret
envelope. Yeah, it's there dude. Mm-hmm. It's fucking, that'd be so cool.
That would be cool. What board game would you be the best at? Would you like to be the
best at? Like what would you like to be the world champion of? Mousetrap, because I could
never figure that shit out. Mousetrap is a really good pick. That'd be crazy cool. Even
Even the world championship of mousetrap, they don't play the board game, they just do the Rube Goldberg machine.
It would be cool if you 3D print your own pieces like Warhammer or something.
And then you're in there just fucking...
Mousetrap, Warhammer.
Yeah.
The mouse has a gun.
I think there is Rube Goldberg machine competitions for marbles.
Yeah, probably.
Whichever one is judged, though.
There's not a clear-cut winner.
Yeah, there needs to be rules.
You know what I like watching? Sometimes, the marble racing videos.
Oh yeah, marble racing is so sick.
That's the coolest shit I've ever seen.
Yeah.
They, a guy builds a humongous slide, right? And I'm not saying humongous because it's,
because of how small I am. It's actually huge.
Okay, so when you say humongous slide, you mean like,
Like it's like a slide wedge over here.
Here's how big it is. It can fit 10 marbles on it.
says huge and he races them he has like a start and an end and he talks about it like it's a real
race like it's nascar or something he was like here comes blue coming up and here comes the
red marble have you seen the guy who does the the treadmill races no oh those are sick oh wait yes
Yeah, I've seen those. Those are so cool, man.
Did you see the ant treadmill? Did you see that video?
No.
It was made a treadmill for an ant to study how ants walk or something.
Let me see if I can find it.
It's pretty cool.
I wish that these guys who do these inanimate object racing things would invent backstories for the different things.
Yeah, I know. Because it's like you got like the teams, like you got like the blue blazers and shit and like the red like...
Yeah, like why are they so... Why are they all about color?
Yeah, he just runs on a ball.
Oh my god!
Oh damn.
That's a fast ass ant.
That's an ant treadmill.
Damn!
It's like a styrofoam ball.
It's like a track pad.
Scientists built a tiny treadmill specifically for ants.
Caleb you might want to try this treadmill for ants.
What is this?
A treadmill for ants?
I'm trying to lose some weight.
Right?
From Zoolander?
Oh yeah, that is funny.
That is pretty funny.
Hey, this from Zoolander.
The gas station?
Yeah.
Yeah, you didn't, if he's saying wake me up before you go-go, a layman would guess it,
I guess did right away. I knew from Zoolander. Right. Yeah. Alrighty then. That's Ace Ventura.
Wait, he's the Zoo Master. Checkmate. Right? The Zoo Master? Zoo Master? Right? No. No.
Is it with the animals? No. Zoolander. Zoolander. There's no... Alrighty then. No, you fucking...
Are you serious? Was that when we watched that impressions guy video, the guy doing the
Ace Ventura impression? Oh yeah, he did Zoo Master. Yeah. Really? He did a Zoo Master
That was pretty good.
I told you guys about the guy.
He was going like this.
I told you that already.
I told you.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, you talked about that.
Yeah, the dude in my class.
Yeah, we watched that video yesterday.
Watched it again.
The video, it's like best Eddie Murphy impression done by a white boy.
Oh yeah.
It's a classic.
It is.
That was pretty cool.
He's really fucking good at it though.
Really?
He's a good Eddie Murphy?
He's really good at Eddie Murphy.
He gets to laugh down.
I'm making waffles.
No, he doesn't sound like that.
He does the hee hee hee hee hee hee hee.
You're not.
You're not. I'm making my own voice. You're not the white boy from the video. I'm the white
boy from the video. Nah, no sir. White boy from the video does the perfect impression
in real life. White boy from video does perfect impression of the video of the white boy doing
Eddie Murphy. The Numa Numa guy. Oh, dude. White boy does perfect Numa Numa guy impression.
If Numa Numa came out today it would be called the white boy sings in perfect German. Numa
Numa Numa style.
Yeah.
Yeah, Numa Numa.
What other videos would be renamed?
That's not German.
I think it's Belgian.
Oh, is it?
Mm-hmm.
Don't give a fuck.
I think Dragosta Dente.
I thought it was like Romanian or something.
Whatever.
It's a good song.
It is.
It's catchy.
And then he tried to do a fucking...
Oh, Numa?
As in Belgian, like French?
Numa Urahe?
Numa Urahe.
Yeah.
Fuck you, Gary Braulsma.
Gary Brauls...
Fuck you, Gary.
It's so...
I fucking...
If Gary's listening to this, I'm fucking...
brought up that guy by his full name so many times in my life.
Yeah, because it's kind of impressive to be like, I know his name.
I know the numismatist's real name.
Gary.
It's like I went to Boston Calling a couple years ago, and I was waiting outside,
like me and my ex were like meeting.
We were waiting to meet Mac DeMarco because we were like 19.
And there's like these two kids who kept talking about Overwatch.
No, it's like a group of kids that kept talking about Overwatch,
and then one of them was like, "Yo, pull up Wikipedia right now.
I'm gonna tell Mac his full name."
Because he's got some like fucked up like Canadian, like,
like it's like McBrayery, like something.
And he's like, "Yeah, I'm gonna tell him his full name."
And I just like, I just walked away from that group.
If I was meeting Mac DeMarco with my girlfriend,
I would make sure she was wearing like a, like a mech suit or a knight's armor or something.
Well that's why you tell him his full name, so you can rebuke him.
You can draw a circle around your girlfriend with salt.
I still like his music, I don't give a shit what anyone says.
I think his newer albums are still good.
You never got into that?
Nope.
Never got into smoking cigarettes?
No.
Smoking cigarettes and finger popping girls?
Oh yeah, Mac DeMarco style bitch.
It's a Mac DeMarco summer dude.
I mean a Lunchable and using my slimy turkey fingers to fucking finger pop somebody.
That's still, I mean, freaking out the neighborhood, still an amazing sight.
You know how he freaked out the neighborhood at that one party.
Yeah, by fingering all the people there.
"Oh yeah, fuck, fuck baby, fuck, fuck baby."
Just fingering people.
I bet he fingers with the pinky white ass male bitch.
That's right.
Well, yeah, when he fingers he has a huge gap between his two fingers.
Yeah.
I think I can still fit a cig in here.
This gap.
What?
No you can't.
No way.
I mean, maybe squeeze it.
I mean, don't do it though.
It's not good for you.
Yeah.
Don't do that.
That's good for you.
That's how his teeth got all fucked up.
Yeah.
I don't trust people with fucked up teeth, man.
That's the beginning of the entire body.
Let me see your teeth.
Yeah, let me see your teeth.
You know, your fucking chipped teeth.
No.
your mouth like this every tooth you own is chipped you know people who are
missing front teeth no that's fucked that's not that fuck it's cool
no the teeth are like the worst part of the body this would be a guy with fucked
up teeth just going around parties like you think teeth are like who cares I am
that is exactly me I'm a guy with fucked up teeth who hates them guy with a huge
a huge hole in his forehead.
- Why don't you get them removed?
- Look, the forehead's the stupidest part of the body.
- I wanna make my teeth look like Shane McGowan's teeth.
I wanna have a life of poor dental hygiene
and whiskey drinking that my teeth turn black.
- You're developing whatever the teeth version is
of cauliflower ear.
- Yeah.
- It's just like an occupational hazard.
- Mouth cancer.
(laughing)
- Yeah, it's just what happens
when you do what I do that long.
I'm so scared of getting mouth cancer.
I'm scared of cauliflower ear.
Can you imagine how fucked up I would look?
All you'd have to do is drain it.
Oh, but you, yeah.
Hold on.
Yeah.
Dude, it'd be over for me.
I can't, I can afford to make my ears look a little bigger.
No, I can't.
I have nothing to hide.
You can't.
Yeah.
You'd be able to float away.
Just on your ears alone.
You know what?
I'd be able to float away.
That's right.
Yeah.
And would that be so wrong?
I could afford to have a bigger ear.
i think that we have tiny my fucking user
honestly everything about you is tiny is he so small
now maria's money like
came here on like
uh... like uh...
hardboard box i came here and i think it's all the rain it came here in a
refrigerator box here yeah
no he's so small that he can you literally like he came here on like a
what like a like a clock or something yeah big ben
uh... when you know you can't it's like you came here in like a key like uh...
like a shoe
has a nice and you are not going to get a chance to let the little sorry i can't
you know that you came here on a bean
the only other chicago being okay
uh... no and also the shoe was the
little lady who was a little bit of the lived in you came here on something some
kind of small i full thing
mhm
don't want to know if you can i have a plan it was a four sixty five what's up
boys hit it
no
uh...
i got that wrong though i can hear unlike the most medium thing of all time
like what
earlier me along island medium
probably uh... not even a long island media are
well
serious she told me you're talking about dixie much is so like that he told me my
fortune all over no yeah fortune how about I put four thumbs of your psychic
bitch yeah do my ex she was such a psychic you say psycho no no she always
knew what I was about to do yeah yeah it was psychic mm-hmm yeah it was crazy I
could never even come home late I would hate I would text her and I
I would hate to be in a bewitched situation.
Yeah.
I would hate to be bewitched.
That's what I just said.
No, no, you said in a bewitched situation.
I would hate for a witch to do something debilitating to me.
I would hate if a witch did a...
Wait, what's that movie with a fucking...
What's her name?
Mercy?
Is that the movie I'm thinking of?
Misery?
Misery.
Yeah.
I would hate for some girl to do that to me.
Seriously, though.
Yeah.
To hobble you?
I would hate for my stepmom to hobble me.
Your stepmom?
for sure and where did that come in
there any of the basis not his that
although that would be a little bit of a lot of it for your movie
it like up
she must be his step-mother
yet
as a rest of my life okay that's as okay
he didn't feel that is that not
he didn't
it's not a good idea
you know you would it was a come here
boom boom boom fall off the bed. What's that movie called? Mom's Story?
Mom's Horny Story?
Mom's Storny? Miss Horny?
Miss Horny? Is it called Horny? Is that what that movie's called? Yeah.
Hornsery?
Hornsery.
Hornsery. Jizz on me? What? What's it called?
Jizz on me.
Compilation of every time Kathy Bates said jizz on me in the movie Jizz on Me.
i just got movie i watched it just watch the player robert altman
yeah that's a good movie the player the player
i'd i'd prefer the sequel
what ready player one
that's the very cool very good what's going on in the sub well-written joke
yet the player that's about me when i'm
on my yet that's that's about it that's about what i do with my dad's about it's
about a t_v_ movie exec real hot shot tim reyner's rats when i go walks into his
office and he says fuck you bitch
give me your money and then they all fucking they're all selling movies
drinking martinis. Is that the one Tim Robinson wrote?
Tim Robbins.
Tim Robbins. Not Robinson.
You think Tim Robinson wrote a Robert Altman movie?
1992? That would be a good movie. That would be the best movie ever.
Yeah, Tim Robinson and Robert Altman working together, that'd be sick.
Yeah. That's pretty cool. And I think it'd look a little something like this.
We're all trying to find the guy who uh... What kind of trying to find the guy who...
We're all trying to find the player.
We're all trying to find the player who played this.
Yeah, that could be good.
That could be pretty good, yeah.
We're all trying to find Robert Altman.
I don't want to be the player anymore.
We're all trying to find the guy who directed this.
Anyway, you keep talking about the player.
We're all trying to find the guy who wrote the movie with Robert Altman.
It's my favorite kind of movie.
It's a self-referential Hollywood movie, right?
people are walking around and they're going Hollywood yeah yeah they're yeah
they're walking around there's a popcorn a candy bar and a soda and they're
walking around and they're all going to the movie they're all headed yeah they're
singing a nice little song about it's one of Robert Altman's greatest
achievement you think those freaks eat in the lobby those fuckers those fuckers
what are the crazy you know if they get are they getting popcorn their own kin
or what I think the candy eats the popcorn and the rock corner scissors
the soda. But then the soda eats the candy.
Yeah, no I think the candy eats the popcorn. Yeah, yeah. Candy eats the popcorn
because chocolate popcorn is pretty good. And the soda drinks the or eats the
popcorn. So they both eat the popcorn. What does the popcorn eat? You're bad at this.
Hold on, the popcorn. He's never played rock paper scissors. The popcorn drinks the soda because it's so salty.
The scissors cuts the rock
Because it's so
Figured it out. I mean
That I mean the truth that rock should just be both of them. Yeah, dude. Yeah fucking I can't I would lose to a rock. Yeah
If it was rocks paper scissors Caleb, I would lose honestly only one
I'm being real. I lose it two out of the three. There's no way that I could beat scissors the nor rock
I know lasers how oh swat him out of the way
Easy, that's not an animal of them. Okay, if scissors are those
Me if scissors were the same size as you yes, you would lose with scissors. This is an easy scenario
Yeah, I imagine if they were even smaller and the scissors are I mean scissors are already bigger than Caleb. Yeah, they're not
No, I'm not being the same size as scissors. That would be crazy
We may be so big so scary scissors and you get really scared about scissors were the same size as me
It would have to like they'd have to walk like peg-legged
They fly I could I could fucking put my foot out. Just you put your
All right. Here's a hypothetical for you. Uh-huh
Bruce Lee's mind in a giant pair of scissors his body, but it's still
Peg-legging you don't think Bruce Lee could figure out peg leg. Okay half right side
artistic side Bruce Lee's mind left side motor side
Black beard this guy's a peg leg expert. I could still do this. Yeah, couldn't do it
I would not win you would come up with your say you're the winner you kidding me part that it's peg-legging on is the dangerous
You guys don't even know that I have a gun in this scenario.
You don't have a gun.
That doesn't make any sense.
The paper doesn't have a gun and rock, paper, scissors.
You just have a gun.
No, you don't.
You can't fucking, you can't, that is, oh, okay.
You wouldn't, first of all, you wouldn't even have clothes in this.
Yeah, I have no clothes, but I have a gun.
No, you're literally, only you.
You don't even have hair.
Oh, what's this?
I have a machine gun arm already.
No, you don't.
Yes, I do.
Look at it.
That's not a machine gun.
[MACHINE GUN NOISE]
You're just making noises.
just pretending you're playing okay you have a phone are you acting like a
child I just unloaded five thousand rounds per second into Cameron's wall
and I'm not gonna pay to repair it there's nothing there you don't but you
have to do anything you do have to pay to repair it yeah and you have to split
the money evenly between me and him because I actually rented this wall I
just started and putting up is the most horrible post honestly honestly that's a
pretty good idea. This wall, how much a month to rent it? That's not my wall. That wall,
your wall. This wall, you can have that wall for free. Yeah, look at it. Look at that thing.
I don't want no. Look how horrible this wall is. Yeah, that wall sucks. I don't want a
free wall because then that means you'll say no to things. I want to have some skin in
the game. Fine, you can pay me $1000 a month. That's, no, I need an honest answer. You're
not taking me seriously. I said free and you said no. I'm like a serious investor. No,
because I don't want to have. I'm being serious too. I want to have leverage. I will never
do anything with this wall. This is your wall. But I want to be able to do anything I want
to it. Yeah, he just offered it for free. He's lying. Once this shit, you better, you're
going to regret the day unless I get this. Okay, then $1,000. You're talking too much.
Okay, then you can't rent it. How about this one right here? No, this is the only wall
you can rent. This is my wall in this apartment. Okay. Even for, okay, what if $1,000 for this
I don't know. A thousand bucks a month? Okay, rules. No animals. No blood. Okay. And that's
fucking it. Is this the only rule? Then no. And no food? You can have this wall for a
thousand dollars. Okay. If you want me to be serious, I'm being serious. That's pretty
good. I play hardball, dude. You see that right there? It's got a dip. It does have
a
walls in your room? Yes. How much to rent one? The one with no windows. One with no windows?
On the left side that has my oblivion poster? Either one. Honestly, you pay me $100 a month.
Really? You can put anything on my wall? You're a whore. Fuck slut. Look at you, slutish whore.
100 bucks. Slutish whore. But that does include a security deposit and first months. How much
is the security? $100. Okay. And you have to pay for Wi-Fi. Yeah. And electricity and gas.
No, no, he's not your manager. No, no, no. $200 in? Well, $300. $300, okay, but I get
it last. First month, second, first month, last month. First and second month. First
month, last month. And security. Okay, to move in on that wall. So $300. And I get it.
Then it's $100 for 14 months. Okay, what are your ground rules? What can I not put on the
wall. Look, if I don't know what's happening, dick can go up. What is that?
It's a fucking wall in your room. Look, I have to get into fights with my
mom that I live with as a wall lord. Okay, wall lord. There's gonna be a lot of
problems with your wall, okay? Yeah. And you're gonna tell me
about him, I'm not going to fix them, and then I'm going to scream at my mom about dinner.
You tell me you're going to start fucking punching holes in the wall when your mom takes
away your cigarettes?
You don't know.
It's not my wall.
There's other walls that I have to take care of.
You're subletting the wall to me?
No, I'm the wall lord.
First month, last month, and security.
What if I put, honestly, what if I go to a screen--
And I argue with my mom all the time.
You hear it and it's like inappropriate time of night.
I go to a really...
It's like 10.30, like you have work tomorrow.
Well, I'm not living on the wall.
No, I know.
I'm just saying that this is what goes on in my wall.
You can rent this wall for $50 a month.
Okay.
But...
Unless...
Cameron has to argue with my mom.
Well, that's a given.
My Polish mom.
Unless you rent a path to the wall through my apartment on the floor for $50 per foot,
you can't come to the wall.
You don't have free...
You can come in once a month for 10 minutes unless you rent a path along the floor.
Oh, that's fine.
That's fine.
I don't want to see the wall.
I'm going to go to a print shop, get a giant, like perfect vinyl, like exact dimensions that
covers this, basically a wallpaper of just like a big piece of dookie, like zoomed in
with corn in it and even red peppers, you know?
Yeah.
And just blow it up as much as possible, highest possible picture quality.
Getty Images, I'll put that-
After that first day, I don't think that would bother me anymore.
I have to be completely honest.
It's mostly for these people.
Yeah, that's true.
To walk by and think that you-
Yeah, my girlfriend's work meetings too.
That would be pretty good.
Right opposite.
Yeah.
They're like, "What's up with the wall behind you?"
We're renting it out.
Yeah, sorry.
Yeah, it's not ours.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's just our crazy tenant. It's a photo of him.
I can't evict him because he keeps calling a lawyer.
Yeah.
And I would call a lawyer. I would get a serious... you'd be breaking my contract if you...
Dude, I want to be a wall lord so bad now.
It's a good idea. It's funny that I never think about how funny the term lord is until you
remove it from landlord and put it into something else. I mean, that's like objectively pretty cool
to be a lord.
To be a landlord?
I'd be a landlord in two seconds.
It's the coolest job.
It literally is, dude.
It is.
How is it not the cool you do you get to argue with your Polish mom?
You get to like smoke cigarettes inside cuz who's gonna tell you it's your bill
Yeah, you can do whatever you want
You can like if someone's like dishwasher breaks and it's leaking water from their apartment into the apartment below
You don't got to fix that shit. You can just call someone else this is two months
You are being so scathing right now, and I'd like to let you know this past three years
I've actually been an undercover agent for Bill Maher and we want to have you on the show really. Yeah, it's true
No way. No, I want to have you on the show. No, I want you to do this
No, I'm that that tip it over the line. Mm-hmm
I want to do a lot like I can't I can't join I can't join Bill Maher now
I want you to come to know I can't join the show
You know why why because I'm also I'm a my DSA chapter will not allow me to
I've actually been renting one of the walls on the Bill Maher set really
Yeah, they tricked me. It's not it's never on camera senator. I'm a landlord
That's pretty good
That was a crazy shit dude. It's crazy. He just said that
It wouldn't even like no Martin. You do whatever the fuck. Yeah, that's right. Yeah, he earned a lifetime pass. Yeah, come on
Yeah, he just slithers around like you remember that like say Bill Maher others man. What that's fucking anti-semitic
that's so anti-semitic. He literally is. He's not Jewish. Look it up right now. No, Bill Maher is
Christian. No, his ethnic background is Jewish. Bill Maher is not Jewish. You want to put $100 on it?
Hold on. Put $100 on it. Hold on, it says Bill Mafe.
No, that's Jawish. Bill Maher, Jawa.
Is Bill Maif Jawish?
We did some research on this question.
Alright, I guess, yeah.
He's Jewish.
No, he's half Jewish.
Oh, are you really doing this to me?
He was raised, until his early teens, he was unaware that his mother, whose family is from Hungary, was Jewish.
He's still Jewish.
So he didn't know he was Jewish.
If your mother's Jewish, you're Jewish.
you
my view you know yeah fucker well he wasn't Jewish trust me I know exactly
wasn't he wasn't Jewish until he unlocked it later oh he reached a level
Uh-huh. He leveled up in his teens and then unlocked Judaism.
That'd be cool.
And then he fucking hit first prestige and got rid of all that shit.
He did, yeah. Prestige once, level 50, hitting Judaism, level 50, going back to 1, Christianity.
No, no, atheism. He don't even have a religion.
True. So true.
Yeah, dude, and he's staying at level 1 because he's better at it.
But he's got the banner still.
Yeah.
You know, Danisky used to be so high level.
I
- Can it be like a live stream though,
like with a desk?
Can we please have a desk?
- Yeah.
- Yo, if we get office space,
we're gonna do a political talk show live stream out.
- Of course, dude.
- Oh, I can't wait to rent out the walls in that office.
- Oh my God.
- Oh, that's actually a good idea.
- We should rent them out to the fans.
- That's a great idea, like 10 bucks a month.
- 10 bucks a month, you could put,
if we get an office. - You could put any poster
in our office.
That's actually such a good idea.
- Maybe that's the $20,000 Patreon goal.
get in an office. We take more money. We get in an office and then you can put...
$20,000, I'm putting my foot down. $20,000 Patreon goal is we're making a feature
film. Non-negotiable. We're making a feature film. Feature length
film. If we make $20,000. What's major motion picture? 115 or 130? I feel like it's
130. It's gotta be 130. Well, 115, I feel like it would be
technically feature length but it would be a cop out. By feature length film we mean
fan film and by fan film... No, we mean film and by feature length we mean at least three
hours long and also probably I mean I know it's like a fantasy epic yeah yeah
yeah like basically like 300 400 million budget yeah yeah big stars yeah but you
have to pay for it no we pay no no we play why are you trying to they need to
be excited for this patreon goal yeah what you want to fucking go to 20,000
and be like oh yeah can we have another fucking 200 no we're gonna make a
feature-length film that's gonna open in 3,000 movie theaters across the country
And in China. Yes, even more in China. It's gonna be six
And it's called adventures of China
Honestly since China like always wants like cool like American movies that are think China is awesome
I'll make like just a whole movie. I would rule China's just release it there, right?
Yeah, we could just do that right we get a nice window in it. We get in contact with
Jackson we say hey we do we're like we're really
the famous comedians, or actually screenwriters, and actors and directors.
All three of us were outdoors.
We're very famous multi-hyphenates.
Yeah. And we would like to make a movie about how basketball was invented in China
by the Chinese. We would like to come and make that movie. And we would like for that to be
a lasting generational movie.
Yeah, we're going to make a series too.
A whole series.
It's going to be a series.
Like seven or eight movies.
And we want a Starbury hookup.
Yep.
Yeah, we want a Starbury hookup.
Absolutely.
Sponsored by Starbury.
That's what it was called, right?
Yeah.
Starbury hookup.
I want to wear nothing but Starburys.
They're sick, dude.
I used to have a pair.
Didn't they make like a...
Fuck, I think it's Starbury made like a shoe with speakers in it.
I don't remember.
That shit used to be cool, man.
They used to put so much shit in sneakers.
Yeah, I think they made like the bubble
They should I they should do adult light up sneakers, yes, that's what it was they put spinners in a shoe
Did you guys ever have Healy's? No, no, I wasn't allowed. I wanted them. But yeah, there's no way
It's whatever gotten them for me or these I thought they were so cool
Yeah, my little brother had Healy's growing up and I just fucking trip him all the time. Yeah, they're pretty dumb
they're not they're definitely they're
They're cool, and you're like I feel like it's a good thing to be like in fifth grade
You see a sixth grader cruising down the hallway. You're like my god my mom
My mom didn't let me get Heelys cuz she heard that a kid was on Heelys and was gay and rode into a plane
propeller I
Think she made that up. I think she made that up to scare me out of everyone
go that fast on Heelys. That kid had a lot of, he was like, oh look.
She said that he tripped and fell into a plane propeller.
What the fuck?
Indiana Jones style. There's a lot of shit that I think my mom just lied to me about so that I wouldn't want it.
That's what happened to Indiana Jones.
Yeah.
That's how he died.
So they haven't made a movie in a while since Crystal Skull.
I feel like they probably fall over a lot on Heelys, right?
Because it's just like, it's well, it's like on your heel.
So if you ever put your heel down, it just rolls out, right?
I mean, it's like a high heel in a way.
You're walking around on your tippy toes.
Yeah.
I don't know, I've never worn
Heelys with the soaps though.
There was a security guard at the mall
in my hometown who rode around on Heelys.
Whoa.
I saw there was a movie about a security guard
who rode around on a Segway.
Yeah, I remember that one.
He might have been doing a little
budget imitation of them.
Yeah.
I might become a mall security guard.
For me that's more of an honor than like defending like Fort Knox.
Yeah, absolutely.
You know, defending a game stub.
The greatest stuff in the world is in a mall.
Defending an Orange Julius.
China Walk.
Yeah.
Master Walk.
I would want to be stationed just to one of those like touch screen directories to make
sure people aren't like fidgeting with it or anything.
Oh dude, I'd love to watch, I'd love to be the mall security camera guy.
Yup.
Oh my god.
looking in a Claire's I bet you would know you would know he's literally
blushing there's big hearts coming out of like an Animal Crossing character yeah
this I always why do I put my foot in my mouth so much I don't know it's crazy
it's impressive you know what it is is you guys are able to twist everything I
say into some weird fucking shit yeah you twist your penis into a pretzel at
at the mall that you want to be a security guard at.
Okay, I was trying to give you a layup there.
I was trying to help you out.
Yes.
Yeah.
Owned.
I guess I've been owned.
Yeah, you have.
I guess so. I guess I have.
Don't freeze up on me now.
I would be the security guard of the food court, but I would be like a lord.
I'd be like a vassal.
They'd have to give me tribute, like every restaurant in the food court,
or I wouldn't defend them.
Like they'd have to pay me up.
Like if I didn't get Auntie Anne's, I'm not.
I'd have one of those nightsticks.
You'd be letting kids run out.
It's not mom protection.
Pretty much, yeah.
You're walking around.
Okay, but more medieval is how I would play.
I'd walk around with those nightsticks that swing out.
I'd fuck you.
Yeah, sick.
I'd probably batter at you.
Any college kid acts up, any college kid gets drunk and acts up, I'm smacking them in the
head.
That's right.
I'd get plastic surgery to look exactly like the heavy from Team Fortress 2.
I'd walk around yeah just smacking the just smacking the cashier yeah around so
I can get synth all injections to look exactly like the heavy yeah I literally
just want the samples just doing the voice yeah yeah so I get it put this
dispenser here just like
Planning the mall do you have to have you planning?
Like the heavy and then the engineer that he's just got like the like the toolbox
and he just keeps building, building, dipping the hot machines in the mall.
And then a sniper.
Yeah.
Yeah, but you know what the sniper's doing with that jarate?
Oh, hell no.
Oh, is that what he calls his boomerang?
No, that's his pee bottle.
Yeah.
Somebody didn't taste test the items in TF2.
I didn't, I'm sorry.
Oh, I remember the sandwich, alright.
Now that was funny.
YouTube video in the eighth grade, seventh or eighth grade,
of like how to make Bonk Cola.
And it was a kid like putting like--
- Oh, I've seen that.
- Yeah, dude, it was like a kid putting like
five hour energy in a Red Bull with like
juicy drop pop liquid and like pop rocks and shit.
- And that shit'll toot you up.
- Dude. - Holy.
- That, I, like drinking that would just,
that drinking that would kill a child.
- How to make the dot from Pac-Man.
How to make the dirt from Dig Dug.
Yeah, that is a funny, yeah, how to make like this food or something.
But also, I get it, because when you were a kid, like you fucking, all I wanted to do...
Oh yeah, did the Fallout 3 cookbook?
I wanted to eat the slime from the fucking Cat in the Hat movie so bad.
Oh yeah, dude, the purple slime.
Have you seen the Resident Evil 2 remake burger?
Do you want to see the worst food item in a game?
Yeah.
Here.
uh... yet you'd like the
but my friend of a friend who was telling me that there's a good overwatch cookbook
that's good and how the fuck do you do that yeah
the overwatch cookbook and then what the fuck
that's the burger in the resident evil two honestly that looks so good that
it's covered in cheese it's like a wet like a little bit of a little bit of a
alcoholic when it's due all that looks so good did
that's not like an old burger in the game that's not honestly that looks like most
burgers you get it five guys yet it i'm not a guy i mean i would buy this looks
like it looks like fungus the yeah
yet as we're going to look like she had to show
to i'm not eating me right now good
you know you have a month no meanest i do i do like uh... a day where i don't
need me yeah i do like a pretty much like
i'd say about four hours a day where i don't need me in between my meals and
is something I've been doing.
- I've been making a lot of like tofu stuff.
- That's why you've been acting so girly.
- Yeah.
- That's why you've been wearing that beautiful dress
and putting on that sweet lipstick and blood kisses.
- I made an orange chicken tofu.
- He keeps ruining the mirror in my bathroom
with his beautiful lips.
- Yeah.
- I've been drawing, signing it.
- I've been kissing the bathroom mirror, yeah.
- So annoying, dude.
I get it, you want me to fall in love with you, stop.
- And I miss having like a high-powered blender
and making like seitan and like having it,
like putting the seitan on my counter to like knead it out
and it looks like shit.
- It does look exactly like dookie.
- Dude, it looks so gross.
- Yeah, I feel ya.
- Seitan is like, I mean, it's like okay.
It's like a good like, yeah, it's like,
oh, meat substitutes, like, but it's all,
first of all, it's bread.
- Yeah.
- Second of all, it looks like dookie.
- It'll make you fart.
- Dude, yeah.
Oh my, it's all wheat protein.
- Yep.
- I made seitan ribs once.
I fucking, like, you have your head like one of the,
like a fart that like is so hot when it comes out it feels like you laid an egg
yeah I know a fart that has a head yeah yeah yeah it feels like you're giving
birth to a slimy it's not like it's not like a shark like no no it's literally
just the heat yeah mimicked like moisture yeah and it felt hot and and
wet but then it wasn't anything yeah yeah that's every seitan part I've ever had I
I didn't know that my body could produce such heat.
That should be killing me.
It should be burning a hole through every...
It felt like I had an ulcer.
I should have checked my pants for blood.
Yeah, definitely.
It's just pure, just fucking...
Yeah, Satan ribs destroyed my gullet.
Yeah.
It's also one of those ones where the fart doesn't shoot out like a...
it like wraps around your ass like an asteroid just hit Earth.
You can feel it.
And the shockwaves.
A part you can feel come all the way out of your shorts.
Yeah.
You feel it just ripple down your skin.
Like, have you ever seen, have you ever played like the first Battlefront 2015 and it's like
on Sullust there's like the gas bubbles?
No.
Like the volcanic gas bubbles?
No, damn well, neither of us.
God damn it, somebody's listening, dude.
Did you go to my middle school and meet Mrs. Tumen?
Mrs. Tumen? Yeah. She was two men at the same time.
She was the fucking, the guy from... She's dead, dude. She died, dude.
She died having sex with two men at the same time. Come on.
The Phantom Menace announcers that were played by the Sklar brothers.
That's Mrs. Tumen.
No, she was a very sweet lady. I think she's alive.
- Yeah, and she died.
- She didn't die. - She died peacefully
in her sleep.
- She died when she met me. - No.
No, not true.
- She died when she saw me.
- Yeah. - 'Cause of how ugly you are.
- Yup. - No, you know what?
All right, here's a better example.
A fart like that looks like the bubble
in a witch's cauldron.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, absolutely.
- It's like if you put dry ice at the bottom of liquid,
and you can see the smoke come out.
- The smoke come out of the bubble.
Yeah, that's what it feels like.
It feels like you're protruding,
you're smoking smoke when you when you when you when you when you like buy one
of those like instead of using soapy water you buy like a bubble mixture like
what and and you pop it and you can feel like slime on your hand that type of
bubble yeah yeah feels like it feels like a boba tea bubble just shot out of
your ass I don't think that's pure yeah it's like a bird flew out of a cannon
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's kind of like if a bouncy ball went over a jump rope. Yeah
It's like a bunch of candy coming out of a pinata pretty much. Yeah. Yeah, it's like a chili dog in reverse
Yeah, it's like when you see a cat lapping up milk. Mm-hmm. Yeah. Oh, it does sound like that though. Yeah
Yeah, almost exactly. Yeah, you know like the the farts that come out like
And they smell like horrible, yeah, I had a fart the other day that Jana I farted in the
I'm going to end on this. I farted in the car and we were on a road trip and Janice smelled
it and said, she was like, "Oh, did we just pass a Chick-fil-A?" I was like, "No, that's
my ass."
All right.
All right. Bye.
Bye.
Alright, bye.