Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
- Premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- I don't wanna blow my voice out.
- Okay, I just started recording,
so they actually heard him ranting.
Everyone heard him ranting and being rude to me just now.
- Nobody heard me ranting and raving.
- You see the physical assault
that Cameron deals with every day in this office.
- Yeah, it's a physical sonic assault.
- It's not physical, it's soul.
- It's physical, the sound waves,
but they vibrate my body and give me bruises. You're a loud voice.
It's a
wow. We are seriously on our Alvin and the chipmunk show. That was so
beautiful. We can make really good three chipmunks. Alex and the chipmunks?
That's a different show. What are you talking about? It's not Alex and the
chipmunks.
No, he goes,
oh, okay.
No, no, you guys are completely wrong.
He goes, "Alvis!"
Elvis?
Yeah, 'cause they sing, it's Elvis and the Chipmunks.
Oh, it's like the movie that just came out.
He goes, "Elvis!"
There's a new Elvis and the Chipmunks movie?
Yeah.
Really?
They meet Frankenstein.
Who's that?
Jewish guy.
Mmm.
Elvis Frankenstein?
Yeah, Elvis Frankenstein.
He's, he teaches them, it's a Hanukkah special.
Nice.
For Alvin and the Chipmunks.
Which is okay these days.
Yeah, it's a good thing to have.
Yeah.
I said that like it was
It's actually I think it's good I think it's good I think it's good
I think they should do a breaking bad
Special Jerry Seinfeld speaking of holiday specials Jerry Seinfeld had a book about Halloween
For real this I think what what is I had it as a kid
It's just an it's like an illustrated children's book that all the audio is a stand-up
bit about Halloween. There's an audio of a book. What it's it's comes with a cd
and you can listen to it along. I just don't believe you. I just don't believe
at all. I choose to not believe in anything. I know I know you're correct,
but the but
just saying all the audio in the book. I don't know that you're correct. I think
that you're lying to me every time he says something like that. He's right is
the thing. Nope, he's just lying. I believe he's right. I do. I believe in
him because the I'm going over of this we've is crazy we've recently
he's ignoring it I'm showing him the pundit he's literally his phones off he's
just showing you so can you show proof of the CD yeah or did you recently
discover that Patrick is right about almost everything he ever talks about
but instead of kind of giving him more more benefit of the doubt in situations
where he says something crazy I'm gonna go the complete opposite way I'm not
I'm not going to believe a single word. He said yeah ever
this was on the CD. This is an ad before the CD starts wow.
It's literally called Sun felt Halloween. Yeah, so there's no
proof. This is a CD. It's a YouTube video
can
get candy, get candy, get candy, get candy, get candy,
So food Seinfeld has always been a thing. Holy shit I didn't realize that
Seinfeld invented our whole wave. Yeah this is a whole book about him getting
candy. Yeah. The fuck? You know what's also crazy about Jerry
Seinfeld is he's one of those guys where Superman is his favorite superhero.
That's not right. That is a sign of a freaking narcissist. What are you talking
What is it? How's that crazy? The most popular superhero ever. That's crazy to be to have Superman be your favorite superhero.
That is yeah, it's weird. What?
Yeah, it's like everyone likes Superman. Everyone likes Superman sure, but like for Superman to be your like number one guy.
So it would be okay for Superman to be your number one guy if you lived in like the 50s.
Yeah, what kind of people? He did live in the 50s. If you lived in the 50s. He lived in the 50s!
Yeah, but now. I think he was born in the 50s. Now it's the 20s.
Yeah, you can't be doing that anymore. Why it's weird to have Superman be your favorite superhero because it's like
It's the same as picking Mario and freaking smash. It's like having your favorite meal be breakfast lunch or dinner
Yeah, instead of the in-between ones the snacks. Mm-hmm the brunch liner
Midnight night second breakfast breakfast. We took us a dinner to breakfast. So yeah, that's midnight snack
That's midnight. That's midnight snack or first break winner
breakfast. My mom my mom just a dinner to breakfast, so my mom used to take me out
for first breakfast at midnight because brick because Brenner would be lunch
because that's right between breakfast and yeah right, so you it has to be
deck fist yeah, it's deckfist didn't but it's commonly known as a fist yeah,
fist yeah, dink fist midnight meal third fourth meal third meal fourth meal is
Taco Bell. No, you're thinking of second meal. No, fourth meal. No, Taco Bell does
second meal. You're not right. It's between breakfast and dinner. I know you're not
right about this. Oh, I'm Patrick and I'm right about everything these days. They
actually had a CD at Taco Bell. They did. The audio of my taco was crazy. You get a CD of
that guy singing and he's, "Four times a steak, four times a thick juicy succulent
steak, you all say wow it's like a whole turkey crumb." I bet growing up he knew the lyrics to every
commercial. Yeah I did. Definitely. I was shopping for a new car which one's me? A cool convertible
or an SUV? Too bad I didn't know my credit was whack now I'm driving on the lot in a
used subcompact F R E E that spells free credit report dot com baby saw their ads on my TV
thought about going but was too lazy now instead of looking fly and rolling fat my lights are
shaking to the vinyl and my boss is getting laughed at F R E E that spells free credit
report dot com baby it's a hip-hop commercial seminal hip-hop commercial
yep how does that free credit report website how the fuck they pay for those
commercials everything fucking free that's it we're really a thinker hmm
general that's gotta be the worst animation I've ever seen yeah seriously
looks like complete shit what's our do it head-on what the hell was that even
four Sham Wow that's gotta be a hooker he bit a hooker and the chip slap chop he's
talking about slapping nuts yeah yeah my nuts the fuck is going on with that he
made like this movie so before he was the Sham Wow guy he made this movie called
like the underground comedy movie and it's not good it's very bad comedians of
comedy no no it's like sketches and then he after that he was making a sequel to
it but then decided to make it all about apps and then the movie is called in
appropriate comedy inappropriate comedy yeah I think directed and wrote that I
think whoa uh-huh it's very if you watch it's pretty appropriate yeah yeah it's
really not all that I think it was inappropriate at the time maybe yeah
things have changed. Oh wait I think he does blackface in the underground comedy movie.
That doesn't surprise me. Well you don't, it doesn't surprise you that the Slap Shop guy
did blackface? Not at all. He also bit a hooker. I don't think he's a good guy.
What? I think he's probably a bad guy. But he gave all these great products. I think anybody who
tries to get, who becomes a job as like a seller, which I think is what they're called. If anybody
Anybody who like who gets who has a like a really small thing or small role and
get really gets really famous thing and gets really famous like gets like viral
or famous from it and embraces it really hard is a horrible person except for bad
baby yeah she's cool but every other person every other bad baby type person
is evil. I think Slash was in the underground comedy movie yeah Slash Chop
Yeah, and the the the DVD cover is a two women taking a shit
Holy fuck
Damn, I should call it the under ass
I wish I was underground under the toilets that those women are shitting into so their poop would go into my mouth
Yeah, that's pretty cool. Yeah, would you eat Pamela Anderson's poop? I don't think I'd ever eat any poop
What about okay everything everything has to have like a there's a qualifier. So every yeah, there's no it's not
- Yeah, there is definitely a situation.
- Only a Sith deals in absolutes, my friend.
- That's right.
There is only, there is situations where you would eat
an entire log of poop.
- I don't think there is a situation where I would eat--
- What if a woman--
- There he is, a black face and hair curlers.
- What if a woman ate so much--
- That's woman head, too.
- What if a woman ate so much delicious birria--
- Okay, fine, it tastes like,
if the poop is a whole log of candy--
No, no, no, it tastes like complete shit.
It's the reason why you're doing it though.
The reason why I'm eating it.
It's like your entire family is bundled up, completely bundled up.
I have to take a bite of poop.
And they're being dropped into an alligator, a giant alligator, the hugest alligator ever.
I have to eat the alligator's poop.
And the alligator's saying, I guess he's saying telepathically he's communicating to you.
So maybe you're just thinking this.
But it's like I have to...
Maybe you're hallucinating the whole thing.
Yeah, yeah.
You have to eat poop.
have to eat my yeah and then yeah okay so your son gets pushed into the lion
enclosure at the zoo but you and you're thinking one of the one of the lions is
telepathically telling you that you have to eat shit or he's not gonna right okay
so you're schizophrenic and you eat poop against your own will yeah would you I
think I would have to okay so if you yeah if you if you if you were forced to
eat poop and there's no way to get out of it
poop would you do it if I was forced to physically yeah if you're forced to
physically or mentally physically restrained if my face was not a rubber
if you're being restrained if you are being restrained from eating poop would
you escape and do it no what if you were born and your head looked exactly like a
like a flesh toilet and you were just like oh I gotta try this one time like
everybody's saying I look like a toilet also would you go for pee or poop first
I'd probably go for pee first. Oh my god. He wants to drink pee. Yeah, what's wrong?
Oh, there's no that's not like uh
That's not like a ramping up thing. Those are just two different. Those are just two different gross things
I want to drink
You'd you'd rat you want to rather eat
Than just poop would you rather drink really clear pee or really yellow pee yellow? He's dehydrated
Okay, would you rather drink a gallon of crystal clear pee or do a cup of?
really yellow stinky pee
asparagus pea. You would choose the stinky? I would drink the... A guy, he's a
trucker, a fat sweaty trucker, it's a vegan trucker and all he eats is asparagus and
and radishes. And farts and beets. And beets, yeah. And farts, he eats farts too.
And he also sucks down fart stuff. Yeah. And he... Yeah, I would drink that
actually. And his butt is... And his butt also pees. And his butt has a
a pea gland. He has an issue with his body where his butt is really hot so it like
cooks it like boils and cooks whatever comes out of it. Yeah. I think poop's
already fully cooked. No but it's way more. It's bubbling.
There's so many vegan food like meat replacements that look
like poop. Yeah it all looks like poop. I think that if you cooked poop it would
look exactly like that. Yeah. Like a seitan steak. Some nice grill marks on a log.
yeah like a seitan steak I think I've never had a poop log it's always just the
fuck just the most insane tic-tac orange juice yeah you're something wrong with
you we know that we've established that like a long time ago like what is a
you've always had something really wrong with you in the toilet and be like that
was a seriously like are you proud of it no no I'm never proud of what I do in
I'd be so happy I think if I looked into the toilet I saw just a log.
If I pooped like a football maybe.
Yeah.
If I pooped a poop that was the size of a football.
My shit looks like a fractal.
The thing is I still wouldn't be proud, I would be worried.
Not necessarily about my body but about the toilet too.
You could probably do like tea leaf reading with my shit.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think so.
I guess what happened to me.
According to this pattern it smells horrible.
the room will soon smell bad.
Yeah, I found out I found out a huge
thing today yeah, which is that if you don't have a license plate on your car,
because of my life, I got stolen by an TFA. I don't know if I talked about that
on yeah, the show you did, but
if you have a license, if you don't have a place on your car, they can't give you
a parking ticket.
So I've just been doing a legal. I've been parking in front of fucking fire
I've been not paying for parking.
Nice.
And they just don't even, they can't even tow it because they can't put it in the system.
That's sick.
It's fucking incredible.
Well, you have the piece of paper in the back, right?
Yeah, I have a piece of paper, but it just has a license plate number on it, so they
could just, they won't give me a ticket.
Yeah, it could just be a random number.
It could be the person in front of me, I just wrote it on there.
Yeah.
You know?
And then I'd never have to pay the ticket.
So it's like, honestly, it's so fucking genius.
That is crazy that you got your license plate stolen.
so I mean it's it's been such a blessing dude yeah yeah probably one of those
probably one of those at um quirky s restaurants stole it it's definitely
hanging up at a Twin Peaks yeah don't worry in Virginia it's made it's it's
the final piece for the big metal license plate bra they had yeah yeah
it's in some I was talking to I was talking about breasts around see other
day misleading name yeah there's a lot of restaurants yeah like restaurant well
yeah remember we saw yeah I do remember we saw hoots isn't that so fucking crazy
they don't even have waiters at hoots they've like no wonder like you just
ordered well yeah cuz if they did waiters that's true of course I can't do
waiters yeah there's no reason yeah they that is that's funny that they are there
if they really just can't have waders there yeah cuz everybody's gonna be oh
well these wait what's up do you waiters nobody also that yeah they'd have to
wear like well I understand is why I can wear the full why not just call it
something completely different yeah should have called it wings yeah with a
why it's way better wings that is good you remember that you remember that
dispute in like 2011 2000 something or when I was in middle school do you
remember they legally had to call boneless wings wings with a Y because
wings have to have the bone in them no who's they and what do you mean they
legally big three the big three Pierce Paul Pierce Kevin Garnett and Ray Allen
yeah they legally made it so you have to call boneless wings boneless w-i-n-g-z
Why does this do the Y and the yes? Why can't be it can't be called the wing?
I remember there was some there's some I've a similar type of thing I remember
seeing a really good memory of seeing an imitation crab meat thing called CROB.
C-R-O-B. It's already had called imitation. Yeah I know. It's so funny dude.
It's the same thing as like the like the chicken, you know where it has an apostrophe instead of the e in my in my hometown
There's a place called P T's
Which is really it's like burgers and fries place and they have lemonade and on their menu is the only thing the entire menu is
like this it says
in quotations fresh and in quotations lemonade and
They may it's just made they make the lemonade in front of you
It's just lemons and fucking water quotes at quotation marks and like around something on a sign is one of the ultimate
- Scary. - Gen X humors.
- Yeah, it really is. - I think it gets them
every time. - Every single time.
- They can't get over it. - It's funny.
- It is funny, but they could see a million of them
in it every time.
- Do you guys remember they used to do--
- Using, so legally they can't be called wings
if they're actually not, if they are actually,
or they can be called wings if they're made from wing meat,
but they're not made from wing meat.
They have to be called wings.
No other misspellings are allowed.
The product label must be submitted for approval.
White meat must be used.
The wings asterisk term must be prominent.
An asterisk must link to a statement
that indicates the product is not made
entirely from wing meat.
- Say asterisk again. - That's a crazy,
I mean, I feel like, yeah, it's fine
that you can't call them normal wings or whatever,
but to say you have to call them W-Y-N-G-Z,
you can't, no other spelling, is crazy.
chicken tender it's a chicken tender
you exactly discuss boneless wings I've been trying to remember what a boneless
wing looks like and I just can't remember
a chicken tender it's a chicken right it's not it's pretty long right yeah
yeah well it's short it's shorter than a
so it's a wing it's a well it's a wings it's a wings
well if it's if it's used if it doesn't you just use entirely
wing meat you can't call I'm gonna use you entirely I'm gonna use your wings
I'm gonna I would I'm gonna use your wings to get my satisfaction I will use
every part of you like a Native American.
- Nope.
- I really will.
- You won't.
- I'm going to.
- There's parts of me that aren't even here anymore.
- That's, I'm gonna hunt them down.
- I'm gonna hunt them down.
I'm doing a treasure.
- You're not gonna find my parts.
- I'm doing a treasure trek.
- You're not gonna find any of my parts.
- I'm gonna find every last one of them.
I'm gonna find your baby teeth
and those are gonna go up my butt.
- When I was in like third grade,
I lost, I had like a full metal tooth
in the back of my mouth, like a silver.
- Naturally?
- Yeah, grew in.
Whoa, but it was cut was a metal crown covering a baby tooth and one day it
fell out and then I lost the crown and I was so upset about that.
Isn't it? I see what I call it a crown because it fell off. Okay, you know,
you know, you know, well, you know who gets crowns in real life to always the
most rotten people
they get, they get crowns, but yeah, and there and it's and and you know the
another thing about these people who get crowns what you know they're
standing there standing all next to each other down in a line. They're all
they're all look the same. They're white yep white rotten people. Yeah crowns
white with little happening. What just flew out of your mouth phlegm and you
know what we'll say it white with with wh yt black holes in the middle of
their bodies. Yeah, where the soul should be yeah, but the soul of the
tooth yep, that's right. Yeah, I got a soul of the foot. I think about the
entire world that the sole of the foot on my tooth.
You want to put a foot in your mouth? No,
I think I could. I think it would take me a year of conditioning and I could
start getting boners from feet.
Yeah, I feel like there's there, but there's probably one there's got to
be. There's got to be like a gateway foot like an entry level foot where
it's like okay, even a guy who's not even a guy who's not. I'm going to
look that up what's the hottest the best foot sexiest foot who's like the hot
like kate upton of feet exactly because yeah anyone can appreciate best there has
to be one sexy okay i'll also when you look that up megan markle apparently has
the world's most beautiful feet while emma watson's are near perfect according
to golden ratio okay here are the top ones 10 sexist celebrity feet bizarre
our website ranks top ten sexiest a good has a ninety five find out on which I
accept should I accept all except all except everything you need to accept all
of those okay. Let's see okay. So it's not a great start. It's going to be
okay. So it's just talking about wiki feet. I was like Emma was this are you
looking at the Sun the article on the Sun not looking at the episode though
that they have the rating next to the website planet radio dot co dot UK.
I'm gonna try to get a boner from one not too many pictures no pictures no
pictures oh come on how a mall cloning this without makeup is tough to handle
look up look up Emma Watson feet new Subaru's final early on sale all right
I'm looking at well that's giving me a boner I'm looking up Emma Watson feet
right now I have to I mean we're doing this for the show now yeah Emma Watson
okay this picture is clearly not real this is on deviantART okay a little man
- Yeah, there's a little man eating,
like looking like a bug.
- Okay, well here we go.
EmmaWatsonFeet.com is the top result
when I Google Emma Watson Feet.
So I'm just gonna go to this website.
I think they'll probably know what's up.
Wow, they have a logo and everything.
This is a very professional website.
- Wait, what?
(laughing)
- Whoa, EmmaWatsonFeet.com.
- Yeah.
- It's like a Squarespace.
- What do they have with logo?
- Wait.
- They have a contact page.
- Contact us.
- We have to get it to you.
- In case of question,
don't hesitate and contact us via this email.
support at I want to ask if they wanted you an interview I do want to collab
with them but go to about I want to see the about page our mission our mission
is to collect the beautiful pictures of Emma Watson's feet we collect them from
all over the internet and do not do now own the rights on them if you are the
owner feel free to contact all the rights on them we are nonprofit
organization dedicated to promotion of the beauty of female feet is you think
actually an NGO. They have a privacy policy. Okay they have a terms of use too. Wow they
have a whole legalese terms of use. Wow. Wow but let's look at the gallery. Yeah
that's what we're really here for. Emma Watson's feet became very famous among the
foot lovers. We selected the best pictures of her feet for this collection.
We added not only barefoot photos but also high heels, toes, soles, and anklets.
This isn't doing anything for me. Yeah this is the best that feet have to offer.
I think that yeah these are kind of nasty to me.
Well all feet are nasty.
Yeah.
I have to sit down.
You know I don't know.
I don't...
Feet videos by FeetWonder.com.
FeetWonder.com.
These are better.
These are better feet.
So okay I can tell when a foot is better.
But you can... this is the number one foot.
You're saying the opposite.
No that one...
I disagree.
I mean it's not an objective.
is is Meghan Markle. I heard look at me and Markle feet. I hope I'm hope there's
a website.
You just search Meghan Markle look up feet. Oh, yeah,
stupid. I'm feeling out of it today. All right. Well, there's a wiki feet.
There's not a website dedicated to it, but she it was ratings three stars.
Okay feet. What are you talking about? You're a liar. There's a Sun article
that says she had 90. Let's see who feet of the year is feet of the year 2021
contest results finals or Neal a caper and Anna de Armas. I don't know who
Neal a caper as an look at let's see Anna de Armas. Well, you like a for one.
Oh, she did yeah. That's a hand. This is you. That's a hand. Most of these are
hands. Wait. Why is there so many pictures of this woman's feet? Who is
she? That's the other thing. It's got to be like there's got to be some just
vlogger or something. There's yeah, yeah, probably somebody's screenshots
somebody's not even five stars gorgeous feet, shoe size nine us birthplace turkey.
This bitch is made out of you can you can get notified for new pictures. Yeah,
let's get notified. Okay, let's look at an adarmus here.
The length of time that this website takes to load makes me worried about
what's happening to my computer. No, it's just how many people are accessing this
at the same time as you all right. This is the one we want to look at this one.
No, see the feet are barely in this one. You're not committed to the feet lifestyle.
Yeah, you're right.
Let's check out this one. What do you think about these feet?
Those are definitely, see that's what I mean, those are definitely better than Emma Watson.
Yeah, but those toes look kind of dead. She might have gangrene on this foot.
She does have three fucked up toes.
Yeah.
So, but okay, so now I guess the appeal is like you look at it with your friends and like
talk about it like it's like the like top five in the barbershop.
come on when you're at the barber shop, you got all those comments.
She is a beautiful woman, no doubt, but the overall shape of her feet and the
Morton's toe drops her score by a couple stars in the Harley score. She
definitely isn't in the same foot category. This literally is the the top
five. She definitely isn't the same foot category as Emma Stone, Selena Gomez,
Taylor, shifter, Sandra Bullock, the overall foot and toe shape of anada
arm is out of proportion by my standards. I know I do have a tendency
score a little on the harsher reserved side, but I know what I think is
beautiful and if I give a beautiful rating, they deserve it to me, though,
and okay rating is an average attractive guy. I'd be happy to massage any time
this guy's a Simon Simon Cowell. This guy's a complete Simon. He's he is
tough, but he's fair yeah right like he's not bullshit. He's not saying
everybody's a five. I like it's it's so interesting just like what turns you
These people have oh my God, this is this. We need to destroy these people.
Why I also prefer a longer second toe. I think it looks better and give that
feminine touch agree. She is beautiful, but here we rate feet. She has hammer
toes that would never allow her to enter my beautiful rating. I need I need to
see I need to put my feet on there. I need to know what my my really is. I
just like I don't think there's anything wrong with these people. I'd like to
join their ranks personally, but at first I need to do something to my brain.
I just want to know what people would think of my feet.
You have shit feet.
I definitely, me or Cam have the worst feet though.
I have really, I have a pretty ugly feet.
I mean I have a broken toe still.
Actually no, it's starting to wiggle again.
But that's like a cool unique, that's like when a girl has like a beauty mark.
Yeah.
You know?
Or like a gap in there.
I have feet like the scene in Watchmen when Dr. Manhattan is like growing back into human
form by like skeleton and muscles.
I the I don't know. Do you think there because I know of their there is a
jencom article about a guy who pays like skaters to buy like d3s and like big
puffy skate shoes and skating them all day and then sell the shoes to him so he
can sniff them to him. You think there's a guy like that that could give me a lot
of money. Yeah, here's a comment. This might shed some light on what feet
lovers are looking for. Okay, this is because this is a comment on an ad to
the arm is from a feet love. What is the beauty standard? Well, I'll tell you
now it's it's says here well here he rated five stars beautiful feet and the
comment is her toes look like French fries and then a bunch of drooling
about
okay, oh my God, okay, but but maybe he's just hungry. Maybe just reminded him of
French fries and he's like they look like French fries kind of a homer. She's
one sexy cuban fries she's cuban that's what some of that's what someone says
Spanish yeah. I think that guy's lying. There's a comment from ye olde doc rated
four stars nice feet as wally sean said parentheses princess bride inconceivable
wait where's this jenkin feet article.
I just I believe you you don't need to pull up the article patrick. Oh here is
doing an entire Tyler a skate shoe fetishes wants your old socks and here's
a picture of him sniffing a pair of circa Lopez's he doesn't look anything like me
I don't know why it doesn't look like we did stop showing me this guy but yeah I
guess like what what kind of boot camp what I need to get into yeah I I just
I'm curious I just don't get it this is a pretty crazy photo he's got it he's got
one big red Osiris D3 on his crotch and one in his mouth.
You can't smell with your penis, dude.
Yeah.
This guy's kind of an idiot.
He's not very smart.
He can't smell with that.
He's kind of, yeah, he's kind of confused at the very least.
Do they want the women's feet to smell bad?
I think so.
The smell of feet is, that would, I don't think I could ever get into that.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm not a fan of that smell.
So the thing is, if I was into the smell of one smart food like I
I make that smell so much yeah, I don't need a I don't need a beautiful Cuban
woman to make that for me yeah. If anything,
what I'm looking at the sidebar on wiki feet and let me read you the pages
they have in this website, so they got home, yeah, celebrities, videos and
then dating platform. Well, I've heard a lot about wiki fee, but I've never
actually. I've never been. Yeah, it's always been a punch line. It's never been like
a people don't give these people a chance. We are here to give these people a
fucking shit like just yes, there's we're being real right like I want to get into
now they want to call their feet dating platform soulmates. That's really good.
That's amazing. We get in contact with Emma Watson feet.com real quick. Yeah, I
want to do an interview. Yeah. Yeah. Let's see. Let me get the email up here. I'd
really just like I think we should I think we should do a little bit of like
like a yeah an expose not an expose and expose a kind of take them down. You
know, just completely take them down. Take them up. I want to completely
bring them down another another level. Okay, I'd like to put them on. Yeah, we
should put them on. Okay, and then take them down. Can we co-sign you? Can we
take them down? Ask if they would be interested to come do a live show to
support at Emma wants to be to hurt. That's the your contact subject. Hello
interview yeah hi there we subject to three famous guys yeah three extremely
famous guys hi there we yeah we are three guys yes we do a podcast about all
sorts of things yes that's really good yes that's really really good we are
really interested we're interested in learning about feet and you seem yeah
feet and say like you're like you seem like experts we would love to have you
on our podcast experts we would love to have you or somebody involved with the
website on our podcast yeah to do an interview about a long-form interview to
to do a and then do parenthesis form inter a lot wtf with mark maron
f with mark is a mark with a cc yeah mark. I can't make a mistake in of
course, not be embarrassing yeah and let me actually put the french accent mark
over an a la so they really know we mean business yeah along from interview a
lot wtf with mark maron yeah about feet and emma watson's feet and your
influences we could cover your influence your guys we would cover your influences
interests outside of feet and favorite movies interest outside of feet and
favorite including favorite movies songs including movies songs and and food yeah
movies, songs, and food. Hopefully we can drive some more traffic to your website, to your
very professional website.
We have 100 billion downloads.
How many downloads? I'm going to put the actual number of downloads.
No, we don't want to tell everybody how many downloads.
Yeah, don't say it out loud.
I'm not going to say it on the podcast.
I'm not saying it out loud.
Oh my God, 600 billion downloads.
billion down. Oh my god, wait it's actually 10 trillion. Really? Yeah, it's actually 10
trillion. Whoa, I think we're celebrities now. Over 6 trillion downloads. Look forward
to hearing back from you. Cameron, Caleb, Patrick from Podcast About List. And Fudd.
(laughter)
- And then when they're on the,
when we interview them we'll be like,
FUD couldn't make it.
- And FUD.
- Uh huh.
- Okay.
- Alright, that's a good email.
- Wait, wait, wait, end it with a foot pun.
- Look forward to--
- Looking foot-ward to meet you.
(laughter)
- Looking...
Foot-ward.
- Maybe not foot-ward.
- Foot-ward is perfect.
- But there's one, there's one.
- Yeah, looking--
to
- Word to walking a mile.
- P.S. love the pictures.
(laughing)
- Yes, yes.
- They gotta know we're on their side.
- P.S. love the logo.
- Love the pictures, love the gallery.
- Yeah.
- Send.
Should I, any attachments?
- Maybe a photo of us.
- Yeah, a photo of all three of us.
- Okay, can we take a photo of all three of us?
- Wait, we have a photo.
- Oh, wait, like right now, we'll take a photo.
- The one with Phil.
- Oh, true.
- Our promo photos.
- Yeah, yeah, if you have that.
if you have a see if I can find it yeah you guys have to talk while I just
scroll through your files I can't just remain remain sign I fucking want bitch
yeah you can't tell me what to do you yeah shut up
you're deleting the email then cry baby don't delete the email but your bitch
yep fine I'll fill the air see my Christmas line see my what is the best
gift you've ever gotten for Christmas I don't have it or not just send it with
no picture wait wait wait no I have it I can work I know just drop it to you
right now send it so we can wait I can airdrop it to you right now it's already
sent it sent it's all you fucka. I just found it. You can follow up send reply to
the thread with a picture of it. Okay, best Christmas gift you ever got right
now. Best Christmas gift. I'm not am I pointing at you. No, I'm not. I'm pointing
at Cameron. I'm trying to think right now. You have five seconds. Five. Stocking.
You got a stocking? Yeah. You got a stocking. Somebody stocked you? Well, of
of course it's new. It's a gift. We think I got something old as a give gave you a
stocking my family, but for crit not like it was there all December and then it
was filled on Christmas, like the stocking itself yeah,
that's okay. All right, hey, that's why it was a few years ago. I got a lottery
ticket one a hundred bucks. That's my best. That's by far my love lottery
tickets on Christmas, doing scratchers on Christmas, so the best I love it. What a
beautiful tradition I cannot with that is one thing. We're like I will
definitely give my kids scratchers.
Yeah, absolutely.
There's no question.
Yeah.
Scratchers or Keno cards.
Scratchers is more fun.
They're both pretty fun.
I really like Keno.
I'm trying to think of the best Christmas gift I ever got.
That's a hard question.
Yeah.
What's yours?
Your lottery ticket?
Yeah, winning lottery ticket.
Yeah.
Nothing else was as good as a winning lottery ticket.
Not even my space ship.
Probably my jet pack maybe, actually.
Maybe it was friendship.
Yeah.
Maybe my unlimited video game detector.
Yeah, my beautiful friendship just shows if there's one around and then I go
play. What's the unlimited part mean? No batteries. All the friends I got. Yeah.
Did you guys ever have you guys ever go to a YMCA grown up? Yeah, I think I went
to the YMCA for somebody's party. I went to like a summer camp there. Our YMCA
had a I never once exercised there, but my mom would and they had a little
daycare area that had a Sega Genesis in it. Oh, that's sick. It was the sickest
I think about it all the time.
It was like the room was so small and it was me and 10 other kids all taking turns on a
Sega Genesis.
That's so cool.
Oh my god, dude.
I used to bust those kids' lips trying to play the fucking WWE games and shit.
I would love to have every video game console ever.
Yeah, and make them into a table.
Damn.
Put them in the wall.
That'd be sick.
Oh my god.
That'd be sick, dude.
Fuck.
have I gotta get an HD HDMI converter converter HDMI converter HDMI converter
what's it gonna convert into into just screen convert convert into the screen
mm-hmm okay cuz I've that we haven't touched that we in so long everybody has
a way that they know but we and so the fuck is up dude let's can we just heat
up okay you're low energy I'm you're bouncing your leg too much let's meet in
the middle okay let's be just I just completely on fire three Alvin's yeah
okay
you can't have three Alvin's shut up shut up yeah bitch-ass see two out like you
two Alvin's and one earnest or what's his name the nerd-ass bitch one I'm not
I'm not Simon. I'm definitely not Simon.
You are Simon right now.
I'm definitely not Simon.
You're Tyler the chipmunk.
You're acting like Simon.
Cameron is Simon.
In what world is Cameron Simon? He just yelled at you and called you a bitch.
Are you kidding me?
Are you baby the chipmunk?
Yeah, that's right.
I'm the little green one.
you know that i don't know if you don't
know who's the door poops and alvin eats
it so you are you already have a
person out of the city are you Simon
Simon is a Simon but he already said he
wanted to be Theodore and then he
agreed that Theodore a poop even though
it wasn't true
yep your combination listen you're
Simon because you're a nerd in a know-it-all
but you're also Theodore you're also
Alvin because you're total dick who
doesn't care about your friends
yep but we're out of the world a good
we're the good part of Alvin we're
Alvin do you think Alvin to be in the
doctor Jordan Peterson I do think he
would
yeah yeah I think it's going because
he's always wearing that red hat.
MAGA hat.
He doesn't wear a hat.
Alvin wears a hat.
Nope.
Not in the movie though.
Not in the movie.
Oh wait, no he does in the movie at some parts.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Are you going to agree with Simon/Theodore/DooDoo or are you going to agree with your fellow
Alvin?
I don't have to agree with Alvin, I am Alvin.
I said fellow Alvin.
I think you're going to be on the side of Alvin.
Which is me.
I don't know.
Well they should make a new Chipmunks movie.
They made three new Chipmunks but they were girls so it should have been three new guys.
I remember when I agree three new guys yes three new chipmunks yeah maybe their
names are Caleb Cameron and Patrick oh my god they get I don't know like maybe like
a black a black shirt and then a black another black shirt and then a third one
with a black shirt you can't copy us there's three black shirts and they may
maybe one of them and they have the same voice. Yeah, I have noticed
yeah, like an actual chip like a realist monks fucking apart. Yeah,
not a million years got to tell to chip. I remember unless one unless
dog's glad unless it is glasses. If one has glasses that helps when I
was downloading a bunch of like we should make now. No, she is OC a
bunch of let's open up Photoshop right now and just a bunch of
Nintendo DS ROMs like in like playing them on an emulator on my
computer. I got like one of like an album in the chipmunks game. Yeah,
and it was like a rhythm game type game where you had to like draw shapes in the
rhythm of the song and like it started out and it was like like circles and
squares and stuff. Yeah, as the sun go on, it starts having you draw like
Viking room. Whoa, oh yeah, i'm really question. That's cool.
Yeah, the
like a
I think there literally was like a lightning bolt that like makes you drop
like
twice. Oh man yeah yeah, it probably also makes you draw maybe a fucking cross.
Oh yeah, which is also a symbol of hate in my eyes yeah and my my little chip
mark guys yeah and my little beady black. She's how the song should have
gone me. I want no hate on earth yeah. Yeah, we should stop killing and
converting people who are different than us.
- Me, I want peace in Ukraine. - Not in space.
- That's right. - Me, I do love Roe V. Wade.
My name is Alvin Blade.
- He's a new character I made up. - Alvin Blade?
He's gonna take over the world and make it peaceful.
little chipmunk. Is he similar to Blade at all? Yes. Okay. He's half chipmunk, half
person. No vampires? So he can sing in a high voice and a normal voice.
Well that's where the world peace comes from. He's like Charlie Puth. Yep. Damn.
Alvin Blade. That's cool. That's really cool. So okay, so maybe there's, we do two
new movies. One is three Alvins. Yeah. Or three chipmunks. Three chipmunks named Caleb, Cameron,
Patrick that wear black shirts and maybe the black shirts have like logos on them
maybe they have different bands wait heavy metal chipmunks though yeah they
sing heavy metal you're gonna really enjoy disaster movie yeah yeah okay they
get rabies yeah and then they start singing they kill Elliot death metal
holy crap it's fucking onage uh-huh like they kill Elliot Page no yeah he's not
in that movie he's no he's Juno in that but no no he's Juno in Juno no oh no
it's the lady from mad TV yeah I mean I would've been a huge get for that movie
I think her but destroys a city. I think it's a fake Kim Kardashian. No, it's the real Kim Kardashian
It's her only movie. How could they possibly tell that to rage a isn't such and his penis and his balls
Yeah, she's the worst sex tape. It is it's so bad her her vagina is look just so weird
Yeah, so got all these lines on it
The hell's that about
all these lines lines up and down line going in and out of a weird yeah it's
great a big-ass penis on raja yeah huge we see Ray J's sister is Jesse J all
J
dad is dr. J yeah yeah yeah leaked meat on a tape that's a big Ray J dick pics this
This is from leaked meat on Twitter.
Leaked meat?
Yeah, what is this account?
Leaked meat.
Can we get an interview with leaked meat?
Dude male celebrity.
I would fucking love to.
Can you message them right now?
Jude Law looking good.
Leaked meat shirtless bulge while filming for the new pope.
Chris Brown.
I forgot about the new pope.
Chris Brown dick pic.
Nice dick.
Arnold Schwartz.
He's not nude.
Send him a message.
Arnold Schwarzenegger nude?
He's not even nude, dude.
They fucking lied.
DMs are closed.
Do they have a contact?
Maybe support@leakedmeat.com?
Not yet.
Zac Efron naked cock and leaks revealed.
I mean this just seems like pretty...
Okay, I just looked up...
Leakedmeat.com.
They do have a website.
Whoa.
Okay, good.
Oh, here's Arnold Schwarzenegger's penis.
Oh no.
I have horrible news, guys.
Whoa, swag.
What?
We got an automated response from Emma Watson Feet.
Hmm.
found your message wasn't delivered because the address couldn't be found or
is unable to receive mail. No fucking way bro really? Disgusting. They have a fake
support email account? That's so fucked up I was so excited. How do we get in
contact with them? I don't know. Why even why even include the contact page? Yeah
well it must be just to some default bullshit. So fucked. Some fucking bullshit dude. This is so horrible. This world sucks!
we know we should do we should have everybody everybody should DDoS them and
destroy their website down Emma Watson yeah let's just get it for Emma Watson
let's just get yeah now that I now that they denied us I actually think that
using a woman's disgusting and hosting them on your own website is fucking
disgusting yeah it's not right disgraceful I just don't want to have
any part it's discriminatory and I would not want to do an interview with them
them and also FUD is not even a member of the podcast.
And they were tricked.
I'm glad.
They literally believed it.
The look on their faces was completely priceless.
I am glad that we didn't attach the picture.
They don't deserve that.
Me too.
I agree.
And also they would have thought that Phil was FUD.
But you know what, maybe if we did attach the picture, or we did attach the picture,
it maybe would have, maybe they would have replied.
Okay, so I found emmawattsandfeet.tumblr.com.
I think it might have been an earlier version of the website.
their contact us page. They have the same email, but they also have a google
form you can fill out okay. Let's so let me because i'm actually interested in
getting in contact with them again. Let me get this on let's submit this on the
podcast account here
all right,
okay,
okay, emma watson feet. This is the blog which is dedicated to the beauty of
emma watson's feet. We selected the best picture from the internet. We always
update our gallery with the new content for you. Welcome and enjoy are you a
new or existing customer, yes or no, yes, yes, i am one of those get the
fabulous pictures of emma watson feet and there's two bullet points emma
watson fee and emma watson feet pics and what they both have pictures of emma
watson's feet. I'm going to go with the one that's just the feet on the red
carpet fee. No, the one that's just the feet on the red part of the carpet
parquet the red carpet. How did you hear about this event website friend
newsletter or advertisement?
Website, the other website.
Can we pause because I have to poopy so bad.
Yeah, we can do that but okay.
You just go poopy, we'll finish this form.
Okay, I'll wait until it's finished.
How did you hear about this event? Website, friend, newsletter,
advertisement? Website, because we learned about it
from EmmaWatsonFee.com.
Name, I'll just paste in the email.
What does it say? Why does it say Emma Watson Fee?
We already covered this.
You weren't paying attention.
I'm happy to pay it if it
if it lands us in a big interview like this. Yeah. Okay. Well, so the name I'll
put Cameron, Caleb, Cameron, Patrick, Patrick and Fudd. Then I'll put our email
in. No, okay. Fudd with one D. Interesting. I don't think that's how he spells it.
Okay. Well, I'll add a D in a second. Okay. Fudd. And then there's the last
question says submitted by, and I'm going to paste in our email that we sent.
Okay, perfect. All right, and now I'm going to submit this. All right, that
should be okay. So thank you for your response. All right, cool. So now we
got that's at least that'll go somewhere. Yeah, yeah. Oh, okay, we're
back. Sorry, Patrick just had to take the stinkiest shit of all time.
Literally, it's probably the worst smelling shit I've ever taken. And you
took it in a room that has no fan. And when you left, you left the door open
for a second.
Leaving the door open at all is huge faux pas.
You should literally be sliding through a little crack.
I sat in there with that air freshener thing.
I did 16 squirts.
It doesn't work.
You did 16 squirts in the toilet.
Or you did 17.
So you have to do one squirt per squirt.
I drank one whiskey.
I am of the belief that even if it doesn't smell bad, you should always close the door
to the bathroom.
I agree.
That door should never be open.
I can't do that at my apartment anymore, because my I think my bathroom has black
mold. That's not my problem. Yeah, I don't.
You should you should what do you mean you think your party seen black mold?
Yeah, and if it's in a toilet, it's probably poop. Oh yeah, you're putting
black mold like when you go to flushers black mold all in a toilet. Yeah, it's
more brown mold. Yeah, that is really dangerous. Actually don't inhale that
black mold. Yeah, I've been inhaling it for months. I think it's been there for
What do you guys think is
Black mold I feel like I didn't hear about black mold until I was like 15 16. It's fake. It's not real
I don't think it's real. Yeah, like what can it? What does it really do to a person gives them pneumonia?
It's how they got Brittany Murphy
No, she was addicted to drugs. Yeah, but then she got pneumonia and the drugs amplified it
So because I'm not I think I personally believe that people who are addicted to drugs have demonia
you think they're demons don't ever say that about Brittany Murphy again Brittany
Murphy was an actual fucking succubus who fucking ruined him in his life I don't
know who she is what it's only in a movie I hope it's really like a whole
it's called eight mile where do you think you grew up eight miles away from
Detroit and that's where the movie takes place isn't it eight eight miles in a
what's that movie it follows yes it is yeah they go there and they're like you
don't want to go there yeah that's where Eminem and white rappers start yeah you
don't want to go there it won't follow us here yeah I was them and then shout out
Eminem shows up he starts battling the kids he looks at the sex ghost and he
says like that's a cool hot coffee pot I don't think he tries to get away I don't
think they try it they're like the the fucking monster won't follow us to to the
fucking like I don't think that's how it go to eight mile yeah but I don't think
like well we're going to 8-mile because the monster wouldn't be caught dead in
that bad of a neighborhood I don't think that's how it works hmm I don't remember
anything you're not like well the monster be too scared of getting getting
robbed or and mugged and bad why did they go to it they have all there's a
monologue I think they go so does it has a monologue prostitute right is that why
they go there oh is that really yeah is that really
I remember that movie well. I hope that that doesn't happen in that movie. I saw it one time.
I saw it one time, too. That's a movie you can see one time. Yeah. I thought it was pretty
cool. It was. I thought it was good when I was like seventeen. I liked Krampus a lot
more, though. Krampus is sick. Krampus is fucking cool as fuck. I saw Birdman in the theater
and I was like, "This movie's going to win an Oscar." That movie can suck my balls. I
never saw Birdman. I never will see that bullshit. Any movie that has a gimmick, unless the gimmick
is either war or nudity that we've not seen before.
- Well the gimmick in that movie is Batman.
- Those are the two acceptable things.
War can be the gimmick of a movie,
or brand new, the first time an actor's been naked on screen.
Those are the two gimmicks that'll get me in my ass
in the AMC theater scenes.
- Or a new enemy for Thor.
- Yeah.
- If Thor has a new enemy, a new villain.
- Not necessarily, it could be anyone.
- I mean, if you've seen there's like a--
if Thor has a new story to tell yeah and that was in the movie if that that'll
get me in them and there's a horse spider man or that I think I don't know
maybe the Guardians of the Galaxy Thor second I would not I would not he hangs
out with him in this new movie it wouldn't last even a fucking sec I cover
my eyes during those you guys want to go see that right now I'm gonna do I am
going to see the new Thor movie because it's an IMAX and I love IMAX it is out
tonight. I climax to the max at IMAX. And I shoot a wad of
spackle out of my bait and tackle. I shoot a wad of spackle out of my bait and tackle.
And Thor and Taika Waititi's voice makes me cackle.
That's right. He should be in shackles. He's from the islands.
I saw this video of him of him like doing like some like interview or like
podcast thing or it's like a video thing where he's like he's like playing with
an action figure while he talks and the interviewer guy is like completely
silent and take what he's like saying something about like a movie or show or
something and then he just looks up and goes I'm a gay icon and there's just
like ten seconds of silence. He's not gay is he? He's not gay. He's cheating.
he's a big icon. The funniest part is that I'm a gay icon and then just the
interviewer doesn't say it's like literally just long just silence. Yeah.
I think he's cheating by saying he's a gay icon. There's been a big backlash against Taika Waititi.
From me? Yeah. There isn't that much of a backlash. There's been a big enough backlash.
I will say, I liked Boy, I liked Hunt for the Wilder People, I liked Eagle versus Shark.
I like Thor Ragnarok, I like this Roland Free guy, but I fucking hate this weird creep.
Yeah, I don't think he's a weird creep, I think he's based, dude.
He is actually kind of based.
There's this movie he made about two Maori kids in a car.
What?
Yeah, I think he's a pedophile.
I think Taika Waititi's a pedophile.
obsessed with making movies about little kids. I don't think so. You know who he
should collab with? Thorophile. He should do a movie about Nicki Minaj. Yeah. I'm
gonna do a movie about your butt. Yeah. I'm doing a movie where I get a camera right up
your butt. I heard he's bringing back his role as Hitler in the new Thor.
Yeah. Oi, check me out. Hello Thor. Hey Thor, can I touch your hammer? I'm Hitler.
- Yeah, let me touch your hammer.
- Marvel's The Avengers, wait, no,
Captain America already fought Hitler.
- Captain America fought Red Skull.
But Brown Hitler is still out there.
Brown Hitler is still out there, Red Skull Hitler.
- Brown New Zealand Hitler is still.
- No.
- Huh?
- What?
That's what he plays.
- Who?
- Tiger with TT.
- Oh, oh, sorry, I was thinking of a different guy.
- A different Brown New Zealand Hitler.
- Yeah.
thing but yeah remain Clement he kind of plays Hitler in that Rio movie is he the
Hitler of birds he's a serious bird Hitler kind of tight Hitler yeah hi but
his high put your wings up and do this do the arm motion with your arm Rio that
movie made me so horny when I was a kid yeah I think came out I was 17 when I was
kid I maybe so horny oh - came out when you were 17 dumb fuck they bounce on the
ball no but they do they bounce on the but they bounce on because I was like
the hottest shit I've seen somebody that I know yeah told me that Brazilians are
obsessed with butts somebody that you know told you that yeah you know that
somebody told me that somebody told you that somebody my sister's baby daddy
somebody told me that really yeah is that way is that true do you say
that the zillions are obsessed that way is that why I went a Brazilian wax is
when they take all the hair off your butt. I think they take your butt off. I
think they take your butt. Well, I thought that well the BBL is your
realiant but lift yeah yeah I have to go to Brazil to get that they lifted up on
the pedestal. They I guess butts are huge down there. Apparently, I would hate to
apparently I heard they have a whole party like Christmas but just for butts
that bigly bounce really should do a new thing and we should investigate it yeah
oh that'd be we should do a true crime investigation into carnival mm-hmm yeah
where we have big plague doctor sniffing nose masks and we walk around and we're
getting to the plan we're getting to the bottom of the we're gonna we're gonna
sniff this mystery out yep and also we'll go on the hottest day of the
summer yeah yeah it's good it's gonna be my god this is like a job for the cheese
crew the cheese crew might have to make an appearance yep the cheese crew but
But venture in Brazil
And that's the thing we will also set up a stand at the carnival for all of the beautiful women with giant asses
Boy that we just giving booth and we're different things with lactose in them. Just a bunch of lactose
It's a sniffing booth like a kissing booth and it's like 25 cents it gets nift
We all have different masks on. One is like a Groucho Marx giant nose mask.
Plague Doctor. Man, dude.
Yeah. Pinocchio.
He's the third big nose. Oh, Pinocchio.
Yeah, Pinocchio mask. Every time you sniff an ass, it gets even bigger, too.
Yeah.
Yeah. And also, while we're there, we'll smell their feet.
That's the experimental part.
Just to see-- well, no. The whole thing is experimental.
That's the control.
Yeah.
Yeah, this is what an awesome smell is.
So let's check out a butt now.
that's because that's for the cheese that's going to smell a little more like
cheese for the cheese crew probably yeah that's gonna be a little cheesier yeah
yeah we're gonna be i'm pretty excited about our new trip yeah i can't wait to
eat a no that's peru what eating a guinea pig you keep saying this i i don't i
think it must be i told you about it i saw it's true i saw it we literally
never heard that before i feel like in when i was in i asked my cousin and his
his mom is from Peru and she there's a key food at on on Lorimer that we can go
to and I can show you the I'm sure it's making go buy one and I think I think
you're a hundred percent true. I feel like there's no way that you're wrong.
Yeah, it says it's per a popular Peruvian delicacy Cuy a delicate. Yeah,
Cuy see you why but I feel like I it was one of those things that they just
always would say in school when we would learn about like the Aztecs or
something and they'll be like, you know they actually, they invented chocolate and they
ate guinea pigs. I feel like I heard that like 20 times.
This is a tote bag. This is a tote bag with a cooked guinea pig on it.
Yummy, good boy, tote bag.
Oh, I love, you can see, they just cooked the whole thing. Look at this.
Yeah, you just like eat around the fur, like scales on a fish. Holy shit, bro.
You can see though, it's the heads on, the arms and legs are on.
- I'd eat that, that looks pretty good.
- It looks great.
- It looks like pork.
- Yeah.
- Looks just like pork.
They're so adorable though.
- Oh my God, their little arms and legs and head is like--
- Wait a minute, I can view it.
- Oh man.
- I can view this background. - Oh Christ, bro.
- Look at this.
(laughing)
Dude, you can see its eyes, oh man.
- Oh dude. - That's so sick.
(laughing)
- I think I will buy that.
- Let's look, I'm gonna look at a recipe here.
Peruvian guinea pig delicacy plus recipe how to eat your best bet for eating koi
is to really get your hands dirty.
Eating koi is a little like eating chicken wings, in that you essentially
use your teeth to get the most meat off the bone. You're like a guinea pig, but
like it's head and little necks and just-
Oh, dude.
All right.
Going at it.
I guess we'll have some.
Oh my God. They say it tastes a little like chicken.
We'll make a stop at Peru.
has a deeper, fattier flavor than chicken with a game your taste. Look at this one.
This one's even better. This is pre cooked. Christ see this tote bit. We have
to buy this tote bag. I would gladly buy that with you.
It's only thirty one dollars. Oh, this is the ingredients are really this is
simple. Okay, I think we could make this today. Maybe is all here's everything
you need flour. Okay, check human. I guess all in my pantry. Check salt and
pepper. I don't think I have any salt that's I got some salt. I'll bring some
salt over oil yeah, yeah and then just guinea pig.
Wow sounds fucking delicious. That sounds amazing. I throw a little bit of
paprika in there. Maybe yeah, I mean for this bag
you buy that right now. Yeah, you have to buy that okay, and this is an easy
recipe. I mean step one is to de hair that can you
and pat it dry. God that's so good. I'm so hungry now. I actually really am hungry.
Let's go get some food. We can get an iPhone case and a framed print. Let us get some food.
We have to buy this guy's coy iPhone case. Portland and Seattle we're having a guinea
pig dinner in your city in mid-August. I forget the 18th and 19th I think. Swagpip.com/shows.
gonna want to buy tickets it's gonna be fun you can't miss it it's gonna be the
only shows where we will eat guinea pig live on stage you'll never see that again
you can buy a duvet cover actually do that yeah we're buying if you want if
you want a guinea pig tote bag from us you're out of luck but you can buy some
shirts that are
shop yep shows shop easy to remember yeah swag poop comm check it out
slash slash has got to be there and and I won't we won't stop saying it and
and annoying you with it until you buy the shirts and take it so you better do it.
Yep. Listen, we don't want to do this. I don't want to do shows or sell shirts.
It sucks. No, I hate selling shirts.
You know what I want to do? I want to watch fucking, I want to watch Interstellar.
Yeah. That's what I want to do. And eat a steak and cheese sub.
And eat your steak-er. Yeah.
Okay, bye. Bye.