[MUSIC]
Exterior, Gun City High School Day.
The camera comes through the clouds and glides over the prestigious Gun City High School
sponsored by Stakehams Federation of Bodies and Spaces.
The last public school on planet E-Bomb.
We get a full view of the industrial courtyard where students ride their hoverboards,
bum cigs off of the assistant teacher on suicide watch,
and watch porn on their PSPs at full volume.
We push into the building itself, a massive brutalist structure
that looks identical to the Shane Dawson maximum security prison on the outside.
The inside of Gun City High School is filled with muted,
but somewhat colorful, geometric steel plating that covers nearly every inch of the place,
with massive sterilized classrooms not dissimilar to hollowed out submarines,
all lit harshly by fluorescent lights that may or may not take an average of five years off of a student's life,
according to a pending lawsuit.
Every student is a number, number one that is, unless you're all the students who aren't number one.
In a lot of ways it's like any other high school. You got your straight-A nerds, your popular kids, your goths, your bullies, your theater dorks, your 35 or so Latinos whose names you don't even try to learn,
the kid with the wet mouth, a partially AI staff that hasn't threatened the smart house at school in three weeks,
a synthetic lunch meat made entirely of artificial gum exudates,
a wrist communicator that displays your class schedule as an interactable hologram,
rolly backpacks, Nestle chocolate milk fountains that only cost 10 tokens to use,
an army recruiter who follows you home every day,
classes on things like systemic racism, inequality, and sex work
taught by some of the most awesome comedians in Brooklyn,
a white vice principal, all kinds of stuff.
Tuition for Gunn City Public High School only costs 100,000 tokens a semester,
though it is subject to change moment to moment as the school continues to invest in speculative markets.
However, luckily for the students, if you can't afford the rapidly changing costs
for enrollment, you automatically go into debt, an incredible service for those who
aren't already in debt and are therefore at risk of being vaporized. Now, today isn't any day at
just any day at Gun City High. Today is Independence Day. As with every holiday in Gun City, whether
it's Christmas, Hanukkah, or Dark Christmas, each one is auctioned off at the start of the year,
including New Year's, to the highest bidder. This year, the Bill Murray Foundation of Pranks won
the auction, so the celebration is on Groundhogs Day, which in Gun City is on July 4th due to both
the clerical error and the total extinction of groundhogs 50 years prior. Footnote here,
after the homework riots of 2204, school was all year round in Gun City. The bell rings,
echoing into each student's ear through the cochlear rift implants. The younglings,
as they're called, file out of their final class for the day. Race science, the science of racing.
filled with excitement for today's mandatory after-school event, the Independence Day
Sports Ball Exhibition Match between the Gun City High Lame Frogs and the Bullet Town High Toads.
You could feel the energy in the air due to the leak in the school's TechnoSlam reactor.
One particular group of students are a bit more special than the rest,
right? With a friendship that is as strong as an ox, which are also extinct. Who are you guys?
My name is Blotus Piss and I'm 14 years old. I'm a freshman here at Gun City High School and I hate
it. I can't wait to graduate and enlist in the army as a general or a sniper or a combat medic
who also gets to snipe. I don't pay attention in any of my classes. None of this stuff they teach
us in gym class or intro to marksmanship will matter at all when I go to boot camp. I wish they
would teach us actually useful stuff like how to go across monkey bars above mud or how to climb
over a wooden wall, or how to point and laugh at the fat recruit who can't climb over the
wooden wall. When I'm not at my desk daydreaming about my civic duty to explode a guy's head
with the awesomest gun ever, you can probably find me hanging out with my three best friends,
or "Batallion," which is the army word for "best friends." They're the only reason I
haven't dropped out of school to become a child soldier. I almost did one time when I
I got a really good offer from a warlord, but that whole
Kony 2245 campaign really messed that up for me.
I don't know what the future holds, but I know for certain
I'll end up in the army.
I don't even mind if it's a desk job just as long as I don't
become a detective or archaeologist.
I have no respect for those professions.
Yeah.
So it's a little blow toss.
He's pretty much the same as big blow toss, except he has a
a slingshot, and he's got some cool sticks,
instead of his patented Grinch gun and dual pipes.
He's got a couple of abilities that are familiar to some,
and you'll see them when we start playing.
- I will go next.
- Yeah.
- Oh, hey, you're the new kid, right?
I'm Ray, you're the one who transferred,
yeah, from that prep school?
Oh, what's it called?
Don't tell me oh, yeah, I got prescribed prep down on 4th Street. I hear it's a real bitch
You'll have an easy time here though. The teachers are total pushovers. Plus most of them will let you finger them
This is sexual. This is here's my damn box. Mr
Diarrhea pretty much all of them will let you go Jeff Dunham down there if you're willing to get an F in their class
That could just be me being awful at fingering though
I keep trying to make my fingers come but I'm almost starting to think it's impossible
so
Anyway, have you ever been fingered?
Well, it would just be nice to have someone to practice on I'm failing almost every class at this point
Maybe you could come over
We could put on a movie cuddle up on the couch and then pause the movie and I could start going to work on you
Like you're a rotary telephone
*laughter*
If not, it's okay, but I will hate you.
Anyway, welcome to the school.
*laughter*
RayWilliamJohnson is still a demon with a computer on his body.
Hell yeah, I am.
Um, yeah, he's uh, again, he's also pretty similar.
I removed his sexual grenades for legal reasons.
Um, and uh, yeah, otherwise though, I mean, you're all gonna enjoy.
I actually gave him digital missiles, which I guess takes on two meanings now.
Digital missiles.
Yeah, it's basically a re-skinning of magic missile, but now it's a re-skinning of fingering.
Yeah.
So yeah, it's good to have you here. Now, Mr. Yoda.
Oh no! Oh, what time is it? Oh, jeez, I've actually been asleep this whole time in this damn class.
Ah shit. Hi, I'm Patrick Yoda. I'm 19 years old. Yeah, I got held back twice. Who gives a shit?
Uh, I don't need school at all because when I'm older I'm gonna be a famous singer. Listen to my singing
I'm through standing in line the clubs. I'll never get in. It's like the bottom of the ninth and i'm never gonna win
Life hasn't turned out quite the way I want it to be
Oh god damn, I hate this fucking school so much
I hate my teachers and the principal the most but the janitor is my friend for real
He and I will sometimes smoke e-cigarettes in the janitor closet and he'll tell me about his life
Real life real experience fuck all this school shit. I'm going to school at hard knocks, but I'm still in this fucking school. Ah
Man, I fucking hate it pisses me off how much they lie to us here. Oh
I fucking
They fucking lie to us here while I collect real education like how to do flips and shit on my hoverboard and how the janitor eats
His wife's thing out. God. Damn is class over. I'm so fucking pissed at life
Can it be lunchtime yet? Oh god. I have to go take a massive shit in the bathroom for real, man
I wish something horribly wrong would happen to school like
Terrorist attack
I hate this place.
*laughter*
So, uh,
Will Patrick Yoda still has
uh, he still has his hoverboard, that's not
gonna change. Still has his bad attitude
mask, right?
Oh, that.
Instead of his hoagie, he's got a PBJ
with the crust on, as his
melee weapon. Um,
and he can still shoot lightning out
of his hands, so, um,
this is some of the cool stuff. So you mean I don't got my hoagie,
I got it right here in real life.
Patrick Yoda has his hoagie.
Now, as we all know, there are these are only three of the four
best friends in gun City High.
Everyone knows these four because they're always together always
hanging out always having the best time together and their
fourth friend is maybe the most beloved of them all.
Colin tell me about yourself.
Good morning.
Everyone.
My name is Colin.
Despite being a tubby little 14-year-old piggy boy with a lisp,
I am incredibly well-adjusted.
My healthy self-perception was forged in the flames of my stable home life and loving parents.
Oh boy, do I have so much to live for!
When I'm not warming the hearts of the coldest bullies by wiggling my little tail adorably,
putting an apple in my mouth and laying on my stomach deliciously,
or hearing the poor meanies out compassionately,
my favorite activities are playing in the cyber park or at the futuristic beach,
Practicarmi Espanol and playing the Robot Style Recorder.
Above all though, I love to hang out with my best friends in the whole world.
Blotoss Piss, Patrick Yoda, and Ray William Johnson.
I love them so much!
Yep, little Colin, the beloved little piggy.
Is he in student council, Colin?
Are you in student council?
Or no?
I am the vice president of student council.
Okay, yeah.
He's beloved.
He somehow captured the hearts of these three delinquents who just love hanging out with
him and he loves them.
And it's a beautiful friendship that will probably just go on and on and on.
And we'll see more of it throughout the time, their time in gun city together.
But yeah, you guys just filed out a class.
You're sort of in the hallway.
It's the last class of the day.
So everyone's getting ready to go to see sports ball.
What are you guys up to?
What are you guys thinking?
Oh, I fucking I can't believe they assigned us more homework for this stupid class shit
Or can help you learn more about the world around us. How about you do my homework Colin?
Okay, that sounds like a great idea because I will learn more than oh god. You're my best friend
So awesome do my homework - man. Come on. What kind of friend are you?
I'm well adjusted so I have to establish boundaries at a certain point
I think that I won't have enough time to pursue other interests in my life. I just too much ah
You are so cool. I hope you
live forever oh
Man oh you guys make the day easier
We're all fawning over Colin principal Barney walks up to you guys
Well, I hope you guys are getting ready to go to the sports ball game. It's gonna be great. I hope you eat my shit
Oh Patrick Yoda, you're always with the quick, you know telling me to eat poop
Oh, you're a principal Barney when I go to the army, they're gonna give me a license to kill
Don't finish that sentence or I'm gonna have to do something
Well, you know as we all know a century ago gun city belonged to Transylvania a country of vampires that ruled over everyone
Similar to the movie Daybreakers have any of you kids seen Daybreakers man. Shut your bitch old ass up
sit on these
Well, I will not be doing that though. I thank you for offering me the finger finger me as you've offered every single
Faculty member so far. How about these I give the left hand
I find film fascinating, but my parents don't let me watch that much stuff, actually.
Oh, Colin, you don't have to worry about anything forever.
Thanks! And then Colin leans down and smells the nearest flower and smiles really big.
You go to lean down and it's a school and there's metal everywhere, but for some reason, as you lean down, a flower wills itself from the ground to meet your snout because it's so pure.
Yeah.
Well, I'm gonna head to the sports ball game.
I hope to see you all there.
I'm Barty!
And he just sort of, uh, runs off to the sports ball game.
God, I hate that freaking guy so much!
If he was dead, there would probably be joy to the world!
Yeah.
Also, like, this is the future. Why is there a dinosaur here?
I actually don't like him either, but I need to be polite to everyone.
that's true you're ah man you just know how to defuse every situation man god you're perfect
so uh yeah do you guys want to go to the sports ball game you guys ready to go yeah you want to
wait around a little bit there's other i there's a locker um and i just break into it okay yeah uh
do i have to do anything yeah i'd say let's roll you're just punching it yeah like i'm
I'm punching above the lock.
Okay.
Yeah.
Um, you see a kid go on that, that like in between each punch.
That's my, that's, uh, that's my, uh, that's not this fricking locker.
Won't they never gave me my combination.
They hate me here.
That's my, that's my locker.
Shut up.
Uh, do you, do you want something inside of it or, um, maybe actually, yeah.
Can you tell me my combination for my locker?
I don't know your combination for your locker.
Wait.
So why do I keep punching this one?
The combination is in the locker like on a piece of paper in there. No, I will help them get it out
Okay, and so he goes to unlock the locker which it's all it's retinal scan and then rectal scan and then he types
in a few buttons and
He opens it up. He's like I have some homework in here
Ah fuck that shit, this ain't my locker
Get that shit out of here man!
I don't even want to see that!
go
thanks colin you're the you're the man
i can't wait for for for you to for you to become like a president or something
really big and
i wanna be an astronaut
and i think i'm gonna live to be a hundred and ten due to a healthy lifestyle
you know what that's
i can't refute that
i'm uh... i'm gonna go to the sports ball game i'll see you guys later
And this kid wanders off to the sports ball game.
Can somebody tell me where my locker is?
I've been in this school for a year now!
[Laughter]
It's probably...
It's probably somewhere around there.
Do you want to do an investigation check?
See if you can find your locker?
With disadvantage.
Oh yeah.
You've made yourself forget where it is.
Four.
Okay.
You know what? It's perfect.
[Laughter]
You like, smash a few lockers.
Like, just...
yelling in the each time you smash one
and it's just not working
you're not finding it
you know i find it a lot of shit sucks
god this school hates me so freaking much
yeah yeah
and
and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and
uh...
it ever see you every day makes it better colin
I love you guys more than you'll ever know.
We love you too, Colin.
Yeah, so you wanna go to the sports ball game now?
Let's all go!
Yeah, so you guys head to the sports ball game.
Uh...
I'm wearing a giant foam finger.
Can we pass my locker on the way?
It's got like a big sign.
Don't forget, Patrick, this is your locker.
Patrick's covered in like memento tattoos until we're in the circus.
You try to just scrub it off, "Ah, I got this fucking stain on my arm!"
"I hate this rash that I keep getting!"
Uh, yeah, you guys head to the sports ball game, um, uh, you're at the Stakehams Arena Junior.
Um, where sports ball is played. It's a game spawned from the blood of athletes, and fine-tuned through the science of competition.
It's brilliant, brutal, and perfect.
When Gun City gained its independence from their vampire overlords in Transylvania, they
did it through genius guerrilla warfare fully inspired by "The Ingenious Game," as Sports
Ball is often called.
The rules are elegant and simple, but iterative and elastic, designed to evolve play and generate
new ideas and strategies sometimes within a hair's breadth of the last innovation.
The official rules of Sports Ball are thus.
So in sports ball, some inescapable ritualistic gathering occurs where people line up to watch
men in tight clothes run around and play a game.
Okay.
You have your ball and it for some reason has seams on it.
And like it was so sloppily sewed together or something.
Or maybe it's made of pigskin.
Uh, weird.
Especially for Colin.
That's what the sports ball says.
Yeah.
And it's shaped like a foot.
Is that even a ball?
Okay.
Also it has these little bumps on them and sometimes it's black and white and has pentagons all over it, okay?
Uh, well anyway, all these guys, and it's always only men,
are running around on this field that's painted, like the grass is painted,
and when one of them puts the sports ball in a hole or a basket or something, they all say "Ole", like in another language.
"Huh?"
And that's when they hit a home run, I guess.
And where you run around a bunch of pillows in the dirt and hope no one touches you, it just sort of goes on like that.
It's just completely insufferable.
It's very hard to parse what the rules are.
And so the goal, you'll start to get the sense of what it is when the announcer
tries to give you guys a play by play.
But yeah, it's this, there's in the stands, like in the arena,
everyone's forced to stand every minute by an electrical buzzer
because the wellness division of the Stakehams Corporation
We're upset about all the sitting that goes on.
You have like hot dog vendors, but they say things like get
your meat tubes here your meat tubes with a weird starch bond
to hold them and put packets of goop on top of it and ice-cold
alcoholic beverages that we serve to increase your willingness
to spend on our food products here.
And so they all just like do that all over the place.
But yeah, so you guys where you guys are you guys in the
and
It's for the faculty only
Want to go try to find a way to sneak some of that beer whoa
Appropriate level of bad boy
We've been able to find common ground through a number of different ways
But he's not sexually deviant
*laughter*
a
like to be doing kind of like a Winnie the Pooh style thing just where it's like I'm wearing
just like a dorky like um you know polo shirt that's yellow and no pants but it's fine.
Yeah of course it's fine yeah you're smooth down there.
Oh yeah I've got the Jankos on I've got like a big like uh DC shoes hockey jersey
and a backwards Fred Durst hat.
Hell yeah.
Yes dude.
That's how I'm looking. I got Osiris D3s on too. I've got this outfit out.
Like 10 wallet chains.
Yeah, you're gonna have disadvantages to help you just change. So yeah, there's the obviously you guys can see that there's the, you know, alcoholic beverage vendor walking around.
And you can see him going back to where he supplies it so that might be a place you can go or you can try to nab it off of him. What are you thinking, what's the plan here.
here. I'm going to go talk to him. Yeah, let's go talk to him.
And then if that doesn't work, we can just take it. Yeah, let's
let's go. Yeah, yeah, right. You guys walk over to the alcoholic
beverage vendor as he's sort of passing his drinks to the
faculty. Hey there, buddy.
Hi there.
How you doing? I'm good.
I'm 50, you know how it is.
Can I get a beer? We're brothers.
We went to we have we live in the same house.
Alright Colin, you're making this really complicated.
It's as simple as this, I'm 50 years old.
Hi there, I'm their dad.
I've been the only kid that hasn't seen me in 50 years.
No, there's this 50...
Wait, dad?
Wait.
[laughter]
We're cousins too, we're cousins and brothers.
Dad, I haven't seen you in so long.
And that Yoda over there is our family enemy.
Yeah, so okay.
What are you talking, hey!
He's our, listen, shut up.
He's our family enemy and he hates beer.
So if you care at all...
While I'm doing that, while you're saying that, I'm like looking through the trash to find like half full beers.
So he hates beer and so basically we need to, we make our enemy very mad by you giving us some beer.
Yeah I would hate it if they got beer and they got me one too.
And he's a real asshole too.
Fuck you!
I'd stop talking and start doing a cute little piggy dance.
Which is my role performance.
Okay.
Oh my God, he got 21.
Okay, it's a very...
I wiggle my little spiral tail.
You know.
He's like, "That is really cute."
There's more where that came from
if you give us a beer.
That's right.
The one you're calling your family enemy
is the most obviously teenage boy
I've ever seen. I'm 19, bitch!
Yeah, he is.
I can still be an enemy.
Yeah, he is our enemy. He is. Now listen, that guy is 19.
We're all in our 50s to 100, but
Even if they weren't in their 50s, I'm their father so I could give them permission. I might also be their uncle
I don't understand what the situation is here. Boy. You're illegal drinking age is 19
I think that one sounds like he's about to cock-a-doodle-do. I'm gonna let you guys sort of
Pitter patter amongst yourselves. I got to give beer to some real adults. Very cute dance though. You think I'm fake?
a
good job persuading. I think we were a little bit disorganized.
Okay, you're right. Who's the best at stealing and being sneaky? It's not me.
It might be me. I'm seeing a number four in my head.
Okay. Yeah. Well, then what I'd like to do is I'd like to say a little poem on
you to do Colin's cute inspiration. Um where I say, would you kiss a fish?
Would you eat a dish? Would you make a wish? This is Colin's poem for this.
And now you can add an additional 1d6 to any check.
[Laughter]
Fuck yeah.
Yeah, you can. So, yeah, you saw that guy. He's obviously a little wary of you all because of the insane story, family drama you told.
I was really interested. I wanted to hear more about this.
Yeah, I'd like to do a one-off about that instead of this, if that's okay.
Yeah, we can just sort of pivot.
Hold on, let me delete all my files on the computer.
No, Patches, don't!
No, that's a bad idea!
Stop!
Ohhhh!
Do it!
Um, and you also see Lil Gary C. Enterprise runs his own sort of lemonade stand
at the, uh, at the, uh, by the bleachers where you see Haseki Tsune, it leads a cheerleading
group. I should, I forgot to mention all the people you go to high school with. Um, yeah,
Pennsylvania gym is the star of the sports ball team. Of course. Um, uh, yeah, you have
Haseki Tsune, Gary C enterprise. Uh, you'll see Sullivan later. You all know who Sullivan
is. He's the senior who tries to hang out with you guys.
All these people at this, at this sports ball game, I feel like either we're going to meet
them again when we grow up or our parents already did based on what the timelines
that we're not sure we're in at the moment. One thing I'm for certain of is
that Colin will interact with all of them in the far future. Yes, I'm excited to make
friends with everyone in the world! You will, Colin. I believe in you. I want to ride a hot
air balloon. I want to travel to Spain. I want to go to grad school and discover a cure for something.
And you will, Colin. Absolutely. You will, Colin. I want to be an astronaut. God, he's so beautiful.
He's so gorgeous.
His light shines so bright!
Thank you guys.
And then, uh, thanks.
You guys are-
You guys are my best friends.
You too, Colin.
Why are you crying?
That-
You just-
You have such a spark.
Thanks.
Yeah, hopefully that spark never goes out.
A flame that will never die.
I am the phoenix.
I am eternal.
That's right.
So do you guys want to try to steal
the beer? Yeah.
Yeah, you guys are trying to steal it.
So yeah, you do have a you do have a bardic
inspiration. So if you roll poorly, I'm just I'm
looking it up real quick.
I want to make sure that I told you the right
die that you can add to it.
Ah, it's level 5. Okay.
Yeah, it's just 1d6.
Okay. So yeah, I'm going to roll a stealth here.
try it. I'm going to, should I sneak to where the supply is or should I just try and steal
it from this guy? I feel like supply. Yeah, I'm going to sneak into the supply place.
Yeah. Yeah. So the supply place, just before you roll, I want to give you some of the picture of
it. So supply place is just a little bit off the side of where the bleachers are, right? It's like
sort of like with a catering hall where you have stuff in the back out of sight. So it's just sort
of like a refrigerated storage unit basically just sitting in the back there. So you can go there
and when the door opens would be like maybe a good time to go in unless you want to try to like
figure out the passcode or hack in or something. I'm just I'm gonna I'm gonna wait what were you
saying? Oh I just wanted to ask if I could try and do something with Gary C enterprise.
Yeah you could do anything with Gary. Okay I'll wait. Let Cameron's thing play out and then yeah
yeah yeah for sure we'll come back to that. Okay I'm gonna yeah I'll try and sneak in when the door
doors open. Okay, cool. Yeah, I would say yeah, roll just roll
stealth and then that should be enough. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. The
D six. That's a fourteen plus. Four so eighteen that's good.
Yeah. I mean that's very good. So yeah, you managed to get
there and you see the door open slightly and you sort of just
slink your way in there and the door closes behind you and you
You can see it's a treasure trove of just the shittiest, wateriest beer.
It's everything you could dream of and more.
The only issue will be trying to get out.
But yeah, you can take as much as you want.
Okay, I'll take as much as I can carry.
In the ghillie suit you have?
I'm going to take it all, everything.
I'd say you can get like six beers.
I'd say grab a six pack.
I'm grabbing a six pack and then I'm going to try to sneak back out.
OK, cool, so I mean you you can sort of look around.
You feel a little bit of a draft coming from like behind some of the boxes,
so there might be a way out there or you can wait for the guy to come back.
Sort of like, you know, go open open with the door and then slink.
Kind of see what's going on with the draft from the back.
OK, is there any way that I can see that this is happening
and try to try to distract someone?
I'm trying to think. So I mean, obviously the beer guy, the beer guy is still doing his thing.
He's back in the stands now. So he's not going to be back there for a little bit. So you
can get him maybe to go over there. But as far as distracting people, there aren't too
many people around there. There's a couple of guys on their smoke break. But if you want
to distract them just in case, I would totally recommend it.
I guess I'll go up and I'll just go up in front of those guys and I'm just going to start
doing another little dance without talking. I like chop my little hooves.
You know, it's not actually really much of a dance.
Okay, that's an amazing performance. Holy crap. Yeah. Okay. Yeah, they're like,
you see two guys in a smoke break and they when they see you and they're like, Hey,
All right.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
It's like yelling.
I'm just so happy.
Yeah, I would say, Cam, you have free reign to get out of there.
Roll a stealth check, but it's not gonna be too high of a DC.
16.
Yeah, you're good. You sort of sneak out of there.
You're like crap your bring your arm out.
You see the end like you see just his arm first column while you're dancing with the six packs on it.
It's like yeah, so you see the rest of them come out of the little little space there.
Yeah. Yeah. No. Yeah, way to go pig.
All right. Yeah. Yeah, cool.
And I just I kind of like clumsily stop and then just sort of walk away.
All right, take it easy. Let's just go back to smoking cigarettes.
So yeah, you guys, you guys got the beer.
I guess both of us you're hiding it in your ghillie suit or something.
And so you're trotting back to the stands to give it to your friends.
Patrick, what's going on?
Well, while that was happening, like the stealth thing, I was like,
man, there's no way he's going to get that friggin beer.
No way he's getting that fucking beer.
And then I go over to Gary C.
Enterprise and with his lemonade stand and I start talking to him.
Hey there, Patrick.
How's it going?
Hey, shut up.
Listen to me real quick.
All right, called this called yeast.
Alright, we're gonna put this in the lemonade and we're gonna let it ferment and in a little bit we're gonna have beer.
*snort*
Uh, okay, yeah, that's gonna take a really long time.
*laughs*
What do you mean it's gonna take a long- what the fuck are you talking about?
Oh, just- just, the like the time that- look, I've done the calculations on this and it's just the overhead, it's just way too much.
I don't think we're gonna make a profit that way, pal.
Ah, bullshit. What are you talking- we can make beer right now out of lemonade and yeast.
Okay, you know what-
At least kombucha.
*laughs*
Okay, you know what that gives me an idea here. I'm gonna portion off about 15% of my lemonade, okay?
Yeah, give that to you
You put your yeast inside if in an hour that yields kombucha we can sell that will split the profits if it doesn't I'm gonna have
To take that amount back from you, right?
So you're gonna sort of put down on some money you're gonna take a little bit of that back about math
I'm not here to do homework
All right. Well just take the lemonade see if you can make kombucha out of it at least. Okay? Yeah, well shit
I thought we had something I thought we had a better business plan
Hey business, I
Love business, I guess you hate business. He looks at you and it's like death is behind his eyes. I didn't mean that
Is this I didn't mean what I said? Anyway, I'm
I'm gonna go and as soon as I say I'm gonna go Cameron's like already
Cool yes, you guys bring the beer back
Yeah, you're what he goes you guys gonna start drinking the beers hanging out. So hell yeah
Yeah, I'm too focused on my on my beer that I'm trying to make that I'm just drinking active dry yeast
Okay roll a constitution saving throw
You just vomit like it's disgusting
Years, you're so wasted
You're so wasted right now you're vomiting all over the
I'm still looking scared
I'd like to grab a beer and try to drink it. Yeah, go for it Colin. Yeah
Yeah, I try to drink it really really fast just experience with liquids is apple juice
Yeah, I would say Constitution saving throw on that for sure.
See how you can handle your liquor.
Oh no, it's six.
Colin, you're gonna get a little tummy ache from this, I think.
Oh, this hurts!
We need to pump his stomach, not a tummy ache.
My tummy seriously hurts, guys.
Colin, are you with me?
Look, don't go into the light.
Okay, I won't.
I'm gonna call the cops!
*laughing*
I don't know what to do!
You guys are my best friends!
Yeah, you see Hasekitsune look over and he's like
"Those guys are such weirdos."
They're always trying to pump their pig friend's stomach.
*laughing*
I get into some weird stuff sometimes.
You're just saying that
while your friends are pumping it.
*laughing*
I drink one of the beers
and I go, "Wow, I can't wait
to like, I'm in the army and then I get
get back and drink 36 of these at night while I'm recording calls from my wife.
So yeah, now it's the crowds are now sort of, you hear they announce her over like the thing.
Ladies and gentlemen and V-folks, it's time for sports ball and you hear like, you know,
whatever fucking fanfare music is playing. You see like the crowds are going crazy,
starting to gather. You guys are drinking, you're getting freaking hammered.
You're having a good time.
While that's happening, I've mixed a beer with that lemonade and yeast.
*laughter*
I was like, "This'll do it!"
You see, like, as soon as you finish pouring the beer into that, like, concoction of lemonade, it just has a face.
*laughter*
With no expression on it, it's just looking, like, at you.
Colin's gonna try to drink more beer after getting a tummy ache.
Oh hell yes he is.
We'll do a constitution saving throw on that too with this advantage.
Gonna keep trying.
Okay yeah.
Oh baby.
Yeah you can hold it down.
It only takes one for Colin and then he's got it.
Colin gets it right away.
He just immediately knows how to be cool.
This is sick.
The announcer's like uh.
I wanna spray paint the school.
I want to spray paint the school.
Whoa!
Colin, you're crazy!
Calm down, Colin.
I want to spray paint the school with a picture of an A+ on a homework assignment.
Oh, you are so damn adorable.
That's just a mural!
Oh my...
You hear people around you after college, they go "Yoooooo!"
Bring that tummy over here and let me jiggle it.
Okay, I'll do that.
the
first are visiting team hailing all the way from bullet town their toughest
nails and ready to wait it's the bullet town told
loads
well
all
and more
a bunch of guys
who are clearly like
like thirty years old plus are just coming out one guy is probably sixty
to
Yeah, you guys are booing. Everyone else is cheering.
It's it's a they're like pretty competent.
Actually, despite the name, you see the team come out.
You see Pennsylvania Jim come out and he's like, you know, posing.
And he like credit like does like finger guns, the husky kitsune.
And, you know, everyone's like, ooh, like, you know, is it the high school
sweethearts and also from the back, you see the gun city lame frogs mascot,
which is a lame frog.
Underneath the costume of this lame frog is Sullivan,
the senior who looks exactly like the mascot and he's just also in a mascot outfit.
Yeah, and so the announcer goes now for the gun City National Anthem this year sponsored by Halliburton in accordance with the Bill Murray Foundation of pranks as sung by Sullivan the frog.
you see solving the frog who's just still in the outfit that looks like him with the microphone
and
problem with the vampires and he just goes on to talk about vampires why they're scary how to kill
them where's the best place to shop for wooden steaks and garlic and all these things what the
i think i'm tripping from the beer he's tripping and i'm not talking about colin i'm talking about
Sullivan. And as Sullivan finishes the song, the
announcer goes, "Arm, play ball!" And it begins.
I try to drink my face lemonade.
As it's getting closer to you, you hear like a very low hum,
like as you bring it closer to your role constitution I would say yeah wisdom to
see if you become afraid of it 22 yeah you're just like I know this face it's
fine I throw my beer can at Sullivan nice
second go tripping on beer I as soon as I start drinking I have like a full like
like yellow submarine like acid.
[Laughter]
Overlays, I can't see anything.
I just see colors and shit.
You see as Blotas
throws the beer, you see it turn into like a bird
and fly towards Sullivan's
head and Blotas, make a range
attack.
So just do your
slingshot basically.
Oh my god!
[Laughter]
Can I describe this?
describe this. Yeah, it looks like it looks like it misses
Sullivan, but that it flies past him and it bounces off the
helmets of one of the like the the away team's helmets and it
flies back and it flies into the briefing hole and Sullivan's
mascot costume goes into his mouth. It gets the it goes into
two mouths. Yeah. Yeah. Ray William Johnson. You're just
seeing like a bird fly past Sullivan and like Kareem off
the head of a dinosaur and then like fly back into Sullivan's mouth.
Oh, boo boo boo boo.
Like you're going like into the mouth now, like you're following
it through.
Yeah, you just hear you just hear cuz Sullivan still has like
the bike up with him.
You just hear.
I turn to Colin which is like the the wisest way ever and I
just look at him as a you're going to die.
*laughter*
Can I roll like a wisdom saver or something?
Yes, of course, yeah.
Oh my god, he got a crit!
I just look back and go,
"Yes, we all die one day."
*laughter*
But I am Colin, I am the Phoenix, I am eternal.
And then I kind of like shake my head and go, "Beer's weird."
*laughter*
And so, yeah, the game is ongoing.
The announcers like and the two teams line up on the painted lines all crouched down in the squatting position staring at one another.
One guy starts yelling a seemingly random string of phrases and numbers.
Hopefully someone could decode them after the game and he throws the ball between his legs.
Everyone is ramming into one another.
Hopefully they let each other pass, but they seem fairly determined to do this.
One guy has the balls now bouncing it over again again.
So all the ball changes over and over.
So it's a football, then it's a basketball and he's bouncing it.
Then he throws it to some guy who hits it like a baseball bat, who then heads it into
a hole, like into a golf hole on the other side of the field.
Like sports ball is just all those things together.
I look down at the cup and see that the face in the cup has been saying this the whole
time.
And I just look at it and go, "Okay."
He's been saying it like in the exact same, like at the same time as the announcer, just
like an octave lower.
He's like, this is a very trippy episode, folks.
Yeah, and so yeah, he starts describing it and then eventually it's the
scores tied up.
It's halftime whenever the lame frog score the husky tuning the
cheerleaders come out and do a full choreography to did it did it by
black pink the K-pop group.
Nobody knows them.
They're good.
And then look, I like K-pop.
So, um, half time show begins with the marching band coming out again and they're playing, um, uh, ants go marching.
Uh, and Sullivan is of course singing, uh, ants go marching.
(Sings)
He still has the beer can in his mouth.
He couldn't get it out.
His arms don't reach in the costume.
Yeah, so as it's approaching the chorus, uh, the marching band makes a target symbol.
to symbolize how Gun City always hits its mark.
And Sullivan goes like, "Tenayersk, baa!"
And then like, it's like you hear him like try to cough up the beer bottle.
And at first you don't hear anything though.
Sound is a lot slower than light, you see.
So you're always going to see something,
like 500 adamantium coffins roaring through the sky before you hear it.
They don't catch wind as they fall or blast sirens to warn you that they're coming.
they just plummet from some mysterious floating castle, as massive as a small town.
When the castle, of which you could only see the bottom, vanishes into a black vapor, whisked
away by what must be a supernatural wind, the careening hunks of metal death one by one
appear as dark imperfections punctuating the sky until they become an epic, malignant shadow.
The shade it provides is so brief that only a few can react in time.
One of them, thankfully, is the ever vigilant, ever anxious Solvin the Frog.
His eyes lift towards the sky as he hits that high note.
And when he realizes what is happening, he's the one with the microphone in hand.
So he's like, "ANYWAY HOLY SHIT VAMPIRES!"
And just...
DUNK DUNK DUNK DUNK
The coffin smash onto the field, shattering the thick earth beneath them,
aiming for the perfect target formation the marching band for.
Some of the students get flattened immediately, their limbs are sticking out
while their body is in the ground.
mushed in a pre-made grave with a pre-assigned coffin.
Other coffins shoot through the stands,
crushing cheerleaders who still grip onto their pom-poms to the very end.
Some of the coffins are hovering in the air,
like shooting lasers outside of the sides of them.
People are screaming and running.
Methods of transportation just being obliterated.
Many of the metallic coffins that land on the edge of the school grounds,
and they have these little antennas shoot out that
generating this massive red force field that blocks out everything.
After they land, that's when the Transylvanian menaces emerge, armed to the teeth and to the teeth with their cyberknight blades and bloodblasters.
The feast begins. You see them going, grabbing students, biting them, faculty.
You see all of them going crazy, everyone's running around.
In the Pandemonium in Chaos, you're able to spot what must be the leaders of this invasion.
One, a thick-lunked, nude, impossibly muscled, scan-a-scaly grey, almost gargoyle-like, with
massive bat wings and a horrible monster's face.
The largest vampire by far, this behemoth begins to carve up as many students and faculty as
he can find, ripping a few in two and drinking the blood as it pours from their severed halves.
Another, a gorgeous womanly vampire, buxom and hypersexual.
One wave of her hand, of her silk-gloved hand and a sway of her silk gown, men and gay women
turn on their own, beating their brethren to death in the name of some form of dark possession.
She weaves her hands to and fro, casting a spell, and the possessed follows suit, forming
a carriage around her out of their bodies, and then wheeling her at a remarkable speed
toward the school.
Third, you see a nasty rodent-faced man, thin, bald, and poshly dressed, with a chrome cloak
that covers his new Victorian guard, with cyborg eyes that glow a harsh red.
From his cloak he produces a wave of small vampiric rodents, with eyes matching his, that
swarm the field, crawling up the legs of the unsuspecting, gnawing at their face, moving
swiftly to the next victim with unfeeling robotic precision.
As quickly as the rodent-faced man unleashes his vermin plague, you see him turn into a
bat that appears to be part V-Folk, and fly towards the school, phasing through the wall.
Finally, emerging from the sole coffin that's been unopened, upon which sits a raised, upside-down
cross made of obsidian, is a handsome vampire of repute. His full Yoji Yamato outfit in Vantablack,
the ruby heart that sits upon his outfit above his own, slicked back silver hair,
striking golden eyes, a feared commander in the Transylvanian army. While his lieutenants may
be unknown to you, this is a man whose face is plastered all across gun city propaganda channels.
Not since Vlad the Inhaler has someone struck fear into so many hearts. Hearts whose blood he wants
to suck. Count Loveyalots, he looks to the four of you and gives a curt nod to that big brutish
vampire who has just finished supping from a math teacher's skull. The big vampire sort of like
turns you all drooling in blood, just drooling blood coming out of his mouth, and while Loveyalots
turns into a pink sparkly mist and vanishes. Principal Barney, with his like arm bleeding,
Runs up to the four of you.
*panting*
PLEASE!
YOU HAVE TO HELP US!
You're the adult here!
We're- we're useless! We're cowards!
Again, dude, you're a-
you're a dinosaur!
Just fuckin' bite 'em, dude!
What the fuck are you doing, man?
You're huge!
Man, look at me, Greg!
I'm made of felt!
I really regret saying I wish there was a terrorist attack earlier.
I just wanna say, straight up,
this is not my fault.
Oh, well, if wishes were fishes-
OW!
He's just, like, gripping his arm.
Please, please, I'll do anything. I'll even bring back summer vacation. Just please help.
Okay, I'll help.
No, we're in.
Summer vacation?
Yes, just get rid of the vampires, please.
Got it.
That's easy for a guy like me.
And I start army crawling.
In no direction in particular.
Army crawling around.
So yeah, you see the big, gray, scaly vampire. He's kind of walking towards you guys.
And he sort of looks to the four of you and he says my master has deemed you worthy
My name is Gary vampire
I'm gonna kill you. Hey Gary
What what's up? You suck?
Pretty good. I'm gonna save you for last
Delicious - hey, don't say that to my friend
and
I have stared into the pulsing veins of fate earlier today.
Did it went well?
I was very confused by what I saw in 14.
Well, you're not going to be confused by by this.
Everyone roll initiative.
Yeah. Roll initiative. You guys are 19.
Yeah. So first up is going to be you actually, Patrick Yoda.
So where are you guys?
Are you guys on the stands still like the principal Barney run up to you guys
the stand. Yeah. Alright, cool. So, you're sort of like, like,
you know, probably like 25-ish feet away from him. He's sort
of down below looking up at you all ready to sort of pounce. So,
that's where you are though. Okay. So, Patrick, what are you
thinking? I'm gonna throw the drink at him. Uh you're gonna
throw the **** up face drink? Yeah. Okay, cool. Alright. Yeah.
Can it be like some kind of like persona like?
Let's let's talk it out. No, because we because I've committed to this. So let's figure it out.
Like what's like as soon as I throw it out of the cup, it turns into like a full person.
Yeah.
Stand.
Yeah, it's like, yeah, I fuck with that heavy. Yeah.
Okay. So what would I roll for that?
I mean, if you're basically just summoning him, so that's just like an action you can do.
Unless you mean you want to throw it at him so it can grab him.
No, I'm throwing it as a summon now.
Okay, yes, that's just your action.
Yeah.
Alright, yeah, so you... he looks sort of like...
Do you guys know...
Shit, have you guys ever seen Bobabo?
You know, the jelly guy?
The jelly man guy?
He's like blue and he has this super serious human face.
He sort of looks like that except he's yellow.
Um, and he just makes no expression on his face.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Yeah.
That's like, I do remember this guy.
Yes.
That's what he looks like.
What are you naming your lemonade guy?
Uh, his name is Lemon Party.
Mr. Lemon Party.
Okay.
Yeah.
You, you summon him and he has that like stone cold face and he turns to you, Patrick Yoda,
and he like gives you like a thumbs up.
Like, like, yo.
Yeah.
Yeah, he like nods curtly and turns to face the guy. So I will say that like he has an action now
and you can use not this turn, but next turn you can use your action. You can instead do his,
it could be his action and you could have him do something. So he's just sort of like standing guard
this lemon party guy who I will give some stats now and it'll make him just like a summon you can
I just made it so hard.
It's so sick, dude.
You're better at science than you thought, Patrick Yoda.
Oh shit, maybe I actually learned some cool shit at this fucking school.
I'm giving him some stats.
Okay, very quick.
And then let's give him a close-up attack.
It'll be pretty strong. And a ranged attack.
Okay, cool.
Something very simple. Okay, cool. Yeah, we can trick about another time. I fuck with him. No, Mr. Lemon party. So yeah, okay you summon him it is now
Ray William Johnson's turn
I'm going to you. I'm going to use my my matrix beam on fuck. Yeah, dude on this odd, man
Okay, cool roll for them. But I also am still kind of tripping. So I
He just looks like a normal guy to me. I'm not aware. He's a vampire
there. Okay, cool. You actually he's got pretty high AC so you actually miss that. So you
just shoot this beam at him. And he puts like his wings around him. And as it sort of like
you sort of like takes the blow kind of you just see a guy you just see a guy. What do
you see this guy do it's a guy just like put up his hand like Neo.
I'm like, holy **** that's okay. Cool. Yeah, that's your turn.
Uh uh and now it is um uh this guy's turn um uh uh Gary
Vampire's turn. So uh Gary Vampire is going to fly up
towards you, Colin, because you said he sucks.
- Wait, as a reaction, I'd like to tell you
that you said you'd save me for last.
(laughing)
- What?
- Managing memory on Colin.
- Yeah, you said you were gonna save him for last.
- Yeah, you'd break a promise to him.
- Are you not a man of your word?
- Look at his little tail.
- I think I found your weakness.
It's not being kind.
- It's honesty.
It's integrity!
It's all those things!
You see him like, frozen in the air with his claw out,
and he just sort of like, frozen pivots over towards...
Blotas, and uh, he does an attack roll.
Sorry.
And uh, oops, he got a crit.
That's okay, Colin, I get it!
He got a crit, so it was probably for the best.
Uh... oh boy.
Yeah, that's 20 damage, Blotas.
he just fucking claws you.
Oh my god.
God.
He just did?
I have 12 HP left.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
So he just like stops in the middle and turns to you and just claws you.
Just fucks you up.
And as he's fucking you up he turns to you, Colin, and he goes, "This is what's gonna
happen to you."
Probably not.
And it is now, Blotas, it's your turn while this guy, while you get clawed up by this guy.
Wait, can I use my reaction when he hits me?
I have the "this is war" ability.
Oh yes, I'll give you that.
It's basically hellish rebuke.
Do it.
Yeah.
So explain it.
When somebody damages me, I can use this on the person that damaged me and deal damage
back to them.
Okay, cool.
Yeah, so it's a dexterity saving throw.
So let's see how he does.
Okay, what's his dex?
Okay, he does manage to save, but he still takes half his half damage.
So roll.
Yeah.
He takes more damage.
So you declare war on how do you got how do you declare war?
How do you like do this on this guy?
I I don't know.
Something about about me is that I I'm really into the army, but I don't really know anything
about the army beyond boot camp.
So so I just I you're you know,
you're kind of like an evil drill sergeant and this time I'm
going to make you drop and give me for four damage.
That is yeah, and it's just like a fire like reverberates
from your you say for damage for his chest.
Yeah, he gets burned from that though.
And it is now your turn, Colin.
OK, oh, it's sorry.
No, it's sorry.
It's what's up with the reaction.
I'm so sorry. That's right.
And then I'm going to I'm going to see neck right next to me. Yeah.
Hmm. OK, I'm going to hit him with my cool sticks,
which are there.
They're devil sticks, but I lost the yo-yo part like a year ago.
So yeah, do it. Do it. Do it.
OK, that's a six.
Yeah, you just whiff. You're just like swiping at the air.
Yeah. Oh, I do have an additional attack though. I'm
gonna do it again. Go for it. That's a nine. You continue to
whiff. Uh yeah, you're up, Colin. Okay, well, first, I'm
going to do Colin's insight. Um. Perfect, yes. So, it's
Basically, fairy fire.
But what Colin does is he's able to use his ability
to just discern things.
He's a very bright little piggy
to help give advantage to his friends.
So we're gonna have our guy roll a dexterity saving throw
against your spell save.
You're gonna have a guy roll your next damn round
'cause you're a spell save.
- My spell save is 13.
- Yeah, he fails.
So what do you do?
What do you figure out about this guy?
- So I go, I have identified his insecurities.
It wasn't honesty or being mean or integrity.
it's kinda commercial
uh...
this is a great
we see a little
and i think it's here to roll down his i'd
no
that i'm going to have a good turn to ray william johnson and i'm gonna go to the
politics action
which means i'm saying out loud
I'm gonna say I can dance all day. I can prance and say Heidi Heidi. Hey, that's what Colin say
Do a
Colin's pig spiration on you so you now have an additional d6 on your next okay?
Dad some just my mouth open just drool
You don't have to use it on your next thing you can you can save that for like I think 10 in game
in minutes. Yeah, what is my buff?
So it's you roll a D six and add it to any attack roll or ability
check, basically.
Cool. You don't need to use it now.
Mm hmm. So yeah, that's a great.
That's a fantastic turn.
So you now you now all have advantage on this guy
because you guys have located his puppy nips.
OK, he's just like, no.
How he's like been naked this whole time.
(laughter)
- Amazing, okay cool.
We're back to the top of the order.
Patrick Yoda, what's going on?
- I'm just staring at his man boobs, I'm going,
(groaning)
- Yeah, you lose a turd.
- And then, yeah.
(laughter)
No, but my summon,
he's gonna attack the,
I tell him to attack the boobs.
Yeah, okay.
Cool slap that man's titties.
You see him face you and go.
He just like exactly what you said.
Yeah, and he goes to attack this guy's titties.
So let's roll with advantage.
What does he use?
What do you what does he use?
You tell me.
Force lightning ability.
I think because he's lemon.
He has a he has you want to give him the lemon.
You want to give our force lightning?
Okay.
Spark.
[Laughter]
The lemon.
Because he's lemon, he has the lemon spark.
Yeah, yeah, it's called the, it's called the zest.
The attack of zest.
Oh yeah, that's good.
Alright, so, um, if we'll give him force lightning, we'll say it takes from your techno slime to do that.
Um, if you want to do that.
Okay.
Okay, cool.
So that'll be minus five on your techno slime, um, and then roll the force lightning, um, in your chat.
Twenty.
Roll again to see if you get crit.
Twenty-three.
OK, roll for damage.
OK, cool.
It's at 5 and 9.
Nice, yes, you do 14 damage.
So he just like just used to see the
electricity like coursing through his
like lemon body and just like shoot
out of his fingertips at this guy.
And this kid, the vampire.
He wasn't here before the fuck.
It's just like just like getting
electrocuted as a less good.
I'm just like shooting lightning
out of his hands.
Yeah, he's not looking too hot though.
After that it is your turn Ray.
You're going to have to
It is your turn, Ray.
Okay, I will I'm gonna use my
My homing missiles
I have two of them. I'm gonna shoot them directly at his tits. Yeah, your digital missiles. Yeah, I'm gonna lock them in
Yeah, those those hit automatically. You always get your target. Really? Yeah, dude. It is the best thing ever
So you can do like I feel like we're doing too much too early
I feel like we should wait on some things.
No.
No, I think we gotta use it all right away.
Yeah.
Our, not only our school, but our country is in danger.
This is true.
That's a good point.
It's Independence Day.
Okay.
So I just let them fly.
Okay, cool.
And so I would, yeah.
So you just take, so that's three.
You have three you can send.
So send, you can send two more.
Okay, I send two more.
Yeah.
Um, okay.
Uh, uh, describe your kill on this.
Oh my God.
He I'm still so fucking high on beer
that as soon as he looked like a normal guy until somebody said
that he had tits and then he just turned into two giant tits
in my in my view.
And then they they exploded like balloons.
What's my my missiles hit it and then
like a pinata candy flew everywhere.
Yeah, fuck and I I'm like somebody give me another beer
This is awesome
No, well, you'll never defeat our other lieutenants that are inside the school somewhere. Oh
Wait, where are they? Oh nice try. Hey crap. He dies. I'll bring you back to life
You see him like he's like eyes closed for the real
Yes.
He dies, yeah.
No!
Don't worry guys, I'm an army man, I learn to track.
I can track their footprints.
And I start following the footprints where I was army crawling earlier.
Blotoss, Blotoss, stop.
Hold on one second.
While the lieutenants are inside and we're out in this field where presumably nothing
is really happening since we killed Gary, I think that we should take ten minutes to
just take a breather and I can do my Colin song of rest where you can heal some
you can heal some points. I will say there is definitely like vampires killing
people out here. You can 100% ignore that and just don't care. Let's go hide where we stole the beer from.
Yeah cool all right take 10 minutes in your 10 minutes short rests and recover
some of your HP yeah yeah Colin go tell me about it.
What's your song?
Can I recover techno slime in this?
Ok, well, actually instead of a song, actually I'll do a song.
I love you more than God, I love you when I'm thawed, I am your awesome friend, my name is Colin.
Alright, and so yeah, what happens?
Well, so, I mean it's, it's, it's, technically, beginning it, you can use soothing music or oration to help revitalize your wounded allies during a short rest.
If you or any friendly creature who can hear your performance regain hit points at the
end of the short rest by spending one or more hit dice, each of those creatures regain an
extra 1d6 hit points.
Nice.
So if you guys use, which I guess this would in this case really be mostly for blow toss,
if you want to start using those short rest hit dice, you can.
Can I use them one at a time to see?
Yes, absolutely.
All right.
Wow, and after the song is done, there's just like a single tear running down my cheek.
lemon guy lemon party also like goes back into the vat that you have and you just see his face
just sticking out of it that guy thinks cool he looks at you call and you see him like
just like for the first time make an expression on his face and it's just like it's one of like
sort of like profound pity as he looks directly at you colin i just smile back
Cameron you get to roll an extra d6. Okay. Yeah, that's cool
um
Um, but
Sorry, I have the ability to heal too, but I feel like this whole thing will
Probably won't be able to actually just go to sleep and go all the way back. So i'm trying to sort of yeah
You know, that's that's okay you
You're perfect
You're absolutely perfect. Also patrick yodar also has four skin still too. Yeah
I should have gotten rid of that one too. I guess you're 19. Okay, thank God.
They're children, so I don't want to use that.
Alright, it doesn't do... He has this ability and it does not do what it does.
But it does heal them.
Okay. That's the rule. I use my hit dice to get back to 31 out of 32 HP, so I'm all set.
How about this? How about this?
What?
A byproduct of the VAT thing gave me like a little bag that I could put over their heads and that's how the foreskin works.
Or it's the VAT guy, he pops out and he gives everyone like-
And his foreskin.
[Laughter]
He's a kid, so it's fine.
Yeah, we figured it out.
I'm gonna teach that little guy to make an experiment that will make another Patrick Yoda with a foreskin.
[Laughter]
So he just like he just gives you all bro hugs and you heal for the amount
What's up? And it's like you like it's just like very chill hugs. Well, you have an idea
He goes up and he says I'm proud of you
Cool okay. So yeah you guys did your little short rest
You're outside the school
Which looks like the you know, it basically looks like a prison you hear pandemonium and chaos still going on outside
You see the giant red dome over you, you know, it's it's it's it's gonna be tough
But you think you could probably fight your way through the school
Obviously you can go through the front door. There's other entrances in the school. You can do whatever you want. What do you guys think it?
Well, toss you are the most tactical
Do you think of you know any alternative doors other than the front door? That would be most tactical
well
One tactical move is going through the window, but I don't know if we can reach the window from down here. Here's the thing. I
like
Boys with the janitor. He gave me his keys dude. I can get in any fucking room
Listen if they're expecting us what's what I mean
What's more obvious than going through a window or a secret door or something? Shouldn't we just walk through the front door though?
They won't expect it. What if we just stay outside?
Yeah, and we use the loading dock to go in
Hey patches. Do I have any equivalent of a disguise kit?
Oh, yeah, I was gonna say yeah, I guess you do. Yes
All right
I think that it would be a great idea for me to use my clever piggy disguise kit to fashion a little a little
Adorable vampire outfit for myself see if I can trick them
I really want to see that.
Can we take pictures too?
I just want to remember it.
For no reason.
I mean, it's not like we're ever going to have to remember you.
Hey, listening.
Listen, building memories with your best friends in the world is great.
And sometimes you just need to take pictures.
I point at Colin and say, "This guy's..."
Hey, how about this guy's my best friend in the whole damn world.
Love his little damn thing.
What are you saying?
Are you saying this guy's?
Did you say this guy or this guy's?
This guy over here is my best pig friend and I love him.
I don't know what you're saying.
What does that have to do with this?
I hate this guy and I hate this guy.
That point of view.
But I love this guy.
Thanks.
You guys, I love all of you.
Can I put on my little outfit now?
Yeah, you put on your outfit. Sorry.
Should I roll performance to see how...
Yes.
Okay.
Got a crit, baby.
I'm looking like an adorable little vampire.
- You look exactly like a vampire pig.
You look amazing.
- To the point where we all get scared.
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna, well, I'm still cute.
But I'm gonna, I'm just gonna be like,
I'm gonna just explain to them
that I'm one of the new hired generals of vampirism
or whatever is going on here.
- Okay, cool.
So yeah, I mean, there are like, by the front door,
there are two vampires who are like sort of standing guard right now
so what's the uh... what's it's what do you think
okay i'd like to try to up to them and be like
you guys i'm the new boss in town actually
uh... and i i have these prisoners here
that seemed actually extra delicious and i'm
student knowing what's delicious because i'm you know
uh... and uh...
I'm taking them to the head guy, Mr. Kiss-a-lot.
[laughter]
Um...
So, just let me through.
Roll persuasion, uh, with advantage, obviously.
Oh my god!
God, a crit, god damn.
Damn, they just go,
"Well, as you know, his name is Mr. Loves-a-lot, but that's okay."
[laughter]
I'm so important that I don't pay attention to that.
Right this way, sir. And they just sort of open the door for you.
And yeah, I mean, you could see what's going on inside now.
There are vampires, like, you know, attacking students and teachers cowering behind the students.
And you see sort of that, I mean, like, if you want to know where they're going, I mean, I'm sure they can tell you.
So he's in the gym. The Mr. Count Lovey-Lots is in the gym.
the
sad about it. Oh, oh, no. Oh, oh, wait.
Well, that's good. That's fine.
Thank you. Thanks. Where would you say who's who's like the second from the lowest tier
of in our ranks here? Third, then? Yes. Let's we think. Oh, oh, oh, I need. Thanks for probably
Probably I've I'd never came up with a name for her
Madam boobs
On me that would be so scary
Yeah, the other ones all have like either a low effort name or a pun, but her I just made madam boobs. Okay, uh
Yeah, so she's in the auditorium. They would tell you so
You could head over there if you'd like
Okay, yes, of course
And yeah, you guys
Say you guys walk over we because of that disguise and because of your story like yeah
Like you guys walk over there with very little interference
I can I say I when we're walking there
the one of the school
Army recruiters like run by he's being chased by a vampire
I see him and I'm like, oh this this guy right here is my best friend. Wait guys
I have to show my push-ups and he just he just he just runs and runs back towards the vampire
Yeah in the school where army recruiters follow every student home
They all hate blow to us about joining the army.
Yeah, okay.
So you get to the auditorium, you know, it's a big lavish auditorium, but as lavish as the arts are deemed to be in gun city and you see center stage that beautiful vampire woman.
And you see her weaving her hands as all these men and gay women are doing a performance
for her.
And she's like, "No, no, no!
It's all wrong!
It has to be like this!"
And she's trying to perform and show them how to act and do all these things.
She hears you guys sort of come in and she looks at you and says, "Ah!
Who is this and what have you brought to me?"
I am Colin the pig-pire.
And the vampi- I'm Colin-
Say- hey, say- say "ham-pire."
Say "ham-pire."
Um, I like- I- I am Colin the ham-pire.
YAAAAY!
I've brought you some delicious things.
Also, I must say, you're very beautiful, but I- I am asexual.
Um, so just don't-
I understand the effect I have on people and I just, you know, before anything happens,
I'm an asexual kind of character here.
So I'm being presumptuous, but it isn't due to...
I don't recognize you.
You don't recognize me?
Really?
I don't recognize you.
Mr. Loves-a-Lot hired me to specifically go through each of his admirables, admirable
admirals, and um, to discover how admirable the admirals are.
Okay, roll, roll persuasion.
Alright, um, uh oh.
Okay yeah.
She looks at you and she says, and she looks at you and glares at you, and she snaps her
fingers and like the door shut and a spotlight goes on her and she says I
used to live in gun city you know I was an actress a real one too in Hollyweird
not like those whores in the clubs at Raytheon Square I was starring in
pictures holographic VR I was even in the first movie ever to be shot in the
Matrix 2, but I was getting old. At 19, I knew the wonderful men who run
Hollyweird would find some other hot young thing soon. I was worried. We still
belonged to Transylvania at the time, so I had my agent pull some strings and I
got myself turned into a vampire. I thought once you see some of the some of
the men and gay women she's a possessed or like crying at the sad story like
like very dramatically. I thought once I became a vampire I'd be the talk of the
town. Young and glamorous forever, mother wouldn't be able to say a word to me
about my flabby arms or my crow's feet or my forehead being too weird. But no one
in gun city wanted to see a vampire, they all hated them, and when I tried to act
in Transylvania, everyone was a fucking vampire! My career was over. Naturally I
joined the military, but no. On this stage where hundreds of children have
perform the pajama game and bye-bye birdie I will play my greatest role yet
woman who kills teenagers and um...
after she finishes her whole uh spiel
yeah yeah yeah
I like very quickly throw a pencil on the ground in front of her and I'm like
"let's uh I think you dropped something you might want to pick it up"
"I want to bend over and pick up that there pencil"
"yeah I'm actually asexual too yeah asexual ass motherfucker"
(laughter)
Show me what you workin' with.
Oh man, roll for initiative.
(laughter)
I thought you'd die.
Yeah, me too.
Dude, that pencil's a wooden stake.
You better keep that in mind.
Actually, pick it up and put it in your boobs real quick.
(laughter)
Okay, cool.
Okay, Ray, you're gonna go first.
So you see her, just sort of start to weave her hand.
and you see the men around her, all the people who are in
fat with her just run, you know, start to start to get
themselves ready to fight. They're all like, you know,
basically NPCs so you can do there. I mean they'll try to
hurt you but and she's sort of getting herself ready. What do
you want to do though? I will use I will use my matrix beam
hell. Yeah directly at her. Yeah so hard. Ah **** zero one.
Yeah, yeah, you try to do the.
How do you hold this damn thing?
You're just like using you're like looking at your hands.
You're just still tripping instead of like coat ones and zeros that are coming out.
It's like ABC just letters are coming out and it just like washes over her.
It doesn't do anything.
Okay, cool.
It is now mad.
No, it's actually Patrick Yoda's turn first.
You know what? I'm gonna try and do a hoverboard.
Hoverboard. Boomerang?
Boomerang, yeah. Yeah, for sure.
So I like look at her and I like pull the hoverboard out. I'm like,
"I know you ain't rocking with this!"
I hit the hoverboard and I get a crit one.
Oh no! You're all totally transfixed by her beauty.
Yeah, you just like I mean you just fall on your ass like you just try to do it do anything with the hoverboard and it's like butter in your hands.
It's like if you were holding butter and now it is Madam boobs turn and she turns to you all boobily and she opens her mouth opens her mouth.
Oh, go on and reaches.
And I need you all to roll a wisdom saving throw 14.
I got a fort.
I got it.
I got a 10.
Mm-Hmm.
That's not good.
Oh, Colin is too wise.
Yes.
Okay.
Yeah.
So yeah, you all managed to save as this screech sort of reverberates
through Patrick Yoda.
I guess you forget to put your hands over your ears, maybe.
My ears are too big.
I'm a Yoda.
Yeah, your hands are too little and you're too big.
So you're going to take some damage and then you're going to be stunned.
Yeah, it's a big problem these days.
Okay, yeah, you take seven damage and you are stunned for one round.
you're not going to be able to move or a few other things. I want to make sure I get stunned
in 5e right. It's a little different than paralyzed and it's a little different than the other
ones. I don't get stunned so you don't have to look that up. No. That's easier. It's taking
way too long so we just shouldn't do that. It shouldn't happen. We just get the fight
- It's too much. - It's a sun creature.
- Yes, now. - A sun...
You just let me finish. A sun creature is incapacitated.
- Oh, it's another condition. - This is too much.
But you can't move and you can speak only falteringly,
automatically fail strength and dex rolls.
- Right. - I can't move and I can't speak?
- Yeah. - You can speak falteringly.
- Yeah. - Moving and speaking.
Hey, Patrick, speak falteringly if you're gay.
*weird noises*
That's what I thought.
Love that interpretation of Falteringly.
*laughter*
You know, Falteringly, when you sound like a Galaxy Quest character.
Uh, okay, cool. So, that happens.
*weird noises*
I'm still trying to prove I'm not gay.
Yeah, you're doing a great job, buddy. Keep it up.
*laughing*
You're just breaking up in real life.
Um, you are up now
uh, uh, Colin.
You wanna yell at me and my
friends? You wanna yell at
me and my friends?
Oh, that makes me so mad!
*laughing* Yeah, we just heard you.
Colin, scream!
Oh, yeah.
Wee!
OK, Colin uses shatter his version of shatter.
So which means he could basically choose
where he wants this loud noise to be.
She's going to use it on her,
so she has to roll against it.
That's pretty good.
What is her con?
I don't think it's.
I like that we all have like shit that we do
and then Colin has like moves with his name in them.
He knows that he can do.
He practices it.
along with Espanol.
Oh wow, she got a high.
She got a high save.
She still takes half damage.
She still takes half.
Oh, God damn.
Pretty good still.
OK, he's so good at this,
so he got a 23,
which is literally one less
than the Max he could have gotten.
So that is going to.
We're going to round that bad girl up to 12.
So that's nuts.
Okay, so she takes 12 damage.
So you scream at her and you hear,
she puts her hands on her ears like,
oh, this disgusting pig.
Ah, and she's like,
what did you say about our friend?
(laughing)
And that gay one.
So, uh, cool. Yeah. Great turd. Call it. Um, okay. It is now a blow toss. It's your, your
up man. Yeah. Um, I'm going to, I'm going to go for it with my slingshot. I'm going
to shoot at her with my slingshot. I have a scope on my slingshot. That's an 18. Yeah.
That fucking hits brother. Okay. Five damage. Nice. Yeah. You just shoot that and you just
like get her right as she's like holding her head and screaming and moving about. You managed
like
another. I'm doing a slingshot again. Do it. This is 17. Yeah, it's 6 damage. Nice. Yeah.
Oh man, you just get it in the same spot. Dig that in deeper, making her forehead weirder.
Okay, cool. Yeah, she is not looking good. You guys did some serious damage this round.
So we're back to the top of the order and you are up Mr. Johnson. All right, I turn
the matrix beam around so that it's facing towards her this time and then I use it again
and aimed directly at her forehead. Hold on though because matrix beam costs
seven technoslime points. No. So you're at, I technically missed it last time so you really
should be at zero but you're at three technoslime points right now. And I go up and I punch her in
in
I think. Yeah. Oh, okay. I'll add that one d6 to this attack.
Yeah, go for it. This thing's dog **** Alright, let's see.
And it continues to be dog **** Yeah. Eleven. That eleven.
Yeah, you run up to her with the dong blade and you try to
swing it at her and she waves her hand and one of the guys
just goes, no, he just jumps in front of it and takes the
blow. Um uh yeah, I'm still like I'm smiling because I
killed someone.
Job well done.
Cool, cool.
Alright, you are up, Patrick Yoda.
You can't take any actions or anything this round.
So you're just sort of incapacitated and just faltering.
We could just sort of...
It is now her turn.
going to point her her finger at you Ray William Johnson and I need you to roll a
charisma saving throw. Seven. She says to you you're a big strong man aren't you?
I'm a kid.
[Laughter]
Shut up, shut up.
It's the spell.
You're instantly charmed by her.
And so,
you will not attack her.
And you will
actually follow her command
when she says to you
to go
get me that piggy.
And you go run up and attack
the pig. It's just basically what you
you are now except you're listening to her.
Um, yeah, I'm gonna attack Colin or I have to get him.
Oh, you're gonna you're gonna grapple him.
Yeah, you're gonna try to grab.
Okay, so roll guys do a strength contest against one another.
Okay.
Hey, Colin, get over here you big son of a bitch.
I've been hitting the gym lately.
Yeah.
Oh, he's so sneakily strong.
Colin, you're just able to like bat him away and crawl through his legs.
I was also like, I'm a little bit oiled up from a sheen of sweat.
*laughter*
You're just a cute little piggy.
Yeah, I squirm out.
Aw yeah, so cute.
Okay, yeah.
Nothing cuter than an oily pig.
Yeah, I don't know if that's cute. I'm like covered in oily sweat right now.
Just squirming around.
I like little pigs.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Whatever, man.
next turn. Yeah, you'll be trying for the rest of the round just for this round. So next
turn you'll still yeah. And so that's what she does. And now we're back to the we're
back into your guys's turn. It's Colin you're up.
I'm going to try to you to think hard about what her voice sounds like. And in my own
piggy brain, try to like age that voice a little bit to try to sound like a mother and
Use minor illusion to be like those crows feet will get deep and you'll be ugly with your weird
Forehead and look at what you've done you actually that's colin's ways. Look at what you've done
Oh, you got your weird forehead even weirder and now none of the producers are going to want to kiss you for a role
Oh
Darling, look at what you've done to yourself. So ugly
Okay. Yeah, uh, I guess you'll roll against that. Um
the
is what that was is an investigation check against the Spellsave DC.
Okay cool.
Which is 13.
Okay, so let's see how she does on that.
Her investigation is not anything special.
Oh yeah, she beats it and she says "My mother doesn't talk to me anymore!"
Okay, then I'm gonna gasp and as a bonus action, turn to I guess, Blowtoss, and say "Remember
Remember that time at Sarah's house party when you were afraid to ask Rebecca to the future
style dance and then you did and she said no but you took it like a champ?
You are brave.
So remember that.
Um, so, uh, I'm ironically inspired.
Yeah, you're inspired.
You got these six years and you're up.
Um, yeah, I'm so inspired.
I'm so inspired.
I'm thinking of the girl, this girl who rejected me.
I'm looking down the scope of my weapon at a time when I'm not.
I'm like, I'm so inspired.
I'm so inspired.
I'm thinking of the girl, this girl who rejected me.
I'm looking down the scope of my weapon at a time when I'm not.
I'm like, I'm so inspired.
I'm so inspired.
I'm so inspired, I'm thinking of this girl who rejected me, I'm looking down the scope
of my weapon at a new woman.
I take aim and fire my slingshot at the same spot again.
That's a 19.
That's 7 damage.
Let me see her, where's her health at?
Oh it's not good.
Okay yeah, she's looking pretty bad.
I'm just doing it immediately, just doing it again.
Yeah, I'm, yeah, I'm...
*laughter*
That's a crit.
I mean, you're gonna have to describe your kill and
whatever else you want to describe,
I'm absolving myself.
*laughter*
Um, I, yeah, I just start, I just
start rapid firing the slingshot,
just like pulling it, but like, like shooting it like a
machine, at a machine gun rate.
Um, and then, yeah,
and then I see the, I see the pencil
that that um Ray William Johnson dropped on the ground earlier and I'm like
that's it and I pick up the pencil and I launched it out of the slingshot it's
the final shot and it goes right through her damn heart oh and guess what she's
heartbroken now yeah she's like oh no oh she's very dramatically dying just like
yeah like and you watch as she she falls to the ground dead her hair splayed out
out and she's like looking very like pristine and and and
then you watch all the guys around her who were just like
like there's some of them were still like some of them were
still in the shape of a wheel because they look like a
carriage earlier and they just like sort of like fall like
what am I what's going on here?
Damn, she's dead.
Yeah.
Yeah, you guys get her.
Thank you so much calling for inspiring me.
You stirred some deep-seated emotions within me,
and I think I better understand the reasons
I want to join the army now.
(laughing)
- I'm happy that I could be of help.
Just dry those eyes and let's keep on truckin'.
- That's right.
- So you guys defeated one of the second lieutenant.
Now there's one other.
- Am I fine now?
- Another guy, yeah.
Oh, you're stunned for the rest of the day.
Yeah, you're fine now.
(imitating gunfire)
I'M NOT FUCKING GAY!
*laughter*
A little late on that one.
Yeah, all these people who are just no longer possessed are like
"alright, alright"
They're just like clocking that and just trying to ignore it.
Um, do you wanna do...
BUT I WAS STUNNED!
SHE HAD A- SHE USED POWERS AND SHIT!
I- GOD DAMMIT! THIS SUCKS!
I'm saying like everything that I was saying.
I've just been repeating myself on and on.
*laughter*
I just want to reiterate, I love you guys so much.
I love Colin!
I can't stop screaming right now, I'm so mad!
You're pretty much our best friend in the entire world, and I know we're gonna-
After this is over, we're gonna have probably thousands of adventures together.
It's gonna be the four of us together forever, going on missions and adventures.
I- I clap.
Before we go to the next lieutenant, I wanna- I wanna smoke some damn techno slime in the school auditorium.
I can't lie. Yes, brother.
I'll light up. Fuck.
Wait, I got a question about these.
Since I'm doing spell slots
and I have something called techno slime refills, am I able to?
Yeah. If you Colin can only will smoke techno slime if he wants to.
I don't want Colin. Colin can do whatever he wants with.
Does it? Will I get spell slots back?
Is that? Yeah, I think let's do that that way.
I think Colin is just absolved from the addiction system.
Yeah, I think that Colin is like Colin.
Yeah, Colin exists in like a different magic system
that every other character in the game.
He's the only person in the entire universe who has spell slots.
He's the only one.
Magic is real.
[LAUGHTER]
Sure it is, Colin.
Magic is real.
I've seen the face of the old ones.
All right, sweetie pie.
Man, I'll have what he's smoking.
How many spell slots do I get back?
I would say you get once.
Well, let's say two slots per techno slime.
So one level two or oh shit.
One level two or or one like or yeah,
or like two level ones and that's for each techno slime refill.
Yeah, that's not much probably.
Yeah, five.
Yeah, let's just do like.
Maybe just one slot per one.
I think that's OK, cool.
And then would you be okay with me finding a way
to use TechnoSlime to rejuvenate Bardic Inspiration at all?
- Yeah, I think that's totally fair to do that.
We can just do that one for one as well.
Just like maintain it that way.
- Yeah, I'm gonna pull out, instead of TechnoSlime,
Colin's just gonna pull out a very old looking book
and like his eyes are going to go a little bit blank
as he stares at it.
And if you guys look at it,
there's just no writing on the pages.
*laughter*
Go Khaled! Go Khaled!
My father gave this to me, and my father's father gave it to him!
*laughter*
Okay!
My father cryogenically froze me from Whoville! Either that or he's me!
I'm not- I'm not sure!
*laughter*
Um, okay, cool.
How many techno slime points do we recover from a refill?
Is that full?
No, you get five, five.
Oh, perfect one.
So you got to get them out.
So do I, do I smoke it too?
Yeah.
I mean, techno slime is a drug you can take anyway.
Okay.
Then I guess 10.
Techno.
Yeah.
You can take a shit too.
My shit.
Yeah.
And so when you do, as we all know, you got to roll the constitution
saving throw, which just, it's just going to be against a DC of 11
plus your proficiency bonus.
So 13 to see if you suffer from addiction.
Okay, I got one.
You're going to roll a wisdom save.
Okay, I think we all well.
Uh-oh.
Okay, all lost.
Yeah, older than time older than time as yellow as the aged
pages of this book.
Mountain escaping as far as the eye can see.
So you only get three points back and you have disadvantage
on Dex rolls of any kind.
So, uh, like saving throws,
dexterity checks for the next in game 10 minutes.
So it's not too bad.
That's just the first level.
Um, so yeah, you're just kind of fiending a little bit, um, scratching maybe.
Um, but that's, it gets normal for the children in this universe.
Um, okay.
I, I, I didn't really get what I wanted out of that.
So I'm like, fuck it.
Let's hit it again.
I'll rip it again, dude.
All right.
Roll another constitution saving throw.
There's no way this one will go bad.
Oh, it didn't. Okay, great. So you just just have the first
uh failure effect still and I get five for that one and
you'll get five for that one. Yeah, you get the full five.
**** that beer **** That **** too hard, man.
Cool. Yeah. So you guys are just sort of lighting up in the
auditorium. Um it's the dead vampire on the ground um and
Yeah, so you can try to find the next lieutenant.
Can I can I roll investigation to see if I can find anything cool
on the corpse of a vampire?
Oh yeah, me too.
Me too.
We're all going to do it.
We'll just have one.
We should all probably investigate her body.
Of one check that 16.
Yeah. All right.
Cool. That's 16.
That's pretty good.
Before we reveal what he got from her,
Ray William Johnson, what's a crit
wanted being a female body investigator?
A dead female body investigator.
Yeah, I closed my eyes and I'm like,
I'm like rubbing the like her like heels.
I'm like, these boobs are humongous.
Oh my God, she's so hot.
Even then she's dead.
Oh fuck, I'm gonna bust dude.
And then I opened my eyes, I'm like, I'll stay doing this.
I'd like to close her eyelids and then whisper something that no one else can hear into her
ear.
Yeah, you do that.
You do that.
And yeah, Colin, with that 16 you find a pendant that was on her neck, you know that you're
able to sort of like, look at and sort of get the sense that there's something a little
bit more special about it than just being a pendant.
Wow, Colin, you should hold on to that and you could pass that down to your
children and they could pass it down to their children's children and they could
all pass it down through your very long family line. It's extremely prosperous.
The Colin name will live on forever. Exactly, I'm an only child so it really drives my penis up.
And after your parents of course, you know, your father got his
vasectomy and your mother's sort of at that age now so it really is just
you. They didn't need any other kids. You were perfect. A
culmination of eons. I'm just thinking about how all your
your hundreds of ancestors way back thousands of years how they
all came together to create you and it's just so beautiful. I
smile and not go many into one. I'm a little bit weird now
after the thing with the book.
the
sure. Okay. 12. Yeah, I mean, he has like civilian clothes on. I put on his shirt. Gross. It's
like bloodstained, but go on. I put it on and then I realize how bloody it is. It's
also big on you. Yeah. He's like a full-size human. And I take off the shirt. I was like,
I thought that shit was gonna look tight, but it didn't.
*laughter*
Patrick Yoda, you have all kinds of bling. Do you want to wear this cool pendant that I found?
Oh my god, Colin, thank you so much!
This will look great with the rest of your bling!
Oh man, and it's a perfect 26 inch chain on me 'cause I'm so small!
*laughter*
Yeah, exactly, here you go!
Oh!
Yeah, Patrick Yoda.
This is the best day ever!
As you put the pendant on, it starts to glow a little bit.
And you hear, you hear, um, uh, Madam Boobs.
Madam Boobs.
Come in, Madam Boobs.
This is, this is, this is Klaus.
This is Klaus Kloekske.
I'm in the basement.
How's the auditorium going?
Over.
Hey.
Hey, baby.
Hey, girlfriend.
*everyone saying hi*
I think we did it.
Hey! Hey!
Perfect display.
I don't realize that it turned off and I'm still just doing the "Hey".
Hey!
I will cherish these memories for the rest of my life.
So yeah, you guys can go to the basement.
Now imagine Patrick Yoda, if you're friends with the janitor, he can actually show you how to get there.
Yeah. Do I still have his keys?
Yeah, you have his fucking keys.
Yeah. Okay, yeah.
So yeah, you guys walked down the hallway and you find sort of the door to one of the sort
of where you would go.
I say, "Hold on.
Let me just check something real quick."
And I open up the janitor's closet and he's dead inside.
He's dead inside not because of a vampire, but because he hung himself.
Oh, shit!
No!
Man, I told him if he was gonna jack off like this, he had to tell me!
Shit, man, this is worse than any death that happened on this school today.
You have such a special relationship with that adult.
I wish I could have one of those one day.
I probably will.
Man, I wish you could have met him, Colin.
You probably, honestly, you actually probably did.
We both go to the same school together.
Yeah, I was sort of friends with him too, but not as much as you.
Oh man.
He helped me with my espanol.
I'm gonna miss this fricking old piece of shit so much.
I think I need to investigate his body.
Yeah, you can do that.
Okay, I roll an investigation check.
20.
Yeah, hell yeah, dude.
You find a letter he wrote.
It's entirely in Spanish.
You see a lot of...
Yo, Colin, I need you to read this for me real quick.
This one's in cursive.
Somebody take this.
Yeah, it's a lot of Te Amo and things of that nature.
It's clearly a goodbye letter to somebody.
Why does he keep saying my name is?
Wait, oh my god, I read this mentioning I'm like, oh my god. He was secretly a vampire
I'm learning star and s so I still don't I don't exactly know what this means, but i'm still learning
Yeah, um, yeah. Yeah
and him, uh, um
Whoa
I
is the tallest closet of all time. He used to shoot me how to smoke cigarettes in here
and throw rope over that pipe. And he used to tell me everyday if I was going to kill
myself it would be here on a day of the vampires attack. Man I just don't know why he did this.
Does he have any cigarettes around?
Yeah, there's some cigarettes.
Yeah, he's got a lot.
I want to try one.
Yeah, for sure, you can go for it.
Do you guys have a light?
I have fire abilities.
He has a light, come on. Yeah, he's got a light on him.
You take his light, you want to try one, Colin?
Yeah, I have a lot of time
to learn about the consequences
of my actions. Now is really the time to make mistakes.
Yeah, go for it, Colin.
You smoke a cigarette.
cigarette.
Nah man, you inhaled.
You're not supposed to inhale cigarettes.
Carla, you might, you might, be careful, you might develop lung cancer later in life.
Please.
Yeah, now you can really take some years off your life way far down the line.
Yeah, I think that I'll, I've learned from this and going forward for my long life of
healthy, healthy living so that I can live long and enjoy my family and my kids.
I, uh, I think that I've learned a lot from this.
I think that I've learned a lot from this.
Please.
Yeah, now you can really take some years off your life way far down the line.
Yeah, I think that I've learned from this and going forward for my long life of healthy
living so that I can live long and enjoy my family and my kids.
I think that I'm not going to do this anymore, so I put it out.
Wait, no, no, put it out.
Give it to me.
Okay, I blow on it a little bit to re-spark it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I hand it to...
How do you know how to do that, Colin?
I thought that was your first cigarette.
My uncle's kind of weird.
So yeah, you guys, I guess, see this dead body and then you walk towards a you go down a few a couple of flights of stairs. You find the basement, the door to the basement so you can have the keys you can go in and you see that like it seems like it's just you know basement has like a generator has, you know, a couple other sort of a classic sort of accoutrements and basements of schools.
and beyond see like a vampire anywhere or like anything like that.
And this is as low as the school goes.
You're pretty sure wait guys.
I see ancient Spanish hieroglyphics on this door.
What does it say as for 10 see ya?
Oh, that means warning.
Yes, there is a more of it says warning on it and you can try to use
one of your keys there, Patrick Yoda. Yeah, there's 50 keys on this ring. Okay. You try
all of them and roll 50 d20s. Yeah, none of them seem to work on this door. There might
be another way to get in it though. Don't worry, guys, I learned about this in the army
and I run into the door head first. Okay. You do? Yeah, you do. You bang on the door
And you hear it sort of reverberate around you and you hear sort of like that behind it, it's a lot
bigger, whatever's going on behind there. You sort of get this sense that there's sort of a much
larger room behind there. And as you sort of get the sense of also where you are and everything
gets around, you see like little, there's obviously like tons of like little hideaways and little
vents, little corners. You guys could probably start figuring out sort of another way to get
get through that door or at least like another way to get into that door.
I'd recommend just start snooping around.
I start snooping around.
Me too.
Okay, cool.
Can I go with the 50d20 roll instead of the 11 that I got?
I got a 25 in this.
I got a 9.
I got 11.
Ray, you sort of look around you and you sort of are still kind of tripping a little bit on beer,
and it gives you sort of a clarity in terms of the environment around you. And you see like a
little vent and you see like two pairs of eyes poking out of it. And when you see them and they
see you, it just poofs away or runs away. I don't see anything. That was weird.
What was weird? I think I've come to a realization in my beer trip. I think that we are all one
one beer. Evangelion moment over here. And also there's some eyes in that door.
Yeah, you see the van, you see the eyes pop out again. And you see like, I immediately fucking
three stooges of and you realize it's it's a little Michael the crawler who's
crawled into the vents hey Michael you need to buy some oh no I'm good right
now man okay what are you guys doing down here what's going on do you know
what's going on no I've been in the vents all day it's where I'm always at
Oh shit, man. There's a bunch of vampires and like everyone's mad at each other and they keep fighting what?
Everyone's mad at each other
Yeah, it's pretty much nailed it. Oh my god. I hate that. I hate that. Oh, that's awful
Do you guys have my vent?
Yes
Okay, you see he's he's smaller and as a kid
So it's just like a face and two feet and a flat hat on his head
He sort of waddles over and opens the the vent.
Great.
He's like, come on.
I know some cool places you can go and he sort of lead you guys
in the vent.
He's flopping around and he makes a right and then it opens
up to his like, this is a really cool.
Oh and he looks down and this was like a big sort of area
behind that door where he usually goes to hang out.
But now he sees all this fucking shit.
They're like tons of like inexplicably.
There are like lab tables there.
You see skeletons of students who got lost down there before, lost homework sheets and notebooks.
You see a full class field trip that goes to underneath the school world.
And they're just all dead in the school bus. And in that cavern, you see tables, beakers,
test tubes. You see a MIDI organ far to the back that keeps playing Bacata's box,
staccato in fugue in D minor type beat.
Like it's just playing that over and over again.
And to the right of this organ, you see that nasty rodent looking vampire.
The one that you assume was on the pendant call before.
And he seems to be like working on some sort of cylindrical contraption that has several
hard plastic tubes jutting out of it.
And they're flush against the walls of this cavern.
And each of them are linked to different glass incubation pods that hold humanoid looking
figures that appear to be a bit vampiric like he's growing vampires and even recognize faculty
and students in the tubes and some of them are losers but some of them are really popular
too.
He has several of his vampire rats stalking the grounds caverns.
None of them have seen the notice you yet because of where you are coming through the
vent but they're looking around and like sniffing around and stuff.
Michael the crawler's like this is not yeah I usually go here and I just do dip but this
is awful.
Oh crap.
*everyone laughing*
We have guests bring them to me rats. You see the rats as they're coming towards you guys. What do you guys want to do?
The rats don't seem to react to that
As they're bringing you dragging you down
He's like you fools. Don't you see this is the perfect breeding ground for the vampire army? No one cares about public schools
No one in your stupid city will notice that right beneath their upturned snouts a menace grows bigger by the day
A vampiric threat that will threaten their existence
Soon, I'll be able to infect not just mortals, but computers. That's right
Vampire computers. Wiggity wiggity what now? You computer demon!
Why don't you volunteer? You could be my first vampire computer
Imagine an immortal computer that sucks data from any source in the galaxy
the
right now you're a pedophile.
That's not even how that would work.
If you don't kill yourself,
then you're a pedophile. I'm sorry.
That's just how it works.
Unfortunately, this is true. I'm a ham-farter by the way.
And I have to say,
as Mr. Lovesalot,
I'm Mr. Lovesalot's second in command,
you know? I'm his secret second in command,
his second hand command.
Second ham.
I'm familiar with the parlance.
the
grow the army and then all of Transylvania's might will invade.
No, I understand that but why are you playing around with kids?
It's not all children! Some of them are faculty!
And what if the rat's under your control if you're a pedophile?
I'm not playing with them! I don't control them, we have an agreement!
It's not all kids is a very weak argument for what you're doing here.
That's a good point.
*laughter*
Your honor, it wasn't just kids.
Yeah, aren't you saying it's better because you're mixing adults and kids together? Is that-
Yeah, just, you know, I said it once. I'll say it again, if you don't kill yourself right now, you're a bad boss.
Honestly, I'm prone to agreeing with the guy. I think, you know, uh-
Which guy?
Patrick Yoda, this-this guy.
Okay.
Oh, yeah, no, I'm agreeing with my prisoner here, which I'm not prone to do cuz I'm a pride
Don't believe you you came in through the vents
You don't even know about being sneaky like a vampire
Are you even of your pedophile and probably not even a vampire? I am a vampire. How dare you?
Say that say that I'm not a vampire
His eyes are looking back and forth like he might not be a vampire.
Wait a second.
I'm leaving!
You're fired!
I saw you fade through the wall earlier.
You're fired.
You can leave.
On behalf of Mr. Lovesalot, you're dismissed.
Go diddle kid somewhere else.
Even if...
[laughter]
Even if I'm dismissed, I will make the vampire computer.
Rats, seize that demon!
And yeah, roll for initiative, guys.
Oh, dude, now I'm...
like the star or something is sucks.
Oh, I'm like the famous one in this episode.
This sucks.
That's got nine.
I got an 18, baby.
There you go.
That's some big money moves, right?
I'm going to get some some guaranteed crits.
That's not come on.
What does that mean?
It's not going to happen.
Come on.
I have the assassinate ability.
Oh, right.
I have the assassinate ability!
That's my fault that you have to say that, so...
Okay...
YES!
Okay, Blowtoss, you're up.
Okay, um, without missing a beat, you know, slingshot right away with advantage.
It's a crit already, it was gonna be a guaranteed crit anyway.
That's 12 damage.
Fuck yeah, dude.
I'm going again, I'm... do I get... can spells have crits?
Yeah!
Okay, I'm yeah, I'm gonna use my oh wait is that right kind? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. What am I saying? Yeah
I'm gonna use my my second there the poppy chucos bad kid firecracker
Which is I hurl a firecracker at him if and if it hits he takes fire damage and
Flammable objects ignite so I'm thinking maybe you know
maybe he has some like rats on him that I could set on fire and and and do
something cool with that or something you know what let's see that's 20
with advantage that hits okay so it's a guaranteed crit - so that's - I just do
yeah 10 damage take 10 and then 10 12 yeah I mean you fuck this guy up really
badly I gotta not give you that ability you just fucking just fuck him up you
He's like, he's like, get them my rap.
He's just like you just shoot like two like fucking slingshots in his throat and then you
just like throw a firecracker down there to light it and you see some of his record squirting
around on fire just like going nuts.
If there's anything that the army hates more than foreign countries, it's pedophiles.
Yeah, he does not look good.
At all.
his
roll on you. Don't touch me I'm a child!
You guys are so mean to the cat. That's not gonna stop him.
Yeah you're giving him advantage. What's your AC Colin?
Uh 10. Yeah he bites in and he's gonna suck at your blood. It
tastes delicious by the way. Yeah it's so good and he
eats. He eats 10 damage off of you.
He just sucks your blood and you see him like sort of his
wound start to heal up a little bit after that.
So and then it's going to be your turn Ray.
Okay.
I think I have enough for my Matrix beam now.
So I will be using my my beautiful beam do it on this on
this perverted pedophile.
*laughter*
I don't know, yeah you just have literally the worst luck of today.
Yeah, you just, yeah, I mean it's just like-
I just throw my gun on the ground.
You know what dude, I don't fucking even want this thing anymore.
Dude, just fucking, whatever, turn me into a vampire, I don't give a shit anymore.
I just don't want to have to roll anything ever again.
Whatever man.
Yeah, amazing. Okay, it is your turn.
Colin.
Okay, um, as I'm getting the blood sucked from me, I'm like, Hmm, I wonder if I should use a power to distract you by making a child appear over there.
But I say that out loud to him and then I go, haha, just kidding. And then I just go.
*laughter*
Okay, yeah, he's gonna roll against that.
Oh, got him.
Oh, and that was so tactical! You totally got him off balance
by distracting him by explaining one strategy
and then using another!
That's a classic army technique!
Thank you! I appreciate that!
He got a crit
resisting that.
Does that mean that he takes none?
No, I think he still takes half.
I haven't heard of that rule, but...
I don't think so. Cool. Okay. Yeah. So yeah, shatter is still, I mean,
I think you're, I think you're still going to kill him. Okay. Yeah.
I, um, do I kill him? Yeah. Roll three D eight. Did you roll for the,
Oh yeah. It's 13. It's not, it's a low roll unfortunately. Oh, okay.
Um, does that kill him though? No, it gets very close though. Uh, yeah.
You just screech at him and you see the bat like,
so he's like to flap his wings like, ah, fuck. Like he's just like,
or flying way worse.
And it's super effective and deals double damage because of echolocation.
Bats have very sensitive ears.
Okay, well at the very least he's blind now because it ruined his senses because it was
a loud noise that ruined his echolocation.
I would say yes, as long as he remains in bat form for one round he's probably in trouble.
Yes!
Okay, and now it is your turn Patrick.
I'm just gonna throw the hoverboard.
Sometimes you gotta.
Yeah, describe your kill.
You don't even have to roll for damage.
I'm like, just trying to think, like, what else can I say to make this guy admit he's a pedophile?
And I just kick the tail down because I'm thinking too hard and it spins around and hits him in the head.
Yeah, yeah, he's like, "OW! FUCK! SHIT!" and he just like, crashes into the machine, which blows up,
And it's fucking all the tubes break out all these like vampire like, uh,
court, like half vampire people like slide out of the tubes.
You see the rats all just like flop over on their backs and just like
deactivate almost. Uh, yeah, you guys killed him. I mean, that was so fast.
Yeah, he's just dead.
I live with you on our team. We kill, we defeat all our enemies so easily.
I know that this is good.
This is the beginning of a long and fruitful partnership in combat.
yes I agree we've been friends for so long but who knew that we could kill
together as well first the janitor and now this bad guy I mean how often do you
kill two pedophiles in one day this is beautiful
Just on another level today. I do I do a little cute dance for you guys
So as staff of the machine explodes the debris sort of falls away you see an elevator to gym
Is right there. So if you want to take that
Jim I want to look around for anything in this sciencey place
It looks like it will make me feel more healthy like heal me. Yeah role investigation. Yeah, I'll say that you find
a healing potion or equivalent so but I would say instead of 2d 4 plus 2 it's 1
d 4 plus 2 a sort of a weaker healing potion
Oh, damn Collins luck. Um, so six
um
and then um
I know what eight plus six is that's fucking easy for me
Um, yeah, and then is it okay if we just take a breather here for a sec, I I just i'm I i'm
remembering things about my my weird uncle that this guy kind of
of
the
ability to
Work through problems in my head. I have completely come to terms with what's happened in my life, and I'm fully mentally healed
Thank you guys for bringing that to a conclusion now. I can go on with the rest of my life
That will be long and prosperous
Without any unneeded trauma lingering at the back of my head. You're gonna live forever Colin
That's my game
*laughter*
You see uh, the vampire
that he just killed, uh, Klaus Kloosky
on the ground
and he says
"You gun city vermin
we will rule you
again!"
*laughter*
You think you guys are getting away with this
this terrorist attack?
After the gun city military
out about this we're gonna fly over your country we're gonna bomb the shit out of
the vampire State Building Transylvania station - and you're a pedophile bitch
So yeah, what do you guys want to do? You can go right up to the gym.
You gotta get to the gym, dude.
The elevator's right there, yeah.
We gotta fuck this guy up.
Yeah, you guys go out in the elevator,
leaving all the like half vampire half people,
like corpses just like in this basement area.
You see Michael the crawler just like holding back vomit as he tries to clean up the little place he likes to hang out in.
And you guys go up the elevator to the, and you see that it opens up where like, it looks
like lockers would be, but it's just painted over and it's just an elevator door.
And you walk out in the hallway and you see the gym and you see that the gym had these
like three locks on them.
Then you see that they're open now from killing the lieutenants.
And yeah, you guys can just walk right in there.
And when you do, you see in progress sort of like a sports ball game happening, but it's
a scrimmage with Count Love-ya-Lot's vampires are going up against each other.
And he's watching this game go down and he sees you all come in and he sort of immediately
stands at attention all his vampires stand up around him and he goes "sports
ball is a delicious game you know they say you non-vampires were able to become
free because of the ingenious games reliance on the type of tactics that
echo those of guerrilla warfare you've done an admiral job defeating my
lieutenant" and he like flicks his hair back and like and like all the like all
the vampires go "Huuuh" like Psy.
Uh, um...
Why? Why do you defy us?
You could join us.
Take over Gunn's city.
Make it your own. We'll
install you as leaders of the colony here.
I don't want a stupid
widow's peak!
How about I install you into
my asshole?
How about that?
I look to everyone and go like,
"Pretend I didn't say this."
Hey, you suck.
(laughter)
Oh, Garland!
All the vampires are like, "Yoooo!"
(laughter)
You gotta chill, Garland.
I see. I'm hyper.
(laughter)
You made your choice.
We'll play sports ball to the death then.
And, uh, yeah.
So, you guys are suddenly a peer
lined up on one side
of the sports ball arena,
and
that
up and it's solvent he's holding it by his head and he pulls up another frog
And it's just a real frog
That's pretty good actually much cooler
Yeah, he's just like in the field and like eventually you guys figure out how to usher him off
He's like, okay
ready set arm play ball and yeah roll roll who's gonna be like the
Quarterback who's like so there's four be like I'll be the quarter. Yeah, there's like basically four four roles here
There's somebody who dribbles the ball and throws it
There's somebody who hits the ball with the bat
And then there's somebody who has to head the ball in the goal
And then the fourth person would be whoever is like helping defend everyone. That's kind of how I want to break this out in this
I'll play defense because I have Warren so I can't maybe I'll be the guy who hits the hits the ball with the stick cuz
I got my cool sticks like Colin quarterback, dude. Yeah
Okay, and Pat
Patrick Yoda, you're gonna you're gonna head the try to head the ball into the golf golf hole at the other end of the gym
Yeah, he's got the putter. All right
Okay, so we'll start with first athletics check will be Colin quarterback. Okay, the 20 fucking baby
Just inexplicably so fucking good at this
Yeah, it's as perfect your dribble the ball around and like do some like fucking
Like Globetrotter ass shit on these guys
Ray William Johnson roll athletics to see how well you defend them -
Yeah, okay, we'll resolve that then we'll resolve your thing right, okay, yeah, so I'm going to
look at Ray and say
Ray ray ray, okay
Come up with this shit I feel amazing right now. Okay. Yeah rolled d6 added these next ray I think to this
Thirteen
Hell yeah, baby a very a very a very respectable
Blocking job you do you you're able to sort of help sort of like get some of the guys off of Collins back as he's dribbling
And Colin your smooth moves just help clinch it you get to all you why didn't you try out for the team Colin?
You're incredible
But I only have so much time and so many things to do like
Espanol hang out at the cyber beach with my friends
Have the best summer of our lives
But time
Yeah, so you uh, yeah and your smooth moves just like put you in the best position to
toss the ball to blow toss. So you're going to toss that with advantage to blow toss and
another athletics check on. Nice 16 is a pretty decent toss. So blow toss the way that this part
works is it's you and another vampire are fighting to see who's going to get to hit the ball. So
I also I still have a bardic inspiration leftover that I didn't use. I just want
Hell yeah. Okay, cool. So if you want to, you can either hit the ball or try to do something to him
or whatever. I think you have a moment beforehand where this was happening before he threw the ball.
You know what I mean? Yeah. I think I'm just going to slug it. I'm going to do my best to-
Yeah. Go for it.
No fancy stuff. That's a 13. I might as well add the DSA. Can I wait to see what the other guy's
result is before I add it. Okay, I'm going to go ahead and add it might as well. That's a three.
So 16. Nice. Okay. Yeah. And let's see how the other guy does. Yeah, no, you just edge him out.
You guys are both going for it. But your stance is just far superior. You got that real classic
Mike Piazza stance. I got the army stance. Yeah. And you slug it. And now as you slug it, it's
going to go towards a group of different vampires and Patrick Yoda, as you are all going to try to
of
uh, the sort of basically all successes that have happened so far.
Um, so you're going to clinch this for everyone.
What's your, what are you going to do?
It's a, it's a soccer ball that you're, yeah, yeah.
I thought it was a golf ball.
No, it turns into a golf ball when it goes towards the hole.
Okay.
That's the final ball.
Then I, I, I still have the putter.
Okay.
Yeah.
So all the vampires are using their feet, but I just have a putter.
[laughter]
Okay, cool.
And I'm swinging, I swing the putter at the ball in midair.
Yeah, roll with advantage.
12.
God, okay, cool.
So yeah, you hit that, and let's see how they do.
They do beat you out, so they manage to get the ball first.
And it's going towards the hole.
So what-
Can I get in front of it?
Yeah, I'll say you can you I'd say you can kind of think of it like this. All of you guys can nominate
one person to try to redirect it. And that's sort of like your chance to redirect it before it goes
towards a whole athletics role. Right? What's everybody's athletics? I don't want to minus four,
- five yo big demon that's right mm-hmm
This is I I wish oh my god
It's like something right it's like you got a guy a weird fucked up bug in your computer, man
Yeah
You just I mean you Lucy in the football it like the ball like asks you to come kick it and then it pulls itself
away from you. And you just fall on your ass. Yeah, I was so beaten down by these rolls
at this point. I don't even get up. I just yeah, as it rolls towards the hole and the
vampire score point and they're like, ha ha, that's one point for the vampires. Okay, okay,
we're gonna play. It's two or three best two out of three. And if you lose, you forgot
To mention that if you lose you die, but yeah, that's what happens. What is beat you up and we lose
It's not a big deal. No
Take a look at these guys and see how tough I think they are if we were to just like
Pretend like we were about to play and then instead just try to kill them. Yeah
What should I roll inside? I guess yeah inside inside
Yeah, uh, the vampires are not the toughest. He's pretty tough the other guy
You could probably take them in a fight, but you think could we get a surprise attack in?
Yeah, I think so if you like break his rules
I believe in I believe that there's no way that I get another
correct one roll
So I think we should we should rely on our athletic ability here and not yeah to violence just yet
Okay, okay
How about if one of us fucks up really bad one more time, we just instantly break out
into violence.
You're beautiful.
You're saying this in your huddle.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's amazing, coach.
Okay, cool.
Break.
So, alright, you're all gathering up again.
Also, I'd like to bardically inspire Ray William Johnson and, again, and just be like, it's
impossible for you to mess up again.
You got this.
You're so strong and smart and honestly I can't wait until we're best friends and we're old men together
and we have a beer and remember the good old days and
And then I our wives are friends too. So I guess it's more
We're friends. We're all friends
So beautiful Collins
That it was amazing it's turned over obviously is a turnover back to you guys
So you guys actually get control of again so we can do all that again. So Colin you first
Okay, pretty good
Okay, Ray William Johnson start blocking. Oh
Fucking amazing block you deck a couple guys you'd like lay some guys out. What's up? Yeah, I'm calling
Yeah, Colin as you throw it
a
for you, Glowtoss, on this hit. Okay. Roll again. 21. Okay, 21. Okay, and advantage for
you as well, Patrick Iota. 21. A crit. A crit. Oh, baby. You fucking just like take your
little putter and you just fucking nail it perfectly. You just like get the soccer ball
right and it just perfectly falls into the hole. It turns in midair, goes, turns into
to
That was really funny, Blowtooth!
[Laughter]
Thanks, Colin! You always know how to make me feel like the best guy in the world!
That's because you are.
- One. - Whoa!
Hey, but what about me, Colin?
I think that you're also the best guy in the world.
I can't believe that four best guys in the world all got to be friends at the same time.
And forever, too.
- It's so beautiful. - One more point.
and
my
a perfect spiral basketball throw
yeah roll again cam with advantage
fuck yeah
i mean they're not the vampires not going to be able to beat that
and now patrick yoda
it's all up to you
fifteen
alright they're gonna roll against that
let's see how they do
i'm watching this happen
biting my fingernails and they're just flying all over the place
as he connects with it, blow toss perfectly connects it
right in that sweet spot in the bat.
It flies in the air,
go vroom, turns into a soccer ball.
And you just see this crowd,
like in slow motion of vampires all going around.
And Patrick Yoda's so small,
like you could kind of see him sticking out from the top.
And Patrick Yoda, you sling your arm up in the air
and as the putter's going up in slow motion,
just dunk, like just fucking like breaks
one of the vampire's jaws, like breaks another one.
And like with the blood on the putter,
you get it perfectly it falls towards the hole
you guys with it
outlawed you lots
he shrivels up in his big coat
uh... no
no
if you lost
the pride it's straight of the nation of god city
yeah i'm dying a little bit of a little
No!
In celebration, I grab what I think is like a cooler full of Gatorade and dump it on Colin,
but it's just blood.
It just gets carried.
Yeah, um, actually, it's not blood.
It's boiling hot oil.
What?
I don't know.
I screamed.
what
newt ginger
it
you see these vampires right over with those
with a big giant buckets they can't they just stick it through you call it
They put you on a rotisserie
starts spinning around.
Oh my god!
What the fuck, man?
Wait, what?
This is a-
Oh my god, they're running to Syrinia
but they're also- his guts are coming out!
This is the most violent death
I've ever seen in my life!
His eyeballs are hanging out
on his brain!
Oh my god!
Colin's still kind of alive, and just
Call me says I can sit on a bed. I can draw the color red. I can pat my own head
Uh, i'm just a complete shock
Like when the brother in hereditary knocks his sisters
Yeah, we all just stand there for a minute and I turn we will never speak about this ever again
*crying*
Colin, do you have any last words?
Um, hmm...
Hmm...
Nah, I just shriek again.
*laughing*
*screaming*
I hope this summer never ends!
*laughing*
It won't, Colin, I promise!
He's gonna be spending time at beach in heaven, at the beach in heaven!
I hope they speak espanol up there!
As the vampires die, and the coffins fly up back, and the force field goes down, and an
One easy but welcome quiet washes over the blood-soaked grounds of Gunn City Public High
School.
The survivors of the invasion slowly start to pick themselves up and dust themselves off
while you're all watching this horrible sight of Colin dying.
Sullivan the Frog, who besides being in this void behind his back, was also hiding in the
bleachers, crawls towards the center of the Stakehams Arena past the corpses of his peers
and the vampiric dust that litters their gushing wounds.
He spots the microphone among the carnage.
He gently picks it up, wipes off some viscera stuck to the head of the thing, swallows back
some vomit, and then goes "Hello?"
And there's no response.
People are still cowering, they're awaiting their heroes.
He goes like "Hello?"
And then nothing still.
People are still afraid and scared.
And then he finally...
*clears throat*
Gunn City, brrrah-p-p-pah!
Gunn City, brrrah-ka-ka-ka-ka-ka!
Halliburton-
He starts to sing the national anthem,
and slowly everyone comes out and starts singing it together,
and as the Gunn City flag superimposes itself
on the image of all the other images you're seeing,
as the three of you walk out, carrying Colin,
He looks delicious.
I have an apple in my mouth at this point.
Yeah, you do.
And you guys saved your school
on this wonderful Independence Day
freeing it from the vampire menace.
Epilogue, though.
Somewhere on the planet of Suckafuckabob,
an old Yoda senses a stirring in the air.
He feels the rise of a new age.
He's a young man,
but he's a man of his word.
He's a man of his word.
He feels the rise of a hero of his own, but something dreadful looming over the horizon.
Seized by narrative import, he drops his hot cocoa he was drinking, burning his nephew's
foot, and stares past himself and the world around him.
The shroud of weird guys has fallen.
Begun the Vampire Wars half.
Happy 4th of July everyone.
Happy Halloween!
This is gonna be the best fucking Christmas of our lives!
Woo!
It'd be funny if Kai died like right after this game.
[Laughter]
I get hit by a truck.
Or one of my friends, of course, with my leg.
[Laughter]
[Music]