you're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content!
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately!
[explosion]
Round two. Are you recording, Patrick?
[music]
Yeah.
Round two.
[music]
Trying again.
We had to stop. We tried to record this episode one time.
We got 20 minutes in and
And we got hacked.
No, Caleb's internet.
[music]
Not true.
I was- I was- I was- I was-
Caleb was gnawing on his ethernet cable.
Wrong.
What did you guys think of it?
I was a victim of a DDoS attack.
Yeah, by your own- by your own
rodent-like teeth chewing on your ethernet cable.
No, no.
You were a victim of a dad's-
dad's dick-awned sucking.
No, I was a victim of a- of a
DDoS attack from a, um,
from an un-
from an undisclosed-
I was a victim.
Yeah, a victim of being a rat and mouse
combined. No, no, no, that doesn't even make sense. You're crawling around a room on a horse. That's called a hamster and it's a very popular animal.
No, that's called a rouse. That's called Caleb the Rouse. It's not called Caleb the Rouse. Caleb the Rouse is not a, that's not a
cryptid. You crawl around under your bed, you chew on cables, you chew on cheeses that you find and you get stuck in traps. If I was a mouse,
I would simply buy cheese at the store,
eat that, and not bother anybody.
But so you know what you would do.
He would get kicked out of the store for being a mouse.
Yeah, you--
He'll kick you out of the store,
nobody gets kicked out of the store.
You get kicked out of the store for being a mouse.
Yeah, yeah.
If ratatoing taught me anything.
It didn't, it didn't, clearly.
Have you seen Ratatoing?
No, I haven't.
I know of it, though.
It's on Amazon Prime.
I have seen it, but it didn't,
I didn't relate to the mouse.
the rat and you thought you wept open no no you know you are all the characters
no Patrick Watson thought he's a it was a mirror no you watch yeah because you
were you were like this is my cousins he thought it was a mirror and he thought
the big tall guy was Caleb was like oh my god my family's big break they all
got that dream including me the main character the Patrick credit or Patrick
crawls Patrick crawls into his parents Patrick can't hair Caleb crawls in his
parents bed cuz he's scared of a nightmare that he's fine sometimes
thunders crawls in from the bottom of the bed up mm-hmm he gets under the blanket
goes in between them and he goes in and then he and Patrick tried to crawl back
into his mom no I didn't yeah I had to crawl back into your no Patrick tried to
crawl back into his mom back into your mom when you know went into their bed
Patrick saw Patrick saw Bill and Ted's excellent adventure and he said I want to
time travel so he crawled back into his mom's pussy.
No.
And his dad's penis.
Yeah, but you're a mouse and a rat combined.
And he fit better into his dad's penis because he's so small.
You crawled back into your mom's pussy and you, whenever your dad's penis went in, you
went "whoop!"
And he fucked it.
Patrick is, Patrick is, Patrick is, scared you?
Patrick is one.
Whoop!
Latched on.
No.
Yeah, you hung on to it and your dad freaked out because he was like, "There's a little
mouse!
biting my peepee.
Patrick is one molecule big.
Patrick is one molecule big and his webcam is a microscope.
No.
It is.
Caleb is a Webkinz.
No.
Yeah.
You're a little penguin.
You have a little W in the code.
I'll fucking shoot myself in the head before they chip me.
You're a little penis.
Shoot yourself in the head because they already got you.
No, Webkinz have the mark of the beast in them.
They don't.
They just have a number that you use online.
The W stands for winning comma God.
They believe God wins.
No.
- It stands for winning Charlie Sheen.
- Were you guys, neither of you were raised
particularly religious, but were you ever,
it was the end of the world ever explained to you
as something that like-- - No.
- No? - No.
- That's like all anybody talked about
when I was growing up.
Everybody, do you guys know about the Left Behind movies?
- Yeah. - No.
- So there's this movie series for the fat guys
who don't know what I'm talking about in the room.
There's this movie series called Left Behind
and it's about the biblical tribulation,
which is a seven year period between
when the beginning of the apocalypse happens
and when God finally ends the world.
- Oh my God. - And it's basically,
it's awesome.
It's about, 'cause Christians--
- You almost cut out again.
- No, I didn't.
- Yeah, you did.
- I almost did, but I didn't. - That's why I said,
"Oh my God."
- Oh, I thought you were just so scared.
- Oh my God. - Of the tribulation.
(laughing)
So I was taught growing up that what would one day I would just wake up and if I
didn't believe in God I would just like go downstairs and I would make breakfast
or whatever and then I would look around and my parents would just be gone.
There would just be piles of clothing. Yeah there would just be piles of clothing and I
would have to fight people yeah on this in the streets Mad Max style for
the next seven years until I finally get to die. Yeah. That's the other thing they
- I said nobody can die during the seven years.
- Oh, that's sick.
- You can't even kill yourself.
- Oh, you can just do whatever you want.
- That's true, everybody's a superhero,
but if everybody is, nobody is.
- So it's kinda like you are going to heaven.
- It's kinda like the Incredibles.
- Yeah, wait, wait, wait, let me get this straight.
I can't die and the parents are gone.
- Yeah.
- And I'm the one who's gonna be in hell?
I don't think so, buddy.
Sounds like paradise to me.
- And seven years, I mean, eternity's too long.
I would only, like, seven years of heaven?
- Seven, seven, - Sounds amazing.
- Seven heaven.
- Yeah, at the pedophile dad from the show.
- Yeah, seventh heaven.
Yeah, you tell me this.
- Have you ever watched that show?
- No. - I had no idea.
Like I knew that there was like,
obviously like the dad's a priest or whatever,
but like I--
- I don't know anything about that show.
I know the name.
- My cousin would babysit us and she would watch it,
so I had to watch it a bunch.
Like I watched that show.
I think I watched that show more than like SpongeBob
when I was like six.
- Damn, dude.
Yeah, I hated it.
Yeah, sounds bad.
But it's just, yeah, it's just like,
there's a whole episode where like,
the son, his name's like Simon,
and Simon like, becomes friends with these kids
who are huffing spray paint.
Was it like the drug episode?
I miss the drug episodes.
That was their drug episode.
It was fucking spray paint.
They should have a drug episode in every show.
Wait, we should do a drug episode.
We've never done one.
That's a good idea.
Wait, hold on, hold on.
You guys, I've, do you guys wanna try this?
Yeah, what is it? Come on? Oh, come on bros. Let's light up
He just what are you? What are you? Why are you? Why are you lighting one end of a dildo and putting the other end in your butt?
I'm
Cuz it's a new drug man. It's called it's called Cameron. You're smoking on a peener wiener
I'm not you guys are you guys for madness, dude
No, I was actually testing you guys
To see if you this was a combination drug and gay episode. No, and you guys passed the test. Yeah
Also, all of our grandparents just died and we have to cope with it. Yeah. No, they disappeared. Yeah, they got taken up in the heaven
What about a heaven just for grandparents? All right, that's enough of that. We're gonna move on. There's no Florida
There was a left-behind kids book like like kids series for kids my age
Your age right now?
Kids yeah kids who were 23
It was so now I can start reading it.
For adult kids
That's like when they have like ages 8 to 108 on things.
They probably are gonna do something like that's gonna because right now everybody
There's so many people our age who are into like young adult fiction and young adult movies
they're gonna have to make like a kid adult like a old young adult they're
gonna have to make a kid adult they're gonna have to go in a lab and make you
put Jeff Goldblum in a teleportation device oh yeah with a kid yeah they're
gonna fuse him with a kid and he's gonna have like a he's gonna come out wearing
overalls yeah can I um can I play with toys please I love Percy Jackson yeah the
last time I read I what books did you guys read growing up like what was your
like I love I was into this this book series called I think I've talked about
this called pin dragon oh is that the one where they um where he goes to the
different rounds read that shit yeah he goes to the different realms yeah I read
the shit I know you read that do you remember the write up your fucking do
you remember the first the bad guy was named st. Dane
Yeah, he had a dog's name. Yeah, do you remember in the first book? He goes to like he just goes to the past
He just goes to pre-world war two in New York and like tries to stop the Hindenburg disaster or something. Yeah, and
He were he hangs out with like this bellhop or something that like fought in World War one and they call it
They call it the Great War. Yeah, and
Like that's what they called it and at before he leaves and goes back to earth. He tells that guy's like listen
you keep talking about this great war I gotta tell you there's another great war
that's gonna happen and it's gonna be way worse and the guys just like shit and he
just goes for a walk that's the perfect if somebody tells you the Holocaust is
gonna happen yeah I'm not gonna try to stop it or anything but man I need a
bellhop dude what is he gonna do that's yeah he could block Hitler you are not
allowed to stay in my hotel. He could go to Auschwitz and say no Jews are allowed in here
yeah he could say he could say excuse me Hitler sir may I take your bags and then
steal the bags yeah that contained all of the plans to do the Holocaust. Yeah Hitler didn't know what to do yeah he had to write he's one of those guys
had to write everything down or else he'd forget.
Oh no!
And he stole his moleskin notebook that said "Do the Holocaust."
Ah shit, I had so many things written in that.
God damn it.
I know I'm forgetting to do something today.
Oh my god, all of my mom's old recipes were in that.
There's something I'm supposed to do this year.
I'm gonna forget, yeah, if I don't write down the New Year's resolution I'll forget it.
I just walked in.
That was his New Year's resolution.
Yeah, 1938.
Adolf Hitler was like, "This year, I'm finally gonna do it."
Yeah. I just walked into this camp and I can't remember what I walked in here for.
Yeah, I guess I just need to leave.
Yeah.
Go back to watching TV.
Those books rocked.
Yeah, they were sick.
I read like...
Fuckin'... I read like mostly graphic novels.
and tracks Tony Hawk's autobiography why really is his like four kids
autobiography I know a lot about Tony Hawk's like kids his his one it was like
a schoolastic like Tony Hawk autobiography and it had like it had like
a bunch of facts about him in the back it was like Tony's favorite band is and
it was Devo. What is it? Devo? Yeah. Damn, it's a terrible band. He had also had a track of
um, it had like a playlist of his favorite songs and I listened to. You listened to the
playlist? Yeah, let me look up, let me look up this book. I was super into these books
called Cirque de Freak. Oh yeah, you and Ben. Yeah man, I loved those. I reread them like
last year because I was I remembered them like being like I was just like I was
super disturbed by them as a kid I remember being like super gory and they
weren't that gory but there was a bunch of stuff in there I was like oh man they
shouldn't be selling these at like book fairs there's a bunch of scenes where
like people get their like intestines ripped out or they like you're like
looking into the eyes of their friends while they're dying and like they're all
like it's they're very violent they're not that's cool yeah man the fucking the
Tony Hawk autobiography I read as a kid was just called Tony Hawk professional
skateboarder. That's it. I mean what would you want it to be called?
What else would it be called? I don't know like the legend and adventure of Tony Hawk. The legend of the
Birdman. Tony Hawk's my struggle. Yeah. Yeah I mean that seems like a normal book name
about someone to me yeah I mean it's I don't know like boards the Tony Hawk
story I don't know is something like that like Tony hot like okay so there's
another one called Tony Hawk occupation skateboarder that sounds like a like a
something Donald Rumsfeld has a file
skateboarder Tony okay there's another one Tony how did I get here Tony Hawk
the ascent of an unlikely CEO. How did I get here? He's just confused. Yeah. On the
halfpipe dot dot dot with Tony Hawk there's a good title. That is what that
should have been the first one. Yeah how did I get here book is just a stream of
consciousness of Tony Hawk writing like where am I what what what is this
typewriter doing here? Yeah he writes on a typewriter. Well he woke up and he has
tattoos on him that say "write a book" between board slides and burnout my notes
from the road by Tony Hawk. Tony Hawk wakes up and he's covered in memento style tattoos
that just say skateboard. It's all the trick names. I guess I'll do a 720. It says
There's judo air on my wrist.
(laughing)
Why does it say dog piss?
Yeah.
I would always go to the Scholastic Book Fair
and try and get the, they always had like a joke book
or two.
Oh yeah.
So I would always grab the joke books.
I used to get the joke books.
I would get the joke books and the cheat code books.
My favorite thing about the joke books,
the one, I got one particular one
that I think I still have like in storage somewhere.
and it was just like, you know,
it's called like a thousand jokes
to tell your friends or whatever,
but it was clearly from like the turn of the century
because all of the jokes were about leprosy.
(laughing)
And I, like one of them was like,
was like, what do you call a leper in a bathtub?
Soup.
And I remember going to my dad and his,
while he was like working, I was like,
hey dad, what do you call a leper in a bathtub?
Soup. - And he was like soup.
is what I was and my dad was just like I don't even know what that's like yeah
that's it that's one old-ass book yeah we should write a joke book that might be
the best yeah we should definitely should write another book yeah a joke book
would be a good genre you know when was the last time you saw a joke book I found
you and I wish I had there was a I had the there was when I was in Edinburgh
there was I was staying at Aaron's place and they like um they just had this bookshelf that was full
of books from like the previous owner and there was one there was just like this joke book where
just none of the jokes made any sense at all and I can't remember them but like they're all just
stuff like like what uh what happens when a bully there's a schoolyard fight and then it said the
answer is like there's likely to be a collision it just like just it just like isn't jokes I wish I
had it oh that's that classic British way yeah that's that's like British humor
yeah that's like Stuart Lee that's like Stuart Little that's exactly like
Stuart Little Stuart Little did I'm imagining a Def Jam comic named Stuart
Little who's never heard of the movie I'm reading the table of contents of the
Tony Hawk book yeah I bet you are. That should take you a day or two. Yeah. That'll keep him
occupied for a while. Yeah yeah there's um there's a chapter called chapter one guys
there's a chapter 15 is dad slams whoa chapter 22 is cancer stinks yeah 25 is
1999 the year of the nine. Imagine being Tony Hawk. Being Tony Hawk like a guy who a guy who
we grew up like skateboarding or whatever like you know probably it was pretty rough and tumble and
then you go to write your biography and they're like this has to appeal to seven-year-olds.
Yeah. Like you the the one that the chapter you wrote that's called fuck cancer in the ass you
You have to change it to "cancer stinks."
Yeah.
And you have to cut out all of the text from it, except for "I don't like cancer."
And you have to take out your drawings, Tony.
Yeah.
Your drawings cannot be in the book.
That whole chapter about your divorce and what you were going through, that will not play to kids, man. I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Did he get divorced?
You should also, you should probably take out your log of every single night while you were married.
Your detailed log of events.
I mean not because it's not for any content reason it's just like 500 pages
long and we can't put that in the book. You logged a whole year. Yeah you
spent way too much time writing down what you ate for dinner every night.
We're not gonna be able to put that in the book. Imagine going... And we're gonna have to change the title from
The Dinners of Tony Hawk. It's gonna have to be called Tony Hawk Occupation
skateboarder. Imagine like going to a bar and you see like a you know a
sultry minx just waiting for somebody to buy her a drink and you're like can I
buy you a drink? She's like yeah and you get to talking and you're hitting it off
and you're vibing and then eventually you come to the point of the
conversation where you ask occupation and you're like yeah I work for H&R
Block what do you do? And she's like I used to be Tony Hawk's wife and I just
have all of his money that's not too far off from how from how you met your wife
Margaret Margaret Hawk yeah she kept his name yeah dude you know that I'm taking
her last name Hawk is the coolest Patrick Patrick Hawk yeah how'd you get
that last name I married Tony Hawk's wife
you know she saw some crazy stuff in the bedroom yeah there's security footage
like the like the whole sex tape it's just standing on her the snowshoe ads
that the what like the ones with steve-o where he's the human skateboard it's all
stop-motion yeah he did that with his wife yeah he was into some real freaky
shit now he'll never come on their show yeah you will Tony Hawk will never come
on the show now yeah that's a reverse jinx he will come on the show he was on
Hollywood handbook Hollywood can't fucking get him we could get him
Hollywood handbook where they have 50,000 more listeners than us we can do
Yeah, we can get Hollywood hamsters.
They just made a show called Hollywood Hamsters.
What's that about?
What do we do in Hollywood Hamsters?
It's a bunch of hamsters that live in Hollywood.
Okay, well.
Anything else?
You got anything else?
Nope.
All right.
No, but did they do anything else?
No, they just live there.
Do they know that they're in Hollywood?
I mean, they're just like...
You don't talk, so it doesn't really matter if they know or not.
just hamsters talking or well not really talking but it's just hamsters like
saying like names of places in LA like like the comedians do out there yeah
yeah where like your whole joke is just that you're saying like the street name
like oh yeah the 7-eleven near Sunset and Pico yeah yeah and people go crazy
you guys ever run until you start wheel at Silver Lake yeah that's what they
And they're like, "Yes, I do. I do know that."
Yeah.
Until you name like a street where like a single Mexican family lives.
Right.
Everybody just has white eyes.
Yeah, they start booing.
Boo!
Go back to the places we live.
Yeah, the Glendale Roscoe's Chicken is better than the one on Sunset Strip.
Yeah.
The Silver Lake Roscoe's Chicken where all the employees are white.
yeah man i'm fucking i'm thinking about rosco's now fucking so good that's good yeah
yeah it really was they really did live up to the hype yeah it's really good it was really good
i see why all those rappers go there yeah very good very good uh ambiance for rapping very good
you know yeah the fact that they always have an instrumental dj premiere beat yeah running in the
background it's very conducive to the rap lifestyle yeah that's why it was good
for me because I could sit there rap like a freestyle yeah I in big red letters as
you walk in on a sign that says rapping allowed you can sit in the wrapping
section or the no wrapping section I don't like you know why I don't know I
was saying it like smoking or no smoking hmm yeah it's cuz Patrick walked in and
said please not the rapping section yeah I don't wanna I I can't I can't rap I'm
just I'm just a white boy if you put your mind to it yeah dude I can I can't rap
did you guys read Percy Jackson when you're gonna do a crazy white boy right
I think they should make I'm gonna surprise you guys with a crazy white
alright then do it that's why I fucking talking and do it yeah well I'm not
gonna do it now yeah that's what I thought that's like me that's that's out
character that's like me telling a story that goes nowhere yeah one time in high
school me and my friends saw a t-shirt that said let's go play and then I asked
my brother if he could eat dinner with me that's a bad story yeah my brother
actually had a he had he had like five or six video games growing up so a kid
story is like is like yeah my mom was driving me home and I jumped out of the
car and I and I tried to beat up my teacher and tell her that she looked
ugly pregnant and then here's a Cameron story that's right I don't have any
get it yeah get it because I've had a boring life I have his camera's lived in
a single cube all oh yeah life I said was a little sealed away you've been
yeah can you imagine how cool would be to grow up in a dungeon with ghosts and
gobbles oh my god dude you'd be so badass
tell all the funniest comedians yeah like Richard Richard Pryor yeah back in the
day you stuff have to pay your dues to guys like the dragon in the dungeon oh
Oh man, the dungeon, man.
What a great room.
So many goblins.
Oh man.
So many goblins and ghouls.
People being tortured on racks.
Yeah, there was always the guy
who was being stretched to his body's limits
on the wall across from you.
And sometimes, and the thing--
What a room.
If you knew a comedian was great,
if he could get people's attention away from that guy.
If you could kill despite the man being drawn and quartered.
The only comedian I've ever seen
find the treasure chest was Freddie Prinze Sr.
And you know, what a great, what a,
it's like a huge loss.
What a great-- - Oh my God.
I love those old stories Boston Comics tell.
Just like, oh my God,
the guy who used to just absolutely destroy,
his name was Fat Fucking Retard.
And he would go in, and people just fucking,
they just couldn't believe this guy, he was so funny.
He would fart into the microphone for two hours
and people would listen.
- Yeah, the older Boston Comics who were like,
yeah, we used to go to this place in fucking like downtown.
Yeah, it was just called Cancer.
That was the entire name of the club.
It was called Cancer, and the host was this guy,
his name was Jimmy Savino, and Jimmy Savino--
His name was Jimmy Saville.
Jimmy Saville, and he actively was
being searched for a manslaughter case.
Yeah, yeah.
And he talked about it all the time.
He was so guilty.
But he called it being on tour.
There was this big fat guy, O. Patrick O'Sullivan, he used to throw full beer bottles into the
crowd and hit women.
We loved him, dude.
Oh, he did this bit this one night.
You wouldn't see someone like that in New York.
He did this bit this one night.
It was so crazy.
He called the white lady the N-word.
It fucking destroyed.
It destroyed.
You have no idea how bad that killed.
Oh my god, dude.
Some of the greatest comedians ever.
Pussy the pussy the pussy.
I mean, come on, dude.
You know, you got Pussy the Pussy, you got, uh, the Great, uh...
The Great Vagina.
Chocolate, uh, Chocolate Bambino.
You got...
De- uh, Dennis Leary.
Yeah, and he's...
And Dennis Leary's there and he was stealing everybody's jokes.
Oh, man, Dennis Leary stole all of Chocolate Bambino's material, man.
Dennis Leary would be nowhere as the wizard of the jungle.
Louis C.K., Eugene Merman, Klu Klux Kanye, I mean these were the comedians in the 90s.
They would go up at the studio and they would fucking just destroy for six people.
Oh my god.
- Mark Maron, Mark Maron says this story about this one time
that he saw a French, he saw French Stewart go up.
(laughing)
- No, don't say his name.
- He saw French, French Stewie Griffin go up.
- French Frenchy.
- And he saw French Stewie Griffin go up at the studio
and for 20 minutes he just said, all he said was F-A-G-I-T.
- Yeah, I mean that's like truly the secret
to all the like, you know, romantic stories
that comedians tell is you have to keep in mind like,
oh, they were all on, they were all high out of their minds
on cocaine. - Yeah, right.
- There was nobody in the audience, they all sucked.
- Yeah. - Right.
It's just in some quiet, like literally like the Middle East
where everybody's like, like all the fucking,
the most representative thing of like any comedy scene
I think are those Sam Hyde videos
where he's just fucking up the mic.
- Oh my God, where John Paul Rivera has to tackle him to--
- Yeah.
- I talked to, apparently one of the videos,
I looked this up 'cause I was talking to,
you know Liam McGurk?
- Yeah.
- So I was talking to him about all that shit
and he was like, he's like,
"Yeah, I'm like the star of one of those videos."
And I was like, "I have to find this."
And it's a video where just,
apparently Sam would like bring like 20 people
who are like his fans to all the mics at the Middle East.
- Yeah.
- And McGurk one time went up after him
and like called Sam gay or whatever,
and they started recording and it's just,
it's Liam McGurk, it's like that Bill Burr set
in like Philly where he's yelling at all the like
Philly fans, but it's Liam McGurk with like 25
just like of the biggest losers in New England.
- Damn.
- It's incredible.
- Yeah.
- It's so funny to watch the Guttaman thing
and be like, oh, I recognize people here.
- Right, yeah.
- Yeah. - No, that was the craziest thing.
- I think one of the Guttaman--
- That was so crazy.
- Like Sean Carter, he namedropped Sean Carter
at the beginning of the Guttaman set or something.
Something crazy, yeah.
- And Rob Kreen, when he does the Retard Kyle video,
where he's like, "Thank you, Rob Kreen."
- Yeah, man. - Yeah.
- Oh, he just lost his mic.
- Rob Kreen? - Yeah, 'cause
Greg Scott shut down. - 730?
- No, 'cause-- - No, no, Greg Scott is--
Now Great Scott's the uh...
Well the gas is gone.
Yeah the gas is gone now.
That's what you do, you're gas dude.
They'll just do shows at 730.
Those are um...
That's true.
Yeah, those are...
The gas is where I saw Dan Licata and Joe Pera.
And Conor O'Malley.
Oh really?
Yeah.
It was a good show.
We should get Dan on the podcast.
We should do anything.
We should do...
We should do something.
We should fucking do something, yeah.
I'll ask him.
Yeah, we gotta get...
We gotta fucking figure out...
Let's make a, who are, what's our dream team to come on?
- Our dream, my dream guest on the show.
- Dream guest, all right.
- Tony Hawk.
- Maybe.
Bam Margera, but that's already been done.
- Coney Hawk.
- Coney O'Brien.
- Coney.
Coney Hawk.
We should get Chocolate Pampino.
I don't think that that's.
(laughing)
I mean, he's still in the scene.
He's still in the Boston comedy scene.
You see him, you see him every--
- You see him preying on young women at every mic.
Every night, every night at Thunder Bar.
- At the women's mic in a wig, man.
If I know Chocolate Bambino.
- Oh, Chocolate Bambino's up there.
- Oh my God.
- He's fuckin' up there, dude.
- Legend.
- Legend of the scene.
- That was one of the weirdest things
about being in the Boston comedy scene
is just realizing at some point
that everybody in it is 45 years old.
- Yeah, and then you go up and no one,
like half the time, it's like, oh, was that funny?
or did they just not understand me
'cause of some generational--
- Yeah, a huge generational gap.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause they grew up watching "M*A*S*H."
- They grew up watching, yeah, fuckin' they're like,
"Oh, you look like the guy from 'Different Strokes.'"
And it's like--
- Yeah, yeah.
And they also all just drink more every night
than I have in my life.
- Yeah.
- Just Irish fucking--
- Dude, I miss it so much, dude.
- Oh my God.
I don't miss hosting, but I miss just like--
I miss hideout more than anything.
I was thinking about it.
I'm thinking about it right now
because I'm just drinking alone.
And I just say, oh my God, if only I could,
only I could be drinking a beer in the same room
as some guy named like fucking Irish McIrish.
And he's going up--
You can just say Irish O'Neil.
Yeah.
(laughing)
Fucking Irish O'Neil.
He's doing some set about how he's like,
how he likes heavy metal or something.
Yeah.
That sounds like a killer material to me.
that long right now can i do some so let's hear some i don't know if you guys ever
heard of this iron maiden but i prefer uh... metal man
well and i don't know are
are steely dan
do another rhyme okay so what if
pakistan imagine if we took uh...
metallica and instead of metal was made out of wood what would that sound like i
think it'll go a little something like this
hello come in
That's a little bit of my like, kind of play with the format.
Dude, that's that is the best part about Boston comedy is that
like every once a week, some guy some old like 70 year old Boston
comic name. Yeah, Jimmy, Jimmy. Mr.
Well, Jimmy, Jimmy, Jimmy, the fuck, he'll walk in off the
street in a full Adidas tracksuit.
Oh, I know what guy you're actually
Yeah, and he'll try doing prop comedy without any props.
Yeah.
And he'll be like, "I saved the props
"for a paying audience."
And make little jokes like that.
Yeah.
And the best part is he kills, everybody loves him.
Dude, it's so, I don't get the audiences here.
That's the biggest reason why I stopped hosting
is I don't understand.
A guy went to the hideout, Mike, one night,
this old guy who was in from Philly,
And he just went up with a notebook and he'd been taking notes on everybody's set before him
And he started doing-
He was like, "I haven't written any new material, so I'm just gonna do other people's sets tonight."
And then he was like, uh, Sam Hyde- or Sam Hyde. Sam Hyke was hosting and he was like, "Um, alright first to host,
I'm a black guy."
[laughter]
And he fucking killed dude.
God damn.
that honestly that's so much better than like some fucking like oh it was so funny
dude like yeah I category 5 overreaction who are you talking about yeah who are
we talking about I've never talked about this guy on the show yeah but did I I
missed it I'm excited to I'm excited to be back yeah it's so funny how long
Muya stayed open like while everything else was shutting down around it like the
mic yeah like every other mic like they kind of like didn't do like Muya was one
of the only mics that stay on. Yeah man, Mooya's still going. Yeah it's still going right now.
They're doing curbside pickup. Do write a joke down on a little piece of paper. Yeah,
Gurby's hosting. He's showing up like three hours before. Yeah. Yeah, they're, they're
fucking, for the listeners, there's this guy. He's turned it into his speakeasy. Yeah. Gurby's
hideaway. Yeah. Dude, Gurby, that one time that he, that one time that he fucking went
up and said that whole set about how white women are ruining comedy and then like
after that was just it was just for just for Emerson girls had like signed up
immediately after him and it was one of the days I think it was one of the days
Ben was hosting damn dude which I think I might have been hosting I don't know I
like that for whatever reason open mics have become like the final frontier of
of social justice.
- Right, like who fucking--
- That's so funny, just who cares, dude.
- Who gives a shit?
- You're talking, you're speaking directly into the void
if there ever were one.
- Yeah.
- Right, like nobody laughs at open mics, dude.
- No.
- Nobody laughs, people just wanna say like,
like literally open mics would be so much better
for people in Boston specifically
if it was just like you say your joke
and then people go like, yeah that was good
but you could use some work right there.
That's how when me and Neil first started going to Mouya like three years ago or whatever
and we were both getting started.
It was three, it was four people there.
With De La Volpe hosted?
Yeah, De La Volpe hosted.
There was four people there every week and most weeks we would walk in and he would be
like okay there's four people here, we're not gonna like turn the lights off, we're
just gonna have like a joke workshop and it was by far the most like the productive like
like an hour you could spend in Boston Comedy.
Just because like it doesn't, I don't know,
everybody's on their phones, nobody cares.
You know what I mean?
Everyone in Boston Comedy just wants
to do their fucking thing.
Well, but that's the truth about just like
open mics in general right now.
Is that the market is so flooded,
the only people who go to open mics,
there's so many of them, and the only people
who go are other comics, and other comics,
like I mean, I don't care about anybody's jokes
except like the three close friends I have there.
You know what I mean?
I'm not gonna listen to somebody set.
It was great when it was just like us
on like the Thursday mics when it was basically just like us
and then whatever fucking dumb ass were off the street
would show up.
Yeah, man, that was paradise.
Dude, that was the best.
But then it got too big.
Yeah.
Then it got up to, you know, 15, 16 people.
15 people, that was when it started to suck.
That's really the, that's where, yeah.
I mean, that is true.
It's like when I was hosting the Muya Mike
and we would get like 11 people
and everybody would do seven minute sets,
It was easily the most fun I've had doing live comedy.
Oh my God, the first time I did,
the first time I ever ran a fucking Greg Pepper set.
Yeah, it was way back when.
Uh-huh, the Subway 2.
Subway 2.
Uh-huh.
God.
Cameron used to go to Mike's.
What are we, old men?
Yeah, we're all reminiscing about shit
that happened a year ago.
We're no better than those 80-year-olds.
Yeah, I know.
In Boston comedy who remember--
Jimmy the fucking bitch.
- Jimmy the fucking pussy wagon.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- We gotta go to like a show at like Calhoun
or like Princess Pizza.
- I was talking to Gus, I think Gus is gonna get me
some spots at Calhoun because--
- Damn. - They pay really well, dude.
- Dude, Calhoun-- - For people who don't know,
Calhoun is like a tiki bar.
- It's a Chinese restaurant that's Polynesian themed
for some reason. - Okay.
It's got like, it's huge.
It's one of the biggest places I've ever been in, I think.
Yeah.
It's like a Walmart.
Yeah, it's the size of,
it's a restaurant the size of a Walmart.
Patrick has never been anything bigger than a Walmart.
No.
He's never been outside.
Patrick walks around a series of underground tunnels.
Yeah.
He has a hamster habitat.
I'm Patrick Mohlman.
But it's in Saugus.
It's next to the Saugus Walmart.
I used to live really, I lived like 20 minutes away from it.
You used to live in the Walmart, dude.
Yeah.
You lived in the Walmart bathroom under the toilet.
Apparently they pay like, you know,
250 bucks for a hosting gig there.
Oh, that's not bad.
Yeah, so I was like, yeah man, I'll fucking,
I'll do that, no problem.
I'll embarrass myself in front of--
Soggiest townies?
The fattest people in America.
I don't care.
The food there is fucking great.
Yeah, I'll never find out.
Dude, you gotta do it.
You gotta-- - Do I?
- We gotta go to Kowloon.
- We should go to a will in this one.
- We should, honestly, if we at some point this year
do a live pod, we should do it at the Kowloon.
- Yeah, dude, that'd be awesome.
- That'd be so sick. - When I did the poll,
when I did the poll, it was basically even
New York, LA, Chicago, Boston.
So we might as well do it in Boston.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- And Kowloon is like, you can drive to it.
We could do a carpool, who gives a fuck?
- Yeah.
We'll just pick people up in a van.
- Yeah, just driving around Massachusetts,
picking people up.
- Just picking up various podcast fans,
taking them to the Kowloon.
- And making a fight to the death.
- We could get like six or seven
poopoo platters for everyone.
- Yeah, and then a special poop-he-pee platter for Patrick.
- What is a poopoo platter?
Because the only poopoo platter I'm aware of
is from A Bug's Life.
- It's like appetizers,
it's like the entire appetizer menu.
Chinese restaurant it's like you get like the why would you call it get why
would you okay if it's like a if it's a matter of my favorite it's my favorite
thing to get with people at a Chinese restaurant getting the poopoo you just
like you just like ordering something with poopoo in the name yeah it doesn't
it helps the truth is that order walked into a Chinese restaurant and asked for
poopoo and then they brought him the poopoo platter and he's like well it's
not what I ordered but I guess it's good yeah this is I know this is meant for
two people too so thank you yeah cuz there's two poos mm-hmm Patrick order
goes into Kowloon and he asked the waitress for a pea star pea star platter
asterisk he says it out loud like that yeah he's a nurse mm-hmm that in the
Kowloon adventure that's another good menu item I'm gonna take you on a
Kowloon adventure motherfucker I'm gonna take you yeah China and leave you there
I'm gonna take you on a Kowloon adventure when we go to Kowloon for the show. I'm
gonna put you through a legend of China. Honestly the more I think about it the
more a Kowloon live show is so great. It's so funny. Yeah. That's so good. We will
definitely be doing that. Hopefully. I mean if it ever reopens. Yeah if it ever
reopens and like shit. Yeah. Because I mean a Moo Yat's live show would be
terrible. We can't do that. It's not... I can't subject people to that.
Yeah. You know like I've done I think for me I've pushed the limit to that room.
Me too. I don't want to. Yeah. I can't do a fucking like yeah for 40 people or
whatever that that room holds I can't do that to people who it's like yeah I want
you to yeah I want keep liking me. I want you to save the Grinch. I can't subject you to this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I yeah leaks man when we were doing oh my god
when we were recording on John's album there there was a
There was a woman in the back. Thank God. It was somebody from from Emerson
but there was a woman in the back who was
the entire show just like a gallon of water was being dumped on from a leaky pipe and
Thank God that bitch shut the hell up kept it to herself because I was watching her the whole time
I mean that would that is like truly weaponized like shyness. Yeah, it was just watching her like
Like I was like, oh this is for once like like one of these fucking dumbasses not knowing how to socially communicate
He's doing me a huge favor right now because she's not complaining in the middle of us recording an album
But she's having she's just getting absolutely facial by do you water from the worst fucking fucking fast-food restaurant America?
The fucking pipe bleep the pipe burst at the PowerPoint show we tried to do so funny man
That could not have happened at a better point in this
Yeah, yeah, I put it put that show out of its misery
Yeah, I mean we we that was the first time I've ever hosted and I felt like oh
I'm doing a good job
Finally like I've found a rhythm and everything and then like we did the Jamie show Jamie loft this show like a week later
And I was like oh
Yeah, none of this this isn't for me. I can't do this all of my jokes fell flat. No one in the audience liked me
That's what I like to see man. Yeah, my boys thriving. Uh-huh. Yeah, just just just unable to talk in front of people
No, I like everything that I like Ben and I would try to like talk to each other
I think at one point I said like something like hey, if you don't do that, I'm gonna kill myself
And then it was just dead silent. I mean, that's probably not the audience to do that. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, I don't know. I don't know if the the Jamie Loftus audience is gonna be very receptive to be
Threatening to kill myself. Yeah, I don't know
She does she does nice. She does nice stuff. Yeah
Yeah, that's tough like five separate people in the audience dial the suicide hotline for you. Hey, are you okay?
They raise their hand and they wait to be called on
And then they say are you okay?
Yeah, yeah, you guys think apes will take over cuz here's the thing let's get out of this. This is - yeah
I don't want to talk about this
Cuz I've been watching the reboot planet of the apes video movies the videos
These are great videos, but by God are they fucking long I haven't I I haven't I've watched the first two
I haven't watched the last one yet, but the way that the apes take over is that they the humans
Create a virus in a lab
Whoa that the virus infects the monkeys and makes them really make smart, but it also but it infects humans and kills them and kills
Like what is it? I didn't know I didn't know it kills humans. Yeah, it kills
Why they get rid of the people only one in 500 humans survives. So that's why all the people are gone
So you do you guys think that maybe in the redwood forest right now the apes are building a castle
While we're all dying from the virus and the virus is making them stronger smarter and more agile
And the animal is definitely more affected by the virus
This isn't it like pangolins. It's not bad pangolins the fucking the little angle armadillo look you fucking idiot
There's no a layer. What's your dog?
Pangolian is an instrument. Yeah
Mongolian is the kind of person that works at Kowloon.
That's the fusion of Polynesian and Mongolian.
Yeah.
Well, I think that the apes are going to take over.
I think it's a different animal that's rising up.
If bats rose up, planet of the bats.
That's what I'm saying.
Now, that would be scary because we would be dealing with a whole bunch of Draculas.
I feel like lions are number one.
No.
Can you imagine if there was a lion with a calculator?
No imagine a lion with a calculator.
You know how you throw a ball of yarn down a big hole, the lion's jumping down there.
He's too smart, he's creating digital yarn.
He can't suppress the instinct.
He's using yarn on his computer.
Yeah, yarn.io.
That's what he's doing.
That'd be cool if...
That's what's so scary about that.
Because that is true that a lion's greatest weakness is yarn and it's the only thing that's
keeping him from destroying humanity yeah if the ape if apes gain intelligence and
are about to take over and then they discover apps and they just are on their
phone all day they can't take anything else app they discover Twitter playing
slithery Oh for hours a day and their their eyes aren't adapted to screen so
they all just make any of my followers do any of my followers in San Francisco
know of a good banana place?
Yeah. Can anybody recommend a good tree in Chicago? They all crash, they all join
warzone and there's they crash it and they all kill themselves because they
can't play. That's right. It's not meant for the monkey mind. Yeah. Yeah a
monkey is running around warzone right now looking for a banana yeah yeah they
see a banana clip on an ak-47 and freak out for a moment but alas they were
wrong yeah hey I don't know if you guys I don't know if you other apes are
noticing this but it seems that this guy has been flinging his poop at humans and
to do that to humans is one thing but he's also doing it to other apes you
know in the ape community has to support yeah it's not apps that destroy the ape
the ape army it's social justice they all join Twitter and they discover like
like woke let woke speak and they just yeah yeah they can't they can't fight
anymore you think there's ape racism yeah like gorillas like think of like
orangutans like as a orange yeah yeah he's a fat ass mother orange haired
fatties they're the Irish that's true if you're gonna be racist against one kind
of ape orangutan I mean I've been saying orangutan because of the the juice me too
Orangutan is just a very stupid looking animal.
- It's so cool. - Yeah, it's like
lanky Kong. - No, if there was an animal
that could do like real life magic,
it would be an orangutan.
- Why, what? - They just look like
they could do magic. - Wait, oh.
I think I'm thinking of, are they like the ones
with the flat faces? - Yeah.
- Oh, okay. - They look like mystical.
- Yeah, no, I agree. - No, dude.
- Yeah. - They look like they could
wave their arm and a wall of energy would appear.
- Orangutan, any sort of animal that has a face
that you can drive like a steering wheel is a huge evolutionary disadvantage.
True.
Because you can, I mean...
No, dude, the things that...
If I was a gorilla, I would be making orangutans suck my dick all the time.
Those frill, those handles on the side of the orangutan's face, they frill out like the
dinosaur in Jurassic Park that goes like...
Really?
Yup, and they spit poison.
That's not true.
That's true.
Orangutans do not.
No, it's true.
There's not a single ounce of poison.
Caleb, tell Patrick it's true.
Patrick, that's true.
I just heard that it wasn't.
- You're not gonna trick me.
- Dude, it is.
- From Cameron.
- Did you know orangutans could fly?
- Yeah, they extend their faces so far out
that they're like wings and they flap them
as if they are angels.
- Have you heard of wings?
- I'm not looking it up.
I'm not looking it up.
- You're not looking up what a wing is?
It's kind of like an arm with big flaps on it
you can use to fly.
- I don't, I know that this isn't true.
- It is true.
- It's a trick from you.
- No.
- You're tricking me.
- No, dude, I'm being serious.
- You're trying, there's a monkey.
- Scientifically-- - There's a monkey with wings.
- Scientifically, they've determined that orangutans
are the sexiest animal.
- Scientifically, they've determined that Patrick is a monkey.
- No, they haven't!
No, they haven't. - Patrick Fitzpatrick--
- If anybody's a monkey on this podcast--
- And this is true, folks. - It's Caleb.
- This is true, folks. - That's true, yeah.
- No, it's not true. - You're the chimp.
- I'm too smart to be a monkey. - You're a chimp.
- Not a chimp. - You're a chimp.
You're a white chimp.
- Yeah, what-- - Just because I can make
a perfect monkey face. - You look like an albino chimp.
- No, not albino.
You look like an albino chimp.
You're albino, dude.
No, just a normal...
You're albino.
No, just a shaved chimp.
You look like if Edgar Winter was a chimp.
You look like if Edgar Wright was a chimp.
No.
You look like if Edgar Allan Poe was a chimp.
That's what Patrick looks like.
Honestly, Patrick does, yeah.
I don't look like Edgar Allan Poe at all.
You do.
You look exactly like him.
No, I don't.
You guys know that shitty statue in Boston?
Anyone with bushy eyebrows, you guys say I look like.
Anyone with a bush?
Yeah, anyone with a bush.
A huge bush.
Huge bush.
I'm talking huge.
Yeah, the statue next to that skate spot.
The Statue of Liberty.
I don't know, I don't recognize it as a skate spot.
I recognize it as a P.F. Chang's.
Across the street.
(laughing)
That is a P.F. Chang's.
Yeah.
But go off, sis.
There's a, no, there's a skate spot.
You know that skate spot where you can skate
on all the Chinese people's heads?
It's awesome.
- What's the skate spot there?
- Across the street, there's a,
in front of that furniture store,
there's like these two like angled,
like ledges, like marble ledges.
And you can do like wall ride to like grinds.
Wall rides to grinds.
- Yeah, you can do a wall ride to a grind.
- Dude, you're gonna do a wall berg in the PFKs.
- I've always wanted to go there.
- There's actually a whistleblower,
a whistleblower contacted me this week
and said you're a fake skater.
- Who?
- Tara Reid.
(laughing)
Yeah.
I know I'm a I'm what skaters call a kook but I don't think I'm a fake again with that word. Yeah
Oh my god, I can say it
You can say kook. Mm-hmm with the K with the K
I'm sure that my my my New Hampshire dialect with a K and a G at the beginning. No, I heard it. No
No, no, that's not what I said. I understood the spelling immediately. No, I think so. Yeah. No someone did call me
a no comply head ass friend and yeah I saw that yeah I'm done YouTube yeah YouTube
comments are brutal yeah they're very brutal they're taking you down buddy
taking again Patrick down a peg again I I welcome my haters I don't I just like I
noticed like a week or two ago that we've just been getting like YouTube
comments on our episodes which I just like yeah they're going up on YouTube
and there's some stuff but like we had one episode a long time ago that said
like with Tulsi Gabbard does anybody know if Tulsi Gabbard is actually on this
episode or if they can you give me a stop a time stamp for the Tulsi Gabbard
content yeah yeah
and people are like there's literally no there's no discussion first of all
Tulsi neither Preston's Lump. They don't even get into Preston's Lump. Yeah where is the
Preston's Lump content? Yeah. I need a diameter. I want to know where how big
the lump is. Where on his body is the lump? Is he going to die? Yes. Yeah. No all
we haven't talked about we'll talk about it now Preston his lump is both large
and voluminous and it will kill him yeah full of cancer say you say your final
goodbyes to old Preston yeah yeah his lump is taking over pretty soon it's
gonna be lumps Preston if you know what I'm talking about I didn't know you
before the lump but but after the lump I hate you mm-hmm I can only imagine you
were worse before the lump started to sap your energy mm-hmm I will say I would
love to the lump is sapping my energy I'd love to get a hand on Tulsi Gabbard's
lumps what her lady love cancer she has cancer you found a lump when I was
having sex with Tulsi Gabbard I actually found a lump on her yeah and I found her
you told her that you found a lump as a prank yeah imagine having a girlfriend
prank I told her I found a lump. Yeah, when we were having sex last night I felt a lump.
That's like a Joey Salads, that's a Joey Salads social experiment. Yo I'm gonna be doing this
social experiment on my girlfriend. I'm gonna tell her that I found a lump while I'm uh touching a
boob. Yeah and then some black guy, some black guy he hired hits him in the head with a lawn chair.
And he's like see that's why, that's why racism, that's why reverse racism is a thing. Yeah.
Dude, it rules so hard that like his fucking, his stupid fucking profile picture of him with
that scally cap.
I haven't seen it.
Oh man, that's him trying to win the Irish vote.
You like the profile picture?
Yeah, he likes it.
Have you seen it?
He said it rules.
You said it rules.
It looks good.
Joey?
Okay, interesting.
Joey Salads?
Joey Saladino?
Joey Saladino.
It's the glare is on.
Oh yeah, that's a cool profile picture.
Patrick is like Joey Hot Dogino.
Right?
(laughing)
Yeah, he is.
- Dude, that looks good.
Jello Saladino.
(laughing)
That's my name, I'm Jello Saladino.
- Yeah, that's pretty good.
- Did you watch, speaking of Jello salads,
did you watch Aunt Myrna's cheese salad?
- What?
- No, what that is.
It's a video, it's like some guy,
he's making his aunt's cooking stuff,
his aunt's recipes, but they're all like,
I don't know if they're like post,
they're all like 1950s recipes,
like you know those shitty cookbooks where it's like,
like when the refrigerator was a status symbol,
so they would just make just like things--
Still is.
Yeah.
That's the first thing, when people walk into my house,
it's the first thing I show 'em.
They notice my gold-plated refrigerator
with spinning rims.
- Yeah.
- We don't have a bathroom,
but check out this refrigerator.
- This fridge, it makes ice.
You just have to put it in a tray,
but you have to put the water in the tray,
but it makes ice.
- I'm not sure how it works.
I think temperature may be involved,
but it does make ice.
- But it's like, yeah, when people used to make Jell-O,
'cause it was like, oh, this proves that we have a fridge,
and it's like, she puts like,
it's like a bunch of cheese and a bunch of Cool Whip
and like celery,
And God, it's like a neon yellow.
- I miss when call out culture was when you told
your friend's wife that she doesn't have a fridge.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- I know this Jell-O was made in the garage.
I know you don't have a fridge, you fucking bitch.
That's just a cardboard box.
- Yeah, you got an ice box.
- Yeah, you got an ice box, you don't got a fridge.
I don't even taste the Freon in this shit.
(laughing)
- Trust me, I would know.
Oh, trust me, I know what Freon tastes like.
Yeah, plus all the stuff in the Jell-O's hot stuff.
Yeah, it's not even jiggling, it's just wet.
Put meatballs in the Jell-O, they're still hot.
What's that, it's called like an ass pick, right?
Yeah, the thing that you use every night?
Yeah.
Yeah, it is called an ass pick.
It's what I use every night.
I'm gonna give you an ass pick lobotomy, buddy.
Yeah.
I'm gonna give you an ass pick lobotomy.
- Lobotomy.
- Low but-tomy.
- Low butt in me.
- Yeah, I'm gonna put your low butt in me.
- Yeah.
- And I'm gonna give you an ass pick.
- Ass pick low butt in me.
- I'm gonna give you a toothpick lobotomy.
- That's harder.
- I'ma just--
- It's easy for me.
- That's easy for Cameron 'cause he has tiny hands.
- No.
- Cameron does it accidentally every time
he tries to use a toothpick.
- Yeah.
- No, he accidentally pokes himself in the eye
each and every time.
Cameron has little hands and he's orange.
I keep losing toothpicks in my eye.
The lobotomies are so fun- that's so funny that they did that.
It's so crazy dude.
They were just like "Oh we finally cured girls."
Oh you stick a knife in their skull.
And you turn off their brain.
It's the fucking sim card release button.
(laughing)
- Except you removed the SIM card.
Yeah, it is funny that they named the,
it's the Rose F. Kennedy Greenway or whatever in Boston.
They named it after the one that got lobotomized.
- Oh yeah, they named it after her
'cause she got the lobotomy.
- Yeah, I don't know if that's why they named it after her.
- That's why they did.
- You know, maybe.
- Yeah.
- Where is that, the Greenway?
- It'd be funny if they forgot to plant all the flowers in it.
(laughing)
It's basically, it's like where all the big dig shit was.
Now they have a green way that is named
after the lobotomized Kennedy.
Damn, well I--
John F. Kennedy got lobotomized in a way.
Yeah, he did.
Yeah, in a way.
Yeah, it was the first bullet lobotomy.
The ultimate lobotomy.
Yeah, it didn't work so great.
It worked perfectly.
I mean, it stopped him from cheating on his wife, I guess.
Yeah.
That rocks.
It is funny that like the,
like something that women could be diagnosed with back then,
it was like being uppity.
Yeah, like hysteria.
Yeah.
So sick.
Dude, it was crazy.
It's just like she wants to go to college.
They cured it with the,
they were like, oh, we need to cure this hysteria
with a Hitachi wand.
(laughing)
Yeah.
Hold on.
Wait, you want it?
Yeah, you want a job?
Let me call in my samurai friend.
(laughing)
I'll forge his doctor's license and we'll get you fixed up real quick.
We're just gonna put you in a room for a while.
See what that does.
That was another thing that did.
A padded cell for the wife.
Yeah.
Yeah, this is called the work room.
There were like some people who made their wife go out in the shed while she was on her
period or something.
It was you, dude.
Yeah, it was me.
Or was that just a thing I heard in a sketch as a kid and then believed it is true?
Probably you heard that in a Mr. Show sketch and you believed it is true.
Yeah.
it's a white that's why I believe if I ask for change a man yeah to the
president of it yeah yeah yeah man I was watching the first that's also it's also
I think half of the people I meet in my life for David cross yeah even even the
even like people I was gonna make a joke about I feel I don't know I feel like
those two the bucket that the sketch where he like puts his hand like on his
neck and talks like a black guy. Do you remember that one?
Yeah, say it. Of course, even black people, but I don't know. I don't think that was...
Yeah, even black people with my eyes are closed. Yeah, if they're... They always are
because I have sensitive blue eyes. Yeah. You have... I learned that recently.
Blue eyes are more sensitive to light, supposedly. You have, you have like
Bosmer eyes. No, I don't. Yeah, you do. No. He's got little Bosmer ears, too.
You're a baby Bosmer.
Yeah. No, I'm not.
You're a little baby New Year Bosmer.
No.
A baby New Year, do I look like I'm wearing a diaper
and holding a flag?
No.
I'm wearing Dickies and I'm holding a beer.
If you put a top hat on right now,
you look like baby New Year.
No, I'm baby brew here,
'cause I got a brew in my hand right here.
Babies don't drink beer.
Yeah, put that down.
Definitive proof I don't have a baby.
Yeah, you're drinking a bottle, all right.
You're drinking out of a bottle.
- Yeah, a bottle of Coors Light.
- No, no, a bottle of baby juice.
- Did you know that when--
- A bottle of mother's milk.
- Baby juice.
- You're drinking juicy juice.
- No.
- You got your Bosmer bottle, dude.
- I'm not drinking any NuNu, I'll have you know.
- Yeah, you're drinking NuNu.
You're drinking Pedialyte.
- No.
- You're drinking Pedialyte 'cause you're a baby
and you need to make shit.
- You're drinking a poop smoothie.
- You're drinking Pedolite.
- You're drinking Pepsi Baby.
(laughing)
- Bud, you're drinking Pibb Cosby.
I can tell you that right now.
- I'm not, no.
- You're drinking Pibb Cosby.
- Dr. Pibb Cosby to you, buddy.
- Yeah, Dr. Pibb Cosby.
- The honorary Dr. Pibb Cosby.
He got an honorary doctorate from somewhere.
- From Temple, right?
- And I think we should give him another one.
Bill Cosby, if you're listening,
you have an honorary doctorate from the University of--
- From the Viper Biglia Institute.
(laughter)
- Yeah, from the Mike Birbiglia Technical Institute
of Secaucus.
- That would be really funny if it did get legally,
like, we created an institution called
the Mike Birbiglia Institute,
and the first thing we do is give Gil Cosby another duck,
and it's just him just being like,
"Hey, I don't wanna do that!"
(laughter)
Alright.
Yeah, that's an hour.
Um, episode 100 coming soon.
Coming soon, something very special, very particular, very tricky, crazy.
You better finish your plan.
Finish your part of the editing, Caleb, because my part's going to take a long ass time.
I'm going to put my gun in your ass.
I'm going to reflect it using my solid ass wall.
He's going to stick your gunch.
I hate it when you do that.
Yeah, I'm going to put my stick in your gunch.
Bye, everybody.
Goodbye.
the