Let me see your butt
All right, dude, this is all righty, oh my god premium episode number 100
Than the normal 100 that's right. Yeah
This is basically I put on my sexiest outfit for this.
That's not like shit.
Yeah, I can't see stupid as shit.
I don't like part of the outfit.
Where's the way is this?
No, I'm showing off.
Oh, my God, stand up, stand up, stand up.
I want to see the sexiest.
Not all your chest hair.
Let me see.
I don't want to stand up now.
Come on.
It's not too sexy.
Are you embarrassed because it's too sexy now?
I don't I don't want you to see my skirt.
OK, but you bragged about how you said.
that
We won't make fun of it. You made fun of it and you don't want to see it now. So that's I want to see it
That's how I'll get to see it. I have no problem standing up. Look at this.
Oh he's wearing it.
Hey look, I got, look at my pants.
Look at my pants.
I have no problem saying that these aren't that sexy.
Like, dude, that's a joke.
And we didn't get made fun of, did we?
No!
It's perfectly safe for you to stand up. It's fine, come on.
The real reason is I don't want to stand up and
hit all the cans by my feet.
Pat, there's a quarter right behind you on the ground.
I don't want to kick all the cans on my feet.
Yeah, bend over and get the quarter.
It's real shiny.
Pat, there's a new quarter.
All right, I found it.
No, I don't--
no, it's four feet away.
You need to--
Yeah.
Oh, wait, Pat, there's a new--
Pat, there's a new--
There's a new skateboard trick on the ceiling
that you have to grab.
You have to jump up real high.
I got some Imodium.
Pat, you should stand over the vent on the floor of the room.
Patrick, there's a diarrhea stain on your ceiling,
and you have to wipe it off.
Come on. Now we do tongue.
Stand on the chair.
I think you have a problem and you need to fish your webcam through your body.
Oh no, Pat, your chair is on fire.
You can't sit on it anymore. It's burning your butt.
I got to stop jumping on my chair.
I think I heard like a spring go.
Like, go what?
You have like an ergonomic chair.
Yeah.
How do you like it?
I don't want to break it.
I don't like those. I don't like the mesh.
and
a chair most chairs should be free.
Yeah, I agree in a free chair right now.
I'm so yeah, I know, but I think about
that I was going to be in the chair
more often than not.
Well, the thing about office
chair type stuff is that like
the quality is like increases
with the price up to like $50.
And after that, it's like
how many like Transformers
robot parts do they attach to the chair
to make it look cool?
Do when you sit down in an office
chair market chair parts,
if it has more than one lever on it?
Oh yeah, dude.
Oh, and then, yeah, you sit there and they'll look, they
they'll look like monster energy cans.
You know, they're yeah, exactly.
Black and green and angular.
Speaking of, it already said that I got carded.
Oh, yeah.
You said, did you hear about this, Pierce?
No, I don't.
No, that's no, he told you told the story on an episode already.
But we didn't.
I mean, it's yeah, but I didn't tell that with Pierce present, right?
That's the way we have a reaction.
We'll have like a fun joke to say.
You feel like you could have something funny to say about this?
I'm oh yeah, my mind is racing.
All right. All right.
OK, all right.
Go, go. I went to the quiet.
OK. All right.
You quiet now.
Mm hmm. OK.
I went to I went to Walgreens and I got
carded for a monster energy.
OK. What? Sorry.
All right.
What do you got?
Yes, I know I'm waiting for the story to end.
Oh, it's done.
No, it's done already.
No, that's it.
No, come on.
No, you like unplug the TV at the at the climax.
Let's see. Let's see how it actually ends.
I know you're just.
All right.
And then I bought the monster after I got carded.
I had to show my ID.
OK, well, you told the story out of order.
You got carded.
You bought the monster and then you showed your ID.
No, I showed my ID for the monster.
OK, he's tearing you to pieces right now.
Somebody ring the bell.
That's a TKO.
Oh my god, holy.
I was trying my best for the story to be good, but I mean,
but you read a serious disadvantage.
Can we can we all right?
Here's an idea.
We edit in the story from the other episode where you walk
it up and say, yeah, yeah.
And I and then or we could we could play it to Pierce like
the the grizzly man scene where he's shown the show the wife
like the uh the bear footage and then you're like you should never tell this story again
the way you told that story was like someone else told you that it happened to you and then you are
explaining it from someone else's memory like i didn't i didn't feel like i understood how you
felt about the situation someone paid you if there's one thing that i know the fans really
respect it's my storytelling ability you told that story like you were in a blackout and your
friends had to tell you what you did.
Mix you up the order.
Yeah, I ran around and then I got up.
No, I got up and then I ran around.
Oh, fuck.
So I guess I woke up and went to sleep.
You should and then I cleaned up my puke and then I threw up.
You should just do.
And then I and then I'm thinking, huh?
Even that would have been a good. Yeah.
Dan, I.
But yeah, I mean, it's a monster energy.
It's not a monster energy.
Alcohol doesn't have any alcohol in it.
It's got a guy.
By golly, I think it has energy in it.
But I'm a dozen years old.
It's got L-carnitine in it or whatever.
I do think that's the that's the culprit. Right.
Then we then we find that.
That's what she said. She pointed. Yeah.
Well, I already said this.
She's got you may have tried to check out at the pharmacist.
The part of Walgreens could be.
Yeah.
So this is a great start to the
they can't sell you
100 premium episodes just to do the last episode again.
Well, it makes sense.
They can't.
They're not allowed to sell you one.
They're not. It's like it's like a seat of Metaphin, right?
They're not allowed to sell you like more than a couple of Monster Energy drinks.
Right.
In case you go home and you make a really big Monster Energy drink.
That's their worry.
That'd be too much.
It would be too much.
I do. I know.
Like I'm sure you want to introduce this this this premise here,
but I love searching monster and creature on this website.
Oh, yeah, I was do I did about.
Yes, I searched monster and there's a lot of shit about monster.
And let's let's get into this fucking shit.
No, wait, do you have any more stories?
Yeah, let's hear some more stories.
I have a story.
I went to the I went to skate today and people kept sitting on the damn ledge sat on your face.
Your stories are like language arts quizzes.
(laughing)
- Yeah, it's like,
- Just like identify the subject of the predator.
(laughing)
- Pat is like so horrible at like a party too,
'cause he will,
somebody talked about something like,
like for a while, like 10 minutes,
and then Pat will be like,
oh dude, the other, he'll butt in,
he'll be like, oh, you know, your mom died.
My, the trucks on my skateboard are like really close
to giving out pretty soon.
- Yeah.
sits there. I don't I don't know why I do that. I think it's like
I think it's an ADHD thing. I don't really know. I think I
just focus on one part of the story and then like one one
part of the scent like whatever. Yeah. One part of the
sentence. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And then I get focused on that part
of the sentence and it's like, oh, I have to tell you this so
bad or else like I'm I'm gonna forget it and we're not gonna be
able to like it's gonna piss me off like my brother my brother drowned in the
swimming pool when he was four years old turned completely black and blue Oh blue
actually my favorite color blue hat you're like you're like this one at the
other like Microsoft clippy yeah you make a suggestion to change I wish I
wish that I wasn't like that I would say you're a lot more like sticky keys yeah
it's something that's something I got to unlearn but for right now it's uh you
It's just how I act.
Yeah, no, it's fine. I actually like it a lot.
I do think, yeah, it is yes and, but to a...
to like, it's like a psychoanalyst's approach.
It's actually adorable too.
It is very sweet and cute.
That's the only thing I forgot to mention.
I'm making it sound like a bad thing. It's a...
I like it.
No, I know. It's just like any time somebody mentions like skateboarding or anything
I have to like, oh, dude, like the other...
Were you there?
I thought you were doing it right now.
skateboarding yourself and then you're like, "Oh, by the way, I'm skateboarding."
No, no. Were you at the open mic the other... Were you there when the...
What?
There's this pro skater, Terry Kennedy.
Who...
Oh, so you are doing it.
He is doing it.
I just want to make sure that you were here for this.
I wasn't there, no.
Oh, he, Terry Kennedy had a mental break and killed a guy in a bar fight.
Last night?
No, no, no, no.
One of the people at the open mic that we went to, it was his friend.
Were you there?
No.
He had a one on one with me and he was like, I don't know.
For the 100th premium episode.
I just did it.
I just fucking did it.
We told you you were doing it like three times!
I don't- I don't know!
I thought it was genuinely perfect!
It's like you're playing like Wikipedia roulette!
Yeah, but you didn't-
Oh fuck!
Skateboarding to the open mic- Oh I get it.
I was trying to trace what the
linkage was, but there was a pro skater there.
No, there was a pro skater
at a different place.
We were talking about him losing focus
and bringing up stories that don't matter.
He said, "Yeah, I always talk about skateboarding."
and then told a skateboarding story.
That was impressive, dude.
You are a master.
- God damn it.
I didn't even realize I was doing it at the moment.
- That was so good.
Holy shit. - Holy fuck.
Oh boy.
- So for the 100th episode,
we have obviously very special guest, Pierce.
- All right, yeah.
- And we also--
- I just searched monster, very searched one.
I feel like I am a monster.
I feel like my intrusive thoughts
are taking over my good thoughts
and I'm becoming a bad person.
That's a perfect intro.
This is a website called Practo,
where people, they post,
they're looking for the help of doctors.
It's like Yahoo Answers, but it's for people who need doctors.
It's also pretty much, you know, let's be real,
only in India, it seems.
Yep, it's all Indian people who need,
they're in desperate need of medical help.
Isn't it an Indian website?
I think it's an Indian website.
Okay, so I'll start.
This is a real medical question. This is titled dream about
this is. When I see some dream will come about women so that
time my private part standing straight how to control and then
a psychologist response. Please I advise you to talk to a
mental health professional. I love the fact that all the
psychologists responses and and the request for help is always
so polite and it's always like please advise in this tricky situation. Please
give me the advice and they try they try really hard. Yeah, they do. There's
a lot of good advice. Take a tablet. Take a tablet. Yeah, they love tablets.
Yeah. Here's here's one. Here's the first one I found this is this is a
query entitled my pay nice is small and slime.
But you do tell my pay nice is small.
Sperm falls faster.
I want to make my panic size 5 inch fat and it take a long time to fall sperm.
Is there any good medical advice on that?
Yeah, take Ayurvedic medicine to enjoy sexual activity completely for 30 to 40 minutes.
Nectin for further information.
Consult me privately.
Really good.
Trying to get some.
Yeah, the way I first found this website.
was I just searched in quotes tummy worm because
my my girlfriend and I were talking about gummy worms.
And then I said, I have what you call a tummy worm.
And what I meant was that my penis is a worm that grows out of my tummy.
And I wanted to see if it's ever been done before.
Yeah. And then so I found it was about someone having an intestinal
parasite problem.
But then I did searched.
I searched for other worm.
There are so many worm based problems on this fucking website.
I guess.
Will you read the tummy worm one?
Because I do love that.
Tell me.
It's so classic.
OK, tell me worm.
Asked for female for years.
Tell me worm by bidding child constantly what to do at home.
He is crying.
It's two o'clock in night and I can't understand what actually do.
And the response is hello.
Liquid zental to be given in one day, either as whole or in two times.
OK, bye.
So this is a it's not the person's penis, right?
No, it's not your version of the tummy worm. Right.
No, there's a worm inside the child's tummy that is biting constantly.
And it's 2 a.m.
And the child is crying.
I told my friend Jake about this and he was like, I really can just imagine
what a nightmare it is to be a parent of a child who's crying at 2 a.m.
And then eventually you just have to log on to the doctor website.
Try your best to ask for help.
Yeah. Yeah. Just trying to describe that also.
And also it's got to be a tummy worm.
Yeah. Well, you're just using the exact words that like the kid is saying.
I'm like, there's a worm in my tummy.
You're like, I feel like a worm.
Ask in your room and then you're in the computer room and you're like,
so what is it?
And child just says tummy. You're writing tummy worm.
Tummy worm biting constantly.
and looks at the clock at 2 a.m. in the night.
OK, let's ask all these doctors.
Here's one asked for female 25 years.
The title is Pussy Eating.
Hi, my husband.
What this is like, I don't really want.
I love searching pussy.
Pussy is so good on the like.
Now, I didn't think it would come up.
I was like, this is going to be a medical website.
No, no, no, no.
Lost in translation, just ass fingering.
eating. Hi, my husband want to insert melted chocolate inside my pussy with the help of
injection and after that lick it until chocolate and my juice come out mixed. So my question
is it safe to insert liquid chocolate in pussy? So he wants to, this guy's a fantasy where
he puts in chicks. Or vagina poops. Yeah, but I guess he wants, he said he wants it
to chocolate and juice come out.
Yeah, yeah, he wants the the uncrustable.
Oh, yeah, it's
crustable.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Oh man.
Here's one.
This is a lot.
So yeah, a lot of these are about about I think it is some
gross penis stuff.
So this yeah, I'm not going to get a lot of advance warning.
I have a lot of this one.
He should see men is a dark black goo.
After a male of 35 years.
Wait, a dark black goo?
Hi, I was just having a session, and when I ejaculated, my cum was a dark black.
I am worried about it because I have been ingesting charcoal.
My baby was born silver.
My baby was born stillborn?
Is that what it said?
Silver.
Silver!
This guy's eating so much charcoal and he's coming black and popping out a silver kid.
He had a damn silver surfer, what the hell.
The advice is why were you ingesting charcoal?
It's too late to answer that question.
I have one here, this is a stomach problem, asked for a female 30 years.
My son constipate a lot.
He had a hard pebble-like stool.
What should I do?
Can I give white oats?
And this is an answer from Dr. Rakesh Malhotra.
And Dr. Rakesh said, "Do share the age and weight of child.
Give roughage and diet and plenty of oral fluids and P-E-G-orally on a regular basis."
P-E-G-orally?
E E G O'Reilly?
I don't know what P E G O'Reilly is.
I'm guessing it's ORLY and you can't read.
Well no.
No it's spelled, you know, insanely.
It's spelled O R A L L Y.
Okay.
*laughter*
I guess I've never seen ORLY spelled out.
Dude.
Is this a website run by aliens?
Wait, a new practice
*overlapping speech*
I thought it was spelled wrong, I thought it was 1L.
This is "Ask for male 24 years
having trouble with spelling and stories
please advise."
Fuck you.
*overlapping speech*
Alright, I'm gonna do an ass
lightning round here.
Alright, um...
*laughter*
Ass problem. I'm a 23
years girl, I've been getting pain in my
ass and dropsy also.
It's from five days after my delivery.
Ass finger.
When I when I finger my ass, a slimy cum like stuff comes out.
What is it? And why is it there?
Please tell me, doctor.
That's by the way, that's like one thing I love about like a lot of these.
There will be like they'll just say like I like a fucking
I like a shit in my ass or like something like that.
And then their question is not like I need stuff.
I need like medicine.
It's always like, do you guys know who put that in?
*laughter*
Ass fingering. I am addicted to fingering in my ass. Is this normal? Please suggest your valuable advice.
Ass size problem. I want to increase my ass size in a short time.
Can you give me suggestions so that I can increase my ass size?
My ass is blading. My ass-haul is blading.
I have too much pain. I have this problem for one year.
and worm in my ass. I can't sleep yesterday night due to earthworm in my ass.
*laughter*
Please suggest me some medicine and what I have to do.
Earthworm in my ass.
Due to earthworm in my ass. I can't sleep- as if sleeping is the problem.
*laughter*
They had the earthworm in their ass all day and they're like "Oh this is fine."
The second that it interferes with my sleeping, that's what I'm saying.
Oh god dude, how do you get it?
Wait hold on.
Asha put it there right?
I have corn on my ass.
I've been, I've been corn on my middle and upper part of ass.
And it's hurting very much even, I can't sleep on proper position.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Ass fuck risk.
Sir, I know.
I like to get fucking ass, and once I tried wooden brushin' ass, is it get any risk?
A wooden brush and ass?
*laughter*
Are you- is your ass-
I am a guy!
I am a guy! I want my asshole to be big!
That's the title and then here's the description.
I am a guy, I want my asshole to be big.
Is there any tips that I can have sex?
*laughter*
Oh fuck.
Oh fuck me.
I found this one. I looked up beer.
I have two beer ones here. Real quick.
They're pretty, yeah I just have two of them here, they're pretty quick.
Beer quantity, asked for male 28 years.
Sir/Madam, I take 500 milliliters beer per day.
Is it good for health or I increase or decrease the quantity of beer per day?
And Dr. Ashish Sadhana says all quantities of alcohol are bad for health, however small
it may be.
And this one is typhoid one month before can I drink beer?
Before I, before can is one word here.
Now can I drink beer?
Before one month ago, I was suffering from typhoid,
but now I am okay, so can I take beer?
And then I think this is the Dr. Shushma Shah.
The, I think this is the same woman from Tummy Worm.
- Good, yeah.
She's always in all caps.
- Yeah.
Hello, intestinal tract recovery may not be there yet
if no symptoms you can have, but in a limit, okay, bye.
I like that both of those phrases, "taking beer."
Yeah, that's nice.
That's a good--
That is really--
That's a smart way--
Also, well, yeah, if you're trying to trick your doctor
into saying, "Yes, you can have beer,"
that's a good, that's a really good--
Can I take 50 milliliters of beer?
500 milliliters of beer.
Just, you're out to drink with your fucking friends
and they buy you a beer, and before you drink it,
you just sprint to the bathroom
and write to any doctor on your phone.
Just got over typhoid.
Just got over the fucking Black Plague.
Can I enjoy one beer?
Can I please take beer?
Yeah.
Here's one.
Please.
Wet dreams asked for mail.
17 years when I get wet dreams from my pants.
It also gets onto the bed sheet.
So I changed my sheets, but what to do if the mattress?
Okay, I have one here all mine are so just nasty sex.
You look good.
I'm in poop.
This one is pussy loose and blackie.
Yeah.
Have you seen this one?
Well, I searched I had my fair share of.
Yeah, there's tons of pussy searches on here.
My pussy gone loose and it's gone blackie.
I did sex more time with my BF and finally he left me.
So now I want to marry to someone but I don't want that.
My would-be husband know that I did sex before and more
important thing.
I'm gone irritate because every time my pussy stayed damp and
come something like white thing.
So please can you give a good advice?
What should I do?
This person and then a doctor just says,
"Yes, we can give you all the details on your concerns."
(laughing)
But this woman has a black pussy.
- She is, it's black and black.
- What's wrong with that?
- It's blacky.
- Yeah, that's normal.
- It's not quite black, but it is blacky.
- It's blacky.
- And also something damp and white come out.
- Yeah, here's a smelly penis.
As for male, 24 years.
I have a smelly penis, but there is no itching.
I haven't washed it since last six days.
I am worried, please help.
- How about, I have a bump on my ass that appeared.
I noticed a bump on my ass last week and it hurts.
It won't pop or anything either.
I'm just a little scared.
- Cam, did you read this penis problem one?
I know you read one already.
- Which one is it?
- This one is male, 22 years, a penis problem.
My penis is not stand properly and it not strong, dooding 3 year.
And my left testis is smaller than my right testis.
And there's an answer here that says, "Auvedic Medicine is there, we provide the same."
Good.
Here's, um, here's a mental problem.
My mom told a stranger I'm mentally handicapped and that I have special needs.
That's the whole thing.
That's good.
That one's impolite because he doesn't request help formally at the end.
This is, is gay sex help.
Asked for mail, 22 years.
Hello, I'm gay and I have BF we do sex obviously, but every time after sex his penis seems dirty with my waist
Okay worms everywhere some sort of parasite in skin and under nails
Small white worm like also black dots appear and fall off
That's this was so horrifying. This is my favorite like like subject line of any of them
I could this one was making me laugh so hard.
This is on my cum squirts like a power washer.
Sir, my semen shoots / squirts and it's a really big turnoff
for me because it's messy and it's shot as far as my face and
it's disgusting.
So I was curious if there is a way to make my cum dribble /
ooze out.
I just don't want to cover my face with a towel when I want
to check off.
So how can I make my cum come out at a slower rate?
I cum like a power washer.
How can I make my cum come out like a really calm waterfall?
- Holy fuck.
(laughing)
His dick is sneezing.
- Wait, I just found one.
That's really good.
It's a bit of a, this is a bit of a curve ball.
General query, ask for male 35 years.
This person is 35 years old.
This is what they're wondering.
Can I get rabies from drinking water from a water cooler
after a person who seems to be mentally retarded.
(laughing)
- Oh man.
- And Dr. Raj Parekh says, "No."
(laughing)
- It's good, it's good that he said that.
- Oh my God.
(laughing)
- I've read so many about being a pervert
that we'll read eventually,
and so many of the doctors' responses,
"No, that is not normal."
(laughing)
Okay, so this is another speed round.
I don't know if I wanna read,
I wanna read a lot of these titles,
but for some reason,
These are all making me laugh so much.
This is just like, this is just like when fucking Roger Ebert says the word turtle is funny.
Okay.
I have been scratched by an eagle.
I have been scratched by an eagle on my head when I was on the roof of the house.
It was a minor scratch, but blood did come out.
What to do when scratched by an eagle.
It's a completely different one.
Okay, I was standing on the terrace and an eagle scratched my head.
Eagle bite.
I was standing on a balcony, something hit my head and run away.
Maybe it was an eagle or crow.
Eagle bite. Sorry, there was some mistake in the earlier question.
Eagle syndrome.
So many about being scratched by an eagle.
Scratched by an eagle.
I really can't get enough of scratched or bitten by an eagle.
Alright, and then...
Eagle bite is such a good phrase.
Eagle bite.
Alright, good.
All right, good. I have I have one here.
I am a gay male.
Twenty two years is a kind of a long one.
I have accepted that I am a gay, but sometimes various pictures,
various thoughts come into my mind due to which I become unconscious and disturbed.
He blacks out every time he sees.
Yeah, every time you see something gay, he gets the vapors and he faints.
Wow. This one is incest feelings.
As for male, 29 years.
Hi, sir, slash ma'am.
I am Jagdeep Singh, which is really great that he said his full name
from Chandigarh.
I am working at Hong Kong before when I was young.
Me and my mom have some incidents.
She always called me to massage her.
Then sometimes after massage, she tell me to lay down on her back.
I get hard when I do that, but she never react.
We sleep together always at night.
I have incest feelings for her.
Oh man.
And Dr.
Anil Kumar Jain says, I can understand your concern.
Incest is illegal.
Here's a here's I want to make love.
Asked for female 60 years.
My boyfriend is not circumcised.
We cannot get his head out.
His sack feels like a cauliflower.
This one is smell problem asked for male 19 years.
I smell some smells differently example curry milk.
I smell these things differently differently rather than their
original smell.
He's got a smelling issue.
Got a brain problem.
Yeah, wait.
I'm sorry.
I meant to do a set an incest speed round, but I forgot that
I had two more.
Let me finish this real quick.
This is sex with incest as for male 19 years old.
So this guy my mom wants to get fucked by me.
(laughter)
There's literally a hundred porn titles
my mom wants to see.
It gets better. These two sentences are perfect porn titles.
My mom wants to get fucked by me, but I'm scared to have sex with her.
Can I have sex with her?
She is a sex figure, and I'm scared to do that, but she is forcing me into sex.
So can I participate with her in sex?
Dr. Ramesh says no, not at all.
But I like that he's like saying like, "My mom is smoking hot and she wants to get fucked
by me."
He does sex.
Sex figure, I'm guessing he's trying to say like sex symbol.
Yeah.
Right?
Maybe J-Law is his mom.
She's famous.
Yeah.
All right, do you have another one?
Oh yeah, one round over.
This one's really short.
Incest sex thoughts.
"I want to know why it is wrong to have sex with my mom.
I'm very much interested in it."
Yeah. Okay. I have one here. This is the sun destroyed my life.
Ask for male 28 years. This is another a bit of a curveball
here. Since I wear t-shirts all the time, my arms skin which
is exposed to sun is darker in color.
So looks like someone has copy pasted some black person's arm
to my elbow.
My girlfriend saw this and left me.
She got a new complete black boyfriend now. I am depressed
Please tell me how to make my arms fair or make my full body black
This girl saw her boyfriend got a black arm and she's like, oh I like that a lot
Wow, where can I get that but all over?
They make people with that all over
I have I have a steroid speed run here. These are people asking if they can take steroids.
Is steroids good for health and which one is good and how much can I consume? What are the side
effects? I want to use steroids and I want to consult a doctor regarding this and want to know
how which one I should take when and how. I am a male 21 years I want to take anabolic steroids.
Which one should I take? I want to bulk and have less body fat.
Okay. Yeah, I mean...
Consulting a doctor for steroids.
You just want permission. You want permission to be huge.
Yeah. Is it illegal to want to be nasty?
No, it shouldn't be.
Yeah. All right. This is one guy who posts on here literally all the time with the same problem.
And the description is always suicidal thought.
Okay, suicidal thought. When I was staying in a hostel room at one night, I don't know what happened next morning.
My roommate showed me a photo. On that photo, my hands are inside my pants.
I don't know how it happened. He fought with me, saying that, "Why are you masturbating in front of us?"
Still, I can't even complete in college. I can't overcome this thought.
I feel myself as a pervert. I have masturbated publicly now.
If you're reading this post, just say whether I am a good person or pervert.
And then, here we go again. Suicidal thought.
I was filmed while masturbating when I was staying in my house
So my friends bullied me a lot even after finishing college
I cannot overcome this incident feel like committing suicide if you're reading this, please tell me if I'm a good person or pervert
Again suicidal thought when I was staying in hostel
We used to share room with my friend one morning showed me a photo on that photo
I on my hands are inside my pants. He quarreled with me saying why did you masturbate in front of us?
Please change the room this is right all over college. I was branded as a pervert by my friends even completing college
I can't overcome this incident. Am I a good person? Am I a pervert?
Two more, same exact thing.
I hope a doctor got back to him.
Wait, I have discovered a new lightning round.
Me too.
So you go first, but I got it right.
I was just thinking about Cam's one and I, apparently, there's a serious problem with
people becoming black.
Oh no.
Pretty common.
Oh God.
I still have the title on this one.
I am becoming black nowadays.
My fair look gone.
I'm tired with YouTube tips.
This one, becoming black.
By birth I am white only, but nowadays I'm becoming black now totally.
Then this one, day by day, this is like a poem.
Day by day I am black.
Previously I'm fair, too white, but now I am black.
I am at home only, but I am blackening day by day.
I searched for blacken, blackening, actually my color is white, but now I am blackening
day by day.
Why?
What may it be?
Blackening, actually my color is white, same one.
I am blackening day by day.
This poem isn't over.
My total body and face, my total color is black.
Previously, I am pure white and fair.
Previously, I used medicines for psychiatric problem.
the cause of my blacking and darkness and then it says this tell me is this caused
tell me is this cause tell me is this cause tell me is this cause tell me
cause tell me is this cause tell me is this cause female 26 years
okay here's my my lightning round is I just I just went on here and I just
search "sparm". I've searched "sparm". "Sparm come out". Sorry to ask for this, sir. When I was in
sleeping and deeply sometimes, sparm will come out of my control. Why I come like this, sir? Please
send me solution. "Sparm count". Hello, sir. I think my sparm count is less or normal or sufficient.
Don't know. How do I am confident for this? "Sparm leakage". At the time of sex, release sparm
immediately. So I am not satisfied. Please suggest. "Sparm health". Sir, my sparm thick. It's good or
bad for my sparm health. It's color white. If it's a problem, then what can I do? There's
so many of these. I feel thin sparm, low sparm count. Short penis, low sparm.
I found one here. Itching in vagina. I don't know why my bad smell is coming from my vagina.
After I do pee, itching starts badly. My vagina remains wet every time.
I like that you read in a southern accent.
Oh man, my vagina, my vagina stays wet every time after I pee.
It's a yeller vagina.
Here's another, here's another poem. It's entitled "My Sex Life" by Male29Years.
Okay.
I am 29 year old boy. My penis size small. My sparm within one min out. Sparm quality low.
No eriction, no edulation. No edulation? No edulation. All right, strange revelations.
Please answer to my question concerning a strange but real revelation from an intelligent
"being" which has been revealing and responding to me for several years.
This spiritual being reveals to me that I am a boy pedophile, but he
also "encourages me to, I would put it this way, imagine having sex with women,
kind of taking their role of their husband.
This, he shows, will prepare me for a marriage with a now teenage girl
to win my sinful desires.
Is it possible, according to psychiatry?
Really good talk to this creature.
Strange revelation.
Wait, and also childhood boy pedophile.
Strange fucking multi headed Hindu God told me that I'm a boy pedophile.
Childhood flashback.
I have a grudge against my childhood pediatrician.
When I was a kid, my mom brought me this new tricycle.
The design of it was flawed.
I kept on falling once I was hurt so badly.
My mom had to take me to a pediatrician.
He was asking where it hurt.
I kept saying on my head was hurting, but that evil monster
kept on lying to my mom that it wasn't hurting.
I mean, why would he do that?
I didn't do anything to him, nor did I knew him before the incidents.
I am having flashbacks of this today.
I was angry at the doctor.
I'm crying and I'm upset about the incident.
I'm not feeling well.
I don't know what to do with this guilt.
*laughs*
What age was that? Does it say?
Uh, it does not say.
Oh, god.
Here's one, uh, this is ADHD crimes.
Asked for male, 23 years.
If a person with ADHD murders someone, will he or she be punished?
*laughs*
Because the law says that section 84 of IPC
says that cognition impairment is considered as an unsoundness of mind
and ADHD has similar symptoms of cognitive impairment.
I think, I think, um, I think that person's onto something.
Here's one. This is, here's, "I want to get fat. Asked for male 26 years.
I want to get fat. I want to get fat. I want to get fat. I want to get fat. I want to get fat. I want to get fat."
Yeah, I gotta date it to character limit, I guess.
I feel like this one was written in a dream.
Yeah.
I am a 26 year old female and all my teeth are literally crumbling into pieces and falling apart leading to painful infections and teeth having to be pulled.
What could be causing my teeth to be so weak?
It would be a nightmare.
They're having the tooth dream.
Yeah.
I looked up the word crumbling.
That's good.
This is a quick one.
I just like what the articles of clothing that this person chooses for this.
This is I'm a guy that dress up in girls cloth.
Hi, I'm a guy that dresses up in girls cloth like bikinis and
figure skating dresses.
Can you help me?
I got a sport that he's yeah.
Yeah.
I mean, you know, he just found those two articles of cloth on
the ground.
Yeah.
This is the only ones he had access to.
Here's foamy foamy urine.
I got foamy- I got foamy urine almost everywhere.
When standing peeing-
But if I shitting position, no foam, just micro bubble.
In December I dumb test.
All normal.
Picked one standing, picked two shitting.
Is that normal?
Micro bubble.
I got foamy urine almost every time when standing peeing,
but if I shitting position, no foam, just micro bubble.
Okay, this is for fear of my child.
My son suffering from fear.
One day we went to we went to departmental store and drunk
water.
My son poured water into into refrigerator.
After he said I done mistake.
I poured water into the hole.
So electric fire start and total mall firing.
He said many times like that.
And another day he said, "Devil is inside me, and I have fear like that."
Now he is okay, but sometimes he behaves like that.
Why?
I do love search. Did you search "devil" for that one?
Yeah.
Here's one, uh, this one's "skin condition".
Male, 16 years.
I have had a red itchy circle for a while on my wiener, and I have tried antifungal cream, but it has not worked.
Wiener?
There's a few for wiener.
I searched cobra the other day.
*laughter*
And I've got penis form problems.
Hello, my penis doesn't look normal to me.
Well, everything is normal.
But when it isn't hard, it's like a cobra with extra skin.
*laughter*
Um, this one is like a little bit of a different kind of thing.
This is asked by mail.
14 years old.
to kill I have an urge to kill something or someone in a large amount and never
get found I don't know why but my mind has already made hundreds of plans to
get away with it and I can't stop I didn't like get the link to this one but
I saw one earlier - that was like hello I I have killed a hundreds of small
animals this is what Mika agar well psychotherapist is this doing swimming
class or yoga class here's um here's I bro flirting every time my mom eyes is
now a very much flirting day by day and BP low have no fucking idea what I bro
Alright, here I have this is a psychological problem. Asked
for a mail 24 years. I am not forgetting an incident. I was
ill and going to my home by train. There, a person met me
who told that he knows magic and he can cure me by his magic.
So, he hold my hands and said that he is doing his magic. So,
I believed him. For about 10 minutes, he holded my hands.
After that, he said that I will become well. When I reached my
home then I realized that he was making me fool this incident was happened about
four months before but still I am disturbed from one thing that how I
became fool one deceased I don't know dear sir under my leg I noticed before
one week there is a small black dot no pain and irritation today I open that
dot. It has some hard wiener and now I have pain.
I fart every hour, at least five, six times per day and smell
is not tolerable.
Motion is normal.
I fart a lot and loud throughout the day.
It is working at woke up.
I fart every hour.
Sometimes I feel the fart.
Hi, doctor.
This normally doesn't happen, but sometimes I feel the
sensation of the fart trying to come out and bursts inside within the anus.
Why does this happen? Does the fart air require force and quantity to come out
or am I causing it? Well gas and chest pain. Hi, from last two months I had
gastric problems, hurting frequently and chest pain as well. Three months ago. Is
Is this because of my piles?
I'm not comfortable.
(laughing)
- Here's Insecure Girlfriend.
Asked for male, 61 years.
My girlfriend stalks my Facebook page
and sees pictures of ladies with big breasts.
She does not have them.
She makes a huge ordeal over it
and says that since that's what I like, I'm a pervert.
I can't possibly like her.
And then tells me she need a drink.
What can I say to her to stop this attitude?
(laughing)
- Okay.
Had sex with wife after beaten by dog.
I saw this one too.
I was beaten by a dog
and taken vaccine immediately after beating.
I did sex with my wife at the same day
after one dose vaccine.
Now should my wife also need to take vaccine?
Not bit, beaten by dog.
- Yeah. - Hello, OMG not at all.
Don't worry, relax, your wife has nothing to do.
I have a really this is probably going to be the most insane speed round.
I don't know if you guys are familiar with this, but
apparently there's like a very pervasive Pika habit in India
where people will eat slate pencils, which are basically pieces of chalk.
I didn't know this until I went on to this website,
but there are hundreds and hundreds and hundreds
slate problem.
I used to eat slate every day.
can't tell if I can get rid of the solution without conselling a doctor. I don't want to tell my mom
eating slate pencil how to stop eating slate pencil desiring more and more every day to eat slate
pencil slate pencil eating I'm eating slate pencil often nowadays please help me get out
I'm eating slate pencils can't stop I've been eating slate pencils for three years does this
affect me eating slate pencil I'm impregnate and I always feel like eating slate pencil I want to
stop it please suggest some ways stop eating slate pens I can't stop eating slate pens I get addicting
very day. Is there any medicine available so that I stop eating
slate pens? Oh, I am eating slate pencils. What harm I am
eating slate pencils will affect my health or digestive system
habit of eating slate pencil. I want to eat a lot of slate
pencil. It's feel so yummy and comfortable by eating slate
pencil. I'm unable to control eating slate pencil even now I
want to eat it. Can you please suggest how to control? Stop
eating slate pencils problem. Hello, sir. Four years old my
boy eating slate pencils daily. slate pencils eating cause
Eating slate pencil slate pencil addicted.
How to stop eating slate pencils.
Stop slate chalk habit.
Eat slate pencils.
Craving slate items.
Eating slate pencil.
Habit of eating slate items.
How will I stop eating slate pencils?
Slate pencils.
Addiction to slate pencils.
Slate pencil is harmful.
Eating slate pencils.
Eating slate pencil.
Craving for slate pencils.
Oh, well, yeah, I mean, I feel like I need to try these now.
They're probably good.
Probably pretty good.
Yeah, probably pretty good, right?
Just like a dunkaroo or something.
Yeah, they taste earthy.
That's what people say.
I found I found, I guess, a high roller on here.
Really?
But I'm not.
We didn't read this one.
Afraid of afraid of getting HIV.
No, we've not read this.
OK, I fucked a Nigerian prostitute in Dubai yesterday.
Last night, I used two condoms for one shot just for two minutes.
my shot is done so can I get HIV? This guy is a high roller. Yeah. He's fucking a princess in Dubai.
HIV, hi doctor, I fucked one prostitute.
And then it says ABO. Oh that's the other one. That's the other one. If you search prostitute
there's 5,000 questions that are like I kissed a prostitute, I fucked a prostitute, I have HIV?
Yeah, here's um, this is underwear wearing asked for male 24 years. Is it necessary to wear underwear for guys?
If I will not wear is there some risks because everyone force and say there are some risks if we don't wear it
Thank you so much. And then the top answer is from dr. Goon John. Signe
sexologist 11 years experience
maybe
About scorpion touch in morning scorpion touches in finger of my wife
that she's feeling itching near that.
So you just go to the hospital, your wife got stung by a scorpion.
That's the best part is how many of these are like, are like,
"Knife fell into leg. What what I do?" "New Year bomb detonated near house."
Yeah, "My head exploding. What I am doing?"
I'm a man. This one's called personality doubts.
I'm a man 34 years old and I'm a scorpion by birth.
I don't want to read anymore, but it's pretty good.
This is about blowjob.
Is blowjob normal in India or it is only done outside the India?
Can my wife suck my penis and drink my sperm?
And doctor, this guy's a neuropsychiatrist, 12 years experience, doctor major, Srinivas
Gupta.
BJ has done everywhere.
*laughter*
Here's-
Very clinical.
Here's one, uh, bleeding gumps.
*laughter*
I have bleeding gumps for over, uh, two years, and not sure what kind of treatment to take to cure it.
I found gumps, and I also found chumps. Here we go.
Chumps?!
Yeah, tense for chumps. I had sex two weeks before my date, uh, late 10 November, but nothing went inside.
Last month, chumps was regular and I had urine flow beating chumps.
Mo had intercourse and then forgot.
So she took six pills and then from then past days, seven days bleeding.
And still she now is bleeding.
What's up with her chumps?
I guess chums is like having a period.
It's like slang for period, but people just calling it chumps.
Interesting.
Pretty good.
this one sex very interest so tell me some of the tips for my lover sex
And then Dr. Ramesh Maheshwari says, "What tips you want?"
That's a good question, but I also like that you wondered if we had read that yet.
Here's a, "Death due to attack maybe.
There has been a death maybe due to some attack.
Please come and provide a death certificate.
The body is cold."
The body is cold.
Dude, is this like 911 in India?
People have like very serious problems that they seem to think this website can solve
for them.
Yeah.
sexual health. The spermy coming out of my penis. How to do? That start when I make evil
love with my girlfriend.
Lazy and porn addicted. Sir, today I was shocked ever going through cell phone browser history.
Since my wife and me working, we keep my son at home and sometimes with daughter five years
old. I found history full of porn sites with cartoon characters like Pokemon Spider-Man.
Completely set standard at hostel. Came to know this day we are shocked as we are working
hard for sustainability. He is lazy and he seems always dreaming often disinterested.
Study wise average but good and understanding any subject knowledge kindly advise us.
This is a...
Hold on just how to stop it easy way for me. I'm 14 years old now it is really bad. I started
masturbation at 2015 now it's 2018. It's been three years. How do I stop it? I'm helpless.
Please help me. I didn't want to do it but in the first time I didn't know anything about
masturbation.
Actually, the story behind this is I saw a porn video on
Cosson's mobile.
I was searching for cartoon movies, and I saw that the cum
was come out from the male penis.
I didn't knew about it and tried to do it myself.
So awesome to see a picture of cum coming out of a dick.
And I'm going to do that.
I'm going to go home and try that myself.
Yeah, I can try every trick in the book to get a different
liquid to come out.
Here's is let me do this real quick.
This is a this is just a again, a bit of a different genre.
This is watching movie during pregnancy.
I am six months pregnant.
Oh, yeah, I have a doubt that is it safe to watch movie during six months of pregnancy
and I'm X.
It was one of those I saw, too.
That was like, I love to watch horror movies, but is it okay to watch horror movies?
If I'm pregnant, it's so awesome to be like so concerned about your baby that you think like an IMAX movie is going to cause a miscarriage
'cause it's just too cool.
Yeah, there are so many awful ones on here.
Just like why did I have a disgusting period
four months into pregnancy?
Yeah, miserable.
Pretty rough.
Horrible.
Penis problem.
My penis size is small,
only four inch after ready for sex
and spreen fast pass in my penis.
Is it normal to hear water splash sounds?
Asked for male, 33 years.
Is it normal to hear water splash sound on stomach when I shake or push little hard my stomach?
I am lean man if I breathe deeper I feel water sound on stomach even after I eat at night.
There's water sound on his stomach? Is it normal to hear a water splash in your stomach?
Splashing? This is a good one. I am Rita sex problem. And then the body of the text is just
sex problem dot dot dot dot dot dot dot dot dot dot dot dot dot
I really like the ones that have nothing to do with any medical
anything at all yeah I've been trying to find some of those
this one is is do ghost exist?
yeah
respected doctors
I saw a ghost yesterday
my question
do ghost exist or
it's just my thoughts I am very sacred
here's another one
Here's another one that doesn't isn't very medical
human beings beauty asked for male 24 years in
Human which creature is more beautiful. Is it man or women because I have a doubt regarding this so many years
The age old question dude, it's true felt like it was gonna explode
I have confirmed suspicion to believe my alkaline water was poisoned
I'm wondering if my brother put cortisol in my water because I had been talking about hormones and since my IQ is like 30 plus points
higher than my family.
I am the black sheep.
I also feel like my younger sister,
who my younger brother has been sleeping with,
put estrogen pills into my water.
I started noticing I had been crying
and being way more emotional than normal.
My face also started looking more feminine
like a pretty boy.
- Dude, that's actually genius.
If you hate your brother,
'cause he's-
- Turn him into a pretty boy?
- Yeah, give him cortisol and estrogen.
- And alkaline water.
- Yeah.
If he only drinks alkaline water, he's so smart.
He'll never, he'll never notice.
He'll never suspect it.
He thinks it's his best water.
Yeah.
He'll think, oh, that's just the alkaline.
Yeah, exactly.
Oh, it just tastes good.
Here's a, oh, you go ahead.
Okay.
This is I'm 19 years old and my weight is 48 kilograms.
As for male 20 years, I was shocked by electricity in 2009.
Now I am very thin and weak.
You can suggest some good suggestions for my health so that my weight
and health are healthy.
I wanna hear more about the electricity shock.
It's electricity in quotes.
Electricity.
You shocked me.
Here's uh...
Now I am thin and weak.
Yeah, the electricity made you tiny.
It's like in Mario Kart when the...
The light man to America.
This is uh...
My amount is debited but not video call.
Asked for mail 36 years.
video call with doctor but amount is
debited. And then Dr.
Viji Balakrishnan says you can
inquire about this in customer care
options for patients. They are so
professional. I like sucking of penis, is it
harmful? I like sucking of cock, is it
Harmful to my body, please tell me this is an irregular basis can't stop very crazy
It is quiet safe and nothing to worry only care should be taken of hygiene and avoid multiple unknown partners
They're addicted to sucking
Here's another - one - size
Why my penis is so small when I watch porn movies automatically watery comes from my penis sometimes sperm comes within a second
It's very sad negative thoughts killer get killed. Do we do we'd read this one? Hold on. Hold on. Oh, well negative thoughts
such as slaughtering terrorism
Can't think in a positive
This is one redness and pines I
Have redness and pines for skin from two days it pain when contact with any cloths any any solution for that
Here's one here's a short and sweet one
called humiliation porn
Asked for male 25 years if I stop humiliation porn to normal porn. I got severe anxiety and depression
whoa
Humiliation porn is like all it's keeping them grounded. Yeah
Yeah, pretty cool. Actually the problem is there is no porn that isn't humiliation. Yeah, it's all pretty true
I mean having sex is humiliating
Sex on camera and not being humiliated. Yeah, you have something wrong with you. Yeah, this is a there's a there's a little animals in my pads
That's for female 16 years, so I know this sounds disturbing
But this morning when I went to wash my pads, there's this very little two black animals
And I'm freaking out right now
Because does this animals come out of my vagina and from I recall my vagina were hurting the night before
Please help man. Thanks. Sorry for my bad grammar. So this woman is waking up with animals
No, she doesn't know what animal it is. She's sure it's an animal. Yeah
That reminds me that's that's similar to this other one here. Is it possible for a bed bug dot dot dot?
My friend didn't want to ask her own doctor, but is it possible a bed bug could go inside a female's private parts and
The answer is just yes. I
Like that they're doing the like I'm asking for a friend. Yeah
hell with me yes I was hoping you would read this one how much does it cost to
create your clone and does it has soul in it then if your clone will die does he
will suffer in hell and if 100 of clones of yours is created then does 100 of you
will suffer in hell and this response is so fucking unhinged from dr. Sarthak
Actually, what we do in clone making is take part of your soul by surgery and put it into
a person who has actually died a person.
Then we perform plastic surgery on that person by making him look just like you.
So as he shares your soul, so does he share your destiny.
If you have done something to suffer in hell, then definitely your clone which has a part
of your soul will suffer in hell.
It doesn't matter whether you make one clone, a hundred clones, as all of them will have
your soul.
Health tips! Consult me online for further queries and advices on how much clone making
will cost you.
Wait, is there like a, is there an industry in India for clone making?
There is a clone, there's a cloning industry in India.
Clone making?
Yeah.
I mean, it's made, it's been made apparent.
I mean, I feel like unless anybody has one to top that, that's a good, good way to stick
up.
Well, I mean, I feel like we should read, I have two more.
Alright.
I just wanna, I just have a couple.
I've also got a couple of good clones.
Okay.
Let's just, I mean, we might as well keep going, right?
Yeah, that's right.
I like this.
This this one.
This one is clear that this guy was like doing something bad with his mouse
rat bite on my penis, mouse bite on my penis, and it start bleeding.
After a while, bleeding stopped.
What do I have to do?
Do do do take?
I'm idea biotics.
Pretty good.
And then this one is desire of drinking human blood.
Yo.
[LAUGHTER]
This one also-- this one also does the, like, oh,
it's actually my friend.
Doctor, I have a friend called Saravava.
He say he feel like killing people and drinking blood.
He keeps speaking to himself as though he's
speaking to someone next to him.
He warns people, like, move away from here.
I have a problem.
I will kill you.
Mainly, if he sees someone alone,
he kills them and drinks their blood.
Doctor, let me know the name of this disease.
[LAUGHTER]
Yeah, all he wants is the name.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
My face keeps changing every
time, every time I look in the
mirror, I see a different person
somehow. Sometimes it's brilliant.
Sometimes it's hideous.
I just don't get it.
How do I go from Michelangelo's
David sculpture to Frankenstein
in no more than an hour?
But it happens.
I just don't get it.
And it really frustrates me.
Also, every mirror sends
a different image.
Consult psychiatrists.
That's the advice.
*sigh* Jesus dude.
Um...
So awesome.
All these long ones.
Here's one, um, mental torture.
*laughs*
My son of 12 years age
had come across some sexual visual
images a few months ago.
Now he is suffering mentally, telling
that he is getting same postures in his mind
with all the known faces of the family
members, and his legs are shivering
if he looks at ladies chest.
and so many doubts like this.
Can you please help me too?
Wow.
He's just a nerd.
We need to be on here asking questions, dude.
Yeah. True.
You should ask a question right now.
Anybody have one more we can finish on?
How about Happy Doctor's Day?
Okay.
Okay, ending on a good note, I'm thinking.
Here I wish every doctor a happy Doctor's Day.
You're the ones who save our lives and there for us every sec.
Thanks a lot. Happy Doctor's Day.
Happy Doctors Day everyone!
Happy Doctors Day!
Yay!
Thank you Pierce for coming on.
Thank you Pierce for showing us this website.
Happy 100 everybody.
Happy 100 episodes everybody.
Bye!
[BLANK_AUDIO]