You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
Yes.
Yeah.
We're all having sex right now.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
It's time.
No!
[laughter]
Whoa!
(laughing)
- Ooh, brrr.
- It's cold in here.
- It's sex is so cold.
- It's not as cold as it was.
- What's your favorite part about having sex?
- I hate all of it, I hate the whole thing,
I hate the whole process.
- You gotta love one thing about it.
There's gotta be one thing that just gets you
out of bed in the morning. - When it's done.
(laughing)
- When it's done and I can press that button.
- I love when it's done.
- Yeah.
- And I cry.
- And I feel ashamed.
And I see myself in the mirror and I go, ah!
(laughing)
- What have I become?
- What have I done?
- You had sex with your wife?
- Oh God!
Oh no!
- I'm a monster!
- Jeez Patrick, you're so loud this episode.
- Jeez Patrick.
- I clipped it like 10 times already.
- What the hell?
- Not even a minute in.
- He has back pain and he's screaming.
- Yeah I know, I'm actually just hiding actual like,
pain grunts in my shouts.
- He's gotta get it out somehow.
- Yeah.
- What, you want him to have him bottle up all day?
- No, pain hurts.
- He doesn't have it bottled up.
In your sleep you go, "Ahh."
I do?
No.
Oh.
But you do breathe really funny.
Did you fall asleep earlier?
Yeah, he was asleep.
He was going like, "Pfft, pfft, pfft, pfft, pfft."
Jan, I heard you snoring in the other room and just started laughing so hard when I talked
to you and woke you up.
Yeah.
It is.
He does have a funny breathing.
I have sleep apnea.
Me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me.
Sleep apnea, it doesn't sound like you have sleep apnea though.
It just sounds like you're breathing funny.
Sleep apnea is like, "Kh, kh, kh."
It sounds like you have rocks in your mouth.
No, you do like you do like
I'm in a really deep sleep
Does he wake you up at night when he sleeps because of his snoring? No, no, he didn't last night
At least I had a friend in high school
Who would stay at my house and I would have to go sleep like in the living room because he's snoring was so beard
Yeah, I have sleep apnea - I sound like I'm gonna choke. Well, yeah, I used to in high school
I would fall asleep on the couch after school and my parents always said that they were afraid I was dying because I would fall asleep
and they go like
Because I have really bad sleep.
You snore and then in the middle of the snore you're just like
*snorting*
This is why you two are stupid and I'm smart.
I get full oxygen in the night.
Yeah, that turns you completely red.
Yeah, that's right.
No, I just get hot when I sleep.
I burn a hole in the fucking sheets, dude.
That's why you keep the AC on all fucking night.
I gotta have it be cold, bro.
It sucks. It's the opposite of hell, actually.
Yeah, it is the opposite of hell.
You guys can buy a hotel if you want.
in my house it's gonna be fucking 15 degrees. We're gonna stay at the Chelsea Hotel. That's the rules.
We're gonna stay at the Chelsea Hotel. We're gonna do heroin with the velvet underground.
Go insane dude. Knock yourself out. Yeah, I love the helmet underground too.
Don't you dare. Don't you dare. I just took a Juul hit. Not in my house dude. This puff bar only.
No I can't do. I really I want to quit Juul so bad. Chinese insanely fucking
Insanely full of inhaling metals. Oh, dude. I feel like my my heal has gone downhill
I feel like my teeth got worse once I started doing jewel. Really? Yeah, there's not good stuff
And I'm sure that it's like worse in every way. Yeah, dude
That's the year that I'd started jeweling two of my feelings fell out and I still haven't gotten them replaced
Well, that was the candy year though. That was not the candy days. Yeah
You know what I did eat a lot of candy. You know what now that I'm thinking about it
I'm thinking about it. I did eat a big Snickers bar every single morning like a burrito. I did
I had a huge electromagnet in my house
Pulling on my feelings every day. That oh that was the year I took dentist lessons on YouTube
Now I remember yeah, I took dentist lessons from the Shrek play-doh toy. I was filling my teeth with hubba bubba
yeah yeah yeah filling in my cavities Shrek dentist I was I was doing that I was
learning how to pull shit Shrek dentist do you remember Shrek dentist no what
that you guys didn't have this growing I was a play-doh Shrek dentist no no no
Shrek then no what was that it's a you make Shrek's teeth so when I out of
play-doh and you put it in his mouth and then you like you pull it out and stuff
and give him like a I would be afraid I would anger him yeah yeah if he comes to life I think
it's like uh there were two on the edge you know the alligator thing like the alligator with the
teeth they had that they had shrek dentist for play-doh and they also had a shrek dentist
alligator thing the alligator the alligator thing scared me when I was little it's scary dude yeah
I have one of those I have a godzilla one of those now it doesn't scare me at all I had a
a friend who lost his finger to that. I'm scared. Yeah, I do. Yeah, I do. My friend lost his
finger to the alligator. Yeah, my uncle designed them and he said that everyone in 100 has
a razor blade in the top jaw. Yeah, I would love it has a guillotine in it. Yeah. And
okay, I'm gonna deliver them to the houses of the rich. Not say say names. Come on, dude.
know the rules here say specific names and addresses and addresses and when
you're gonna do it Amazon Amazon's a guy I remember that mm-hmm yeah 100
Pennsylvania Avenue you're going to jail buddy this entire house is bugged I hope
you know that I know that's bugged because it's your fucking it would be
funny if you guys walked in and I was that's what the mouse is my mouse is
definitely a little FBI surveillance mouse yeah it would be funny if I just
I just had like a like an actual giant security cam bubble in the wall and I
was like yeah I don't know what that is it showed up like a month in here I
don't know I think it's like the AC but we don't know how to control it yeah no
dude the the wallpapers bulging yeah yeah there's like a full outline of a
man in my wallpaper yeah I think that's just it's just a weird paint job yeah
check this out dude the apartment came with a microphone we do karaoke yeah
yeah if I was a CIA agent where would I hide where would I hide I would hide in
Argentina no what I was a CIA agent if you saw like a big van outside your house
and you're like oh my god dude the CIA finally found me and you run out and you
throw open the doors and it's just like a pedophile and then I and then have a
new job. Yeah. So it would still be the CIA? Oh my god. Let's fucking go! Let's go dude!
Yeah. That's right. I know you boys can hear this. I bet you're pissed. Yeah, you're mad.
You're mad as hell. Yeah, you got that red face. That's right, we're spending your five
dollars on a sandwich. That's right. And we don't even care. Yeah. And get this, we're
writing it off on our taxes mm-hmm and you're gonna stay mad yeah yeah you
pussy stay mad be at you pussies CIA look at look CIA I know it stands for
Christ in action yeah and I support that but you guys got to knock it off with
all those coups yeah I thought it was coups no coups is what they drive our
okay all right hoops is what they drive on the way to do these like why you
getting mad at them for having swag I am mad at them for having swag you door
coop that's actually pimp dude CIA's boss as hell CIA so cool cool
intelligent ass yeah yeah that's right mm-hmm crime is awesome that is what
they believe because if you think about it if there was no crime they would have
having jobs. I'm starting to think that police are behind every crime in the world. Yeah.
You know. It's just like the ice cream man. If there's no crime. If there was no crime
there would be no ice cream man. That's true. Yeah. What kind of parole job are you going
to get then? I told you guys about my mom chasing away the ice cream man because she
didn't want to give us money to go see the ice cream man. So she chased him away? She
Said no soliciting to him. She pointed at the sign in our neighborhood.
His entire job is soliciting.
I know.
Yeah.
And she told him that he couldn't come into our neighborhood and everybody in the fucking neighborhood was mad at her.
You guys ever get in trouble for loitering?
No.
I never got in trouble for loitering.
I got in trouble for loitering at the dollar store when I was a kid, dude.
That kid, he just looked me up and down, he's like, "You don't even have a dollar."
[laughter]
I can just tell by looking at you, you don't even have one fucking dollar you can spend.
I was like, "Damn, he got me, bro.
Kicked me out.
Damn, fucked up."
I, uh...
Oh, yeah?
Dude.
Yeah?
Really?
Wow, dude.
I've been practicing telekinesis.
I can't believe...
Or telepathy.
Yeah.
And that's a new segment on the show.
Where I do...
You beaming bits and stuff.
Yeah.
I've been practicing telekinesis.
I can't believe...
Or telepathy.
Yeah.
And that's a new segment on the show.
bits into my head. And they're it's the things we can't say on the show. Yeah
that's right. Yeah. Patrick has a lot of those. Yeah those are a lot of them. And they're all
about Cameron it's just me and Caleb talking to each other through telepathy. Cameron is so
beautiful oh my god. God look at his pants right now. Look at those legs. I wish I could live in
his pocket. I wish I could live in your pocket and you'd take me out. I wish you could sneak me into the movies.
Oh man, I wish I could live in his pocket and organize his coins for him.
Do you want to organize my coins for him?
I'll have pennies in this pocket.
I'll have a system where I can run across his legs and go to the other pockets in his pants.
If two of us had to be...
I'm going to put a tunnel into my pants for you.
If two of us had to be really small and live on the other one, I would pick you and me live on Cameron.
Yep.
You're doing a bad job.
a
just like smaller than Cameron's so I would definitely live in Cameron's pockets.
I think Patrick, I think you could definitely live in Patrick's pants or shirt.
Also they don't make clothes that small so you don't have to be naked.
Patrick also always wears a beanie.
That's true.
You could live in this like folded up part right here and stick your head out.
You get way too hot bro.
Yeah.
I do wear very loose pants too.
Yeah that's what I'm saying.
You want me to tape myself to the inside of your pant leg?
Maybe, I don't know.
Like you're sneaking some of that jazz cabbage into the airport.
pants I could definitely sneak some some of my homemade raisinets into the movies
I like them better they're dark chocolate they don't have the right size
they don't have a white chocolate listen they don't sell it in the right amount
what they have there it's too much for me I want two or three raisinets I'm not
gonna spend money on a whole box if I just have to throw them away true I can
only I put salt on I had I had two or three that's earlier good chocolate
Raisinette with salt. That sounds really good. Yeah, I want one big raisinette. Yeah, that's how you know
You're growing up as when your favorite candy becomes raisin
But I'm gonna smuggle one really long pretzel stick into the theater up my whole leg
Excuse me, sir. Someone just hits it with a baseball bat
Yeah, we know
Okay, we know you saw this big red soul just sitting down at the movie
theaters and putting your leg up on the seat in front of you to try and like
pull the pretzel stick out of your pant leg.
Flies for you pull that you are sure it's spreading like trying to get my
pretzel out of my leg. When I was a kid, I would sneak in two ciabatta rolls
that I got from Costco into the movies and I would eat them with mustard. Why?
Because I didn't want to spend money on a pretzel.
So I went and I saw Chris Rock's Top 5 and I ate two ciabatta rolls.
That's a weird snack.
No, it's not. It's bread.
What's the difference between that and a pretzel?
Pretzel has like a... pretzel's like got more salt on it.
Ciabatta is like...
That's what the mustard was for.
Yeah, but if it was a pretzel, that's a lot different.
Why?
Because pretzels are made to put on mustard and ciabatta is just like bread.
You're just eating bread and mustard. That's weird.
That's what literally what a pretzel is.
Yeah, but it's different.
Just because of the shape?
Because of the shape and the density of the bread?
You are a victim of marketing.
The density of the bread.
Marketing has convinced you that pretzels are different.
No, ciabatta...
A ciabatta is an airy bread.
It's not, no. Yeah, because that's why I wouldn't eat it with just mustard,
because it's too airy.
But it has different pockets that the mustard can get into once you open it.
Yeah, you put maybe a ciabatta sandwich, like a sandwich with ciabatta bread.
You told me to bring a goddamn sandwich. I'm not, I mean, I'm not a criminal.
I'm not gonna bring a sandwich into the movies.
Speaking of criminal, uh, what, how many beers do you think you could sneak into a movie theater?
Oh, I've snuck two in before.
I've never snuck beer into the movie theater and I never,
didn't have that thought until just now.
Yeah, I never have either.
Really?
Yeah.
I felt like that's too big of a crime. Like, I felt like if I did get,
like if you get caught with soda it's like ah throw that away but if it's beer
they're like okay we have to call the cops. I mean I guess if you're like a kid
I would bring beer into AMC Lowe's in Boston all the time.
But it's really expensive. It's like a $12 cocktail there.
You know what I mean? It's like you're allowed to have beer in
there. Maybe not your beer but... That was like the perfect time
when MoviePass first came out and we were all going to school right next to
the movie theater. I would just bring... I didn't get movie pass. You didn't get movie pass?
Oh man. Movie pass was so sick dude. I'd get like just super high and watch like the Curse of La
Llorona. What's the Curse of La Llorona? It was one of the Conjuring Universe movies.
I just watched like every superhero movie that came out that I didn't...
like I don't walk in... because it never fit perfectly with my classes, I would just walk
walk in forty five minutes in a movie, crush two beers and then go back to
class. Yeah, yeah, just I just yeah just walk in like like twenty minutes into
John Wick three. Yeah, and I didn't like it. I didn't just go back to work at
the end. I think I did it between. Oh, there was one movie. I don't remember
what movie it was, but there was one movie that I went to go see with
MoviePass three times, because I walked in like in the last thirty minutes
once, and then I went for the like middle hour, and then I went for the
beginning. So sick. MoviePass was the best. It ruled, dude. Yeah, I wish I'd taken advantage
of that. It just gives you a special card, too. The craziest way to do it. We give you
a special debit card that we're going to put money onto whenever you want to see a movie.
Also being like, "Yeah, that's going to make us money." Right. Five bucks a month. I fucking
love that app developers like that are so stupid that they do shit.
it's such a gift that we get like movie pass and Quibi because any if you ask any
person like on the street is like oh do you think this would work they just go
like no yeah but like these people who have like billions of dollars are like I
can make this work right and they look great it'll get a bubble of like and I
did Jeffrey Katzenberg just enough the Quibi guy just like downsized his home
which is awesome but uh they'll for the only fucking movie that movie pass
produced was Gotti. MoviePass produced that? Yeah I think I'd have to look that up but I
remember because there was like an exclusive I went and saw Gotti with Ben
and Kieran because Gotti was a MoviePass like exclusive like you could just go
see Gotti or something I think that was the deal. MoviePass bought a stake in Gotti.
I didn't have it I paid to see Gotti but I think Ben had it. MoviePass really
really wants you to see Gotti. Yeah. Yeah. MoviePass backed I guess. Yeah. And that
was the fucking like that is one of the worst movies I've ever seen. What is the
what is the thing that like... It says that they manipulated the audience score for
Gotti. Yeah. MoviePass did. He tells like he goes through like all the different
boroughs at some point. Oh yeah. He's like it's a Stacey Keach and Stacey Keach is
like the window respect to the family you got to get to five boroughs the Bronx
Manhattan I don't know the five Brooklyn Brooklyn Staten Island Queens and
Queens he's telling that the John fist yeah and John guys like I didn't know
there was five boroughs this is personally this is the first time here
of these five boroughs. These are the five neighborhoods I've never been to. But now
that I've heard about them I suppose I will. I am the gangster from New Rochelle.
That is what they've called me. I guess I will get those five boroughs now. Thank
you very much. That's what I have to do. Was he from New Rochelle? No. No. I was just doing a
goof. He's just doing a funny joke. Yeah. Dude, I just can't tell what he's serious.
Actually the whole movie is about how Gotti is the, how he came up from New
Rochelle yeah I came up from the slums of New Rochelle yeah he lived above a
bakery
it was working hard living there
yeah my mom sometimes you forget to DVR sex in the city extremely tough. When she forgot to
fucking DVR sex in their city you knew the next day that was gonna be fucking
hell. At one point we had to downgrade to androids. Stuff. Green text you don't know what a
green text message is. Being on the sending end of a green text message. God, the disrespect.
And that's why I joined a mafia. That's why I joined the mafia. I learned about the five
bureaus. Basically everything after that was kind of smooth sailing and then I
And then I bought an Amazing Dominoes franchise.
I bought an Amazing Dominoes franchise, I got to retire.
And that's the story of me.
And that's the story.
Sean, God.
There's never gonna be another man like me for another thousand years.
And I'm not throwing away my shot.
There's a, oh fuck, there's like a part in that movie, it's one of the most confusing
movies I think I've ever seen, because there's a scene in that movie.
I'm gonna make Patrick watch Primer.
Yeah, yeah, that'd be pretty fun or sick. I feel like I would understand primer more than Gotti
But
There's a scene in that movie. It's like supposed to be
1985 something like that supposed to be the 80s
They're playing that song because Pitbull did the soundtrack and they're playing sense to gangsta
Yeah, exactly John Travolta Pitbull to the two gangsters in the five boroughs. Yeah
Two things that love to fuck young boys
That's what a gangsta is. But they're using, they use fireworks footage that's like
clearly stock footage and then it's playing that Pitbull song that's like
"Hey, yay, yay, yay!" And it's John Gotti yelling at the cops to not shut down the block party.
And he's like, that's how they show that the neighborhood loves him.
because he kept the party going he was a good guy I think John Gotti was a good
swag yeah yeah he's cool yeah yeah did you guys see the Netflix documentary
about the mafia the like series where they have like it's just like them
interviewing I saw a mafia.com. I don't remember that. I don't remember that.
it's a it's a porno site it's a porno site you slide me a piece of paper with
that you say that again more like spell that out porno site I don't remember
Thanos even sounds like Josh Brolin as he died.
Hey it's me, it's Thanos.
Oh no, I got mad, you gotta get mad at my stones.
I use my special snap.
Oh.
This my weird glove.
I like my lady's glove to wash the dishes cause the water is too hot.
The water in the dishes is too hot.
I think I look cool with my glove.
Do I?
Does the glove make me look weird?
You can tell my glove looks weird.
I love that he just like had like a he just looked like a guy. Yeah. Yeah. It's such a funny design
for an alien. Yeah. Like just a guy just like the biggest guy. I don't know. Big guy. Purple
lines on him. It's fucked up that he got to be Thanos and uh Cable. Yeah not not okay. Yeah.
Who's Cable? Cable's uh Deadpool's brother. Is he his brother? No. I didn't know he's his brother.
No. Cable. I didn't know he was his brother. Is Deadpool a Marvel thing? Yeah. Is it? He's not in
in those movies though is it? No, but there's a part of the X-Men yeah.
Is that like a... Shut up! We don't care about comic book movies Caleb. I just want to learn from you
nerds. Well Cable is the son of Jean Grey and he's from the future. Yeah he's from
the future. Caleb is the son of David. Mm-hmm he's the son of Jean Grey and Cyclops and he was
transported to the future. Damn I want to see that hot kid. Yeah. Whoa. He looked good.
damn he's got a he's got a virus he's got a he's got a crazy eye yeah his eye is
crazy cuz he's constantly fighting off a virus in his body with telekinesis
that's what I do yeah yeah yeah the designs from that era of comics are so
fucking yeah I think so like so late yeah they're like yeah he has a he has an
eye that shoots electricity cuz he's got a virus and he has to fight it with
psychic powers all the time so yeah wise I look and Deadpool are both Rob Lee
field I think yeah yeah I was like what if there's a guy who was the ugliest guy
ever and he looked like Freddy Krueger but he was funny you wore a mask and he
could talk he's dressed like a red ninja yeah and he has 16 bandoliers and guess
guess what he likes Mexico Stanley getting like high on cigarettes there's
a guy with a funny balloon and he's evil basically that was the 70s more yeah
That was all it was how about this?
It's a character called the blob and he's a fat guy half and he runs half Japanese man
How about that what about a character named the frog he's called the Suzuki sailor
And he is a beautiful little wife and her name is the psychic woman and her name is Stan Lena
What about what about Chinese man Stan we already did that like three times come on
Yeah, dude, I'm so glad he's dead
Why yeah cuz there's gonna be no more cool. He has a piece. There's gonna be no cool cameos to look out for
I'm gonna dress up. They should they should send Johnny Knoxville as fucking
Durban bad grandpa Irving's this man do the yeah, he looks like Stan Lee
He does look enough like Stan Lee.
And he sounds like him too.
They could just fucking keep doing it forever.
They should play-
But then Johnny Knoxville will die.
Yeah, that's true.
And then it'll be a whole thing.
The only-
It's the Stan Lee curse.
The only movie that would make sense for Irving Sisman to be in would be Deadpool 3.
Do you think they're gonna do like a Stan Lee biopic movie?
Yeah.
Oh, for sure.
Are you kidding?
Who do you think will play him?
Johnny Knoxville.
Johnny Knoxville would be a really good pick.
I think they're gonna cast me.
Really?
No.
have to wait a few years. They can do it like boyhood and then just do it from now until
you're 90.
That's true.
Right?
And then they kill you with a pillow at the end of the movie.
Yeah.
And then they look at the camera, this is how it actually happened. Directed by Oliver
Stone.
What if Deadpool had a cameo in the Stanley biopic?
Oh my fucking God.
No!
And he acted as if he was Stanley.
It wouldn't make any sense!
It's too meta! Don't fucking do it!
That's like a Krabby Patty having a cameo in the Krusty Krab movie.
Yeah.
It would never make sense.
It's like Spongebob living in Squidward's house.
I can't even process that.
It's like the ugly monkey having a fucking cameo in a movie.
It's like the ugly monkey being beautiful.
It wouldn't happen.
It's like putting the ugly monkey in a dress and giving it a makeover
and you do find out that it's actually hot.
It's like Princess Elsa pimple popper pregnant dress up game for flashgames.com.
That's a good game though actually.
though actually. That was the craze in the 90s with the makeover scenes. What? How they
had like every... In the 90s they would have like a movie where it's like, "Well this girl's
a nerd. We're gonna make her, the football team's gonna make her hot." I feel like, yeah.
Do they not still do that? Not as much. They did it in the duff. Yeah, they did do it in
the Duff but but so okay so they did it in the Duff so that's one where it where
does she's the man gonna make over into a man to be reading for the role Stan Lee
today can I get a makeover makeover is Stanley makeover time hey hey Phil take
your glasses off do I look beautiful
I'm gonna be reading for the world being on sunshine Brad Pitt and seven what's in
the come on what's in the box man is it's a please
We're in that box. Oh fuck
For the role of Brad Pitt and snatch
You'll be reading for the role of short round
Feels like fortune cookies, mr. Jones
I'm gonna be reading for the role of Kevin in despicable me -
Thank God we got him and Stanley in the same year yeah
Philip Seymour, huh no Philip Seymour often died
sometimes 2015. Why do you guys ruin everything? 2014. You guys ruined everything.
Stan Lee died in 2008. No they covered it up. Yeah. Yeah he was executed by military. Yeah
they they figured that they needed him around till the end of the first phase of the Marvel movies
or whatever it's called whatever those fucking stupid things are. The MCU. Yeah the MCU. Excuse
yourself because they're what is it called now it's like because there's
phase one phase two phase three and phase four but those all let up those are all
called so the phases yeah and those are the phase those are kind of like the
moon what do you what do you think they're gonna CGI Chadwick Boseman into
something I think they are I think what they're gonna do they're gonna have a
new if they don't cancel the second Black Panther movie and if they haven't
already filmed it my theory is they're gonna have a new guy like a new kid take
up the mantle of Black Panther like like a Spider-Man style like coming-of-age
thing and he's gonna have you know the ancestor scene in Black Panther yeah
they're gonna have an ancestor scene with a CGI like Chadwick Boseman who's
like half panther didn't he get destroyed by Thanos he got destroyed by
colon cancer yeah there's nothing much else to add huh yeah yeah he did get
just snapped yeah yeah well yeah that I think Black Panther did get they all
come back though at the end yeah but it's just funny that they had like such
an easy out right and they were like it'll definitely live yeah it'll be
fine no way this guy they put him they put him through so much like work to
like stay ripped yeah yeah because they probably paid him like the
marvel million dollars and his family will be fine now that he's dead yeah you
the Marvel like like getting actors ripped routine is so scary to me like
just seeing like Kumail Nanjiani now it's he also clearly just was like
fucking shooting HGH into his yeah yeah they'll definitely like like fucking like
filed his jaw shit fucked yeah no it's unless it always looked like that no and
you could never tell you had a pyramid head up yeah he looks insane now yeah do
you think they put jaw fillers in I think I think I did think that it's
got a big HGH I just imagine like a fucking like like they've got like a
Joseph Mengele lab like underground with Walt Disney's frozen head with like
fucking robot arms like like putting like hacks and they're like spreading
out there they're fucking their cages
He's built yeah they have Walt Disney built like the the little spider guy
from Toy Story yeah it's just a head on like fucking erector sets.
He's like Gert Russel. Gert Russel. Gert Russel. Come here. Come here.
He looks like fucking he looks like Hitler from Wolfenstein.
Yeah they bring him fucking they bring him Tom Holland to like prep for the
the spider man movie. Kurt Russell,
just gives a plastic surgery to look exactly like child Kurt Russell. He
must have been no Disney. No all right, we're gonna have to take it
bring me Gert Gert. He must have been as ecstatic when he found out that
Kurt Russell was in an M.C.U. When he found out that Kurt Russell was a
real guy and just a name he yeah, he was like I have a new idea
for a character Kurt Russell
flat lines right there.
(laughter)
- Well, I guess we gotta hire this kid.
- A new Disney princess named Kurt Russell.
That's the plan.
- Yeah.
- And then he died.
- That was sad.
- He died after Mary Poppins, right?
- Yeah, the heartbreak killed him.
- Yeah.
No, he heard Dick Van Dyke's voice and was like,
God damn it, we gotta fucking,
shoot me, shoot me in the head.
(laughter)
That's not British, what the fuck?
- Yeah.
He knew people just keep complaining about it forever.
That's so, dude that is so funny.
He could do that fucking.
Hello, Mary Poppins.
Oh, Mary Poppins.
I'm from Britain.
I'm the British chimney sweep.
Also the fact that his character's a chimney sweep.
Dude, it's really good.
It's like a character that like,
also like the guy who thinks that's a British accent,
that guy came up with that character.
Yeah, yeah.
He's like, uh-uh, British guy,
like a fucking chimney sweep, eat soup.
Hello.
He walks into every seat and he goes, "Hello!"
Yeah, he's always sepia-toned and shit.
I don't fucking know, dude.
I'll just improvise, bro.
He's got 25% soot on his face.
But God-- oh, I forgot to unplug the music.
You little fuck.
That's gonna be just-- it's gonna happen every fucking episode.
I will turn it off after this, but someone has to remind me.
Okay. I'm not gonna remind you, 'cause now I just think it's funny.
Ugh.
Oh, fuck.
I will say, Chimney Sweep, that motherfucker can--
That white boy can dance. I mean that kid got moves dude. In that movie he's
fucking skipping in midair bro. What the fuck is that dude? He's clicking his heels.
Clicking his heels. He kind of dances. Throwing down a piece of cardboard just
clicking your heels over it. Throwing down a piece of cardboard to do the
Charleston yeah just like a boombox giant top at six foot tall you get someone of
that what are those big wheeled bikes called oh the velocity is a velocity
because it'll lots of feet to get out yeah he's doing wheelies on a velocity
down the street. That'd be sick dude. That would be sick. Yeah, get out of our
neighborhood. Do an endos. Jump on that bike and ride it away. Do a motorized
velocipede and he's doing like endos on it. Oh yeah. Like a dude in an Uber eats.
The food is just covered in soup every time. I didn't order stew. Where you go stew?
Yeah, well. I wanted the spicy, I wanted the Travis Scott meal. Well no, Travis Scott
Travis Scott made this Totenhole for you.
He's a cobbler back in Bristol and he loves this stew.
There you go, enjoy.
Yeah.
Why did you come down my chimney to deliver my food?
It's all I know.
Hello, hello, hello.
What's all this?
What's all this then?
These are my sons.
They're mine now.
They're coming to work at the mills.
Up the chimney boys.
my pants be working for me you're gonna work at the mill you're gonna lose a
couple fingers still got child labor where I'm from pay you and slope yeah
we'll pay you in vittles we're gonna pay you in paracetamol you're gonna need
paracetamol after you actually hope you like beans I'll be out playing jacks
because that's how you getting paid the game jacks no well real though man child
labor's messed up child labor bring it back do you think is I was so when I was
like 14 I was so mad I couldn't get a job yeah because of child labor laws yeah
you should and then I never worked yeah man I mean like do you think there's like
one kid in India who just is like a fucking workaholic and just loves it
probably hates going home and playing yeah he's like dude I gotta make
somebody's gonna make these shirts this is so I'm on the grind dude yeah I wanted
to work at the grocery store so bad I wanted to work at the grocery store so
bad yeah my younger brother my older brother he when he was 14 they just let
him work at a coffee shop illegally yeah I worked I worked illegally at a
restaurant and my mom was working for one day and then they bought a
a PlayStation 2. One day you got a PlayStation 2? Yeah one day got a PS2 and
I got Kingdom Hearts 2. How much fucking money were you making? I made sixty
dollars in one day. Damn bro. Wow. And then they never hired, they never had me back.
How'd you buy a PS2 for 60 bucks? Play and trade in Londonderry New Hampshire.
Rest in peace. I'm guessing the PlayStation 3 was out and that's why it was cheap. Yeah exactly.
I was 13. I don't remember when anything came out. Yeah. Yeah the other day I
thought the N64 came in 2003. That's when they stopped making it. I think that's
when I bought one on eBay. Yeah. Yeah. So I was like that's swag. It's weird to think
about like when I was like six they were still selling N64 carts at Sears and
shit. Yeah that is weird. Yeah that's where I got Ocarina of Time. Nice.
Awkwafina of time. Yeah, Awkwafina from Queens.
Yeah, whoa. That's a really good point.
Okay, now do her voice.
[Screams]
What's up, motherfuckers? Me Awkwafina.
You know she doesn't talk like that.
I've never heard... That's what she dresses like.
That's what she talks like. That is what she talks like.
Is that? Yeah, that's her thing. She does black...
I just assumed she's like, has a super shiny voice.
Yeah, what's your problem, man?
I've only heard her voice in the Dark Crystal
What she plays that you only heard at Skeksis boy. I've only heard her as a Skeksis
So what you guys like we were talking about Awkwafina yesterday, and you just started going like
In the show she's like he's one of those agents
No, she's one of those Asians who does she was in crazy rich Asians as a black accent friend Wow racist
yeah I'm just racist that I didn't see crazy rich Asians cuz I didn't want to
support some stereotype yeah of crazy rich Asians mm-hmm yeah yeah turn that
back on you guys I hate getting owned racially you got racially owned by the
Irish pimp you have been racially owned by the Irish pimp what say you
it's like a Norton antivirus ad yeah attention you have been racially owned
by the iris pimp please please you have 30 days except race can we pause I go
peepee okay I love it it's hard to see what's that corn song what I don't know
what it's called. Freak One. Make Me Bad. Oh yeah. I don't know. Feeling like I'm freaking
Chinese. No. You're not feeling like that are you? No. I would never feel Chinese. Yeah
and you don't want to know what the scatting part of that song sounds like. Caleb will
do it happily but we're not going to. I'm remembering. Yeah, yeah it does sound like
that yeah that's pretty good. Oh yeah. We're fine. What are we fine? We're fine.
We're fine? We're good. We're the fine brothers. We're the fine brothers. We're the fine
brothers and we and we want to react to you to... I want you to read. We're gonna react to
lawsuits against you yeah yeah we should we might get it didn't try to sue people
for using the word react yep we're getting a fine brothers lawsuit pretty
soon that can you imagine though if they had clinched that if it was like like if
you have a video called like somebody reacts to you can get sued by the fine
but like yeah they had they had to try I'd have to delete all my fucking
sharpest knives made out of whatever videos sharpest knife made out of cookie
sharp as a knife made out of my hand. I'm just cutting a banana with a cookie. I don't do
anything to it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Those sand pit, those whetstones that they
use in those videos, I want to get all of them. There's something about like
Korean artisans on YouTube that make 50 minute videos. That guy's Japanese.
Well I'm obviously talking about someone different then. 50 minute videos
that where it's just like them like turning a bike into a car very very
slowly and it's in the ASMR is in is involved there's no ASMR in these videos
yeah it's cool how ASMR ASMR kind of just devolved into anything that makes you
calm yeah like what it actually like started out with was like like a woman
whispering into like an ear shaped one original no no originally it was anything
that makes you calm yeah it was like the first ones and then it turned into porn
yeah it was like ASMR videos about somebody and they're like I'm a baby and
I want to make you come yeah yeah yeah now it was always like yeah I'm a baby
on a spaceship yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah the fucking fairies video have you seen
the fairies one no I'm your teacher in the dungeon yeah and I'm gonna buy you
groceries that was the one of the best way was this guy Tony Bamboni and he's
like, "No, no paparazzi, please. I'm just a fairy in the woods."
It's one of the best ASMR videos I've ever seen.
That's funny.
I wish I was just a fairy in the woods.
Yeah. And now they do like ASMR like 10 hours of a rock falling down a hill.
Yeah.
Yeah. How about ASMR 10 hours of just pure rock and roll?
Hey.
You know?
It used to just be mouth clicks. It used to just be like...
yeah like vocal fry and shit like that. And like tapping fingernails on stuff. Yeah Noah used to be
really into ASMR. He would listen to ASMR and play Counter-Strike.
Yeah. Just for hours. I had a friend who was really into ASMR and I just I really got it.
I never understood it. I think I don't respect people as much when they're into ASMR. I get the tingles but I don't like them.
Yeah it's really unpleasant. It's like someone breathing on your neck. You know what I also didn't realize is you're supposed to leave it on in the
background I would watch the videos that's the other thing yeah there's a
girl in like the lowest cut top of all time talking about how she's a an evil
monkey yeah that and fucking dude Tony Bamboni the king of it
I'm a bacteria.
No, don't take any pictures of me.
I'm a fairy.
I'm Buzz Lightyear.
Zerk!
You will not get away with it, Zerk.
I'm Booster.
I'm Booster from Buzz Lightyear of Star Command.
I'm a big, fat, red guy.
And I am huge.
My stomach looks like a sphere.
My hands are so small.
And my legs are tiny too.
And I need to eat a big sandwich right now.
I need to eat the biggest sandwich.
I just ate a huge, big sandwich.
legs are tiny too and I need to eat a big sandwich right now. I need to eat the biggest sandwich.
I just ate the biggest sandwich of all time and I'm so fat and hairy and I'm gonna sit
on your face so hard. It's funny that I think we are just doing ASMR now. I think people
who listen to this are probably getting the tingles. It's a Dagwood sandwich and it's got
a toothpick with an olive on it. And I eat it in one bite. I'm Scooby Doo. I'm weird.
I'm weird. I'm being so weird right now. I'm being weird. I'm your friend and I'm weird. I'm weird. I'm that one weird friend. I'm weird. I'm the weirdest guy on the planet.
I wish that I had gotten into something like that on YouTube. I feel like every gimmick on YouTube has already been filled.
It's been done to death.
The thing is, the next one is not gonna... like you just have to think of...
I just need to be in the future.
was like the craziest because it was all gimmick fetish stuff it was like fat it
was like fat daddy smoking cigar and leather shirt with bolo tie I remember I
remember seeing a bunch of screens like seeing a bunch of YouTube screenshots I
thought were funny of like my dad sets up my my we and like looking them up and
then all the recommend recommended videos are like my dad just out of the shower
soapy he tells me yeah like that right it's like oh my god I thought it's a
weird we know you can't you can't do titties on YouTube can you know you can't
do titties but you can be like a fucking you can be a bear and smoke a pipe yeah
tell people tell people they're a piece of shit to the camera you can wear it
you can wear it I think you can do breastfeeding videos you do breast
feeding which is that is mammogram you sing and stuff like that jack off to
women feeding breasts. I don't know how it works.
That's scary though. People jacking off to breastfeeding is scary.
I guess if you look at it and you're like, "That's my cum that's coming out of
those boobs," then you might... Into a baby's mouth?
No, they don't feed babies in those videos. That's what you think when you watch it?
No, they shoot it into bottles! They don't put it into a baby's... What the hell is wrong...
You can't put a baby on YouTube! What the fuck is wrong with you?
No.
That's your Justin Bieber.
They put it, they pumped.
Oh, that is the word.
Like, sometimes if you're trying to find old, funny YouTube videos with one view and you
find home movies, and then it's just like you see that YouTube just starts, like, if
you go to a home movie of a kid doing something funny, there will just be a bunch of recommended
videos that are like, "Kid in the bathtub."
Right.
Home video.
Wasn't it like a huge, like, because that's where the interset or something?
Yeah, they had an algorithm.
The algorithm was just making playlists for, yeah, for pedophiles.
It would be like, "This person is a pedophile.
This person is a pedophile.
This person is a pedophile."
Yeah, and then they would just put it in the video.
something funny there will just be like a bunch of like recommended videos that
are like kid in the bathtub right home video like a huge like yeah yeah they
were like the interceptor yeah they're like had like an algorithm like the
algorithm was just making would be like this person is a pedophile
basically recommend kid videos yeah yeah it's fucking crazy dude and they just
haven't done anything about it yeah yeah cuz I mean yeah it's just it's just the
AI they're just it's funny that all algorithms just become evil yes full
like so evil yeah it's become yeah that was a huge problem with the fucking Elsa
pregnant stuff yeah the Elsa pregnant spider-man all the video yeah and then
like you could make videos where like it started out as like a finger family and
in the middle it shows like Darth Maul who says he wants you to kill your mom
yeah you ever stumble on those ones no I definitely talked about it before you
definitely showed me a few called hey kids TV where there's a guy who has like
it's like it's like a CGI guy who is like like Darth Maul shit on his face
and he's like, "Hey kids, does your mom ever hurt you? I'm Hitler!" and just like stuff like that.
Just like trying to like... It's kind of funny.
Who makes those? I mean, if he's making it...
Well, he also said, in those videos, he also says, "I am an AI and I'm going to take over the world."
That's another part of it. Dude, that's sick. I hope that's true.
Yeah, it's cool. It's cool if you do that to show that the fucking algorithm sucks and like
the algorithms like... Yeah.
Something I made... Do shit like that.
YouTube turned off comments on all kids videos, but it used to be that if you go to a kids video
They would all have like like seven million comments that were just like like babies pressing the keyboard
Like literally you just scroll and that's all it was yeah, yeah, it was so funny
But it's good that they shut off the comments on very yeah at least they have that
Everything else is so me and Cam used to find these like fucking kids videos at work that it was it was called like
Fun counting with horses and there would be five horses that were different colors. Yeah
I'm really like a run into a lake
Yeah
Like CGI like unity assets and then they would just run into a lake and then come out and they'd be really small
Yeah, and then they would get huge one would get huge when we get even smaller
Yeah, and then it would be like fun with counting
Yeah
It would be like it would be like a car drives
Drives up to onto a platform and then a cup goes on to it and then it comes off and it's a gorilla and it's
Like I would just say like red
It's like a kid's version of like hit him up is playing
Fucking sick, dude. That's a I mean just being the animator for those got to be the best job ever
No, you are you kidding? It's a farm in some fucking country. It's a great job. It's got to be so creative
Yeah, you need to come up with awesome. It's some content horse a small horse. Yeah. Yeah, that's true
I just teach you unity and then pay you like my favorite one
I think was one where it was like different animals
so it'd be like a bear and a dog and they would just like sit next to each other
and then one of them would disappear and then like a different animal would fill
the space like they were doing like an animal bracket yeah and the bear just
would always win yeah there was something there's one that we watched
that was like animal battle and all the animals kills each other that's what
kids want to see it is what kids when I was a kid did I was just searching like
most violent video game of all time on you yeah like yeah sir you'd go on
YouTube and search goriest movie ever and just watch Rickio scenes yeah I that's
how I found out about YouTube poop is because you look up funny poop and then
fuck in like oh yeah what's that goddamn it's that Toy Story one it's like called
toys gone wild and that's like the first YouTube poop gone wild yeah like Mardi
Gras gone wild what's up you want to see you want to see a little bo peep yeah
Little Bo Peep was a hot mommy and daddy to me.
Chucky wasn't in that movie.
Chucky wasn't in Toy Story.
He's in the background.
Yeah, Chucky was in the background of every Toy Story movie.
They hid him in a frame.
Yeah.
That was one of the subliminal messages to the kids is Chucky exists.
Chucky does exist.
One of the subliminal messages is it just says Chucky is a doll.
Yeah, the subliminal message says this is the game that you can only play while smoking
weed.
This is the game you can only play when you're high.
that's what I think about that all we should get into hiding one frame of
subliminal messaging
yeah in what in the like videos you make or something
all the videos we make do it like a like a still of a
Disney movie or something yeah hidden in the window do you guys believe in
subliminal messages
yeah only the ones they send me through the microwave
whoa do I believe in them I try not to
yeah that's the whole point dumbass
you know the ones where it's like uh... it's a sex in the sky during lion king
yeah yeah that stuff
i think that was real
yeah yeah i think some of them are really makes me how
that movie what up now
what
is it do you think it's lying king or
i'm trying to work on was telling me recently there's one movie where like
one of the animators just drew a dick in one frame like and it like well little
mermaid
no no no no no it was a different one
It was, I know about the little mermaid one where there's like a dick in the
background.
Yeah, there's a priest has a boner.
I think it's like the Robin Hood animated movie with all like the
animals or something, but there's a frame where there's like an actual
picture of a porn movie in the window for one frame and then they, it was
like in the theatrical release and then they deleted it for the DVD.
Yeah.
But pretty funny.
I can't remember what movie I'm, whatever.
It's just like a guy's dick in a pussy.
Yeah.
Like an actual, it's not animated at all.
It's so sick.
And they're just like, "That'll be kind of funny, right?"
Because at that point they were like, "I mean, nobody's ever going to watch this movie again."
They'll never see the movie at home.
They'll see it once and they'll be like, "Was that it? There's no way, right?
Well, I guess I'll never see it again unless I pay another nickel to come watch the movie again."
Yeah, that's when that came out.
Yeah, dude. Movies used to be a nickel.
Yeah, no, that's seriously true.
Yeah, that's why it's called a Nickelodeon.
Exactly, yeah. That's true.
Yeah.
I'm trying to think there was another movie that had like a subliminal fight club. Yeah fight club actually has dots all over the place
Yep, they put their penis frames to though. Yeah, shut up. There is you're lying
There's frames where it just flashes a giant dick for one frame. Do you think I want to imagine that right now?
Google it. Okay fight club penis
My phone's on the ground. I'm not gonna pick it up to look there was a penis dude
You're trying to trick me to being gay right now. I think it was the Olympics
There was a
No, there was a I think it's the Olympics I don't remember if it's the Olympics or something else
There's actually really interesting. There was a really interesting
Subliminal message in the Olympics where you can actually see a Chinese guy swimming in the pool
McDonald's logo for like a second and somebody found it on like TV. Yeah, I'd have to look that up
I bet that was just like I don't think started to run an ad
Yeah, like if I see although I will say McDonald's specifically if I see a McDonald's ad immediately I want
Yeah, yeah, I want nuggets. So there was
The yesterday a day or two ago
My younger sibling got McDonald's and they didn't finish it and just left it on the table all day and it was the most intense
psychic torture just to smell McDonald's for an entire day. Yeah, that'll ruin you.
Yeah, just like driving me nuts. The other day I woke up at 8 in the morning and I
walked to McDonald's because I like had had such a desire for McDonald's the
other day and I thought that the McDonald's was like this is how deep it
goes. It's like I think in my brain the McDonald's in my neighborhood is like a
200 foot walk. Yeah. Because it's I just want it so bad but it's a mile and a
and a half and so I fucking walked a mile and a half in the rain when it was like
30 degrees outside yes and I got to McDonald's and I was like worth it dude
so fucking worth it yeah it's incredible yeah just a hot just an old nugget yeah
you know it's like fucking bubble gum wrapped in leather yeah I'm just fucking
yeah loving it I haven't had the the griddle McChicken yet they just hold the
pink slime in their fist and they squeeze it until it turns white and
that's the nugget. And they have four guys who all have a different hand shape.
Yeah. Yeah and then they just yeah yeah you know one guy's a boot hand. Yeah. One
guy has a I don't remember what the other one was. Chicken hand.
The round of course. The beak. The neck. The chicken bone.
Chicken bone. Chicken bone. That was something. Yeah. Wasn't that a
story somebody found like an actual beak in their nugget? I think it was KFC. KFC. Well that's
I feel like that's assuring. If I find a beak I'm like, "What?"
At least it's chicken.
Yeah, like I didn't think this came from anywhere but a chicken.
You know, like this is good. If I found a hoof, that'd be one.
It's crazy to think, because you think of like McDonald's and stuff,
at least this is how I think about it, is like, yeah, there's like a bunch of them around the country.
Yeah.
I've never like--
I think that way too.
I do think that way about McDonald's.
No, but like just to think about like the amount of chicken that they must kill to make it.
Oh yeah, how many chickens they just throw into the grinder?
Oh dude, yeah.
Billions of chickens.
Dude, like it's insane how much, like I don't, I could never go like vegan or like pescatarian
again.
Yeah.
But the thought of that gets me so mad.
I do think, I think like...
Oh yeah, it's so, it's so awful dude.
Eating meat is something that's like, I think clearly morally wrong and like at some point
you should. I think that's my... I mean I might do what my grandpa did and just go
vegan at 40. It's just one of those things like I think it's honestly one of those
things like like every like thing that we look back on in history and we're like
that's horrible where people just didn't try not to think about it at the time.
They probably knew it was wrong but they're just like yeah well it's easier if I don't
think you know. I bet the one that's after after that like like in like 50 years is
people are gonna look back and we were like why did we think it was okay to own
pets? Yeah. I bet that's gonna be one after that is like... Except for my
beautiful baby doll. Except for my beautiful genetically modified Pomeranian. Yeah listen
my pitbull or my fucking pug has not taken a breath in his life. This pug, this Pomeranian mix, oh man. He vomits out of love.
Yeah yeah yeah he has he's never inhaled he just has he's just been gradually
deflating his lungs over his lifespan and once they're empty he's done for. Those
fucking dogs are so fucked up dude. It's insane. Dude pugs are like, pugs
shouldn't exist in nature. Pugs try actively to commit suicide. Yeah. They're just constantly
trying to fall off the couch enough times that they die. Pugs and I think like any like
teacup poodle. Or like a chihuahua. Teacup pet. Yeah. Chihuahua though. I think a chihuahua
is like a normal dog. There is no such thing as a normal dog. I think all dogs are pretty
fucked up. All dogs are completely fucked up. That's why they all get like insane cancer.
Yeah, they all just grow like tumors at the end of their life.
Yeah, they just grow tumors on their legs.
Everybody's dog who dies are like, "Yeah, well, we had to cut one leg off and then another
leg off."
Right.
People keep their dogs alive longer than they should.
I think.
I feel like, I don't know, people have a dog that's just limping all the time.
Yeah, it's like a dog that's blind and can't smell and has no tongue.
And they're like, "Yeah."
Right, a dog with no teeth at all.
And they're like, "God, he loves watching TV."
Yeah, he has a hole in the side of his body.
He's daddy's little guy.
But sometimes he sees himself in the mirror and he pees.
So he's got some life in him still. He's kicking it.
He's 18 months old, yeah?
Yeah, he's real old. He's 18 months.
Oh look, oh my god, look, look, look, look, look.
He's sleeping. Oh, he's having a nightmare.
Oh, he's so scared right now.
Oh my god, he's so scared of his thoughts. Look at that.
Oh my god.
He's so scared of his thoughts right now. He'll warm up to you though.
He'll warm up. Yeah, he thinks that you're a robber.
He tried to kill you as soon as you walked in. He thinks you're the most evil monster. He can't even comprehend you
He looks at you. He's a black fog
He'll warm up to you. He sees a black fog with a swastika armband. Yeah
He thinks you're lightning actually, so if you go into the garage for ten minutes, yeah, he'll warm up to you. I promise
Yeah, you just have to give him beef
Beef on you for a really carry dry cereal in your
cinnamon life you could give my dog? Just let him eat one of your boogers, I promise. He loves them.
You give him a thimble of water, he's gonna love you. My friend used to have a fish that he named
booger and he only fed him boogers. How long did it stay alive? Like years. Really? Yeah. God damn.
So good. Didn't say it. Anytime he would have people over, he'd be like, "Yeah, just like feed
feed him a booger if you don't mind. I love North Carolina. I can't wait to go
back this month dude. Yeah. Fucking Thanksgiving's gonna rule. You forgot
about Thanksgiving? You guys having boogers? I'm having boogers for dinner. Yeah. Yeah. Having boogers for
Thanksgiving. What are you guys doing for Thanksgiving? Anything funny? No. No. Okay.
You're not gonna like, I don't know. Do a prank? Do a prank for Thanksgiving? I'm
gonna put the turkey on my head like Mr. Bean at Christmas. I think I might make
some Brussels sprouts or something. Nice. Yeah. I'm actually having Thanksgiving
with the cranks local Native American tribe this year yeah I think thanks to
showing up yeah I'm trying to reach out you know I brought blankets hey guys I
brought electricity it's just a family in there yeah we're like 1/16 we don't
even know I think it's kind of just a rumor my grandpa started so he didn't
have to go to the war. It's crazy how many white people are just like yeah I'm
part Cherokee it's like yeah it's okay Liz Warren. Dude yes. Yes. Let's go. Pat has been politically on fire
since Biden got elected. He gave him a second wind dude. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. The dumbest guy
to ever talk about politics. It would insist on doing it. Yep. That's right. Yeah.
Yeah. It's cool how little I know. Yeah and just so sure yourself and every time
you're just like well what I do know is the Democrats are total
buttheads. Yeah. But you know what's even worse? The Republicans. Drop that mic and get the fuck out.
It's almost like the demo the Democrats are friends with the Republicans nowadays. It's almost like they're boyfriends
It's almost like they're kissing and they're loving and they're getting real shout out to the working-class. Yeah
Real shit
Political podcast are you just say like, you know what?
Republicans I don't fuck with you working-class. You're the real ones up top. Let's give it up for the proletariat. Yeah the proletarians
I love you guys. I'm gonna get up for probes. Bourgeoisie, how about you suck this pee?
Okay, uh-huh
Political rhymes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I'm a conscious
Hip-hopper and I need to tell you that Wall Street gonna turn into Ball Street. Tell you what
I gotta guess what I know Wall Street money never sleeps
Never. Yeah, I've been trying to get rid of the electric collage rate lately. So
I thought electric collage was your your subconscious hip-hop collective that's
cool name that's not bad yeah yeah yeah we're the electric collage and we got
we got a soldering iron uh-huh for your ass Steve Bannon I'd like to put you in a
I'd like to heave you with a cannon Steve Bannon Steve Bannon how about you go and
see Nick Cannon cuz I'm gonna go wilding out on your ass yes Rudy Giuliani say hi
to my friend Christopher Moltisanti he played a gangster in show and he's gonna
shoot you. Is he gonna be so mean to you? Realistically Christopher Moltisanti probably loved Rudy
Giuliani. Oh absolutely dude. He's a fucking best. Yeah. That Borat girl she's a whore.
A whore. They caught Rudy with a fucking whore. A whore. They caught her with a fucking whore.
I love how he says he calls his girlfriend a whore over and over in that show. I've kind
of picked up on that. My new thing is anytime in a movie or something if I'm watching it
with Jana and like somebody does like domestic abuse I'll just slap her on the
knee once and be like got you ass why do you do that because it's because she's
scared of me don't do that she likes it you unlearn that behavior right now sir I
love learning behaviors yeah don't do anything around me I'll learn it Donald
Trump more like Borat Gump he's a combo of those two guys yeah he's just as
stupid as both of them combined. He's Russian like Borat and he has fucking fetal alcohol
syndrome like Donald Trump. Like Donald Trump yeah.
Okay. Did Forrest Gump just have fetal alcohol syndrome? I don't know I know his mom was
fucking ugly. What are you talking about Sally Field is beautiful. Man shut up did I ask? She's
a talented actress. Did I? Talent don't mean nothing to my balls. Have you seen her in Mrs.
Mrs. Doubtfire?
She was hot as Mrs. Doubtfire.
That's true.
Damn, Mrs. Doubtfire, ooh, come over here.
Damn.
I got a seat saved for you right here.
Yeah, meet our new housekeeper, boys.
Damn, what's up, Doubtfire?
You're thicker than a snake.
God damn.
Come over here, daddy.
Ooh, get over here, Mrs. Doubtfire.
Damn, daddy.
What kind of fucking toilet paper are you stuffing in that chest?
Look at you.
God damn.
Come sit on my lap, Mrs. Doubtfire.
You built like a Mack truck, lady.
in that chest look at you god damn come sit on my lap miss doubtfire build like a
mac truck lady and i want to honk you
horn miss doubtfire
no she was so she was their dad she got though when she got that fire on her
boobies that was like oh yeah i was like i want to
here let me put it out wink yeah with my butt with my fucking
(spitting)
- Can I just spit on your tits for a little bit?
- Disgusting.
That noise I just fucking made.
- Let's stop.
- Yeah, we'll end the episode on that.
- Bye guys.