come back a bit
marianne where i thought that's on are as i said we'd you know i'm gonna right
now i'm gonna court give a piece of paper as i am disappointed have uh...
like to make a report card okay yeah i want to make a report on the other
yearly five person oppressed record yet uh... just but i just had the same i
I have this paper here that I wrote a few Mad Libs for you.
Let's hold on a second. We'll get to your Mad Lib in a minute.
We have to start this report card here.
Help me think of some category.
Are we going to explain why we're doing a report card?
If you want to, I don't care. That's your decision.
I took one Adderall before we recorded.
Honestly, this might be good for you to get a prescription,
because it's hard to get a prescription for...
you could show them your report card.
You could bring this to your psychiatrist.
We are doing you such a favor.
Help me think of some categories here.
Think about my little things.
Phone usage is number one.
Right?
Which you've been good at recently.
I would say A- average as of late.
Let's see.
Looking at noises outside.
Getting distracted like a dog.
That's one.
Did you hear that noise just now?
see where my eyes were.
See, like, there's, they were right on me.
They were right on me.
Okay.
Um, and then I would say maybe voice work, maybe if he's, if he's slipping in a couple
voices, a couple impressions.
Okay, voice work.
Right?
Alright.
A couple impressions.
I think he could go for that today.
I think this might be a good day.
I think, um, let the games begin.
What other ones?
I feel like, yeah, riffage.
Riffage and bits, my wish.
I fucking love riffing.
Riffage, just riffing it out.
Oh my god, dude.
Just riffing it out.
Bitsmithing.
Speaking, speaking of bits.
Oh, wait, I got it.
Stories.
it stories you have a bit or a story stories stories with ending stories
with endings yeah that's big I have it I have a bit I've prepared oh my god a new
riffing wait hold up pretend I didn't say that I have a bit prepared okay all
right okay so pretend even that's a little bit pretend he fuck pretend that I
came into this organically okay okay okay so we were doing Mad Libs earlier
yeah so I just wanted to read these honestly these are pretty funny oh yeah
I mean you've seen us do Mad Libs before guys.
We did do Mad Libs before.
A lot of times I'm going to be real.
We've been in a potty humor.
Poop, poop, poop.
I forget their name but somebody at the Seattle show gave us a history of the world Mad Libs.
I want to say thank you for that.
And here's a little thing that we had fun with.
Yeah we did.
Alright read it out.
Read the title of the Mad Libs.
Okay so this one is called Light My Fire.
Okay.
And it's about cavemen.
I'm already thinking some fucking nasty stuff.
about cavemen yeah okay at one time man walked on four legs no spoken short
grunts and did not know how to make a small fire here's the story of the day
that changed mankind forever translated from the peculiar cave speed caveman
number one it's colder than the Arctic in this cave even my warmest mammoth fur
won't keep my body from shivering bruh caveman - if only there was a way to make
the cold cave warmer oh man one I'm bored I think I'll play with these little
sticks of wood. No, dude. Caveman number two, why don't you rub them quickly together and see what
happens. Caveman number one. Hey kids, don't do that at home. Right? Caveman number one.
Caveman, don't do this at your caves. Yeah, hey caveman. Unless you need a fire. Don't do this at cave.
Unless you need a fire. Don't do this at cave. Caveman number one. Wow!
there's smoke coming off of these small sticks fuck me ouch it's hot in the
name of God they didn't we made heat that good caveman number one we shall
call this magical flaming peculiar fire Wow that was I mean hey I know was he
yeah that was another one this one is called Eureka
- I did two. - Oh shit.
- I did two Mad Libs by myself.
- Above and Beyond.
- Yeah, all right, I'm ready to hear this one.
- I'm gonna add a category to your report card
called Above and Beyond. - Above and Beyond.
- Extra credit. (laughing)
Above and Beyond.
Okay, wait, are we doing it?
We're doing a halfway check-in as well, right?
- We have to. - We can do that.
- Yeah, that's why we have two things.
- So at the 30 minute point, we will--
- We'll check in, we'll see how you're doing.
- Yeah, we'll check in,
we'll tell you where you need to improve.
- Okay. - Right?
Me and Cameron will do a little bit of deliberation.
right me and camera do a little bit of deliberation semester one semester to
there you go okay a little parent teacher conference throughout history
inventors have been responsible for everyday things like computers cars and
cell phones. These are some of the most famous jobs in history. A person's famous
little job. Well it says occupations plural. Oh yeah that's what I was
supposed to fill in. And you put John. Oh okay. Benjamin Franklin was not only a
founding father of the United States, he also invented many things including
bifocal glasses which allow people to see things near and far. He also invented the
lightning rod which protects houses from electric bolts of lightning.
No.
Johanns Gutenberg was a German inventor. Bad Patrick! Bad Patrick! Come on. Just
fuck it. Who invented the printing press, a machine that could print words and
images to make books, newspapers, and Bibles.
Fuck you.
That's just too bad.
Thomas Edison was an accomplished inventor.
(Laughter)
No, dude. Do not show this to your parents.
Yeah, my mom's gonna be pissed if she sees what I wrote.
I'll say it. I'll rate it up.
perhaps best known for making a light bulb that the average homeowner could
use he also invented the phonograph which was the first machine to be able to
record the human voice and then play it back Wow and those are just some of the
mad libs that I made yeah oh my god I think you're the fucking you have a mad mind
mind. Yeah, I mean that was twisted. My feathered friend. I actually did one earlier too. You're
as sharp as a fucking axe today. I actually did one, yeah. When did you do one? I just
did one earlier. Oh really? Yeah, can I read it out to you guys? Yeah, I mean I don't have
a credit, a report card for you. Well it's just a mad lib, it's for fun. I mean, yeah.
Okay. Yeah, is that okay? I filled in some funny ass shit. Yeah. Okay. I just wanted
kind of see his kind of all right it's fine no I got one I mean I just filled in
what it's a pay attention see this was another test he's letting you do yeah
okay wow giving him an out I just yeah you know I did the mat I filled in what
was supposed to be on the line for all right I'm right to the mad lips I can
read it yeah this one's called the coat of the samurai okay so that's samurai's
coat or code code coat code like a samurai's coat every pretty sleek be
pretty funny right if it was called coat of the samurai, maybe not I mean I can
you let me do the funny stuff because it's yeah yeah it's a mad live all
right samurai were ancient adjective Japanese warriors who followed a
adjective code of virtue, which contained these a plural noun samurai
believe justice was the most adjective virtue. They always show courage in the
face of plural noun samurai may have had the power to verb, but they also needed
to show mercy to all plural noun. It was important to be polite and
considerate of other people's plural noun samurai. I also thought honesty was
best noun. Plural noun were not an option for the samurai who tried to verb with
honor. Samurai were loyal to their fellow plural noun and finally they had to show
character and that they knew the difference between right and noun. Okay I
would like to add one more category, giggle bear. I need you to add giggle
bear right now because he he did a great job on giggle bearing right there. That
was a right. He helped sell it. He giggle bared that. That was huge. Okay all right
so the giggle bear is out. All right so read the categories back real quick. Okay
so we got and then we can formally start okay yeah yeah we got phone usage yep
looking at noises outside
voice work i'm watching like a hawk voice work stories with endings above and
beyond and giggle bear. I should is that out there there's no noise that they
didn't even look he didn't even look dude we're going to train you into oh my
God he looked at me, but i'm inside, but he didn't look outside yeah, no or i'll
outside or upstairs. That's okay. Yeah, outside or upstairs. That's a yeah,
ignore ignoring children noises upstairs and stuff. Yeah.
Yeah. So earlier we did like we did a sweep of the office. We started
organizing all the costume closet. Yeah, we got to take care of stuff like
that. I'm a listen. I'm a bit. I'm a small business owner. Okay. We have to
sometimes you have to throw out eight ghillie suits. Yeah, it's just part of
being a business. We also did an audit of how I've been using the offices.
storage unit. Yeah, we did look through what all we found. Okay, so we thought I
thought that this closet was full of just crate like a huge pile of costumes. Well, okay, okay, let me
preface this by saying, hold on. Put prefacing on there. Prefacing, put a lot of...
So, before, so I used to keep a suitcase here of all the clothes that I
couldn't sell at Beacon's Closet. Makes perfect sense. Yeah, because I didn't want
to have a giant suitcase in my house. Yeah, and there's no other place for
clothes to go. Exactly. Yeah, no one needs those. Exactly. So I kept under in a
smaller closet that we have here that's under a staircase, I kept a suitcase full
of clothes that I couldn't sell. Yeah. And I thought no one would ever notice it.
And then... So you actively thought like... You were trying to put one over... You were
trying to pull the wool over my eyes a little bit. Yes, and I admit it. Oh wow. I mean I saw it every single day.
And then we needed a suitcase for the Pacific Northwest leg of the
the tour and so you don't know that was the biggest suitcase we had so I threw
all of the clothes into the into the costume closet. Okay, so that's why all
my clothes are in there. So yeah, we found I thought that it was all
costumes. The first five things I pulled out were just t shirts that were his
yeah. I would say it was way more. This is the bag of of your clothes. Well,
it's not just it's Joe stuff to Joe had maybe two shirts and Joe had a lot more
than now. He had he had two shirts and a completely white pair of jeans, which I
believe he bought in the first place. Well he had those for the birthday boy video.
I don't think so because I've seen him wear them before that.
Really? Yeah. He was he ruined them in the birthday. He claimed that those were good jeans.
Yeah. Fully white. Well they were Levi's they were uh what are they like 514s? It's fine to
wear white pants in the day of summer but listen if you're gonna wear white pants. You gotta wear
a white shirt too. It can't be jeans. White jeans is weird. What are you Pitbull? Why are you walking
around with white jeans on? White jeans are cool. Not these ones dude. These look like shit. I like
I like the Dickies Painters Pants.
Those look cool.
- Yeah, but that's cool if you get a bunch
of your paint on 'em.
- Yeah, you get a bunch of paint on 'em,
or you go like a Heathcliff shirt thing.
- My personal paint got all on my Dickies.
Had to throw 'em away.
- Okay, see, if you had a report card right now,
that would be a fucking F for being crass.
- What, it's okay.
- Yeah, put crassness on there.
- I have not even said a single crass thing.
- Oh my God, I'm having a crass day.
- Yeah, cussing and crassness.
Like, 'cause that's a crutch, right?
Everybody's guilty of that sometimes.
us to I feel like crassness covers the grass this includes cussing as well
crassness yeah so no I'm talking about I need don't talk about your used napkin
don't talk and what you used it for your squelching your skin welching sock leave
us to that no no come shot don't don't say listen don't say a couple of used
napkins of yours today those are from sweat that makes it worse I wish it was
my food. I wish you was food, but it's your sweat. Don't I just don't Pat. I
don't want you to be it today. Don't say anything along the lines of when
scientists looked at my bathroom napkin through a microscope. It looked like a
Hieronymus Bosch painting. Don't say that is like Chris Bosch's brother.
I was the guy who drew all the sperms. He drew hell a bunch of his body did a
lot of the scary hell. Okay, you got another F for being too obscure. Yeah,
it's not obscure at all obscure being obscure. You guys are just uncultured.
yeah i don't have a report card so you cannot create my mental report
always a report i don't see it i don't have a brain which you would be able to
see and i'm grading myself to ok i'm yeah i'm re i'm greeting you that's
really what i should go in above and beyond listen listen tonight can i tell
you guys i don't know beyond you get up i'm giving you a point above and beyond
is a great myself
uh... with some point system it's it's it's a normal grateful it's letters but
i will say i i i am i'm grading uh... caleb and a plus
for being judgmental because i don't think he should lose points 'cause i'm
I'm not judgmental. I'm doing the same. You better be judgmental because we're judging
him. I'm judging him. I'm not judging you. You get an A+ for sweetness and kindness.
Thank you. You're talking about cleaning up the costume closet. I get an A+ because today
I watched four Planet Earth clips, so I get a curiosity score. And I cleaned the costume
closet. That's big. I almost am coming in with a serious kind of A potential, right?
I took a short listen. I'd like to give you guys both a plus for for holding it
down while mommy was away. We did hold it down. Did it go well fire s episode? I'll
see you know we did an hour five. Well, it's fucking fun. We were having all the
credit and beyond and because I couldn't tell how long we've been recording
because I actually stopped the recorder a couple times. Yeah, but it was it wasn't
actually stop it because he said stop and I didn't know that you could pause
it. So I click the square because I thought it was the rules. Well DVD rules
still the square is not yeah this way I was not allowed to use the remote as a
kid yeah cuz I thought I turn on closed caption ever get those DVD games as a
kid yes the Santa Claus to the replacement car yep they have the games
in the yeah anything and you just like yeah go back and forth you do that with
monsters ball and can pretend you're controlling Halle Berry's body with the
remote control no it's the swordfish one you press up and down on the mmm she
does that in Monsters ball - oh really crass toss no not Tommy Lee Jones bad
Santa what's his name Ben Stiller bad Santa no oh bad Santa he would be a bad
Santa because of his heritage but who's the actual bad Santa Billy Bob Thornton
Billy Bob Thornton Halle Berry there's a conspiracy theory yeah that Halle Berry
actually had Billy Bob Thornton's penis in her in them but that was when Billy Bob
was with Angelina Jolie that's why it's a conspiracy okay yeah do you think any of
those I want to get that Billy Bob tattoo so bad I've talked about it before what
is it I think Steve-o did it already was the say it on it it's literally Angelina
Jolie had like a tattoo on her bicep that said Billy Bob with a dragon you
want to get that I want it that's a video yeah what do you guys ever think
that actors and actresses when they're in those movies are actually fucking
having sex and not simulating. I think a lot of porno movies, I think it's
unsimulated. Really? You think so? And a lot of porno browsers. Yeah. I was thinking
about... I think sometimes it's simulated. I think sometimes it's simulated. I think it's unsimulated. I feel like you can tell when somebody is faking having sex.
Yeah. You know, because they look too normal. You know, they're not like... I mean
some of these actors and actresses though, they're so famous, they're having sex so
constantly that it's like to them it's like nothing. A chore. Yeah, it's like a chore to me.
It's like when I like have to eat my sandwich or something.
Would you guys ever do a sex scene in a movie?
Yeah.
Whoa.
You answered that so fast.
Whoa, all right.
My man.
No, I definitely wouldn't.
You definitely wouldn't?
No.
What if it was a part of the movie, though?
Maybe if I got like rich.
Why would I be in a movie, first of all?
What if I was an actor?
You're the lead actor, right?
Okay, if I was an actor and I lived in Hollywood, a completely different life, then yes.
No, you don't live, it doesn't matter where you live.
I'm an actor. I'm an actor. No, you're in a movie. Okay, and it's a movie. Huh?
I don't live in Hollywood. It's a good question.
I see the hypothetical guys.
Is he fucking a human or a beast?
He's in Beast Fucker.
Okay, it's like a if it's a but he's fucking a human and if it was a beast,
I would say yes, because probably like a puppet or something.
Yeah, but they probably put a fleshlight at the bottom.
Olivia Olivia Munn is in the puppet suit, right?
And you're and also your girlfriend's there because she's the director.
damn yep and she's gonna want to direct the sex scene part she doesn't want to
direct the movie she's doing it to get out of a student loan debt damn yeah so
with this scenario in mind actually that should be the real I live in Hollywood
it doesn't matter where you live it does live and you live on Hollywood Boulevard
you live every single my famous actor yes you're the most furious oh I looked
it's bright out right now. He looked. That's a sound. I'm marking that down. That's a demerit.
He looked. Well, I was using... Okay, well, hold on, hold on. That was a full...
Bringing me back to my original story about the costume closet, I had to hand wash...
He's kind of saving it right now. I had to hand wash my Austin Powers costume.
Yes. And I was like... Tell them why.
I put it... It was covered in sand. It wasn't sand. It was some kind of body
thing that he put on it, some kind of fungus. I think it was a fungus.
Yeah. No, there was a fungus on it. Yeah. Well, I had to hand wash it.
yep and then and then I was gonna hang it up from the curtain I was gonna hang up
the pants from the curtain but they were a little bit too wet so I put my
sucking wet I put them outside and I was like guys what if it rains and you you
told me who cares it's not gonna rain Austin Powers cost immediately started
raining well does it matter if you rather have dripping wet floor or a wet
costume that was already wet or you can clean up the floor yeah I'm looking now
because the Sun is out tomorrow. Okay I honestly thought you were gonna redeem
yourself for looking outside and you completely you just made me even more
mad. Really? Yeah so now in that category well we're not quite yeah we're not
I've been taking some notes on here so just know that we you're gonna see we're
gonna need to see some improvement in that second half on that specific
category. Okay. All right I'm just telling you that. Well that's fine.
Anyway, would so you have you would you put the piece of don't they take a pill that like a hills their boner cuz it's like
They do that
Kills your boner and then they put like a string around your penis
Cuz if I'm if they put a string around your penis and they yank
Blaming I'm not blaming any actor for yank it to the back of your butt
They have a string and then as soon as it gets near any kind of vagina or you had a hole they they have a guy
That's what the best boy does. The best boy, if there's a sex scene, he holds a
string and he yanks it like he's pulling a tooth out.
I just saw Cameron taking notes, sorry. But the people who are...
I don't know why you're saying that.
We need to do this every episode.
This is so good.
I do not blame any actor or actress for...
if you're, oh you have to fuck Angelina Jolie
or Chris Evans or something,
and they're a MILF and you're a slut,
it's like, dude, I'm popping one.
- Exactly.
- And I'm sorry.
- But if there is a pill that you can take
that kills your boner--
- Why am I not taking it all the time?
- Yeah, why did I--
- Why have I ever popped boners?
They should be giving that out to school.
- There's so many people who sit on my lap on the bus.
- Yeah, if you take--
- So many old women with dementia think I'm a seat
on the bus and they sit down and I get heart.
If you ever take a bus, if you ever have to sit in a classroom, or especially like a classroom,
like a once a year classroom, like a driving class or some shit.
If you go to the DMV, you're definitely getting hard.
If you're opening up, you're 110% popping a boner at the DMV.
I haven't had a public boner in so long.
Because I never go out early in the morning anymore until we went on our multiple trips.
and I've had so many like this. It's so I've been sitting on so many planes and
buses and trains with a big boner. I had a really, really bad moment on the on
our flight back where I sat down. I was like fuck. I have to pee, but I was like
fuck. I have a boner. I wonder if I can kill it before I get up and you guys
hadn't sat down yet and I was like all right, I'm going to go get up to pee and
then I got up to pee. I have a boner, but I'm like you know what if I just walk
confidently and I don't bring attention to it, nobody's going to notice and I'll
be right in the bathroom and then I get to the bathroom. There's a five person
for the bathroom. So I just sat there behind a lady waiting for the plane
bathroom with a boner. I'm sure everyone noticed.
Which flight? The flight back.
Flight back, yeah. Flight back you sat in the way back of the plane. Oh no it must
have been the flight there. Yeah, because I sat with you. Yeah you would have had no
problem. You were sitting next to me. No, not a single boner dude. I texted
you to let you know, because I remember I got stuck in the back of the plane.
I had to go to the bathroom and I walked all the way to the back while the guy
had maybe he got stuck between the the he got stuck behind basically the the
concessions person yeah because he went and used the bathroom and then as he
popped out they had the car was already going uh-huh yeah and there's nothing
you can do yeah he just had to sit back there and I was sitting next to two
people who were... They had a big greasy bag of KFC. They like brought through
security bags of KFC and they were eating dried squid as well. Yeah, I texted him because I was like
dude the lady next to you has a bag of grease and dried squid. It was one of the worst
flights of my life. I told you I had... The Crusher? No, he's the Beater. The Beater.
Yeah, he said he was the Breaker. The Breaker, that's what it was.
To my right... The Crusher, the Beater, the Breaker. To my right... Those were two other guys that were on the plane.
To my right, there was a giant woman who had headphones in and was snoring and
then farting really loudly, like really stinky farts the entire time. To my left,
KFC and dried squid. To my, basically, catty corner to me, crying baby, right in
front of me, a kid, two kids and their mom, and the kid says, ten minutes into the
flight, "Mommy, I'm a new superhero. I'm the Breaker." And she goes, "Oh, that's funny."
And he just starts beating the shit out of the seat that's right in front of me.
So I'm hearing the knocking of the breaker, right? I'm hearing the screaming person,
the screaming kid. I'm smelling farts, hearing the farts, hearing snoring,
Dried Squid KFC right next to me. And that son was a breaker to his own mom.
Yeah.
Yeah, because it was a mom's son and they're speaking, I don't know the language, but they
were fighting. The son started beating up his mom like every hour pretty much.
Wow.
He would just punch her in the arm a bunch of times.
That's crazy.
Yeah, it was not a... I really did not like that.
The screen in the back of the...
Yeah, our TV didn't work.
work. Well yours yours work. No I didn't I wasn't it was not that it didn't work.
It was not that it didn't work. It was mine was completely there. His was fine.
I do all I could do on it. He couldn't get to his channel. He like yeah that was
I wanted to watch my screen. My screen was completely broken and that it was it
would be black and they would flash white over and over so I would have my eyes
closed trying to go to sleep and I would just get white flashes in my eyes over
and over the entire night. It was so horrible. I feel like that would have
brought me right. I have such a terrible fear of a plane being struck by
lightning so it kind of looks like is that what you think lightning hitting a
plane would look like no but I find my sleep and I'm woken up by a bright flash
that's not a great thing to be woken up by if I'm scared of lightning we were
responsible for the emergency exit we'd were we did a great job the best possible
it was great it was even you know what it was it was it was literally yeah it
was it because usually because yeah usually when you get more legroom and on
all the plans when you have the most legroom and come on top of adding more
legroom I feel like on a lot of planes you get emergency row you can't put your
Personal item under the seat, but we could still do that. Yep. We had we had personal item access and extra leg room
That's why you should have fucking came with us when we got our seats. Yeah, you were being on
I was I don't want to I want to go to the bathroom
I had I was in the bathroom you guys
And then you said go up to had to do this with me. I know I don't want to I want to go to the bathroom
That's a good now you have to do an impression of me this is you an animal crossing I
I don't know what that is. Do a gay girl reference thing and give him an A+ for that.
A gay girl reference? Yeah, because he knows what I'm all about.
I'm not going to do a gay girl reference. A lot of normal men play Animal Crossing.
You think gay guys aren't normal? No.
That's really, really interesting. Okay. They have a lot of...
Put a homophobia one. Homophobia category.
Gay guys have very good taste in dance music. I think honestly...
completely redeemed myself. Not homophobic. I do think goth people are, after
going, rivaling the LGBT community for nightlife. Well, usually I think there's a, I think those go
hand-in-hand. Really? But you can have one without the other. So I think, yeah. I think
that, but I think goth is either neck-and-neck or beating out the
LGBTQ community as far as having fun parties and bars. Somebody told me last
last night that that bar Talon has a goth night. I can't remember what I think I
think that I know where that one is I think that a goth night is not as good
as a goth bar. I think that's gonna be the bad version. Goth bar has to because
goth bar you not everyone at the goth bar is goth right it's just where the it's a
it's a home base. Goth night is also where I think goth night is where people
who aren't goth will pretend to be goth. Exactly and there's a difference between
a karaoke night in a karaoke bar, I'll tell you that much.
Yeah, absolutely. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Don't even get me started.
True. Just don't get me started. Don't. No, all right. All right, Pat.
Don't even get me started. I was going to get him started. No, no, get him started.
I was going to get him started and he told me not to. No, Pat, listen.
I'm just following the rules. For your report card, next topic, what are we talking about? I brought up
the sex scene thing. I want to, I do want to do karaoke again. I love karaoke. I'm honestly,
I was like it used to be a thing where it's like trivia night where it's like I if it's there
I'll do it. But like now I'm like, I'll fucking I'll just go there. I was told of a guy who has a living room somewhere in
Brooklyn and it's like is like a big-ass living room and it's I think it's not like invite only but it's you you
You have to like know about it to some degree. They don't have like a website or anything, but you
It's a it's like the best karaoke system in
world I don't know about the world
just in this guy's house I guess him and his wife really love karaoke I guess I
want to know what does it mean the best one you guys maybe it's me what I don't
understand what what the tech what's the tech different machine that's also a
a gravity bong yes okay yeah you can put weed in the in the mic you put weed in
the mic and it smokes it out like it's hookah I saw one of the most evil
fucking disgusting fucking Democrat inventions I've ever seen in my life in
Seattle yeah it was a it was a coffee mug that said wake and bake and it had a
built-in way to smoke marijuana dude what the fuck what kind of person would
do that that's not right smoke marijuana and drink coffee what the fuck is wrong
That's like mixing - that's like a high and a low, that's an upper and a downer.
Exactly. You're putting your heart at risk.
You could die.
That is what Chris Farley died of.
Nice.
Weed and coffee.
That's why his nose was bleeding in the picture.
He drank too much weed and too much coffee.
He bought an eighth of weed.
Chris Farley died from smoking weed.
Actually, he pushed three cups of Café Busteau out of a French press too.
That's dangerous. That's high MGs.
you guys know why they call it an eighth of weed? Why? Because when you smoke it
you end up in the eighth circle of hell. Yeah that's right. The eighth and the
eighth. And there's only seven. Yeah yeah. I thought there's not. I thought there was nine.
It's a hundred. There's a hundred? Oh sorry have you guys been to hell? No.
Have you? Okay good. I've been to hell. But probably there's a hundred. You've been to hell?
Oh shit. Holy fucking shit. Oh my god. He's going for he's going for a plus. I always forgot.
That's above and beyond right there. I forgot that I technically did, I passed my driver's
test, the written part. Yeah. But I just can't get behind the wheel of a car without like
freaking out. Just close your eyes. Yeah, I guess I should do that. Will you teach me
to drive Caleb? I would love to teach both of you to drive. I'm a wonderful teacher.
I really would like to. I tried to, I took the driver's test and I accidentally, I went
into the wrong lane. You know what the worst part of the driver's test is? The only hard
hard part is when they are the at least the guy that I had he was like he does a
jump scare he's like okay so what you're gonna do is you're gonna come up here 15
miles an hour break he says well and he's like reaction testing you I feel
like that's not fair cuz when you have to break suddenly it's not someone else
break yeah yeah where'd you go the just for laughs driving school I went to
actually ranked yeah that's my bad yeah I shouldn't have done that but I was
already up there. Yeah, that's why you're driving a clown car. Yeah, where did you go to the
Korean web comic driving school where they jump scare you? Yeah. I forgot about that.
That one's scary. That is scary. Oh, 30 minutes. Okay, all right. All right. Quick check. Let's
go through here. All right. All right. Phone usage. I mean, that's A+. That's an A+. He
hasn't even looked at it. And it's not in the normal middle of the table spot where I
can easily do a monitor on it. It's off to the side, but I haven't even seen you reach
for it. But you have a better vantage point. No, he hasn't gone for it once. Looking at
noises outside or upstairs. I'm going to give you because of that one. I'm going
to give you a B plus. I think a B plus is fair, but that's pretty good. You know
that's above average. That is well above average for you. Yeah, voice work now we
have now what have you done all too much voice work, but you did me me me me me
so we'll just animal crossing. He also did he did a stoner voice when he was
talking about up. See he's he's on top of this stuff. He slid in yeah. He's going
for it. Okay, well I'll give you an a minus just because that neither of them
were really like full impressions. Well, I think there's a bias here for that a
minus. Why? I think it should at least be an A. Because one of them was making fun of you. I feel like I think I think it was an A. I think him being on top of it and throwing in the stoner voice because he knew that the me me me wasn't hitting. I think that's deserving of it. But were either of those voices on their own A's? I don't know. I'm not. I think Caleb the animal crossing. I'm going to give you the A minus with the expectation you're going to hit an A plus in the second half. Yeah. Because I can see you. I can see you getting there easily. I'm going to give you room for improvement. Also is this
is this a cumulative or these separate I think these are separate or we can call
a cumulative I guess all right that's probably better yeah that's fine because
then you can get to perfect here yeah and then we got stories with endings now
here I'm not so sure about this because you had a story about the suitcase right
and the ending was that you put your your costume outside and we also have a
story about your driver's test and the ending of your story about your driver's
first test is that you went into the wrong lane and I'm wondering here what
we think on the grading committee about these endings. That was not a story.
That was an anecdote. I think a story is going to be a story yeah. I don't think
we have shorts. It was the short short story and it did have an ending so the
ending, but what happened after you went like I failed the test, okay, but I
kind of want I just need to wrap up a little bit. Is there any other part of
that maybe we need to know. This is just right this is like right at the end of
the of the semester like hey can you just turn in like one little extra paper on
whatever you want. And then I tried to I had the same instructor. Oh so you went
back? I went back the next week, same instructor. Okay. And I did the same thing.
That's a good ending. Okay, alright we take that. That's an A+. I have more driving stories.
We'll give you an A+. See that's a story I might not be happy to read in a
book. Yeah. But it's certainly you know. I'd love to hear from my friends.
exactly face yeah that's a plus above and beyond. I had you I had you down for
two above and beyond points. I don't remember what the first one was for the
second one was for that that incisive comment about the DMV, which was good
that was inside that was fucking good yeah I liked that a lot. I mean this is
kind of an extra credit section, so I'm thinking maybe we do points instead of
a great view seven extra points. We'll give you seven points for the first and
that could possibly bring you up from like you know if that stays a B plus
then maybe if your distractions one stays a B+ we might be able to move that
credit kind of over give you a full A. Yeah yeah you know and then we'll
calculate your GPA at the end as well. Now we got we got we got Giggle Bear.
What are we thinking Giggle Bear? Honestly I think I've only heard you Giggle Bear out
once this entire half. That's not true. This first half. And you've been great at home.
You've laughed. You've laughed but I'm not sure you've Giggle Bear that much. We'll give you two
Giggle Bears. Yeah. Which counts. Which to me is also an extra credit. You think
the giggle bears and actually credit buddy you're the giggle bear the you are
giggle. We need you to giggle bear. I think maybe that's a c plus well yeah,
we'll give him a c plus we gotta be we gotta be fair here. Yeah, so I'm all I'm
saying is you better be smiling this and now unfortunately pet that brings us to
crassness and there was a regretful comment you made about a string being
tied around a penis and you also uttered the word vagina. Vagina is a medical
term. We'll give you vagina but putting a string around a fucking penis. Yeah that's rough.
I was talking about the process in Hollywood so I was actually explaining. I don't know
there was a tinge of irreverence to your penis comments. I don't know that you can go behind
the scenes with this one. I don't think that's a good excuse. Although I'm willing to add
behind the scenes knowledge as another thing. If you know any more behind the scenes facts.
I will give crass, so we're rating it obviously an a is the least crass
right yeah, okay, I'm going to say that's a going to be a B minus yeah,
all right, because that's not so
yeah, exactly one. I mean, I would say it's very crass, but it was only one
one, but he didn't say he also action. He didn't say and then the penis around
the day come in my mouth. Yeah, yeah, the penis has ejaculated into my face.
I'm jacking off the penis. I'm sucking okay, so what did you say that was I'm
say B-. B-. On crassness. Okay. Alright. And then as we go into the second half, I'm gonna
go get myself a glass of water. Okay, so a thing that I'm gonna expect here is that you
have something here, right, to fill this time. Yeah. It's just gonna be you two. Okay. Okay.
No brother. Alright. So I'll be right back. Have I told you about my driver's ed instructor
that I had? The one that I dropped out of driver's ed. I don't know. This is good cohesiveness.
Okay, let's get some water now, Caleb. I think I've told you about him before. He, I definitely
have because I took three of his classes and then I couldn't like he the first
day of the I had just gotten two weeks prior I just got my friend got into a
car crash with me in the middle seat uh-huh and the airbag went off and like
broke her eye or some shit whoa it like her I she got out of the car and the
airbag like made her I like blood broke her I was a hanging out of her face it
looked it honestly could have been it that's crazy it wasn't it was just
covering I've never seen an eye covered in blood before remember when when how
about Joe Biden a red-eye yeah Brandon yeah Brandon's cuz he was getting
punched that's right by an airbag oh you think so yeah but so two weeks before
that I got into a car accident or I was in a car that got into an accident I
wasn't driving and then the day one of that class he showed us just nothing
put car crash footage to show us how ABS brakes work and it was just car crash
footage and he's like this like five foot like four Italian guy with giant
wingspan but very short guy. He looks like a Lego man and he's like telling me
like, "Okay well if you take my class you're not gonna get into an accident
like this. If you learn from me I'm here to prevent because driving is a
privilege it's not a right okay and so he said that he could prevent a kid a kid's
death he could have prevented a child's death okay someone who died at my school
real quick no wait someone died the kid got into a car accident and then day one
of my my ex-girlfriend's driver's ed class he made a comment about how he if
he took his class he could damn that's a story I'll say this that was a story
with a voice and I'm not gonna elaborate on on what other kind of story it was
but yeah yeah I some kid drove up a telephone pole at my school damn I knew
this I knew somebody I shouldn't that's too sad
basically just wiped out an entire you never happened in your hometown where
just an entire lunch table whole lunch table one accident damn
That was a huge bummer at the school and this little guy who smoked Paul Malls was just like,
"I could have stopped that. It would have been different if I was his teacher."
What if he had stood in front of the—he could have been the buffer between the two cars?
I think that's what he meant. He could have lifted the car up with his big arms.
Did you guys see that video of the guy? He's sitting at a drag racing thing and he walks
too close and he gets hit by the rear of the car. He flies out and he has an Uzi.
No, but have you seen—there's a video I saw recently.
he like gets fucking his spleen is exploding. It's these guys doing like uh like you know there's
like the burnout circles. Yeah that's what it was yeah. Oh oh I thought you were talking okay well
it's one of those videos and a guy gets hit by the car. Oh yeah. Under the car and the car pants him.
Whoa. Yeah. I saw another one there's a bunch of videos of people getting hit by those cars of
those. Oh yeah. One of them the guy gets hit knocked cold either dead or something a dude
walks up immediately and this is being filmed by like 50 people a guy walks up immediately
checks him for his wallet, takes a lot out and smacks him in the head.
I do remember that one.
I was like, "That was so good."
I saw two guys fighting over... two Middle Eastern guys in front of my apartment today.
And the reason I bring up why they're Middle Eastern is that they're fighting and they're talking to each other
saying like, "I've been American since the day I was born." You're not from... to each other.
they're fighting about who is American and then they got into the same car. I would have stopped them and said I'm
American. They were like fighting each other, they were like pushing each other ready to like actually like fistfight.
Maybe they're brothers. And then they stopped and then they got into the same
Mercedes Benz. They are the fighting brothers. Yeah, they sound like the fighting brothers to me.
But I was like, I don't, I had to leave but I was like, I really want to kind of go over and ask there
Yeah, what's going on? Maybe go John Wilson on it. I wish that I had an entire...
- Which one of you is actually more American?
- And one of them is a little bit more American
than the other.
- I wish that I had a documentary crew
to follow me around constantly, not to film me,
but just anybody I see who looks a little weird,
I would love to just do a full interview with them.
Just like a full, like, just an expose.
- Do you think it'd be funny to,
it's funny that that is a show where you could,
any guy with a camera could literally ruin the show
he just followed him around as much as possible like somehow found out just him
well if he found out it's three camera if you found out all the people and that's
behind the scenes stuff so what that was behind the scenes yeah but if we yeah we
get higher people just ruin a network television show to just walk like what
was his name and just jump in front of the camera Joey boots like yeah they
never know where Joey boots from Stern I think that was a name Joey it's either
it's not Joey Pants, I think it was Joey Boots, it was this guy who would run up to like
news reporters and he would just go "Bubba Bully, Bubba Bully, Howard Stern's
penis!" Yeah that's what I was gonna say, if you're gonna follow a
camera crew around, why go for John Wilson? Yeah. You could like do it to like a news broadcast.
Because he doesn't have like people with him, right? It's just one guy walking around filming
things, or three guys, and so you're walking around just... Two guys, one girl.
Okay, so two guys one girl, so you're walking around and you're maybe dressed funny
And then you're just you ruin all the footage because there's a guy fucking dress. I mean honestly you dress like Hitler if I'm gonna
I'm gonna be completely real
You could do completely
Or an Alibaba Hitler outfit you just ruin everything cuz every single shot he takes there's Hitler there
Yeah, you're not even running up to him. You're just you just have to walk
And now the next season of the show everything's filmed at 3 in the morning
Yes, the fucking avoid Hitler who's outside his house every day, and there's no there's nothing wrong
Like if you're in a public space you can just walk around get in front of cameras. It's it's a
You know because if somebody is dressed up like Hitler, and you were trying to
Record like something that's interesting the most interesting thing in that is like it's always Hitler
This guy is about to get his ass beat. I don't think
like Hitler
I'm an actor, I'm just an actor. Do you not see the camera?
The best part of that too is that ruins the footage in a way that ruins it only for John
Wilson because anybody who's, if he ends up having to put a bunch of Hitler footage in
his show then it's everyone else is like oh this is great there's a guy who dresses up
like Hitler in New York and John Wilson was following him around and he saw some crazy
stuff but John Wilson, no he wanted to get a video of a donut on the ground.
all of a sudden he has no control over his show. Yeah right we've completely
annihilated his yeah, because every single episode he's trying to talk about
and sometimes love is like a butterfly and then the butterflies landing on
Hitler's. It's landing on Hitler's finger like a like a perching parrot right is
actually so g that is that is like the most that's gang stalking yeah. You if
you want to get it honestly, if I don't listen John Wilson, I love your show. I
think you're I think it's a great show. I think you're a genius, but if you do
want to gang stalk somebody, he's a clear target. Yeah. If you want to be like,
yeah, ruin a guy's life, he's so easy to ruin his life. Yeah, yeah, because
you're not just ruining his life, you're ruining his livelihood. Exactly, yeah,
and then like all of a sudden he has to come up with a new idea for a show,
right? And or you...
Well, best case scenario...
I mean, all I'm gonna say is you guys will know what happened if you see an
announcement from John Wilson he's like the next season of my show will be
filmed in Antarctica. Well you do have you have to be a billionaire for this to
work because you have to be able to follow him around the globe wherever he goes.
There's a certain magic to it. You hire private investigators this is what to do
if you're a billionaire. If you win the lottery you should do something like
this. You hire private investigators, you follow him wherever he goes, you know his
schedule every single time and then you just dress up completely like Hitler. I
I would say it helps a little bit if you're not white because then you think
you do get a little bit more of a public pass for being Hitler right nobody's
gonna stop a black guy dressed like Hitler right they're gonna be like I
think a couple people might yeah I think I think you're gonna run into Israelites
who might not be that keen on black I think you're gonna run into problems
no matter what this is Hitler yeah I think I think if the black Israelites
saw black Hitler on the street there they're not there but again but again
you do you do you sit you it's the British accent it's a British accent
every single time
It's versus black Hitler's
deadliest warrior.
It's just like a full like fucking yeah. Westside story
snap off battle. Yeah, that's a
yeah, they see each other like like
perking up. Just like, "Oh, fuck. Oh no."
Yeah.
They're the black...
"Hey, this is the black...
[laughter]
Scram!
Get the fuck out of here!"
[laughter]
Oh, no.
Do they also have big signs that say Hitler was black, though?
Yes.
Yeah.
That's what the black Hitlerites are.
But their whole thing is they're, like, very friendly and chill.
[laughter]
Instead of, like, yelling at people, they're like, "Yeah, just come check it out.
We don't even know what we're advocating for, we just think that this is what happened.
We just know these colorized photos are doing...
Honestly, we're not... we don't even like them, we just are trying to spread the word.
We hate it.
We completely hate it.
We're not proud of it, but yeah, he was black.
It's just, you know, it's just evidence of whitewashing.
Yeah, that's what they're mad about.
We just don't like that, so we dress up like Hitler and we walk around.
I'm trying to think of if there's anyone else...
They have like a bake sale, the black Hitlerite bake sale.
Is there anyone else but Hitler that you could dress up as?
I think actually, you know, now that I'm thinking about it, I think you could probably walk
around dressed like Hitler without any trouble if there are enough of you.
Yeah.
Because I'm thinking about those-
It's a Santa con.
Because of those- Yes, exactly.
Because of those Hitler vaccine protesters.
Do you remember them?
Oh my God.
They marched around dressed as Hitler.
We did see people dressed like Hitler.
I saw them two times and I never saw anybody a costume.
They were dressed as Nazis.
They did not have those mustaches.
They did not have- They didn't have- They wasn't a full costume, but I will say-
It was a no mustache.
dressed as a Nazi I think you'd normally run into some trouble. It was one of the most
multicultural events. It definitely was. They had people from all races dressed up like Nazis.
I don't even remember what was their thing? They thought vaccine mandates were
fascist. It was Hitler's stuff. Okay. That's Hitler's stuff. That's what it was. There was a sign that one of them was
holding that said "vaccine mandates are Hitler's stuff." There was another sign that said "we don't play that Hitler shit."
Yep, that's right. Yeah, they did. Do you remember the same day we saw a guy, there
was like some concert or something at Central Park right? There was like
summer series. Every day they have like Bon Jovi in the middle of the
concert and nobody even knows until, it's like all just tourists who walk up.
So yeah there was a guy, because there's that huge line for like people waiting
to go see it, and there was a guy in a diaper and a Joe Biden mask and with a
sign that just said "Where am I?" I got a photo of it. There was a while where people thought that he
was disappeared I remember yeah yeah it was probably around that time well he was
getting facelifts and I'll tell you what he's back he came back yeah I saw some
crazy videos of him just seeming normal he's popping fucking vive ants yeah I
swear to God yeah he's probably taking like he's taking like a they've been
trying to hop him up for a while I think they finally found the right it's got to
be the right cocktail it's got to be TRT they're putting him on I think he's
looking virile. They're putting him on trend. He's about to look like a liver king. He's
lifting weights. Yeah, no, he's got some high test right now. Yeah. Yeah, I'm really excited
to see what kind of fisticuffs he's throwing in this upcoming election. It's gonna be so
cool. It's gonna be so cool when he like just gets completely jacked because they're putting
like the Bane serum in him from Batman and Robin. Yeah, the venom. That green goo. The
thing is, if I was the president, it's a disappointment if you ever die. If you were ever the president
and you and they let you die.
Yeah,
even after office.
They're supposed to back you up in a computer like
me.
What's his name?
You should be getting the first Vegas the first of all the
crap,
right?
Yeah,
I'm getting the fucking you should be getting the Boston
Dynamics robot dog body and all that shit.
Yeah,
I think the president should be the first to try like the
like the new flatbread at Taco Bell.
You should be.
Yeah,
if you're the president,
yeah,
I think that's the only benefit.
Yeah,
you should be able you should get all of the you should be able
to buy a shamrock shake mid-December. Oh yeah. You know what I mean? Year-round shamrock
shake for the president. No, that would be huge. Yeah. What is it? There's like a
joke in that show, I watched it with my mom, that show Raising Hope where
someone is on death row and they try to get a McRib and a shamrock shake as
their last meal so they were kept on death row for a long time. That's funny. I thought
that was a good joke. Yeah. Don't people on death row usually get kept on death
row for about 50 years though and then just die? I mean here's my new,
I even better than that. I mean that's that's a good idea, but I mean say that
you say that and they announce it the next day right that is coming back or
something. I would say I want a new food that I invented that takes 3,000 years
to I want squim. Yeah, I want I want a bucket of rice. I want the type of rice
I made that gets cooked and also it needs to be cooked by me and it needs to
be cooked in a mansion cooked in a mansion for a century. I love whenever
when whenever like I'm serial killer gets like a crazy last meal as like a
way to who ate a who ate one one one B is one being one grain of rice all that
stuff and it's like I really got one over it's like you're about to be filled
with fucking poison but I think that they win they'll just give them a bean
off nice one dude that's yeah yeah we get it you're great it's it's not as
crazy as when you killed 30 do they have like a price limit on them can you like
just there I think it's like some states I was reading about this recently it's
like some states are like I think somebody tried to get like lobster or
something and they're like no you have like they can either give you like a
sheet and then you can like fill it in or like it's like some states give you
like up to $10 for your last meal.
Why can't I just use my money?
Yeah. What are you gonna do with that? Leave it to my children? I killed them.
No, yeah, exactly. I ate my kid.
That's why I'm here.
My other kid.
I've been trying to get him for a while.
I've been telling him to come visit.
Will you come visit?
And will you sneak me in a bottle of barbecue sauce?
But the pat, they'll find you. You gotta cover yourself.
You gotta cover yourself in sweet baby
rage before you come in here.
Please. Dad, are you sure?
Yeah.
What big eyes you have, Dad!
See, he's dressed up like the
the big bad wolf even though he's already a serial killer yeah that'd be cool
above and beyond mm-hmm Big Bad Wolf reference Big Bad Wolf dude that'd be cool if you were
a serial killer and your nickname was the Big Bad Wolf that would be fucking sick
because you dress up like someone's grandma oh my fucking god holy shit I
think if I were a serial killer I would want to have if I got to choose my
serial killer name I would choose the murderer I would choose can you imagine
the power that that name would have I would choose Richard Ramirez that's
that's taken. I would what that's completely take it, then I would do like
Sam Berkowitz. That one's not taken. I do. Caleb is that no is that is that son
of Sam yeah, because I was like I think that might have been David Berkowitz.
Sam Berkowitz might be somebody I know yeah, I would be called Caleb the Ripper.
I think that's good. I would be called I mean John Wayne Gacy. You guys have to
but the murderers is sick. That is good because because they were the headlines.
The murderer was caught yeah. I was like who's the killer that dude my crime
would be that I followed when Williams around the killer is good to sane one.
The killer is that you're doing Google search. Google search results would be
will be yeah. I think I think you could you could do what if we spawn a serial
killer called the terrifier like a fan of our podcast is like you wanting to
kill. Do you think anybody listens podcast is a psychopath who wants to kill
and probably has blood thirst i have a feeling of the probably
yeah i mean statistically get out of what is it like one in every fifteen people
as a murderer there might be i might be able to play it
i think so
i bet i could if i search on you to be sound this sound that makes you a
murder i could play it over the mic
and see if playing on his phone
not playing i'm looking something up i don't think we want to hear that i don't
want to turn in the middle of this program is phone i want to see i guess
I was going to look something up for the podcast.
No videos.
We want to see Pat shine.
He's only got eight more, seven more minutes before we do our final report on him.
I will say I was doing something that I thought would be, that would help the podcast.
I wasn't playing and it does, it does make me a little, a little iffy on Pat here, kind
of trying to come at me for this, seeing as I'm the one grading.
I don't even have a report card.
I don't have a report card.
His report card?
See, Pat is trying to take the heat off himself for I'm not sure why.
Cam, perfect, but he did just two minutes ago, he did hiss like a snake and it really
scared me. I didn't know what that was. I thought there was a rattlesnake in the office.
I laughed. That's not a laugh. That's a type of laugh. I do laugh like that sometimes.
It is weird that there are types of laughs that are just like doing like. What? That
is not a good radio laugh. I do all different kinds of. No, I know. That's what my dad does.
Yeah, we got to get out of it. No hissing loud anymore. My dad does a crackle.
My dad laughs at something and he's like, "Oh, I shouldn't laugh at that." He goes like.
he goes like i can't does straight down straight i do it too and i definitely know that i've heard it
yeah you you do a crackle yeah you like ernie's laugh you have a giggle bear laugh and then you
also have a yeah he does have a hiss too though i know i just hiccup i also have the i laugh really
hard i have a full hic i just go like yeah i also have that sometimes i think i have all the you are
a snorter and then you have all the nose things yeah and you cover because you're so decent like
Princess Diana. That's what you remind me of. Princess fucking Diana.
See, I just did one that was like, "Lady D."
Lady Di.
D.
She died. That's why they call her Lady Di.
I don't think so.
They call her that because she died.
Do you think Trump fucked her?
No.
I think the timeline matches up.
Michael Jackson did.
No, John Travolta.
Easy to confuse.
Yeah.
They both say he he.
They do say he he.
Yeah.
So Michael Jackson, he didn't do that, right?
What save all those kids? Yeah. Yeah. And the Moonwalker game? Well, that was a video
game. He didn't actually do it. What was the movie he was in? Moonwalker. Thriller.
Where he was like this on the cover? Moonwalker. No. Oh, oh, this is it.
It's a fantasy movie, right? Wasn't he in a fantasy movie? He was in a fantasy movie?
I think I'd have sworn, man. Oh, it's time to stand. It's time to stand? According to this thing.
Yeah, according to my health app. Okay. Stand? I guess so. I just do what it says. Listen,
I'm trying to be healthy. I haven't been I haven't had a drip of alcohol since we
got back from the Pacific Northwest and I'm sleeping like three hours a night. I
thought it would do the opposite. I've been sleeping like three hours, waking up,
feeling incredible. I can't believe it dude. I think I've unlocked a new
ability. I think I have a no sleep ability.
I have been, my sleep schedule has been fucked up because I'll call my
my girlfriend before bed and she's not home. She's on the West Coast. Yeah,
yeah. Right now she's coming home. She's coming. I'm so tired because I got
haunted by a ghost, but it's not a big deal. Yeah, but I was up. I was like
yes, it doesn't matter. No, explain that. It doesn't matter. You can't just
say you got haunted. No, I don't want to talk about it. I would love to hear
something from you. It was a good- I had a- I had a- I had a- No, let's just hear
what Pat has to say. It doesn't matter too much what I had to say. It was a- I
on the phone with her last night at like my time like 2 in the morning. Ending.
I know, 2 in the morning I was on the phone with her and I was like doing
Trump voice but the whole thing was just Trump talking about being
neurodivergent. Mm-hmm. And then I thought it was really funny for Trump to go
"And then I got molested and then I completely got molested and it changed
my life." And then she said "You have to stop saying that I'm not wearing
headphones right now and I'm in the kitchen and all my roommates can hear you.
And she'd be, they'd be, they'd walk in and be like, "Oh my god, are you seriously
talking to that fascist Donald Trump right now?" Are you talking to Donald J. Trump?
Wait, he got molested and he's neurodivergent? Okay, I'm actually feeling a
little bit of sympathy for this guy. Right? And then all of a sudden you've created...
I got a 504 plan, they let me chew gum at school. Now you've created three new...
They let me chew gum before my test. I took occupational therapy. I took occupational
when I was a little kid, not that old.
- That's not okay 'cause you're humanizing him.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
'Cause now-- - That's a good point.
- They taught me how to hold a pencil.
I couldn't hold a pencil before, now I'm the best.
- If he said that, he's creating--
- Now I'm the best at holding a pencil.
- Five million new Republicans, 'cause they're like,
well, now we know his story.
- Yeah. - Right, the whole thing
with a guy like Trump, I don't wanna know his story, bud.
I want his story to end with him
on death row for his crimes.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Him in the electric chair. - You know what he'd ask for.
I mean you know what he'd ask for as a last meal.
Him in the electric chair like Marv from Sin City.
He'd ask for a complete fucking hamburger.
He'd ask for over 100 hamburgers.
Oh my god.
He would totally do that.
Probably with a side of kofefe sauce.
Yeah, he'd basically get a kofefe hamburger and he'd say, "This complete hamburger with
kofefe sauce is...
Oh my god, it's a fake news hamburger.
And I'd like 100 hamburgers.
And I'd like a side of Injustice.
Yes, I'd like...
And then...
Oh, and you know what I'd like on a hamburger?
Collusion.
I'd like Russian dressing.
And then they'd do a wink to the...
my camera fucking guy and I want to get peed on I want to pee I want my p tape I
want my p tape now I do I'd he would be like and I want all that food in the
paper bag and keep it closed with a p-tape like a piece of tape you say
piece of you say p-tape he's like no that's just how I say peace and I want
to create a car like abbreviating and I want to curse Jeff Diedrich for bringing
me here and to death row and I want a reply and can you go to Canada and pick
me up some poutine poutine poutine poutine nice a Putin nice it I said no
that's just how I say maple syrup we basically owned him that is that we got
Trump finally yeah we've had him for a little much on the forefront of tearing
Oh yeah, we really did some Judd Apatow tween style shit where we totally took him down.
Yeah, and yes, I know that what we're doing and doing a Trump voice is, it's about four
years too late.
No dude, we brought it back.
Even as a joke thing, it is back.
We 100% brought it back.
And we're not doing it because it sucks.
No, we're doing it because it's actually funny to do it.
I would say less than a month after we started doing it again, everyone else started doing
it again.
Really?
the beginning of tour. Yeah. And now this stuff now this stuff's going on. They got
Jamie Foxx doing that. Jamie Foxx video is unbelievable. It's crazy. Yeah. He's the
best one ever. He's the most talented man in the world. He I actually I've believed
that for a very long time. Yeah. Yeah. I remember seeing his like. He does a
really good Quentin Tarantino too. Have you seen that video? No. He has a great
impression. The Jamie Foxx video where he's on Howard Stern and he's
talking about Quentin Tarantino's like directing style and he says the first
the first day on set with Tarantino, Tarantino like took him into a room and
close the door and was like what the fuck are you doing out there your character
is a fucking slave you're a fucking slave. It was like to act more like a
good video and then and then how it turns like well would you work with him
again and Jamie's was like a thousand he loves him yeah he I mean how can you
know every interview he does he's like yeah Tarantino could say the in where
you can do whatever he wants now Jane. I want you to get on the sibian there you
That was a little Alan Alda I would say.
Yeah more Alan Alda than Stern.
That's okay then, I had a voice.
We crossed the line.
Now Beetlejuice I want you to write this.
Hey, enough, enough.
Now it's the liberation.
You're trying to get someone past the buzzer, it's not going to work.
These shots, shot clock violation.
Yeah.
Alright, alright.
Phone usage, that's another A+.
Easy A+.
A+ and I can't, I mean, like I said, you've been on an A+ kick with that, so that's good.
Yeah.
That was great.
at noises outsider upstairs have to say could be another it could be it could be
a think that's an I think it's an a let's give it an a-plus cuz he really turned
it into he didn't do it all he turned it improved yeah yeah no it's about it's
not about how you just look how you finish that's not it's pastime you can
look at the hose you can look at whatever you want love looking at now
all right now I love look I love looking at I think one day I'm gonna get x-ray
vision I'm gonna see the water go through it you want to see the person in the
shower let's be real yeah we got that old lady we got voice work now and voice
work he really he's really made a serious we have a driving instructor voice yeah
that he had we had a we had a we had a John I've okay that story had a
different ending no you can't get this in past I just want to he was raiding
babies. What? Do you remember that? I don't think so. I found his Facebook account and
he him and his wife were on this website called rate my baby and there was a bunch of pictures
like he posted his baby but then he was posting other babies going ah so cute. Whoa okay alright
that's crazy. Alright let's stories with endings are pumping all the way up and voice work
I'm gonna give him an A+ he did like four different ones. We got driving instructor.
Oh you have a list okay. We had John Wilson he did a serial killer voice. Yeah. I didn't
notice that one, but he did he did Trump.
A+ A+
That's A+
Yeah, that's an easy A+.
This is a fucking, this was a great second half for you.
Stories with endings.
We had a driving instructor story.
Now, I think maybe the way that we can rate these these stories
as if we can remember the endings and what they were because
I feel like I'm at the time.
What stories did we have?
We have driving instructor ended with him saying he could have
saved a child.
Okay, so we got driving instructor and then the other big
story was Trump getting molested talking on the phone story.
I'm going to say I basically gave you the ending for the Trump thing for us to get out of that
story so I don't think that one had an ending.
What are you talking about?
What was the ending?
Because I said her roommates come in and then and they think that it's a...
Well I ended the story and then you picked it you picked it up with a riff.
Fight fight fight.
Just joking.
You're right that's a good point but the story I don't think was all that I would have left
it there if I thought that it was complete.
I'm gonna say that's your only normal A no plus.
Okay.
to
translate to a different number of yeah. So i just let me i think three
thumbs up as a three no i let's let me listen here. Let's let me talk points
is in a thumbs up. It doesn't matter right now, because what i'm telling you
is a three thumbs up is not correlate to any points. It's just there were three
good things that you did for above and beyond which i will read out. If you
give me a freaking second here yeah the first one was that you carried you
carried it. Well, caleb got water completely carried it that was perfect. I
didn't even say a word nice. Then the second one was you had it bad behind the
scenes information about John Wilson yeah, that was behind the production of
how to he had a gender that was that was a how to and then he also we gave him a
thumbs up for the big bad wolf,
which is something you said to give him to wait. What wasn't there another one on
there? What was the other one? I didn't take it down. If I wait, this is above
and beyond this is above and beyond I I'm going to say that those are the
three things that I marked down for above and beyond. I'll give you another
seven. I would I mean last time he only had two I'm willing to go eight
Okay, let's go eight. Yeah, let's go eight. Okay, that's an eight for above and
beyond. Then we got Giggle Bear and I know you had a very impressive Giggle
Bear this time about the Black Israelites versus Black Hitler. Oh yeah,
you did Giggle Bear out of that. You really giggled. You sold that one. Yeah,
because I was a little uneasy going Black Israelites versus Black Hitler.
Wasn't sure how well that would land. Giggle Bear. You really Giggle Bear-ed
it. Complete compass, dude. Yeah. He's a compass. He's showing the people. I
I think that was a really good giggle. Yeah, that's completely filled it a plus
on the giggle bear a plus a plus just on that one alone and you know what I have
good news crassness. I didn't have to know write down a single thing. Wow,
we're completely we're clean as a whistle. Look at you. Wow. Oh my God,
that's an a plus for a so so we only have one a which I think we can easily
bring up to an a plus using the above and beyond beyond. So we have buddy you
got an you got a straight average pluses four point oh GPA and I would say by the
Wittwicky principle, you get a car.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
- Well, what I was trying to get out of this
was an Adderall prescription.
- Oh, I forgot about that.
- Yeah.
- I forgot you took Adderall.
- Well, you will, under the Wittwicky principle,
you will get an Adderall prescription,
but it will transform into a robot.
- Yeah, it's gonna be like--
- That embroils you in an intergalactic war.
- It's gonna be the same as the Beats pill.
- Right, so I have to take--
- Yeah, robot, yeah.
- But an actual pill.
- I have to take a 20 milligram Adderall
before we record every time.
- You know, when, I mean, that's your choice, you know?
your body, your choice. I get an A+ for that.
You can hold on to this report card. I want you to bring this to your doctor.
We need to sign it. Yeah, we do need to sign it.
All right. We've completely, I'm allowed to do drugs on the show.
Yep. We both need to be doctors here because we have a kind of a teaching doctor.
That's how doctors write, though.
True.
Yeah, that's how doctors write.
You write it with your left hand. All right, and that'll do it.
Yeah.
Here's your report card.
Thank you.
it was a pleasure it was a pleasure to serve such a fun episode
all right well
that's that i guess not anything nothing to announce now it's this is a
we have no it comes out saturday this is out tomorrow because there's
nothing we're going to announce nothing we're announcing
All right.