you're listening to Israel's number one pod
this is premium content
if you are not a premium subscriber
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately
*laughter*
ok so
no, before we do anything
there could be a giant bang sound
during this episode
there could be a huge bang
and it's nothing to get worried about
or ashamed of
you don't need to be ashamed
here
a little ashamed but I left my window if you they're doing stuff with metal
outside that who God knows what but but if they bang it if it's let's say they
decided to make a bang if you're one of the fans who's who's Caleb's neighbors
one of the like 20 fans who lives right next to Caleb you're out there and you
start banging metal when you know we're recording because you can hear our
voices through Caleb's open window you're going to hell. That's just rude dude.
That's your, listen I wouldn't care, listen you bang metal anywhere anytime a
day I don't care but you start to fuck with my money I come after you. That's
right my money no fucking shot brother. That's right you're not banging
shit during my work. That's right I'm gonna, I'm gonna fuck shit on you. Man I don't come to
McDonald's and bang metal at you.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, I don't come to the dick sucking factory and bang your metal.
At your metal... or whatever that is.
Whatever the fuck is.
I don't come to the robot factory and bang metal.
Yeah.
Right guys?
Right?
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
I'm doing it.
I'm doing it too.
You're so good, dude.
Yay!
That's so good.
Yes, dude.
Yay!
a
now we have a patrick i know all my god all i do is win now
uh...
uh... man but there's a word now
what did you ask me did you guys see the mandalorian
they brought they brought in with me anderson on
i think seen the mandalorian should be mandatory and and fun exactly
and they brought in a mandatory fun like you know
yeah that's right
the
and he plays a yoda now
what about this
he doesn't play a yoda
yet me voices a yoda
let's find out about this case
they went back to the man to report the mandatory fun
with weird al baby yoda bitch
mhm wall
yes he did
did a little bit of a crush it
yet they go to the go to
baby yoda's home planet finally
you have so many fans angry at you
i don't care
you do care every time you say something you go "i think someone's gonna get mad at me"
and this is the thing that people are gonna get mad at you for you realize that right
it's not that you say like
it's not that you say "retard" people are gonna get mad that you spoiled the mandalorian
that's true people are gonna message you now
i can't believe you didn't think about that one
they're gonna crucify my boy dude
we gotta start planning we need to get an escape plan
yeah that's true
that's easier right now
that's true
do you have a go bag?
i do have a go bag
what's in it?
chocolate chips
no you need more than chocolate chips in a go bag dude
no
it's just a grocery store bag of chocolate chips
just a rote go bag
what's that for?
it's just a go bag
What's that for?
It's just if I have to go.
Yeah, and do you have like a safe place to hide?
Do you have the bathroom?
Yeah, I'll put you in the bathroom.
I'll go to the bathroom.
I lie down in the bathtub.
I go down the stairs.
Yeah, across the street there's a bench.
Yeah.
I can sit here.
I have a great place to hide.
I would never tell you where I hide though.
Where would you hide it?
The attic.
*laughter*
You immediately told me dude.
This is terrible security.
This is like the worst episode of the show right now.
What do you mean?
You're like blowing up your whole spot.
You fucking spoiled the Mandalorian.
So if anyone's angry about Patrick spoiling the Mandalorian,
you know exactly where to find the chips.
Go to that, excuse me.
I just thought it was crazy that they had Anthony Anderson on.
I don't know if Anthony Anderson is.
You probably could have stopped at that.
I said to him.
He doesn't kill himself.
He does. He commits suicide.
He doesn't kill himself. No.
He does suicide by cop.
He does.
At the end.
They take, um, what's his name?
The guy who played Gus Fring.
I mean, I already spoiled it.
Why not just keep going?
Might as well spoil every TV show.
Speaking of Gus Fring, what happened to the name of Breaking Bad?
that
you can even bring himself to do anything but drink
and then what happens
he exploded
yeah that's right
that's what i fucking thought man
this is a spoiler episode dude
what does your mug say?
all mama wants is a silent night
amen
daddy's got a squeeze box
where daddy's got the squeeze box daddy's got daddy daddy has a squeeze box
mama wants a silent night
yeah now in in twenty twenty daddy's the one who's got the squeeze box he wears on his chest
daddy's got a squeeze box mama wants a silent night
yeah
it's true
uh... yeah fuck that's a great song
it's one of the best songs what are you guys gonna do with your with your silent night
what are you gonna do
what he is going to do with your six hundred dollars i can't even taking a
look at disney world trips
and i'm not even getting one fuck ok so cam so i've been meaning to tell you
that i was on my dependent still
we're talking this is now did the disney world this is the money that i heard i
have a little money to this is the i have a credit card i could pay for
disney that's literally not money that's plastic so
yeah i could make it work i could go to disney we don't really care
we were on it we can have a one-day we'd be a little embarrassed look yeah I have
no if you're a currency world with the credit card they make you wear a sign
around your neck that says this guy doesn't have money
oh no they make you tell every worker just you know I have HIV at every single
ride they make you say that yes I start bleeding you're not allowed to remove me
from the ride yeah you have to just let it run until I run out of blood even if
I just cut my finger. I just did it.
Yeah. Sorry. Yeah.
Just sitting on a roller coaster.
Like, sorry, you have to get off.
Like the next people need to go on and you just show them a
paper cut and you're like, I wouldn't try that.
If I were you and I'm going to put my hand.
I'm going to sit in the front.
I'm putting my hands all the way up.
So when people start screaming, you know, yeah, you know what
they're screaming about.
Yeah, that's my blood.
Yeah.
That guy's blood.
Did you guys ever hear?
like I feel like every single amusement park I've ever been to someone has told
me you know a kid lost his hat under one of these rides oh yeah I need to get it
and he got his head that was six like chopped off that was six like that one
Superman ride though it happened at every know that water slide where the
kid got get decapitated you know like most fucked up stories I've ever heard
dude tell it to me the kid was going down a water I forget which park it was
at but it was like a it was like a bring your kid to work day so that like this
kid was going down a water slide and like he was like below the weight limit
or something so he was like bouncing around in the water slide and there's
like a net and he bounced up and that like like there's a net with like a
metal bar and he bounced up and his neck hit the metal bar and his head flew off
like into the air and the like his whole family and just a bunch of people just
all waiting at the bottom of the water slide and they're just like waiting and
and they just saw just a bunch of blood come down
and then just his headless body.
- Whoa.
- I would hate that.
- It's like insanely like so--
- I think I'm gonna throw up.
- I couldn't handle that.
- His whole family dude, like his siblings and everything.
- If that didn't happen, if that happened to my son,
I probably wouldn't play video games for like two years.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- I'm serious.
- That's it, two years?
- He's so upset.
Yeah, I mean I do that.
- I mean, yeah.
- Granddad thought of six as boss.
- Yeah, I knew I came out.
- I hate people in that decapitation.
- Yeah, God, I beg to hate that.
I did. You just got decapitated. I did. No, but the, uh,
the, uh, six flags, decapitation, the guy with the hat,
that was at the, uh, that was at six flags, New England.
See, that's what I mean. I think I couldn't go to,
I couldn't go to amusement parks until I was 13 because of that.
Cause they thought that you, why did you buy mom?
No. Okay. You know what?
Also, your mom, I don't believe anything that she has ever said.
You know why I couldn't go to amusement parks until I was 13?
Is she saw a psychic and the psychic told her
that I was going to have an accident at an amusement park.
So until I was 13, until I was 13, I was like, Mom,
you know, all that's bullshit.
Let me go to Canby Lake.
The future. You did facts and logic on your mom when you turned 13.
let you know when I was 12 when I was 12 because I went to change that story.
This is all a lie.
It's not all.
I would.
Oh, you know, my mom well enough, you're lying.
Psychic told her something.
She would believe it.
You are. Look me in the eyes and tell me you're not lying.
I'm not lying.
Why do you have your tongue out?
I always do.
I call them retriever.
I'm reading this article about that kid who got decapitated on the water slide.
It was in Kansas and there's the guy the the owner of
Schlitterbahn water parks and resorts.
All right.
Well, all right.
That was it says like that.
They that they built like a prototype of the water slide without like
testing it and they knew it was dangerous and it says mr.
Henry who is also one of the water slides designers expressed concerns
before the slide open that he could be hurt or killed riding it.
According to records obtained by investigators.
it is a seriously dangerous piece of equipment today because there are
things we don't know about it the indictment quoted him as saying
there are things we don't know about it do you think that news stories what john
how john Knoxville got the idea for action point
yes
is exactly it
i'm gonna do that
and then he did see did you see there was already two accidents on the set a jack
ass
uh...
no i get going on our jackass dude
Yeah, yeah, they're gonna beat us.
They're gonna beat us to jackass for dude.
We have to beat them.
Well, let's think of some stunts we could do.
Okay. Okay.
What if we get like a crane, right?
And we bring it up like--
I like where this is going already.
We bring it like the biggest crane in the world,
like thousands of feet in the air.
A mile.
A mile in the air, maybe a mile and a half in the air.
Two miles.
We're gonna put Pat in the crane.
No, why do I have to be in the crane?
It'll be like, just shut up.
No, I don't like heights.
I'll throw up.
Shut up, please shut up.
- No, that's okay.
That'll make it funnier.
- Because of the ending, it won't matter.
- No, I'll throw up.
I can't do this.
I have to quit.
I have to quit this.
I have to quit Jackass 4.
- After doing a podcast and we get to get your money from it?
- No, no, I have to quit Jackass 4.
'Cause I'm gonna throw up.
- Can you let me finish?
Okay, you have a blindfold on.
- I'm already gonna throw up.
- You have a blindfold on, you won't even see it.
- No, but I know that I'll be up there and I'll throw up.
- You're a mile in the air.
- I'm gonna throw up.
a claw machine type situation,
and then I get to press a big button
and it just drops you.
- That was what we had to get through all that
just for that?
- And then you die.
- Patrick's trying to make himself throw up.
- I don't wanna do it!
I don't wanna throw up!
- Okay, how about this?
- I don't wanna throw up,
but I'm gonna have to do it through a point.
- This is better, this is better.
We put you in a cannon, right?
- Okay, cannon I can do.
- And we aim you at the sky,
and we shoot you into the sky.
Where do I land?
The ground.
How about this?
We get a crane
one inch tall
so he doesn't throw up.
One inch tall
with a fifty foot crane. That's what I was going to say.
We lift that crane
to a mile. Okay, no, we take the one inch crane
we shoot that out of a cannon.
okay then he's technically he's only lifted one inch off the ground even
though he's launched into the sky
if you think about it in a technical sense
what if we shove you in a volcano? what if we shoot you into a cannon and you get caught by a crane
that'd be a cool stunt
I think claw stunts are cool
every stunt has to involve either a cannon or a crane
I'm gonna put you in a field and you're gonna be a human scarecrow
oh ho ho, okay
yeah what we're doing we have a funny like a funnier thing
like a uh... you don't have a brain
no no but do we have like a 'cause you know like
what like
in jackass they'll have like a thing
but do we have a funnier thing than a crow?
okay alright but do we have a funnier thing than a crow?
than a crow. There's nothing funnier than a crow. We put crow food on your balls and they
have to come eat it off. There's nothing funnier than a crow. Alright, you know what Cameron?
That's real shit. I didn't think about that. What do you even mean by that Patrick? He's
saying like could we replace the crows with like toucans. Yeah, no, you know like in Jackass.
and
I was on your side for a minute.
No, but you know, can it be like Jack in the boxes?
Maybe that'd be pretty funny.
No, you know, like Jack ass like, like there's got to be some gay twist to it.
Like Margera sitting on the, uh, the, the hammer, the carnival hammer thing.
You are the twist.
You are the gay twist in this scenario.
I'm the gay twist.
So it's the, so the, so the stunt is called the gay scarecrow.
Yes.
You just and you look at the crows and you say hey
And they all fly away. I love that. I'm honestly I'm on board
All right. Do you have anything to add to jackass 4?
Also you're gonna be on a hundred foot crane when you do that
No!
Yeah you're on a stick in the field that's a thousand miles in the air
You're on the edge of the atmosphere. Yeah, and the crows are being shot at you out of a cannon
It sucks
Yeah, I've got
Hmm
So what if we get like a little person that looks like Caleb
not hard
And put them on I could just get surgery
Okay. All right. We make a tiny we make sure we shrink a cut
I think you could do that right just cut my spine down and my arms down and my legs down and
you can donate those to like
And make my head bigger yeah, yeah, yeah, so
So we do that and
So get the little Caleb and then we put him on a crane
I'm fine with that. Yeah, it doesn't bother me thinking about Caleb on a crane and
we drop the crane into
Into a piece of into crap
I can in big enough to shoot a crane
Yeah, I agree that would have been really scary in world. Yeah
Yeah, we're shooting cranes
Yeah, the axis. Yeah. Well the Germans the Germans are shooting cranes at us and you want to know what's in the crane
Nazi Hitler. Oh my god. Yeah, and he's gonna use the crane to start picking people up. I'm not
Places they would have won the war if they just like put Hitler on the front lines. I wish I'd gotten really psyched out. Yeah
Like the medieval warfare thing where you just like use a catapult to shoot stinky stuff at your enemies
Just like they were just like rotten fish and stuff cuz they're like this will really grow
We surrender
he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he
the
and native americans had to teach them
that rules
it's just so funny to select the i'd just don't understand like this we're
like fetishes patient that is a jaded with the big
but you have to get their time for a durst is a soon
this is a
of like
other races
to a point where it's like
we were so stupid
as white people were so stupid until these magic white people are superior to
the other
that's what you're saying
i'm so i'm saying what you're saying
i'm not saying i'm just saying what you're saying
okay patrick stupid
you saying what i'm saying
yeah i think uh...
i i i i think they have probably could have invented if no one told me about it
i probably like i would have done it by accident the thing about the people are
but i bet that like in the sixteen hundreds a bunch of people were trying
to invent bathing but every time they went into the river like this got bit by
a snake
through which i have been bathing but then they would keep throwing like
onions and carrots yeah yeah i couldn't lose a little bit of a little bit of a
group of myself
I was in the water.
It was trial and error.
And the Native Americans, they were mad smart.
They like didn't put a single piece of doo-doo on themselves when they were bathing.
No, they put no poop in it.
Yeah, that was like a new sort of invention.
You know?
That was like their version of jazz.
Yeah.
The thing about the bathing thing is like,
I'm sure people did bathe, but also like in London,
they were just, in the fucking like 1900s,
they were just like pooping on the street.
there
on
on your own the street like you gotta be pretty shameless to do that now
okay
and that's how that's also what people thought that that that's how you got
sick was just because it smelled so bad in the city
because it is a male yeah they thought it was they thought it was smells that
may be sick
probably a little chance when they put that's where they had the plague doctor
masks with the uh...
to my bathroom and it's not a six sometime
it puts them down and walk into my bathroom and i'm like
i need to go to the doctor
i guess this is making me smell like a so sick or for we recorded i
i took a
i think the new key you want this to be just like a nasty disgusting show
where you talk about your shit all the time is that what you want? is that the direction
you want to go in? i don't talk about my shit nearly as much as you. me neither. i never talk about my shit.
this is the only one who really does. my shit is not... you have the worst bowels.
no one talks about my shit
about their amazing
they're perfect
their their uh... the cool
the night back to the same poop every single day
my battles are popular but that was a cool that's right yeah
they're good
but you know there's nothing which you know horribly wrong with them to know
about me with something or other with them
no
there are battles is popping my battles is cool
stop making songs did that we want this to be a son of a pockets receipts on the
but shit
podcast about shit come on dude
people can't
all right
i was trying to think of uh...
away to make
my bowels is popping about pro lapses
did you tell you
did you guys see that brock obama likes netflix originals
way
you watch the queen's gambit
are you serious you know we all like that
that's what this with the girl that's uh... is smart
yeah i don't know who looks like an alien who knows how to play chess
do that so be used to it i fucking love watching that he liked it he likes
you like your his t_v_ series he likes
okay recalls all
who all gambit
that's not a luxury you'd be a the boys and my likes the boys did you
yes and it's not a reasonable or is there a wasted
devs the last dance mrs america
the good place
do
and city so real
I didn't know that he was a girl.
Dude, he likes Manc too.
That's a Netflix original.
Yes!
I heard he also likes that Dank dude.
He likes smoking weed, man.
He also likes cigarettes the other day.
He's so cool, man.
Cigarettes are the other kind of Dank.
Would you let him fuck your mom?
No.
Why?
Well, your mom would not do it, but him.
It's not my place to let anyone do anything in this world.
Exactly.
That's actually so savage.
Yeah.
Wow.
You should have an Netflix original.
I do.
Really?
Yeah.
It should be called The Monk.
It's on.
It should be like a cool white monk.
It's called Monk.
Yeah, that'd be perfect.
Yeah.
Well, you guys have never seen my show Columbo.
I'm really good in that show.
Is it sick?
Yeah.
Yeah?
I play this guy named Columbo.
Whoa, that's awesome.
The one who sailed the ocean blue.
Yeah. Wow.
That guy was savage, dude.
Yeah, Christopher Columbo.
Yeah. Christopher.
Christopher Columbo.
My name, Christopher the Gumbo.
No, no.
Christopher the Gumbo.
My name is Christopher the Gumbo.
How y'all doing?
How y'all discover?
I discover the island in the swamp.
Yeah, I discovered a treasure over there.
Oh, I discovered the bayou.
It was a voodoo magic man living there, but I discovered it first.
He turned me into a frog.
I didn't get a kiss.
I didn't get a kiss from a beautiful woman.
Christopher de Gumbo in 1982,
he has sailed across the bayou, man.
That's some real shit, man.
We've done enough Cajun voice for a year.
Yeah, it's probably true.
Is this the are you guys getting so excited for Christmas? What's up? Oh me too. How we feeling?
We're gonna do some christmas mischief next week. Uh-huh
I love christmas you can miss this
With that mischief because I fucking love christmas. I don't want to have any you guys get good gifts for your family
Uh, I haven't ordered a single gift. Oh, they're not. Yeah, me neither. Yeah, they will
They will come post the postal service is fucked. No, yeah
my dad my dad
is a package man
your dad's a whole package?
your dad's got a package?
oh
trust me. your dad's not a package man he's got a package man
oh yeah yes sir he's more package than man that's right
yeah
at this point yeah he's more of a man package yeah it's like batman and man bat
that's what i've been saying
did you guys get your family anything funny
i've got no anything yet
i think i'm gonna get you be a female like freeze-dry
look at
taco bell meal incident to occur
think that might be funny 'cause it's pretty funny he uh... yeah i gotta send
him something some sort of prank gift right
yeah i will too
okay also a lot for you know that address right now
and then
and we'll just put a sensor beep here.
Mexico Road, Mexico Lane, Lano, Mexico.
Oh, no, Mexican.
Oh, El Rodeo, Mexicano, Rodana, Mexicano, Rhodesia.
Yep.
Georgia, Georgia, USA.
Yeah.
Yeah, Maine.
He lives in, he lives at Uno Dos Reis.
I'm not going to
Clam he loves clam dude get clam -
Yeah, that's right
He's constantly having sex
Dude, it disgusts me
Stream and everything we should go we should go on an international world tour
I want to do that so like what like the Rock Gods of yesteryear
We could go to do it like a world tour and just have like two people come to every show
We could have like a Van Halen style rider too and just be like
Dude, and we could have a van and we could drive across the world.
I'd love to be a diva.
We should, we gotta get some roadies dude.
And some whores.
What are they called?
I'm gonna be the biggest diva on the whole tour.
Yeah where you already are.
Patrick, Patrick you have to be on the show.
I'm not going out until I get six hamburgers.
I'm not going out until my dad hugs me.
Dude, the record label's gonna drop us.
He's thousands of miles away, Patrick.
I'm not gonna move until I get five dollars.
You have to pay me up front for this show.
We spent all your darn money on hamburgers for you.
I'm not coming out on stage until you say hello to me.
Yep.
Where's my hug?
That's all I'm asking.
Where my hug at?
I just want you to listen to my problems for a little bit.
- You have to listen to my EP and then I will come out.
I've been working on EP over the entire tour.
It's techno, it's techno jazz industrial.
It's six hours long, it's terrible.
You have to listen to it and then I'll come out.
- And you have these audio engineers
playing other people's music before the show.
What's that?
- Yeah.
- What's that about, man?
What is that? We're here for our music.
You should be playing an episode of the podcast before we come out as a warm up.
And what is this? We weren't good enough for you? You got a band to play before us?
That's what they do at podcast live shows is they just play other podcast episodes.
As a little warm up. So people start laughing.
Yeah.
Okay, but not too much. You got to play something like "Wait, wait, don't tell me."
people are like, and then they get ready.
And then we come out and they're like,
this is the French, the French show. Exactly. Yeah. Yeah.
We probably don't have a single French fan. I think, I think they're,
I think they're too cool for us, man. No, we're like Jerry Lewis.
Probably was Jerry Lewis big in France.
We were like huge in France, like Jerry Lewis.
and we like
just didn't know about it
that's where all our money was coming from
that'd be cool what would you guys do
i would assume that they were laughing at us
about french
people
what did you say about french people
they
be eating snails
they be eating snails
that's what you got
maybe they would like that we make fun of
cajun people
that could be true i'd yet i don't know that he has a very well you know they got
there
you know that there's like a french chris rocker does a french versus cases
routines somewhere
it
do you know more on the uh...
but i think that the thing they hate canadians are or
or probably probably could work well people
you are not going to be quite a private cases his cases are not
french at all but some they claim a little bit of it
Canadian people at least like they have like a functioning society.
You know?
Occasion people like trade each other leaves for meat.
Occasion people have a voodoo government.
Exactly yeah.
Yeah.
They're like we're gonna make a law where you can't smoke a cigarette anymore and they
just they take out a little doll that has a cigarette and they throw it into a blender
and that's how they make laws.
Yeah, anybody who had a cigarette in their mouth is now dead.
Yeah.
I don't think this is true about Cajun people.
It's true.
Okay, what do you think is true about Cajun people?
Oh, now we've gone too far for Pat with the Cajuns.
You should hear this guy off mic.
He's going insane on us.
I think they have a big-- He thinks they're subhuman.
Can I finish?
No.
I think they have a big crocodile in charge.
Okay.
Yeah, like Donkey Kong.
uh... yes he did i have to tell you that i would like to go to a great big
it'd be difficult
it's all about the end of the country
so that the homes
and we're having been a little bit
he had to have a good news that you see on the path hanging out with your nephew
hang out with your nephew and you know that i have a it's all about having a
family where you were all of your first names are just adjectives
"Oh, that's Stanky. Stanky the Gumbo."
"Stanky Gagnon."
"And that's Little Guy Gagnon over there."
"And we call that, 'That's Evil Gagnon. You don't want to go in his shed.'"
Yeah, you just have like, yeah, just your entire personality is described with your first name.
It sucks that they got rid of Lanky Kong.
Yeah.
Lanky Kong was so cool.
He's cool, dude.
will
call
cool record
He's he's gone off the deep end. It's cuz he ate breakfast today, dude. Yeah, that's probably it. He got breakfast brain
Mm-hmm, but my fucking tooth really hurts, too
Did you get the thing back in to it
Just start nailing
No, I that tooth completely broke
Sorry, I looked at it
there is a so I once it fell out of my mouth like when it was like in my hand
there was like a Dremel size hole in it too so this whole time I had I was like
I wonder like that little like the dental tool they accidentally drilled
into it and didn't tell me oh my god so that's probably why it fell out is
because there was a fucking like hole like that big in the tooth and I was
is
going when he was putting a crack he he he
and you don't feel this tomorrow that's that's the more
and he they both do that voice they don't both do that we are steve martin
delhi site that he does see martin goes excuse me
you know
and that's pretty much the same voice
he says feed me teeth more
yet
that's what they said that they should have made that they should have had a
plantation of that a big everyone in that everyone in that movie should have
said should have had a different line.
"Feed me something more."
"Feed me food more."
Yeah.
That's what I say when the waitress
comes in my driveway.
"Feed me food more."
"Feed me all
night long."
"Feed me a hot
dog."
Anybody who gives you food is Foodmore.
more. Yeah, my mom gets really mad at me because when I wake up in the morning, I'm like, hey,
food more. Where's breakfast? Food more. I'm not your food more. I'm not your food. Well,
a
the pizzeria to order a pizza and is singing to them feed me food more.
Feed me food more.
Man why are you doing that voice?
You don't sound like that.
Why do you sound like an old black guy?
You know what I don't know.
It's just the rules of food more.
The golden rule of food more.
Feed food more the way you'd want to be fed.
the
green
was going to be should've done a
christmas song
kirk
green and red green and red
and i think that there are
you could say christmas christmas christmas christmas christmas christmas
and get
let's just let's christmas carl what are you know what about
on a gun christmas on a good
yeah that would have been good
the new york christmas rap songs
yeah what we are
we only have lake
sensitive and i was in the cell album there's there's a there's a
album called christmas on death row and it's like a death row records christmas
now men i have it and there's a they put a ghost of two park on the back of it
really will priest carry as the ghost of a song
the yeah
uh... but it's more of a halloween take yeah of course it's like it's like a
christmas carol kind of ghost of the i think that's the kind of the uh...
Curtis blows it again
the chain they should have given them the
the because the christmas past chains on uh... onto park
mood
ludicrous made a song
now
press that christmas song
for fred claus called ludicrous miss
that was a good
for a movie he put his name in it
tell santa claus to bring a ten million dollar check was that what a little
it'll be a slight couple years he'd a little chicken drink a couple beers just
kick back
and chill just like a player would do
that's the best christmas of all time
do you think what's the funniest made for a movie rap song you guys can think of
uh... well probably i mean
the obvious answer is wild wild west
the one i really like is um... l_l_ cool jay who was in uh... deep blue sea the
movie about super intelligent sharks
made a rap song that plays in the credits called deepest bluest and he just says a
bunch
my head is like a shark's fin
there's a song there's a song that they play sometimes in the sopranos when
they're at the bata bing which is the strip club that tony owns
i'd we know that i'd cam doesn't i don't care
fuckin dumbass
but so they'll be at the strip club and like this will happen like once a season
the strippers will be dancing and there's a song that plays it's just
shake that ass
shake that ass shake that ass
and that's the only lyric that lasts for like
like in a three minute scene it'll just be playing in the background
it's my new favorite song
listen to this dude
looking for killers gotta eat too my world's deep blue killers gotta eat too
looking for human flesh to rip my teeth through
other fish in the sea but barracudas ain't equal to a half human predator
created by a needle
dude that's fucking sick
all you see his trails of blood even god will intervene nightmares of darkness my
appetite is heartless
fuck that's so sick
half man half shark my jaws don't fall
hack man half shark my ass don't fart there's a lot of stuff about god here
better line our father who art in heaven hallowed be thy name killers sworn to
beast swallowed them in flames this switch might be a day trip me into cool
j i can't fight the feeling i'm born to kill prey
to
excel fuckin fresh meat cipher these guys oh my god oh my god yeah that's right you think mario
you think mario judah could go up against the shark no way no yeah you think turn him into mario scuba
god that's right yep yeah yeah that's that would be the first that would be the first hurdle they
would have to go over if there was a shark at the double xl freestyle is all the rappers would be
in scuba gear but the shark has the clear advantage.
True, well because they'd have to do it in the water for the shark.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
That's a really good point.
And Playboy Cardi, he's going to be Playboy Shark Meat soon.
That's, that's fucking right.
Yeah.
I know that's right.
Little, little Uzi vert, it's about to be blood is oozing, he's hurt.
Yeah.
You know, something like that.
Little very hurt.
Little very hurt from the shark bite. He just got it the cipher fuck Megan the stallion would be Megan the shark
Megan the galleon and she's a big ship
Yeah, yeah, I'd be sharky eat
True yeah, so fucking true. Yeah, and they're gonna turn whoop into jaws
Wow, dude, just a wet stuff
Wet ass pontoon
That's fucking right dude, uh-huh
There could be like every different kind of shark could have its own best rapper like you like the different coasts
Oh, yeah, there could be a rapper named hammerhead. There could be a rapper
and his eyes would be huge and he had a hammer for all eyes on you instead of
all eyes on me oh my god is like a shark uh-huh I think shark grab might be the
new big thing in our brains yeah yeah yeah I mean it won't ever happen in real
life but don't don't don't act like it won't how would it happen
wait tell me how it happened the genius I'm on genius for deepest bluest sharks
fan by LL Cool J and the about is out of context this song and several of its
details make little sense it is only after viewing the film it was made for
deep blue sea that you may unravel the song's true meaning I'm gonna go on
every like Korean rap page on genius and do that exact same paragraph the ocean
is also home to sharks creatures that served as inspiration for LL Cool J's
hat the Sharks fan is considered by sharkologists to be the hat of the shark
sharkologist excuse me I'm switching careers yeah sharkologist I'm a
scientist but only about sharks I study what part of the shark is the hat anything else about sharks
I can't I can't say the title of this song but Rayquan and Ghostface
is
They made a song called shark and words.
Is it lighter?
Is it swag?
That's a parenthetical.
It might be good.
You hate biters. OK, well, that would be the problem with sharks
is that they would keep biting other people's.
Oh, no, it's a skit.
Steez. Oh, it's a skit.
It's oh, I'm sorry.
It's just a skit.
Yeah, there's no rap in this.
I think a lot of animals would make great rappers.
True. Yeah, I think an anteater in a beanie would be funny.
That would be cool.
Yeah.
Do you think of an anteater rap to be like...
[mimics anteater]
'Cause his mouth is so long.
Yeah.
It'd be like 6'4" 5AR.
He would have the best ad-libs.
He'd have like a little like...
[mimics anteater]
And he would just go like...
I'm eating ants! I'm eating lots of ants!
I'm wearing cool pants!
When he has the ad-libs, it's just like him going...
[mimics anteater]
[laughter]
Exactly, dude.
That would be the advantage of an animal rapper
or
Oh my god.
Yeah.
And you would say like, "I don't hang out with that stupid ass Tony."
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
And I'll eat you like you were bologna.
I'll eat you like Carole Baskin's husband.
Oh my god.
Like, "The white man's trying to turn us all to Tonys.
I'm gonna turn them to bolognas."
Something like that.
You know?
Yeah.
I'm gonna eat you like Carole Baskin's husband.
I'm gonna throw your ass in the cage that I came in.
Didn't rhyme.
Y'all watch Tiger King.
He's got a different flow.
Y'all watch Tiger King?
I'm the King Tiger.
That's what he would say.
Whoa!
Oh my god.
Yeah.
You look at my thing, my thing get wider.
That's right.
That'd be kind of a funny way to get a boner is that it just goes wide like an umbrella.
Yeah.
Like you're resizing it on Photoshop.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
And you don't click lock ratio.
It just gets wide but not any taller.
That could be some pretty funny ass shit.
That could be funny.
Dude, raccoons...
Er, what am I talking about?
What?
I don't know.
I saw a picture of a raccoon.
Dude, what are you talking about?
Dude, that was sick, man.
You saw a picture of a raccoon and you just went, "Raccoon!"
And you're like, "Oh, what am I talking about?"
That's literally like, fuckin', like, cartoon ADHD.
*laughter*
I'm straight up half cartoon idiot
Just saying everything that you see
Why are you looking at a picture of a raccoon?
It popped up!
Did you search animals? What did it pop up on?
I was looking up animal rappers
*laughter*
Raccoon
Raccoon, oh raccoon!
It would have been worse if I saw like a fucking squirrel or something
that's like straight up, god damn.
It's out of Over the Hedge.
I'm the stupidest guy of all time.
You are the dog from Over the Hedge, man.
Yeah, how does that feel?
What if the animals in Hoodwinked could rap?
Then it'd be called Hood Hood.
Oh my god.
Didn't they have a rap at the end of the movie?
Yeah, they did. Come on.
I remember in one of my college classes, we like showed our professor Hoodwinked,
and
She has a whole crew of like AAV affecting animals.
Yeah, and the wolf.
He's cool.
Dude.
It's so that the CGI in that movie who were talking about this
last night, but like the CGI and like so many things that we
watched when we were younger just has not aged correctly.
And it's so scary.
Yeah, like hoodwink looks terrifying.
It looks insane.
It looks like one of those like kids YouTube videos made by a
by a yeah an Indian robot.
Yeah.
a
movie on tv show looks more polish
yeah
also the fucking the character design
of jimmy neutron
so we are affected so weird kid with hair is weird
uh... fat and i did meet a great showed carl and she nurse are the perfect
perfect romantic friends perfect friend characters yes ship them
i ship them
i don't ship you somewhere else
now you look in it
has looking at uh...
records looking at jimmy neutron stuff and i found uh... are slash k_s_i_
and somebody made k_s_i_ into
jimmy neutron
in real life
yes
what's k_s_i_
k_s_i_ he's the guy that boxed jake paul
uh... is jake paul gonna is he just gonna become a boxer now
yet it is
way where did you find that that review of jack at her of uh... of
uh... what was it was c_k_y_ c_k_y_ a letterbox
is that like someone you know
no at some of the i found because i was looking through all the reviews of c_k_
y_ to see if
and said anything bad houses
i was a bad i was there
i was thinking it'd be really funny to like
only use letterbox to defend the cky movies you probably have a lot of work to do yeah
i assume there's a lot of reviews like that where it's like right but it's like immature
what is it is like oh if you love destruction of property then you're gonna love this
right if you this is basically jake paul of the 90s it's like just how if you're looking at cky
or jackass it's like from like a film perspective you're fucking you're just a pussy dude you're
you
the bromance of jackass. Is that true? Yeah. Yeah, that's true. Dude, that's sick. The bromance
or is he insinuating that they're gay? I haven't read the book. I think it might be an insinuation
of like the homoerotic relationships. Somebody in jackass is fucked. Yeah. Right? I mean,
just look at Bam and Ryan Dunn's relationship. If Jack had... No, I didn't even think... Oh,
Ryan Dunn's dead, oh crap.
God, I didn't even think about it. No, but like thinking about like, uh, fucking...
Someone, there's definitely, because I found it on, I found it for South Park, but like the people
who do like ships on Hauler. There's definitely a Ryan Dunn, Bam Margera ship somewhere.
Like a cartoon of them fucking?
Yeah, like cartoons of them kissing.
There has to be.
Fanfiction.
Especially after Ryan Dunn died, maybe, maybe Bam is like, like kissing like, like an angel.
a
die no that's the first scary part and then you you go you start you an escalator a shining
golden escalator appears and you look and you have wings and a halo and you're so excited
you start going up into the clouds you get to the clouds we're wrong hell is up in the
clouds and heaven is underground oh that would be the twist of a light angels go to heaven
hell and give ghosts go to heaven and also good people go to hell and bad people go to
heaven there is yeah well and ghosts do you think ghosts go to hell? Do ghosts go to hell?
Do ghosts go to hell? Here's the trick. Do you think Bigfoot is gonna go to heaven or hell?
Bigfoot? Um... You think goblins? Where do you think goblins go? Can I just do one thing at a time?
Bigfoot is going to hell. Where do you think Anthony Bourdain is? Hell, definitely, with Bigfoot. Okay, and goblins?
heaven oh dude i'm sorry i found
yeah it's a thing is it uh-huh do jara do jara secret love this is a
wow
wow that oh my god okay so this is a your eyes just got so big they're
watering i feel like i'm watching you watch the end of interstellar right now
*laughing*
we gotta read these
we gotta read these on the show sometime
this is insane
ok ok here
this is uh ok
oh my god
do jera secret love
it's called do jera cause dun
read it! marjera
i know you're stalling cause you have to figure out how to read the first sentence
no i i i'm so confused
so the title of this
i'm so confused
released rating NC 17 for language and sexy time warning features some water
sports disclaimer don't own cuz you can't own people from 2007 so before he
died BAM came back from the skate demo tired bruised and horny as hell although
it was nearly 2 a.m. before he got to the castle his first order of business was a
text to Ryan hey bitch my ass hurts from skating get over here and ice it for me
Bam smirked as he set his cell phone on the dresser in his room.
He began shedding his clothes as he made his way towards the bathroom,
looking forward to a relaxing shower.
The sound of the water pelting toward the base of the shower filled the room
and Bam left the water running so it could get nice and hot.
As he stood in front of the mirror, he rolled his head from side to side,
loosening his...
The word "neck" is in bold.
[laughs]
Loosening his neck muscles, his eyelids heavy as he studied his reflection,
he watched himself trail his hands over his taut chest and pecs,
down to-
*laughs*
-towards over his abs and further towards his pubic-haired cock.
He imagined his hands were Ryan's slightly larger hands,
working their way all over his smooth, tattooed flesh,
teasing him and making his dicks-
his dick-
DICKS STIR!
*laughs*
-and Ryan Doman my dick stirred.
-MAYOR DUNN, YOU BETTER GET OVER HERE AND MAKE MY DICK DICK STIR!
(laughter)
Oh my god.
As the steam from the shower filled the room, Bam walked in and stood beneath the powerful jets,
the tension and aches soothed by the hot clean water.
Bam was lost in his own thoughts of pleasure and the feel of his hands on his skin,
so lost in fact that he was oblivious to the sound of Ryan in the bathroom,
stripping his t-shirt and shucking off his trainers into the corner.
While he was content to watch his lover,
he turned slightly to the side as he bathed and teased himself,
nonchalant and unaware of his presence.
presence. Ryan watched as the rivulets of water trickled seductively down Bam's
back and sides, tracing his butt and ass crack like ghostly fingertips.
What did they know? What did they know?
Oh shit, dude. Fuck.
Yeah, and then Ryan died in a car crash.
Ryan chewed his lower lip as he imagined his tongue, instead of the clear droplets, mapping the soft flesh.
As his belt buckle clacked on the cold tiles, Bam finally turned to lock eyes with his scruffy
blonde lover, pinching the water from his eyes with his thumb and forefinger.
He met Ryan's gaze and licked his lips.
"You get off watching guys get clean, Ry?"
Silently, Ryan acknowledged the lack of pleasantries.
Not that he was complaining, he had enough plans for Bam's sweet mouth without banal
banter taking up precious time.
Fuck, this is so well written.
i know
you're always dirty bam bam his eyes glistened at the double entendre
and the miniscule non sexually charged portion of his mind marveled at the fact
that he knew what double entendre meant
all of our and all my god
they have noticed ryan casually caressing his balls that looked tight
against his skin as he spoke to him he joined bam in the shower and became
immersed under the pelting water
his eyes darkening in random trips falling into his eyes
you look damn drip hot dripping wet in the shower
you look hotter dripping in my fucking car
at that day i'm one of the feral growl press slips are against ryan's
right is to recruit for bans supple asks in the flesh he could have been sick
it's large pops
uh...
you loaned from the dual assault of the water over his body in the heat from
Bam's fluid tongue fighting with his own. They didn't kiss like girls, all sissy sweetness.
They kissed firm, hard, hungry for satisfaction and power. The heat in the shower increased
when the passion emanating from the two men. Their moans and pants echoed around each other
as their hands roamed over each other's saturated bodies.
As Bam tightened his grip at Ryan's soaking strands of hair, he felt Ryan slip his hand
between their bodies and surround his hard cock, the head twitching with every long stroke
as Bam sighed against Ryan's neck whilst he attacked it with lips and tongue.
"Fuck, Bam.
You're so fucking hard."
"Hard for you, baby.
Wanna make you cum so bad."
Em's breath caught in his throat when Ryan held both erect dicks together in one hand.
The tight, warm, slippery from the shower felt so good to both men.
Then Ryan began to feel familiar pressure in his groin, but it wasn't an orgasm.
"Oh shit."
He murmured, slowing his ministrations.
Bam looked dazed as he looked at Ryan.
"What the fuck, Ry?
I'm so close."
"Uh, sorry, Bam."
Ryan tried to edge towards the door of the shower.
"I gotta piss."
Bam paused, smirking.
So?
Ryan wasn't quite sure.
No way!
But he could have sworn that for a split second, a defiant red glint flashed in Bam's blue
to
the older man's both still
at heart and dripping bam felt seconds away from exploding
right didn't know what was happening only that he knew he had to piss badly
that's a bad the first bad sentence
it's not only bam was leading into ryan's ear panting as his fist were
quickly on his cock
piss on me rye
ryan's eyes rolled up into his head at the words
he mumbled a few fucks as he held his full cock
Jesus, Bam.
Ryan looked into his boyfriend's- his boyfriend's eyes.
What?!
They were clouded with sheer animal lust, the complete willingness to experience every avenue of sex and play with him, and only him.
*Gasp*
You want my piss, baby?
*Laughter*
Bam nodded, his hand cupping and tugging his fold balls, the other hand rubbing his leaky cock.
Ryan felt the hot piss poise for release.
You gonna take my cum too?
Fuck yeah, Ryan.
Fuck, fuck.
Fuck, I gotta piss Bam, where do you want it?
Bam was panting, feeling the orgasm bubbling, his balls tightening, on my dick when I cum.
His knees shaking as he pumped furiously on his dick, fuck Ra, do it, do it.
Standing close to Bam, holding him steady by the shoulder, Ryan moaned as he pissed
a hot golden stream onto Bam's engorged cock, sticky white ropes of cum spurting out as it
mingled with the urine, some of the release sliding over Bam's hand and dick.
Bam breathed heavily as he came down from his high, his eyes mesmerized by the remnants of
cum and piss, not yet washed away by the rapidly cooling water.
Ryan still held his dick, surprised to feel it was getting thicker so soon, but his eyes
were locked on Bam and his reaction to the new game they just played.
He tilted Bam's face upwards and looked at him intently.
So how was it?
Bam brought his hands down towards his face and examined the last drops of both men's
released that still remained on his digits.
Lifting his eyes to meet Ryan's, he brought his fingers to his lips and sucked them hungrily,
cleaning them of all the liquid.
That was cum-fucking-tastic.
Ryan was speechless as he witnessed his lover accept both tangy and bitter juices.
Looking behind Bam with his free hand, he turned off the shower, looked Bam dead in
the eyes and said two words, "Bedroom.
Now."
Wow, dude.
Whoa.
What a fucking ride that was.
This is on LiveJournal, so at the bottom it says, "Current Mood, Busy."
Fuck yeah, you're busy, dude.
That was hours of work went into that.
That was crazy.
First, for there to be, okay, there's enough for there to be like gay porn, sex stories
about Bam R. Jarr and Ryan Dunn, but then to also include pissing on each other?
Yeah.
Peeing on each other in the shower?
is
one true pair.
all
been slaving over essays that i need to send to uni tomorrow but i really want to
get back on the fic train when they're all done and dusted that's where you
lovely folk come in if you would like me to write a challenge based on your
prompts then this is the place to do it
i need five prompts please insist these are going to be one shots they may be
porn but if you would like more fluff than filth just say
one color
two emotion three taste slash flavor
four scent slash smell five sentence or phrase
thanks peeps current mood hopeful
god damn
- Dude, we should get into a journal, man.
- So, can someone write one of these for us, dude?
(laughing)
I just wanna see who's like, the best at sex.
- That's true.
- Who's topping, who's bottoming, who's middling?
- Can we just see?
- All right, I'll write it, fine.
Whatever.
- All right, we have to make it ourselves.
- Whatever.
- All right, I think,
I don't know where we go from that.
So I think we're probably done.
- Yeah.
Oh, I got a,
I think it comes out today when this comes out.
I did an episode with Sleazoids podcast.
- Oh yeah.
- Which is a genre film podcast.
They're really great.
You should check them out.
I talked about Killer Clowns from Outer Space
and Brain Damage, which are two really great movies.
I'll probably definitely like tweet about it too,
but you should listen to them
'cause they're a good podcast.
If you like movies, that's beast.
Yeah.
Yeah, dude.
That's basically LA Beast.
That's fuckin' swag.
Alright.
FUCK YOU!