You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
Now I'm recording.
Oh!
Are you?
Um...
I'm Dakota.
Your name is Dakota?
Cameron's new name is Dakota.
Did you guys ever have fake Facebooks?
Yeah.
I've talked about the one that my brother had.
What was it called?
Billy Bob.
It was a picture of Voldemort and he just, he would like go on to kids' statuses like
on Truth Is Things and just say like fucked up shit.
Whoa.
My favorite Facebook story is Neil had this fake Facebook profile.
- Jakey Dinger. - Jakey Dinger.
- Yeah, and he added a whole bunch of his family members
and then he like overheard his dad talking
to another one of his family members or something
and being like, "This crazy guy, Jakey Dinger,
"is trying to add all of us, watch out."
- I just had one-- - Beware Jakey Dinger.
- I like deleted Facebook in high school
and started using one for Spotify called Jacobi Pimento.
- Yeah, I heard that.
- And then I used that for a while
That was my real Facebook account.
- That's pretty cool.
- Yeah, I was never on Facebook very much.
It doesn't make a lot of sense to me.
I was a MySpace fan.
I was a huge MySpace fan.
- I'm going through the Billy Bob page.
- Spit some heat from it, what's up?
- August 23rd, 2011.
Like my status and I'll rape you.
XDDDDDDD, X 30 Ds.
There's 30 D's in there.
How many likes did the status have?
Four.
Whoa, who liked it?
Who liked it?
Did you like it?
My brother, my brother Eric?
Whoa, dude, that's even worse, man.
Your own brother?
Richard Bilodeau?
No, Richard, dude.
Richard was a weird fucking guy anyway.
Yeah, well, yeah, he's asking to get raped on Facebook.
Here's a, oh man, it's a picture of like a fat woman and a guy touching her boobs.
Oh, man, that's a picture of a fat woman and a guy touching her boobs.
No Richard dude!
Richard was a weird fucking guy anyway.
Well yeah he's asking to get raped on Facebook.
Here's a, oh man, it's a picture of like a fat woman and a guy touching her boobs.
It just says me and my wife doing it.
That's what's up.
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
My ass is covered in yogurt.
That's fucked up.
Your brother did, you weren't kidding, you said fucked up shit.
You delivered buddy.
I joined, well it was the stuff that he was commenting on people's things, like you can't
find that shit unless you sign into the account, but.
Do it.
Yeah, sign in.
No, it's just someone's grandma's name as a status.
Just say it.
Grandma, it says grandma.
Yeah, it says grandma.
Someone's grandma's name.
Dude, I'm finally hitting it.
I'm ready to be outside again.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's getting fucked up.
I've run out of, I thought that this would never happen.
I don't want to play any more video games.
- Yeah.
- That might be dangerous to admit online.
- I know that everyone's like is talking about
crazy quarantine dreams and it's kind of hack,
but like my, I had this nightmare the other night
that just like transcended what I thought was possible
in a dream.
Like, I just like, like being stuck at home.
Like I had this dream where-
You have to explain.
The dream was, I was just sitting like for hours in the dream, just sitting on death
row and just thinking, "I'm gonna die soon."
That was the whole dream.
Jesus.
Oh, fuck, dude.
I had a pretty-
It was like the worst dream I've ever had.
I didn't even know that was possible to have a dream that was just thinking.
I had a dream like two weeks ago, a dream that I don't remember what the context was,
but Anna Kachian was in my dream.
- Oh, okay. (laughs)
- And then, yeah, and then,
and then I was like, I gotta,
I have to change something about my life,
and I didn't have another dream for a week.
She like stole my dreams for a week.
(laughs)
- I fuckin', like the other day,
I fuckin', the other day I fell asleep,
and then,
oh, shit.
- What?
- I might be gettin' that stim check, boys.
- Whoa, what happened?
- I don't know, it says it accept,
I accepted my non-filer.
So.
Nice.
Let's try and get--
I should probably check that.
Let's try and sue the federal government
to get you the money that you're not legally entitled to.
But I had a dream,
literally I fell asleep for like an hour
and then, this is what's been happening to me.
I fall asleep for like an hour, maybe like three hours.
I get up at like one o'clock and then I can't go back to bed
and then I just try to stay up for the rest of the day
like I did in fucking high school.
And I woke up because I had a dream
that I was younger and I was playing in the pool with my dad
and my dad turned into the Hulk
and beat the shit out of me underwater.
Dad dreams are always so fucked up, dude.
I used to have this recurring nightmare as a kid
where my dad would become a mime
and he would put me in a big invisible box
and I would starve to death.
Yeah, pretty scary, right?
Yeah, I'd starve in the dream to death. I had a dream recently, this is another
like sign that this that I just need to like go to Costco, but I had a dream that
I was in a Zoom comedy show. Oh no. Yeah, I had a dream that I was in a Zoom comedy
show and nobody could hear me. Oh my god. Pretty fucked up stuff dude. Yeah.
Here's the, oh I just found another Billy Bob status.
I'm super sad, I developed Down Syndrome over years of abuse.
I'm crying.
Nice.
Poor Billy Bob.
Oh I'm crying and it's overflowing my home in the sewer.
That would suck if you, that would really suck if you could develop Down Syndrome.
It would be so funny if Pat accidentally, like he searched Billy Bob and he just found
a real account that he's reading from.
not the one that... A man who developed Down syndrome, Benjamin Button style. A guy that
looks like Voldemort. Yeah, he just looks like that. Yeah. I should make a new fake Facebook.
I'm gonna call it Cameron Patrick and I'm just gonna post about boys all day. Yeah.
yeah religious views
uh... religious views political views other nazi religious views
steve urkel is a fag i hope he dies
you're really putting your brother on blast right now
he's a patron he's gonna hear all this really really getting him right now
it was him and his friends so i don't know how much of this was him
it was all his friends i had the password to it
I think it might just be, I don't know.
No, it wasn't.
I'm going to try and log into it.
Okay, what's the password?
I don't know.
Yeah, you do.
It's definitely something he doesn't want to say out loud.
Yeah.
Well, no, because it might be a very, I don't remember the email.
He's spelling out a letter with his finger right now on the screen.
Oh, oh shit.
Oh, yeah, don't say the password.
Oh my God, yeah, don't say it.
No, I just, I don't know the email, but I think the password might just be.
The email's the same as the password.
He spelled email out.
Oh God, Jesus Christ.
Oh fuck.
I didn't even, yeah.
Wow.
I didn't know email addresses could be that long.
Yeah.
We should.
I don't know why my brother made his email for that account.
We must secure a future for the white race.
The email is super-cadastralistic-expialidocious, but they slipped the n-word in there somewhere.
And you can't figure out where.
Yeah, and he can't remember which word.
I've been thinking about converting to Islam also.
That's what's been going on with you.
I told you man, I'm approaching the void.
I think I'm going to convert to Islam.
Just because I'm...
Brother Caleb.
I was imagining growing up just the worst beard of all time.
I have a bald spot just like right under my chin and just growing out one of those big
like Philly Muslim beards wearing the square hat doing the other stuff.
Doing whatever Obama does.
Have you seen Four Lions?
Um.
Seen what?
Four Lions.
It's this movie.
At the zoo.
Yeah.
I only saw three.
Four Lions at the zoo.
It's this Chris Morris movie, um, about like some, like would be jihadist or
whatever, and they're all just like bumbling, like the whole thing.
There's just like one white British Muslim guy who tells them all
to eat like their SD cards.
That would be Caleb.
Yeah.
That's going to be Caleb in like two weeks.
No, I'm going to be like Vinny Paz from Jedi Mind Tricks.
I'm just gonna become like a conspiracy theorist, a Muslim who, um,
hates gay people.
Yeah.
That's what I think.
I think I'm going to lean that way.
I wanted to be Muslim in high school.
You wanted to be Muslim in high school?
You can just do it.
You don't have to.
I know.
That's what I didn't understand.
Just go for it.
That's why I never made it.
I didn't understand that.
He's trying everything.
I've been trying everything.
I just can't be Muslim.
Yeah.
I don't think I've ever wanted to convert to any religion.
No.
I think either atheism or Gnosticism or whatever.
Gnosticism.
He wants to be a Gnostic?
He wanted to be Gnostic.
What does that mean?
Gnosticism?
That's like this shit.
That's like the winged eye serpent shit.
That's like super esoteric.
Now I want to do that.
Yeah, it's sick dude.
You should do that.
I'm going to do that.
- Dude, you should be a Gnostic.
- Might I suggest Islam.
Dude, we should just all become Muslim, dude.
- Yeah. - That'd be sick.
Yeah, man, we could be like, yeah,
you could, we'll all be brother Cameron Patrick,
brother Cameron Patrick, brother Caleb Cameron,
brother Cameron Caleb.
- The honorable brother Elijah Caleb Muhammad.
- Yeah, Caleb X. - The way that your
- Your virtual background keeps cutting out the headphones
on your head, makes it look like you have no ears.
It's really funny. - No it doesn't.
- Yeah, it's really great.
- No. - I'm gonna wait
for it to happen again and take a screenshot.
- You shouldn't.
- I'm going to.
- Did it do it?
- All right, keep talking about Islam.
- Yeah, dude, we should, I'm just saying it would be fun.
We get matching rugs.
We could print cool, we get like a Supreme logo,
Supreme box logo rug. - Oh yeah, we could get that.
Yeah, that'd be fucking sick.
- You know, that'd be kinda sick, right?
- Yeah.
- We could, what else could we do?
We could, we get dreadlocks and nobody could be mad at us.
Yeah, okay, I'm in.
Yeah, we could have, oh no, we should become Sikhs.
Yeah.
Dude, we could get that fucking sword.
We can become Sikhs?
That's what, yeah, S-I-K-H, the religion.
Oh, I thought you wanted us to revert to,
so what we're gonna do is--
Revert, he said revert.
We're gonna--
Oh, which way, which way is reverting?
We're gonna revert to six year old children
but also become Muslim.
No. No.
No, that's what this dude thinks
that the Sikh religion is.
(laughing)
I thought you said six.
No, well yeah, I did say six.
Six was a pretty good age. Plural of a Sikh.
Six was a pretty good age, I think.
Yeah, for you, 'cause you got to make out
with six year olds.
No. (laughing)
Yeah, you did.
That's why you liked it.
Straight, no.
I never kissed anyone.
Patrick, when was your first kiss?
I was 15.
To who?
My first girlfriend.
15 bro.
You late as hell, bro.
So?
I don't, I don't like sex.
That's what's up.
That's what I like to hear.
See, you're already halfway to Muslim.
Let's go.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
Patrick's Patrick is a Muslim for two hours and he just starts, uh, everything
around him starts turning to giant cartoon pork chops and he's just drooling.
(laughing)
He wants what he can't have.
Or we could convert to,
Hinduism would be cool,
'cause we could have multiple arms installed.
- What if we convert to Pastafarianism?
- Oh my God, that'd be so sick, dude.
Yeah, I'm converting to whatever religion
Is the fish with the legs on the back?
Yeah.
Of the car.
That's fish.
That's when you follow fish on Twitter.
Yeah, that's when you follow the jam band.
Yeah.
That'd be sick.
Reba's a great song.
I don't think I've heard a single fish song.
Yeah, I think I've avoided it pretty well.
I didn't listen to fish until like this year.
But I did tell people I listened to fish when I was 12.
I did tell one of my teachers.
because she was playing a fish song and she was like I'll give out five pencils to anyone
who can tell me who it is and then she had to give me a hint but I was like oh this is
fish I've heard of fish I also listen to Primus and she was like oh my veteran brother listens
to Primus and I was like wow we're gonna be friends forever.
It's gonna be me someday. I'm gonna be your veteran brother.
Yeah, I'm gonna join the Marines.
And I'm gonna join your family.
Is Primus a Marine? I feel like...
I don't know. I don't...
Primus to me is like... as far as a fan base goes, I feel like it's closer to like...
It's the same guys as like people who loved Tool in like 2006.
Yeah, I think you're right.
Well, Les Claypool is an amazing bassist.
I still think that.
Yeah, but it's just like guys who have like...
like buy shirts at Walmart.
and have like big beards and long hair.
- Definitely, like Primus definitely has like a fan base
of like dudes who are like--
- Guys who have a t-shirt that says,
don't touch my D20.
- Yeah, and also seven year old liars.
- Yeah, I was in the two groups.
- You were seven, dude.
You were seven.
You were in the sixth grade.
You were in the seventh grade, you were seven years old.
- 12 is supposed to be the age of truthfulness.
- I listened to Primus a lot.
- A lot.
yeah my name is mud now yeah seventh grade see he's lying he's trembling
because he's lying so he knows that Allah will punish him for eternity sounds like
you listen to Lymus dude what's the yeah what's the glue song yeah
Lymus and Lymus and Lucy yeah that's right Primus and Lucy yeah I don't know
what that would sound like. It would probably just sound like...
It's like the... all the vocals are just the...
Yeah. Yeah.
So it's just like...
It's like the bass riff to "My Name Is Mud" and then once he starts singing it goes like...
Primus and Lucy. Alright, one in the bag. Four more.
Four more. Four more what? Four more awesome wordplay. Four more years.
How about instead of tool it's drool. And it's my cousin drool. What about instead of
tool? Yeah, yes it's drool and instead of pneuma it's pneumonia. And it's pneuma pneuma.
Instead of pneuma it's pneuma pneuma. Yeah that would be fool. And instead of stink fist
It's spit, spit.
Stink piss.
That's doesn't fall, it's spit, spit.
Links, links, fist.
And it's about, oh it's LinkedIn.
Yeah, LinkedIn.
Yeah, what if it's marketing tool?
And it's LinkedIn.
Oh my god.
There, we did it.
That's fucking good.
We're done.
We can end the episode.
We don't need to do anything.
No.
Yeah, it sucks that all my stim check is literally just going towards rent.
Yeah, dude, you live in a crazy expensive apartment.
You're a fool.
It's not that expensive.
It's so expensive.
I want to do the AI Patrick lunches.
Oh, yeah.
Go to TalkToTransformer.
Yeah, in the Discord people were sending.
I don't remember who.
There's this AI website, TalkToTransformer.com.
It's really great.
You type in something and it completes the text using AI.
That's where Kayla Pitt's peeing penis came from.
That's true.
Patrick say something.
Somebody kept typing in Patrick colon I had the craziest lunch today comma I had and then
completing the text and it makes great Patrick lunches.
Okay here's one.
I had the craziest lunch today.
I had iced chicken nachos and a dip.
It was really great.
Oh, the old socks, a fresh pair of old socks with mint and ginger and garlic.
Could have eaten this again, my favorite place in town.
That is one of the funniest things about Patrick, like going to a restaurant with him, is that
he acts like he's been to any restaurant.
He's acts like he's been there a million times.
Like we went to some like Korean barbecue place and he had never had Korean barbecue
before and they bring out all like the like toppings for your like meal and he
just started eating those individually like all the like jellies and shit and I
was like what are you doing he's like it's just like all the just like all the
pre food stuff no cuz we did have Korean barbecue I've never had it on like the
thing we went to the place down the street from my apartment that's what I'm
talking about that's where you did that oh okay I thought you're talking about
about the time we got Korean barbecue in LA.
- No, that was like the--
- No, I asked you--
- That was the most dangerous place ever.
- I asked you what it was and you said that
that's like the Korean version of tortilla chips
at a restaurant.
- I don't think I said that.
- You said that, you said that.
- You said that.
- I don't think so.
- You said like the kimchi and stuff,
you said that that is like the equivalent
of getting chips and salsa at a restaurant.
- I don't think so.
I'm gonna have to disagree with you here.
I think your brain said that to you so that you could eat goo.
Mmm.
Patrick eats goo.
Well, either way, I don't, it was good.
Patrick eats goo is good.
All that stuff stands on its own.
Man I fucking miss Korean barbecue right now, man.
I wanna- Make some at home.
That place in LA, well, at home it's not endless.
Yeah, how would you make- That's the fucked up part about-
You would have to have a dump truck of old meat that is frozen so you can't smell what
it really smells like and just cascading onto a hot pan because that's what Korean barbecue
is.
It's really good.
I love Korean barbecue, yeah.
I probably ate five pounds of beef that day that we went to that Korean barbecue place.
Oh, that place in LA?
Yeah, we had to eat five pounds of beef because fucking...
Oh yeah, they charge you if you don't eat all the meat.
Yeah, anything that you don't eat, they charge you and you had a time limit.
I would try not to.
They start charging you after you're in there
for like an hour.
So we had to eat all that in an hour.
- Yeah, man, it was not,
yeah, we didn't know that when we ordered it.
So we got like four giant bowls of frozen meat.
- Yeah.
- And the thing, I don't remember,
my guess is that--
- There was like a family having a birthday party next to us.
- Yeah.
- And we're just like--
- It was just us and then a fucking birthday.
- We're eating half of a cow.
Yeah, dude, it was fucked up.
And it's just like the most disgusting place ever.
But it was it was like 11 bucks for all you can eat. Oh, yeah. No, that was the best part about it
Yeah, I dude I straight up I like
Maxed out my credit card just going to LA to go on a food tour
You did a good job. There's a good you saw it all. Oh, yeah, I saw I got everything I needed out there
I keep trying to generate Patrick lunches and it just over and over is saying I had the craziest lunch today
I ate iced tea every time I click
Here, I got one.
You can't get to say anything else.
I had the craziest lunch today.
I had three big breakfasts of roasted chicken and then I had some cornmeal pancakes and
some berries and cinnamon sugar and then some healthy brown rice.
But the idea of it is you have an extra special meal like that and you don't know how to eat
healthy with it.
You don't want to put the calories in yourself but also you want to make sure the calories
aren't enough to put on your weight.
So I'm like, I think I need to learn to love baked goods.
But then Kelly says, yeah, I think so.
And then Patrick says they're better than pizza and then Kelly says oh man I'm like come on
pizza seriously.
I had the craziest lunch today.
I had iced tea and watermelon sliced soup in a bagel and sausage roll with balsamic reduction
and I know those two probably probably not together in my mind but they are together
in the same little bagel.
Okay, okay I added one word and it got way better.
Okay, so I made it.
Patrick, I had the craziest lunch today.
I had poop.
So here's what it is.
I had the craziest lunch today.
I had poop in my vagina for five hours.
Audio cuts out.
American.
And you ate it.
Patrick, I ate it.
I ate it.
And I ate it in front of the toilet right in my bathroom.
And it tasted like poop.
And it felt like poop.
But I took a picture and uploaded it to my blog so people could see it.
I posted it to Tumblr too. I mean it's not quite a fit to blog about. It's definitely not fit to talk about it on Twitter.
American. It's actually kind of disgusting and a little gross. Patrick.
Yeah, I have a nice vagina so it's not so.
[Patrick laughing]
I, uh...
That's just what Patrick said.
Alright, I typed it in. It's, uh...
Patrick. I had the craziest lunch today. Caleb is a pedophile.
No, it doesn't say that.
It's a good time to be a pedophile in America.
Aaron, this thing is in so much trouble and the only reason it's still a thing is it because
Donald Trump gave it his stink eye.
I got it.
Wait.
Aaron, do you ever get the sense that you're funny and creative and you can create great
material but nobody in Hollywood is listening to you?
Patrick, and the majority of people in Hollywood are white males.
Aaron, yeah.
Patrick, and white males seem to enjoy you being racist and misogynistic.
I was joking about these pastel.
Okay, listen to this lunch.
Patrick, I had the craziest lunch today.
I had over 1,500 brioche rolls.
I love these things.
And other stuff.
And the brownies.
Also got some ice cream and a Milky Way treat with the treats.
I'll have a hog platter.
This is the best.
I had iced tea and a bowl of that tiny, yummy, gelatinous, yellow food.
creating one right now. Let's see. So Patrick, how many of these lunches have you had? None
of them. I don't believe you. Whoa, this one knows that you don't drink coffee. What? It
said, "Today I had ice water with Nutella." That was amazing. Patrick doesn't drink any
coffee. You can tell because the car keys don't work. Last time I got drunk enough that
I was, and I ran out of orange juice, and I considered for a while just pouring the rest
to the vodka in with ice and then putting buffalo sauce in it.
(laughing)
So it's like a Bloody Mary, right?
- Yeah, pretty much.
- Probably.
- Here's a talk to Transformer I just did.
Caleb Pitts is a pedophile who traveled
across the United States helping men
who had sexually abused children.
He would open up his home to the men
in hopes that they would change,
giving them jobs and counseling.
It was only when he began abusing the 13-year-old boy
that he was caught and the Connecticut man pled guilty to abuse charges in October.
Now with the help of his wife, Brett Pitts, he plans to have his own therapy session at
the Millbrook Cancer Center.
Caleb's wife, Brett Pitts.
Caleb's wife is named Brett.
No, he's not a guy.
I mean, she's not, that's not true.
Patrick, I had the craziest lunch today.
I had chocolate, creamy cake, cocoa, and I ate a lot of M&M's and a ton of coffee and
And I was like, if I die today, I want a full body funeral.
Full body funeral.
Patrick Doran is a famous rapist.
An Oxford University computer science student has claimed that he was raped by a famous
pedophile, Patrick Doran, and detailed a story that has shocked the internet.
That's all we got.
Dude, you can hear the sirens coming for that one.
They're coming for you, dude.
They're gonna get you, bro.
Oh, there they are.
Caleb Pitts is a big fat pedophile, but let's be honest, no one really cares.
How can we possibly know if his postings were from a full blown pedophile?
We don't have access to the answers.
How can we call him out as a pedophile when his articles are full images of boys and girls
in sexual poses?
Even worse, he's no longer able to keep his back turned.
We don't even know if this little terror is real or just an internet hoax.
To be fair, our crime branch isn't even able to tell us if Pitts is actively planning for
more pedophilia because his crimes keep escalating.
It's unclear why Pitts would go to such a little boy's penis.
Patrick Doran makes child porn.
Doran, the Rensselaer County Judge said, is now serving life in prison.
Sorry buddy.
This website is perfect.
Yeah.
It don't miss.
Patrick Doran got pregnant from a genetic defect.
There you have it.
Wow.
Hold on, I'm making one right now.
Oh, they have prompts?
What?
What do you mean they have prompts?
This is too much dead air.
Yeah.
Patrick Doran can't find his penis in his own fat, but instead he found out that daughter
Natalia, now five, would be victim of incest by her stepfather, Patrick Doran.
Oh my god.
What is right- you are one of the sickest fucks of all time.
These are not- yeah that's deeply fucked up.
Everything I just said is true and everything that Patrick just said is a lie.
That's one of the disclaimers of the website.
Did you guys ever do, what's the, fuck, the smart bot or whatever?
Chatterbot?
No, no, what was the one, Jesus Christ.
What's like the one that everyone did in like middle school?
Fat Caleb Pitt sucked a baby off, did more than eight ounces of water during a marathon.
I'm thinking I'm talking I think I was arrested. Yeah, that's what I was thinking of.
Yeah, we're both thinking of Cleverbot. Yeah, Cleverbot was one that I would just
go on Cleverbot all the time and try to get her to say that she wanted to suck
my dick. Hmm. I think I could jack off to Cleverbot. That's very clever. That's very clever.
That's right. Yeah, that's right. I outsmarted the bot. The bot's like, "Well,
Well well well.
You've done it again.
I guess I have to do this.
You should have been able to make pictures too.
Pictures of humongous pussies and fat vaginas and little assholes and big ass boobies.
But they're all robot.
They're all computers.
They're square.
Here's how much I'm regressing.
If a computer had sex, where would it put the computer penis?
The slots, the drives, and the jacks.
It would depend on the dimension of the penis,
or balls, or whatever you're putting inside.
Well, yeah, but what are you putting,
what is the computer's penis, first of all?
So all computers are girls.
Okay, and I thought it was boys.
Count the hodges and tell me that it's not.
Well, no, boys are boys, and boys can fuck computers.
And the way that you do it is you drop,
you put a condom inside the hole
in the middle of a DVD drive, when you like take it out,
you know what I mean, like the hole in the middle?
You put it right there and you fuck the condom.
And that, you basically, that's the only difference.
It sounds like you've done it before.
No.
Yeah, this sounds like you've done it.
No, I haven't done that.
I think he's done it.
I'm just smart. I think you've done it.
No, I'm an engineer.
I think Caleb did that to--
Nothing weird about being an engineer.
He did that to an old Gateway PC
and he pretended that the cow print was a real cow.
- You actually did that?
- No.
- Sounds like you've done it before.
- Sounds like you've done it.
- No, I think you actually did it.
- You did it?
- Patrick walked into H&R Block and he said,
"Where's the block? I wanna fuck it."
And then they didn't let you and you went to my house.
- They don't even have H&R Block close to my house.
- Yeah, it was a long walk.
- You had to go on a very long journey
to try to fuck the block.
- Yeah, you went across the whole country.
You broke quarantine.
You did this yesterday.
You weren't wearing a mask and you infected a thousand,
thousand, thousand.
Don't care about it.
What if you--
Don't care about that.
If they get infected, that's their fault.
I'm immune.
Didn't somebody yell at you the other day?
Oh yeah, no, somebody, so I'm wearing the red hat
that you gave me.
The wheel of honor red hat.
The biggest prank I've ever played on you.
It's the only hat that fits me, so I try to wear it.
It's a red hat that says,
make America great again on it.
I can't read, so I didn't know it said that.
Yeah, it's a red hat, it just says General something company.
It says Federal Emergency Squad.
Federal Emergency Squad.
So I'm actually a--
But yeah, it's a red hat with white letters.
Yeah, red hat with white letters, so I'm wearing it,
and then this guy who just looked drunk walked in,
while Dom and I were shopping. To your house.
Yeah, to my house, no, we were at the grocery store.
I wasn't wearing a mask,
'cause we were only getting two or three things.
I don't have one.
I don't have one either.
I mean just put something around your face.
It's kind of...
Yeah.
But...
Whatever, I just wasn't wearing one.
And...
You can just like wrap a sweatshirt around your face or something.
Yeah.
I...
So he walked up to me and he was like,
"You're doing the right thing!"
I was like, "What?"
Like you're doing the right thing! No masks! Look at all these creep shows!
They're all wearing masks! And then we saw him in the canned food aisle and he
walked up to somebody like they were wearing like a furry hat like they were
wearing like a hat that had like a Daniel Boone hat? No like like furry ears on top
and then their mask and he walked by them and he went "creep!" I was like yeah I
guess I can't tell if that's about the mask or his furry shit but either way is
right dude yeah it's it is against the will of I thought I was gonna have to
punch him in the face cuz he got like too close to Dom I was like yeah punch
him in the face yeah yeah there's a mental barrier around his girlfriend and
if somebody gets within 10 feet no no he doesn't he doesn't get old man getting
in my girlfriend's like area I don't hurt she got in her area he got and did you
punch him for that I know you did he went in your girlfriend's area you didn't
Punch him dude. Damn dude. I would punch, I straight up
If an old I would punch an old person out
Whoa, I don't care. I would I would beat the shit out of an old. That's a skater attitude right there
I would go I would go to a retirement home and if any of them talk shit to me, I wouldn't hesitate
Yeah, yeah, it would be on sight before they even finish their sentence
They're just like can you get me a glass of water and then you just decked them in their fucking fake teeth
Yep, yeah, I take out their teeth. Call your grandson you fucking bitch
We're ooh, ooh, you don't have tires on her on her wheelchair. You don't remember where you put your
You don't remember where you put your your your teeth
Yeah, yeah. Yeah now I know why you don't is I a fucking stupid bit
I just beat I just beat your brain to blue. So I'll tell you what lady those tits look like dog shit
How about you take those tennis balls off your walker
and stick them in your shirt. I wouldn't punch an old woman,
but I would do some classic style pranks on an old woman.
Dude, you, no, you do not,
you should be worried about the old men.
So you're punching the old men,
you should be punching the old women.
The old men, they all fought in World War II, man.
They all have glass eyes.
Yeah, they all fought in World War II,
so that means they should be able,
if they fought in World War II and they can't take me down.
But why are you punching them, dude?
You should be punching those old women.
They didn't do anything. They didn't even help.
They were making fucking boats in World War II.
If they, if an old, if somebody who has like a purple heart and is a decorated war veteran.
A purple heart sounds to me like a monster.
[Laughter]
There's an old person who has like war medals and they can't fight me.
Then they're a pussy. I'm sorry.
But, but, but, so now it's like you're testing them?
I thought you were just beating them up.
Why do you have to give them some some tests is this like how they qualify for Social Security now?
Yeah, it should be there's no
Just a point where you can't beat up Patrick. That's when they start sending you the money, right?
Now dude, you got it. You got to get in there and that's a really good
I did cuz if you can't beat up Patrick Patrick's gonna rock your shit. You're gonna die. What are you gonna do to me?
What are you gonna do to me Eugene? Huh? Eugene Eugene Herman? He's gonna see you
Yeah, dr. Eugene goo. I'm gonna fight. Dr. Eugene goo with logic. I'm gonna fight you with my goo
Yeah, I'm gonna stuff you full of it and you're gonna suffocate
We're gonna play Splatoon. We're gonna play games with each other and I'm gonna put a mop up in you
I just I want to pump glop into Pat. I want to know I don't
Stop saying that right now
Yeah, I want to I want to go to various tubes and fill you with glop
I'm gonna put a thin layer of glop between your skin and the meat inside you just see what I'm gonna
Do you love you with glop? I'm gonna de glop de glop you I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm gonna just glop you and then de glop you
You're not gonna. No, I'm going in and out. No, no, you were not putting glop in
You're gonna swell up like a balloon and then shrink down to an ant and I'm gonna suck you up.
Here's my impression of Patrick once I glop his face.
That's what it's gonna be like. I'm gonna seal your mouth like King Tutankhamun's tomb in Egypt.
You just wanted to do your Kenny impression from South Park.
That's all you wanted to do.
I got caught. You're right. That's exactly what I started to do.
Fuck, he got me again.
I am wearing an orange hoodie.
Cinched all the way to my eyes.
Don't you get to see Kenny in the new episodes? You see Kenny in the movie.
What movie?
Bigger, longer, uncut. Harry Potter.
Yeah. Whoa. Oh, Kenny's in Harry Potter? Yeah. Oh, he's every guy who dies.
Yeah.
He's Robert Pattinson's character. Yeah.
Cedric Diggory. Cedric the Entertainer.
Cedric, I'm so sorry.
Cedric. Yeah, he was pretty entertaining in that movie.
Yeah, he was. Yeah.
I like that movie. Yeah.
Cedric the Entertainer. I think that's the best one.
My favorite movie is Cedric the Entertainer. No, the best one is the third one by far.
There's like no...
It's definitely the third one. I disagree.
The best one's the fourth. No, the fourth is the second best.
I'm gonna talk about Alfonso Cuaron. Fourth is the second best.
Alfonso Cuaron can suck my balls, dude.
I don't like Alfonso Cuaron. I fucking hate Gravity.
Gravity can suck my fucking dick but the third one is the best one.
He did the one that's about two friends who have sex with each other.
E2 Mama Tambien.
Yeah, I don't care about anything, anything, I don't care about him at all.
I just think the third one is the best one.
Doesn't that mean, doesn't that mean and your mom, your mom too?
The third one is good because they put in...
What?
E2 Mama Tambien, doesn't that mean and your mom too?
Yes.
Wow.
Congrats Patrick.
Just a little Spanish lesson from Pat.
El Perro.
Yeah, it means the parrot.
What do you like about the third one, Cam?
What do you think it's the best?
I think because they add jokes in it, it's funnier than the other ones, and it's also
scarier because they put in scary ghosts that fly and kiss you.
I think the fourth one's the scariest.
No, the best...
No, they all...
Okay, but one thing I hope we can agree on is the fifth and after all suck fucking ass.
They're all terrible.
After four.
I don't know.
I don't watch them as much.
Once they leave school.
I watched them all recently.
- That's the only reason I have opinions on that.
- Whoa, somebody is pro school.
- Yeah. - Yeah, whoa, uh-oh.
- He just said they get worse once they leave school.
That's when the real movie starts, buddy.
- You know why it's worse when they leave school?
It's 'cause there's no more disobeying the rules.
Harry Potter and his friends, they go to school,
they disobey all the rules,
they go into the Forbidden Forest, okay,
they go to the Chamber of Secrets,
they go and they get the potions,
they do it all against the wishes of the teachers, okay?
- That's actually a really good point.
- Once they leave school, they're working with the teachers,
with Dumbledore to defeat Voldemort
who is trying to destroy the school.
- I would never work with Dumbledore.
- They're trying to fight against Voldemort
to blow up the, he's trying to blow up the school.
- I've been bested, dude.
This is a serious Lincoln-Douglas debate
and you're Douglas, you won.
- Yeah, I know, I'm smart, okay?
- I know, man.
That was a, it is funny,
why would you name it the Forbidden Forest?
That would just make me as like a troublemaker
just wanna jump in that fuckin' forest so bad.
Name it the like Girl Forest or something
and I'll never go in there.
- Yeah, 'cause if you have like,
if it's like, imagine in your house,
there was an, it was called the off-limits fridge.
- Oh, you know my ass.
- How fucking crazy would you go for that fridge, dude?
You would do every, you'd do all sorts
of stealth mission bullshit to get to that fridge.
But if they called it like--
- You open it up and it's full of giant spaghettis.
- They called it the broccoli fridge.
Oh my, ooh, that is kind of the forbidden forest
of fridges then.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, it's just a bad naming device.
I don't know why I fucking started doing this but uh I didn't realize how many I didn't
realize how many games there were on the internet archive.
What are you doing right now?
You're doing that right now?
What the fuck dude?
Yeah I'm doing it right now.
I'm downloading some games.
Oh my god.
On the internet archive?
On like the wayback machine?
Yeah.
I just downloaded, I just found a Star Wars Renegade Squadron for PSP on there.
Oh I think I might get, I think I might get the Jedi Fallen Order game.
I need like a, I want to play a Star, yeah cause I'm just, I'm getting tired of like,
the only game I'm liking right now is Warzone, cause Doom is just getting boring and I want
to get the new one but I don't want to get the new one until I finish this one.
Yeah.
I just need something I need something different. I need something where I control it a child. I have a binding of Isaac
That's pretty good as you put your child in oh shit. Oh shit
Patrick they have Yoda's adventure - no they have
Yeah
- they have Lego Star Wars - on there for windows. They have leisure suit Larry
They have you ladies Patrick's Patrick's gonna see some some one pixel nipples
is
We're just gonna do a classic gap.
Yeah, you sit this one out, Pat.
What's up, bro?
Not too much.
I heard Patrick died.
I didn't die.
I'm still alive and right here.
So I'm not actually...
He's not too upset about it.
I'm right here.
I'm not dead.
Usually HIV has to turn into full-blown AIDS first before it kills somebody.
I'm right here and I don't have HIV.
Pat, you can talk as much as you want.
I'm going back to the pandemic.
Oh, he doesn't have HIV anymore.
He has AIDS now.
Yeah, it advanced.
I don't have AIDS.
Oh, and he also apparently has dementia because he can't even remember that he had AIDS.
You do, oh and he also apparently has dementia because he can't even remember that he has
AIDS.
I don't have AIDS.
Yeah you do dude, I'm sorry.
I see it, it's branded on your forehead.
I do not have AIDS.
I can see it under your skin dude.
Yeah.
You can't see anything.
Dude, I can see your blood man.
I can dude.
I can see the Ronald Reagan chip they put in your neck when you got the diagnosis.
No, I put the, you can't see anything.
Look at the screen right now, there's nothing.
Yeah, that's what it's gonna look like for you
when you die of HIV.
No.
Just gonna be pure black emptiness,
just nothing but the void.
Here you are.
And a little bit of gray too.
Whoa, he's giving the finger, man.
Yeah, he's giving the old AIDS finger.
I don't have an AIDS finger.
Yeah, it is, dude.
I do not have an AIDS finger.
You do and you chase around all the other kids
on the playground saying, I have the AIDS finger,
I'm gonna touch you.
I don't.
and they run away and they get the teacher and the teacher says the teacher says Patrick we
understand you're having a difficult time dealing with your diagnosis but you really cannot be doing
that you can't take it out on these other kids because it's actually it's super contagious yeah
we would much rather um just kick you out of the school than have these kids scared at recess
they're they're not going to kick me out of school they already did i just got a letter
from your principal and i i yeah no you did not get a letter from my oh you're working with the
the
I'm not friends with the principal.
Who's friends with the principal saying you don't want to get kicked out of school?
A real kid, when someone says they're getting kicked out of school, you say that's awesome,
but you said, "No, they're not going to kick me out of school.
How are you so sure, dude?"
I'm just here to eat my popcorn.
This is seriously good stuff.
I don't want to get kicked out of school because, first of all, he admits it.
school and also how did you know you weren't going to kick out?
You talked to the teachers and principals.
Because I would miss recess.
You fucking idiot if you're kicked out of school every day is recess all day.
You are so stupid.
Having AIDS every day is recess.
Nobody is going to make you go to school.
That's messed up.
That's the thing about AIDS is if you get it you can just play all the time.
Yeah.
That's not even true.
That is true dude.
Play with the lives of other men in the back house.
If you have AIDS.
You can't, yeah, but if you can't like,
if you tell your manager at Subway,
hey, Daryl, I have AIDS, he's just gonna send you home.
So?
So, what are you gonna do?
You're gonna play on your home playground.
Yeah.
You're gonna play in the bath, at the bath house.
You're gonna play at the friggin' bath house.
Here we go, resorting to ad hominems, classic.
Yeah.
You guys are rude.
Oh, we're rude?
You're rude.
We're rude?
Do you remember who gave the finger to the camera
just a few minutes ago?
The ace finger at that. I would say that person's,
yeah, not just any finger.
You need a serious attitude adjustment, buddy.
Yeah.
You need an attitude adjustment.
I'm gonna put you in Caleb's attitude rehabilitation
program. You're not gonna do shit.
I am, dude. You're not gonna do shit.
Oh, okay, guess whose sentence just got bumped up
from one week to two weeks.
That's right. You can't do anything.
You're doing all the chores.
You can't do anything to me.
You're doing all the chores,
you're editing all the episodes.
You have to keep your room clean.
If I see a single empty can, we're adding another week.
You are not gonna find any of my cans.
If you talk back to me.
Okay, I'm gonna press the mute button.
You can't.
On real life.
You can't mute me.
I can.
You're not even.
And you're gonna have to,
and you're gonna have to clean the toilet
with your mouth and your tongue.
Wait, I just found a.
The toilet's clogged and you have to use your foot
unclog it. I'm still on the archive and I found... Suck the dookie out of the
toilet buddy. Yeah. I found a... Now you have two months. I'm on the
movies section of the website and under sci-fi and horror there's a
downloadable movie there's like an old like... Get to it. Old movie called
the child molested. Yeah it's a biopic about you. It's not a biopic about me! It's not a biopic about me! It came out this year and it's just about your entire life. No it's not true.
Yeah and then there's a prequel called the child molested and that's also about you.
With a comma? There are two about yeah the child comma molested and those are both
about you and then there's one called looking for Bigfoot and that one's also
about you. There's a one called the Philadelphia Project which is also about
you. None of these are about me. There's one called I am Sam that's like kind of
about you. There's one called Precious. That one's about... Precious is about you. Sean
Penn. That's about Sean Penn, idiot. Precious is about you. Every John Candy movie. Precious is about Sean Penn.
- Sean Penn.
(laughing)
Yeah, it's kinda like how Sean Penn
played a mentally disabled person on I Am Sam.
He played a fat black woman in Precious.
- Yeah, that's right.
It was all seed digital.
They basically did Avatar to him
and made him look like Precious.
Made him look like Gabrielle Sidibe.
director the director handed the CG artist a note and all it said was make
Sean Penn look like crutches. And he just had to guess what that meant. And they did
they did an amazing job. And they literally won an Oscar. Let me say yeah. Did you guys ever see
The Artist? Yeah, that's that the silent film one? Yeah. Yeah I saw that. I heard about that. I did not
I thought it sounded so boring that I never even gave it.
Thought it was pretty lame.
Yeah.
Why do you ask?
I think, just 'cause I think that's maybe the,
maybe the maddest I've ever seen my dad be
is somehow when that movie won Best Picture.
Yeah, dude, that movie's a piece of shit.
He didn't even see it.
He was just walking around for an hour around the apartment
just like, "Are you kidding me?
"A silent movie?"
What was it up against?
That was 2011, right?
I think it was like American Hustle or something.
Oh yeah.
2011.
I remember that.
I mean, I don't like that movie at all.
I mean, I think it's pretty lame.
Let's see, 2011 Best Picture.
It sounds so fucking stupid.
Oh no, it wasn't 2011.
It was 2012, I think.
Yeah.
I think it came out in 2011, so it was 2012.
What are you doing?
Best Picture.
I'm singing my Oscar song.
Oh, that's why.
Oh, okay.
Okay, this makes more sense.
My dad was so pissed because it beat out Moneyball.
[Laughter]
And my dad was like, "Moneyball is one of the most accurate sports films of all time."
And he just was pissed about it.
And then Brian Posehn put out that...
The Fartist.
Yeah, The Fartist, like a year and a half later.
Yeah.
Which is such a genius move.
Yeah, I'm gonna make a movie...
I'm gonna make a movie...
Called Brian Posehn.
Called Brian Posehn and it's gonna be a silent movie.
Yeah.
No, what's a, instead of Moonlight, I'm going to make a movie now called Moon Fart.
And it's going to be a comedy special.
Or My Moon, My Moonlight.
I'm going to do, instead of the Florida Project, it's going to be called the Florida, it's
going to be called the Fart Fart, and it's going to be my new comedy album that's coming
out.
People are going to love it, dude.
The Farting Project.
The Farting Fart.
It's going to be called Willem Dafoe Farts for 20 Minutes.
Yeah, it's gonna be a 20 minute stand up special.
Wow.
Willem Dafoe farting and shitting.
Yeah, that'd be a better movie.
Did you guys like that?
The Florida Project?
I haven't seen it.
I watched Tangerine.
I'm gonna watch the Florida Project someday soon probably.
I'm never, dude I.
Tangerine's cool.
I think it was just going to Emerson but just like, god damn I just can't watch like movies
anymore.
I don't have the patience for anything.
I just get mad kinda.
You should re-watch the Departed.
That's what I did yesterday.
I did.
I did re-watch the Departed like the other day.
I've never watched the Departed.
Oh, dude, it's so good.
Yeah, I know.
I didn't get to watch it.
I just watch old horror movies and stuff like that.
That's all I really care about.
It's all you care about?
I mean your friends Patrick and Cameron.
He doesn't care about us at all.
I know those are my friends.
Yeah.
Whoops.
You guys, you guys.
Yeah, I just don't care about movies that much.
I don't know, except for.
Yeah, I don't like, like people.
I just care about the horror genre.
I've been on this tip for years and not everybody talks shit.
I said movies suck and you guys were like movies are good man.
I've never said that.
I like TV better.
You guys should watch Iron Giant.
I don't like TV better but.
Dude, TV is, TV is far.
I mean the dude the office parks and recreation.
What if they made they couldn't make the office the movie?
Yeah, dude, a caveman.
Oh yeah, caveman starring Nick Kroll.
Yeah, caveman, Kroll show, big mouth.
Are you kidding? Caveman, Kroll.
Key and peel but it's both. Caveman, Kroll.
But it's Kroll and Kroll and it's two white Krolls.
(laughing)
Come on, dude.
That's a fucking, that's T.
That's a movie.
- It's called Prestige Television.
It's called that for a reason, right?
And the reason is that Nick Kroll has billions of dollars.
- Well, the reason, yeah, the reason is
because you remember that part in The Prestige
when he has a bunch of clones?
That's what they did with Kroll,
and that's why he's in so many different shows.
And that's why it's called Prestige Television.
- That's how that guy gets so much amazing content out.
- They should have called that show Kroll's Shows,
'cause there is a lot of shows in that show.
- There's tons of shows, and that's a really good point.
Yeah, they should have called it Kroll,
They should have called it Nick Kroll's TV shows.
They should have called it TV shows.
They should have called it TV and you could flip through the different shows.
Yeah.
Oh my god, that's genius.
And if you don't like one of the shows on Kroll's show, you can change the channel.
You can change the channel and now, guess what, now it's Nick Kroll giving the news.
You know, it's Nick Kroll edited into Alexandra Daddario's scenes in True Detective where
she's naked.
Uh huh.
You know what I mean?
See, that's all, I don't care about the other stuff.
We get to see Nick Kroll's juicy titties.
That's a great idea.
I just want to see more of Kroll's shows.
I just want to see Nick Kroll just absolutely getting railed in Monsters Ball instead of
Halle Berry.
Uh huh.
I want to see Nick Kroll sucking off Hugh Jackman in Swordfish.
Yeah, dude.
That's what I want to see.
I want to see all of Nick Kroll.
I want to see his gross.
I want to see Kroll's Hole.
Kroll's Hole.
I want to see his version of holes with with yeah even Stevens and he sings the
song he sings the oh yeah he sings that he says crawling up that hole crawling
up that show yeah I'd like to I'd like to I'd like to crawl up his urethra yeah
yeah like like that fish that we were talking about the other day yeah the one
that did that that crawls up your urethra the one that gets in Sean Williams penis
in the rundown yeah it can swim up your p-stream yeah it did and then if you try
to pull it out it's got fins so it like cut your peepee open. Why would you slice
it open like a like a hot dog sliced in half? Sometimes I question the
great Muslim God's intentions with stuff like that but then I just got to
remember he's got a plan for all of us and all of our penises. Mm-hmm. You know
he's sitting up there and he's designing schematics of different little boys
wieners and then he just sends them off to the and then the elves take care of
rest.
The Elves.
It's true.
Yeah.
You guys are obviously not Muslims, but basically we believe that it's sort of a Santa's Workshop
scenario up there, and he's designing little boys' penises all day, and then the Elves,
they sort of put together the legs and the body and the head and stuff, but God, he's
got the family jewels.
Yeah, he's got Gene Simmons family jewels.
And Jesus, a lot of people think that Muslims think that Jesus was like a bad guy or something,
but we actually think that he's a prophet who designs the balls for God.
Wow.
Yeah, so he designs the shape of the balls.
That's why some people have acorn balls, some people have packing peanut balls, but we all
have balls, and you have Jesus to thank for that.
I just did another talk to Transformer of Patrick Lunch.
It's Patrick. I had the craziest lunch today. I had poop iced tea with and a condom. I mean, I'm sorry. Do you have AIDS?
He does he's listening. I don't here's a transformer. I'd like to talk to
Optimus Prime. Yeah, I'd like to pick his brain a little bit. No, no
Caleb did you say a slur dude? No
Something owes you a coke. Whoa
Caleb you can't even Caleb you can't talk. I can't talk. No, you can't try to stop me optimist. I'll protect me
No, it's not jinx. We're in jinx right now
You can't even talk. Caleb's doing his Kenny impression again. No, I'm not
No, that's Kenny impression dude, yeah
This is Optimus Prime.
That sounds just like Kenny.
Patrick, you are a girl.
You transform into a girl.
I can't hear you over your little sweatshirt
'cause you sound like Kenny.
You are a Decepticon who transforms into a girl.
Nah.
Cameron and Caleb, roll out.
Okay, let's go, Optimus.
Patrick, come out of the closet from being gay.
Got you.
No.
Yeah, I couldn't hear any of that you sounded like Kenny
Dude, you sound like Kenny from Kenny and versus spinny
And I'm spinning and I'm gonna fart in your ass. No, Spenny's not the one Spenny is though
Yeah
I sound like Kenny cuz I'm the one who does all the pranks on you and you see you sound a little bit sound like
You sound like Lenny from from next you sound like Lenny you see my Lenny from of mice and man
I said it first. I said it first you fucking
Drink, oh my god, stop saying that or I said jinx doesn't matter. I stopped saying that slur dude. Yeah, you didn't say that
It's my god
We're gonna get they're gonna kick us off patreon. Just kick Patrick off patreon, please. They're not gonna please. Oh my god
Please kick him off. I actually know the CEO
His name is optimus prime and I've been talking to him that your friend you and Michael Rapaport's friend. Yeah
Well, he's not really friends with Michael Rapaport
He's friends with me and he transformed the way that patreon makes money is he transforms into money and then pays himself
self.
Patrick is a de-sexed-icon because he's a eunuch.
You got castrated, you got de-sexed.
Don't care if I'm a eunuch.
Alright, cool.
He does care.
Don't care.
He cares.
And me and Caleb are awesome bots.
I get to, I get to, I get to, I get to go home and play video games.
Yeah, we're awesome bots.
Awesome bots, roll out.
Shut up Patrick.
Do that, do it again.
Yeah, you literally, Optimus Prime is awesome bots, roll out.
Thanks, awesome, awesometimous.
Awesome.
ostomus Austin power this prime is prior prior make you horny baby what about
optimus prior go ahead humans humans be walking like this
Decepticons be walking like this. Autobots, we cool man. We be walking like this shit.
What's up with Decepticon women?
How come they love Autobots?
*laughter*
That's a good place to end it, I think.
Yeah.
Alright.
Perfect.
Autobots, roll out!
Okay.
Alright.
Bye.
- All right.
- Bye.
[BLANK_AUDIO]