You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[laughter]
[explosion]
I'm recording. Yeah, I'm pretty much recording.
I'm recording too.
Yeah, I'm basically the best at it though.
Yeah, I've hit the button so damn hard.
No, I basically hit the button better than anybody.
I have it rigged up to a Staples "That was easy" button just so that I can feel some real feedback when I press it.
You practice pressing buttons by pressing guys' P-stot.
- Yeah. - No.
I don't press anybody's P-stot.
If I did, it would be a woman's P-stot.
- Yeah, your own.
- No, I'm not a woman, I'm a guy.
- So you do touch guys' P-stots.
- I don't touch guys, first of all.
First of all, okay, I'm gonna break this down
one step at a time.
- You just touched your fingers together.
- Not a woman. - Yeah, you're touching a guy.
- But I'm not a woman.
I'm explaining to you I'm not a woman.
I'm a guy and a half, if anything.
So you're XXY?
No.
You're Kyle.
He's a guy and a half, you're XXY.
No.
You are Kyle, XXY.
I'm XXX.
I'm three X's.
Yeah.
I'm three X's like--
And we're here, you have to answer to your crimes.
What crimes did I do?
I didn't know crimes.
You did all of XXX crimes.
Name one crime he did.
I actually don't know.
Yeah, see he doesn't even know.
He stuck, didn't he stick a fork
into his pregnant girlfriend's vagina?
He stuck a fork into an outlet,
which is a crime when you're a baby and he got cancelled for it. I don't know what he
did. I don't, I don't, I don't.
He threatened his girlfriend a bunch and beat her I believe.
Yeah, so did Patrick though.
Don't say that.
Yeah. Patrick and Cameron have both done everything XXXTentacion has done, they have both done
too.
Yeah, I made really awesome music.
yeah yeah what do you mean blended perfectly over ten genres into a
masterpiece of an album no no they both stuck forks in each other because they're
both girlfriends of each other yeah I don't think so you did and you both
zapped each other with your with your men's electricity men are full of
electricity and women are full of water and that's why it doesn't work that's
true it's so fucking hot here dude yeah this is recording in a mirage in the
Mojave Desert. This feels like that episode we did that we like scrapped after we ate a bunch of
chicken honestly. We ate a bunch of chicken honestly. That was a week I
remember that we recorded two in a row we had to scrap the first one because it
was right after we ate a shit ton of KFC.
We ate a shit ton of KFC and we were just sitting there just like...
Oh yeah, we had chicken brain.
In the middle of the summer.
Yeah, we had chicken brain.
We had chicken brain.
That was the chicken brain episode.
It was one of the lost episodes.
There are so many lost episodes of this podcast.
There's a couple lost episodes where it's like we said something sort of out of pocket,
you know, or we ate too much chicken.
(laughing)
- I wish we had just not even recorded another one.
We'd just been like, sorry, new episode.
(laughing)
We actually ate too much chicken before we recorded.
- The thing is, we like don't even say things
out of pocket that often.
So it's mostly like any last episode.
- It's way more the chicken thing.
- Yeah, it is honestly the chicken thing more than anything.
- It's way more like we ate too much chicken
or it was too hot.
- Too hot, it's too hot.
It was a combination of it was too hot
and we ate too much.
One of us didn't sleep enough.
Yeah, we got excited about a website too much and just didn't talk and just looked at the
website instead of talking when we were supposed to be doing the list.
Stuff like that.
Shout out to the kid who sent me that list to @bitbyacarp who I can't find his Twitter
now, but we had to scrap your episode too.
Because the website was too good.
The website was too fun to look at.
We spent too much time just clicking on and laughing to ourselves.
Yeah, so that's the revealed reason that we haven't...
Hopefully he's a patron, because then he'll fucking hear this.
We'll make that the teaser, just me trying to be nice.
That is the reason we unlocked a premium episode,
is because we waited until the last minute to record,
and then we got too distracted by a website about sex and love.
And also chicken. We also had chicken before that too.
I did go out and I went to the grocery store and I did buy a bag of grocery store chicken.
The bag chicken is insane.
It's so gross.
It like sticks together and it's cold.
There's no difference between the skin and the meat.
It's just all just like mashed potatoes.
Oh but it's so good.
Oh my god.
Dude I honestly, honestly considered going out and just buying just a rotisserie chicken
and eating the whole thing last night.
Oh I've done that so many times.
Oh my god.
Gus told me that him and his dad when they went there when they've like gone on tour
Basically if they go on a road trip
They just buy a rotisserie chicken at the beginning of the day and they just eat that for their and like all of their meals
throughout the day
Just a rotisserie chicken with their hands while driving. That's the dream dude. Yeah, that's I wish I wish my dad
Would eat a whole chicken with me. I
Used to me and my dad used to get the fucking market basket
Rotisserie chickens. Yeah, leave it in the fridge and pick at it the bag chicken though
You can get the spicy you can get the spicy chicken, which is just red chicken. Yeah, it's like comically red
And there's it's not spicy at all. Yeah, it's not they it's spicy like
It's just paprika
Exactly. Yeah, it's just paprika red that's I and like it like it's temperature is a little hotter for some reason
The way that they make that is they just they get the chicken really mad before they kill it
it. They just really piss it off. They jump on its head twice but not three times which
would kill it. They jump on it twice right before it turns into coins. They play I Know
an Annoying Song, an Annoying Song, an Annoying Song over and over on the speakers before
they kill it and it turns red and steam comes out of its ears. It's actually pre-cooked
because it steams itself.
It's one of those, it's like a sous vide,
but in like a human.
What?
Or like, I don't know.
It's a sous vide in a human?
(laughing)
God, my brain is liquid right now.
Okay, so you put some steak in a bag
and then you swallow the bag,
and then when you poop it out,
it's safe to eat.
Oh, it comes out hot.
It probably would be kinda cooked.
Yeah, it's warm in there.
'Cause your internal body temperature
is like roughly 100 degrees.
Can your body melt glass?
Isn't a sous vide kinda cook stuff at that level?
- Can your stomach ask it?
Can your stomach ask it?
(laughing)
- I need to get, I'm crowdfunding to get a million PCs.
- Patrick is like a computer.
Like, he has like an operating temperature.
Like if it's too cold or too hot,
it doesn't work anymore.
- And it's 56 degrees.
- Yeah, 56 degrees exactly.
Any colder or hotter, and he sucks.
- No.
- Ugh, bleak.
- I'm thinking, that's probably the first thing
I'm gonna do with the podcast money
get a sous vide machine. Yeah? Yeah. Just I don't want to put my hand in it. I gotta get...
See if it'll cook my hand. Just eight hours, eight hours recycling, circulating water at
120 degrees. It's not even that hot. It's not that hot. It's like a jacuzzi. Yeah. Do
you guys ever wanted to eat yourself? Eat parts of yourself? Yeah, pretty much every
day of my life. You ever think about like cutting off your finger and like cooking it
in a pan and then like putting it in a quesadilla and then eating it. I've never thought about that.
I've thought about that. Have you ever thought about eating Patrick because he'd be the most
delicious of us? I would not. There's so many chemicals in me. No, Patrick's legs.
That's true. No, that's why he'd be so delicious. Have you ever had like GMO raised cows?
Yeah, that's true. If you didn't, you cut possible.
Eating me would be like eating like Burger King. Yeah, Buku King.
if you tried to if you cut Patrick in half his flesh would just be like blue
like bright neon blue like electric blue yeah he's it's sizzling
he's carbonated his meat is carbonated sparkling Patrick oh my god dude i would
love to get a carbonated hamburger just bite into it oh you know when i was
- When I was young I used to call carbonated hamburger,
yeah, Pop Rocks Burger.
(laughing)
- That's more, that's more like, that could happen.
- That's like a food challenge.
- Yeah.
- I wouldn't be surprised if I went to like
some shitty neighborhood, or some shitty like
small town in Massachusetts, and they were like,
yeah, the only thing here is like,
we have a restaurant that has a Pop Rocks Burger.
- Yeah.
That's what we're known for.
- And you go and there's pictures of people like,
like, with the, like famous people there with the owner,
but none of them look happy.
- Yeah.
- They're all just like, oh, fuck.
The famous people are all people's dads from the town.
They're not even famous.
Just community members.
Dan O'Brien Kia.
That's the old thing.
It's the little, it's the kid.
It's the 3D, the little 3D guy.
The 3D render from Dan O'Brien Kia, yeah.
That guy's awesome.
Boston, Boston's the only joke.
Cam, is it you who in LA we went to,
is it you that I went to a diner with that had the like pictures of all the celebrities
on the wall but then one of them was just like some random guy
and he was like eating an omelet and smoking a cigarette inside and it was like
Dan 2003.
He's sandwiched between like Brad Pitt and like
Leonardo DiCaprio and it's just like Dan and then just some ugly guy.
He rocks dude. I have a picture of it somewhere. Do you remember that diner we
went to um what was it called the one that was
was just like, yeah, that one was crazy. It was like this, it was this diner that was
like kind of, it was like part of a hotel but not really. Like it was its own thing
but it was like connected to a hotel. So like everyone in there was just like
people who were staying at the hotel. But like worst hotel ever. Just like a terrible
sunset strip, or sunset boulevard motel. Yeah and it's like the the TVs were all
like doing this crazy, this weird glitch. Like it wasn't even like static, like the
TVs were just like glitching. It was very, it felt like it was the most
purgatorial place I think I've ever been in.
- Yeah, it felt like it was the motel California.
That's what that place felt like.
It felt like we would never leave that place.
We'd be, and also, I don't know why,
we ate there probably five times.
It was like the worst breakfast I've ever had.
- It was so bad.
- It sucked, but we just kept going back.
- No, it was just weird.
- It was like 15 dollars.
- God.
- There was something about it, I don't know.
There was some, that place, it draws you back.
- I just liked that it was called Dreams and it was crazy.
- Yeah.
- It was called, I thought you said it was called Kareem.
I wish dude.
That was easily one of the worst places I've ever eaten probably.
Yeah pretty bad.
Yeah.
But we went.
What was, oh we also went to that fucking, that place that was like part of a college
that was like the, was it like a Korean, like a Korean church or something?
No, yeah no it was part of a church.
Yeah.
It was like, we went to like, there was this restaurant downtown LA.
It was in like Korea town and there was a Korean Baptist church and then upstairs there was
like a cafeteria.
Yeah, but it was like you had to go up all these crazy flights of stairs, you had to
go around the back, like it was so hard to find to get into this place too.
It was a fucking nightmare, but it was pretty good.
Yeah.
Honestly.
It was like a cafeteria style diner.
It rocked.
I miss that shit, just cafeteria style.
Cafeteria.
God, you gotta give me some fucking-
No, no, every single time I'm gonna call you up.
Pat just said to Caleb, "You gotta give me some fuckin'."
Whoa, alright.
Get ready, I think I'm coming up to bosses next week.
Dude, it's like 80 degrees in here.
You gotta get a fan, dude.
Yeah, my thermometer says 80 degrees.
Are you sure that's a thermometer?
Yeah.
It's a mirage.
I don't even know.
He's hallucinating, dude.
Yeah, I'm hallucinating.
He's looking at the clock, and he's also...
also yeah hasn't a piece to think it says 80 he's looking at the grandfather clock
he has and the grandfather clock has big eyes that are following the the tiki
thing what is that called that's called the grandfather's penis yeah cuz it's so
big yeah yeah yeah it's good it's big because he's old it's not cuz it has it
is gravity gravity has played a huge role in a grandfather's penis yeah yeah his
penis was so grandfatherly. That's like a beautiful, that sounds like a line in like
a Jack Kerouac book. Yeah. And he had a very grandfatherly penis. Stop talking. Yeah. I'm
trying to fucking record. Come on man, we're trying to hang out dude. Yeah, that's fucked
up. That's fucked up. Um, so I'm moving. Yeah. I'm moving. I don't understand why you're
You're doing it now, why not wait?
'Cause it's cheap, everything's really cheap right now.
That's true.
And it's gonna go back up.
And I can avoid paying like a security deposit and shit
if we move right now.
You're moving, so are you moving to Boston and then there?
So coming back up to Boston, packing stuff,
and then driving to Queens, baby!
Jamaica, Queens!
Nice, good for you.
I'm moving to Jamaica, Manchester.
(laughing)
Two white boys in Jamaica.
Uh huh.
That's right.
And I gotta tell you something, Mr. Donald Trump,
you better not come to my city.
Oh yeah, dude, Caleb's gonna be outside your fricking tower
every day flipping you off. Yeah, giving you the finger.
You better not come to Jamaica, or you bombaclat,
Donald Trump.
Donald Trump bombaclat, muy bueno.
Spanish Jamaica is where I'm gonna be staying in Queens.
Yeah, it's a very diverse, Jamaican Queens is very diverse.
It's mostly Spanish Spaniards with dreadlocks.
Spaniards like conquistador guys.
Yeah.
Walking around with giant dreadlocks going,
"Bomba, clack, taco bell."
Yeah.
And it's gonna be really, I'm gonna fit right in.
Yeah, man.
I'm pretty excited.
I'm moving to my like 10 minutes outside of my hometown.
That's nice.
So things are going great for me.
That's every young man's dream.
Yeah.
Yeah, to move back to the man's chair.
With 10 minutes outside.
Well, yeah, but 10 minutes outside,
I mean, that's the beach.
Yeah, that's a big distance.
Yeah.
That's a long, that would take you,
you know how long that would take you to walk?
I mean, like a literal border.
Do you know how long a letter would take
to go from your house to your parents' house?
Probably a couple days.
Yeah.
Yeah, so that's a day's worth of travel
between you and your parents' house.
And that's with no breaks.
If I mail myself.
And that's if the mailman doesn't take a break
the middle to drink a Gatorade. Yeah, which you know he does. If I see a mailman
taking a break, I run up to him and I hit him on the back of the head and I start
kicking him. I run up to him and I just give him more mail. I say, "Well, you want to take a break?"
You have to deliver all this now. You want more mail?
I point to my garage, which is just stacks, piles of just letters to Santa Claus.
Santa Claus. He just has to process and throw away. Yeah. Damn. That is the mailman's
dilemma. Yeah. He looks at, he gets the, he gets the letter, he looks at it, he says,
"Do I throw this away or do I deliver this to the North Pole?" It's one of the
hardest decisions a mailman ever has to make. Yeah. Yeah. I fucking, I like, when I
was going to community college, I like, when I was in Laconia and I lived like a
a couple minutes away from my parents.
Aconia.
Yeah.
It's like Winnipesaukee.
That's where Dracula lives.
Draconia.
That's, I think that's an actual other city, but, uh, I fucking, I
looked up how much it would cost to install a motor onto my, onto my
Walmart bike that I bought so I could get around up there and I like for,
for like two weeks, I was like, yeah, I'm going to buy a motor
for this thing.
And then I'm going to drive home every weekend with it.
It's called a souped up.
It's called a souped up a Mongoose.
I found out, I found out it was a woman's bike halfway through.
Yeah.
Belong to you, man.
Cause men's bikes have on the seats.
They have a little hole where you can put your, you can hold your
balls in your penis.
Yeah.
It's a cradle.
And you can fuck it too if you, if it's a really long bike ride.
Yeah.
Exactly.
I deeply considered getting a motor for it and now that I'm moving back, I think I'm
going to do it.
You just need to learn how to drive, dude.
Learn how to, I'll teach you.
Yeah, but it would be funnier to have a motorized bicycle.
You would get wet.
Somebody imagine this.
What if you get into a chase scene.
My bike has a motor.
They can't go into the alleyways.
What if somebody just cause 2 style shoots at your gas tank and your bike explodes?
I will fly up and do a backflip.
I know how to convince you.
They're not going to let you through any drive-thrus on a bike.
Even if it has a motor.
Yeah they will.
I can chain up my bike and go inside. Nice try.
No you can't chain up.
Not in coronavirus.
No, they're just doing, they're canceling restaurants forever.
It's only drive-thrus.
They're using all of the chains.
I'm going to, I'm moving back to New Hampshire.
I'm moving back to Liberty, Free State Project,
New Hampshire.
No.
They're gonna open up every restaurant.
When was the last time you were in New Hampshire, dude?
It's pussified.
Yeah, they changed everything there.
Now they love rules.
They put lines in the middle of the road
so you can tell which lane you're in.
Yeah.
Did they really?
Yeah, might as well be California now, bro.
They raised the age of consent to 11.
People are gonna be fuckin' eatin' avocados and shit now.
Yeah, people are gonna have auto toast.
(laughing)
People are gonna be talkin' auto-tune out there.
People are, I'm gonna have to,
I'm gonna go into every fuckin' restaurant
and some guy's gonna be like,
well, it's a two burger king.
Yeah.
People are using credit and debit cards.
It's gonna be automatic movies and automatic toast.
What next, 3D movies?
Come on.
No.
Yeah.
Never.
This is New Hampshire.
Yeah, New Hampshire still has 1D movies.
Yeah.
We're still playing the One Direction movie at the drive-thru.
A 1D movie.
Because they are normally about nine months behind on every single release.
A 1D movie is when you go to the movie theater and you just go up to the guy at the popcorn
counter and you just say, "Hey, can you tell me what the movie's about really quick?"
And he gives you a two-sentence summary.
That's a 1D movie.
And then you don't have to pay.
And then you have to guess.
You don't have to pay if you can guess which movie he's talking about.
You've already told me everything. I would like a refund.
And then that's how you get unlimited popcorn. You keep asking what the movie is
and then you get a refund and you buy another thing of popcorn.
Then you ask what the movie is. And then you have points because in...
because you can actually get points at the movie theater now.
Because everything there is made up and the points don't matter.
That's right. Yeah, it's sort of a...
The points are kind of like...
But also sometimes they do matter and it's like points, you know, like that.
The points don't matter.
And then whoever, well, if you win the most points, you get to do the
hoedown at the end of the movie theater.
Yeah.
You get to do the Irish drinking song at the end to everybody.
But only if you have a black friend who's actually like the,
he's really good at singing.
If he's there, then you can, you're allowed to do it no matter what.
Well, you get to judge the hoedown.
The Irish drinking.
Oh, you get to judge.
Yeah.
That's why they, that's why Drew would sing it sometimes.
Because sometimes he didn't win.
Why, are game show hosts, is it like a casino
where the host is like the house?
Yeah.
And like he is trying--
That's how I've always looked at it.
He's trying to win the game also.
Yeah.
Well, that's the thing, there's also like Family Feud,
in order to get like the full amount of money
on family feed you have to get
every question right
even the uh... and you have to get everything right in like
the uh... the survey questions
so really people go on family feud and just walk home with like fifty bucks
it's pretty good to me man
fifty bucks fifty bucks hey fifty bucks richard new or yes i get to hang out with
my family i get to make fun of another family i get to hug and kiss steve harvey
after the show
and i got fifty bucks
- It sounds like a pretty good deal to me.
- Yeah, I'm thinking it fucking rocks.
- Yeah, I'm thinking I'm going on family feud.
- But that's split between your family though.
- Huh?
- No.
- That's split between you and your family.
- No, my family doesn't know about money,
so I just pretend that money doesn't exist
and then I just take it away from them.
- I go on family feud and I play every member
of my family like the clumps.
(laughing)
I'm just running around back and forth.
- Hold on, Steve, hold on.
I am not in my father yet.
- Caleb!
(laughing)
Yeah, and then I play like my grandma being like completely mortified that someone had a sex answer.
Where it's like, "What do you put in your asshole?"
"Um, a penis!"
"AHHHHH!"
"You said a penis!"
[laughter]
And then I have to switch to my dad.
And then I'm like, "Mama!"
"Hell yeah!"
"Mama!"
Pretty awesome.
You should like on Wheel of Fortune,
you should have to battle Pat Sajak for supremacy.
He's battling for supremacy.
Yeah.
If people get close enough to the answer
and he doesn't like them,
he'll switch the answer to something else
with the same number of letters.
Well, that's 'cause he's a genius.
He actually comes up with everything in real time.
Yeah, sometimes though he messes up
and they'll be like too far along
and he turns it into complete gibberish.
And yeah, and they'll say,
"I'd like to solve the puzzle."
it's on what's up doc and i go actually know it's worth a little bit
it's been a little bit
sorry guys you got it wrong
yeah they should do it is you know we look for to make
a hangman and if you lose pat c jack dies he hangs himself
is it didn't quit
is the only way he quit his aid date they uh... they propose that idea to him
yes i think that he was like you made conservative voices
Yeah, Pat's, is Pat Sajak a conservative?
Pat Sajak is like a dumb, he was like a tea party guy,
I think, him and Chuck Woolery.
So are you.
No, I'm not.
But you're still out on this show.
No.
Yeah.
Please don't say that during this time.
He is, he's a tea party guy.
He's got a big red hat on, he actually does right now.
Yeah.
He's a big red hat on.
I got a new hat, so.
Why aren't you wearing it?
It's not here yet.
Yeah, right.
And you didn't get it, you ordered one.
Yeah, I ordered one.
a new hat but it's not you don't have it you didn't get a new hat yet I got it
and it's in the mail no no I stole it out of the mail yeah and he mailed it to me
actually and I'm a little bit yeah and we're playing monkey in the middle right
now I'm looking at the mail the mail I can't wait till it gets here and it
doesn't fit me we're playing monkey and the mailman yeah game for ps2 that I got
you play as a monkey and you have to beat the shit out of the mailman and
then steal his clothes and then work his job and then you get out of his job and
you go home and you fuck his wife and she doesn't even notice that you're a monkey.
It's like a Farside cartoon.
Exactly.
Yeah.
That's kind of the joke of every one of those cartoons is like, yeah, there's actually an
animal who's pretending to be a guy right now.
But it gets me every- I think they're so funny.
Farside's so good.
It's so good, dude.
A bug with a wife?
Oh my god, dude.
Are you kidding, dude?
A monkey reading a book?
What is this?
That just ain't right.
God man, God save you.
Yeah, whenever I get a book of Far Side comics I flip through whenever I see an animal with
the speech bubble I just white it all out because animals shouldn't be able to talk.
It's not a very funny comic to me.
I write in this all the sounds, all the cows are just saying moo.
Wasn't there like a documentary about, oh no wait, I'm thinking documentary now.
Well that's probably based on a real documentary.
It was a documentary about a guy trying to find the guy who writes the Farside comics.
Oh, Gary Larson?
Yeah, I mean he's a guy.
He's trying to find Gary Larson?
He's trying to find him?
Yeah, that was a Documentary Now episode.
I thought it was a real one.
Is it like an exit to the gift shop thing?
I don't know.
Oh, okay.
Okay, cool then.
I don't have the brain capacity to remember past that.
You don't have the brain capacity to fucking spell, uh, capacity right now, Patrick.
C-A-P-A-C-I-A-T-Y.
Nope.
I bet you can't spell "I-cup", dude.
I-P-C-U.
Aw, crap, I can't spell for shit right now.
Dude, you're so stupid.
Nah, he's so stupid. His brain is being melted.
And it's just tough because his brain is made out of hollow chocolate like an Easter Bunny.
Yeah.
Yeah, and you know that because you like to eat poop like an Easter Bunny.
I don't like to eat poop like an Easter Bunny.
First of all, the Easter Bunny likes to eat candy.
The Easter Bunny likes to eat candy.
He doesn't eat poop.
Second of all, I am not the Easter Bunny.
You're eating one of Cameron's dad's Easter Bunnies.
Nah.
Yeah, I am.
That one, I actually am.
You're not eating one of those.
He would never give you one of those.
He already did.
No.
He gave me one.
He gave me one too.
I'm pretty much his best friend and we like to play video games.
Specifically we like to play foosball in your garage when you're not around.
That's not- And he calls me dad.
I don't have a garage with foosball.
He says, "Can I call you dad?"
And I say, "Yeah, as long as you're okay with it."
Can I call you Cameron's dad?
Yeah.
He says, "Can I call you Cameron's dad?"
And I'm like, "Yeah."
He's like, "You're such a pervert!
You're such a pervert, Cameron's dad!
Fuck you!
Fuck you!"
Yeah.
Ugh.
He really lets me have it.
Yeah.
"Kermit's dad, you ruined your marriage for no reason!
What's wrong with you?!"
It's awesome.
[laughs]
That's cool, dude.
Yeah.
And that's your dad.
That's not my dad, though.
And then I call my dad, and then my dad comes, and he's driving a really cool car.
Maybe Herbie the... the lovebug.
[laughs]
When he shows up...
Everyone in school thinks you're the coolest kid 'cause you got dropped off by Herbie.
(laughing)
- Who's driving that car?
Oh no, no, the car was driving me, okay?
- That's Herbie.
- He lives in my garage and I feed him gas.
(laughing)
- That's basically the whole movie, isn't it?
- Yeah, dude, except I'm the Lindsay Lohan character.
- What was it, Herbie fully loaded?
- Herbie, yeah.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- 'Cause he was full of gas.
- That, there's too many movies like that now.
Like, there's too, they've made too many of the Herbie movies.
Yeah, they need to shut it down.
Herbie goes bananas.
Yeah, Herbie goes to the moon.
Herbie fucks my goddamn wife.
Herbie goes to prison, that would be a good one.
That would be pretty good.
Just a car and prison.
(laughing)
They keep making new license plates for him.
He's in a women's prison.
They're like, "He had a hole on his back.
We put him in the women's prison."
His name's short for Herbina.
They have to take off all the bars to put him in the cell and then put the bars back.
He just barely fits.
He just everyone in the prison ties because it was exhaust fumes.
He's doing prison push-ups by just lowering and raising his suspension.
He gets hydraulics.
He's doing push-ups that way.
going up and down. Yeah, Herbie goes to prison. Pretty much one of the best movies ever. Yeah.
Herbie's family vacation. Kind of a raunchy Herbie movie. Yeah. Herbie the naked mile.
That'd be pretty good. I can be Herbie all by myself. That's another one. Yeah. Which
Halloween. Yeah. Herber Shop. Herber Shop. Chop Shop. That's what it'd be called. Yeah.
Chop Shop with Herbie. Chop Shop with Herbie. Chop Shop with Herbie. No way, my dog is looking
at the door. He wants to get in on this Herbie stuff. Yeah. You can't have any of the money
we make from this dog he's got all the Herbie jokes he's got Herbie fever yeah
don't even joke about Herbie fever yeah that's like it's like dengue you know
from the same place yeah Herbie fever it's like dengue but you get it in
Wisconsin mm-hmm you get Herbie take place knows here we take place all over
the world isn't he like an old Volkswagen like a Nazi like a Nazi era
Volkswagen. Herbie was a Nazi project. Yeah, they brought him over in an Operation Paperclip.
Yeah, he was like, he was Wernher von Braun. Yeah. He was his car. Yeah, they imported his
consciousness. Yeah, as soon as there was a little heat on him, they just threw him in a car. Yeah.
And now he fucks Lindsay Lohan, I guess. We are going to give you big eyes. And she will drive
you are at your partner around do the cars from cars have a brain they do it's
the engine no the engines the heart okay then the end the brain the brain the
brain would be the top of the car I would say there's and there's this movie I
said there's like a some production company that makes like like Southern
evangelical Christian movies they like made all the left-behind movies but they
They also made this movie called Flywheel, which was about...
It's about fly leaf.
My parents made me watch it when I was a kid and it's basically about a guy whose car gets
haunted by God.
And it's like God is using the car to speak to him about his...
Because all those movies, it's just like a white guy whose marriage is failing because
he watches too much TV.
And then like, and then it's like, oh, he has to find God so he knows to like not ignore
his wife.
Yeah.
And so like he keeps telling his wife like, "I gotta go work on the car."
And then he walks out and the car just keeps like spraying oil simultaneously like on his
face and then also on like an open page of the Bible and then he picks it up and the
Bible verse is like, "Stop watching TV."
John 3, 16.
Yeah, stop.
work on the car and hang out with your wife.
(laughing)
It's awesome, dude.
I wanna make a movie like that,
but about a different religion.
About freaking Satan.
Yeah, about the devil.
Yeah, about the flying spaghetti monster.
It's kinda what Herbie is.
Herbie kind of is a possessed demon car.
Yeah, he's an Anunnaki.
Yeah, the Anunnaki of infected cars.
Yeah.
He's kinda, now it's crazy that Herbie,
You know how like, you watch movies like Idiocracy
and you're like, whoa, that's like becoming real, you know?
But then also--
Yeah, Herbie's becoming real too.
You watch movies like Herbie, yeah,
with the Tesla self-driving vehicle, you know?
Did you see his fucking rocket exploded?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm the one who did it.
Yeah, I did it too, actually.
Yeah, actually, I put a thumbtack under the rocket seat.
(laughing)
I popped it.
It was pretty awesome.
Yeah.
Was there like guys on that?
I don't think so.
I think it was just...
They definitely should be putting guys on it.
Because I feel like every single time he tries to launch a rocket, it explodes.
Well, they...
No, it...
They did a test launch of it and it worked.
And then it was just like sitting in the rocket chair.
I don't know, whatever they put it in.
Whenever it's not flying...
It's a chair.
Yeah, it's a chair that they put it in.
And then it just blew up and they don't...
When I read the article about it, they didn't know why it happened.
Yeah, but I think it was...
Got the freaking car- you know who did it? Carole Baskin.
Yeah, I'm thinking it's the freaking Tiger King TV show that got this happening.
Carole Baskin did it.
She married the rocket and then killed it.
She covered it in sardine oil.
Yeah, and she had a tiger- she had a tiger plant C4 at the base of it.
Yeah.
And then exploded it.
Wait guys, I think this just gave me a new idea for a Twitter display name.
Get it.
Joe Exotic on Musk.
Elogic.
- Carol.
- Carolian.
- Carol Explosion.
- Carolian Musk.
- Kanye Exotic.
(laughing)
- Joker Exotic.
Can you imagine?
- Joker.
- Joker Fight Exotic.
- Joker Donald Trump.
- Hmm.
- Oh my God, that's terrifying.
- I saw something.
I saw a post that made me laugh so hard.
There's somebody like all indignant about just like people.
It's so funny when people get mad about when people,
other people like don't post something.
And somebody was posting about like the Minneapolis stuff
and they were like, yeah,
so where are all the white male Joker fans at now?
(laughing)
And I was like, what a crazy,
what a crazy fucking group to be like, yeah,
where are the white male Joker fans?
- Yeah, hey, you guys remember those people we said
we're gonna do terrorism everywhere
and kill a bunch of people when this movie open?
Why aren't they on our side right now?
- Why aren't they?
- Why aren't all the school shooters helping us?
(laughing)
What's up with that?
Yeah, it's just--
- That's not a bad idea.
We can put all the cops in school.
(laughing)
Yeah, put all the cops in school
and then let loose a white male Joker fan.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, just a Craigslist ad.
Looking for white male Joker fan who hates school.
school and police. Yeah, that's how they put out the searches for like crisis actors.
For the shooter, like for Steven Paddock, they found him by just saying, they posted
on Craigslist, looking for a guy who wants to see the Joker movie. And they, just looking
for... They hit him with a bunch of strobe lights and he's like, I need to go to Vegas.
They played the Joker movie backwards. Yeah, that's what it does to you if you play it backwards.
yeah they played him in one of those exclusive screener copies before it was
even made but they played an extra fucked up version where it's the they digitally
replaced Joaquin Phoenix with Heath Ledger Joker so it's even more like
fucked up and crazy yeah you know cuz he was on pills he was actually on pills
during the time of that movie yeah yeah he actually used to you know it's crazy
he got so into the character that he actually played a joke on his friend
it's true yeah yeah yeah this is breaking Jared Leto got so into character that he
actually went and performed at a birthday party in clown makeup oh my god he's a
psycho yeah what a fucking fuck yeah him and Harley Quinn seriously deserve each
other yeah yeah imagine the NDA Jared Leto had to get
harley-quinn assigned to have sex with him that's right yeah he's pulled out a
roll he got so into being Superman that he literally started wearing glasses at
work pretty fucked up Superman yeah yeah it's so crazy when movies crossover
into reality like I just love when people prepare for roles yeah this actor
lost 400 pounds and he did and now he's dead yeah now he doesn't exist anymore
yeah yeah that's why you lost 400 pounds for a role when he originally weighed 200
pounds and now he's some sort of vacuum in space-time. Yeah he's kind of like an
inside out guy. Yeah I smell an Oscar. Yeah Daniel Day-Lewis congratulations you won. Daniel
Day-Lewis turned himself into a baby with a baby Ray preparing for his role as
baby New Year in the Avengers 50. It's pretty awesome. It's so funny how like Daniel
Day Lewis, like he literally just didn't shower to play a
character in the Crucible.
He's still, you can still shower for it.
You just come up with excuses.
Yeah.
You know, like, yeah, that's all method acting is, is excuses for bad behavior.
Eddie Murphy, he was, he was preparing for a role when he got caught with a
prostitute in LA, he was preparing for a role as the coolest guy ever.
Yeah.
And John Travolta was actually, he was preparing for a role.
He was preparing for Gotti when he went to all those massage parlors.
Yeah.
Harvey Weinstein was preparing for his debut role as Harvey Weinstein.
In the documentary, the one where he did all that shit.
Yeah.
That's.
Woody Allen was preparing for a role as Genghis Khan when he took his Asian child bride.
Let's prepare for some roles, man.
Yeah, yeah
I'm preparing for my role as a
Fucking guy I'm preparing for my role as Patrick, and I'm gonna eat how many coins?
Yeah, I'm just guessing. I don't really know
We've talked about my coin
We've talked about we've talked about the black coin so many times at this point. Yeah
Something about coins. I don't know
Coins is so money like - yeah
Something about coins, just money.
It's just so shiny.
Man, there's just something about coins.
There's straight paper to me.
Something about those things, dude.
Yeah, that's paper.
This is how it got.
You know how a girl puts cucumbers in her eyes
to fucking relax?
Guys put silver--
I put dollar bills in my wallet.
This is what guys put.
Couple of beer bottle ying-ling Coors Light caps.
My man buying ying-ling.
Yeah.
He's buying ying-ling 'cause he looked at it
and he thought he was buying a youngling.
Yeah.
I'll bring home with him.
Nah.
You wanted a youngling.
You wanted to be a Jedi Master.
Nah.
Yeah, I killed twelve younglings.
I crushed twelve younglings last night.
But you had the Yingling.
Yeah, you crushed twelve younglings.
Yeah, you crushed twelve younglings, dude.
I was drinking.
You were drinking out of a youngling?
No, I was drinking out of a Yingling.
Caleb was drinking a youngling's juice.
I wasn't. There's no juice in a kid.
You get juice when you turn thirteen.
But, duh.
I'm Patrick.
I think you get juice before you turn 13.
You idiot.
You get juice all the time as a kid.
You stop getting juice and get older.
Maybe you did and that was the problem.
Why?
Because I'm diabetic now?
Because he's diabetic now.
I'm not actually diabetic.
Because of all the juice.
He is.
Patrick is diabetic, but the kind of diabetic who like didn't even eat, wasn't even allowed
to eat candy.
He just like turned 21 and ate too many apples when he lived by himself.
And now he has diabetes.
You know, the most embarrassing kind of diabetic.
- I got diabetes from Cliff Bars.
- Yeah, whoops.
(laughing)
Yeah, I was drinking, I drank Insurer
until I fucking got diabetes and lost my foot.
- Yeah.
- Tom, I went to the TB12 store,
took too many of them damn supplements.
- Yeah.
- I got supplemental diabetes.
- I was scared that I was gonna get diabetes as a kid.
- Yeah, I wasn't.
- I thought, 'cause my mom told me I could get diabetes
if I put too much jelly on my sandwiches.
(laughing)
- So I was pretty terrified.
I didn't even realize,
I thought it was just if you do something wrong,
you get diabetes.
(laughing)
- It's a punishment.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, it's your body's punishment
for doing something it doesn't like.
- Yeah, too much jelly.
Did you guys have health nut moms?
- My mom tried to get us into health food and shit,
And then I was like, okay, well, I'm just not gonna eat it.
- Yeah, you went on a hunger strike.
- She tried to get me to eat like sun butter or something.
I don't remember what it was.
- She was trying to--
- My mom tricked me once.
She bought this blueberry pomegranate V8 juice
and then she told me that there were so many
antioxidants in it that if I drank more than one glass a day
I would die.
(laughing)
'Cause she didn't want me drinking her juice 'cause it was good.
That rocks.
When I, uh, my mom was like super into, I mean we just only had like whole wheat bread and
like natural peanut butter and shit.
And I remember this kid, Dennis, I took, he, I, I like did some favor for him and I was
like, uh, yeah, you just have to- Oh yeah, we know what kind of favor you did for him.
Nah, yeah, you know, it was probably like I saved his life from like a burning building
or something.
Yeah, you saved his life, you had a buildup of cum inside of his dick and you had to suck
it out like a, like a snake bit him out of a bite.
Even if I had done that, which I didn't, if it had saved his life, it would have been worth
it.
You got married to him after.
I didn't get married, but basically I did a favor for him.
It was probably like fucking his girlfriend or something because he couldn't get his dick
hard.
We were 10, but I was like, yeah, just we'll trade lunches in exchange for this.
And he was like, yeah, sure.
And then lunchtime comes around and he has a normal peanut butter and jelly, like Wonder
bread, Jif peanut butter, red raspberry jam, and I have like all organic like dog shit crunchy
oatmeal bread with like the hard oily, you know the peanut butter that's like half of
it is oil?
Yeah.
You have to mix it.
I have that peanut butter and I was like, "All right, so let's trade."
And he was like, "Oh, I'm actually, I'm allergic to organic stuff."
And I was like, "No, you're not.
It's bullshit."
And then he got the teacher over and he was like,
yeah, he's like trying to throw this organic thing in my face
but I'm actually allergic to organic things.
And she was like, wow, I had no idea.
I'm gonna write that in your file.
It was awesome, dude.
That was back when nobody knew what organic meant.
Yeah. Yeah.
I still don't really know.
I think it just means small.
It just means small and high priced.
Yeah, like me.
It means they put sand in it to give it texture.
That's true.
I wish. Sodium chloride or whatever.
Yeah, sand is sodium chloride.
Sodium dioxide?
That shit is awesome.
What tablets?
The tablets that people are eating to like...
iPads?
Yeah, yeah.
Hamburger iPad. That's what I meant.
What are you talking about? What tablets?
People are eating like sodium something tablets.
Like basically chlorine to like try and kill COVID in their bodies.
Oh, hydroxychloride or whatever.
I mean, hydroxy cut.
It could work.
People are taking hydroxy cut.
Yeah.
My dad took hydroxy cut and I think he stopped taking it because his penis, it ruined his
penis.
It ruined, how does it ruin your penis?
I have no idea.
It splits in half like a hot dog when you don't cut the line.
It's like when you microwave a hot dog and it shrivels.
It shrivels and it splits in half and shit.
Well I just said it.
(burps)
Oh man.
Shut up dude.
That sounds good.
Whoops.
That does not sound good.
I just ate some, I will say before I did this,
I feel good but I did eat a piece of fried chicken.
(groans)
So this may never see the light of day.
There's gotta be a rule, no chicken the whole day.
I got Subway today, I don't know if that counts.
You had what?
I got Subway.
Did it have chicken?
rotisserie chicken at Subway? I did put a whole rotisserie chicken between two
loaves of bread. Two loaves. You brought your own rotisserie chicken? And I brought my own loaves of bread. And I sat down in that Subway and I said "reopen the state!"
Has anything, like a restaurant, restaurants have reopened here. It's crazy.
People walking around fucking and sucking in public in a restaurant.
People have been walking around here just a lot in general.
Yeah, no, it's like anyone who's like never been jogging before is jogging now.
Yeah.
Finally I have a good use for my 100% realistic replica Darth Vader outfit, including mask.
I just walk around completely protected and scaring people who are infected.
Yeah.
You can use your lightsaber and use that as a six feet marker.
marker that's right don't you don't you fucking get near me monster yeah
get out of here get out of here yeah sir you're not doing the Darth Vader voice
I'm sorry I was doing I was doing Chad Vader yeah I was doing epic rap battles
of history Darth Vader there's actually multiple Darth Vader's have you seen the
Joker movies it's like that. There's four of them. There's 16 Darth Vader's that you need to know about.
I'm preparing for a role as the greatest dad of all time. Oh did I show you
speaking of like Batman and stuff and like preparing for people asking for
roles did you guys see that thing I sent you? Oh yeah the guy who wanted to be the
Riddler. I did see that. It was awesome. He was like call me the Riddler. It was just a guy dressed up as the Riddler and he was like doing like
hashtag his name for the Riddler like at Zack Snyder he was an extra in a Zack
Snyder movie that's coming out on Netflix so he thinks he like he's like
oh I know I'm off dude yeah pick to me what what the Riddler you'd be Bane dude
yeah I'm gonna be Bane Patrick will be Clayface I would not be Clayfab you play
body I would be calendar man no no cuz I'm always now you'd be cat woman you'd
You'd be Batman animated series Lex Luthor.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah.
Or no, not Lex Luthor.
No, what's the name of the fat guy?
You don't even know.
(laughing)
No, if it's Lex Luthor.
What's his name?
No, the bald guy.
The pain man.
You'd be Kingpin, dude.
Kingpin is Marvel, you fucking idiot.
Okay, well you'd be him.
I'd be Daredevil 2003.
You'd be in Marvel and me and Cameron wouldn't even,
you wouldn't even exist in the same world as you.
Yeah.
'Cause I'm too cool.
- I would be the Joker in the sequel to Joaquin Phoenix Joker
where they would replace Joaquin Phoenix with me
and I would get the face paint,
but I would also get technological weapons to use
that I could use in a power exo suit
that would actually grow to immense size.
If I use the code phrase, I could grow up to supersize
so I could fight any giant monsters
that might attack the city.
'Cause I'm actually a good guy in the sequel.
- So you're Arkham Asylum Joker.
- No, I'm in Joker 2.
I'm in Joker 2, no, no.
- Cameron would be Poison Ivy
and he'd have two little leaves covering his nipples
and no you know you know who it not the rest of his vagina you would be boys and
guy please because you like boys and guys okay so you shut the fuck up I'll be
joking - giant Joker I stomped down the city
okay guys that's what you would be all right and your power would be to send
out vines and you should be dead no you should be dead you should be dead yeah
I'm gonna make sure you're dead. I'm gonna grow to a giant size and step on you. You're gonna jack off to it
I don't even care. I'm in the Marvel Universe. I don't even have to deal with this. Yeah, dude
You're getting you're getting dicked down by Thanos. No, but it's like getting down by Santa
It's like it's like it's like Captain Marvel how there's one in DC and Marvel Universes and that's boys and guys
Please and it's me and Patrick just in separate universes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, it is and you're in you're in there and you're you're boys and guys pleasing
I would be like spider-man but like spider-man in the new spider-man
Now you'd be you'd be
You'd have
You know how in all the like gritty reboot like superhero movies
There's like a scene where they like finally like say the superhero name for the first time like that's like the name drop
Like you in Caleb's we are you watchmen? Yeah? Well, it's just like yeah like in Man of Steel like it's not until the end
and they go like, "They're calling him Superman."
Just like shit like that.
But, and you guys--
- They're calling him the guy.
- Yeah, you guys, in you guys' movies--
- The famous guy.
- Be the moment where you'd finally,
you know your parents got killed by women,
so you turn gay, and then you say,
"Boys and guys, please!"
And that would be the end, and then it has the title card.
- If you were a superhero, you would be,
you'd probably be Harley Quinn.
- No, she's not a superhero.
She's a villain. She is to you.
No. She's a villain to boys but a hero to women.
[laughs]
No. No.
You'd be a bird of prey.
No.
You'd be a flightless bird of prey.
You'd be a turd in bed.
You'd be a chicken or a turkey.
I'd be the penguin. I know you guys are gonna say that.
You'd be like an emu with really short legs.
Yeah.
Just like a big ball.
Cameron would be...
Who's the...
You'd be Mr.
What the fuck?
You'd be the stretch guy.
guy mr. fantastic yeah I'm fantastic mr. mr. man's ass dick no yeah and you can
only stress your asshole big to accept a penis no yeah your whole thing is you
just do poppers that's your whole power no fucking son no okay if I had that
power I wouldn't use it for that I would use it to make mondo shits in the toilet
and fill it up and clog it.
- Oh my god.
- I would use it to just have more pocket space.
- I always thought it'd be cool,
it'd be cool to be able to flatten your shit out
and just dump it all out at once like a trash chute.
- Yeah, I was thinking--
- It just falls like a pancake.
- Like a month or two ago,
like if you had enough control over your asshole
that you could like contract it fast enough
that you could like chop things into coins.
Like you could poop and like--
- Whoa.
- Oh, you could make poop coins?
- Chop it, poop coins, yeah.
Or if somebody tried to--
- Or you could be like an artist.
- Fuck your ass, you could--
What?
(laughing)
You could be an artist and you could make sculptures.
Out of poop?
A 3D printer.
You could, my ass is a 3D printer.
Yeah, with just a bit of poop though.
Technically, if you think about it,
a regular printer's a 3D printer too.
I don't think so.
Yeah, I don't think so, pal.
Can you, what is the limit of like things
you can make a gun out of,
if a 3D printer can make one out of plastic?
What?
Probably make one out of candy.
You could probably make a candy gun.
Yeah, you probably could make a sugar gun.
You could, I mean, it's like those videos,
the knife videos.
I'm sure if you got the right Asian guy to do it,
you could probably make anything into a gun.
Yeah, I would do a bang up job.
MacGyver is the Asian guy I'm referring to.
Can make anything into a gun.
I wanna be, I just wanna buy one of those knives
off that guy.
Yeah.
But I want it to be like sharpest pussy knife.
(laughing)
And it's made out of a pussy.
Yeah.
- Yeah, out of yours.
- Sharpest, sharpest boobs knife.
- Yeah, out of your pussy.
- Sharpest boobs.
- Sharpest boobs, world's sharpest boobs.
It's just him sanding his mom's tits for hours
to big pointy things and then he kills himself on it.
- Yeah.
- He commits seppuku with his mother's breast.
- That's every Japanese man's dream.
to commit seppuku with your mother's breast.
Yeah, that's what Japanese Freud said.
(laughing)
Fuck.
It's getting hot in here too.
It's been, there's like a tropical storm here now.
Yeah.
It's getting rainy outside.
Oh, it's a tropical storm.
It's getting nice in here.
Guys, I think this is it.
I think this is 2012 is coming to life.
Honestly, it does kind of feel like--
Yeah, and I'm John Cusack
you two are both Joan Cusack. I'm actually the earth. She's not in that. Yeah she is.
She's not in that. Yeah she plays the hot, she plays the hot principal who's kind of a
mean bitch. I know. She plays the stunt double scenes for John Cusack
where he's grabbing his own tits. Joan Cusack is John Cusack's stunt double. That's why his parents had her.
you need to you need two kids one an acting man to a girl to take the yeah
we're doing this scene where we were John has to get the shit beat out of him but
yeah this is Tom Cruise's sister Tom cruises she does she does all his cool
jumping out of plane stuff yeah yeah he has he doesn't like the prestige he has
like a million sisters and they die every time there's no parachute and any of
those stunts I wish I had a million sisters million cousins whoa
please blew my mind spring into the into the villains year how about this make it
happen million cousins yeah get me a million cousins right now I know
500,000 cousins and 500,000 I need tanks
automatic weapons grenades
Hello, I'm three dozen man if you can't deliver to me 1 million cousins by the end of the day I
Will then I'll find them myself
Cry
Then I will be very lonely my birthday will not be fun. This will be the worst
birthday I'll make sure of it I'll get you those cousins I can't ruin your
birthday yeah it doesn't matter it doesn't matter if you're a villain
everyone deserves one good birthday I need you to have a good birthday you
You could have the birthday I never was able to have.
I need to see my cousins, it's been too long.
I got you some tech decks.
A million cousins and two million tech decks, so we have something to do.
I got you the Ryan Sheckler ramp.
It has photos of all of his sponsors on them.
I got you a Wii.
A brand new Wii.
So you can play with your cousins.
It only has Wii Sports on it right now, but the bowling game's pretty good.
It only has Wii Sports, but it's one of the later ones that has Wii Motion Plus built
into the Wiimote.
Actually, wait, I think I have Raving Rabbids around here somewhere.
Yeah, here it is.
Oh, it's a bit scratched up.
Do you have any Windex and a microfiber cloth?
We can buff that out.
I'm gonna try the toothpaste trick.
I have banjo tooie but you need to blow on the cartridge.
I think there's some dust in the cartridge.
How are your cousins doing?
You'll have to take turns.
Each of you can play for one second.
I've only brought enough controllers for two cousins.
I brought an xbox but we can play more if you have another one.
We can do system link.
*laughter*
We can do system link, hang him high.
Or blood gulch on Halo 1.
*laughter*
Yeah. Stop yelling at me dog!
Get the fuck out of here. I don't have any bones.
I hate when my dog...
I don't have no bones!
My dog asks for bones.
Yeah, my dog's always coming up to me and asking for bones.
Yeah, in English.
Yeah, I say no can do.
Can I have some bones? And then they say fuck you mom.
'cause they think you're a mom.
- Yeah.
- Dogs think you're mom.
- Gods, dogs, dogs think that Cameron's their god mom.
- Yeah.
Do you guys have god parents?
- I do.
- Yeah, I do.
- You have fairy god parents.
- No.
- My uncle DD and my uncle Jack.
- Timmy Turner, bitch.
- If I had fairy god parents, that'd be pretty cool
and it wouldn't be something to insult me about
but I don't have them, so.
- Yeah, I would wish for--
- I do.
- I would wish for--
- I have fairy god parents
and they don't grant any of my wishes.
I would wish for unlimited wishes.
Yeah.
I would wish for unlimited fairy godparents.
I would wish that my parents would die so they'd be my real parents.
Be my legal parents.
Yeah, if you had fairy godparents and then your parents, real parents died, couldn't
you just wish them back to life?
Wouldn't that suck if like-
Wouldn't that be a da rules violation?
What if the fairy godparents fell into the hands of like Adam Lanza?
(laughing)
Wouldn't that be catastrophic, dude?
That'd be pretty bad.
Yeah, they just hop out and they're like,
"So what do you wanna do?"
(laughing)
And he's like, "First I need some hair dye."
Yeah.
Yeah, does the kid have to go through screening
to figure out--
Yeah, no, yeah, 'cause if every--
Psychological.
Before he gets fairy godparents.
(laughing)
Yeah.
if you have a floating part of your hat that's not attached to your head, you're fine.
But...
Yeah, if you're a bad kid, they just give you two Cosmos.
Yeah.
You save the Wandas for the really good kids.
Sometimes they mess up. Like Steven Paddock, people say, "How did he
shoot 52 consecutive clips from an AR without pausing to reload?"
yeah you ever noticed you ever noticed the AR was green and pink?
*laughter*
you ever noticed the bullets were pink and the gun was green?
and they both had faces?
and little crowns on them?
yeah i think we cracked the case
that's what Dan Bilzerian saw that's why he needed a gun
get me in there
get me in there i have Darule's book right here
this is clearly against Darule's
this is a violation of Darule's
was that he did
well
uh...
was the the teachers name
dubster crocker mister
her
here
he was actually
yeah
but what did he find
shut up it's not real mister roger
you crazy mister crocker
yet that's what mister crocker was a good idea to a man from
uh...
the
Mr. Crocker was the good guy because he knew how dangerous it could be to allow fairies.
They're adding an amendment to the constitution to limit the use of fairies.
It's pretty fucked up.
Fairy control?
Yeah.
I agree with it.
Oh man, I need to take a shower.
I'm like sweaty.
I already took a shower.
I'm sweaty from last night still.
I'm sweaty from the marathon I just ran.
Yeah.
Yeah, I ran it as a joke.
I didn't even care about it.
Yeah. Pretty cool.
I ran a big marathon.
Yeah, I basically ran a marathon with my eyes closed.
Not that hard to do.
As long as it's a straight line.
(laughing)
I'm so smart I could listen to music with my eyes closed.
Yeah.
(laughing)
That's how smart I am.
And I don't even get scared
and think the band is in the room with me.
Yeah.
[LAUGHTER]
All right.
We're done.
Yeah, that's a dab.