You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[Laughter]
That was... we just counted down for 10 minutes.
That was the best countdown we've ever done.
That was incredible, dude.
Fuck, dude, I feel so good.
You want me to fucking talk about...
Me and Kayla both got some kind of like super power G.
Oh my god.
Dude, I think it's COVID.
I think I got the exact right amount of brain damage.
Well, I don't have COVID, so it can't be better than me. I think...
You don't know that.
That's true. I think I was just like touched by God or something.
Yeah, did you open that letter I sent you?
You have COVID-19, dude.
Whatever, dude.
I'm so lucky that COVID-19 came before scientists developed a way to send like
smells and breath over the internet.
That is true. Yeah, that'll be a much worse virus.
Yeah, that's a good point.
You got an email from your buddy.
You've got smell.
You have wind.
Yeah, and you open your mouth and it blows out of your speaker.
Fuck, dude.
Fuck, dude. Adam Sandler sent a fart to me in my fucking smell mail.
Oh, no.
Snail smell. That's what they'll call normal smelling then.
They'll call that snail smell.
Oh, yeah. I smelled that last night by snail smell.
Yeah. Do you still use snail smell?
I've had my tubes tied years ago.
- Smell smell is when a guy brings the thing
to your house for you to smell.
- Yeah, just a guy carrying dog shit on a stick.
(laughing)
- And it gets a tracking number and everything.
Dude, we do need some kind of--
- Smellogram for Patrick.
- There needs to be, like you look at a tracking number
when something is getting shipped to you
and you get really excited.
There needs to be an evil tracking number
so you know when something bad is coming to you.
there's a true number like old dog shit is coming to my house or a guy who
you're not a bomb
no it's like a kid it tells you how long it's going to take a drink and i
worrying
army
yet that looks like rebel but it's not
but
still i mean it is really seeing says read right there
what the fuck is that the current it doesn't it probably bowl
all the further
I'm sorry I interrupted you Cameron, I'm just, I'm so, what the fuck is, Red Thunder?
Red Thunder?
Yeah dude.
What the fuck are you putting in your mouth?
I'm asking you, I'm asking you what you're putting into your body.
Red Thunder sugar free energy drink with caffeine.
Right before we started recording, Patrick was telling us that he drank something called
highball so I don't know if there's a leg to stand on in this one. It is a caffeinated
sparkling water and a lot of people drink it. I mean that sounds equally as... I mean
at least you're not drinking like the knockoff version of highball I guess.
Highball! Slime mall! They have they have ads... Sky mall! They have ads with comedians. Highball
does yeah well I'm doing one right now sugar-free energy drink with caffeine it
comes from Aldi and it's four for three dollars oh that's actually yeah now you
talking all that shit no you didn't tell me it was an Aldi brand I mean the thing
about another thing about knockoff energy drinks is that normal energy drinks are
already like poison enough I don't think it matters if you have for the knockoff
one like you're already fucking like embalming your organs I think it's my
might as well just like the one that cost 50 cents no no certified synthetic colors
I mean uncertified synthetic I mean who could there's no nobody you would not
believe yeah buddy don't even look at the ingredients of this there's gonna be
some fucking like dude that's lovecraft like it doesn't make it it makes you go
crazy kind of shit it doesn't make any sense to they say no colors in it but
it's red thunder right that's the drink metal pours it to your head for it make a
cup I'll put it in my mouth to show you well no cuz that'll I can't see it is it
blue taste pink it's not recommended for pregnant women also I think this is the
cure for COVID-19. I have COVID-19. Do you have it? You don't know? I don't know. I think I
probably do but I'm still gonna go to PAX East. Nothing will stop me.
Nothing will stop me.
If you think I'm not going to PAX East with you, you got another thing coming.
And if you're going to PAX East, that thing might be COVID-19 for me.
Come up and hug me if you're going to PAX East.
I'll be fine. I'm wearing a big hazmat suit.
I'm gonna be signing
Tissues for anybody who wants to come by my booth. Are they having a PAX East this year?
I hope so dude. Otherwise, I'm just gonna be alone in that big-ass convention center in Boston
Just blowing tissues, you know a couple of might might shoot it shoot a load into
Convention center well, if there's no one there it doesn't matter
red thunder, so i just searched red thunder, just that, just on google images, the first
one two three four five six seven eight nine ten pictures are just of thunder that is red,
the next picture is a nike jacket, then there's more red thunder, and then there's a picture
of a liquid called red thunder biodegradable degreaser, it removes grease, silicone, and
heavy soils safe to use on aluminum and most other vehicle surfaces.
Alright, I am in trouble.
And then they have a spray bottle called Little Red Thunder.
I don't know what, look at my eyes dude, that just made me cry for some reason.
I'm not kidding, I don't, I think this might be a side effect of the coronavirus.
just brought tears to my eyes learning that I'm drinking an imaginary drink
drinking a degreaser I mean I don't want grease in my body that's true do you
pizza you drink some degreaser yeah you don't have to blot it with the napkin
anymore I can go for a big I'm drinking red thunder right now I'm gonna fry you
like a fish and I'm gonna do and I'm gonna go - I want to get like a big big
stuffed lobster or something I miss eating the nastiest crap in a line one
of those seafood broilers. Oh my god. The deep. Like the fisherman's platter. I miss getting
a fisherman's platter from like the grossest fucking beach restaurant. Dude I miss. In New
Hampshire? I miss shrimp bowls and crawfish bowls. You can still do that dude. Yeah you
can still do it but it's not the same. It's exactly the same. I have to wear a mask. You
can still sit in. No you don't have to wear a mask in New Hampshire dude. You just go down
and sit by the beach or something. I have to wear a bib when I'm eating it too. I gotta
wear my I gotta wear a tuxedo - you know I onesie and shit
they're making me it sucks so much I have to wear my spider-man mask when I go to
the place now cuz I'm banned
changing which spider-man I am okay okay you're in a spider no it's fucking
carnage I'm dressed up like carnage right now you go you go that you go try to
walk into the store with your spider-man mask on and they like point to like a
picture of you they have by the door with a spider mask you're like ah that's
ultimate spider-man right six one six so I technically am allowed in here what
are you talking about I'm just I'm fucking spider ham yeah the John Mulaney
voiced one did you see into the spider-verse I'm a cartoon I'm spider pig
from the Simpsons movie yeah so do you think they made me brother do you think
they made spider-ham the character after spider pig was a thing or of course dude
are you kidding yeah do you remember how many people there that was like when
kids first started getting phones and that was their ringtone or whatever
spider spider I have no I have bad news for you guys spider ham spider ham first
appeared in 1983. Wow. No! Take it back. That's like how they have a frog. Yeah.
Frog is a. You just. Oh. I was about to explain it. Shut up. That's like a frog. Frog is a Thor. Frog is just like a
a Thor a frog that picked up like Thor's hammer or something and then he's like
it's just a frog in a Thor costume.
His name's Frog?
Yeah, his name is just Frog.
Oh, here they had a whole thing where they just made superheroes into animals.
I'm looking at this here.
They've got...
Eugene Pattillo.
Dude, they're really good at this.
Spider-Ham, Peter Porker, okay, good.
May Porker, J. Jonah Jackal, right, okay.
Flash Tomcat, yep, okay, right.
And then of course there's Mary Jane Water Buffalo.
(laughter)
- No, that's-- - Elevator Superman, dude.
- That's pretty good.
Oh no, it's Throg.
It's not just Throg, it's Throg.
- Yeah, that makes way more sense.
Throg would be, that guy's getting fired, dude.
Stanley himself is taking him down, dude.
- Yeah, I think Throg does make a lot more sense.
But it would be cool, oh no, you know what I was thinking?
I was thinking of Frog from Chrono Trigger.
What are you sending me pictures of this now?
A swine lady girl?
Is that his daughter?
Why does he have a cane?
Oh no wait that's the bedside I thought he had a cane.
I'll post that picture too.
It's Peter Portsch and I guess Mary Crane Watson maybe?
Oh!
Looks like a crane.
That's pretty good.
Of some kind.
Alright, so I need you guys, you guys will be my doctors because I'm not going to the
doctor.
I need you guys to help me cure my COVID-19 virus disease.
You don't know you have it.
I can't taste anything except Red Thunder right now.
So this might be, I think I have it.
I think you have it.
I think you probably have it.
I do, I have it.
I've been living with this fucking.
you can't taste if you can't taste red thunder i've been living with this bitch who has fucking
cove and also here's the best part she went home visited her family got coved told her whole family
like you have to everybody get tested i definitely got it from you guys you guys don't wear masks in
the restaurants and stuff nobody but her has it we have no idea where she got it it's like she's
just like like breathed in like you know you know what yeah it was probably like just one germ just
just flew in the window one single day just right into her mouth just sitting
there with her mouth open yeah it's like the feather in a cartoon yeah it's just
a snowflake landed on her fucking tongue she has she just got it nobody else did
so yeah I'm pretty much fucked dude hmm so how do you want us I thought I had it
the other day just come up with a cure for me dude I'm just sorry I'm suffering
I'm having to drink Red Thunder five or six of them a day.
I thought I had it the other day before you applied it to my mouth.
Patrick, we're talking about cures right now, okay?
We're not talking about your little problems.
Well, I'm just saying.
I'm saying.
Okay, I don't care.
I can fix Caleb.
We're going to go through this scientifically, okay?
So what are the symptoms that you're having right now?
You can't taste anything, right?
I can't taste anything.
I can't have sex with my wife.
Okay.
I can cure that for you right now.
I stayed up too late last night.
I...
All right.
a bunch of shitty cooking YouTube videos. So those are most of my symptoms.
So the first thing, so... You just became me.
Yeah, because you can't have sex with my wife, buddy. You better watch it.
The way you cure a disease is you cure the symptoms one by one, right?
Yeah. Everybody knows that who's a scientist or
so you can't taste anything you got to get something real spicy you got to get
oh wait you gotta get the white boys nightmare on your taste buds
Caleb I have a night boy having right now with the red thunder so what's the
opposite of red thunder Caleb go to your kitchen water Caleb go to your kitchen
right now get your hottest hot sauce and a red onion okay that is so a red onion
ketchup. Alright? Even better, even better. Go get that right now and eat it on camera.
Okay. I mean we can diagnose you. That's not gonna taste good though. Oh wait, it won't matter.
Right. Yeah. If I don't have- Dude, you should just be eating this- come on, just-
That's what I'm saying! That's what I'm saying! But I can taste stuff still.
I think. You said you couldn't. Go eat- okay, go get a f*cking coffee grounds and eat the coffee grounds. Oh I'll do that, no
problem dude that's like fucking that's like chewing my own cud to me oh what was
the second symptom Caleb's you have sex with my wife she's dead she's out there
dying could develop a robot maybe okay and marry it and marry it all right what
if I just marry my hand right now that you know what I do are you ordained
Pat you're a dame right? Yeah let's do this. Okay let's do it. Ready?
Dearly beloved we are gathered here today to witness the, um, let's witness the
matrimony. I don't know. The holy union. The holy union. Holy union. Bams on holy union.
We're here to witness Bams on holy union between Caleb Michael Pitts and Handley
Handley Pitts. Just Hand. Not even Pitts yet. We're not married yet. Okay.
Handley. Your Hand has the same last name as you. No, it's a different thing.
I can't agree. Handmantha Handley. The union between Handley. No. Handy Milonakis. All right.
Continue. The union between Handy Milonakis and Caleb Michael Pitts. If
If anybody has any objections, please speak now or forever hold your peace.
I do. I have an objection.
Whoa.
I think the robot idea was better and we should do that instead.
I have an objection. I don't want to fuck my hand.
It's also-
I don't know where to go from here. This is my first-
I think your job is done.
Um, okay.
Did they just stop the wedding when someone does that or do they keep going?
I don't know.
Do they just say, "Okay, we'll reschedule it. We'll do another wedding when you invite that guy next time."
"Okay, you are uninvited from the second wedding."
'Cause also, if you have an objection, do they have to listen to you?
Do you have to stop the... Do you have to stop it? Is that part of the wedding rules?
Yeah, you have to stop the wedding for sure.
Why? Why don't you just talk over them?
Oh, sorry, I can't hear you. You're in the back.
Yeah, I mean, 'cause in that situation, the bride could just turn to whoever and just say, "Oh, shut the fuck up."
like something like that. But they've already objected. Yeah. Do they have to like, I think
they should have to write a form and bring the form to the wedding. I think objections,
I think, I think objections in marriages. They need to have a judge at the marriage. Yeah. I
think that it's it's a thing that nobody thinks about because I think it'll never happen but
nobody you know Boy Scouts motto you got to be prepared. Exactly you gotta, you gotta be prepared
to marry a Boy Scout if you're a priest. That's a Boy Scout's motto. Yeah. But yeah, no, a
judge there who can like you know also who can hit his big hammer you know at
the end when they say like you may now kiss the bride you could go you may now
kiss the bride and then go like bang with the hammer. True. And you have to get registered.
You have to get registered too now that I think about it. You probably have to get a jury in there. And an executioner.
Yeah, just in case the objection is a crime. Wait, so when you know gruffer - and you might want to do it in a courthouse
Yeah, yeah
When you do get married you do have to go get it like like the day before the wedding or whatever you do have to
Go get it like like right that I maybe I'm thinking of dogs. You have to get like this
Right not like I mean you don't have to register a dog
It's true. You don't have to do you
Don't register
No shot if you don't give your dog a shot it's not gonna trust you you should be scared of needles and they are sharp
Are you scared of knives?
Fucking idiot. Are you scared of dogs?
You scared of sure you took your dog to the doctor and they said alright
We have a doctor here with a mosquito nose and he's gonna stab your dog. You would leave
We have a doctor who's a mosquito. Do you want to stay? You'd say, "Fuck no, dude. I don't want a fucking mosquito bite."
He's too small. I mean, I
I'm going to the natural food store, and I'm gonna get some mushrooms. If my doctor was too small
I wouldn't listen to a thing he said because I couldn't hear him. Hell no. I don't trust a doctor under six feet. Mm-hmm
That's just true. What are you gonna do? What are you gonna do? I'm not gonna look down on my doctor, dude. Right.
Which I would if he was 5'11" because I'm so tall. If the doctor was
Was one inch tall though. I would be okay with it. If the doctor's below a doctor's got to be over six feet or under one foot
Well, yeah, that's the other thing. Your doctor was like tiny if you had like a little tiny one-inch doctor
He would be able to find you would get into your different areas
Yeah, he would definitely know so much more about the human body cuz right like ant-man going into the Iron Man
So here's the thing, right?
It would have to be a doctor that's one inch tall and also has a very active sex life because then you climbing all over people
one you would know doctors. The perfect medical situation you have one
one-inch doctor and one very big doctor. Oh so they can one can check your bottom
parts. Not just your bottom. One can go up in you up inside you.
One can look in your head. What about an eight-foot tall doctor and then
each of his fingers are doctors. Doctors should play different
positions at different heights like a basketball team. Like the shortest one
should be like kind of a point guard like leader. The shortest doctor is
the jester. Yeah and as they get taller also. And that's why his name was Dr. J.
True. That's a good point. Yeah. No, no the tallest one should be the tall people,
the taller somebody is the stupider they are. The harder it is for
blood to reach their brain. That's fine with me. As long as there's one jester
doctor. The seven foot doctor needs to be like a bumbling oaf. You know what I mean?
who walks around like duh are you sick and then the small doctor needs to be kind of like
an evil genius. It's like pinky in the brain. Yeah and it needs to be a gradient between
those two where there's different doctors at different heights who can say you know hey
I'm like the second smartest and second shortest doctor and I'm here to check out your hips.
You know what I mean? And they have to have a coach and it's me and I get to hang out
with the doctors after work and listen to their stories. And we all drink at a pub and
sing Irish songs together. We all drink in my basement. We sing "Come Out You Black and Tans"
together. Yeah. And we do some pranks to cars. We sing the "Whose Line Is It Anyway"
Irish drinking songs. As if they're actual Irish drinking songs and we have them all
memorized from every episode. Yeah and we play Warhammer on the weekends. You don't make up your own?
No you don't make up your own. Why would you fuck with perfection dude? Wayne
Brady are you kidding? What a talent. This guy can dance, he can sing, he can rap I
I guess and he can do a backflip.
That's true.
I don't know if he can do it anymore.
He's kind of old now.
No.
Let's ask Wayne Brady if he can do a backflip.
You guys, you could trade doctors too and there could be a big Dr. Draft.
You think about that.
Oh my god.
Dr. Draft.
And they could play basketball.
That's a pretty good idea dude.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
LeBron James Jr. he could become a doctor.
Basketball.
Basketball player doctor.
That's the doctor, being a doctor is the new basketball.
And nobody's going to listen to us about this because it's like so too good of an idea.
Exactly.
That's right.
Wayne Brady lotion.
I mean, hopefully.
Okay, what was, Caleb, what was your third symptom now that we solved that one?
My third symptom, well, I'm about halfway through my second red thunder since we started the episode
and now I think this might be COVID, my heart is beating really, really fast.
You think that's COVID, okay.
Well, you know, that's still kind of solved by the tiny doctor. He could kind of go.
Yeah. Is there a doctor who's small enough to touch my heart?
Well, I guess it's not about a doctor that's small enough. It's really just about a doctor
that's brave enough because you could be - you could get a seven foot doctor that puts his hand
down your throat and just grabs your heart and like holds it still for you. You just got to have
the - That's a scary doctor, dude. That's like Jaws from James Bond.
Okay, well, what happens when you get scared? Your heart stops beating.
What about a doctor, well if you need your heart to stop, maybe have it skip a beat,
maybe a doctor you can fall in love with.
Yeah, a doctor who can fuck you.
Well, just, okay, so here's the thing about anesthetic.
It's very dangerous.
Some people have an allergic-
And that's the doctor you fall in love with, her name is Anasthetic.
Well, yeah, because this is what she does.
She is like a replacement for anesthetic because like 1% of people are allergic to anesthetic.
It doesn't affect them.
And then when they go under, they can feel like all the pain and they're completely conscious,
they're just paralyzed.
So she would trick you, she would say sweet things to you and make you fall in love with
her to distract you from the fact that they're cutting open your abdomen.
Exactly.
You know what I mean?
She'd be like, "Hey, babe."
Yeah, she'd be like, "What's up?"
"Hey, baby."
"What's going on?"
"What's up, handsome?"
"Hey, my beautiful husband.
You're my husband now.
I love you so much."
Pause.
"I am in love with you.
I love you so much."
"I love you so much."
I don't I don't like it kind of like a Lord Zedd type figure yeah she's kind of
like a like a bebop or a rocksteady yeah
You can see her brain like Lord Zedd too. She's like a warthog that you can see its brain. It's covered. It's kind of like a mojo jojo type.
It's like a mojo jojo, yeah exactly. Or like a Mars Attacks type thing.
And get this, she's wearing stripes on her.
She has zebra stripes.
She has zebra stripes on her skin.
And her hair.
Her whole body. Like camouflage.
I'm in love with this doctor. Oh my god.
Oh my god.
Fuck me dude.
I think one of the COVID-19 symptoms is I become like Bill Murray style sarcastic.
Yeah.
Well that's not curable.
No, is it?
I was thinking about this the other night.
How like it probably, I was thinking like in five years but honestly probably already
might be happening is like the lame like IT guys or like lame moms are going to start
getting mugs that say, instead of fluent in sarcasm, that say fluent in shit posting.
Yeah, something like that.
I mean, yeah, all the shit that we say now is going to be like old hat in a couple of
years.
Because right now we're on the cutting edge, is the thing.
We're really trailblazing.
It is funny to see people actually say awesome culture.
I did see that the other day.
We did create awesome culture.
There's gonna be like a like a like an NBC like a reality show called like finding
awesome culture pretty soon. And they're not gonna be like game reddit.
There's gonna be a CNN documentary that's like the dark history of awesome culture.
It's so funny it's sort of this one man. It's the stupidest thing I've ever said.
It is the dumbest thing I've ever said. I don't know about that.
No that's crazy that you think that. What? You think I've said dumber things?
I have seen you drink 30 PBRs in one night. Yeah, I've seen you say way stupider shit than that
Like I was I'm always coherent when I was when I was drinking but like I was just loud stupid but as the least
It made sense
Sense
Wouldn't be using it. That's true. We should be coining more terms, dude. Yeah. Yeah, we haven't done. I mean that was like
The first word that can you like this this makes no sense
Yeah, the first thought that came into my head was like coining a term goes fish fry
And I don't know why I think it's really funny
I came up with that. I came up with the word fish. Yeah, you should call it oil boiling
Yo, that might be right now
French oil boiled
K. Oh B. See
turkey oil boil chicken
Hey, too much oil boy. I'm cutting out oil boiled things for my diet. We just got an oil boiler
It's like an oil boiler, but it's oil it boils
*laughing*
Boils the oil in air instead.
God damn it.
That is so fucking stupid.
*laughing*
And then you could sell
an oil boiler and the boiling oil.
Those are like boiling oil.
Oh yeah.
Boiling oil and oil boiler.
Boiling oil does have a very good
It does.
Oil, oil, boiling oil.
Boil boil boil oil boil boil. It does have a very nice ring to it. I will say it's real. Yeah
Which way would it go?
Okay. Now it's oil oil. Something is oil boiled, but then like canola oil would be called boil oil
Cuz it's for boiling. I need to get some boil oil for my oil boiler. Yeah
To boil in my to oil boil
oil boiled Oreos royal royal boil oils
this shit's good as hell dude fuck don't drop red thunder in your oil boiler do
Oh, man.
Fuck it up.
De-oil the boiler.
I'm going to have a heart attack today, dude.
Fuck.
Yeah.
I'm going to have a heart attack so soon.
These COVID blood clots are forming in my brain.
I'm having an oil-boiled poor oil.
Dude, I'm eating some joyful oil boiling for me today.
Oh, I soiled my oil boiler.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, dude, my oil-boiled coil shorted out.
(laughing)
- Yeah, I have to get a new oil boiler.
- My coil's not oil boiling anymore, my oil boiler.
- But yeah, so there's one term, dude.
- Yeah, I've got a good term.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Down evil, it's like down bad, but it's like down evil.
- Oh yeah, down evil. - Shit.
- That's good, that's pretty good.
- That's pretty good, right?
- Yeah, dude's down evil.
- Yeah, I'm down evil.
- Dudes who are down evil.
- Dudes down, the down evil patrol.
Down dudes, dudes who are--
- Dudes who are down low.
I got a down evil due to our down low.
Pictures of John Travolta.
Tom Cruise. Due to our down low.
It's just every male Scientologist.
Pretty much, dude. That's why you join Scientology.
You're like, "I think my penis has been cursed somehow."
"I need you guys to use electricity on it."
I think gay people might have a certain amount of thetans in them.
I think no doctor has ever thought to study.
Doctors are ignoring this excess of thetans on gay men.
This is another thing that our doctor teams are going to uncover.
We're going to have one doctor who's an expert in thetans.
The first Scientologist doctor.
I don't want to get too into Scientology bashing.
I'm very afraid of them.
That is hilarious.
Do you think that you're on their radar?
I don't know.
Somebody could.
No, no, no.
Do you think they're subscribed to the premium feed of a podcast about list?
You think that, you think Tom Cruise
is gonna send guys to your house?
I, have you seen those videos though,
of like them confronting suppressive people?
Yeah, but those, all those people like used to be
Scientologists and shit. Oh that's true, yeah.
Did you, are you saying you used to be one?
I considered it.
(laughs)
Nah. Dude, when I was in LA,
I think I've talked about this before,
but like me and David Potashnik
were like walking around his neighborhood,
and he lived right next to the Scientology like media center.
Yeah. And they have like
this giant gate around it and there's cameras everywhere, but then one side of
it is like zoned commercial and it's like a strip mall. And apparently all of
those... Yeah, they're all front businesses. Yeah, all those businesses. It's like dry cleaners where you
walk in and there's no clothes anywhere. It's also... It's shit like that. Yeah, also
near the like the in the psychiatry museum when I was walking there, I walked
by there a few times and I think the multiple times that I walked by there
they always had construction workers that were standing there and like just
not working. God, what a sick, that is a dream job. That's just a normal construction worker
dude. No, but you know what I mean, they're just like standing, they're just like looking
around. They must have been Scientologists, they started like yelling at women and saying
they're fat asses and shit, saying "Honey, come here," which I think is a code in Scientology.
Yeah, that means "Honey, come here." That's absolutely just a paranoia thing, but it's
so creepy. Yeah. That they just, yeah, and they stand out there and try and get you to
I mean it's got to be a very cool religion to be a part of because all the
celebrities are in it. Yeah of course it's fucking sick dude. Giovanni Rubisi?
Yeah a celebrity based religion is genius. You're telling me you wouldn't
join a religion if Jenna Elfman was there? Can you believe it? Like only with
the power of Scientology could like a like a woman who looks like Elizabeth
Moss be like one of the most famous actresses in the world that's like so
impressive that is the power it's so funny that she's a Scientologist cuz her
like she's in like the Handmaid's Tale or whatever that is yeah she was like
flounder dude I'm just saying that you like a handmaid's tale is about like
like the like evil culture I don't know I've never watched it isn't it about like
how women are... It's about a few... It's about Merle Mumbleton. Yeah, I kind of, I think that is what
what like the the Hulu show is kind of about. It's like a speak truth to power show right? Yeah.
It's one of those shows that my mom calls me, she's like, "This, you have to watch this because it's
happening right now." My mom loves it too. Yeah, and it's like, oh yeah, also the main actress is like evil.
Yeah, the main actress is in an evil death cult. You know who is, and you probably wouldn't
think he is Michael Peña. Really? Yeah. That's pretty funny. That's why he was in Tom and
Jerry. Yep. They need to put Leguizamo in Scientology dude. God, who's your dream Scientology?
I got too many things. Huh? Tom and Jerry in Scientology is what I said. Yeah. That's
your dream Scientology? Well they would tear it down from the inside. You saw what they
did to the hotel in the Tom and Jerry the movie? That's true. Directed by Tim Story,
streaming on HBO Max. Yeah, I've seen it like probably 50 times. Yeah. I mean it's really
I mean, yeah.
But I mean, anyway.
That scene where Tom sings at the piano, ooh.
Oh my God.
When it wasn't a rap music, it just changed my life.
Their joint Instagram story is honestly just hilarious in a way I can't put my finger on
in many different fashions.
I mean, it is like Tom and Jerry, what Tom and Jerry would do today.
Exactly.
It's like it takes these beloved characters that kind of, you know, everyone loved as
a child and it brings them into the modern era.
shows what they would be like in a world full of pigeons that can rap and it has
everything and I'm always on the Jerry or twerking they're doing the wop dance
they both have only fans is and and exactly and it has it has one of the
most creative it's one of the most beloved millennial actresses of all time
Chloe Grace Moretz everybody in our generation is you know that's exactly
the actress you need to bring Tom and Jerry into a more modern era she's a
a queen and that's a dream team and I'm gonna scream when I see that on my TV
and that's kind of an example of the hip-hop kind of rap that you'll see in a
movie like Tom and Jerry. Exactly and you know you just have to respect too that
the director Tim's story I mean his output is just unreal he's he's directed
some of the best films of our time and you know just his his guts to put
himself into the movie as a news announcer pigeon I mean just listen to
Listen to what this guy's made.
This is just something else.
Let me pull this up here.
And while I'm pulling it up,
think about-- Kevin Hart's comedy special?
Tim's story.
Of course his name would be Story
'cause he's a storyteller at heart.
Exactly. Wow.
He's, I mean, and you can quote me on this, AV Club,
he's effing brilliant.
Let's see, he's directed Fantastic Four from 2005,
Fantastic Four Rise of the Silver Surfer from 2007.
He directed the Shaft remake from 2019.
He made Ride Along and Ride Along 2.
He made Taxi and Barbershop and Think Like a Man.
- Taxi was Queen Latifah and Jimmy Fallon?
- Mm-hmm.
- Wait, he made Barbershop?
- Yep.
- Okay, he might actually be goaded.
- He is goaded.
- Barbershop's awesome, dude.
- Barbershop's a good movie.
- He's making Monopoly the movie.
- Did this guy just walk around like a Barnes & Noble,
just pointing at shit, like,
I'm gonna make a movie out of that.
- He directed a bunch of Kevin Hart specials, too.
I'm gonna make a movie out of that Kevin Hart book.
I'm a grown little man, did he direct that?
Probably.
No, I think his budget, I think after Kevin Hart blew up... Yo, wait!
He's directing... Rest in peace, Kevin Hart.
He's directing Humbug,
a contemporary telling of the story of Scrooge. Yo!
Oh, that actually... Yes, dude, that's gonna be sick. That does sound fun.
I do kinda like that.
Ice Cube is Scrooge?
Ice Scrooge!
I don't know if it's...
I don't know if Ice Cube is Scrooge or not.
He better be Scrooge!
I hate this Christmas shit!
It says...
No, no, no!
Universal...
What if he's still in like 1800s like...
Like London?
Scrooge!
You have to go back to the past!
Man, fuck you man!
Universal Pictures has won a four studio bidding battle to acquire Humbug, a spec that is fast
coming together for Ice Cube to star in the title role.
Yeah!
Humbug.
He's playing Humbug, dude.
The title role.
The titular role, Mr. Humbug.
It's gonna be Scrooge, and then he's like a little ladybug and he's like, "Hey man,
what are you doing?"
Humbug!
He's Scrooge's sidekick.
Scrooge's sidekick Humbug and he just walks around like, beatboxing and humming songs.
Yeah, and you're not gonna guess who Scrooge is being played by.
The real Scrooge.
Tom the Cat.
*Gasp*
Yo.
Man, Mr. Story does it again.
I'm gonna make the porn parody Cumbug.
Cumbug?
Yeah.
No.
Yeah, I'm gonna make Cumbug.
I, I, I hate having sex.
Yeah.
I, I will not go back in the past and have sex.
Not on Christmas.
Well, you have no, you have no choice in the matter.
the matter I am the ghost of Christmas past and you must go back to your youth
and and no he's the ghost of Christmas ass oh I'm the ghost of Christmas
ass Scrooge and you have to come in my face I'm the ghost of the future and I'm
taking you to the year 3000 no he's a ghost of the pooper no he's in the future
And he's going to put a Tenga egg on him.
He's gonna-
*laughter*
No, that's disgusting.
I'm going to jack you up with a Tenga egg.
Hello, Mr. Scrooge!
Hey, if you showed a tiny Tim-
I just learned how to jack off!
Look at my tiny penis!
Tiny Tim, that's the biggest penis I've ever seen!
Oh, what a toadser!
*laughter*
Hey, guys.
What?
If you showed a Tenga egg to a guy from the 1800s, you would die.
Yo, that's lowkey a funny tweet.
That's lowkey tweet status.
I might go viral.
Sorry, I've been too busy battling cancer.
Is that why you're bald?
No. Yes.
We should just do that.
We should just pretend you have cancer.
If we just pretend I have cancer.
Alright.
This is a mission for the fans.
We give you black eyes every morning.
So your eyes are all sucky.
Whenever somebody mentions Caleb or something
something just be like oh I know it's so sad just you know guys cancer isn't that
crazy and didn't just let Caleb's like appearance that's like in college when
we pretended that I died for a sketch oh yeah everybody got so fucking mad yeah
which like duh like yeah I because Joe's post took it people took it way too yeah
Yeah, Joe was like, "You never want to hear this news."
And I remember thinking it was a joke until I saw Joe's post and I was like, "Oh, fuck,
wait."
Because I didn't know you guys that well at the time.
And I just remember-
Yeah, the ones that we were supposed to do were just being like, "Damn, this is horrible.
RIP."
And then just like a picture of you making a stupid face and it's like, "Oh, that's clearly
a joke."
And then people were being like, "My heart is broken today and it will never mend."
Right.
just like shit like that I remember like walking I remember outside of like I
think it was the Anson building I remember like seeing Caleb down like
walking down the street I was like oh thank God
you think I was a ghost for a minute yeah I did whoo Patrick you have to come
in my face. I'm the ghost of Christmas. I'm the ghost of Jizz this Pooper. Yeah, Jizz
Jizzmas booper, jizzmas pleasant, and jizzmas ass.
I was trying to think of one for present but I couldn't.
Jizz on this peasant.
And this is about Bradshit.
Yeah.
Those are the trials.
Oh man.
What?
It's still Christmas.
Oh my god.
It's a...
Oh fuck I'm done.
I'm done.
I want to see a Scrooge played by Jackie Chan dude that'd be some pimp shit.
Didn't they do that?
Uh, honestly probably.
That sounds like Jackie, back in the, they were like what if it's Jackie Chan's Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde.
I feel like I would, somebody might have said this before but Scrooge should be the next press tea troll like Joker is.
Yeah.
That would be good.
It should be the next thing that like corrupts actors you know.
Yeah.
You know I mean the idea, the idea that a man could hate Christmas was just.
The idea that a man could think it's okay to say humbug to his employee.
It is fucked up that like Daniel Day-Lewis would be like the most amazing Scrooge.
Oh yeah.
Like he would fucking crush that role dude.
Yeah.
You know who would be a great Scrooge is Bill Murray.
Have they thought about that?
Yeah.
I don't really like Christmas.
Have they thought about it?
They should get Andy Serkis to play Scrooge as like a creature.
Like a Scrooge.
Like that could be like maybe like a modern retell.
It's like oh a Scrooge infected our town.
Yeah, what would in the well? What would a Scrooge look like like an elevated horror like a 24 thing about Andy circus?
And he looks like it looks
It's like the opposite of a Grinch. Okay, no comparisons to a Grinch can be drawn. It's already too similar
So it's not it's not green. It's not furry. You know probably looks like a wrinkled little little thing
I would lizard like a lizard maybe with a penis or something
but you know like a like a flesh-toned like a flesh-toned lizard like a
flesh-toned frog maybe yeah like a flesh that's a Scrooge yeah
and I'll let it as a person's head yeah it's like it's like got like it so like
you know like you know like a frog's head but it's got like a nose yeah mm-hmm
yeah the nose is very prominent I think is what Patrick is trying to say he's
trying Patrick is no I'm not on the nose no I'm not it to be have a certain like
faces in a direction it's like a reedy right like famously yeah famously okay
what religious symbol do you think you would wear on a chain around his neck
probably like a crescent moon with a star
and Bob Cratchit get this his job is he's a well cleaner
he's a well washer but he thinks the well is way bigger than it really is
yep he's like that's also the well over there he's pointing at people's houses
mm-hmm no come on dude and screw the scrooge
whispers evil ideas into him his head do you think we get our
ariester the bob yep okay wait so there's they're all creatures
everything's a creature everything's a creature uh and we could call it
i want to retract like it follows it'd be called it scrooges
I want to retract a few statements I made.
Like what? I would like to retract oil boiling. It doesn't make any sense.
No, oil boiling is very good, but I think... Okay, never mind.
I want to clarify, if a frog
had a nose, it would look weird. Not necessarily.
It would look literally something like this. Like this.
I just want to clarify, there was no... Ew, weep it.
No, no.
You did not.
Don't.
May I have a fly, please?
Don't imply that I said that.
Don't imply that I said a frog with a nose would look Jewish.
That is not what I said.
Whoa!
What the fuck?
Where is that coming from?
What the fuck, dude?
You need to go to the hospital.
Yeah, I think you need to go to the hospital.
You have something wrong with you.
I don't want anyone to get mad at me.
They don't call you Rachel Patrick for no reason.
Why is it Rachel Patrick?
What?
Your full name?
No, it's Rachel.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Yeah, Rachel Patrick Edward Doran.
That's my full name.
I'm sorry.
It's spelled Rachel, but it's like a gay thing.
I love your initials, dude.
R-P-E-D.
No!
I'm just walking on eggshells.
I'm just walking on fucking rakes right now.
Walking on what?
I'm walking on what?
Rake!
Would you say Rachel Alexander Patrick Edward Doran?
No.
My mic stand just broke so I'm going, I'm going, uh, who's a comedian?
Louis C.K.
No, I'm going, I'm going...
Paul Provenza.
Woody...
No.
Bill...
Oh, Caleb, at the thrift store near your place.
Yep.
Located on--
Call it.
Say what it's called.
I'm not gonna, no, I don't wanna say--
Gotham Thrift Shop.
Okay, well if you say it--
Let it fly.
I went there the other day
after I dropped off the webcam for you
and I found a Don Imus record.
Shit.
Called This Honky's Crazy.
(laughing)
And I didn't buy it.
I'm really like regretting--
I'm regretting not getting it.
I'm going there, well I can't leave my house,
but I'm going there.
This honky's crazy, dude.
Yeah.
This honky, I need to see what this is.
It's a picture of Don Imus.
This honky's nuts.
This honky's nuts, I took a picture of it.
It's just a picture of him smoking a cigar.
Oh, that is a good color.
Oh, no, no, no, it's not him smoking a cigar.
It says X-rated on it.
Yeah, it's him sticking his tongue out.
let's look at the amazon reviews here
i wanted to buy it but i didn't want like whatever fuckin anyone like the person
behind the the counter to give me a look
because i was buying this honkies nuts big bit by
don i_t_s_
had the l_p_ not for you who be pc police that's not me
that's one of the that has come out what that sounds like a fucking like
the course of a house music yeah i know that i think there's a meaning to that
that I didn't. Dude, Unchained Imus says the review. Yeah. Damn. He's Unchained, dude. Five
stars. It's Imus. Awful. I hope he can blame this on drugs and alcohol. There's
no other excuse. I threw it away. Do not waste your money. I didn't even realize
that he did stand-up, dude. I thought he was just a radio guy. Yeah, I forgot that he did stand-up until I saw
that album. Bring it back, dude. Come back to her. Oh, yeah. There's a spider in here. Okay, we're stopping
now. Imus should open for us on the road. Damn, that's a big... No, we should open for
Imus. I'm not worried about your... Can you just... The spider's not gonna kill you in
the next 20 minutes. Well, I don't... What if it's like a brown recluse and I don't
know? What color is it? It's too far away for me to tell. Then it can't bite you.
What if it's a bedbug? A bedbug crawling on the ceiling? A huge bedbug? What are you
talk about but that looks really it's a bit of a cm
set up a book to look at down here
i look at eyes over here
look at me i'm i a m s no not over there and i would have looked at that's a
closer look farther look into the webcam are closer to turn a little bit
now other way other way
other way
He's having so much fun.
I hate when you have fun, dude.
This brings a light to my heart.
This pisses me off.
I hope the spider bites you and you get a new power.
Don't!
Don Imus actually had a good, he has really good album names.
The only other Don Imus album, or just Imus, the only other Imus I can find on Amazon is
an album called "1200 Hamburgers to Go."
That's pretty good, actually.
it's pretty good actually that's a really good album
scrolling around on my on this amazon page for this honkys and nuts and my and
there's a section for inspired by your browsing history and mine is just
insane because i was just looking i have i have magnetic mix and match of
dinosaurs and then i have car wax and a bunch of
imus stuff and then a bunch of a bunch of books called like the
innovators dilemma
wow you must be very intellectual very cultured i i was gonna
I was gonna do this thing where I just kept getting shit delivered to Caleb's house and then I realized like
I would have to spend money to do that, but I was
I was gonna
I I didn't I I don't know. I didn't want to just buy a bunch of stupid books that wouldn't show up
At the right time, you know, I don't know but I was gonna buy you the shoe bill storks fact book
Just wait for that to arrive
You can hand deliver it dude. You live down the street from me. No, I know you should buy stuff from me
I mean, we should both go and have something for you.
I was gonna buy 'em, but then I realized
I didn't have either of your new addresses saved.
I had Caleb's house in North Carolina.
Actually, that would be really funny
if I delivered something to Caleb's house.
My mom gets an IMAX record?
Yeah.
Like, what the fuck is?
Well, now I've ruined the bit.
That's a funny ad.
This is actually pretty good.
I keep doing this where I'll ruin the bit
instead of actually going through with it.
I did it the other day with the Nightcrawler stream.
What was the Nightcrawler stream?
I was gonna do like full Nightcrawler cosplay.
From X-Men?
From X-Men on stream.
You're gonna do blue face?
I was gonna dress up like Nightcrawler
and then do a whole stream normal.
And if anybody talked about it,
I would have a moderator.
Ban them?
Yeah, ban them and time them out.
That's good.
Yeah.
You should still do that.
No, 'cause now it's on the episode.
I mean, we'd have to edit this out of the episode.
All right, fine.
Just do it with like Marilyn Monroe or something.
Okay.
Yeah.
- Just come up with something new.
Get some better camera angles.
- Yeah, come up with something funny.
- Just think of something else.
- Just think of a new idea, dude.
- Okay, I got a new idea.
- I thought of one, oil boiling.
You come up with one, dude.
- That's true.
- I came up with one too, I came up with down evil.
- I thought I could just coast off of awesome culture, but.
- No, dude, we're way past that.
- It's a hungry industry.
I mean, making up stuff.
- Okay, I've got an idea.
- It's people wanting new stuff all the time.
- Terms are huge right now.
- It's a hungry industry.
I've got the perfect mascot for the hungry industry.
little hamster and he's hungry. No, that's an old idea. Come on dude, I need a new term.
Not a mascot, not a movie idea. Okay, I have this, there's a spider in my room right now.
What if his name was Michael the Crawler? That's old. It's old. This is all old stuff, okay?
It's, I mean... Ireland. That's a country. It's not making, you're not making any fucking sense
- Just come up with a word, a word for a term.
- Just like one term.
- All right, all right, all right.
- Like slang, like urban dictionary.
- Yeah, urban dictionary thing.
And not like, well it could be a sex thing.
- Okay, I got, what about like a crazy frog?
- You're looking at, there's a,
what do you have behind you?
What's that blue thing?
- Yoda mask.
- That's green.
- Behind that, blue.
- Cowboy hat.
- Underneath the cowboy hat.
What is wearing the cowboy hat?
- Picture of my nephews.
- No it's not.
It's a stuffed animal.
- You're cheating dude.
You're fucking cheating.
You have all of these written on your hand.
That actually is a picture of his nephew as well.
Wow.
That's incredible. You're such a dedicated uncle.
My sister gave me that
for Christmas. Wow, that's a horrible gift.
[Laughter]
Give me a PSP dumbass.
I don't want a fucking picture.
At least give me like a
cool picture. Ansel Adams
photo of a mountain or something.
Yeah, it is a picture of them. It's a picture of my
My nephew's a Santa.
You just go, "Huh, thanks."
Cool.
I'll put, "It's not an X-Fox, okay?"
I'll hide this behind my Crazy Frog plush.
Hey, I know I haven't given you a Christmas gift in a little bit, so I got you a picture
of my dog that you've met twice.
Here you go.
Pretty cool, right?
No.
But I need you to come up with a term.
There is a Crazy Frog era.
Okay, wait, here's a term for that.
Ready?
Schadenfreude.
A lame frame.
when someone gives you a picture of something you don't want for a present.
Cam's on a fucking roll right now, dude.
A lame frame.
You guys know I have the lame frame.
A lame frame media.
I can't think of these things.
The lame stream.
The frame stream media.
Okay, okay, okay.
The frame stream straight, flame.
When Biden came in.
The flame stream media.
That's the Young Turks, because they're on fire right now.
When Biden came into office, CNN became the tame stream media.
Okay, close.
You're getting somewhere.
We kind of just already did two Aimstream media things.
What about the Aimstream media?
That's actually pretty awesome.
What about the Mainstream media?
It's LiveLeague.com.
Stop, do something that's different.
Okay, that was actually something.
But I do want a new thing.
I want you to pick something, or we could pick something.
A rollercoaster.
What are you going to start calling a rollercoaster?
What's a new term for a rollercoaster?
Rollercoaster is already too goofy of a name.
Shocking.
It's a good start.
Good start. Really good start.
Shocking car.
That sounds more like a bumper car.
Or like an electric car.
Yeah, that's like a Tesla.
Crazy train.
Crazy train is an Ozzy Osbourne song.
It's pretty good though. It works.
It's not bad, but it's already a thing.
What about a roaster coaster?
No, that's what you would call a rotisserie.
okay that's pretty that's yeah I got some finger licking chicken off the roaster
coaster at the roaster stoaster the grocery store the stoachery grower yeah
stop and stop I went to the stop and stop and I mean I mean roastery chicken
coming up with new names for like a grocery store like if we were to come up
with like a different thing.
Yeah.
We would just be naming a grocery store
because that's how most grocery stores are named.
But you guys are from Boston.
You guys came up with Bubbler and like all this weird shit.
Have you ever read the book Friendle?
Yeah, I have seen Friendle.
I haven't read it, I've seen it.
You've seen it?
I've looked at it and I've said,
I'm gonna say yes to that.
That was a great book.
Friendle, that's a great book.
You think that is a great book?
Friendle, Moby Dick.
Friendle is a great book.
Yeah.
yeah i'm sure he sees the night might be partial disease that story the whole
thing takes place in new hampshire
so they are partial
parsons
uh...
so i just need a c one-term did
we need one term we only have time for with five minutes left in the epsilon
one single-character your cove it to do it
we have five minutes i thought it was the goal of this episode it's not cure
do it on one of the way that we probably do we have like one symptom left straight
for cover i remember my last sentence was really i was just going to say you
stayed up too late
i didn't have to go yet okay
asleep
so i can't go
the
willful and the
Down will come Caleb, hitting his walls
Dude, I don't want to fall. This sucks. Why would they sing a song about a falling
baby, dude? It puts you to sleep. Yeah, it's telling the baby if you don't fall
asleep right now, I'll fucking kill you. I'll fall on you. Mm-hmm. I'll fall upon you with my
weapons. No. Yeah, so that cured your COVID. It's a Clapton song. No, it did not.
cure my COVID. All of Eric Clapton's songs are about his dead son.
Layla. He did write Rockabye Baby. Yeah. Mm-hmm. After midnight my son's gonna
fall out the window. After midnight. You know what I was saying? Have you guys seen that video of Michael Jackson holding his son over the balcony?
We've talked about this. Okay all right I just think about it a lot cuz I'm like
Yeah.
Relax.
It is an insane video.
Daddy's having fun, dude. Chill.
Yeah, the baby needs to fucking calm down.
Yeah.
Which one? Which baby?
The baby was fucking fine, dude.
Which baby was he hanging? Was it Blanket?
What?
It was a kid named Blanket.
Alright, never mind. That is abuse.
Every part of that video is abuse.
I changed my mind.
Blanket, dude?
What the fuck?
Yeah, Blanket Jackson.
That's worse than the...
the...
the Ha Ha Funny Elon Musk name for his baby.
Yeah.
blanket that one at least yeah that's like that's like they asked Michael
Jackson at the hospital like hey what do you want to name the baby like looked
around really fast yeah I get he did the the I love lamp scene from yeah with his
child yeah goddamn dude I'm in other day he would have been so sick now no no no
look around the room really quick to see what another child was smothered with I
was thinking of Frank's name can you imagine how sick it would have been when
Michael Jackson started supporting Trump for president.
That would have been so fucking funny, dude.
- No, Michael Jackson wouldn't, I don't think he would have.
He would have supported Marianne Williamson or something.
That's what I think.
- Hell no, dude.
Him and fucking Trump are on the same stack.
Same fucking amphetamine stack.
- Yeah, they were.
- I think you definitely would have gone for Trump.
- Nevermind.
- What?
- 'Cause I realized it would just be me
saying somebody else's joke.
I was gonna the uh Lemmy called Conrad Murray the beast slayer which is really good.
He's not uh and Michael Jackson he didn't do that shit dude he's innocent.
Have you have you heard oh I'm sure Cameron probably knows but have you heard of uh Frank
Zappa's kids names Caleb? Moon Zappa I know fucked Mark Maron. Yeah Moon unit Zappa.
Give her a moon pie what's up? And then Dweezil. Dweezil? Dweezil? Okay that sucks.
tell you guys my theory about uh... michael jackson
i think that not only was did he not do anything bad to any children i think
that
the children are who killed him
well
yes uh... they they put
they put drugs in his body i read maria's four kids children are you know
if
yeah that's what you've got to first names
the exactly on the land mary yet that'll be a name
Yeah, take these blugs.
Why did your last name come out of your belly button?
What do you...
[laughter]
So, it's a special procedure I did on myself because I'm such a good doctor.
Frank Zappa's kid's name's Moon Unit, Dweezil, Diva, and Ahmet.
Ahmet is a good real name though.
Yeah, it's just a normal name.
Just imagine being... that sucks though for that kid because it's like, "Oh, you gave
me a normal name."
I could have been called Tonka.
a
think Harley Quinn Smith is worse than I have a boy his name will be maybe
Patrick time and if I have a girl her name will be Pam rune moon unit is at
least like nonsense yeah like yeah that's like a fucking that's like it's
not just like a thing that your dad likes I could honestly be a Starcraft
enemy yeah they had Starcraft in the 70s really big in this story yeah I think I
I think he had that.
He had access to Starcraft way before anyone else.
It was just a bunch of punch cards that you were putting into a big computer.
Damn, I love this game.
You just press numbers on a calculator and it's a legend that the moon unit is.
The moon unit, the boob unit.
Yeah, I'm going to name my kid 8008.
Yeah, and I'm going to name my second kid 80085.
DivaZappa's name is DivaMuffinZappa.
cool I'm gonna name my kid first name Mike Michael Jackson all one word name
middle name greatest last name ever middle name Anna second middle name sent
and no blast Michael Jackson Anacin and it's in pits okay listen I don't want my
name involved my son this my son's scent pits okay do it first if my my my son
okay first name jesus not pronounced jesus like some people do middle name the devil
whoa wow that's [ __ ] sick dude i got a crazy idea for a kid for my kid and get this
horns and a halo that's an expensive setup yeah all right it's gonna be easy dude i just have to
i just have to marry a woman with horns and a halo that's true i had a crazy name
Yeah, you ready for this?
Patrick jr
Anyway, so, um, yeah, if you want to cure covet 19 just follow the steps we outlined in this episode. Thanks for listening everybody
Bye bye