You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[laughter]
Okay.
Alright, so
today we have something special.
And by something special I mean
nothing.
[laughter]
I'm so over packing up.
Caleb joined the zoom call and told us he had a tummy ache and first we thought
he was lying but then we saw one giant tear roll down his cheek. I genuinely
thought that that happened. Can you imagine? So yeah we we have Caleb's
replacements with us today which are Patches and Simon. Hey how's it going? If you watch the
stream you know them that's right yeah
dragons you know patches yeah I invented
Dungeons and Dragons yeah Gary Gygax
stole it from me Gary Gary is that
really their name that's his name his
name is Gary Gary gay Gygax it's so cool
that that like like his parents must have
known when they get oh yeah that he was
gonna do some fucked up nerd shit they're
like look son we're sorry our last name
already makes us sound like a dark wizard so we're gonna we're gonna create some
alliteration and let you just sort of take off from there yeah you're gonna
you're gonna be revered by people who like love weirdly shaped dice yeah
they're gonna invent dice for you son there's gonna be like people in a couple
of years maybe I don't know ten years you're zero years old right now they're
and
It's orcish.
They came, they were coming through Ellis Island and like you know their last name was like
Piotr's or something and the guy was like "Nope, you're Gygax now."
Yeah right.
And they like tried to open like a butcher shop and everyone was like "Gygo bitch."
I like the guy inventing the dice, or like he's a dice maker and he sees this bespectacled
fellow walk by and he just like stops at six sides and he's like "But what if I..." and
he started adding one side and another side.
Yeah, he started, once he got to 20 he was like, "This is fucking perfect."
Yeah, this is, yeah.
That's enough.
That's the opus.
Yeah.
It's like I'm in my own Mona Lisa at this point.
Are there more dice sizes?
Is there a D100?
Yeah, there's like a D, there's a D30, there's a D100.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's a D infinity, I have one.
That's called a ball?
Yeah, it's a ball that I rotate in my mind.
Yeah.
I want to see...
Now I'm wondering who...
Development.
Ryan Dancy believed that the strength of the Dutchess and Dredd...
Alright, this is not...
I want to know who made the 20-sided die.
Who's the guy who did that?
That had to be like a peasant.
Mark Dice.
Yeah.
I was thinking about that the other day.
I was thinking about like chess and how old chess is
is and how funny is to imagine like Dwayne Chess playing with his friends as a kid and
like like they're like you know they're with the Sumerian beard it's all like pawns and
then Dwayne Chess is like well actually this guy's uh my guy's a knight here and he can
actually move like way further than the pawns and he's like a thousand times better so and
there's actually a bit from an Adam Sandler movie uh have you guys seen that one Netflix
Adam Sandler movie that's like the the western he did.
Oh, Reticulous 6 now.
Yeah, yeah, so they have a scene in that movie where it's like a guy inventing baseball and
it's just like a regular game where people are throwing around balls and he like starts
adding like more and more stuff to make himself win.
Yeah, that makes total sense.
That's a pretty good joke.
There's a couple genuinely good jokes in that movie.
Shout out to Adam Sandler.
Yeah, shout out to the Sandman.
the madman of manchester himself
and that is i feel like i'm most games get made though it's like
you make the game you're like oh i bet this would be fun to play with my
friends and he's are playing your friends are beating you and you're like
now hold on a second
yet so say that i didn't get the same in baseball too
and what is the interest in a baseball
well we all the you had that the mat
I thought you were just doing a weird thing.
No, no, no, no.
You've never seen basketball?
He's auditioning to be one of the accounts
that runs John D. Sun's account.
So he's trying out some mispronunciations and spellings.
That was one of my favorite movies as a kid.
Basketball.
So, hold on. The D20, the earliest one ever found
dates back to 300 B.C.
I told you, dude.
Roughly around the time of
Ptolemy won
and
Alexander the Great, began the Ptolemaic dynasty in Egypt.
It's one of those words where it's like pterodactyl, right?
- Yeah.
- The die remains a remarkable condition
despite the passage of time
and displays clear numerals written in Greek.
- Damn.
So it's been around for a while.
- That's older than I thought it was gonna be,
but I knew it was gonna be something old.
- I thought they made it for Dungeons and Dragons.
- Well, they did.
They just had a different name for it back then.
- Yeah.
- They called it a D20-es.
Yeah.
Well back that the thing is back then they had the d20 but they
said they hadn't invented numbers past 6 yet.
So it's still a six-sided die.
They still use it like a six-sided die.
They were just rolling if I came up a number above six, they
would just roll it again.
Right where they would make up a number and that's how they
would make up stuff.
That's that's how they started to get more numbers was they
It must have been so fun being able to just make shit up.
You can't make shit up anymore.
I always feel like it would be, it was probably really scary.
Cause like, the reason why they were like, a volcano would explode and they'd be like,
I guess someone who's a lot bigger than me is angry.
Like, I can't possibly imagine why this would happen to me and everyone I know and love.
the
one
by an acre of miasma hitting building 7.
Yeah, right.
Yeah, the building went PU and then went down.
Yeah.
That's right, of course.
I mean, that's the official, that's on the official record for that.
Mm-hmm.
You read any book about what happened in 2001, they talk about the miasma.
Yeah.
I went to Miasma recently and I was just like, "This shit stinks."
You know?
"This shit smells awful."
I'm just imagining like the an almanac for the year 2001 and it's just like the way I
can imagine it being written like yeah January 3rd okay a lot of stuff happened um it just
I just want to let you know and we're gonna keep going there's a day where it gets weird
it's like the next page it's like all right just letting you know a few couple hundred
pages down it's gonna there's something it's like what is that year except that like that
day I guess I mean like the yeah I was like five I don't remember yeah I remember
getting pulled out of school that day. What did you do? I got in trouble no I got pulled out of
school because my mom was freaking the fuck out yeah yeah right I saw this I
don't know I saw this Slipknot interview video because they they had an album that
came out like in um august right before 9/11 and they were like i think touring during 9/11
and there's like an interview with Corey Taylor where he's like where they're like so like how's
the tour going he's like you know like tour's been great except for what happened on September 11th
and it just keeps talking like god like the idea that that was that's how some people probably
thought of it just like oh yeah i guess that they sucked but well before it was before it was
mythologized. It's the thing about Zack Snyder that like just came up a couple days ago on twitter
of like Zack Snyder being like yo everyone like put on your 9/11 face yeah yeah yeah yeah
sad scene. Well it's like before it was like a mythologized event yeah it was like a thing that
happened i guess you know i mean it was pretty freaky you know i don't know i was a kid but like
it was also just like yeah that was so fucked i mean yeah it's probably the same way that we
talk about like the fucking mandalay bay shooting or whatever now it was awesome
the show went crazy and everybody is listening right now who can clearly remember it and wants
to tell us about um about like what they're doing on that day you're too old to be listening this
Yeah, what were the vibes?
Your 40 year old fans are like, "I remember exactly where I was."
Yeah. I was at Cameron's house.
I'm Cameron's mom.
Yeah, it's great that she still listens.
Yeah.
No, she doesn't. Don't you worry about that.
No, if anybody, it's my mom. It's probably listening.
Patrick's entire extended family.
Yeah.
Yeah, you get the graph charts back for listeners and there's like a door in contingency.
Yeah, my dad recently, when I was in the car with my dad recently, he told me that he wants
to start a podcast now.
Fuck yes.
He wants to start it with his brother and his cousin and he wants to tell stories about
their childhood.
My brother, my cousin and me.
Yeah, that's good.
I'll secure that for a day.
I told him that if he if he really wanted to do it, I would like give him my audio recorder
and help figure out how to do it. I don't think he's going to but I mean that's just like a nice
idea of just them talking to each other and talking about life. It'd be a really funny thing to add to
the universe of this though. You guys have his uncle and his family. You guys become like you
guys are to have the pot about list like family of podcasts. Exactly that's the move. Instead of
the MBMBAM thing where they each have like five podcasts with their wife we can have like a
a podcast with our uncle too. Yeah. Oh, that'd be amazing. Yeah.
It really well. I was just, I was,
I was going through the Rolodex of uncles right now.
Who would I want to talk to that often? There's, I have a couple I dig,
you know, you guys got any uncles?
You can make an uncle. I am an uncle, so I could just,
I could start a podcast with my nephews,
my three-year-old nephew. Oh, yeah, you should listen to my
uncle's podcast. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And you're that would just
be your nephew just saying swear words to you that you taught
them. It's true. The whole every episode would just be a I don't
want to teach them new ones. I don't teach them swear words.
Patrick mentally attacks his nephews. I don't mentally attack my nephew. He goes up to them and goes like,
hey i if you if you touch my hat you're gonna go to hell upstairs and he plays
his video games it's not what i'm sending cyan like psionic blasts at his nephew no
i'll try to think i'll try to think of things to make them stop doing he's doing he's doing
the drunk guy
no the cia like have you read chaos no i've heard like some [ __ ] like mk ultra style
shit to Charles Manson but I'm pretty sure that Patrick's been recreating that
with his nephews. Yeah right. I just remember in like November my nephew
learned the word piss probably because I said it with an earshot of him but he...
Yeah the probably is doing a lot of work there. Yeah. I think maybe you said it to him.
I might have said it. No I don't think I don't teach him swear words he just
learns. I think he might have like, kicked on the bathroom door while he was in there and go "are
you pissing in there?" Maybe. But he like stood up on the table, he was like trying to just make me
laugh and he stood up on the table and went "my penis is piss! My penis is piss!" And then he would
just scream it. I can still do that at 24. I'm gonna start doing that to my friends. I live alone,
I'm just gonna do that.
My penis is piss!
Trying to impress my friends
with the swear words that I learned from them.
[laughter]
Oh man.
I'm just texting Will like, "Yo, you guys
would not believe this, like, swear
word that I just learned."
Just sending him like five texts that just say "fuck."
That was a huge
moment as a child, though, learning swear
words from your older cousins.
Learning, like,
Like, sorry to interrupt you, but fucking the first time I ever heard crap on TV was
out of Jimmy's head.
Do you remember that movie or that show?
No, no.
I think we made it up, dude.
No, no, no, no.
It's a Cartoon Network show.
It was a Cartoon Network show about a kid who gets a traumatic brain injury and they
replace it with like their world's version of Walt Disney with his brain.
Because he gets like Hitler.
Yeah.
So Hitler, so this kid gets Hitler's brain put into his head.
What?
But then he can just see like the cartoon creations that like
they're like Walt Disney made.
And there's a scene.
It's fucking the hands of Orlec, but for kids.
Yeah, pretty much.
And he's like, there's a scene where they're playing basketball
and like his friend is like, Oh, cause he has like their Walt
Disney's brain.
So now he's like, okay, I'm going to make all the new cartoons.
So he gets famous because of that.
And the kids like you're being a really crappy friend right now.
Yo, this is on Cartoon Network at 8 at night.
What the fuck?
Rap is like an eight-year-old.
You're just a what the fuck?
As a as like, you know, like a quiet shy afraid to break the
rules kid crap was such a huge one, you know as something that
like, you know, you can make your parents mad but not like
you don't like to mad.
Yeah, exactly.
I remember being really cheeky with curse words like when I first learned "fuck" and I was
like asking my parents about that.
I was like, "The word 'fuck' and like don't ever say that."
And I remember being like, "Don't!"
This was two weeks ago to be clear.
I was like, "So don't say the word 'fuck'."
My mom just like gave me such a fucking shitty look and I was like, "Alright, alright."
I wasn't allowed to say sucks like this sucks. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah
I mean I swore a bunch as a kid
I'm being some insane words into your head for most. Yeah, we uh my house it was like, um, yeah, no sucks
Uh, no crap. Um, no damn like everything like like if it even was slightly
On Couth we can say did your rude did your parents tell you that like when you were a kid and you said like fuck or
Shit or whatever. It's like did they tell you like you can't say that till you're 18
That's crazy, no, I didn't wait it got to a point where it was just like I think they just gave up on like yeah
Policing our language and I was just like saying fucking shit all the time if you're old enough to swear you're old enough to die
For your country. Yeah, it's true. What are you gonna say when you get shot?
It's so fucked up you can join the armory at 18, but you can't swear till you're 21
Like
Real sergeant calls you a bitch and you can't even say anything bad, right? Yeah, it's so fucking join the army
18 it's so fucking you can join the army at 18, but like you can't play em rated games until you're 30 like
You're 30 and you don't live in your mom's house. Yeah, just like a guy who's just like
It's just purposefully it's not did by his parents and he's like dude. It's honestly so fucked up what we do to other countries
It's but also I can't I can't watch movies
Yeah
It's so fucked up that you can like join the army at 18
But I can't watch movies at full volume in the middle of the night move out of my mom like what is that?
Yeah, I just remember like when my mom would tell me I can't say the swear words until I was 18
I just remember like having the thought like just as a kid like just sitting on the couch with my dad
Just looking at him going fuck
like hanging out.
I'm blown up son.
That's like the well-adjusted child version of like being like
what if I threw this person out of the car right now.
Right, right.
Wait, that's like the same as like think like, oh, I'm
going to have a beer with my dad.
Like, I'm going to sit on the couch and say swear words with
him.
it's like sun
and the uh... he just son you know what
the cure old enough now and he like a a_t_t_ hands you like a piece of paper
with a curse on it he's a little inward past year
that what do you have to have
so i don't want to say yes i i don't know i need to know that i have to tell
you that your grandfather gave that to be a i've got to have to have to have to
that's it
Yeah, yeah, even he was sort of what he gave it to me. He was like, I don't know if we could still be doing this, but he gave it to me and I was going to give it to you.
Imagine how awkward...
Do you remember hearing about great uncle Cornelius? He fought in the Civil War? He got a hair and it's just been danced out ever since.
Imagine how awkward it would be if you lost your n-word pass and you didn't want anybody to know that you lost it.
Because you'd be like, "Oh, I'm going to take a... I'm going to be good. Go take a walk downtown."
Have you like seen something that might have like fallen out of my wallet?
I might need and they're like, what do you need?
Why do you need it for?
It's like, oh, no, no, I'm just going downtown.
I just like to have it on me.
Just like a family heirloom and it's like an n-word pass
and you're like, yeah, I just it's really important to my family.
Oh, what does it look like?
It looks like a piece of paper.
It says some art.
To some people, yeah.
I'm not going to use it.
I just need to know where it is.
we were cleaning out my granddad's attic and we found this old chest full of n-word pastes
we're billionaires
now you're just giving away the gun city episodes
i was at this uh... i went to this record store the other day
and i like i was just like looking around i think i was looking for like
something to hang on my wall, like something to like put in like a record frame or whatever,
hang it up. But I was looking, there's like this, I think it was on Bleaker Street,
there's like two record stores that were like down the block from each other. And I went to this one,
they didn't have it. And then I went to this other one, there's a dude in the front door
and he like, I realize now he was probably like a lookout. Because like, it was this record store,
just like shit was just everywhere. It's just like one of those ones where it's like,
You can't look through anything. It's just like the owner is just a pack rat.
And I walked in, the guy greeted me, he was like, "Hello sir, how are you?"
And I was like, "Oh, he's got a bodyguard."
[Laughter]
The guy's like a 5'6" Italian man.
Right.
[Crosstalk]
He was pretty dangerous.
Yeah, he was in a suit too, so I was like, "Oh, okay."
But I walked in and the guy, it's like way back at the store, the guy's like waving at me.
And I was like, "Oh, okay." And he's like, "How are you today?" I was like, "All right, I'm good."
And then I went down, I was like closer to the register and I realized he's just smoking a
cigarette indoors. He was just like, like I just caught him just smoking a cigarette.
It's like oh, that's okay. That's what I
Probably I had my headphones in - and I just walked in I probably should have like stopped and talked to the guy
But like I just walked ahead
It's not like like
If I was going into a store, I would not see someone outside and be like, hey is the owner like smoking
a bodyguard in a suit is so sick just a bodyguard I think he was just a friend
having a very close bodyguard bodyguard that your friends with and it's yeah is
also very cool it was so funny like nobody in that store was like wearing
masks oh yeah I mean that's not the store where that happens right no that's
a store where the guy owns it smokes inside yeah yeah yeah I think that might
just been a guy's apartment that you were in.
Honestly, it could have been.
It seriously could have been. I wouldn't doubt it.
Did you find anything cool?
No, I didn't.
I was looking for something specific and I didn't want to like
go through.
I was looking for cigarettes.
What were you looking for?
I was looking for like a Prefab Sprout record.
Put it on the wall.
They're awesome.
You talked a lot about them
them and I checked them out I think I said this to you like they're fucking yeah
oh yeah this is like two episodes in a row where I've talked about them
yeah they're really really good yeah I just want I think that Steve McQueen album cover would be
or the swoon one maybe would be good to hang on the wall yeah if I could find either of those
I remember I walked into it I went to the the first record store I went to the guy was like oh yeah I
think I saw one of those I was thinking the other day if anybody remembered them and I was like oh
what like you're like what do you mean pretty seminal you accidentally
triggered a flashback in that yeah dream sequence chimes like you got like this
close to MK ultra activating someone yeah he just walks out of the storage
like yeah is this the guy who owns it or is this the guy who might have been
there yeah he might have been the owner I don't know yeah I like the idea of him
Leaving the store and just like I need a fucking cigarette just like I'm thinking about pre-fab sprout
Reaction from anybody when you like in a store and you ask about something is so funny like, huh?
You know, I haven't heard of that in a while. It's like getting that right like
Like some fucking SVU character like like yeah at you're asking them about like a dead body or whatever
Yeah, do you remember this employee? Oh, yeah
Last night you got a I hop and like that you or and the waiter has like an eye patch and a cigarette
It's like oh, yeah the funny face pancake
Monster
Yeah, I got silver dollars
I'm willing to spend on something
Yeah, I would love to be I would love to just like haunted Denny's and yeah
Yeah become just like I was thinking about that because you could become a like McDonald's guy
That's what I call those you're in the city now Pat. So you you you have exposure to this for sure where they're like just
Regular, is that like a McDonald's? Yes, I mean these are everywhere in the world, but like I've been in Manhattan and in Brooklyn
mostly Manhattan
I always remember like
Like walking by McDonald's and like going to work and like seeing the same three guys and I'm like that's I mean
I know that might not be good
But I also like I'm interested in that lifestyle of like chilling at a fast-food joint becoming like a McDonald's guy
Well, that's you do the same thing in like a small town
Yeah
I remember it like we used to end up at the 24-hour McDonald's like all the time would get like super high and just buy
An ice cream cone. Oh my god, just a cone. Yeah, just
the cone I would eat the cone. This is embarrassing to admit but when you said like haunted Denny's
I thought you meant like after you die. Oh yeah I would want to do that too. Denny's
is like the fast food restaurant where people would be like most susceptible to hauntings
you think? Yeah. I mean you go there at like 3am with like 10 friends and then one person
says I think I saw a ghost because everyone just got really cold in here for a second.
Yeah and if like...
It's the possessed Denny's.
But honestly though if like a Denny's was haunted and like a salt shaker just fell over on its
own or something like the table moved I wouldn't like I'd just be like oh yeah this just happens
here.
Yeah right.
It's just something that happens in this fucking house.
It's just the haunted Denny's.
Yeah.
Oh yeah that's the haunted one right?
Yeah yeah yeah.
I must just be getting like contact hallucinations from the guy sitting behind me.
Do you ever see like there are those, I mean I think there's like actually like a Twitter
account that does that where it's like I think McDonald's specifically and it shows like
the weird McDonald's that are out there.
I think it'd be cool if there was just like a similar one for every fast food chain.
So it's like oh yeah here's the Denny's that is, used to be a pet shop and so it's the pet
shop Denny's.
I would love to see all the weird ones that are out there for different fast food chains.
Denny's, I feel like you're going to have some, I feel like maybe the outside of the
Denny's aren't going to be that interesting, but I feel like maybe like an account that
like posts what they find in the carpet of Denny's might be. That's pretty good.
I'm sure there's a Denny's where you like you rip up the carpet and there's like a chalk
outline under there. Yeah. Yeah. Asbestos. Yeah. Yeah. I want
like a bar graph breakdown of just like the substances cuz
you know, that's where they're that's where they're gonna find
like like like debris from another planet or something.
Yeah. It's like the government. It's over the **** like UFO.
You're gonna see the you're gonna see the color out of
space underneath the Denny's floorboards. You're gonna like
you're gonna you're gonna see the some of this the shit from the aliens in
arrival not around what's no it is it a rival is that the one where you have to
where you have to read and it's fun yeah yeah that but that is will be the best
way to cover because no no conspiracy theorist is gonna try to look into
Denny's for like a like an alien skeleton they're all like wasting their
time
this
This toothy broad yeah, they just mean what they're getting ahead at Denny's when they should be getting ahead at Denny's
And that's kind of what I'm trying to build
You're too concerned about your pancake stacks you're not concerned enough about your paper stacks
That's right. The paper stacks having all the conspiracy theories on yep, right? Yeah
Mmm, the paper trail the paper trail. There we go
Yeah, and not the paper trail. Oh, yeah, I like that
What was the first conspiracy theory that you guys were were like exposed to Oh Paul is dead. Oh
Yeah, yeah, definitely that. Oh, I watched a I got the shit scared out of me when I was like 10
Because I watched one of those and I got like like there was some like music sting and it was just me in like my basement
alone, I was just watching it on the family computer just like
What like the basement got too quiet while I was watching it
I was like what the fuck and I said what the fudge yeah cursing
Yeah, but like my brother walked downstairs or something. I turn her like
Yeah, I thought I saw Paul it's like it's like you look to look away too fast at the screen
Yeah, my brother's named Paul - oh really
It's probably 9/11 stuff for me just because of the yeah, yeah
Yeah, it could also have been like Nazi occultism stuff because I was into hellboy when I was younger and yeah
I did in that movie and stuff
Nazi cultism was also like real like they just I don't to that shit that it's so not it's literally so scary, dude
It's like the most evil people on earth for all yeah, like black magic
Yeah, so come on that's you on the yeah
It is funny to imagine that we think of it all like oh
They were like like boiling children in vats and doing like dark movies over it
They're probably just wearing like party city robes and right rolling right?
Yeah, like that's probably what it was the classic party city
establishment in Weimar Germany
It's like one of those like have you ever parties that McDonald's it's like the McDonald's logo. I think it's a KFC
I don't know but like behind it. There's like the outline of an Iron Eagle
Party City is just a club in Berlin now
Yeah, it's like it's like Burgheim yeah
Like please please like we trying to sell
Fun
Oh my god, who gave Heinrich the lightsaber you are looking crazy right now
Okay, everybody turn off the lights off so we could see the lightsaber better
Turns the lights off
All the lights off and we are going to have a big lightsaber fight
I love this green saber, you know, like, you know, the green sabers the good one, right? He's like
Okay, let's get France in here he's going to play some beats for everybody, okay
Nazis were actually doing black magic to summon Palpatine to our dimension
We are going to
contact Corriban
We are going to we are going to take Palpatine and we are going to make him our father
Yeah, they were building pod racers they thought they were like UFO shit, but it was all that was the end goal of Volkswagen
Yeah, that's what the beetle looks like that
General Grievous is made of all everything in these his stuff is made of IBM parts
It is so funny to imagine like, you know
Maybe like like Nazi occultist like LARPers back then in the like Thule Society or whatever like wearing their big robes and like goofing around
And like they're like saying all these incantations and then just one of them just accidentally does Sith lightning
And there's like oh shit, okay, stop stop stop
No, okay, that's way too scary
*laughter*
It's like they accidentally like
They summon like a like a leg of a demon that's like *weird noises*
Just like fucking freaking like and they're like, okay, okay, okay, okay
Okay, okay
I have read Icarus. Okay, I don't want this to happen to me
You've done force lightning on helmet and now he looks like he looks like a big lizard in his face
Germans saying how do you say and then saying a German word?
How do you say this schattenfreude
right
yeah
man
well yeah i think i think for me the first conspiracy theory
was and i guess this is also a retake
and i also don't do i guess i never looked into it is like is area fifty one
like a real thing
yet is there a reason to be a place yet so i'd like
don't know
groom right ok
so i guess that was probably the first one
so from area fifty one
yes i think that he has a little green mom actually
there was no
uh... and i'm not saying that i think it was because of the like
that uh... you kinda are so i would i would have stopped by the side
saying i know your parents height
i was thinking like i hate
yeah that's true i'm fully out of that's the i'm not half i was thinking like
i think it's because of the arcade game the area fifty one arcade game do you
remember that you might remember that she had no i thought that was the
coolest fucking there was a very cool i was afraid to play i guess i get i was
a thing my mom will be played the gun arcade games
oh yeah
you know parents are very strict against like
like i was a little bit
and games but not like first-person shooters because they like this this is
this one's others list of the lives are off
it was i remember seeing that and just there was the coolest shit in the world
yeah it's all f_m_d_ that's so funny
yeah we've got to make sense honestly like as far as the things to restrict
your kids like
i'm not i'm not saying like you know obviously you're you're what like
forty five patches that you can play a little bit about that
but he said that's what he said i was a little bit about that
if there's a lot of laughing because it's absurd to say that i'm older than
whatever show up at the with
it is a huge honor to like restrict your kids from like probably the one where
they pretend to actually shoot actual people
yeah is a good girl well i do resent my parents forever that now i'm not really
good at like
warzone well i have to leave the right choice probably i have on brian rachel
them for not letting me play FPSs that much.
I play a lot now so I can practice for whatever's to come.
We can see what happens when you get back from the war if you still want to play Borderlands.
I could just play whatever.
I think it was like my mom would just bring home games or we would just get them second
hand from our cousins or something.
Cousin games rock.
I think I got...
My mom brought home Ribbit King one day.
It's not like a violent game, but like, that.
That puts thoughts in your brain.
Yeah, that one, that game is fucked up.
I've been playing it a lot with my roommates.
It's so good.
Yeah.
I'm looking at it right now.
I just played Kirby's Dream Land for Game Boy.
Great game.
Just over and over and over and over and over.
I played Nightmare in Dream Land.
I remember my mother and I had like a Game Boy Advance that we shared and the only game
we had was Nightmare in Dreamland. I remember what would always happen is he would want to play and
then he would get to like the bosses which are like wildly easy compared to like any other game
because it's Kirby. He'd always be like I can't I can't fucking do this man I need you to beat
the boss for me. Yeah those game those bosses in Kirby games I mean I guess it depends on the
Kirby game but Nightmare in Dreamland I remember in particular it's like all of them were hackable
like you could just like if it's the tree one you just jump up in like one part if it's the
fucked up flying guy you just have to watch out when it goes slow. One of the biggest childhood
ruin moments for me is like go like playing that Kirby games again as an adult being like oh I
wasn't good at games as a kid yeah I was just playing the game that was for kids who don't
know how to play games. Yeah that was me with uh Kingdom Hearts realizing just how like the Riku
battle wasn't as hard as I yeah it was. I remember I fucking like it was my younger brother's birthday
And my sister, like, we were stuck on-
We didn't know, like, the Keyblades did different things.
We just thought it was all, like, aesthetic.
And, uh, like, like, power-ups and shit.
Right, right.
Yeah, we didn't know that, like, you should, like, stack abilities or whatever.
Like, it was-
We didn't fucking play RPGs.
You were like, kids.
Exactly.
So, my sister, like, figured out how to beat Riku, and we finally got past that.
And then, um, fucking, I don't know how it happened, but the save game got deleted.
Or, like, she didn't save or something.
something
that
it
Like watching your siblings places like when she be reekoo we're all like holy fuck like we're always gonna be the parts.
Yeah.
And then like we just couldn't we couldn't we couldn't figure out how to beat it and then Kingdom Hearts 2 came out and we're like okay well we'll just play Kingdom Hearts 2.
I remember like I started replaying more JRPGs like that I played when I was a kid and I was yeah I was completely shocked that like I was like that's not if I just paid any attention to anything I was doing.
the
is
Dancing on the moon. Oh, yeah, I mean, yo, Majora's Mask was so hard when I was oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah, we call my god
I remember I got Majora's Mask for 3ds and I need that in like 2018 and I like told my mom I was like
Oh, yeah, I beat Majora's Mask. She's like no you fucking didn't
She was like no you didn't prove it and I was like, okay
You just sit down in the kitchen and just play you play through the whole game
With her watching it's like the next morning other members your family come down and they're like, hey, what do you shut up? Shut up?
It's almost done. It's almost done. Yeah
Also, I just I just got it right at all
I just got morrowind again and like I remember playing that as a kid and
Like the first thing I didn't in there when I first played morrowind is they like you create your character
and then they let you do whatever you want.
But you have to, it's an Elder Scrolls game,
and particularly the older ones,
you know, it's like you have to read
to know where you're going.
And so I just ran out,
and just one of those little worm things
followed me for like two towns and then killed me.
And then I just put down the game.
And so I play it again now,
and I'm like, oh, there's directions,
and there's like, I gotta go buy the giant bug.
- Yeah, I can't, it still looks great.
I just have something in my brain
that doesn't let me do games like that.
I don't know what it is.
I'm just so stupid when it comes to get like,
I remember when I finally got like a PC
that could run Skyrim.
'Cause like, I remember the fucking like
the marketing cycle for Skyrim was insane.
- Oh yeah, there was like--
- Like they had TV ads every fucking like,
like just like, like 10 times a day.
They were so cool.
Like my friends were all talking about it.
I didn't have, like I had like a MacBook,
like, and yeah, no console or anything.
Like fuck, like just played it one time
at my friend's house on Xbox
and we would just like mess around
and get hit by the giants a bunch, you know?
And then like finally, like, okay, I have a PC,
I can play it now.
And then like loaded it up and then like accidentally
aggroed like tutorial NPC immediately
and then like attacked me.
And then I like ran to the next town
and he just chased me forever.
And I didn't get to like finish the tutorial
or like advance in the game.
I'm just like, all right, I'm never playing this game.
- Yeah, I did that with a Fallout 3.
like I just didn't understand, like it was the first time I'd ever played a game like that.
Because like I just remember like the Fallout 3, I think one of my friends had the
Power Armor for his Xbox avatar.
I should definitely check this game out if my friend has the Power Armor.
Oh yeah, the decisions you made when you were that age were always awesome.
Yeah. Right, so I got Fallout 3 and I just had like my first ever playthrough was
just the most evil
character I've ever like had in a video game. Megaton, yeah.
Oh yeah yeah yeah, I did. I tried to...
I went back to that. Go for it.
Oh sorry. I just, I tried to break into the armory in Megaton, and I just like, fucked up the whole game for me.
I was at, I had like, so much evil karma that like, as soon as I figured out how to play the game, I was like, oh I can't fix this.
It's like in real life.
Right.
done so much bad shit and I didn't know that everyone wouldn't like me and now
that I'm thinking about it I have no friends this is a problem yeah that whole
like Megaton choice like going but at the time like you know playing fallout 3 in
seventh grade it was like holy shit like I can be evil I can like it's a
hilarious choice so I have this nuke and then going I like replayed some fallout
3 like last year at some point going back to it's just like he's like hey you
want to fucking blow up this town for no reason. Yeah, in the game too, it's like you can get
$500 or to blow up this town or you can just sort of make sure everyone has water. Yeah,
it's like, it's like, like the choice is, is fucking hilarious. I remember to exploiting
the bat system. So like, you know, like 10 penny that guy up there with the sniper. So
me and my friends found a way to like get him to
we would what we would do is we would fall we would aggro
everybody.
So then there was like all these guys like trying to kill
us and then I would be at we would be up on the tower or
10 penny is jump down.
And if you do vats right before you land after falling off
the tower against somebody you do like land on the ground
and then just hit them with the fucking melee weapon and
not take any fall damage.
So you can just do like yeah, it was so fun and
Bugs in games are cool though. Yeah and I mean fucking Fallout's all bugs.
It's more bug than man. Moral choice in a video game is so funny because it's always like
the way that it's like like like they never really give you any good benefits
for being evil or anything they just know that like the people who are playing
the game are gamers. Like yeah, people are gonna be like we don't need to like add any
benefit to this we know. Yeah you could just get like a cool gun or something
That's it.
Yo, do you want to shoot red lightning or blue lightning?
Right as far as it's literally like, it's the same for like if an 11 year old is playing
the game or like a 30 year old is.
Like it's still, it's just there's some gamer like neuron in the brain that's just like
"Oh yeah, I have to be evil."
Yeah, I have to get home from work or school and I have to go be evil for two hours before
I go to bed.
Yeah, I let off pressure by being evil.
Yeah, it's true.
But in video games, yeah.
Dude, that is the kind of shit that would seem so terrifying to like a person like from like, you know an alternate universe where video games
Just being like yo. Yeah, I just got off from my job. I'm gonna play some call of duty and just
Staring at a screen without blinking and just killing a hundred people for three hours
Uh a medieval peasant would look at call of duty and just start vomiting. Shut up
Fuck you
No, I mean it's a good point though where it is like, it is kind of like, would kind of break someone's brain probably.
Yeah.
Yeah, like I can imagine that.
If you stop and think about it for like 20 seconds, it's just like, oh here's the game where you just like
pretend to be a different person who gets paid to kill people.
Right.
It's so, yeah.
I think like,
Oh yeah.
Like,
It rocks.
When I was like 12, my dad asked me, I think I was playing Call of Duty and my dad asked me, I think I've talked about this, I don't know.
But my dad asked me like how the game were doing he's like interested in it and I was like
Oh, you want to like try and play here and then I put on the no Russian mission
That's probably easier than a tutorial
But you know, that's a lot of people who are thinking about going into the military they think that too
So I gave my dad the controller and I was like, yeah, so this is like the part of the game
where you're like undercover and it's like, I explained the mission to him and he's like,
wait, I have to kill, like do a mass shooting at an airport?
I was like, yeah.
And he's like, I don't want to play that.
Yeah, dad.
So this game is called, this game is called Sallow 120 Days of Sodom.
So yeah, this is what video games are.
Here, let me show you.
you
me for like three months. I told you it's not even that gory. Right. Please, please, please.
Oh man. Who was the, was, who was the, uh, senator who was especially against video games?
Do you remember who that was? No. Senator? I don't remember, but the lawyer was, uh, Jack
Thompson. Yes. Jack Thompson. I remember. I was just thinking like Jack Thompson, like that's,
that's what happened is, is Patrick Doran's dad is actually Jack Thompson. And he was,
he's like play no russian it's so cool to have your like identity be like oh i am against video games
like that's like being like the villain in like a teen movie he was like no partying allowed
my whole thing is that i just [ __ ] hate toys and having yeah like remaking footloose said it's
about like a town that doesn't let people game yeah they have secret land parties instead of
like dancing parties. It ends with a f*cking DDR. It's like being known as like, "Oh, you're
the guy who thinks roller coasters should be illegal." Yeah. "Aren't you the guy who said
that cotton candy was for the devil?" Yeah. "There will be no rock and roll at this concert
"Sorry everybody, but you have to go home."
The guy at the music video.
And if I see a single one of you falling in love...
LOVE!
There will be no tickling at this college.
In the music video that is just...
The music video is just members of sub 41 tickling each other.
At that little place.
Yeah, I mean that's like have you ever rewatched the into deep music video?
I it's so deep the fat lip ones better the fat one is so good the into deep one is like the the jock
Swim team that they're going up against all guys, and they're just like yes
Like oh, that's aged perfectly. Yeah
No, we gotta take gay guys down a peg
2001 like like I get the sentiment as like punk rock guys is like all jocks are gay, but like
So yeah, I as how I respect what they were trying to do and I understand
I I I mean first album I ever loved was some 41s Chuck
Which was nuts? It's fucking sick before it's have you ever like read up on the backstory for it? Oh, yes
I have I'm not kidding when I said it was like my the first album I ever like
Chose by myself and was like this is a great album for me. That was straight out of Linwood by weird
Song concert me too
Yeah, I
Think the first the first CD that I ever bought for myself was also some 41 it was does this look infected? Yeah
Yeah, that's such a good album cover
I remember, yeah, it's awesome. I remember like getting this and being like,
like getting it and being like, oh, my mom, like, my mom can't see this.
Yeah.
Dude, the buying an album where you'd think like, oh, my parents can never know
about this. That's also.
That's crack.
That's what I mean, crack.
Oh, yeah.
I remember, for me, that was, that was Corn Follow the Leader.
That was the first one because I was listening to like All in the Family
and just be like, holy shit, dude.
I remember hearing like the Avenged Sevenfold album where they had the little piece of heaven
that song.
Do you remember that song?
It was on their self-titled album and it's just like oh my god, fuck that song is so
funny now.
It is like a nine minute long, which is for Avenged Sevenfold and Opus, about like a guy
who like kills his girlfriend and then like still like puts her up and like puts her on
the
be listening to this.
I think I had two
I had two moments like that.
I had a
like for music wise that was
when my mom
I think my mom got me American Idiot for Christmas
and uh
there's that line
it's like what's that fucking song
I think it's
it's like one of those songs on American Idiot
that's in like parts
or the other one
the other one where it's like homecoming where he talks about Jesus filling out
paperwork like I was like whoa that's crazy yeah I was like being like a
little shit to my brother or something like we were arguing before we had to go
on the bus and I was listening to Green Day I was like telling him to shut up
because I was like listening to like the CD or whatever nice and then my brother
My older brother had a moment where he was like, "Well he's acting out because of that music he's listening to!"
*laughter*
It was fucking Green Day when I was like 9.
Your older brother's dressed like a pilgrim.
*laughter*
"This devil music my brother's listening to!"
But the other thing that I had like that, I don't know why I thought if my parents, if my mom saw this she would get mad at me,
But I got a copy of Thrasher and it had a DVD of Osiris feed the need
which is like this skate video like this Osiris skate video and the cover of it is just like a homeless guy with a
like a
Cardboard that says feed the need on it and it's not like the Osiris logo and everything and I thought like if my mom saw that
I would get in trouble
Which she did end up finding it and questioned me about it because I had it hidden
Because I hid it in like the like the question like yeah
a
Tell me this is a porn.
Please!
No, Maude, you find a-
Cory Duffel's in this!
Imagine you find a porn magazine in your kids' room and it's called "Thrasher."
That would be the absolute most horrifying title.
There was, in the back page of Thrasher, before the magazine was ended, there was this wheel
company called Hubba, and their whole ad campaign was always, they had the Hubba girls, so it
was just like half naked girls sitting on skateboard wheels.
Which is just like the stupidest, like the dumbest, like, guy.
The skateboard wheels are tiny!
Right. Well, no, they would superimpose the girls onto the skateboard wheels.
Oh, they were tiny girls!
Tiny little girls that you're supposed to squish with your skateboard wheels.
Yeah, that's what the fucking, that's what it makes you think, too.
It's like one of those things where like if you know the cat will like sit on top of your your tire in your car
Cuz it's warm. Yeah, you're warming it up
Girls gave me the same blank stare that my cat does
but yeah, I just remember like
Having thrasher and being like if my mom ever
Fucking saw that ad in the back and I remember reading cuz there was like the the viewer like the reader mail and there was
like a guy complaining like I bought this for my kid and there's a fucking like
half-naked girl in the back what does that have to do with skateboarding like
I totally understood like where he's coming from but then they're like their
response is just like oh fuck you old man like you don't like it stop reading
it's kind of true sir it's awesome yeah well it's kind of true cuz it's like
it's like what do you think why do you think people are skateboarding right you
know how hard it is to skateboard they're trying to they're trying to
better themselves to fuck. Something that's so funny to act like you like
you're to think like oh my parents would freak out they would never understand
this is like like to jump back to like American Idiot I remember like you know
listening to like American Idiot and being like damn my parents probably
don't even know about this Iraq war stuff dude. They probably don't even care.
Yeah, I felt like a huge baby.
I remember listening to like, because yeah, right after I like was listening to Chuck and then I like
through the internet discovered Rage Against the Machine and then like that was it and I
remember just like I would listen to that. Oh dude. Over and over and over again. I would be like
someone told support for I'd be like yeah this is all making sense it's all connecting and I just
I didn't have like any grasp of like what like like like Marxism was or like any of that. I was
was just like yeah everything's fucked up and my parents definitely have never had
these thoughts. I'm the first guy to think things are bad.
I found out about Rage Against the Machine through Guitar Hero 3
and because of that like on our family computer we had like different like like
you know when you have like the different users or whatever for like yeah I had my
account as my background was what's that fucking Rage Against the Machine album I
think it's evil empire i think it's a little empire
well it was a little yeah yeah yeah i might yeah i might that's a good one
my wallpaper was evil empire
it's so good
that's so i thought that was the coolest fucking thing
it's a great album covers a real there's two kinds of like people that are our
age because it's like this people that like
played guitar hero and got really into like reaching into the sheen like block
party
and you know
and then there's people who went to Guitar Hero and got really into Dragon Force
right, Foghat
I'm definitely in the letter
I would love if like somebody
somebody like played Guitar Hero
and like got into the AAS
from Guitar Hero, cause they had maps on there
yeah, the first time I heard Cliffs of Dover
really changed my life
that idea
my fucking mom would never understand
that the wizard flew over the
yeah
My mom's never been out on a cold winter morning.
What's the fucking drought? I don't know the Dragonfort's lyric.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
My parents would never understand going through the fire or the flames.
Yeah.
I know both.
I played, uh, we played Guitar Hero 3 Christmas Morning when we got it.
And I remember I liked Sonic Youth because of, um, like Toy Machine videos.
And I remember like, oh, I want to play Cool Thing. I want to play Cool Thing.
and then like I played "Cool Thing" and like after the song was done my mom was like, "That sucked."
I can't remember honestly, I was trying to think of like, because I never played like guitar hero
or anything, I'm not sure exactly how I found like you know like new metal stuff like Korn
and Slipknot, like I don't know what I really like, I honestly think that the reason that I
started listening to Korn like honestly might have been that I thought that the backwards R looked
cool
might have been the thing that like it
change my life trajectory forever was like a letters backwards i think that
the associated with the are in place are us that's right
like you know this might be toys to
what's that the fucking i saw the
you really music choice on a like to you like the video on demand thing or is
like you just watch music videos on demand
Sounds familiar, but go on.
Yeah, I would just watch like...
So no, but yeah, go on.
I would just go to the alternative one and just like look through like all those bands.
And I watched the video for like Follow the Leader or...
No, no, no, no, the...
Freak on a Leash.
Freak on a Leash, yeah.
I watched like the video for Freak on a Leash and Coming Undone a lot.
Dude, Coming Undone, also great video.
God.
That was such a fucking crazy video.
It's a... I didn't know until recently that the video for Rollin' by Limp Bizkit
was the last thing filmed in the World Trade Center.
- Yep.
- What?
- Yeah, it was the last thing filmed before the--
- No, what the fuck?
- That is amazing.
- It was filmed on like,
it was filmed in like the first week of September, 2001.
- Holy shit.
- They have, Limp Bizkit, like I remember,
I think someone told me about this,
it was probably Will,
but like, told me about like--
- That's fucking amazing.
- They have like a letter-- - That is so cool.
- They have a letter from the World Trade Center,
like, you know, thank you for like, you know,
patronizing us, like we're really glad
you're able to shoot the video here blah blah blah dated September 10th.
Yo!
The letter ended with "you guys seem cool, don't come in tomorrow."
That is so fucking nuts.
God damn, that's amazing.
It's so funny, it's so good.
It's a good video too, fun.
It's got Penn Stiller in it.
Don't come by tomorrow?
It's a giant baby that's going to be knocking down India.
[laughter]
Is that the one with, um...
Is that the Limp Bizkit video with Mike Valleli?
I don't know.
I don't fucking know, dude.
I just know...
That's the one with Ben Stiller.
Okay.
That might be it.
But, um, there's some...
I think you're probably thinking of Break Stuff.
Break Stuff is the one that has a ton of cameos.
Yes!
No, there's a specific video.
Which Limp Bizkit video has skateboarding in it?
of
the
like an interview with Mike Villelli where he's like talking about being in a Limp Bizkit video
and I guess he was just like yeah I never liked Limp Bizkit and then I met Fred and he was such
a good guy and then like he just liked Limp Bizkit after that. That is literally the opposite of what
happens to like everyone else on the planet. Right Limp Bizkit is such great they also they
have the music video for Eat You Alive is where the one where it has Thora Birch in it and Thora
Strap to a chair in the forest and oh yeah you should know and Fred Durst is
just screaming the chorus in her face through a megaphone it's so nice they
have really good celebrities yeah cameos there I mean it's so funny just like
Fred Durst she's being like who am I gonna get for this fucking video oh yeah
my favorite skateboarder when I was a kid yeah they recently Fred Durst has he
made a tiktok and he's been posting his tiktoks on his Instagram story and it's so
funny because they literally make absolutely no sense at all. They're like
yeah like a little bit funny but just like seeing his sense of humor is so
insane because it's just like it'll just be like him walking around in a park and
he sees like a guy doing something weird like that's his friend do it like
acting something goes like oh I like his style and like that's the joke like his
His brain is so clearly fried.
It's so awesome.
It's so funny,
what is it, like Wes Borland
on Instagram, doesn't he do
like makeup tips?
That would make sense, he did a lot of makeup.
I think he does.
I'd have to look that up.
He's such a good guitarist.
Yeah.
Yeah, he does. Wes Borland
just does makeup tutorials now.
He rocks, dude. That's awesome.
All right, so fucking cool. Well, I think that's as good a place as any mm-hmm to end
Yeah, you go go follow patches at senator gun and and then Simon at mulch Lord. Thank you guys for yeah
Thank you last. Yeah, of course
You know, no, we everyone make sure you pray for for Caleb. He's really upset about Anna K being pregnant
Couldn't make the podcast recording. All right. Bye everybody
Bye.
Where's an Olympus Good.