Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
- Premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- And record.
- And record. - And we're live in the studio.
- I wonder why we're so out of sync.
- We're not out of sync.
- We're synced up.
- We're completely synced up.
- Our cycles are synced up too.
- I wish I had a cycle.
I wish I had any, I feel like women have a built-in routine.
- Yeah. - Isn't that nice?
Like I wish that I had a, I wish like once a month maybe--
- The male cycle is food.
- True, three square meals a day.
'Cause women only eat one, or at least they're supposed to.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah.
- And once a month we get McChicken too.
That's also something that we--
- Man, I haven't had a McChicken in a bit.
I haven't had McChicken in ages.
- I don't live anywhere near McDonald's.
It's not realistic for me to--
- I mean, no, and it's also like everything I live near
is like cheap and like real food too.
- Yeah, the last time I ate McDonald's,
I was like insanely hungover and it was raining outside.
- I ate McDonald's out of necessity pretty recently.
- Really?
Just some nice cheap meal?
- Uh-huh.
- Yeah, you know what's also as cheap?
Is to eat something at your house.
- Yeah.
- To eat groceries.
I think groceries might be even a cheaper meal
than McDonald's.
- Nah, I hate groceries.
- Okay, okay, buying groceries.
- I hate grocery shopping.
- Okay, you buy groceries, it's like $100.
Buy a McChicken, that's $1.
- Yeah.
- Okay, so I'm not quite seeing--
- That's a good point, I guess.
- What do you mean that that's cheaper?
That's clearly not cheaper.
- To me, money doesn't mean anything
'cause I'm so rich.
Honestly, I think McDonald's--
- We're definitely so rich.
- Getting the Instacart driver
to bring you 100 McChickens.
- I think that McDonald's might be the only
fast food option that is cheaper, probably,
than making food at home, right?
- Yeah.
- It's gotta be cheaper.
- It's got more expensive, though.
The dollar menu is like, it's horrible now.
It's a dollar fifty nine menu these days.
Yeah, it's terrible.
Especially here in this fuckin' liberal ass de Blasio city.
That's right, they've raised the prices.
Yeah, raise the prices on the best food in the world.
Hey de Blasio, de sandwiches are de too much money.
De Blasio.
Yeah.
How about you de fix your de city that you de run.
De too many de bills, like bill.
Oh yeah talk about bills yeah too many bills from this sandwich. Hey DeBlasio
how about you get off your ass and stop being DeBlaise DeBlaisey ho. Why can't
you be more like John DiMaggio? That's right. And do a black voice. Real man.
John DiMaggio, you think Bender's a black voice? No he's done... It's not
Bender that's the problem. He did a yeah like the boondocks right? Like he was on...
He did a bunch of stuff. Yeah the boondock if they let you do a voice on the
boondocks though you're fine dude you're completely fine I guess that guy rules
he also was in gear he's the Gears of War dude right uh-huh dude legendary like
probably one of the best voice actors ever right he has over a thousand
credited role yeah yeah see he's hit so many characters like a black mask and
black Adam I just finished that general Grievous another iconic black roll I I
just finished that show White Lotus oh yeah yeah it's terrible man I don't care
I don't like so bad gonna watch it it's fucking made by Ned Schneebly right so
first of all that's cool but also Ned has this idea in his head that he like
really has culture pinned right so there's every single episode at some
point somebody will do something and then someone would be like okay that was
seriously not based or and that was cringe-pilled and you're seriously a
trad calf neocon dude I and they go dude it sucks it sucks so it's clear it's
It's like the old, Ned Schneebly's gotta be in his 50s, right?
I was a script consultant on that.
I can tell.
I can actually tell.
Yeah, your fingerprints are all over it, bro.
It's fucking terrible.
My fingerprints that have white chocolate on them.
He's like, "You're seriously orange juice pilled for breakfast this morning?
Wow, that's seriously based in breakfast pill."
It's awful, dude.
Is that the son that says that shit?
The gamer son?
literally every fucking person in the show they have like a 50 year old being
like oh yeah we are in Hawaii and there's vacation here yeah we're
seriously capitalism pilled here in Hawaii where the flowers are flower
pilled and the Hawaiians are pineapple pilled yeah it sucks dude it's just
that's how TV is from now if that's like where the like the like popular culture
like like like reference pool is moving then it TV's gonna suck for the next 10
years and it's cool that we get to contribute to it who we talk about poop
though yeah yeah yeah I have bad news so I think John DiMaggio might be cancelled
after all why I just found out I'm looking at his I'm looking at his
behind-the-voice-actors.com page and unfortunately it seems that in 2016 in
Zootopia he played a character named moose given parking ticket whoa are you
troubling development yeah you tell me they let a white man play moose given
parking ticket and says here in be cool scooby-doo he played stealing Stan whoa
that's not okay to steal yeah no it's definitely not that's wrong and then dr.
do little to he played what's up fish that one actually might have been that
might be wrong tiny puss in the adventures of puss in boots and he played
jumping rats number one two and three in all hail King Julian what the hell come
on he's serious couldn't you give that role to three guys get this guy out of
Hollywood see where it's now we're hiring one guy to play three guys are you
serious that think about all the three guys guys out there yeah yeah wait for
that you're passing over you're passing over so many jumping fellows there's so
many three guys that could have played that role and instead you have one guy
play it do you realize how many roles there are built for one guy I'm right
you know how hard it is for three guys to get a role man it's just embarrassing
dude as I say I mean yeah hey hey for example I don't know Hollywood these
three guys in front of you right now you fucking idiot yep three guys three
three guys three guys you who are a little bit different but not that
different is that ultimately the same ultimately we have the same beautiful
kind soul yeah yeah we all share a same soul yeah is that you can't you're
passing us up makes you three guys instead of just three one guy exactly
three yeah so you could cast one guy one guy in three different roles that's fine
but to cast one guy in a three-guy role so serious right now so fucked up and you
know and the worst part is that is the worst part the giant I just hit the gong
the worst part is BONG!
dude if we get an office we have to get a gong I'm gonna get a gong a gong would be
so cool dude giant ass expensive gong fucking $5,000 gong be so cool man oh
yeah excited I mean we do have an exciting guest we're waiting for we do
mention that yeah yeah of course yeah wait for I mean we get a little darker
yeah we started recording because well I mean we all have we're on a tight
schedule yeah you know I have to go to go to scope with skateboard yeah gonna learn
how to make them Donald's after business meeting they're important branding yeah
we have a lot we have a branding meeting yep I'll say the Sullivan meal oh I
shouldn't have been said though come on you didn't say where it is I didn't said
I didn't say it's 20 flies this should do a meal for an animal that's a really good
idea the only Clifford meal the only company that has cornered that market
Starbucks when it starts everything has a the whipped cream for dogs yeah that
can't be good for a dog no it's horrible it's a tree again yeah it's funny that
We've bred dogs to be so fucked up that like pretty much any food fucks them up
Yeah, like a grape a grape this guy can't eat a grape. Uh-huh. Yeah this
Like a bite force like that can just may like destroy a child's face
But if you feed it one grape or like a Hershey bar, yeah
Oh, yeah. Oh, you're such a you're such a strong buff dog. Oh, well check riding through this chicken bone
what you know they can't even bite through a damn chicken bone what else
are the shards piercing its stomach onion that's why I walk it when I want to
sneak a CBD cart onto a plane I wear a full chocolate bodysuit so that the
canine unit it's like yeah you want to go you want to bite me body spray
commercial I fucking dare you yeah all all grapes and and shampoo and the dogs
kryptonite is a raisinette. That's the ultimate dog killer. Yeah. That is a dark chocolate raisinette.
You cannot take it, that's why you can't take dogs to the movies. That's what the CIA canine
unit puts in their molars. It's one big dark chocolate raisinette. Just a single dark chocolate raisinette.
They just dislodge it if they're ever about to divulge secret information. I would love that.
Yeah, it's like a dog, a dog like in the back of a CIA van and it's just like, "Alright,
we're only gonna ask you once who's a good boy."
And then he just starts foaming at the mouth.
Immediately, it's not even foaming at the mouth, he dies slowly of diarrhea for his two
days.
Yeah, I would love to have a fake molar filled with maybe a nerd or something.
- Yeah, man, I haven't had nerds in a long time.
- You know what they got now?
- Dude, I'm so glad it's Halloween tomorrow.
- They have balls of nerds rope.
- It's not Halloween tomorrow.
- Yes it is.
- I guess when this comes out it is.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, he knew that.
- I know.
- Why would you say it like that then?
- Because he's a good podcaster.
- Right now when you say it, it's not tomorrow.
- He's not a good podcaster.
- Well, if the people are listening to it tomorrow,
it will be Halloween.
- It's true.
- No, when they listen to it tomorrow,
it'll come out today.
- No, now I'm talking to you.
Now I'm talking to you because you want to talk semantics
about what I said.
- You're talking to me?
- Uh-huh.
- Is it?
- So today is the day before Halloween.
- Today is Halloween.
- But yesterday, when we recorded it.
- Was Christmas.
was my friend Ryan's birthday.
It's your friend Ryan's birthday?
Happy birthday, Ryan.
Is it the Ryan I know?
No, it's not a Ryan either of you know.
It's actually a Ryan I made up.
Oh!
(laughing)
Don't get me all pumped up for a birthday, man.
I started to celebrate.
Yeah.
I started lighting a firecracker.
I do see that cake back there
that you have behind a glass that says,
in case of emergency.
- It says breaking case of birthday.
- Yeah.
- And yeah, yeah, there's gonna be glass all over the cake,
but they're gonna appreciate that I brought a cake,
you know, it's the thought that counts.
- Well, you just eat around it.
- Just eat around the glass, you idiot.
I've been recently, I've been just stepping on glass,
like, (laughs)
and each time I keep breaking stuff,
I keep breaking like mason jars and shit,
and I used to like be real careful.
- Why do you keep breaking mason jars?
- 'Cause they just fall off,
I got too much shit in my house, man.
They just fall off the counter and shit.
And now there's glass everywhere and all this.
- I thought-- - Can you step on it?
- I thought that you were having a pickling accident.
- I've stopped trying to avoid the glass
when I break glass.
I've just been, and the truth is, it's fine.
It doesn't hurt your feet that bad
and it doesn't cut you at all.
- Is that true?
- I'm serious.
I've just been picking it.
It just gets kinda stuck to your foot.
It's not trying to hurt you. - What, glass?
- Yeah, it's not that bad. - I think you might have
a different type of glass.
No, no, it's normal glass.
Might be like candy glass or like breakaway glass.
I don't have, I don't live in a prop house.
Okay.
You kind of do.
I don't live in a prop house.
All of your, all of your belongings look like movie props.
That is a little bit true.
They were all, they were all, they were all auctioned off of the Oliver Twist set.
[Laughter]
Okay, I have an Oliver Twist bed, but actually all my chairs are from Emma and...
Who?
That movie, Emma.
Oh.
I thought this was someone we knew.
They based, it's based off Clueless.
Okay.
Yeah.
Jane Austen.
Oh.
See, this is why I have fancy furniture and you don't.
Yeah, I have future furniture
'cause I don't think about the past.
You have future furniture?
What?
Yep, I'm sitting on a hologram right now.
What does that mean?
You're not sitting on a hologram.
Future furniture?
- You don't have the knee strength to sit on a hologram.
- And I'm actually at Caleb's house
where we're recording this,
and we didn't record this on Zoom
because we thought that we needed
an extra 20 minutes of the show.
So, checkmate.
- Don't checkmate me. - What are you talking about?
- You don't even know how to play chess.
- This is so confusing, the recording now,
'cause you said that the Halloween thing.
- What's confusing about it?
- 'Cause we have this special guest coming up.
yeah it's special guest coming to this house and it is a very soon
uh... the issue
what are you confused about confused about looking at my idea of my hand
twenty days about i'm confused
about calm now you're touching me you know i am a little idea you're fucking
pete holmes dot right now you made a weird right now she admitted that we were
just a minute you literally made it weirded
all right that's my bad
you're peeping out did
answer i'm sorry p dot
i'm sorry
You guys see that face I'm doing?
I'm sorry.
I can see the face because we're in the same room.
What a weird thing to say.
I don't remember what he sounds like.
Yeah, I'm Pete Holmes.
Is that what he sounds like?
Something like that.
It just kind of sounds like TJ Miller.
He had that joke.
The aristocrats.
Yeah.
No, no, no, no.
Two types of black people.
Right, Pete Holmes?
Dad is great, give us a chocolate cake.
That was him.
Yeah, my daughter's a shitty cunt.
He did that one too.
Yeah, he did.
Well, he had that one where it's just, he says, "Pier Spring Bierce."
Ugh.
Yeah, do you remember that?
I hate him, dude.
That was one of my favorite jokes when I was like 14.
That was one of your favorite jokes?
I showed it to my mom and she giggled.
You know what my favorite joke was?
Aunt jumping on a homeless guy's birthday cake.
That's a funny joke, okay
And in the middle of New York City ants London Derry, New Hampshire, London Derry, New Hampshire
Oh, oh ants you mean Anthony Kumiya. No, I thought you meant no
He means the but you meant ant the gay gay guy from ask a gay guy on Chappelle's show
No, you met in a boy jumping onto a cake. You thought I meant
Ant from a gun. No, I think you meant ant from ant and not
Anthony Anthony Anthony
Anthony Anthony
My name is Othney Anthony
That's a sick sci-fi name that you just invented on accident
Othney Anthony
I thought you were talking about Ant the gay guy though.
No.
Why do you make everything gay?
Why not?
I guess that's true.
It is Halloween after all.
Yeah.
It is Halloween today.
Tomorrow, no tomorrow's Halloween.
You need to get your mind out of the gutter.
It was Halloween's Eve.
The gutters of the monster house.
Tomorrow is Halloween.
And today is Halloween.
Today is the day that we're interviewing the Dark Lord himself.
Stop, stop, stop.
Stop tipping it, dude.
He's not even here yet.
Why are you ruining this episode already?
He's not even here.
You're going to be so weird in the interview.
I got a text from him that says he's on his way.
He is on his way, but that's...
He was on his way like an hour ago.
He's got a long way to travel.
Why are you making...
I don't know.
I see the sun going down.
I know that's why we're waiting, because the sun's going down.
But he can't even be...
- Just wait till he gets here.
- He probably isn't even gonna travel.
Son is like pretty much gone.
He's not even probably gonna start traveling
until it's gone, right?
- I don't know.
I mean, you know him better than me.
- Kinda, but like just barely.
We've talked over DMs and shit.
He's not like my friend.
I wish.
Maybe he will be after this.
That'd be cool.
- I've gotta hope.
- We need to make more famous friends, guys.
- Yeah, I can't wait to ask him questions.
who's it who's it who do you think is our are going to be our famous friend we have
probably could be this guy
think shia you think we could hit up shia i think shia might be a fan
shia? no i met him once
you think he remembers it?
yeah
i think he didn't fuck with me. when you were working at fast food? it'd be funny if shia
also told that
that story of meeting patrick as many times as patrick has told it
Yeah, I met this fuck. I was at Life Alive and I met this freak and he sucked.
He didn't say hello to me.
And he didn't even say, "Are you Shia LaBeouf?"
I did say that.
Pretty weird.
I did say that too.
I thought he was a homeless guy.
Yeah, I asked him if he was Shia LaBeouf because I thought he was a homeless guy walking in because his clothes were dirty.
I'll say this, if I was a homeless guy and someone asked me if I was Shia LaBeouf, I'm saying yes.
I would say yes, yeah.
I'm saying yes dude. I'm trying to get free shit. That was just a homeless guy.
You're like, "Are you Shia LaBeouf?"
He went, "Ahhh!"
"Ahhh!"
"I'm hideable."
"And my meal is free."
That was the eighth guy that Pat asked that to that day.
Yeah, every homeless guy came out.
The first one who said this.
He hit him with a, "Are you Shia?"
"Are you Shia? Shia LaBeouf?"
"Are you Shia LaBeouf from Newfoundlandia?"
I didn't hear anything yet because it we have to wait a few minutes.
I thought it was time.
Why are you trying to do you are a freak dude you're a fucking monster.
That's strike three.
You are terrorizing us.
You're not you're not acting like Pete Holmes anymore you just became Pete Holmes.
I can see your your mouth is getting humongous like that horse filter on Instagram and it's
turning you into it you're becoming a disgusting freak.
This has been so confusing for me.
I know.
In terms of keeping the story of the thing coherent.
What are you doing?
Stop!
Shut up!
Can we just record this later when we hang out?
No!
Why are you... what are you doing?
It doesn't make sense in my head!
It's so easy!
Just do it!
It's just a normal episode!
It doesn't matter whether it makes sense in your head!
Why are you so stupid?
Whoa, what was that?
Whoa, what was that? Oh, it's our guest. I think our guest might be the door.
Oh, our guest is here. Our mysterious guest.
We're going to cut to the interview.
All right.
Hello.
Wow. Back again.
Back again.
Back at it.
Beautiful. The beautiful show.
Beautiful. The most beautiful show of all time.
But it's not like a normal show today.
No.
No, it's a little scary.
Not at all. It's a little...
It's a little... I would say it's intriguing. It's interesting.
Eerie.
It's not even eerie, dude. Let's just...
Fascinatingly eerie.
No, it's not even, I wouldn't even say it's eerie. Depends on who you ask, I guess.
True.
Ookie, spooky.
It's not ookie spooky. Definitely not ookie spooky.
It depends on what you're afraid of.
If you're afraid of interest.
If you're afraid of intrigue and...
Information.
If you're afraid of information, you might want to turn this off right now.
Because you're about to get a load.
If you're afraid of getting your mind blown.
Yeah.
Having your perspective maybe shifted for the better.
then you might want to turn this off. You might want to shut this off right now.
Viewer beware. Learning a little something about yourself,
the world, someone else. Holding a mirror up to yourself in society.
Or another mirror. Yeah, or another mirror.
Now talk about being blind. Now that's scary because that never ends.
Yeah. Yeah, that's actually really scary. So we have a guest today, but it's more than a guest.
I think if you've been to any barbershop in the world, they have the conversation every day,
day in day out top five most evil people who've ever lived.
Yep.
Right? You have that question.
I ask that's the question I'm asking my barber.
Yeah, Chucky, you know. But we have today somebody who I think gets left out of the
conversation all too often, Dracula. My man, how are you doing today?
Yo.
What's up?
What's up guys?
How's it going?
Thanks for having me out.
Yeah.
Good to have you.
You have an easy time getting here?
Yeah, it was like super simple because I just like Uber everywhere now.
Really? Oh, you're on that tip? Do you have the Uber lift?
You thought you were evil, dude. I thought you would have stick with Uber.
I just like, I get a ride where I can, you know what I mean? Sometimes the apps are all
fucked up right now because of some like legal shit, but that's why I have to do both.
You see, they've been like surge pricing. It's crazy.
Yeah, it doesn't matter for me, for my bank account.
Don't act like you can't handle the surge pricing.
I'm not trying to like...
This guy's a count.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, I am.
The Count himself, some people know him as the Count, we know him as Dracula.
Yep, yep.
Very good to see you. Hey, I got a question for you. You got any Mardi Gras plans?
Damn, Mardi Gras. This year I'm keeping it pretty easy because last year I got like
crazy ass hungover.
Oh yes, I saw that.
There was a photo of you, you were leaving the French Quarter at like 4 in the morning.
Yeah.
Yeah, you looked fucked up.
It was like with all my college buddies, like we were out, you know what I mean?
And like on those holidays you want to get so fucked up, but then you forget we're getting older, right?
So like you can't handle liquor like you used to be able to yeah, absolutely
Yeah, I mean once you hit like the 200s, I bet it's like, yeah, it's a little different for me
Yeah, but I like I go to college once again, like every hundred years so I like have a new set of like buds, whatever
Yeah, where'd you go? Where'd you go this time?
Dude, yale. Yeah
Yeah
Yeah, no, they like knew about me. So they're just like come right in. Oh, yeah
How they let franco like just fucking teach and I don't fuck with franco really y'all have beef
I just you know, I hate his acting like I just like his we were kind of like enemies at school whatever. Oh, whoa
I didn't know that kind of like tall like bad
Bad boy, whatever but and you were he kind of was stealing your swag a little bit. I can't stand pretty boys. Yeah
Yeah, no, I cannot stand pretty boys. No, because you kind of you succeeded kind of despite your looks
I would say. Yeah, a little bit, but like people still think I'm hot as fuck. Like, it's one of the
Yeah, that kind of weird hot thing. Yeah, yeah. You can turn someone into a thrall.
Yeah, pretty much. True. Yeah. Uh, if- Crazy ass abilities. Here's a question. If, uh,
yo, if McDonald's did a Dracula meal, like what would that be, you think? Damn, Dracula meal, like,
so when I was a kid, right, like I love chicken McNuggets. Yeah. And like the older I get,
I'm like, "Yo, what are they putting in that shit?"
Like, I'm becoming curious about that kind of stuff now.
- True.
- It's the pink slime.
- That dude, I saw that shit, Miss Super Million, or what is it called, McMillions, or Super
Size Me.
- The Founders?
- Oh, yeah.
- Never mind.
- The guy that eats McDonald's every day for a hundred years.
- That movie fucked me up.
- Dude, I was like, "I'm not eating there anymore."
You know what I mean?
- Yeah, yeah.
- But then you end up, "I'm gonna come home."
- But then I'm drunk as fuck, like, "You gotta have a burger."
- Yeah, true.
- You get the Casamigos in you, you're like, "Ah."
- I do, Casamigos Gold is where it's at.
- Is that your favorite?
- I like gold, I'll do silver on the holidays.
- Oh, shit.
- I love tequila.
But, yo, my meal would probably be just like
tall ass Diet Coke with vodka in it.
- Whoa.
- Yeah, just like crazy as a Big Mac,
like no cheese, no dairy for me.
And then just like McFlurry, M&M.
- You're off the dairy?
- Yeah, it fucks with my system.
- What's with the McFlurry though?
- The McFlurry, well the McFlurry.
(laughing)
What the problem is, bro, is that the cheese,
whatever cheese, quote unquote,
you can't see me on the pod,
but the cheese is not like real cheese.
- Oh, got it.
- So whatever's in that, but the milk they use is like,
I think it's like powdered or something.
- Yeah, it's like fake dairy.
- So it gets rid of the stuff you're allergic to.
- Plus you pop a lactaid.
- Yeah, yeah, exactly, pop a lactaid.
- Pop a lactaid, you're good, right?
Yeah.
- I bet when that shit was invented,
were like damn dude changed my life food is so fucking good now true much better
than it used to be yeah what was what you would you come up on I've been
around for a minute right so like hundreds hundreds and hundreds of years
yeah so it used to be like beats like potatoes like water like an ale yeah you
know crazy-ass crusty bread yeah all that bread you fuck with hard tech hard
tech yo when I was in Civil War yeah. Which side did you fight for in the Civil War? North
bro you did. Of course I started that shit. Really? Yes dude. I might be evil but I respect
all human beings. Wow that's beautiful. Thank you. Were you a big, did you ever drink grog
back when that was around? Dude grog with all the pirate folk? No I didn't really fuck
with those guys. And women. It was a mix. Mad respect. Did you ever have like a pig
with an apple in its mouth. I always wanted to have that. They still do that shit at certain
feasts. They'll still do that. He's getting nervous around you bro. No that's all good.
You're probably the biggest guest we've ever had. No really? You guys met other celebrities?
We kind of had a line on Frankenstein's monster but he's like real slippery. He kind of goes
Frank Sinatra, he's not all there either. He's kind of like, he got all fucked up.
I was gonna ask you about him. Those piercings are crazy.
Did you like know him like after y'all were kind of like popping off?
So yeah, I mean I can go through it, but he basically like blew up hella to a way where
it's like, you know like if you get famous at a certain age, like you stay that age?
He like basically became an adult the minute he was born because he was reanimated. So
So he became famous immediately, no life experience, busted women, models, money, it all started
to fuck with him so bad.
I respect him but I just cannot deal with him anymore.
I feel bad for him.
He let the fame change him.
He really did.
That's what I like about you, you didn't.
You just kind of stay the same.
I kind of own that shit.
I like to get fucked up.
I like to be in public, like with celebrities.
I like to be evil.
- Like it's not like a,
you're not trying to hide it from anybody.
- No, I'm not trying. - You are who you are.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Except for the sun, trying to hide it from the sun, I guess.
- Oh, thanks for doing this inside.
- Yeah, of course, anytime.
- Yeah, of course.
- Dude, I gotta ask, if you could live inside any book,
like what book would you wanna live your life inside of?
- I know it's not like,
I know we don't like the author anymore for good reason,
But if I could be in the world of Harry Potter,
- Damn, yeah.
- I would be chilling at Hogwarts.
- Because you're like, you'd be like a professor
or a student or like?
- I would be a student and move up to being a professor
and live there my whole life.
- Well you're like super into like, castle culture.
- I love the occult, yeah.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Speaking of Harry Potter, what house would you be in?
- Dude, good, I think about this every day, for real.
Probably Slytherin based on my behaviors, but like,
if I could choose, like of course Gryffindor.
you know what I mean? Because they get the most respect.
Like Harry.
You're the main character, right?
I do have main character syndrome.
Damn. I mean, who doesn't from time to time?
What house would you guys be in?
I think...
I mean, I took the quiz.
You did? On Pottermore?
Yeah, I got Hufflepuff.
I'd probably be like dual majors in Ravenclaw and Hufflepuff.
That's not how it works though.
I'd probably be Slytherin too.
I'd probably be Slytherin again just based on my actions in life.
in life and also because like I don't know like you're kind of an idol of mine
you dude like honestly yeah like you've been influenced it's crazy we got you
on here I know yeah I'm like well I love doing this type of shit
yeah like talking with normalize people like you guys like who was like your
idol growing up though you probably wouldn't have heard of him I knew this
guy named Fedor. How did you know Fedor? He's been dead like 400 years. Oh my god. He grew
up in my village and he was so sick. Really? Hella tall, hella dark and handsome, Spanish
complexion. Damn. And he just was like so, he was like one of the first to be reading
in our village. He's like your OG? Yeah. Wow. He passed the game down to you. He did, yeah
he did. I don't even know if he knew what kind of influence he had on me but it was
into like blood and shit? Nah, most people once they figured it once I got afflicted
yeah by this thing that I have yeah Dracula syndrome I basically got
excommunicated from my village like they don't help me anymore I don't I've been
back there like not allowed they have like all this system set up I can't go
in. Really? They got pitchforks and shit? Garlic and all this type of shit I don't like. Man that's
fun that you like can't even go back to like yeah old haunts and shit that's crazy. Yeah.
Speaking of, you know, I mean 400 years, I mean you've been around, you've been around
the block, you know, what's like the worst thing you've ever seen?
Oh shit.
The worst thing I've ever seen, basically World War I, I was fighting in the trenches.
This like, I mean it's fucked up, right?
So like we were hungry, I don't have to eat, right?
So I actually was eating good, World War I, because it was like fresh blood all the time.
So you're like, you hit every war because it's like fucking...
I also feel patriotic for whatever country I'm living in.
Oh, okay.
That one I really wanted to know.
What did you fight for in World War I?
World War I, I was with the Germans.
Oh, that's a better war to be with the Germans.
They weren't fighting for as...
They weren't Nazis yet.
They were chilling a little bit.
Yeah, they just had some qualms with the war.
It's where I was raised.
I had to go back and kind of...
True.
Yeah.
But, so yeah, I saw some crazy...
Do you see how many horses died in World War I?
Yeah, oh man.
Do you have a soft spot for horses?
I have a soft spot for horses and I saw a horse get taken down.
Damn, dude.
By a cannon.
That's fucking awful.
A cannon?
Yeah, where there is horse shit.
It was near the end of the war, it's like there's no the ancient shit.
They ran out of bullets and started pulling out the cannons.
That's so fucked.
It sucks.
I hate to see that.
I don't even like to bring that shit up.
I mean, you know, just somebody that's led such an interesting life, I want to get all
the...
Yeah, I mean, it's about the highland.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, we were talking about that.
- Yeah, like we were supposed to be bringing up something crazy.
- Yeah, dive deep I guess, right?
- It's for sure all good.
I did fight for the Americans and the British
in World War II.
- Okay, that's good.
- So yeah.
- Did you like start out in England
or like were you like in America
and then like decided to go over to England
so that you could go fight?
- Yeah, well actually both sides wanted me so bad
that I just got to wear like, you know,
I got to wear both flags.
- Oh, Dan Jersey swap, yeah.
- Yeah, exactly.
Well, you know, I mean, enough about like, I don't want to, you know, keep bringing up
wars and shit.
I don't want to get too into that.
What do you order for the table?
Dude, for the table, I'm ordering like, you know, those, I forget what they're called,
but they're, it's wine, but they bring it in those like, those glass things with the
spout and then you like pour it from super high up into everybody's mouths.
Oh, true.
Do you guys not know about this?
No, we're going to different restaurants, I guess.
I think I've seen it in a movie.
Oh bro, yeah I'm sure it's some like X-Games type movie.
Speaking of restaurant, have you had the Golden Tomahawk Steak and is it worth it?
Oh shit, no I haven't.
No?
Yeah.
You haven't been to Salt Bae's place?
No, not yet.
Dude, I know the guy.
Yeah?
So yeah, but I haven't been.
Is it still open?
I think so.
I think he's opening more.
Oh he is?
Yeah, I think he's doing really well actually.
He's such an inspiration as well.
Yeah, he's one of your biggest...
He's great, I mean he's just so kind.
Really?
You guys haven't met him?
No, super empathetic, super kind, like great attitude.
That's the nicest dude you'll meet.
Yeah.
Wow.
Speaking of like cool guys, like who are like your guys?
Yeah.
Like who'd you, like besides Fedor.
Besides Fedor, so yeah I guess in terms of like you want me in actors and shit or like
musicians?
Just people who inspire you.
Well like.
Yeah it could be any, I mean it could be people younger than you.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean most people are.
guess like George Washington, like John Adams, like Thomas Jefferson, like James
Monroe. Those first five were so sick. Yeah, dude, they crushed it.
Yeah. Did you ever party with them? I don't like talking about that because it might change
people's minds about the founding fathers. Really? Oh man. I mean, you know Hancock was
like a party animal. Dude, Hancock was, let's just say he was a little different. Yeah.
Yeah, that's all I'll say.
Kind of a Farley type.
He was like, dude, once you got a little wine liquor in him,
like goodbye, like you're laughing your ass off all night.
Yeah, so sick.
I mean, you can just tell from the--
I mean, tell from the signature.
Yeah, yeah.
He's so big.
It's a lot of flourish.
It's a lot of swag.
He thought--
True.
Is it true that he thought that he was just autographing it?
He did, because he was the top dude.
So just people were handing him shit all the time.
And he was like, oh, yeah.
Exactly. Sunglasses inside type. Did they have those back then?
What? Sunglasses? They had like, you just had to hold like your hand in front of your face.
Oh, okay. So you do that inside? Yeah. So sick, dude.
That's so crazy. Man, it would be a fly on the wall at one of the
founding fathers parties. You realize they were drinking during that process. Oh, yeah.
I heard they were. Smoking. Oh, yeah, dude. I heard they were
toking, too. Talk about OG Kush. Oh, yeah. That is absolutely OG.
True yeah, yeah, man. What was weed like back then? Weed was super sticky back then it was so different like
It just would like one puff you're like to the moon really
Yeah, but did they like know about the moon? I guess they knew about the moon. We knew about the moon
We had no idea the implications it would have yeah. Yeah for sure the implications of moon would have yeah
Yeah, and I mean we haven't even learned everything yet really yeah, I mean coming from you
I mean you've lived through a lot of like I feel like scientific changes
So yeah, you think everything's gonna gonna change again. We're gonna. What do you think the next big like technology?
We're gonna get is I do think like you know about the alien tic-tacs. They saw hovering above the Navy. Oh, yeah
The goal is closed this last summer, but oh yeah, yeah, tic-tac objects that appeared into our reality. Yeah
Yeah, it's the tip of the iceberg disclosures happening in front of our very eyes
That's all I gotta say like wow they're warming us up to drop the big revelation
that we are not alone.
- Wow, that's gonna be crazy.
- That's all I'll say.
- Okay, I bet you got some inside info,
you've been around long enough.
- Yeah, I don't wanna like--
- And you've been up there also,
like flying around and shit.
- I do fly around and shit, yeah.
- Yeah, seen some crazy shit, I'm sure.
- Yeah, I do.
- Do you prefer,
all right, what do you prefer?
Flying dolo in the sky,
by your own accord,
or fucking G1 private jet?
- It depends on my mood, right?
mood right so like some nights and up there like listening to neutral milk
hotel like just flying around like yeah I'm sad as fuck in my feelings yeah
China Japan North America Mexico just like crying my ass off yeah really shit
it hits hard just thinking about like I've known so many people that died like
yeah you know like you guys probably know like one grandma that's not I hope that
didn't happen but I know hundreds and thousands of people that have gone so
It's a crazy burden.
What else gets you in your feels?
Just like sad ass movies like Sam Private Ryan, a lot of Spielberg shit.
Well I'm sure, well I won't get back into that but I'm sure that shit reminds you.
It was so realistic.
What about Take Care, do you relate to that album at all?
Oh Drake's Take Care?
- Like mobbed up at the table, like sipping.
Sipping like, are you a Hennessy or a Cavassier?
- I like Cavassier.
- Nice, man it tastes.
- With a little bit of, it's like, I do like a spritz,
so it's like that in a bunch of seltzer water.
- Whoa, whoa, that's strong.
Yeah, so like you gotta be sitting there.
I mean, you've been, had ups and downs,
you know, to say the least.
- Oh yeah.
- But like at the top of the top, does it feel like lonely?
- Dude, it does, but then you start talking with someone
that's like a little more on the ground level,
like a busboy or like, you know what I mean?
Like a taxi driver, like, or like, you know,
and they're smarter than all these people
that you know that are at the top.
And then you realize like, yo,
like the hierarchy is all fucked up.
You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
- I mean, like speaking of like loneliness too,
like you're one of like the most eligible bachelors
in New York City.
Like you got any ladies in your life?
- I'm like doing a little thing right now
where I'm like, I need to be alone
because I've got my heart broken too many times.
- Yeah? - Yeah.
- Any like really badly, any really bad heartbreaks
that you'd be like comfortable talking about?
- You know, on a day at our mass.
- Yeah? - Wow.
- That's all I'll say, just like you can see in my eyes.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- It was a fucked up situation.
- Not like Kiss and Tell, but I can imagine.
- She went Ben Affleck, me,
and now she's with someone else,
but some other celebrity, but.
- Damn, that's crazy.
- Yeah, I had no idea.
- Knives out.
- Yeah. - She's some knives out.
A little birdie told me you've been dabbling in amateur photography.
Yeah, DSLR type shit.
Yeah, so this is a two-pronged question.
What kind of stuff do you like photographing?
And is there anything that you can't do?
So anything I can't do with photography?
Just can't do in general.
You seem to be a man of many interests.
A bit of a renaissance man.
So for photography, I love doing party photography.
But I like going incognito, right?
wear like the, um, you know, like the, like a mask or whatever.
So people sure it's easier now.
So those photos that you took at the, yeah. Oh,
the photos you took at the, uh, the JPEG mafia show, like JPEG mafia,
his music, I don't understand it, but I'll do like,
it does make me feel crazy. Yeah. Yeah. Uh,
but I love doing the shit where it's like, I mess with like settings.
And so like, you know, like when you do a photo and then you move the camera,
hella fast with like the long exposure the lights look all streaky and shit.
Oh yeah. I'll be doing that shit with every photo. Yeah. It's kind of interesting. Is it
weird that like do you like photography because you can never be in a
photo? I do because it's kind of like yeah I can't be in a photo, I can't be in
a mirror, I can't be in a long-term relationship. I'm proving that. Yeah. It sucks.
I have commitment issues. That may be the thing I can't do is you know give up
enough of my own time and myself to be in a long-term relationship.
Is it more about a time management thing or is it more because like
like you're Dracula right? Like you got like hecka like virgins like being
thrown at you constantly. You know what I mean? Yeah. Like how do you
avoid that temptation in a long-term relationship? It's mostly like it's time
management mostly I would say. Yeah I have crazy ass ADHD like just got
diagnosed in the 90s like damn I got it bad yeah so I just like can't focus and
shit and I'm like I'm like learning I'm selfish but I need to get over it and
yeah la-dee-da are you in therapy yeah hella nice cognitive behavioral therapy
Wow whoa yeah Wow it works yeah yeah but I don't fuck with medicine true yeah yeah
did you do self-medicate like yeah alcohol and music all that shit yeah
What about like meditation?
Yeah, I do that sometimes.
I'm having a panic attack.
You struggle with anxiety?
Crazy anxiety, dude.
I think you're alive for a certain amount of time and you're like,
"I just want to fucking die so bad."
And you can't and you know you're here forever.
There's just so much pressure to be alive for that long.
It's crazy, man.
Do you still ever talk to Van Helsing or any of those hunter guys?
We were beefing hard for a minute and then now we're good.
I just noticed he's dead.
He's been dead for a minute, but his grandchildren are all like trust fund kids, trying to be
actors and shit.
I don't want to drop their names, but I still will see them in a movie or see them open
a new restaurant and I'm like...
You ever run into them at parties and shit?
Sometimes because they do have good taste, I will admit that.
There is some kind of generational like just tension between us because he tried to kill me many a time.
Yeah. I feel you must have like some crazy like stalkers, some crazy fans, right?
I mean, someone your level, right?
I need to get my lawyer might be pissed off that I'm talking about it.
But oh, yeah, I do. Yeah.
Yeah, it's like ongoing legal shit.
Is there like, but probably like no paparazzi though, right?
Because paparazzi can't touch me.
It doesn't work.
Yeah. Yeah.
So they just like photograph all my cars and shit.
Yeah, yeah, which is I mean, hey, yeah more fucking photos right Clarence. I know more McLaren's like yeah as well
I like looking at those pigs. Yeah, what's the way on like any given Saturday night?
Yeah, like I mean, I know that's like a big night for you, right?
Yeah, especially in the in the winter the Sun goes down early. You're like, what's what whip are you hopping in head to 40/40 Club?
I like to go incognito. You know, yeah, so that's why I'm in the blacked-out Range Rover. Mm-hmm with the like
Crazy music playing. What year? It's like the one that Chris Moltisanti had.
Whoa! That's sick.
Like the exact one? It's the same one from the set.
Like I fucked with those guys. Holy shit.
Big Sopranos fan? Yeah, I love them.
I love their lifestyle, like all those guys.
Yeah. It's awesome.
Dude, that's sick. Yeah.
This one's kind of like open-ended, but like
what does paradise mean to you?
Mmm...
Paradise to me means like
Paradise means that I would be able to get over my intrusive thoughts.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
So that would be like me on vacation in Mexico, just on the beach, no crazy ass thoughts trying
to get to me.
Yeah.
I'm just able to relax, watch the Apatow collection, fall asleep.
Do you ever suffer from imposter syndrome?
- Heavily, dude, because can you imagine what it's like
to see your face in media all over the place
and everybody gets it wrong.
- Right. - True, true.
- Do you know what I mean?
Kids are dressing up as you, they're getting it wrong.
Nosferatu.
- The guys, I mean, they made you so ugly in that.
- I know. - What the fuck was that about?
- I know, dude, it's just like--
- Yeah, they had Willem Dafoe play you once.
- I liked Willem, but, or I like him as an actor,
but without all the shit.
- Who's your favorite, like which actor you think
like gotten you the best? Man, so like Gary Oldman when he becomes when he turns
into like the young me because they show him old and yeah when Stoker right yeah
so I feel like there's a touch of him that I relate to or I fuck with but it's
hard to answer because I still haven't seen like an accurate depiction.
He had like though he I feel like it's the only portrayal that understood kind
how lavish you are, how into fashion you are.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- You know, like who are some other celebrities
who are like your fashion icons right now?
- Fashion icons for celebrities like Will Smith,
let's see, Owen Wilson back in the 2000s
when he was on the come up.
'Cause people don't realize,
but he was being asked to model and shit,
he was turning it down.
- Yeah. - Damn.
- What about like Jack Harlow, you fuck with him?
- Harlow, all these young guys, I do like them,
but there's something about the Generation Z
that I don't understand. Yeah. Are you on Tik Tok? Yeah, but I like don't
understand it, right? But I'm addicted. So it's like, I'm like, what the hell?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Just sitting there scrolling in the morning and
list doom scrolling. Yeah. I bet you like doom scrolling. Yeah. Oh,
because of the horse. Yeah, that algorithm is twisted. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
It's kind of scary. That's kind of having every fucking file on your
phone. Jesus Christ. Terrifying right? It's terrifying dude. Yeah. That's the real horror.
Yeah like what scares Dracula? You know like what's your like what's your biggest fear?
Yeah. Famine. Like. You've probably seen a lot of that right? A lot of that over the
years and I feel like that's coming back with like global warming which by the
way is real. Mm-hmm. And like that shit is gonna touch our world in a way that I'm
gonna have to be around for this shit right? Yeah. Me and your children are gonna
have to see the world come to the brink of collapse. Damn. Is that a scary thought?
Very scary. Yeah. Because I don't work well with kids. So you know. So you're gonna be out there
all these snot-nosed brats. Oh yeah trying to fix carbon. And they're gonna be and you know
they're gonna like yeah they're like phones set up doing tick-tock dances and shit. I mean some of
these kids probably never even heard of you too. I know a lot of them haven't so it's and I'm okay
with that. My ego isn't hurt. Yeah they probably heard of Bella and Edward and
shit. Yeah. What do you think of them? What do you think of Twilight Generation?
Did that fuck with your image at all? So here's the thing right is that I do
get like residuals when people get interest in vampires because they did
like set me up with like some of these IPs and so whenever interest in vampire
spikes I benefit right? True. Financially. But the way that I think what I didn't
like was what Twilight taught kids about relationships. Like Edward is kind of
this abusive MF-er, like Bella is staying... it's just like that book, I don't like
that series. Just because you're like a vampire doesn't mean you're mad toxic
in relationships. Yeah exactly, yeah right exactly. So I don't know. That makes sense.
Yeah but you don't shine or anything right? That's a kind of fufu. That is, oh yeah. I do
I do love Robert Pattinson though. He's about to rock the Batman.
That's going to be so tight.
I can't. I watched that trailer.
I bet you're going there opening night.
The Riddler too.
Paul Dano.
Oh shit.
When the question mark's in the coffee.
That's nuts.
I just can't wait for the riddles in the movie.
Me too.
You're famously well traveled. You can fly wherever, anytime of day. Supermoon status.
What's your top three favorite cities?
Paris, Tokyo, and Berlin.
Really?
Yeah.
That's a fast answer.
I'm not sure.
Really? Yeah. That's a fast answer. Well because A) Paris, fashion, Berlin, clubs,
Tokyo, the crazy-ass food that they have there. You ever eat this food? You like Japanese food a lot?
Love Japanese food. Sushi fan? Love sushi, love ramen. You fuck with like anime and
manga? I do like it. I just watched like Attack on Titan and I was doing like
yeah I'm like trying to get into it more. Yeah. I just have some time on my hands. You said like
clubs in Berlin. I'm sure you've been to Berghain.
Those clubs, have you all been there? No.
Can't say I have.
They do it differently over there.
Yeah.
That's all I'll say.
You been to the bottom floor of Berghain?
I'm nodding yes.
And you've seen.
There's some shit there that, I'm a vampire right, there's some shit there that freaks
me out.
Damn.
Yeah.
Some people getting freaky in Berlin.
Freaky animal it's just like there's some so much crazy-ass shit going on true. Was it like that in the 40s the
40s
Yeah, it kind of went a different way. Yeah, people got fucked up in a different way back then
But it was equally freaky damn that's crazy that it's been freaky that long. Yeah, we've been freaky forever
Let's do two truths and a lie. Oh, yeah. Yeah, sure
All right
Okay
Okay, first first thing I'll say
My parents are divorced.
Second thing, I have over $10 million.
Third, I have over $12 million.
Whoa.
Okay.
I think...
You honestly, like I don't mean to be like psychoanalyzing you and shit, you do not strike
me as a child of divorce.
personally that's my guess. How do I tell you? Are you guys gonna guess too?
Yeah you guys should guess. You know what, honestly I don't get that vibe
from you. You seem like a single child, right? You have kind of single child syndrome a little bit.
It leads you to like kind of act out like this crazy way sometimes but I
think that you have like a real good support system or at least you did.
Yeah, you're probably still like boys with your parents like as an
adult yeah. That's so that's so you want me to tell you now? Yeah. All right so
truth of the matter is my parents were divorced, are divorced, fucked me up
heavily. I've worked a long time to like try to present this image that you guys
are seeing. I had hella brothers and sisters I had like 14 they died early
on in my life and so yeah sad but and then the lie you know the lies that I
I have over 10 million because I have over 12.
Damn!
So it's not 11, it's over 12.
Over 12, yeah.
That's big money numbers.
That's still over 10 though, right?
Yeah, I never fucked with math that heavily.
I'm right brain.
Like reading, like talking.
Creative stuff.
Creative, yeah.
That makes sense.
All right.
Would you call yourself like a creative?
Yeah, in a sense.
Like I never stop creating and I never will.
A lot of shit I do will never see the light of day.
Really?
art and shit I write in my notebooks.
It's like, that's for me.
You do poetry?
I do poetry with just like pictures that I put together.
Oh, so like visual poetry.
Damn.
Wow, I would have never guessed.
You ever make like a zine?
In the 90s and 80s, when that shit was really tight.
But this like zine revival that's happening now, like people doing zines, it's like the
internet makes it, just put it on the internet.
True.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, just make it a PDF.
Why do we gotta read all this shit?
Just blog it.
Right.
You know you fuck with tumblr. I'm at the cutting edge of every new network that comes out tumblr
2007 I was on it damn Facebook 2007 now. I'm on this new shit. What's the new shit?
Okay, and tick-tock. I thought you'd like new of like a new thing that's popping up if I did
I wouldn't tell you because I want to be the first oh yeah
Be honest. Are you are you on Raya? Oh?
Yes, I am you whoa
Who's the craziest person you seen already is Bella Hadid whoa?
Whoa! She's on it. She's still on there? Didn't match because I guess she had some shit against
vampires or whatever. Damn. That's fucked up. Yeah. It's probably where she's from, right?
Yeah. Different culture there. Different cultures in there. They're taught to fear. Yeah. To
fear the vampire. Yeah. With us, I don't know, I didn't grow up, my parents never told me,
they almost said nothing about vampires. Really? Yeah. That's why I'm so glad you blew up like
you did because like true like we can see like a vampire yeah like like a famous
vampire and kind of get it you know without having to be taught can I ask
you guys a question yeah of course be honored like what do I seem like what
you thought I would be like I mean honestly better yeah I was honestly kind
of scared coming I was worried you wouldn't be like so like down-to-earth
or yeah but like true I don't mean it like yeah I don't know I kind of thought
you come in and there's like a 20% chance you'd be like, ah, like try to hit me or some shit.
Yeah.
Right. Yeah. Speaking of what's...
I was like expecting to be scared straight up.
What's your favorite...
I'm sorry, but like...
Yeah, like you could check my, my like, my like blood pressure right now. Like it's...
I can sense it. Like it's normal.
Yeah, it's normal. I mean, I have high blood pressure, but it's normal for me.
Yeah. Yeah. Cause you're like working out, I'm looking at the jewel and all this.
Oh, you notice it? Yeah. You think I'm working out?
I love that shit.
You see my pull up bar?
Yep.
Yep. You know, I do work on that.
That's awesome, man.
Speaking of blood, what's your favorite blood type?
Favorite blood type? That's a question I get all the time.
Type O negative, A, B.
I would guess O negative because it's rare.
You know what? It all tastes like... I don't have type sensors.
You don't have a good palate?
It tastes like blood. Everything tastes like blood.
You've been eating it for fucking thousands of years.
Diet has changed some of the taste.
There's a little richer now or there's a little more...
You know what I mean?
But yeah, I wouldn't say I have a preference.
I like do hate to kill people and do that.
But I gotta do it.
Do you like, are you scared about like microplastics in blood now?
My doctor has asked me about that and said like that's something I should watch out for.
But like I haven't noticed.
I mean it's gotta be better than like when like polio was coming up and shit.
Like that must have been some nasty blood.
I had a lot of scares with different diseases through the years.
Like the crazy diseases.
but I've been you know you can't kill me yeah I'm really not in the end and if you
did kill me I'd welcome that shit cuz I'm to be honest I'm tired of being
alive yeah damn yeah that's like that's I like that's it but that's not sad or
anything yeah I've been here for so long that it's like when's this gonna be when
we let's wrap this up yeah yeah it's hard to hear from a hero of mine you
know yeah I hope I never make it to that point yeah it's like understand but I
I get it. Circumstances like... People just have a hard time understanding other people's
stories. That's how I feel.
And I think that you're like... Talking to you has been insanely eye opening.
Yeah, well thanks for having me guys. It's been so fun.
And I guess one more question.
Sure.
If you could eat one of our blood, who would it be? Be real.
Patrick. Really? Yeah. What? Why? Because you got just got done skateboarding and you
can't believe it. Like I can smell you differently. And like you do smell kind of good dude. Like
oh yeah. That's Old Spice Fiji. Is that Fiji? Yeah. Oh shit. You fuck with Old Spice Fiji?
Yeah. That shit. That shit is good. It reminds me of Hawaii. I've never been though but like
it like the vibe that I get from it is like totally Hawaii. Yeah. I mean Fiji, Hawaii area.
We should all ghost, like if you guys have any.
Yo, I'd be so down to be such an honor.
Yeah, I will say too, I'm glad that you like you picked Patrick,
because like we did like get you a gift.
Did you?
Yeah, for guesting on this.
Oh shit.
Yeah, you can like kill Patrick right now.
What?
Ay.
Yeah, I mean.
No, no, we planned this out already.
No, no, no, dude.
I mean, I'm not going to kill Patrick.
No, dude, come on.
Yeah, I got my own system.
Dog, it would be an honor, but like, I don't know.
I got like, just bite him.
Nah man, like I got like.
You know I'm like doing intermittent fasting and my feeding window doesn't start until like 8pm.
I do night time.
Oh, ok.
Alright, well hey, that's understandable. Patrick, I think maybe next time.
Yeah, we'll figure something out. Next guest.
Yeah.
Whoever the next guest is can just eat you.
You guys are twisted.
What the hell?
Nah, we're just trying to impress you, honestly.
It worked.
Well, is there anything you want to plug before you leave?
No, just like yeah, if you see me on the street like don't be afraid to say hi like I'm super chill and
Yeah, I don't got anything else. Yeah, you haven't started a pod yet. They haven't got you with that
I guess I mean this went so well that I feel like
You got to do it
Yeah, I mean last I mean guess last question. Who's your co-host be co-host would be oh shit
Well, he said ear wolf. So like, I mean, it's gotta be like Ben Schwartz, right?
Yeah, maybe Schwartz on the mic. Yeah, like I was just cracking our asses up the whole time
Just like also like that feeling of like doing an inside joke that like, you know, nobody's gonna get
All right, man, thank you so much
You're a man catch you next time. All right. Happy Halloween. Happy Halloween
[EVIL LAUGHTER]