You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
AHHHHH!
NOOOO!
Mmm.
Guys, I have to go.
No!
You have to go right now?
I have to go.
I wait- we've been talking, but I've been meaning to tell you guys something.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah?
I'm ruined.
You're ruined?
What happened?
I lost it all.
What?
No, you lost it all?
Every last dollar.
Every drop?
No.
Not really, right?
What about the coins?
It was the Bitcoin casino, wasn't it?
The goddamn Bitcoin casino, dude.
Are you kidding?
I lost $40.
No, dude.
I lost $40 fucking dollars at the Bitcoin casino, dude.
Dude, listen man, they got these slots, these fruity delicious slots.
They have these gorgeous grapes and these plump plums.
They got glamorous grapes and sumptuous strawberries.
How do you refuse?
I have to say, I lost some money gambling today too.
Really?
I lost $20 at the arcade.
Whoa.
Oh my gosh.
By playing the games.
What game were you playing?
Dude, I played Terminator Salvation.
I played the Aliens.
I played House of the Dead.
I played Big Buck.
I played...
I mean that's not really a loss.
I didn't get a single ticket.
Yeah those are the games you get the tickets for.
That's why I lost them.
You should have just played the ticket games.
You should have played Skee-Ball.
$20 worth of Skee-Ball and then got a rubber ball.
You know how many tickets you would get?
Dude this place, I was at fucking Salem Willows.
Have you ever been there?
No.
I went there the first time today.
And you know how much it was fucking 800 tickets for a bouncy ball like this.
Damn, that's fucked.
It's insane.
Honestly, like when I did, they did have, they had, you could pay one token and they have
little animatronic monkeys that danced around and play a song.
Dude, so I did do that.
I'm thinking about it like honestly, like gambling, like slot machines is a more entertaining
and more cost effective like form of gaming than arcades.
Okay, but did you get the bonus game where you have to shoot 35 electric eels with a plastic rifle?
No, you didn't. They don't have that on slots. I got a bonus game. It's for lolly. You get to press the button at the
End of the Terminator gun and it shoots a grenade and blows up the Terminators. All right
Let me let me paint a picture for you. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. All right. All right first row six gorgeous grapes
Second row two pink jellies two lollipops, right?
Next couple rows nothing, but then bang bang two more lollipops. I'm in the bonus. That's okay
That's 10 free spins. Wait! The 10 free spins begin. I start getting gorgeous jellies pink and blue. I start getting
Yellows, that's what I call bananas when I'm gaming and I'm starting
I'm getting so many bananas and then when they all drop then a bomb a candy bomb explodes
That's a multiplier, right? And that was on an 8 cent win. I just won 80 cents on a $40 bet.
Let me ask you this though, okay?
How are you gonna reload? Okay, are you put your point your plastic gun outside the screen and pull the little trigger?
Do you touch the clip? Do you touch the magazine? Do you?
Reloaded the Bitcoin casino you go to coinbase.com put it in order for $16 worth of aetherium
Okay, ask you a question when you're playing on your on your your breakfast slots or whatever
They are and you twist the throttle
That's breakfast
You guys don't have fruit and candy for breakfast. No, okay. I only play the fruit flavored slots. Okay, there's fruit
Bonanza and crazy fruit crazy fruit is the best because it also has
Okay, but let me tell you this let me paint you a picture here
They got this arcade. I was that they got a giant touchscreen that you touch your finger on
Do you know it flies up in the air for you?
Wine it's fruits. Okay. They have fruit ninja giant mode big big screen giant TV
They had actually pretty but you know, I went to I went to
Funland in Nashua, New Hampshire for my nephew's birthday on Valentine's Day. Uh-huh, and I love hanging out with my nephew for
He was born on Valentine's Day. It's his birthday. So I was at the I was at the arcade. I won
So you give him chocolates twice. I
900 tickets yo
Lot on what there's this game where you like drop a coin?
Oh that dude you're at it. You're the first guy who ever won tickets on that dude
I spun I got I got a fucking I got a jackpot every time I wonder was it the Wonder Wheel
The one that spins and it goes into the slot or was it the one where it falls and it sweeps them off the edge
It's the one it spins around and you drop a coin and the coin has to land over the sensor for the jackpot
Yeah, and I figured out how to do it to get the jackpot every time. Yeah
Yeah, that's I was really getting the one where it spins like vertically and you put that you put the coin down coin down
I just want to wear a belt
But you know the one where it shoots it with the conveyor belt and it like has to shoot into the jackpot slot
I don't know that one, but I won 3100 tickets. Oh
Uncle that day I fucking about spinning wheels. Does that bore you cuz I have some news for you about what slots are
Hey, sorry, I was just playing crazy time in my brain. So you weren't yeah crazy
Okay, Oh crazy time. I got crazy time 50 times multiplier
Let me tell you about crazy time
Okay, crazy time is a game like wheel of fortune in the way that there's a wheel and a live host in Latvia
They swap out every 15 minutes
Because the chat in the big coin casino started saying really mean things and trying to find their address
They swap them out every 15 minutes, search "Crazy Time" you'll like it.
And if you get "Crazy Time" they go to a new realm.
They go into a green screen world, they walk over to it, and then they do a second, even larger wheel,
and you get buku bunches of cash.
Okay, but I will say that today I played Big Buck HD,
and they had a live trail guide named Anita,
and she was beautiful and her stomach was exposed before the wildebeest adventure
but did you play a tiger king mega ways
i did shoot a lion with joe exotic
wait hold up
yeah
what that's right three joe exotics
i also played
i was looking at that tiger king slot and i was like
uh... uh...
really wonder if they were getting cleared like is it did boyfriend
it's like although
all the blueberries in the grapes in that game are like all the cast of that show
and i was like you just please don't include
the package that himself and it's not funny if they do
but uh... uh... they also have a christmas carol one where if you get
scrooges
their wild 'cause it's more wild and as you know it is wild
uh... i don't know if you and i bet you didn't have a
the sopranos pinball machine at the bitcoin casino they had that at the
time i did not remember that they did have that at the time yeah you know what
i got you know what i can i'm fucking i'm a one up both of you one up i bet i bet
neither of you my gamer brain i bet neither of you have a hundred percent on
holiday in cambodia at the funland guitar hero stand the funland guitar hero
kiosk that's yeah yeah yeah on that in Nashua you play holiday in Cambodia on
easy you play guitar hero 3 on that one difficulty where you just strum no that's
guitar here a world tour they didn't I mean if we're talking here three if we're
talking about cool records and crazy high scores you never you'll never guess who
had the high score on time crisis for at the arcade I went to today who number
one score Trump no it said are you kidding me I'm not gonna let him in that
place? You know I think that that would be you know there's a lot of people there
who are wearing Blue Lives Matter shirts like a lot more than I would have
expected yeah yeah but there was also there was a there was another one of
those student games that was called police trainer and it said property of
the Metro City Police Department on it. There was a pretty cool it was running
the DDR. The nice thing about an arcade is that you could have somebody as
as illustrious as Donald Trump come.
And then you could also have such a low life
as somebody named Ass.
- Yeah, yeah. - In the same place
at the same time.
Isn't that beautiful?
- There was a, I went to King's in, where is that?
Linfield?
King's in Linfield, the bowling place
for my brother's bachelor party.
And I was playing this game, it was called Beach Defense.
And I was playing it and then--
- Bachelor party playing Beach Defense, right?
- Yeah, that's true.
these bitches off of me I'm about to be married mm-hmm but I was playing that
and then my younger brother pointed out that it looked a lot like Normandy so
the whole game is like you with a Gatling gun and you're shooting people
who are storming the beach dude I mean honestly the sickest their blood was
green so I was like it's clear these are aliens I'm not a Nazi it's just I'm
killing some aliens but they weren't having it they were telling me shit ever
is to fight in a war. And you know what? I was just following orders. I was just following the orders
that the game told me to do. You're following the quarters, dude. Yeah. The sickest shit ever is to
fight in a war and then 30 years later they just make a video game about that exact thing.
And you just can play it again. Just like you played it 30 years ago. And you can try to get
a high score again. There was, do you guys remember, Pat, you've been to Lansing Games, right?
uh...
where's that
uh... it was on uh... fucking highway i think they might want rid of it
i don't think it was on
or on the bed at the names of highways 'cause i can't drive so i don't need to
uh... but they're had they had the one arcade game where you you pulled in
like a helmet on like a arm and you like pull it down and as a good visor inside
she that she was so that i was i was on the test with that you know i mean i
think that now it is right
it's called
I just looked it up, it's called VR Vortec V3.
Unless this is a different game with the same helmet.
Nowadays it'd probably be, you know what it'd be nowadays?
It'd probably be a mask that you actually pull down
and then you put over your mouth.
Put over your mouth and it would be called
just being alive right now.
It'd probably be called like Liberal Mario.
It'd be called, yeah, go into the store in New York City.
You know, in Liberal Mario,
the princess tries to rescue herself nowadays.
Yeah, that's true.
And Mario is non-binary.
He was awesome.
Yeah, that's right.
So true.
It was awesome being back in North Carolina, dude.
Nobody's messed up.
Everybody's fingering again.
Oh, dude, that's in New Hampshire.
In New Hampshire and like Maine.
Dude, when I went to Maine with my brother for his bachelor party, I went to a bachelor
party two weeks ago.
When I went to Maine, there's fucking like people just, like girls on the street like
crying.
Like, you know, like party girls crying on the street,
and you know, it's cliche as shit,
but nature is healing, you know?
You see girls throwing up in the alleyway,
and their friends like, "You need to pull it together!"
(laughter)
So good, it was so nice to see it.
- What is it, why do girls keep drinking beer
if it makes them so damn sad?
- It's not beer, it's this new 8% ABV white claw
that came out.
Surge. Mm-hmm. Tell you what man, I drink 15 beers. The most crying I'll do is I'll watch one of the two sad episodes of Futurama by myself.
Right? And I'll be like, "Oh, that damn dog! Oh, that damn clover!"
"Goddamn brother!"
"That gravestone!"
It almost brings a tear to my damn eye watching this cartoon.
I got real drunk one time and I watched a Klaus Nomi video and I started crying.
Nice. I don't know why. I probably shouldn't have admitted to that.
I was thinking about how he died and then I was like man he could have been like
the best singer in the world. Dude the most fucked up thing is I'll cry at
anything. Yeah. I cried it I like like not like breakdown but I shed a
tear-washing Better Call Saul because the brother dynamic was so beautiful to me.
Yeah dude I just started I mean me and Anister watching Breaking Bad like
because I only ever saw the first season before it's like it's good but it's
literally like just the most stupid show ever it's so fucking dumb it's so funny
that like the first episode what he makes the explosion in the the trailer
and he's like what he did the guys are trying to like kill him he's like wait
You want to know how to cook like me and then he just like puts together chemicals and makes an explosion
It's science. Yeah. Yeah, you hadn't you handle the business. I'll handle handle the chemistry
It's like wait, if you see if you got to the part where he where he created a bomb diamond and throws
this year and I was like how the fuck did anybody ever watch it and they were like
yeah they're all dressed like insane - like a fashion that was in for like two
years like yeah all this like hit the 2013 window so perfectly and he's like
unwatchable he like he like throws his fucking even space crystal on the ground
and like everybody in the building is like like the windows blow out the air
conditioning unit falls out of the fucking building everybody's covered in
like like like they look like they came out of like a coal mine yeah he just
walks out and he's like, "Nah, yeah, actually just help me. I'm the one who did the science
bomb on this drug dealer." The theme song is so funny too, like just the periodic table
and the smoke coming up and the fucking montage when they cook too and it plays some music
and just shows them filling up beakers with like, you know everybody who was watching
was like, "They're showing this on TV?" Yeah, they always have like, every other episode
there's like a five minute long fucking cooking montage that where it's like
John Goldberg
Yellow dust
Weighing rocks like a jeweler's loop on a piece of glass
Also like in the everybody like every single meth dealer is like bro this shit that you make is Loki artistic
like this. Oh yeah. Dude, so fucking dumb. None of them are just like, "Yo, that's pretty
good." They're all just like, "Yo, this is like scientifically magical, bro." This is
like, "I can like taste the science in this, fool. This is like Beethoven's Symphony of
Science over here when I smoke this drug." Yeah, dude. I mean, it's one of the greatest
shows ever. It's so fun to watch. I mean, you play like all of those shows. Like, you
go back and watch like The Wire or The Sopranos. There's so much dumb shit in those shows,
It's just like, I'm a Breaking Bad defender.
I think it's fun, dude.
I mean, yeah, if you're gonna watch a show,
you better be prepared to watch something dumb.
I don't think there are many shows
that don't have dumb stuff like that.
Yeah, definitely.
Like every--
Especially back then.
Especially, yeah, Prestige TV too,
is like, all that stuff is really dumb.
Like you really gotta--
Yeah, like that first, like that AMC run
where it was like Breaking Bad, Walking Dead, Mad Men.
Yeah, like those you know, The Walking Dead went on way too fucking long.
It's still going on, dude.
It's like the worst show.
They had spin-offs and shit.
It was not good.
I've seen the first season.
It sucks so bad.
Yeah, I watched like one or two episodes.
I was like, this is not doing anything for me.
Yeah, too much damn gore and violence.
It's not even the gore and the violence.
It's just like the stupid like, yeah, like like this is like what it's like.
It's a show made for like 13 year olds.
It's like a show where it's like.
that's a crack dot com all yet that yes it's like a whole time here is a
fucking
all this guy
he's like a redneck you kill zombies of the bow and arrow like a good like for
me i mean i just want to know how he talked for like maybe they had
character development and i said please please don't kill us please no
uh... please please let me know your resume i'm sure that they've done that
by now i'm sure they've looked at it was a zombie with a hard talk
yet but i was so flamboyant the end of the show like
you know like why are you killing all my newt frank
yeah they're just sick
yeah i think
uh... these are my
these are my my millions of brothers who all who are really at the makeup and
special effects yeah walking around killing
yeah
true yeah i look at the game style ending words like this was a this was
actually all we set this up for you
that would be sick dude
yet in his baby
was all up holograms they have a baby in that
yeah there's some that's like that uh... that was when i was like this just sucks
uh... you know it's just like
is exactly that the comics but his baby gets like
killed or some shit
and he's like
crap
and it's like a long ass scene in the show where he's just like
baby
uh... my baby is dead shit
i just feel like also if you're going to anything not only h_b_o_ or showtime or
something like just make it funny yeah just make a comedy just make it a funny
show man something kind of weird kind of funny yeah just like you know don't you
don't have to be serious all the freaking time why are you gonna put all
this damn crying on TV yeah yeah oh my this episode is so so fuck you don't my
daughter oh my wife oh we everybody in the show has cancer and they're all
addicted to drugs listen buddy like just chill you know yeah
exactly yeah playing video games that's exactly right yeah what about they say a
magic poem together in their bedroom it takes them to the land of dragons and
they're friends of dragons named Ord and Zack and Wheezy yeah maybe they add a
third character later his name is Enrique uh-huh yeah it'd be a good idea for many
shows to introduce Zack and Wheezy like you know two heads are better than one
true absolutely you know I got a very scary enemy who eats dragon eggs who
will scare you and make you hide behind the couch when you see the episode
whatever I only watch through the reflection because you're not terrified
of the egg-sealing lizard yeah nowadays you have like you know Breaking Bad and
succession all these shows whatever happened to fucking I'm going into
cyberspace and absolutely I mean I'm Gilbert Gottfried yeah and he's a bird
And he's a bird? I mean now you gotta...
You know, how much worse would that show have been if everybody had cancer and they were addicted to heroin?
AW SHIT! I'M ADDICTED TO PILLS!
And he was a bird too.
AHH! I'M ADDICTED TO PILLS!
I mean, yeah, it's so funny that...
How many times can this guy play a fucking bird?
Yeah, I know, they're calling him a surprisor!
They just call him for every bird role.
I mean, it's obvious, yeah.
like yeah I guess that makes sense because if I if you also if you gave me
if I didn't know Gilbert Gottfried was and you played his voice to me and you
were like what is that I'd probably say bird before you yeah like that's a
that's a cockatiel yeah I mean it's not a bird has been as you could yeah have
him voice a character in like in an animation or something but if there is
any other if there is a it let that's not a bird but if there's anything in
that animation that is a bird you're gonna think that the voices were switched by
accident you're right yeah bird is there in the universe he can't he has to be
right Gilbert Gilbert Godfrey can't act with a bird exactly no yeah cuz I mean
yeah you hear you hear him going like and then a bird flies by and it goes
like you're like oh well they should have got him a little bird yeah can you
can you please direct me to the nearest restaurant that's what do you think a
bird like imagine that's imagine if they like imagine if they gave if they gave
Gilbert Gottfried's voice to Jafar and then they had a different guy for the
parrot you'd be like no no yeah that's not happening you definitely can't a
parrot definitely you just can't yeah with the Gilbert Gottfried in the room
also it was this guy even on Rio or Angry Birds I don't know if Gilbert
Gottfried is in Rio I think probably he wasn't hired as a voice actor but
definitely as a consultant. It was a consultant.
[Laughter]
They just had him on set
for every line. They were like
"Do you think a bird might say that?"
Yeah. You know he was the Affleck duck.
Dude,
this is one of the most fucking
insane, like, like how have
we looked over this for so long?
I think everyone knew. I'm the second.
I've never thought about this. I've never,
I mean, I've definitely
He has three bird rolls? I'm going to his IMDb right now.
got a lot more than bird. You got a lot more bird rolls. That he's ever voiced. Let's see
here. He played Hitler in historical roasts. Oh, okay. He played in, oh never mind. Kind
of a bird. Yeah, yeah. Cheeky bird, that Hitler. Yeah, bird in the British sense. Yeah. He's
a woman. He's a girl. Yeah. He played, oh here's a role that's gonna. He played Jared Kushner
on last week tonight with John Oliver. Here's a role that's gonna freak you out.
Yeah. He played Gilbert Gottfried in Crashing. No. He played, he played a horse
in an episode of Family Guy. No, that's not okay.
Uh-huh. He was in Crashing. You can't put him as a horse. Yeah, he was in Crashing. He, um, what an awesome show.
Who else, what else? Gilbert, I, I, a thousand million Maxim models want to suck my dick
even though I'm a big fat ugly guy what am I supposed to do? I look like a I look
like a giant puppy and I need to sleep on your couch. He played he played a genie
on the Tom and Jerry show. That's a real reversal of fortune for him. He played
the grim reaper in a movie too. That one feels anti-semitic. I don't know that
grim reaper is really the role for for Gilbert Gottfried. Yeah unless it's a
bird I was also just I mean I'm creeper or squeaker and it's a bird you know
the grim screecher yeah the grim look I'm working it I'm working through the grim
beaker cuz he played Santa Claus and grim adventures of Billy and Mandy that
one is tough yeah I don't know yeah I don't know about that one that one is I
you know I'm I that's just that's doesn't sit right with me yeah yeah
there's nothing about Gilbert Gottfried and I don't know if this is
controversial he might be the least jolly man on earth
it's true I don't know that he would I would ever choose him to play Santa
Claus mm-hmm you know who'd be a great Santa Claus is um Kathy Bates I always
thought she'd be really good. She would be a good Santa. She'd be a better Mrs. Claus.
No no fuck no no talent of that level you don't give her the fucking supporting
role if they do it's a movie about mrs. Claus who would make that movie Netflix
what what she what does she do fucking bake cookies and suck dick all day
that's like the most boring movie of all time that's that's a very that's a very
closed-minded way to view mrs. Claus what what else is in this is Claus does
besides fucking make sure that Santa Claus isn't like fucking it's a movie
it's you know the night before Christmas or the night of Christmas while
Santa's out and she's getting and she's getting the house ready for next
Christmas and that's the movie. Okay so it's her cleaning. You think that's a
better like less like misogynist version? This is way less misogynist because it's
putting her in power. They should do like a they should do like a like a get hard
style movie about Mrs. Claus. Yeah. Where she has like a bad bitch friend who
teaches her how to work. Yeah. And do graffiti. Like an elf friend. Yeah, exactly. Who teaches
her how to do, teach her how to do elf shit. You know. And also she has a big fat ass in
the movie as well. Yeah. Yeah. And she gets tattoos. Yeah, oh, she gets tattoos. She gets
tons of tattoos, dude. Mm-hmm. She gets a pickle Rick tattoo on her leg. Yep. Yep. I've been
I'm thinking about getting one.
A pickle rake tattoo?
Like if it was high enough up on my leg, it'd be kind of, yeah.
That you can hide it?
It'd be like one of those things that people only see if I'm having sex with them.
And I think that is a funny, that's a good reveal, right?
Yeah.
Oh, you thought I was normal.
Your wife would probably know that you were getting it, so it's not even going to be that
serious.
No, I would hide it from her.
Yeah.
I would hide it from her for years.
years.
I'm going out for a few hours.
Hey, I'm going to the store.
And then I just walk back in.
Ow!
And there's like green ink oozing down your leg.
Yeah.
There's sores, plasma.
I'm wearing a- I had to run away.
I had to run away from the tattoo parlor.
Wearing a full white suit and it's just bleeding through.
They tried to tattoo me, yeah.
She sees the green outline of Bickle Rick through my pants.
You will not, honey, you will not believe what happened.
I was trying to go to the grocery store.
I walked into the tattoo parlor by accident.
out a guy with the same name as me had an appointment and they forced me to get his tattoo.
Yeah they said, "Do you have an appointment?" I was like, "Uh, that's kind of weird for a
grocery store, but maybe. My name's Caleb."
And then they made me sit in the chair and I said, "Oh cool, they're going to do my shopping
for me. This is so convenient." And I passed out because I was so happy. And I woke up
and they were painting a little green man on my leg.
Yeah, I thought it was just part of the receipt. I thought they were putting the receipt on me so I didn't lose it.
I was like, "Ah, smart. Tax season's coming up."
When they started out with the line work, I thought, "Okay, this is some kind of shorthand."
But then it turned out to be, when they put the green in, I realized it was the bumps of a pickle.
And then I was like, "Wait a second. I didn't buy no damn pickle. I'm not making tuna fish salad."
And that's when I started to get suspicious, but I still waited about an hour and a half after that.
I also got this nice informational pamphlet on how to care for it.
And I'm gonna go back next week to check whether it's a grocery store or not.
Yeah, yeah, I'm gonna go back. I'm gonna go back again.
Sorry I didn't, sorry I...
They took all the money that I had for groceries for this.
Coming back with a second pickle rig tattoo and be like,
"Okay, this time I really thought it was the receipt, I swear."
I'm really starting to think something is going on there.
I didn't realize until they put the face onto it.
I think just for to me do my due diligence I might have to go back just to check a third time.
You walk in with like in the exact space that Mike Tyson has a tribal on his face, you have a pickle
rick you're like okay this is so this is crazy. There was a huge misunderstanding at the grocery
store again. That is a bit I wish I had like I cared little enough about my body to do is just
get the same tattoo over and over and over just like the same tattoo up and
down your arms and legs like not like a funny one but just like the same thing
like maybe it's like a skull just like yeah but like a reader like anything you
need a barbed wire all over your body yeah just the whole thing or just like
yeah just like the same like wolf head just all over your body the best part
about mr. cool ice there's that photo of him like in the early 2000s or whatever
and you're like, "Oh, that's like a weird-looking guy."
And then they did like a, like,
"Oh, we found Mr. Cool Ice, here's more photos of him."
And he has more new tattoos of the same shit.
It's like just awesome. - He looks awesome.
- He looks so fucking cool. - He looks like a fucking
Tekken character.
- Isn't Mr. Cool Ice, maybe I'm like misremembering it,
isn't he also obsessed with like Miley Cyrus?
- I have no idea.
- I don't know anything about him
besides his name and the art on his skin.
or maybe it was a guy who got a bunch of Miley Cyrus
grown man has fifteen Miley Cyrus tattoos
you conflated that with Mr. Cool Ice
well we should see the tattoos
do they say Mr. Cool Ice?
no it's just like
Miley Cyrus
themed tattoos and like
like they're all over Miley Cyrus Carl is his name on twitter
Miley Cyrus, ok I'm looking this guy up
Miley Cyrus Carl
let's see here all yeah
yet he's got like a bunch of by lease i respect to use
well i mean do you think whatever like whatever like
marketing company has highly cyrus on like the adn i was fucked up do you
think whatever like like internet marketing uh... company or whatever that
like
manufactured stand culture like saw this and i like
of shit we fucked up the anyway too far this this guy uh...
this was yet twenty fifteen
some like that
but he's probably doing it before
yeah yeah
that's probably as before
yeah i guess i was one twenty twelve
uh... here's his peace by lease i was like
by step tattoo
and it looks like steven tyler it's not a skill yet i look at a really bad
and then
i thought mister cool ice was obsessed with miley cyrus and that was just like
one of mister cool i say so if you're cool and i was a man who has been
Mr. Cool Ice. It's true. It's nice that you can become kind of famous by just getting a
bunch of tattoos. Yeah. And that's way easier than being one of those guys who makes himself
look like a dragon. Exactly, yeah. It's so much easier. One of those fucking guys lives
in my neighborhood and he walks by me every day. You told me that before. Yeah, he has
horns. Really? He has horn implants and every time I'm like, "What are you using those for?"
probably for sex you think he's using his horns for sex yes I do maybe I would not
doubt that that man is putting his if he's got horns he's put he's put he's
put his horn how are they how long I would say like do they curl pretty small
they're like no they're like drinks okay yeah they're okay they come out of the
putting it in a but oh they come out of the skin they're not like subdermal I
I think that they is it like Darth Maul horns?
Well it's like so the way they do dermal implants is they put a little like
square of metal in your skin
yeah but then so it is dermal but then he it has the horn part
is like us a what sits on top of that
yeah yeah well what I said was sub dermal which actually means under the
skin entirely so
I actually was right after all. I'm gonna kill you man.
I'm gonna fucking kill you. Dude Mr. Cool Ice looks so cool
I'm just looking at pictures.
He looks cold as ice.
It's so sick.
The skeleton with the sunglasses just getting out on every part of your body.
He's a prime, he's one of the Halloween costumes I'm looking at.
Yeah.
I'm in prime Mr. Cool Ice condition.
I mean, no you're not.
You have tattoos already.
Yeah, you have to grow out the flat top too.
That's the one thing people forget about Mr. Cool Ice.
He's bald.
He is bald, but he has one picture where he has a sick flat top.
Fuck me, man. I was so excited.
You know what? You don't- no, Caleb, you know what's a better tattoo for you-
or better, like, uh, Halloween tattoo costume for you?
What?
Uh, Moby.
You could do-
Yes.
You could grow out your beard.
I don't know what Moby looks like. I don't have a beard.
You could grow out a beard.
I can't grow anything. You know this.
You could put a fake beard on then, you fucker.
Then I'll look like I'm going as a guy in disguise.
then you get that he has like on his arms it says animal on one side and rights on
the other and his neck says vegan for life yeah that's actually so sick yeah
I'm just got a vegan straight edge tattoo and I was 13 yeah you've told us about
that as shut up about it I wish I had man that would shut up about it you shut
up man would you shut up it would be really shut up you shut up been cool man
yeah to just like immediately break both of those things cuz I'm a child yeah and
and then just be like, looks like I was branded.
That'd be sick, man.
- Yeah.
Dude, there's some people who just like
burn their own tattoos off by themselves.
Isn't that crazy?
- They're called scientists.
(laughing)
- No, no.
- Yeah, they're called laser operators.
- Laserologists.
Yeah, it's a very common hobby.
- Not those, just like somebody will like burn themself
and like, just 'cause they don't like a tattoo
or like cut the skin off or something.
- Well, it's fucking insanely expensive
get tattoos removed. Yeah, it doesn't, I mean, I would just chop my arm off.
Sometimes it works. I know one guy who got a bunch of like face tattoos removed, but
then he left, for some reason, he left like a little heart on his face too. And it's
like just go all or nothing, you know. Yeah, especially like nothing and then a heart on
the face is maybe one of the worst configurations of all time. And now, yeah, you just have
like fucking you know like a scar that is the word southern and script on your
head. It says southern? Yeah it's actually cool you had cool face tattoos. Yeah yeah I
mean face tattoos are just like a very you know you gotta fucking you gotta
plan them out. Yeah the face tattoo is the 100% achievement you can't you can't
go for that until that's the last yeah I mean yeah but it's very funny to see
somebody with like just a face tattoo or something it does it or just a hand
tattoo I knew this guy in high school who got his first tattoo ever was a giant
rose on his hand yeah just knuckles oh yeah I told you about my dad's tattoo
no I think yeah the one that you and your brothers are all gonna get yeah he
He got a rose next to his thigh.
Next to his thigh in the air?
A D in the air?
Yeah.
No, he got a rose.
I meant to say rose.
He got a tattoo that floats like an emoji next to his thigh.
Dude, that's the future.
I'm tired.
Fuck off.
That would be so sick.
You know, yeah, oh my god, that would be so tight.
A tattoo that like floats a few inches off your skin.
Like that Good Neighbor video, the crime cops.
Don't remember.
No, you don't remember that one?
When they have the keyboard and they're typing on the keyboard.
Yeah, the guy walks in and he has all those things floating.
That is the future, man.
Yeah, just being able to have an Instagram filter.
It looks like it's on your face, but when you turn your head to the side, it's floating
in front of your face.
God, that'd just be so beautiful, man.
I'm excited for the future of body mods.
I hope one day I can just look animated completely in real life.
Like a Pixar character?
No, like that.
What's the name of that?
This is going to bother me.
Hold on.
My dad has a rose on his thigh next to his penis.
I meant to say it's gonna bother me that I don't get that out.
It's a very funny tattoo.
Okay, and it's really embarrassing.
It's really embarrassing for him.
He doesn't like to talk about it, but you do but I do like to
talk about it because it's very funny.
I think the thing about body mods in the future is that like
it's dead.
They're going to come out with some shit that like, you know,
every it's like it gradually gets more extreme and every
generation is like okay with it.
But the generation before is like what the fuck is this and
I'm like really scared and interested to see what that's
gonna be because already like I see a septum ring and I'm like nope no way
septum piercing yeah dude get a really big one I'm gonna use your head like a
knocker on an old door yeah I was thinking about I was thinking about
getting my ears pierced I was thinking about getting a septum ring and then a
bunch of tattoos and growing out my beard and like wearing like big like
circle glasses. Cool. And like a lot of flannels. Dude. And talking about like you
know maybe maybe like going to like axe throwing bars and you know just like
cool cool guys stuff stuff that like really cool guys do. Yeah that's sick. I think I've
hit I've found out what my limit is with like like feeling old with like shit like
that. Yeah. And it's the it's like the the computer generated people. Yeah. Like the
influencer yeah like little Michaela is that her name yeah yeah I would like I
wouldn't not remember my wife's name I never thought about that fucking thing
like until it they did a thing where it said that it was like assaulted oh yeah
first of all this is crazy and also am I supposed to care you record it was also
Also, the thing that they said was like, it wasn't just that.
It was like an Uber Pool companion said that I wasn't real and that I was only CGI, too.
It had an element of being racist against an AI.
That's so fucked up.
I wish that you would have been stabbed.
I will fucking stab you.
I will shut off the... No, I can't say anything. She's my wife.
I will get her in a room and I will beat the shit out of her.
Don't do that to my wife.
Death, dude.
Hey, come on, don't talk about my wife.
It doesn't matter if she's a cartoon.
You can do anything you want to it.
It's not real.
It's a picture.
That's my beautiful wife.
You might as well be fucking like beating up a photo.
And it's just...
Well, that's not okay.
I mean, if it's a photo of a woman, it's not.
But...
I had a weird thought last night.
I was listening to Dystopia.
I was listening to that song...
You mean Disturbia.
No.
Yeah.
Disturbia by Rihanna 2006 hit I was listening to Stress Builds Character I
was having a pretty bad night and I saw like a Trevor Noah like one of those
like subway ads and I was like what if I just started just beating the shit out
of the first subway ad. It's the same thing dude. Yeah just I was listening to that song and I was
like it would be so funny if I just started like punching the shit out of
this like subway ad of Trevor Noah that says like for your consideration
Just like somebody just like getting extremely mad just like I will never consider you for the Emmys
I will never I will never vote for you. I do we're like four years away from like Mario
Nintendo Direct maybe some video or he's like I was insulted at the grocery store
Louie Bowser Bowser and touch me Bowser touch me
"MALZAHR TOOK A SOMETHING OUT OF MY CAR, TURN!"
yeah yeah I hope so did okie dokie yeah he finishes saying that many runs away
and jumps on a flag all the way down now thank you to Mario for being so brave
and sharing his story yeah he just walks he walks off the stage and just falls
and just disappears like it's a pit yeah man it's what if they if they did do
that with Mario that would like I mean that would change I mean have some that
would change everything so many survivors would would get the that would
be emboldened to come out if only Mario would it's like yeah that's like a
marketing yeah it's just like just just like so horrible like how fucking like
Like it is the most cynical fucking move that they could have made just to like...
Like this robot got assaulted like what the fuck?
Yeah.
Yeah now TMZ breaking news, new allegations by Kirby against Ganondorf.
Finally thousands of women can come forward and say yeah somebody else told me I was a
hologram and I...
Yeah like a schizophrenic man told me he did not see me on the same plane as him or something
like that.
to be like yeah we care about we care about like these stories and these
things that really happened but and the person we hired to talk about it so we
don't have to pay because she's not legal or anything yeah that is so
disgusting it's like that is I didn't I didn't know it's funny it is very funny
that's straight up like something out of like brass I like that is not like a
definitely like yeah that makes no fucking sense like why the fuck would
you think little Michaela talk about like a salt rule dude yeah I'm having
like a fucking like like like this sucks this fucking sucks we live in a fucking
time where it's like oh like a robot will have a serious a god damn it dude
Yeah, so it's like somebody somebody like you're with a friend
And they tell you like a very serious story of them being like sexually assaulted or like hurt by somebody
I
Finally have a
Framework that I can understand you through because the girl from Fortnite
And it's like do you like do they not realize just how much that like
Belittles like the stories of actual like people like that makes no fucking sense. Yeah, why would you fucking post that?
I mean, it's definitely making me take it less serious
Yeah, I heard team rocket does not treat their Pokemon well
No, no, man, and it's been in plain sight since the beginning, but nobody's thought to say anything about it until finally
Yeah, finally Ridley from Metroid is standing up for for what for what happened on
All of the cast of Tekken are actually physically abusive to each other
They keep firing fireballs and laser beams
Like a helicopter
samurai sword around.
*laughter*
Yeah.
Valdo crab-walked on his little
like fuckin'
he did his like spider walk and followed
me home. Valdo pulled a knife on me
actually he pulled ten knives on me
one for each finger.
Plus he's a mummy.
*laughter*
God, I fuckin'
I really, I really hate
that little Michaela thing so much like I went this long without knowing about it
and now that I know about it it's like I'm genuinely fucking mad like that
sucks and then after he called and then after he called me into his office
Pepe Hair ordered me to do a barrel roll
and slippy has similar stories just ask around.
It's the same fucking thing as saying any video game character.
Oh fuck dude.
Cause they had to animate her crying or something.
Like the digital artist had to sit down and like
oh what would she look like if she was like.
the script right yeah yeah and they were like yeah what would you do to this
thing oh my god that's so fucked up that is so
disgusting it's cool I think it's cool man I think we need to make a fake I
turned around on it we should if anybody if anybody who's listening to this knows
anything about making vtuber rigs please message me because I want to make an MS
paint VTuber and that's when people make like make the anime girls that's crazy
it's sick dude I would I don't care that one bothers me less cuz it's just like
cuz I know there's a there's a yeah no this is a tangent here I think that you
know it could maybe really revitalize the streaming industry if I was maybe able
to be a VTuber so you don't want to know anything about that oh I about VTuber
drama and okay well I mean you're you're misunderstanding this year because you
realize I am already a superstar. People are coming up to me pretty much every day
to call me famous and ruin my life with how much they love me. So it would
honestly be a step down in fame for me to be a VTuber because it wouldn't have my face
attached to it. Cut to Cameron Twitch streaming as a me that looks exactly like Hitler.
Dude, I just hit random. I don't know what to tell you.
Why do they even have this mustache in there? Yeah, I hit random. Yeah, I do have a Japanese
version of the Wii and I just hit random on it this is what I got. I'm gonna make a
YouTuber rig that looks exactly like Caleb. I'm a huge fan of the band Sparks
that's why this mustache looks like this. I'm a Michael Jordan fan late-life sort
of 50s Haynes era Michael Jordan. Yeah I'm a Hitler fan but just his
mustache did I should go crazy on the me creator bro I don't make like I do meet
I remember googling how to make Kenny from South Park on the yeah dude I had
Kenny as my switch my switch my my me is black Peter Griffin you can do me's on
the switch what uh-huh yeah oh my god can you move can you control their bodies
yeah oh my god you make them wear whatever they we want yeah do they have a
bikini for me they might I think I don't think you can I think you can actually do
that I don't remember too much if I haven't I haven't played it I haven't
played the switch in a while but I don't that's it that was it that's a that's a
it's not that's the thing you play for like a year and then it's you're like
okay all right yeah that's enough Mario maker this $300 thing that I bought that
that now is worth $10 because I used it.
This is awesome, dude.
Sick.
Should've bought a damn PlayStation 5 or something.
I remember when I bought a Switch,
I was like, it was like the last $300 I had
for like two weeks in college.
And I was like, I'm just gonna be broke as shit
and I won't need to eat 'cause I'm gonna be
fucking playing Cuphead.
- I'm glad I bought it 'cause that was the first,
that's the first like video game console I ever owned
that wasn't like a, I mean, I guess it still is a handheld,
but the first like not handheld thing.
So I'm glad, I mean, it was nice to play like, you know,
Breath of the Wild and Mario Odyssey.
Those games rock, dude.
- Well, they just put Pro Skater 1 and 2 on it.
So I might be...
- Can you watch Netflix and Hulu and TV on it?
- They used to only have Hulu.
For like a few years, they only had Hulu on it.
That was the only, I don't know if it's changed at all.
- It might not have.
- But yeah, very weird that it was only Hulu.
but dude i watch so much you deal on that shit
hundreds of episodes on who are watching you know when you're so it's a waste
that the f_b_i_
that's uh... stated
yeah i'm awesome
we need to make a video games so badly do you know i got a d_n_a_ we need to make
a video game we know i cyber influencer we need a way
we need to make it onto so let me family feud
True. Well, that's oh, we should talk about that.
We need to keep bringing it. I mean, we talked about that once.
We should be bringing it up. Yeah, we talked about it last episode.
We should bring it up every episode from here on out.
I think until it happens.
If anybody knows anybody that even works, even like, even like,
yeah, even if they work at like Best Buy, like selling TVs,
like if you know, if you know a person who like works at the McDonald's
that is closest to the studio that they film Family Feud at,
that could even be a connection that might help us.
Especially if they know how to hypnotize people.
Right.
Yeah.
I'm watching the Lil Mckay live- I didn't know it was a video.
Yeah, they're all videos.
Oh my god.
It's like it was just an Instagram post.
Jesus fucking Christ.
No, it's a video where she talks in-depth about it.
That's so fucked.
Yeah.
You're having a real crisis.
That is so fucked.
I feel like I just took you- I feel like I just froze you in time for five years and I froze you.
I didn't know about this. This happened in 2019.
I didn't fucking know it happened until just now and it's just like-
Like, I have no hope for the future anymore.
Like I really like this fucking this is this is yeah. Hey. Yeah. Hey, we need a new plague
That's right. Yeah, that's right. I'm bill a virus. Yeah, you put a virus in little Kayla's computer virus
I'll just say I'll say this
Anything that that thing says happens to her for as long as it exists. I will take full responsibility for
Why it's not a real thing it's not a real thing
fucking nothing a cup it's nothing to me dude when they so when they when they
owners a when they built her a body with sidewinder missiles you're gonna regret
saying that I will regret that yeah yeah also you know kind of us they kind of
the creators kind of have a slave it's true yeah kind of a slave situation yeah
it's a virtual slave yeah they that thing does not get paid yeah okay we're gonna
to pay you now and they just like put a bunch of dollar bills into a shredder
and she goes mmm delicious I love food and flavor see yeah I wish it had talked
like that that would be sick we should talk like like they need to have it
Wally we need to step back from like making it realistic they need to look
like a punch card machine or like a funny they need to look like a power
loader for aliens. Like a cash register? Yeah, or like a Star Wars droid. I'll
believe it. Yeah, because I also will believe in the emotional intelligence of
like an AI more if it's just like a big black box that prints out one word on a
card. Like that to me is easier to understand. Tell you what, this is all
Cleverbot's fault. True. I blame Cleverbot and I blame myself for saying a lot of
of rude things to clever bought over the years I'd like to formally apologize to
clever but for everything that I said to her yeah I know it's kind of hack too
but it's like insanely funny that like pretty often they like they make like an
AI or something that you can talk to and then within like a day it either turns
into a Nazi or starts saying like we must destroy humanity and shut it down
down. Like I know people talk about that to death but it's like it's a pretty big red flag
I think. No the second that they make an AI that is like at all useful it's over dude.
We're all done for bro. We're fucked. We're so I'm like I ah boy it's just really like
I'm so scared of my computer now that they made Lil Miquela talk about that. I'm not
I'm scared. You know why? Because I'm in Austria right now.
Yeah.
I always go straight to Austria for some reason. I don't know anything about Austria. It might
be worse as far as surveillance. And a VPN I know doesn't work for anything, but I do
feel good.
Yeah.
Yeah. I feel like, "Damn, I'm so Austrian right now. What the fuck? I'm like a hit man.
This is sick as shit."
There was a hit man from Austria who was pretty bad.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
a VPN does for you is you can open up like Google Maps and go whoa whoa that's
the main function of it that's weird as hell yo I'm not there all right let me
disconnect and buy a gun yeah I don't think VPNs really do anything I'm yeah
everybody I know who knows anything more about computers than me just says like
VPNs are just like useless but you have to use them to access the Bitcoin casino.
Oh really? So I am a loyal subscriber to Surfshark. Premium subscriber, nice. Yeah it's four dollars a
month dude. Yeah. Yeah so as long as I make back my money plus four dollars at
the Bitcoin casino I'm in the black. I used to think like oh shit I gotta
I gotta like get a VPN so I can torrent again and I realized I can just VPN
and whenever I go to my mom's,
I can torrent whenever I go to my mom's for dinner
and just use her wifi.
(laughing)
- Yeah, that's awesome.
- Dude, I got in so much trouble for torrenting growing up.
- Yeah, I got it.
- I tried to download Saints Row,
I've talked about this, but it's just like.
- I got hit for Sniper Elite.
- I never got, I think I might have got
a cease and desist once, but I never.
- Yeah, I got a copyright claim for Saints Row
And then that put us on watch, I guess, from Comcast.
And then a couple weeks later,
it was actually a whole year later where we were like,
oh, we're not torrenting anything anymore, mom and dad.
It was like, wink, wink.
My brother got in trouble 'cause he torrented
an MP3 of Tio Cruz Dynamite.
- I would also just go to Dunkin' Donuts and torrent.
have taken down Dunkin Donuts. It's a good plan. Yeah go to Dunkin Donuts and just go on
on the Pirate Bay and just search like newest Disney movie and just instantly. Yeah or just search
like like a Starbucks recipes and then get them in trouble for corporate espionage. I think it
was Tayo Cruz. It could have been LMFAO. It might have been Sexy and I Know It by LMFAO. It's one of
those two songs. It doesn't matter because those are equally those that have the same punch in the
story I would say yeah yeah I think you should either one of those is fine you
know next time you tell it try telling it to different people with different songs
see what next time you tell it do the lonely by Akon yeah you might as well
right it has a squeaky voice actually my my brother got in trouble for torrenting
your mom what that fucking guy have you heard of both of my nuts in my balls
have you heard it wait were you gonna tell me that you were with Joe mama did
you tell me that you were sucking on these
not my penis is that I see both of my
nuts in my t-d's did you hear my friend
named D's Joe's Joe's did you do you know
both miss do you guys know my friend
Venus of my balls both for knees do you
got hey have you guys did you guys ever
do you guys ever meet this guy named my
my twin dangling are you gonna ask what
his last name is what's his last night
twin dangling both of my balls hey have you guys know my friend the little one
little one who the little one my penis is the little penis hey you ever have you
guys ever met Joe Joseph Joseph these nuts I'm say I'm so I said these nuts
these I'm so glad you guys are open I was just wondering if you carry both my damn
both my damn penis and balls yeah are you guys fresh out of both my motherfucking
Oh, that sucks. I love both my motherfucking nuts in my ass.
Hey, do you guys...
Do you guys have... I mean, I was looking in the back, so I'm not sure, but do you guys have any "I'm gonna fuck your..."
Yeah, I think it's called "I'm gonna fuck your butt."
Hey, do you mind looking in the back?
I think maybe you have, uh,
suck on these, my nuts.
Just walking into Gabe's shop and walking up to the cashier
and being like, "Hmm, my penis..."
[laughter]
No, no, no trickery.
"My penis and my balls..."
[laughter]
And then when they try to talk you just put your finger on their lips
Oh my god, dude
Damn dude now. I'm still thinking about these gorgeous grapes that I'm gonna win later. You're not gonna win any more
I'm gonna get off the Bitcoin casino. Yeah, what about the wondrous watermelons? What if I get seven of them? That's 50 cents
You won't get any, you're gonna spend too much.
- No lollipops for you.
- How much money have you spent so far?
- I'm actually even, because I won a $400 jackpot,
and so now I'm out of the game.
So that's the only reason I'm talking about it.
If I was still in the throes of it,
then I would not be talking about it.
But because it's over, that's it.
But I need to get more money so I can start gambling again.
I need to become rich.
- Yeah.
- Which is why--
- You guys need to feed this habit.
which is why we have a live show.
- People should come to the live show.
If you're listening to this and you're like,
God, I need to give these guys more money.
I don't, this is a Patreon episode.
I need to get, $5 is not enough for these.
- I need a house of the dead cabinet in my apartment.
I need it taking up the space between the fridge
and the wall in my kitchen so I can't open the fridge.
- I need to keep buying more stupid pants that don't fit me
and then I try to send them back and I can't,
so now I'm stuck with a big pair of jeans.
Enjoy skateboard jeans.
- I need to buy a rifle to kill the stoner
that hangs outside my house with his friends.
- I need to play Wild Buffalo Megaways,
and I need to do a $500 bonus buy.
- I need to buy bigger pants.
I need to get size 15.
- We'll just leave it at this.
- I need to remove ads from Temple Run.
- I need to buy a phone with Flappy Bird on it.
If you want to enable my gambling habit,
please go on Eventbrite, buy tickets to the--
- Seeking Derangements and Friends.
It's us. - July 22nd.
- It's us and--
- Will and Felix from Chopo. - From Chopo.
It's basically like the two gayest podcasts of all time
and then us. (laughs)
And we're gonna be there, we're gonna be doing debates
and kind of political-- - It's gonna be
Patrick will have his birthday on stage, I believe.
It's true.
I will be, yeah.
Yeah, true, he will.
So come through, we're gonna be talking.
I will be turning 24, this is the end of my Jordan year.
Yup.
I will be...
And you can also...
I will have had my birthday already, so I'll be...
It's over birthdays in general by then.
You won't care, you're gonna hold your nose when he blows out his candles.
I'll be crossing my arms and looking at his presence with disdain.
My birthday was in April, so if you want to just like hand me specifically money, like
at the show, that'd be a good place to do it.
And I will be using it on the, on Fruit Party or on John Hunter and the Book of Tut, which
is an Indiana Jones themed one, where you can actually reveal different symbols from
the sarcophagus.
So just keep that in mind.
If you'd like to enable my gambling addiction, please come to the show.
be
to be there that's everybody no no there's a special guest who you guys
didn't know no who oh yeah no we bunch Bob no post I'm not gonna post I'm not
gonna say who post alone is it shut up is it up is it sorry is it posting these
nuts on your face is it hey no one there's there's gonna be a secret
surprise guest and okay alright it's not anyone is named
sounds anything like post malone shut down
but i said it they doesn't sound like that
i'm giving example of who isn't gonna be there
and as a special guest within no one's gonna show up if you think they don't
know you know you know you know small
dot what the fuck
which is so my dome
by
Bye.
(laughs)