You're listening to Israel's number one pod.
This is premium content!
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately!
[Laughter]
No you're not. You're not recording.
I'm recording. Check out this.
Check out this.
Are you in the stew right now? Are you in the booth?
Play Dig. Play Dig.
Oh yeah.
Wait.
[Singing]
We're gonna get stricken for copyright.
Longest metal scream ever.
That's terrifying.
This is so we can text right off the bass.
You have to play one full song on the show at some point.
You have to play the new theme song.
True. We could have like a bass theme song.
Yeah, wait, can you just add a bass track to the theme song?
That's the perfect thing to add.
Yeah, that's not a bad idea, honestly.
It does not change it at all, just this overlay, the bass playing.
Yeah.
Pat, right before we started recording, you said that children can have tumors.
That's actually true.
Caleb said that his 1,000 friends who are all one-year-old children will live forever.
They won't live forever, but if I have--
You literally just said that.
No, no, no, no, no.
You said that.
You said that you'll be friends with kids forever.
Sometimes I'm not wrong.
Sometimes I'm wrong.
listen you said you'd be proud of you want to have a very you should have it
the youngest friends possible because in this is a business
uh... smaller chance of them on dying and you having no friend what they are going
to use that only works on the youngest people
money
it could spread like wildfire through their ranks right like a brain tumor
yeah i think it's a good work
but i was a kid my my mom brought uh... me and my brother to this kids house
who had like, he was like my age or maybe a little younger, he was like 11, and he had
some sort of like terminal cancer, and she was like, "Yeah, we're gonna go and like
cheer him up." And we like walked in, it's just some sad bald kid on like a hospice
bed in his house, and... Now that's your mirror. Now it's my mirror, exactly.
Woo! Let's go! My mom was like, "Yeah, you wanna like hang out with him?" And I was like, "No."
And then I went upstairs and I played with his toys.
and he just had to listen to like all these adults like fucking pray over him
or whatever yeah and just hear from upstairs yeah yeah just the noise of
you just just throwing his toys against the wall yeah it's a toy shot all these
toys suck dude no wonder he's walking or dying I don't want to play with this
kids toys I'm gonna catch his cancer yeah anyway he died like a week after that
his last memory with another kid was me and then I went upstairs I played with
Just walking, just walking downstairs with like the huge bulging kangaroo hoodie
pocket and be like alright nice to meet you kids see you later and he goes
upstairs and just like does an empty room. Take all his toys. Luckily I don't think he was
physically able to go upstairs so yeah he never saw his room again he doesn't
You know what I did in that room?
His mom does though.
Those walls can talk.
That's right.
They can talk about Caleb's playtime.
Yeah, they talk about me putting these transformers in my mouth.
It's tough, dude.
What have you guys been up to?
I haven't talked to you guys in so long.
I've been playing the bass, dude.
Nice.
Check this out.
Oh, fucking.
It's when I try to show off.
Every time you try and show off, you fuck it up.
He played it well earlier.
Oh, it's just me.
I'm making you nervous, dude.
You know that I'm a musical genius, a prodigy, a protégé.
Okay, play it again.
That was "You Can't Touch This"?
Oh, nice.
Is it "You Can't Touch This" or "Can't Touch This"?
It's "We Can't Touch This."
It's "I Can't Touch This."
So that's great to learn because you also learned "Super Freak."
True.
By Rick James.
Yeah, your favorite song.
Because it's about me.
It's about you.
I'm the super freak.
You are the freakiest one, dude.
Yeah.
Yeah, you have naughty ideas.
[Music]
Yeah, he has naughty ideas about BoJack Horseman.
That's right. That's absolutely right.
A lot of people got very mad at me for that.
What did you even say?
Somebody made like...
All he said was "I love comedy."
Oh yeah, someone made some post that was like
"They have a fat person in this show, and that's so brave."
Yeah, and then they were like
"They all thought that I was attacking the person who posted it."
posted it, it's like, no, I just think BoJack sucks.
- Yeah, also just that being like,
the reason you watch a comedy show.
- Yeah.
- It's like, well, it's not very funny,
but they do have a fat guy.
- Yeah.
- It's not, you know, Tommy Boy wasn't funny,
but there was a fat guy in it.
- There is a fat, yeah.
- Yeah.
- Exactly, dude.
Fucking Uncle Buck is amazing fat guy representation.
- Yeah.
- I put the bass down.
- Thank God, okay, now we can actually start.
What are you talking about? I was on fire.
I was on fire, dude.
I'm a huge fan of the...
I had some amazing solos.
I'm a huge fan of the clumps, because it depicts
how kind of a whole family can be crazy.
True. That's kind of
an intersectional movie.
A bunch of fat black people.
It's a bunch of different people could be fat in a movie.
That's true, yeah.
A bunch of fat people could be Eddie Murphy.
I would say Norbit is the most
intersectional movie of all time.
a fat person and a skinny person could be Eddie Murphy. And they never make fun of his weight.
They never make light of it. He's proud of it. Exactly. There's no jokes about it and
it's not meant to look disgusting. Or like a giant quivering ball of fat that's just
like revolting to see. It's not supposed to be that. It is funny that nobody does prosthetic
fat anymore. No. You just get Rebel Wilson. Christian Bale ruined all of that. You don't
get the clumps anymore because he showed how dedicated he was to gaining weight.
Actors think it's cool to get fat and get skinny. I've been doing that every two
years my entire life. Me too. In two years I've hit my peak. In two years I'm gonna go back
down to being a string bean. Yeah. I was gaining all this weight for the role of Patrick on the podcast.
I think my next step is I'm gonna be like Arnold Schwarzenegger ripped. I'm thinking.
I think that's gonna happen for me in a few weeks. Dude, if you got crazy ripped it would be scary.
That would be so funny dude just all of a sudden just like six four like 210 pounds
yeah muscle just shredded you look at Fabio oh you're gonna make me act up
you got me actually thinking I'm actually you got me riled I'm gonna
round Patrick I wish there was a chip better not that Apple could put in my
brain that kept me from thinking I wish there was a chip that was wavy and had
flavor I wish they cooked a chip in a kettle I wish they made a chip with pepper and and
some other ingredient that I can't think of you know okay so you know barbecue you
know barbecue food imagine if that was a chip what is the latte chip man I was
10 years ago I wish there was a chip that Lays made called the Lays chip you
know in in like Australia and then Australia and in England they don't call
it lays it's not only freedom they call it life like a lice yeah lice no it's
called lockers it's called lockers in England and then it's called Smith's in
in like Australia and New Zealand yeah it's called a it's called a spot of the
crisp actually all this spot of tea yeah yeah the potato plate I don't think I
called that it is that I really don't think it's called that I think that's a
different thing I think I finally got coffee breath for the first time I think
I was I was wondering what if there was like a smell and it's just my breath
mm-hmm yeah last night I thought so oh here's a big thing that's been happening
last two weeks what I don't feel safe in my own home why because we have a rat a
rabid mouse infestation. Oh no. That might be my fault. There are mice... did you bring a mouse to my
house? Yeah I did. You did? Yeah. We didn't cause the mouse infestation but we did
give them rabies. We did give them rabies. I don't know if they have rabies but they do
look scary. There's a mouse that just has completely lost all
fear of humans and he just walks on my feet every time I go in the living room
room I don't know how to he won't get it just a great of your is too fast for me
and then I found out last night he has babies or she has babies because they
call me I can have babies well not so a man can't have babies yeah so a man can't
have so many beautiful babies that are behind rewind rewind a man can have
babies it could be a male mouse I don't know anyway when I go to sleep three
different little baby mice crawled out from under my bed and just looked at me.
So? So what if, I don't know, what if they eat me or something like the ants in
Indiana Jones Crystal Skull? How about you grow up? Alright. I'm as old as I'll get.
You're in New York City, bro. You gotta get used to it.
Yeah. I'm not used to it, dude. I don't fuck with these mice at all. Just give them a
chopped cheese. Janet keeps waking up in the middle of the night thinking that
there's a mouse on her and she punches me in the fucking head. She literally like
she like twitches she's like and punches me in the head. It sucks dude.
I'm getting no sleep there's mice that are they they don't even eat
any of my food that's the most most fucked up part there's not a single they
don't go in the pantry they don't eat my food they just walk around and just show
them just fucking show their ass. I mean they're they're just showing you that
they're there I thought you guys would be more understanding about this no I'm not
gonna give me some advice towards your new pet you could have you would give me
some advice you could have like a monster under your bed and all you have
is yeah little babies yeah you just have a new children it's their new children
basically they're a pet they're not my children they're not my pets I have
argued to Jana that we shall thousands of children all over the world have
giant furry monsters in their closet and I'm hearing you they're playing about a
mouse that doesn't even eat anything
there are kids in africa with no mice in their house
that's a really good point
and i wish i was a kid in africa
man if only i could be a kid in africa no fucking mice
no mice
there's a tiger under your bed
oh fuck
yeah if only
you guys want me to play some more bass?
not really
no dude i want to talk to you guys i haven't seen you or heard of you
i can talk and play
- You didn't pick up my FaceTime call last night.
- Yeah, I picked it up.
- Did you FaceTime call me?
- Yeah, I FaceTime called both of you.
I talked to Patrick for like seven hours.
- We did, we did talk for a while.
- Oh my God, now I got left out?
- No, it's your own fault.
You should have picked up the call.
- You know, yeah.
- I'm gonna show you my--
- Do you have that group on mute?
Do you have our group text on mute?
I bet you do.
- I think he does.
- I bet you hate us.
- I got no calls from you last night.
- It's on the group.
It will say in the group message,
I know you have that muted.
- That's possible, I don't have it muted.
- I know you have it muted.
- It does say there's a FaceTime call there.
- Yep.
- Well you know what, I never said I was a good friend.
(laughing)
I never once fucking said that.
I never told you guys that I'm here to respect you guys
and talk to you.
- That's messed up.
That's messed up.
- That's kinda not cool, man.
I mean, I'm not saying that I'm not,
but I never said that.
- I get that you're doing a thing for the podcast right now,
but it's kinda not cool,
and I don't really like where this is going,
to be on your own you know what we respect you and you sit there and you shit on
all our dreams you don't respect if you respected me you would give me a
solution
to this mouse problem okay kill it kill the mouse that's the solution i think
i'm gonna read that book mouse and figure it out from there
they seem like they did a really good job of getting rid of the mice in that book
what it feels like i mean i thought the mice were no wait the cats are the bad guys
way i think i think that my sort of bad guys we read no no no it did
i was confused
uh...
here you are confused that that
patrick read that and i was like you like is the guy i got a guy
you know i don't know
you know i don't know what you're all
i was hitting my jeweler and sorry that i read that book and he was like i wish
this had been based on a true story
come on
me a break you wanna break once no we're not giving you a break you know why cuz
you're racist no I'm not yeah you are I'm the I'm the
wokest one on the podcast say something woke right now well then why are all
these fucking fatties after you about Bojack Horseman?
that's true yeah okay you know what you know what maybe it's Cameron nobody's
ever got a mad at me for saying anything nobody has ever gotten mad at you for saying
anything no never never gotten mad at you for something you said I'm the golden boy
look at this I'm the golden boy what are you talking about I'm the golden boy
dude I'm the golden boy look at me look at me I'm the golden boy all right you
guys vote in the comments of this premium episode who has the best smile
that we're doing right now the best is sweeter the sweetest has a better smile
who has the sweetest smile out of the three of us right now I'm the I'm the
cute one you're not the cute you're not the one you're the racist monster yeah
you're the you're basically not the sexist cute one that low-key cottage
core fascist Bay I'm a cottage court I'm a cottage court lesbian yeah yeah I love
Caleb is that big ugly freak.
(laughing)
And I'm just that normal fellow who sits in.
- I'm just that normal MF.
- Yeah, Cameron's the computer science guy.
- I am God's normal guy.
- Who low-key smiles when he's depressed.
- Yeah, Cameron is that hacker boy.
- I'm that little baby hacker who hacked my pacifier.
I'm that little musician with the most beautiful song of all time.
I'm that little Undertale fan who knows how to get down.
That little Undertale fan.
I'm that little Undertale fan who looked up Sans theme on ultimateguitar.com.
Yeah, you did look that up.
I'm that little fella in the underwear that'll make you act up.
yeah that's true yeah when I was a kid I wanted to be one of those like one of
those kid like pajama and underwear models at JCP that they have yeah as an
underwear model but with the like those like Calvin Klein ads where they have the
giant bulge and he just has like socks just stuck to this it's stuffed in his
underwear. You see the socks coming out of the... He's like eight years old. Yeah, just with a huge-ass
ball sack. Just like one of those guys who fills it with silicone. Just like a
spider's egg. Oh yeah, did you see those ones I was sending you? Yeah, those are incredible.
I clicked on that guy's profile. So there's there's apparently some
fetish that like when I clicked on it... Yeah, inflators. Do you guys ever do this where if
someone sends you like a picture of a fetish or something you click on it and
you go to the replies no no that's not what I'm saying at all you click on it
and you're like please God don't unlock something in me I was I was looking at
those and I was like I was like I don't know if I should watch more than one of
these cuz what if I see one yeah I have to do that to my balls or I'll never be
happy they fill their balls with fucking silicone yeah it's dangerous they fill
them up with silicone and then they put them in vacuum sealers like they get
custom vacuum sealers and then they inflate their balls until they look like
like the fuck they look like bubble buddy from Spongebob pretty much like
fleshy bubble buddy yeah no wrinkles in your balls it's no wrinkles completely
smooth no but the thing is God gave your balls wrinkles for a reason the thing
about okay the thing about the like unlocking like like HP Lovecraft thought
that unlocking forbidden knowledge was gonna be about like oh you discovered the
old God or the origin of the universe but it's actually like the the real like
like forbidden knowledge is when you open up a picture of like a guy who's
inflated his nipples so they look like toadstools and you're like oh my god I
can never go back to normal life again. It'll haunt you forever. I feel this huge hole in my in my life and I
have as long as I've been alive and I feel like one day I'm gonna fill it with
with like, sticking like tri-tip in my ass or something.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Like I'm terrified, dude.
- It's gonna be vac beds for you.
- What is that?
- Vac beds is when people,
it's like they put latex around like a bed
and then they vacuum seal it so they can barely breathe
and then they get their like dick played with.
- Is that like the thing where people like have like a--
(laughing)
- They just hang up?
I mute my video, you guys just hear (imitates vacuum)
you know that that video of the guy who puts the woman under the floor like in
like a yeah dude that's gonna be Caleb's thing yeah I am scared to choke myself
like jerk off yeah what if like I feel like that is something that probably
everybody would really like because it's just like depleting yourself of oxygen
until you come but nobody does it Cameron disabled screen sharing I wanted
show you guys the video again I'm not because the fucking okay the one that I
sent you last night the one from BK Bulge from Burger King Bulge Burger King
Bulge it's clear that his balls are on top like it's clear that that's not his
balls inflated and he inflated his taint oh wait your taint no look look at it
look at it everyone look up okay if I have to look at it yeah look up look up
BK Bulge you asked for it on Twitter and look at these fucking balls all right
I'll open it up again I did ask for I remember asking for it
that's clear it's clear that that because his balls are on top no that
thing that looks like in ball that's his dick tip that's his dick no it's not
tripping you're tripping that's no yeah yeah that's it that's got to be as
clearly yeah that's his dick tip no yeah that absolutely is
- Nuh-uh, it's gotta be.
- Why are you so mad?
Yeah, it is.
- 'Cause I'm confused!
- That is, look, you can see the like,
you can see that's his foreskin.
- Oh my God, dude, I can't look at this video any longer.
- It looks like a bullfrog, no!
- Yeah, it is a bullfrog.
- It's not a bullfrog.
- He thinks he's in danger, and his balls, they grow,
they grow like--
- He's like the fucking, the dinosaur from Jurassic Park.
You kidding?
- I just clicked on another guy, Size Fetish Dungeon.
- Okay.
- Pin tweet, a little gym tug and a video of him
in a gym locker room jacking off with huge balls.
- Imagine lifting with your balls that big?
- I will say, it looks a lot like my gym's locker room.
- Really?
- Yeah, it actually does.
- That might be you, dude.
You might be living a double life.
- I might have a split personality.
- His balls aren't that big.
- Imagine if you had a split personality
in the way you found out as you woke up one morning
your balls were seven times their normal size.
Yeah, you go to the doctor and he's like, "Well, it appears you did this on purpose.
Your balls are full of silicone."
Your balls are extremely huge.
And you have two, you gave the nurse two forms of identification.
Yeah, one of them says John Smith and one says BK Bulge.
Yeah, we just want to know how you got this state ID that says "Burger King Bowl" on it.
I like any fetish that you can't, you physically can't hide.
Because that guy walks around with huge balls in his pants all the time.
Great sweatpants challenge.
Can you imagine his great sweatpants challenge, dude?
I'm imagining right now, and I'm gonna have to hang up the phone.
Just a complete, just a balloon, just...
Mm-hmm.
Just poppin'.
Yeah.
I would just love to bring a needle to his balls.
Just...
Yeah.
and put more silicone in it.
You think he has to be careful of hitting his balls on the corner of a cabinet?
Imagine sitting on a fucking plane!
I don't think this guy's going anywhere anytime soon.
No, he goes to...
He goes to the convention.
He has to go to the Pleasuremen's Ball.
fit my humongous balls in this yeah I'm gonna need you know the car that you
made for Shaquille O'Neal the special made car for his height do that in the
seat for my balls this guy is a new wrinkle in the in the pleasure men's lore
which is funny because he doesn't have a single wrinkle in his pleasure men's ball
if you know what I'm talking about get it get him yeah that's right I'm making fun
of him right now I'm really better you better take down BK balls. This guy's nut sack is so smooth and giant.
This man's nut sack is so damn smooth. This guy's balls are so big. How big are they? They're so big they got their own area code.
Yeah man those are some big-ass balls. Crazy dude. Insane. It's crazy how many new
fetishes I've been introduced to because of Patrick yeah yeah oh speaking of
fetishes diaper talk 3 coming soon oh yeah I did all the prep for it
business where it's just it's so weird to have a thing yeah dude thanks I mean
I do think those people probably on the whole are happier in life because they
figured out something just like can say I'm locked a weird thing in their mind
yeah and they're doing it I respect it they want to they want to come yeah
every second of the fucking day. Imagine doing that much work to jack off that people don't use.
That's exactly right. Yeah. Just fucking imagine doing like,
like building a fucking lego set just so you can come. I mean I guess you get to,
you kind of get to fuck your balls a little. I've unlocked a new area. Oh my god, I can't
- Fuck my balls.
- Human beings only use 20% of their balls.
(laughing)
Imagine if they could use 80%.
- Yeah, that's true.
- Yeah.
- But I don't know, man.
I think those are the people who,
if they don't have a hobby or
something they really care about getting better at.
- Well, they're getting better at their balls.
- That's what I mean.
They can work just a normal nine to five job,
and instead of doing woodworking,
can just go home and fuck yeah do you think it's probably the same it's
probably the same amount of like accomplishment you get when you fucking
to build a shelf it's probably the same as stand-up on yeah yeah it's probably
the exact same feeling yeah yeah it probably feels there's something there's
some nice where it's just really bad I'm thinking of giant balls you have you
- What do you think of quitting stand up?
- A newbie, huh?
No, no, but I mean, I wonder if they think ever.
- Oh yeah, yeah, the same feeling I get.
- Oh, I just gotta make it to 10 years then,
and then I'll get an agent.
- Yeah.
- For having the biggest balls in the world.
- A big balls agent.
- Kid, I think you got it.
Kid, I represent people with huge balls,
and I think you have 'em.
- You have some of the biggest balls I've ever seen.
- You have the world's biggest balls.
- Kid, you brought the room down
when you ran into the wall with your giant ball sack,
you bounced off the wall and into the deep fryer.
- I did, do you remember,
did you guys ever watch videos of people
with elephantitis of the ball sack?
- No. - No.
- I think so.
- They like hang to the ground
and they just bounce around on them.
- Yeah, there's a guy who had like, no.
I'm thinking of my 600 pound life,
but I thought it was called my 600 pound balls.
(laughter)
- My 600 pound balls.
- Oh my god.
- Coming soon to TLC, my 600 pound balls.
- We've talked about this before,
but when you are 600 pounds,
they'll show your balls on TV.
They won't blur them because nobody can tell what's what.
- Yeah, yeah.
Oh, he has another foot.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Those people are gonna get mad at me again.
- Oh, look at this guy's tail.
Yeah, that's the person who's mad at you about Bojack Horseman.
Yeah.
Is the 800 pound person who has to be lifted up by a crane.
Just slowly just destroying the foundation of their house, the concrete.
Something that's so beautiful about the show, My 600 Pound Balls, is it just depicts what
it's like to live life with 600 pound balls and there's no like kind of crude jokes or
rude comments made in the show.
It's just an honest depiction.
And people just watch the support.
I heard the joke.
And I think it's honestly, I think it's hilarious.
I heard that.
And then a...
Yeah, no, that's what you should have said.
And then a, yeah, and then a, like a screen, a Tumblr screencap of like a guy saying like,
you know, my balls are so big they have their own gravitational pull.
And that's why sometimes I feel like the world revolves around me.
And it's like, this is so real to my life.
Damn.
That is what you should have said about the BoJack Horseman thing.
Just like, yeah, you're right.
It did get a lot funnier when they had a fat guy on there.
You're right.
You're right, that was really funny. Started falling over all the time.
No, it's just like, I read that they did that because Alison Brie was getting ripped for Glow.
That's what somebody said. She got ripped for Glow? She got ripped in half?
Yeah. Why? She got ripped for Glow.
Mark Maron ripped her in half. Oh, you mean she got in shape.
Yeah. Okay. No, she got like ripped.
She got ripped in half. No, she got ripped. I read it in the replies of it.
and they made they made her fat in the cartoon to make up for the fact that she
was ripped in real life and also her character was Asian so I don't know what
they did oh yeah she was the one who had the the Asian character and she wasn't
Asian everyone got mad yeah yeah and then they had to do like a whole episode
that was like the background of the Asian character so that she's not just
normal Asian she's from Boston - yeah she's she's special Asian yeah yeah
that's right secret Asian secret Asian you remember that shit remember that
should be the greatest oh my god dude the LimeWire parody no saying that who's
saying that question mark question song by da Vinci's notebook oh yeah that's
that they're like acapella band yeah yeah we should maybe do an acapella thing
I was going low, you have to go really high. I have the lowest voice. Yeah, right. I do.
Yeah, you don't have the lowest voice. My voice is definitely lower than Cameron's. Put that
away. That was my voice. Put that bass away. You do not have a bass voice, you have a baritone
at best. You have the highest pitched voice in the world. I have a beautiful baritone.
You sound like Alvin and his chipmunks to me.
I sound like Ian Curtis.
I don't know who that is.
It's a guy from Joy Division.
It's the second time you talked about Joy Division today.
Getting a bass has ruined you.
You're my least favorite friend now.
You might turn into a rock guy now.
You just keep talking about music all the time.
You get on the call and you're like, "Oh, hold up guys.
Before we record, is the recorder set to a D major scale?"
And I'm like, Patrick, that doesn't even make any sense.
What are you talking about?
You're gonna be one of these guys.
I'm gonna get a job at Guitar Center.
Hold on, I need to syncopate my voice this episode.
I'm like, "Patrick, what are you talking about?"
I ain't syncopating shit.
And then he says, "Hold up, before I say this riff, let me tune myself."
[Humming]
Hold up, I have to tune first.
You're gay.
[Humming]
[Laughing]
it's kind of beautiful it's pretty good to my eyes honestly low-key thank you
all right so what we should what should we discuss for the second half of the
episode yeah okay we're gonna do the second we did big balls big ball we did
well do you guys remember when a CDC wrote a song called big balls no shut up
about we're done with I love rock and roll is your life dude and that rock
never stops but rock and roll is dead not dead okay are we are we even gonna talk
about rap this episode can we talk about rap for one second Patrick Watson should just make it to patch rock
that would be a bastardization of both genres no I think we can make something
amazing no I think we could make something together I should you gotta
you gotta hear this song let it rock by Kevin Rudolph yeah that is that is pure
rocked by Kevin Adolf. Kevin Adolf. No. No. Stop. So now we're talking about Hitler in
the second half. We already talked about Hitler. Oh another one. Yeah we're playing the Hitlers.
Patrick was obsessed with Hitler from the beginning of this episode. No. Let's just
end the episode here and then we'll just copy and paste the first 30 minutes. We could do
that. We'll play it in reverse like Missy Elliott. Yeah but we'll actually do a secret
message here we need to talk in reverse okay ready be lack that's my name
CNIP penis penis penis penis penis what curse words can you guys say backwards
is thinking so hard right now. I see in Patrick's brain. A, G, G, I. You can figure it out. It's
not it's not CNIP it would be Cnip. Cnip beam gus. What? What?
- Pincus?
- Mm-hmm.
- Figure that one out.
- Skin?
- Penis?
(laughing)
- Scapenis?
- C,
seneep,
eem,
cus.
- Suck me penis.
- Suck me, well, real mature, dude.
We spent all that time trying to figure that out.
- Oh yeah, I got a great one for you.
- And that's what it does,
not even grammatically correct.
- Hey Pat, spell, spell, uh, I cup.
- P-U-C-I?
Pookie. Pussy? Oh my god. This guy's ruined. Sime cuff. Sime cuff? Hey Pat, say gin backwards.
Nope. He almost did it. He thought about it for a second. So you heard the N sound, he
went no one day I'm gonna trick you and say the creator of the Simpsons that's
Matt graining there we go dude he's learning mm-hmm I didn't know Pat had
the ability to learn yep he's getting stronger first it's the base now he's
learning the Simpsons creators learning those that slurs now he's learning he's
not allowed to say certain words. I'm gonna learn how to say "bat-grain-ing" on the
bass. You just you just said it again. I said I said "grain-ing". Oh my god. I said it!
We are playing the hits this time, huh? No. I said it. This is a Clip Show episode.
What if you were gonna prank the pilot on 9/11? Oh yeah. What if the dick could fart? I don't
remember anything we've ever said. That's the only thing I remember that we've
ever said hey what if a monkey cut off and run up a wall yeah there's a monkey
outside or something there's a little guy there's a little man there's two guys
there's a poop coming out of somebody's mouth it's a green guy and he hates
Christmas I'm laughing about Hitler actually the the Easter Bunny so the
Easter Bunny's weird. Uh-huh. Yeah. Oh, the Grinch. Oh, Green Guy. Oh yeah, the Grinch.
Oh yeah. I forgot about that. Yeah. Fuck. I want to keep a boo. I got an idea for what
we could do. What if we were from New Zealand and we were in a band? Okay. And it's just
two of us. Okay. One of us is the manager. Okay, bye Pat. See you Pat. No, I'd be the manager.
And then one of us is Kristen Schaal. Caleb is Kristen Schaal. Yeah. Why? I have the
shortest hair of anyone here. You would be. I mean, listen to your voice, you sound exactly
like her. And I already play the bass, so I play the bass, so I get, I'm the musician.
And I'm the cool one. I'm the guy who had devil horns and wore sunglasses and was riding
a motorcycle in the show you're thinking of tenacious D no yeah I'm the guy and
add the one who everyone looks at the cameras is that guy's the coolest guy
I've ever seen no that's not in that show that's no one show no no show breaks
the fourth wall that was in that show they look into the camera they say that
that guy Cameron fetters the coolest guy I've ever seen mm-hmm we're just trying
to make a show yeah do what you're making about you I'm not making the show
You make everything about you. Mm-hmm. I'm not making it about me. That's not even obsessed
They're already talking about me. It was just a character in the show that had the same name
Stop looking into your hand mirror and twirling your hair. I don't have a hand mirror and I don't have hair you
Stop looking you have a ring light hair and pan mirror
Patrick just like I'm looking at you liking your own posts on Instagram. Mm-hmm
Well, that's just you comment that you comment on your Instagram post and said bitch you nasty, but I like it
That's you a nice thing to say to yourself with self-care
It keeps you it keeps you happy to see a comment on your book if nobody else is gonna comment that I'm gonna have to comment
It I will need to see that on my posts. Are you are you laughing out for attention right now?
And you need you said be nice to you this nasty bitch. All right, let's be nice to Cameron. He needs a little love
Cameron you are so fucking ugly. You're bad as hell with fucking stupid, bitch
to me sorry I forgot you're so good this guy's so stupid he doesn't even know
you're so stupid yeah you're the baddest bitch of time yeah that's right yeah
you're the baddest time you guys say I'm a genius you got a fat you're a bird
that's not what I asked Patrick got a big fat don't say that brain is fat I
hate watching you leave but I love to watch you go Cameron yeah I love when you
- I love to see you leave and I like when you go.
(laughing)
- I love to see you leave and I love to see you go.
Get the fuck out of here.
- Get out.
- Mom.
- Get out of my room.
- Hey mom, I love to see you leave
and I hate seeing you stay here,
so get the fuck out of my room, you fuck it up.
- Get your shit, pack up your shit and go.
- Get out of here mom.
- Mom, I'm kicking you out of the house.
- You're gonna have to stay somewhere else tonight mom.
- I'm the mom of the house now.
- Mom, I need the house tonight.
Hey mom, you're in the doghouse and you're sleeping on the couch, etc. in my bed with me.
Get the fuck out of here.
I'm four.
I'm four years old, you need to get the fuck out of here.
I'm four years old and if you don't fucking get the fuck out of here.
Mom, I'm gonna be doing arts and crafts for most of the night, so I need you to get the fuck out of the house.
You can go hang out with your friends.
Oh, I forgot, you don't have any friends 'cause you're too busy raising me, your four-year-old son.
Well, you did a terrible job.
And you're single, too.
And you're single.
And you know what? Your butt is flat like a piece of paper.
Your whole body looks like a piece of paper, mom.
Mom, I'm gonna stomp your clit.
You gotta get out there and find me a new daddy.
I'm gonna stomp your clit 'til it's so recessed you'll need a paper clip to touch it like a SIM card.
Get the fuck outta here.
Don't say that to your mom.
Yeah, mom, don't say that to your mom.
Get the fuck outta here, mom.
Get outta here.
She's working hard for you.
Yeah, she's working hard doing nothing.
I see her, she sits on the couch all day, she watches TV.
mom's side she watches TV and I'm in here trying I'm in here drinking gasoline and
bleach and and dirty water what meanwhile she doesn't even care she says
oh I have to watch BoJack Horseman because of this character that's on here
yeah it looks like you mom it looks like you know what it doesn't even look like
you you know you look like a worm you don't have any arms or legs oh my god
did you hear that I miss dad I miss dad I miss my dad it was the devil I miss my
That was literally the devil and I miss my father. Yeah. Oh, and yeah
You think just cuz you're a witch and you had a baby with the devil and I'm the Antichrist
You think that means you don't have to take care of me. I'm four years old and I'm so evil
That's why I'm so you mom. I'm a I'm making a macaroni painting of the devil. That's right. That's right, mom
I just put a rock in the microwave and I blew up our kitchen. What are you gonna do?
There's a bomb. Do you know if I saw I got a rock that I want to know what a bomb is
yeah I got a rock made of evil and it filled the kitchen with smoke when I put
it in the oven now make me a happy face sandwich mom or I'm gonna get some
smiley rice bitch you better give me those smiley fries bitch did you did
your did your school have an appetizer platter at lunch let's go at everything
no my score every every I think I've talked about this but every Wednesday we
would have the appetizer platter and it was clear that it was just stuff that
they had left over so it was it was it was smiley fries mini corn dogs teriyaki
chicken and mozzarella sticks mini corn dogs yeah it's how many you ate I said
mini that's right man yeah yeah mini corn dogs that's the kind of music you
listen to yeah that's that's Pat if he was a Jedi yeah maybe yeah hugs in your
blood yeah minty corn dogs that's a kind of flavor you like oh yeah yeah you do
like different flavors of corn dog I like you like you get the flavor sampler I
like the flavors what's your favorite every flavored corn dog mm-hmm oh that'd
be great yeah you would love every flavor of corn dogs that has grass
clippings and vomit and toothpaste the breakfast the breakfast corn dog did
change the game you got to agree what's the breakfast I don't know with this
it's a pancake that's a pancake wrapped around around a sausage pretty good yeah
you so dumb but it's on a stick right shit up no I'm gonna put you on a stick
like it is on a stick obviously it's a fucking car you just said no it wasn't I
it's also not a corndog at all that's fighting a corn dog yeah there is no
- No corn or no dog.
Yeah, there's a baby trying to get
into Pat's house right now.
- Yeah.
- It's the baby that we were just talking about, dude.
He heard us talking.
- He heard us talking shit.
- It's the four year old, it's the four year old Antichrist.
- Get the fuck out of here, Patrick.
- Do you guys think that the Antichrist is alive right now?
- But you're right, it's not a corn dog
'cause it doesn't have corn meal in it
and it's not a dog.
- Shut up, Patrick, we moved on.
- We're talking about the Antichrist now.
- I was busy fighting a baby.
- Oh, so you admit you were fighting a baby.
- Yeah, and you were losing.
Admit you were losing.
yeah the baby did make me say uncle so baby cast a spell on Patrick the baby
didn't even know magic it was just a spell it cast with its eyes that's right
it be which has my linda his eyes Patrick's on to the baby's goo goo eyes
I did not Pat would fall right then what did you do would wait what did I do I
will wait for you baby I'm falling in love with you but I'm gonna do the right
thing and I'm gonna wait what come on until we're the same age cuz I'm not it
off no yeah you would you would fall in love with a baby I would know what are
you googling places to fall in love with a baby right now what are the board
notice he say yes I can avoid them best place to go there yeah yeah so I don't
go there exactly here's the answer nowhere nobody should ever fall in love
yeah baby yes yeah exactly listen I'm going on wiki how I'm searching how to
find love with a baby I'm printing out the steps that I'm doing the exact
opposite of every single one I'm looking up those places so I can clear them out
I'm gonna go there yeah I'm gonna head there with a big weapon
I'm gonna go there with a big weapon and I'm gonna enact my dark bidding on the people in these locations
is what Patrick is saying. I'm starting to rethink various historical events of the past
past 10 years might have been saving a lot of people from falling in
love with babies you know if we're gonna play the hits let's go there is a baby
loving convention in Las Vegas no no I was talking about Sandy Hook that time
oh what nobody will ever fall in love with these people what the hell is wrong
with me dude I'm I'm sick you're off the wall today I'm actually off my walls van
I'm wearing Vans right now.
I'm wearing...
Yeah?
Oh yeah, did I ask?
Sorry, did anyone ask?
I'm not wearing shoes.
I got bare feet right now.
Same look at 'em.
Check out my...
I got my...
Ow.
I got Vans' Variks on.
It's a pretty good shoe.
That's your name.
Here's my bare foot.
Does this make you guys like me?
No, my feet are so beautiful to me and other people's feet are so disgusting.
Look at my...
Your feet are beautiful to you?
Maybe that's the thing you're unlucky.
Your own feet.
feet yeah I think I have touched my hard penis with my foot before really
interesting thing is I really am serious I want to have a weird fetish but I
can't find one if anybody could recommend me something just force
yourself into one yeah you can force yourself into peepee just get into just
it's like no dude it's like getting into like Captain Beefheart you just have to
You gotta do it a few times before it clicks, you know?
Yeah, that's a really good point.
That really got me.
Yeah, nobody wants to do it the first time and be like, "Oh, this rocks."
As a rocker, that really got me, Cameron.
Just getting pissed on by a prostitute being like, "Well, I don't like this now, but maybe..."
You know, it's not enjoyable, but it's something about the way it's constructed that really
makes it fascinating.
It's kind of like a subversion of what an enjoyable activity would be, which is kind
of what makes it interesting as an experience.
Can you just give me like a "Safe as Milk" pee?
I don't think I'm ready for a trout mask replica P. Shut up dude
- Captain B fart albums from there and relax tropical hot dog night shut up Patrick
Patrick's favorites Captain B fart song is Dachau blues, but he smiles really wide whenever he listens to it
It's a good son. He only listens to he reads the lyrics over and over you just come and he says I love what happens in
This song you're literally becoming Marin. You're starting a podcast with a riff
What the fuck is wrong with you, bro?
Are you talking about Captain Beefheart?
My dad got bit by Mark Maron in the 80s.
Didn't you work with him?
Yeah, I know. He got bit by him.
And it skips a generation.
And you know what?
I'm like a balding wolf man.
It skips a generation.
And that's why I'm turning into Mark Maron.
You're getting marked up.
You're more like Pork Maron.
Hey, man.
Oh, hey, oh, hey, I'm just I'm just playing around
Yeah, you're more like shark Marin fuck you dude I hate you yeah, nobody called me sparse heron
Nobody say that I said it first and no one else can say it. Mm-hmm. Yeah. Yeah. Hey, that's pretty good
I think the fans will love my newfound love of rock and roll. Nobody likes rock except you anymore, dude
Literally people have moved on. Yeah. It's all about role. It's about the role now. People don't like the rock anymore.
I think a few YouTube comments will disagree with you. Yeah.
Mm-hmm. From unsuspecting people. Mm-hmm. Yeah, I'm a clown at the circus and I actually really like this song.
Yeah.
Yeah. Impressive, right?
Just say it. I know you wanna say it. Yeah, yeah.
We're just talking about like going on like Aerosmith songs and just seeing YouTube comments that are like
I'm the blackest guy alive and even I love this song. It's so it's so funny to see that.
I'm a black guy in the hood and I love this song. Yeah there's comments on like
happy birthday that are like I'm a famous black guy and I love this song. Yeah I'm
actually Tupac and I think this is the best song ever. I saw Christian posted something
or forever ago but he said it to me the other day that was like a it's like a
YouTube comment that was like this is the only song this song reminds me of my
brother like this was his the last song before he died and then the next comment was from
Adolf Hitler and it was this is the best song ever. It rocks. Yeah it's so good I do love those people who make
YouTube channels that called like yeah like fucking Che Guevara and they just
comments on Minecraft videos yeah how do I get good at redstone?
J Guevara. Right, because it's like comments from like six years ago and it's like Peter
Griffin and it's like he will not divide us. Yeah yeah the Noid love Trump's hate.
Oh damn they they breaking out the fleshlight freaks this season. Is that so?
Oh what does that mean? What are you even talking about? Alien fleshlight, Dracula fleshlight,
Predator fleshlight, Redditor? Every fleshlight's a Predator fleshlight. Did you say Redditor?
Redditor. Predator fleshlight. Dude, Alien vs. the Redditor dude. Imagine what that looks
like. Yeah, probably not very fun. Oh hey, when you think about it, the Reddit logo is
an alien. That's true. NOOOO! Oh, this is a fleshlight with two pussies. Damn! So you
That's Dr. Jekyll and Mrs. Hyde.
Yo this fleshlight fucked the whole squad dude.
That's right.
I'll pass it to the left.
Yeah.
This fleshlight belongs to the cyborg fleshlight.
Maybe that's my thing.
Maybe I want to share a fleshlight.
Yeah?
No.
No, it's just because you love communism so much that you want to share your fleshlight
with your homies.
Yeah, hey, seize the means of reproduction, am I right?
Whoa!
All right, I think we just made the best episode ever.
Cameron coming in with heaters.
I think we just hit the, I just think we just hit it.
I think we were getting close and then you said that,
might have put us over the top.
Might be at number one right now.
God damn.
Defcon one.
God damn, God damn.
Do I love this song?
I found my copy.
Oh my God, you found the Communist Manifesto?
I got a copy of Capital right there off camera.
Nice, I have a copy of--
You know, I didn't realize it was this thin too.
I have a copy of the rap yearbook by Shea Serrano.
Oh damn.
It's kind of the same thing.
Damn.
I got How to Develop and Use Psychometry by Ted Andrews.
If anyone wants to learn psychic powers.
Nice.
I could do that.
Very cool.
Do you have a book on how to protect yourself from psychic attacks?
I've been getting attacked lately.
Yeah.
I am getting attacked.
I actually am.
You've been getting attacked by rats, not psychically like me.
They're mice.
I was listening to this podcast that was, I forgot about this period in my life, but I
was really obsessed with learning about like psychic attack and stuff.
I was listening to this podcast that was meant to like develop your mind, your like psychic
powers or whatever.
And it was just, it would just be like a woman talking for like an hour.
And I think it's the closest thing that I've ever, that I've ever come to like being actually
brainwashed. I would just sit there and play Binding of Isaac and it would just be like
this woman's voice talking over a drone that would just be like, "There are
structures on the moon. You need to defend yourself." I would
start listening to it and then it would just be over and I wouldn't remember
anything that she said and I'd be like, "Oh, this is very bad." Yeah. Did you find that in Ascension
- Desmian Fifth Dimension?
- No, I found it on a--
- Oh, remember that shit, dude?
- Yeah, that's like-- - That Facebook group?
- Yeah. - I'm still in that.
- That's a great Facebook group.
- What was our guy who we thought killed himself?
- Desmian Blu-ray. - Desmian Blu-ray.
- Yeah. - Oh, yeah.
- Everybody check out Desmian Blu-ray.
That's a really good Facebook friend.
- I'm gonna check right now if he's been posting anything.
- Remember, I stopped posting or reading anything in there
because that woman sent me that Facebook message.
- I don't remember that. - Remember that?
- I don't remember that. - The one,
it was a woman, a woman called me
asked me to protect her she left me a
face with horsemen. Oh yeah like an older lady?
Yeah yeah it was like an old lady called me
because I had my profile
picture was me holding like it was a photoshop
of me holding a buster sword and
she was like I need you to protect me
I need you to
protect me
we're gonna fight the demons
I was like I can't
I can't be a minister. Did you protect her?
I failed
to protect her. She was killed by a demon
From the Ascension Facebook groups I moved on into all the targeted individual and gang stalking groups.
And those ones are genuinely depressing. They're so fucked up dude.
There are people who will just post videos of their houses and shit and be like
"I am being attacked by microwave rays that are making me think about how I am in love with boys."
And shit like that.
But then you'll also see people will go in there and post little infographics that are like
it's perfectly legal to kill somebody or harm them if you think they are
gang stalking you. Oh yeah I did see that. Yeah and it's just like just trying to get people to do mass shootings it's so
fucked up dude. Yeah. Yeah. I'm looking through my my Facebook groups. We should
start gang stalking someone. We should. We should be the first podcast to actually be
sending someone secret messages. Yeah. Yeah. We honestly should. Derek. Yeah. Yeah. We
We already said that bit before.
We did that bit before with I think the name,
we said like, Michael, if you're driving a car right now,
and then somebody after that episode came out,
somebody messaged me and said,
my name is Michael and I was driving a car,
and you really freaked me out.
- We should, you should have just not responded,
we just kept going with it.
- I did not respond to that, and we're still going with it.
- Michael, wherever you are right now,
just fucking kiss, just kiss your hand.
Start fucking making out with your hand.
- Get a kiss from me. - Send us some photos.
yeah it's me behind the bearded barley
lightly again with the rock oh my god
hey I got one question for you you
fucking lowlife punk motherfucker do you
ever stop rocking no oh my god you're
like the dad in the twisted sister music
you get out of here take these posters
down get these candles out of your room
I want to rock I was when we're listening
we were listening to the like the
classic rock station in your car on the way back from New York and it's just like
it's so fucking funny to me that people heard that stuff and where it was like
oh this is the devil yeah yeah a song that's like jump around let's have fun
let's all party until the Sun and then the parents are like oh my god it's a
crazy yeah that's like that's like hearing like run DMC now and like just
the fucking moral panic that like parent like fucking Tipper Gore had in the 80s
yeah it's like this is gonna lead kids into gang violence
I can't wait till we-
and then all the sons are like "MY ADIDAS ARE COOL AND THEY DON'T WEAR THEIR LACES IN THEM"
well that's the next phase of it is parents are all gonna think that their their children are
turning trans because they're listening to a hundred gecks
exactly yeah it's so fucking weird
I can't wait till we are old enough that we are like so out of touch and have like
because I think people even if they don't agree with shit like that
they have that something is pulling them to yeah there's always there is a
little better nobody has ever thought it was going to happen to them and then it
was i cannot wait for like twenty years when something comes out where i'm just
like i truly can't understand this right that's like that's like millennials
listening to like six four five they are
like jackie yeah yeah i definitely have had a of fucking like what is this crap
moment you know like
what is it is a little like an hour or so they are it's like i listen to it i'm
and I'm like, oh, I understand this.
- Yeah.
- Like I get what it is, but like--
- Come on, Dad.
Everybody's fucking their car.
Come on, Dad.
It's cool.
It's cool to fuck my car.
- Let me fuck the Miata, Dad.
- I'm not sure about all this fucking your car business.
Nah, man, it's cool.
They put an extra hole.
- Everyone's doing it.
- Everybody's fucking their car now.
- You just put a beer koozie in the exhaust pipe, Dad.
Come on.
- That's right.
- Come on.
- Maybe that's Caleb's thing.
- And if you want a really fun time,
you leave the car running.
Do you think people buy like, are there certain cars
that are female?
Yeah, whatever year's in.
No!
(laughing)
As their war's in.
Like, do you think like a Miata?
You think like people who drive Miatas are like--
Probably like a Honda, yeah, like a Honda Samantha.
(laughing)
Honda Samantha.
Yeah, that's probably a girl car.
A Mitsubishi Claire.
Yeah, those are all total girl, 'cause most cars do,
they haven't come out with a girl car yet.
They've always--
Well, that's the thing, most cars look like,
most cars are phallic.
- Most cars look like boys.
- Yeah.
- You wanna tell me that a fucking Dodge Charger is female?
- Convertibles look like vaginas to me.
- Okay, there we go.
- The convertible is the foreskin.
It's also a male car.
- 'Cause all cars look like the driver has a big penis.
- Is that true?
- Uh-huh.
It depends on the car.
All muscle cars, all sports cars.
- It's funny that people think that people
with cool cars have small dicks.
It's like, no dude, they're rich and you're poor.
- Yeah.
- Just shut up.
- Come from me.
- Yeah, sorry you have a Honda Civic.
(laughing)
They're cool and rich.
- Hummers I get, like, I understand there's some people,
like some cars that I'm like, yeah, you know, like a Hummer.
- A Hummer just means that you fucking miss
killing people in Afghanistan.
- Yeah.
- That's why you buy a Hummer.
- No, but it's the people who buy Hummers
who like want to act like that.
- You either miss killing people in Afghanistan
or you really, really wish that you could miss
killing people in Afghanistan.
because it's those guys that it's those guys that like act like uh... it like
they know about like security and shit
yeah guys who like yeah you know i've never served but by also uh... has
scouted every exit every possible exit yeah created i always say i think that
they want to have that they want to get it well i'm i'm scouting the security
uh... uh... tactics of this location i'm seeing there is one door here with a
lock we also have a window that several stories off the ground and in a very
serious situation i could probably wriggle down the toilet hole
I'm gonna be in this there's a very tactical position in the women's locker
room I will be in a tactical position possible. Ma'am, I am putting
the GoPro here for surveillance. My father-in-law every time he walks into a
restaurant has to be sitting at a place where he's looking at the door. Yeah and
just in case a really sexy lady comes into the door. His eyeballs need to go out the door if they touch the wall those contacts will get all messed up.
That's a really good point.
Yeah.
I don't know.
When his eyeballs spring out of his head like that wolf in the cartoon, he's got to, they
got to go out the door or something or a window at least.
I say that but every time that I'm in a movie theater, I'm like, I could, if I needed to,
I could jump off of a balcony.
That's different.
Even if I break my legs, I could crawl my way out of this.
Yeah.
That's, I mean, fucking James Holmes ruined all that shit.
You're right.
Nobody's ever been shot in a restaurant, thank God.
No.
- Ask Robert Blake.
He didn't shoot his wife, he just left his gun there.
- That's right.
- Was that Robert Blake?
- I don't know who you're talking about.
Sometimes you say stuff with these names
that I don't understand and I just say,
yeah, yeah, no, I know what you're talking about.
And I just hope that you move on
and start talking about SpongeBob or something.
- Patrick knows the name of every man
that has ever lived on this earth,
but he can't figure out what three plus four is
in under five seconds.
- I'm different kind of smart.
- I'm just stating facts, I didn't say it was good or bad.
- It's called street smarts, okay?
- Yeah.
- It's called being smart about men.
- It's called knowing every man alive.
- Exactly.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So he, Robert Blake took his wife out to dinner.
- Who's Robert Blake?
- He is the weird guy in that David Lynch movie.
- Oh yeah, dude, the weird guy.
- The weird guy in the David Lynch movie.
- The weird, how downright, of course,
the weird guy in that David Lynch movie.
- Lost Highway.
I knew it was, I knew he had the word highway.
- The mystery man?
- Yeah, he's the mystery man in Lost Highway.
- He killed his wife?
He, um...
That adds another layer to that scene.
Wow.
He killed his wife
at, uh, like after he left the restaurant.
Um...
He returned to the restaurant and was like, "Hey, I left my pistol here."
What? He killed his wife and then was like,
"Ah, crap. I left my... Hey, sorry to be a pain. I left my pistol."
He told his wife and then he walked into the restaurant and he went,
um... well you see i couldn't come i wife cuz i'm actually not in the restaurant
i'm at your house
rick and i'm calling you know
it is fun to have a little bit of a little bit of a left in the restaurant
wasn't the murder weapon
danny strapped up
and okay
uh... again okay
all right
i get i get robert blake and phil specter confused
you get regina specter confused with yourself
Yeah. So?
Because you like to make music so much.
Beautiful.
You like to make girl music.
You like to make music for girls.
So?
So what? That's all we're saying. We're not saying anything else.
You guys are getting mad at me again.
I hate you.
I'm going to come over to your house.
Let's not, don't end this on a bad note.
You're right. I love you so much.
I'm going to come over to your house and I'm going to do some nice things to you.
Yeah. I'm going to tickle you with a feather.
That's so nice.
No, it's not going to be nice. You're not going to like it.
What about like what if I got into tickling next time you guys are in New York?
Can you guys just tickle me all I come? Yeah, sure
Is there any way camera tickled me on the last episode I tickled you a few times did you like it though?
No, I hate being tickled because I like it. You laugh every time dude. I like you love it
I'm a little gig. I low-key like it
Joe don't say do not say i'm a little giggle bear
Don't say that, man.
He said, he said, "I'm a little giggle bear."
Don't fucking say that, dude.
I don't...
*laughing*
I can't think about this right now.
I have a mouse problem I have to deal with.
Now I'm gonna be sitting...
I'm gonna sit in the kitchen, I'm afraid of the mice.
And I'm gonna think, "Patrick is a little giggle bear."
What the fuck is wrong with you, dude?
We're trying to make money off of this show.
And you're saying...
I'm a little giggle bear. Shut up dude. Oh my god.
Patrick jiggles when he chuckles. Yeah. So what?
It's actually, it's one of your better qualities.
Right up with your bass skill. Alright.
Wait, play us out with a song. Play us a song.
Oh my god.
Bring us out with a song dude. No, I want to hear this.
Maybe he's gotten better since the beginning.
Sounds like shit.
Just play tool. Everyone wants to hear tool.
Okay.
I hit the D string. Wait, hold on.
No, I didn't say act like a tool.
What?
Son of a bitch.
I'm ending the episode now.
God damn it.
Bye y'all.
Bye.