You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
Go ahead, JGL, press record.
I did it. I did it already.
I think it is Marie Kondo.
It's hit record.
I think this is Marie Kondo right now.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, I think I am. I think I am gonna step in on this room.
Ugh.
I'm gonna make some big changes in your life.
I don't...
I don't want to talk about my room in another episode. This is the second time.
We keep doing it in your room.
No we didn't. This is only the second time.
I know and both times we have to talk. If we were in a castle, we'd be like, "Wow."
Every time, the castle would be impressive. Every time this room is insane.
I mean, also I will admit if I lived by myself, it'd be like 50 times worse than this.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, no.
There's like-
I'm doing good for how it used to be.
The thing is, I don't think that women--
When I was living at my parents' place, you guys never came over because you guys were
like fucking-- We were scared.
Yeah, you were scared, but scared of my parents.
No, you were afraid to let us near your parents.
Yeah, you were.
But-- Let me near them.
Oh, man, I just didn't clean at all.
Yeah.
I just-- There's no reason to.
I just had clothes everywhere, yeah.
Here's the thing is, living with a girl, I don't think that women should have to clean
everything or like have to do all of that shit but they're really really good
they're like really really good at it and I'm happy to help yeah I'm not very good
at it unfortunately no I'm also not good at it no so I just you know I recently
recently Janice started putting up like notes like on the fridge that'll be like
like that helps so much dude what am I eight years old and then it was like
this is genius. It's helping me so much. Like something that just says like, "Don't put
like a cup of water in the fridge." And I look at that and I'm like, "Oh, yeah, I guess I'll
just finish my water." Like it's crazy shit, dude. Like what my instinct is telling me
to do is like always just not conducive to a house at all.
Man, I feel like the fucking worst roommate most of the times because it's just like if
If I'm done drinking my cup of water,
I'll leave it on the counter just 'cause I wanna go get
more water later and I don't wanna wash a cup.
- Oh yeah, I do that.
Come on, man.
- But you gotta do it in your room, not on the counter.
- Or you need to have a holster that you carry around
with you that has a--
- With a big glass cup.
- Place that can put a cup.
- My Patrick Yoda cup.
- Exactly, yeah, something that could be attached
to your body, maybe like a money clip with a cup glued to it.
- Or like a wallet chain.
Yeah, yeah, wallet so you have a glass cup.
Yeah, it swings on a chain.
It's a glass cup with a hole in it that has a chain.
Yeah, and the hole in the bottom.
Yeah.
This is a good idea.
This is really smart.
Yeah.
'Cause if you think about it,
they already basically designed that
with those old bathtubs that have plugs on a chain, right?
So you basically just, you just have to find an old bathtub
and you can repurpose that.
So that's like green or eco-friendly or whatever,
'cause you don't have to build a new chain.
Yeah, and it's a green cup too.
It's very, it's green.
Oh my God.
It's made out of green.
Yeah. And...
It's pretty smart.
It's pretty smart shit, actually.
You can also take the claw feet off of the bathtub and use them like...
Why do they put them claw feet on those bathtubs?
So they can walk away.
I'm like... That like brought a tear to my eye right then.
I don't know why.
That's why kids hate taking baths.
It's evolutionary.
They used to see all the claw feet on the bathtub
and think it was a bear.
Yeah.
And so they were like, "I'm not climbing in there."
It's like dogs only take him back.
I think it's another dog.
Exactly, yeah.
Because they remember back when there used to be claws on it.
I'll show you this.
Like with ancestral DNA.
Remember like two...
What happened to you, man?
Two episodes ago, I think it's two episodes ago, I talked about how I just got so sweaty
that I had to buy a pack of undershirts.
I bought them from like this like, you know, just one of those stores that just exists in
New York that says like 99...
99.
That's it. Yeah, it just says 99 on it. You go. It's a bro brothers 99. Yeah, it's like yeah 59 cent 99 cent 79 cent
109 all you can have
Lovely brother. I went in there
Happy $100
What is that one in happy 100?
Star and it's like the more you know star. Yeah, what is it?
like a big picture of a baby on it too. Yeah and it's like a picture of that store because I walked
by it. It has like a really really old fucked up uh Mickey Mouse ride. Yeah yeah like happy 100 bb
shop. Happy 100 bb shop that's what it was. Yeah yeah bb shop. But uh yeah just one of those stores
and uh I went and I bought a pack of bootlegs Hanes undershirts. Okay. And uh it has this was
straight out of the pack. It just had a bunch of like letters numbers and letters on it. Sharpied
onto it yeah what out of the pack well let's see I'm trying I'm looking at this
this is not a phone number no no this is like a like like a routing number one
two two four seven four two m h four one nine - two eight three eight - two oh I
swear to God that's like a routing number it's yeah for like a package I
I feel like that might be the last words of a madman.
Of a madman who's lost his mind.
And you know what?
Another shirt in the pack, it was a pack of three shirts, another shirt in the pack on
the back had like, I guess there was a hole in it and they just stitched it up.
It's pretty cool.
Yeah, it's pretty cool.
Come on.
Oh no, I'm not, you know.
A factory made shirt would never have that kind of care put into it.
They would never stitch it up.
I think it's on the back here.
there any red because there was a red there was red on the third shirt I do
not see red okay I have one a similar style shirt from a similar kind of place
that just has like a giant line in the middle of it yeah I didn't know yeah it's
a black shirt with a big white line in the middle of it is it like it's not
supposed to be there yeah no it's like it's like clearly like they just fucked
up like dying this one area and it's just a line of white and does it go all
the way across? No, it doesn't even go, it goes like eight inches across. That's
awesome. It's horrible because I looked at it and I guess I looked at the wrong
side of it when I bought it. You know I got home and I turned it around to the
front, big-ass white line. Yeah, pretty unlucky. Yeah, it's cool. I'm just
learning, the thing that sucks dude is like especially living here, you
just, everything, if you want to have like good shit like that, like cheap
t-shirts you have to buy them from amazon.com. You cannot support any local
business because they are fucking evil here dude I swear to God. They're always
like yeah they like you know and they'll like they try to sell you like the
weirdest shit at the counter. There's always like I'm always skeptical at like
a clothing store where I get to the counter and these are all over in New
York. I get to the counter of the clothing store and there's food for sale.
yeah there's like candy and like like fresh fruit yeah you can't mix those
those yeah I'm like how do you come on the same truck like why do you have this
too yeah like this should not like like a pack of like trident gum and a passion
fruit exactly yeah like where do you get yeah where do you get a knockoff Haynes
t-shirt that like literally fell off of a truck yeah like a barrel of bananas
like a Donkey Kong barrel of bananas it's huge yeah and then like every flavor of
gum why do you sell those three things? I don't know maybe it's maybe it's just
something we don't understand as as a as freaking gentrifiers. I'm not a
gentrifier I'm born and raised in New York City. Yeah? Yeah. Really? I've never
left I'm one of those people who draws a map of the United States in New York City
is like the size of like Florida and then everything else is really small I
I know somebody who drew, who you two know, who's from New York, who in college I had them
draw America.
They left off Florida and Texas, drew a bubble, and then New England was like just a dick hanging
off of the top.
It's the craziest thing I've ever seen.
And I asked her, I was like, "How wide do you think the United States is?"
She was like, I was like, "Really think about this, like give me an honest answer."
said 1,000 miles. This is the worst city. We know it's like 2,000 miles. This makes this
city produces the worst people in the world. It is absolutely the worst. It's so horrible.
People who are from New York are like disgusting to me. It's just Colin, my roommate. Especially
Yeah, yeah, it's Colin Jo and just like defend this yeah, maybe that's no it is it warps your brain. Yeah
No, it's not the water is too good the water has too many little shrimps in it. There's not shrimp
What are you talking about? Why are you anti New York water? It's got a little shrimp in it. When did you see?
- yeah, it was like your favorite. I like shrimp when I can see it
Shrimps it's shrimps and you drink it and they go in your brain and they make you say things like mad brolic
No, that's cool. Those guys from New York are cool. Yeah. No, I mean like like white people from Manhattan are like, oh
People they're all yeah. Yeah, it's like I say brolic like that's that's like why I moved here to say brolic
Yeah, I watched the movie kids and I said that's mad brolic. You took a lot of lessons from that. No, I didn't
Basically my goal is to the scene in
Was watching Harold hunter clips so fuck off I was not you're typing in kid hunter
Kids I
I was watching that it just I forgot that in that movie there's like a in within
like three minutes it's like how to roll a blunt and a bunch of kids just
murdering a black guy yeah it's like pretty it's pretty crazy movie what the
hell were they on when they made that oh my god sugar yeah
Harmony Corrine probably had so much damn sugar he was like I'm gonna make a whole
movie about it. I'm gonna make the craziest movie ever. And also here's the thing do
you think when he do you think he start he was like I'm gonna make a movie about
kids? He wrote that when he was like 17. Okay but do you think he was like, do you think
it later it became weird or at first like at first he was maybe just like
yeah it'll just be about you know. Yeah the director I think it was Larry Clark
directed it and he was probably like very old at the time and I don't know I mean
no disrespect to Larry Clark but if if someone came to up to me and said hey I
want to make a movie about kids probably like all right hold on yeah
no that's what you would have done yeah I'm the hunter so yeah do you guys need
a hunter involved in the production? You guys need someone with like a really good nose like the
nose of a bloodhound. I don't have a good nose. I mean I can help with auditions too.
I don't I'm not good at casting either you are you would be great at casting no
I wouldn't you just treat what do you mean? It's like your own. It's like American Idol
Would not be good at that just fucking admit. You're right. You would you wouldn't let you be the fucking Paula
Mm-hmm you'd be Paul Abdul. I would yeah, I'd be drunk all the time everybody come in you'd be like
Oh, honey
That would be you.
Dude, so, I mean, there's a cultural moment, like, it sucks that it doesn't exist anymore,
but it also makes complete sense that that doesn't exist anymore.
American Idol?
Yeah.
They got rid of all the mean shows.
It wasn't even that mean.
Dude.
Well, yeah.
The only good shit was the mean shit.
Yeah, William Hung, I mean.
I mean, all the mean shit was like the funny and good parts of that shit.
I mean, Sam, we were talking about fucking Susan Boyle yesterday.
Yeah.
like Susan Boyle you would you could never do that today she wouldn't even be
famous because she would come on and they'd be the whole thing would be like
well we expect you to be talented because you're very ugly mm-hmm but then
like it well you know she was a trailblazer in that regard maybe maybe
she changed the whole culture yeah in 2000 like like it would not be
acceptable now for an ugly woman to come out and then doll be like get a load of
this fucking ugly bitch remember this is what the whole thing was they
immediately just like did her hair different when she was like continuing
to like be a competitor on that show and everyone was just like she was
actually beautiful the whole time yeah it's like they just did her hair yeah
they just had like whoever does like the the the stuff for like the show poodles
they had that person they show up they were like listen it's not exactly a dog
but you do she's not very good-looking and she needs to look good enough for TV
it was well she was just like Irish or something she's an old Irish woman she
was the swamp that she's at the swamp then yeah I mean she was cool though
yeah also she kind of leaned into it a little bit you know cuz like there's
some shit you can do to not look well I mean that must have sucked so bad just
like immediately just everybody like like ugly woman sings awesome yeah just
like god I would have fucking killed myself after. You go up there you're like I just
I just look normal I look normal to me and then like immediately it's just like
oh look at this disgusting bitch. Yeah horrible slug monster sings almost
inhuman thing sings pretty good yeah but like also the thing is if she sung like
if she sounded like Britney Spears or something that'd be different but she
also sings like if she rapped. What if she went up there and she did rap
She was rapping granny the Susan Boyle rap is what we're trying to create
Yeah, but if she the problem is that she also has like she has like an opera voice, which is like
Yeah, what ugly people sing like that's like yeah like that. Oh, yeah. No you make perfect sense
Yeah, well, it's like that that the voice France clip where the guy who's like
I think he's like blind or something, but his eyes are like completely
Yeah, and he comes out and he does the like crazy opera singing and then he transitions into lose yourself
Yeah, he does lose yourself. Yeah, but like in like
But singing in not rapping. Yeah, most French, but it's English. Yeah, it's a thing where he's like approximating the pronunciation
Yeah, it's awesome
It's really good
It's funny and also like, you know
that's the thing where like their their their chairs are like facing the other
way and they have to like vote in so you think they're all there because they all
press the button really fast either they like all press the button and see his
cross eyes and go oh no and then just press a button again and go back
turn back around that should be an option yeah that would be so fun the
voice should be there should be one button that turns them around still
going on there should be one button that turns them like 180 degrees so they're
like and and there should be another button that just turns them all the way
around to fake them out. There should just be tubes of spinning around me.
Just constantly spinning. You know the button where you press it and they like turn a little
bit but then turn back and then turn a little bit more and then turn back.
So it's like three buttons like the one to do that and then the third one is to turn
someone else as a prank and you get to use that once. Yeah yeah it's like the
golden exit. And then it can be then the the voting is more fun then they can have
like it doesn't have to be all these like you know celebrities or whatever we can
just have people having that can be like its own the audience has those chairs so
the whole audience is turned to their backs faced to you yeah and and they're
always going oh by ten minutes into the show everybody just that's what they
they're not even watching they're just like enjoying spinning also as the show
goes on every minute the...
One guy's spinning super super fast.
Every minute that passes on the show the motors that turn the chairs get a little bit more
powerful so they gradually start moving faster and faster so you have to be careful because
if you try to spin a little bit but you spin really fast you go all the way around you
know that's it.
Well that's if you're too eager if you're too much of an eager beaver with your spinning
they they pump up they double it every single time.
And then and then after the commercial break they had a button that makes your chair go
up and down yeah like what those shows don't exist anymore but like they just
added higher stakes to them you know I mean like yeah like now we have like the
masked singer and stuff which is fucking to me like I don't give a like the whole
point of those shows I mean what Kermit popped out I was like holy I mean I was
like Kermit. I didn't know you had it like that.
Oh shit, Kermit what the hell? Who knew you could sing?
I think there is a version of the...
Real fans of Kermit know that he sings on Rainbow Connection.
He had pipe singing way back.
The Masked Singer could be like an insanely good show if they picked the right people to be inside there.
Yeah, they got Jenny McCarthy on there.
If they got like OJ Simpson, if he popped out, that would be like...
Jason Voorhees.
That would be really, really good.
Or OJ Simpson is dressed up as Jason Voorhees and they're like, "Who's this guy?"
They also have to have some people that just pop out and nobody's ever heard of them.
There's a hobo.
"Oh my god, it's former French President Nicolas Sarkozy!"
You know what I mean?
Like I feel like there's some mix of people that they could have on that show that would
make it like a perfect TV show.
Like apparently they had T-Pain.
It's like, dude, T-Pain would have been probably the second guest I would have had.
Yeah, don't have any singers.
Yeah.
No singers.
Oh, you can't have a singer on The Masked Singer.
What are you doing, man?
man yeah like just fucking Kevin Hart uh-huh I don't know if he's been on it
but that'd be a good one mm-hmm no they who me Susan Boyle cuz yeah she
wouldn't even have to wear a mask no she would she would take it off the
be like, "Susan Boyle, yeah! Put the mask back on, yeah! Come on, woo!"
Oh man, you know what would be the best one? So like, big, like, caterpillar--
The Headless Horseman.
I'm picturing it now, like, big caterpillar costume, comes out, wiggles out, right?
So like, you know, dude coming out on stage, big, like, foam, like, green--
He's like inchworming.
Yeah. Yeah, he's, you know, he's basically doing the worm on the stage while he's singing.
singing okay you know he does his song and then they're like okay who who the
hell is this Jared Fogle that would be good and if they and if they choose it
should be if he makes it all the way to the end he's exonerated mm-hmm it should
only be like like people who have fallen from grace or been canceled or can get
horrible and whoever wins they get there cleared of wrong doing it ever that's
actually so good I'll be such a good is your voice so good that it can redeem
you exactly that is so good yeah I mean dude my if Michael Jackson was oh yeah I
mean he would he would keep doing it all he would like you would get off and then
he's like bring another kid and come back the next year just he could keep
just getting big free yes thank you did that do I think Michael Jackson did it
yeah let's be real did he I don't know I mean here let me show you a video of a
moonwalking and then tell me. You know I have seen the music video for
Bad and been like man what a talent like. Oh yeah dude. It's crazy. I listen to Do You
Remember the Time and I'm like there's like no pedophiles ever like made
something beautiful right like that's like that's like a natural law right
that's like gravity. Yeah. It's like an evil deranged pedophile cannot make a
beautiful piece of work. It just wouldn't make any sense. Well they all the Greeks did all
that did invented math and and true that shit sucks though yeah I'm talking about
video games and movies yeah there are no pedophile movie makers yeah they made
beautiful ones name a beautiful movie that pedophile didn't make transformers
Michael was a pedophile no he's not yeah yes how do we know you know because he
made transformers I've already speaking of the Greeks I'm dropping some some
logical theorems on you right now oh and you were you were getting owned you're
using a theorem invented by a pedophile? No. Yeah you are. On purpose. I just remembered when I was like
11 when Michael Jackson died. What? Oh you didn't know? No. Oh sorry.
Shit I'm sorry to tell you that. It's okay. In my bedroom. It's okay. When Michael Jackson died
my my uncle Kevin who'd made the most jokes about Michael Jackson being a diddler. A diddler. A
fucking diddler he's a fucking diddler the guy who made the most jokes about it
sat us all down and made us like watch like the vh1 like Michael Jackson loop
and was like he was so talented oh he was the most talented guy ever he was yeah
dude he's like he's number one it what a fucking what a what a moment what a
moment culturally I got a text from a girl in my middle school and it was like
plea it was like Michael Jackson the king of pop has died please pray for his
family and send this to like ten people and I was like and I was like dude I
mean what is a better way to memorialize Michael Jackson than a bunch of 11 year
old
like that is so beautiful yeah so beautiful you know those those texts were
going around like years and years before that was like Oh Michael Jackson he's
about to die he needs a picture of your face right now. It's funny that he was
killed by his doctor yeah the doctor was like I'm fucking I don't know a hundred
pills a day whatever that's just so funny to me. That guy rules.
Yeah Conrad Murray. Conrad Murray. That's a cool action hero name yeah yeah like
that's yeah action hero name. That's like the name of like one of the soldiers in
predator yeah yeah it makes sense yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I mean that guy
should like a medal of honor would be funny to just like you go and you just
show up at Conrad Murray's house and just give him a trophy
this Conrad Murray the pedophile clear a giant check for a hundred more pills
Woody Allen next buddy go crazy damn it's gonna be so I mean yeah funny but
like you know funny to see the like the reaction when Woody Allen like eventually
dies next year yeah just like all the like like all the people who are like
"Yeah, but I mean Manhattan's a great movie" or whatever, like the people like the die-hard defenders and like
Like look I get it like Annie Hall, good movie
Woody Allen
Jury's still out on that guy
The thing is stop making Diane Keaton dress like a motherfucking four-year-old boy. What is she doing?
What is he doing those movies man? I don't think- She's a beautiful woman, put her in a dress. I think she dressed herself
Diane Keaton, you the stupidest bitch on earth
What are you doing man?
I don't think I've ever seen a Woody Allen movie.
Really?
Yeah, I mean there.
Movie night, us three, oh my god.
Yeah, I mean the thing is like, you know, I can, like the Woody Allen movies I can all
day be like, oh yeah, I wouldn't watch those, like because the guy who made them is a bad
guy.
But I've also watched like two guys one hammer like three different times.
Those guys were way worse as like creators of something. Behind the scenes they were pretty bad.
Yeah, I mean the thing is you can't really watch a movie that's not evil.
Yeah, that's true. It's not possible.
I mean, what, like the Weinstein Company made...
They did the first 30 episodes of this podcast.
well yeah that's all I think right it's all freaking fucked up dude it's all
weird and crazy dude Hollywood got me fucked up he's got me pissed off we're
not gonna be alive after this episode comes out do that as we just exposed all
the secrets yeah fuck I don't think I don't think Hollywood people kill
anybody there yeah they're just no they they hire people in Las Vegas to kill
people but they also are like like to them like the sentence worse than death
is like you'll never be in a movie yeah which is like it is I remember the
something always makes me laugh is like like Michael Crichton who's a guy who
wrote like Jurassic Park yeah and shit he like some reviewer or something gave
him a really bad review for his book and then in the next book he wrote he named
a character after that guy and made the character a pedophile with a
the tiny penis. I think more like, more filmmakers and stuff should be doing stuff like that.
Yeah, that is like, yeah, that is the way, yeah, that's so much better than killing somebody.
Yeah. Especially make like a really good movie and people like, are like, remember it for
like years and years. Yeah. I mean, how many people do you think that has happened to though?
Well, let's think of all, who, who's, who dies in movies in a funny way? Uh, Robin Williams.
I would hate to be the guy that Kenny from South Park is based off of.
I would be so embarrassed.
That guy's been getting hell from Matt and Trey for decades.
They've been destroying him.
Are you guys excited for the 400 South Park movies?
Speaking of.
It's so funny.
No, that's exactly what Matt and Trey, or Trey Parker did to his ex-girlfriend in Cannibal
the Musical.
He, the horse.
He named the horse in Cannibal the Musical after his ex-girlfriend.
In the movie, it's basically just like, it's all euphemisms to "she's a whore."
Then in the video, the commentary of the movie is just him having a breakdown.
It's like, "Oh yeah, she's married to a manager at Bennigan's and oh look at me, I just made
the fucking South Park movie!"
It's fucking nuts.
It's so funny, any movie that's about high school or college or something, you can tell,
can like see characters that are like oh yeah this is somebody who the director
knew and maybe made fun of the director one time in the lunchroom yeah yeah
yeah some bully who has like a very specific interest yeah it doesn't really
fit at all yeah you know yeah I think speaking of the like South Park guys I
was saying earlier I was like I think like my goal in life is to have one of
those like 50 year cartoons yeah we're like the cast keeps dying and shit you
just keep doing it forever yeah yeah like what are they they're in talks to buy
Casa Bonita in Colorado I don't know I'm that sounded like straight from a TMZ
headline and you're like yeah what are they in talks right now I did I did see
that on yeah it's like a real restaurant in Colorado where like they're in talks
to buy it yeah they're gonna buy sources say sources say yeah my sources sources
close to the to the conversation yeah Harvey Levin yeah they say in talks to
is like so funny cuz it's in every headline it means like nothing at all
like it just means somebody told me that this guy actually was talking to another
guy maybe yeah yeah I'm in talks to go to the bathroom right now yeah I'm in talks
with the cashier to get a McDouble pretty soon yeah sources close to but the
cashier say that at least. It's just another cashier. It's close to my dick saying I'm pissing.
It's just another cashier like whispering into the ear of the cashier. I mean who are
these people like so if either of you two got insanely famous I would never like if
a TMZ called me and they were like like what's Cameron's favorites lunch I wouldn't like
tell them you know like what's what's Cameron's son mad at him? I know what your
favorite lunch is. What is it? One saltine. It's not. Two saltines. Nope. Three saltines. No.
Four saltines. No. One saltine with cheese on it. No. One saltine with peanut butter on it. You're never gonna get it.
You're never gonna get it. I bet I can get it. Look at me. I actually don't know what my
favorite lunches you're about to okay what is it say something I'm thinking
enough I'm thinking I can't do that look at me no stop mac and cheese no fuck
look at you and fall in love then that was for nothing
one sandwich yeah usually a sandwich oh my god I don't like it very much though
let's go dude let's fuck I fucking I got his favorite lunch and you didn't know
Mac and cheese your lunch my favorite look at me look at me look at me look at
me
got it on this is an easy one yeah macaroni and cheese it's not macaroni and
cheese somebody
yeah I haven't had like a very like a good a good like baked mac and cheese in
a minute. Yeah I would like some of that. We should go to Boston Market.
Dude, I've been just... I would... dude I love Boston Market. Boston Market's
fucking awesome. Yeah when I when I lived in that hotel in Manchester. They always have some fucked up mashed potatoes.
Yeah. When I lived in that hotel in Manchester there was a Boston Market that
is unfortunately closed down now. No. But yeah we got dinner there a few
times and every time I we would take it back to the... you got to eat it there
That's the thing about Boston market somehow it gets cold the second you leave the door the minute you leave
It is the worst food in the world. Yeah, but you eat something about like in the restaurant
It must be like strip it's pretty good lights where they like
Specific way so that it like looks okay. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, is there are there any buffets open?
Are they all closed from fucking I would love to go to a book. Yeah, we should
I want to smorgasbord. So I've been like really hungry for a smorgasbord of something
I dude I I mean I've been dying to have a panoply of the light. Oh, do you guys know of any good cornucopia places?
That might have a cornucopia and like a big
In the in the Lower East Side, there's plethoras. Oh, I love a plethora. Yeah. Yeah
- If it was the real cornucopia, I'd be so fucking sick.
- See, the thing is, they don't have buffets around here
because all the old people here are rich.
- True, and they like little food.
- Yeah, they like little food on a big plate.
But if you go to the Midwest, it's small plate, big food.
- Big food, little plate.
That's the coastal divide.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, little food.
- We need to start making medium plates.
- That's true.
- Medium food, medium plate.
Yeah, I think like, yeah, 'cause you're right.
It's always a Dixie plate with three different sections.
You know, as if that's what you,
as if you're having three instead of 10 things
you put on that plate.
You know, 'cause that's the thing,
get rid of those fucking dividers, man.
I don't, it's all going to the same place.
Yeah, it's all going in my mouth, out my ass.
It's all going out my ass.
I don't need any of these dividers, you know?
And then the big plate problem--
I mean, I will say, I will say,
those dividers are good if you're, you know,
want some condiments maybe use it as like a...
But if you're at a buffet like... I mean the hardest part about a buffet is carrying all
the
food back to the damn table. That's true. That's a really good point.
I feel like a juggler.
You know those tubes they have at banks? Yeah and we put
you put all the food into a capsule.
You put it into the like vacuum tube and it goes boom and it goes
it flies around, it flies to a random table,
and you have to go sit at that table
because there's no dial or anything to control it.
- My dad seriously looked into trying to put one of those
in our house growing up.
- Yeah?
- He was like-- - Those are so cool.
- He was like, "That's the coolest thing ever."
He was like, "Why do you want that?
"Would it help you with work?"
And he was like, "No, I sit on the couch,
"I ask Mom to put a soda in the tube,
"and it appears right next to me."
I was like, "Somebody still has to get the soda, though.
It's not like an automatic, he's on a robot.
Even then, you'd have to calibrate the fucking tube so that the machine doesn't shake up your
soda.
Yeah, soda's gotta be the worst thing to send in one of those fuckers.
Same with beer, the only thing you can really put in there is a can of still water.
You know what movies always made look so cool?
Is having an old house with a dumb waiter.
I feel like in the movie a kid would go in a dumb waiter and go down to the next floor,
like in real life I feel like that's just like a machine that's designed to just
break children's arms and legs. Pretty much, yeah. Or like starve them. I saw I was in a
house with a dumbwaiter one time it was like my mom's boss's house and the
dumbwaiter's like it's like the size of like like a lunchbox. Yeah. No kid could
these dumbwaiters in movies are huge. Those ones are for laundry not for food.
That's another thing that looks so much fun jumping into the laundry chute. Dude
Dude, that, I bet that was sick.
I bet, yeah, dude.
Yeah.
Laundry chute, man.
Man, I wish I had a laundry chute.
We should get one.
Oh, yeah.
We should, we could like--
Hold on, let me check my--
Yeah, can I get a rent reduction?
I'm gonna put a laundry chute in.
Yeah, I have 18 minutes 'til my laundry's done.
Oh, nice, dude.
Yeah.
That's exciting.
Anything good in there today?
No, the machine did not,
one of the machines did not run.
So either I, somebody opened it
and didn't, you know--
- You're a two machines guy?
- Yeah.
- I just have--
- They're too small, I can't fucking--
- I miss having laundry, like I just go,
I have a laundromat now, and I don't even pay the guy
to like do it for me, 'cause it just is like,
even though it's only like 10 bucks extra,
I'm just like, I just don't like that.
- There's no reason to do that, yeah.
- Yeah, he like folds it and shit,
but I just go in and he's always trying to talk to me.
- Yeah.
- And I don't know what he's saying ever.
And so I just say yes, and then it's like clear
that I that he wanted me to say no and then he just talks to me until I leave
and then I come back he keeps talking to me and we do that every time so he just
and but everybody else seems to have the most normal relationship with him and he
just hates me and I've never done anything except spill a bunch of
detergent everywhere you realize he keeps saying you do you hate me do you
hate me do you hate me you're saying yes yes yes it's just every time he's asking
you every time to check it's like honestly that might be like in my week
the worst that I ever feel is leaving the laundromat I'm like I just feel like
I feel like I'm the villain in this laundromat.
- Yeah, I mean, I just hate doing laundry now.
I used to, when I had Inunit.
- You used to like it?
- I fucking loved doing it. - Inunit, what's that?
- Inunit.
- Oh.
When I did Inunit laundry down by the glacier,
this was, it was so easy.
- I mean, the color stayed in the shirts, you know?
It's not like the warm water.
- That's a good point, yeah.
- Can't even decide, can't even decide on the machine
downstairs if I want to do cold.
You're not really. - Really?
- Yeah, it's always warm wash.
Whenever I hit colors. - Oh, I thought you meant
You can't decide.
No.
You're like, "Cold, hot."
No, no. I always wash my clothes and always used to.
Uh-huh.
And now, like, the fucking-- the dye's running out of my shirts and shit.
Pissing me off.
I gotta--
Well, hey!
Pat, why don't you tell me, what else is ticking you off these days?
Come on!
That I gotta do fucking laundry.
Yeah?
I mean, what else are these little-- these little fucking moments in life that just make you say, "Pee-ew"?
What else?
I don't wanna do that.
Come on!
Yeah, come on, give me something.
Give me Patrick's Peeves!
What grinds your gears?
Ummm...
When you go down to the laundry room and your clothes aren't even dry?
That's like the same thing, but go on.
What gets your blood really boiling though?
When you don't have in-unit laundry.
Really?
This is all you got?
The only thing that makes you mad.
How about this?
There's so much fucking war in the world.
That's, that's much better.
You're getting there.
What else? Yeah, I don't know. I don't want to step on Louis Black's toes. How about demons?
Demons? Yeah, do those piss you off? I can take them or leave them. Really? Yeah, me too. I'm kind of on the fence.
Two thieves their own? What if I told... I mean they're red and hot. Does that piss you off anymore? Not really.
Yeah, that gets me red and hot because I'm saying, "Listen you demons, you're in my damn city."
You're a demon. Saying you're red and hot like a demon. No, they get me red and hot as in I'm a demon.
You said a demon is red and hot, and then you said you're red and hot.
What is that poking out of your shorts?
It's my penis, probably. I don't know.
Probably not a horn.
It's not a tail, either.
The red thing poking out of the back is your penis.
This is my normal penis.
Yeah, I have a red penis. Whatever.
And it comes out the back?
Yeah, I'm Italian. You know that.
They come out the back.
They don't come out the back.
No. Why is it...
Come on, touch it!
It's got hair on it.
You have a shaven penis? What's wrong with you?
You have a beautiful no hair penis. Just touch my fucking...
No, actually I...
Oh yeah, you cut a chunk out of your dick? I forgot.
Does it hurt? I forgot you told me that.
Yeah.
Does it hurt?
It did.
It did?
Yeah.
Pat just texted me and Cam the other day, he was like, "I cut a chunk out of my..."
Which is like, I've never done that.
I realized the other day that like I get hair on like the shaft like that's how fucking hairy I am dude. I'm like
It's disgusting. Yeah
so I was trying to like, you know clean it up because it looked weird and
Just immediately I just cut a chunk out
Well, I get this because if you shave if you shave like around your cock
But then not on your cock and your cock everything is Elsa shaving, but then you're like a huge thing
it looks like a goblin plant.
I looked down and there was like one hair like sticking up.
I was like, "Oh, that's fucking weird."
So do you shave it with like a razor sharp ice cream scoop?
No, I have a Philips OneBlade.
Oh my God.
I cut like a chunk out of the foreskin.
Oh God, dude.
Does it still hurt?
We shouldn't talk about this on the show.
Your doctor might listen.
It's true.
It's probably good, right?
like I had a moment where I was like, do I put a band-aid on this?
A band-aid on your cock?
Like the-
I almost did.
You just put on a condom and it holds all the blood in.
Just walking around with a condom taped to her cock with a cotton ball.
And then walking out of the bathroom holding it and it's like filled with blood.
To throw it away in the kitchen trash.
No, it like, I mean it like closed up, the wound closed up pretty quick.
Uh-huh.
But like-
You should have put a band-aid on it like the back of the guy's head in Pulp Fiction.
Yeah.
Because there's like a look thing.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Like I got like a Nelly thing going on with my penis.
Yeah, yeah exactly.
It would have been great.
Yeah.
But yeah, I fucking, I cut a chunk out dude.
Gross.
Nasty.
Yeah.
Maybe, maybe I should, maybe Brandon was right, I should get on that Manscaped thing.
I don't know what Manscape is.
My dad has one.
Really?
Yeah.
like a thing that like it's like suck all the hair off it's like it's like a
ceramic blade razor and it like yeah no fuck you I'm not doing advertising yeah
you better you pay us fucking pay me right now motherfucker you pay me for
this shit that's right I'm not telling you let him know I'm not telling you my
dad thinks about it google it yeah and don't even look at no listen to this and
you own it throw it away mm-hmm yeah throw it out right now it's disgusting
You know what else I hate? MailChimp.com. I fucking... MailChimp...
I go on there, I'm looking up, I want to see a mail chimp. I want to see...
If you ever make me send effortless newsletters to hundreds of people with the click of a
button again, MailChimp, I'm gonna fuck you up.
And, and, speaking of... And...
Yeah.
They don't even have a chimp, they don't even have pictures of chimps on their website.
Yeah, speaking of mail...
I gotta sign up for somebody's MailChimp newsletter called Chimp of the Day and it sends me a
picture of a chimp every day? I don't think so. Through the effortless...
Newsletters! Newsletters! One click newsletter! One button, one click, you're done!
I gotta do that to get pictures of chimps directly to my email? Come on!
One click, one button, you're done. Supposedly that's like the MailChimp promise or something.
And you know what else I fucking hate? Building websites.
Oh god! Oh come on! If a... what's it called again?
I don't even know. Some bullshit like Squarespace or something.
I think it's actually Squarespace. Yeah. That shit sucks.
There's like, here's an annoying thing. You log into Squarespace, all of a sudden
there's hundreds of templates to choose from. And they give you the tools to
help your own business. Oh my god. What's that? What's that? Square integration?
You're gonna make me vomit, Squarespace. Oh my god. And I hate how easy it is to
to start an online shop on there.
- Absolutely.
- Oh my god.
- Just pisses me off.
- 'Cause here's the other thing.
- And you don't even have to know HTML.
- No, no coding necessary at all.
But there are easy tutorials, supposedly,
if you do get yourself into a bit of a pickle.
And the other thing I hate is that it's so fuckin'
affordable.
It's too affordable.
- Oh my god.
- As a web designer myself,
They're stealing my business. I keep buying them. I know. I keep buying websites. And here's the other thing that I honestly hate.
That you know, let's talk about something we love for one second. Sure, yeah. I mean I for one I love going to the post office.
Yeah.
Oh my god, you know what's the best part about going to the post office is buying stamps. I know.
Yeah. You get to look at them. And sitting in that long ass line.
Uh-huh. Oh, I love that long ass line.
I love the lady who works there.
Mm-hmm.
She's super nice.
But what I would hate is if there was some way that you could send mail from home.
No.
I mean, I've been, people have been talking about this and it's like...
Really?
Yeah.
People have been...
Literally been pissing me off to no end.
Who's been talking about this?
Do you know Mark?
Yeah.
Oh, not Mark.
Mark.
Yeah, they got him.
They got him?
Yeah.
Fuckin' Christ.
But he, I mean, let's say this.
He's not like...
- My dad knew him too. - And this is how he betrays us?
- Oh yeah, this fucking guy. - Listen buddy, I get that you don't like the post office,
you have to go ruining it for everyone else. Every real American.
- You know? - Yeah. And you know, I thought, you know,
that guy was like an uncle to me. And you know what?
I'll say it, I'm disowning him right now. Fuck you Mark.
- That's brave. - You're not coming to my birthday.
- That's fucking brave man. - You're not coming to my fucking family reunion.
ask me to go on your show I won't do it yeah no I'm gonna tell you take that damn
ad off of your show and replace it with an ad for going to the post office yeah
exactly what I like to do how about that we should be doing ads for the post
office yeah yeah yeah I did I found out the other day that I have like remember
you remember when like there was a big thing or is like Oh Trump is gonna defund
the post office and then everyone was like buy post office t-shirts and buy
like it's like what the fuck you want you want to chill out money for fucking the
post office the fuck it's pretty weird I found it so when I forever 21 did a
collab with the USPS that's pretty cool flames though it's some of it did I will
say the other day I I remembered when I first moved to New York like a year ago
now I was like pretty broke and I needed like a job and so I asked around and
And some guy hooked me up with this dude he knew who like runs...
You hooked up with a dude?
No, but if I did it's okay because it's New York City.
This guy put me...
He hooked me...
I had sex with this guy who does these like sweepstakes scam things where he just sends
in like a million entries to like every sweepstakes so he eventually wins like tens of thousands
of dollars on them.
And so he's like, "Yeah, you just have to like handwrite these letters and pretend you're
me and send in as many as you can and I'll pay you like 10 cents per letter or like 4
cents per letter or something.
Was this just a guy that lived in your building?
No, it's a guy that a friend of mine knew and I just asked that guy who lives in New
York for work and he was like, "Oh, well I guess I know this fucking weird evil kid."
And so the dude dropped off a giant box of envelopes at my house and then also a bunch
of stamps and I never thought anything about it and then Jan had to mail
something yesterday and the stamps are like 50 cents each so it's like a
hundred and fifty dollars of stamps that I have right now and so now I'm looking
how to if I can sell the stamps that's like I just ripped that kid off yeah
back to that kid mmm so I'm back at a markup I feel like I'm scared now that
he's gonna like break my legs or something yeah well I mean you did talk
about it on the show yeah and I and I like like those things they got to my
house and I I think that was like the last month that we didn't make enough
money with the podcast I could like pay rent easily and then I as soon as it was
like even like a little bit more than that I just I just let that shit sit in
my fucking living room yeah never even thought about it I'm not doing that yeah
but so now I just said if you guys need envelopes or something or stamps I have
like a ton of them. Yeah go to Caleb.com. Yeah. Calebstamps.com it's a website I
just made with Squarespace. Mm-hmm. No. Mm-hmm. No. Mm-hmm. What other what other ads do
people talk about? Yeah I can't think of a single one. You know what I hate? What? I hate how
fucking discreet AdamNeeves.com is. Oh! The packaging. Here's the thing. Oh my god. The packaging gets to my door. I don't even know
what the fuck it is yeah I throw it away yeah I don't want a plane package they
should do they should have been $300 on yeah I want them I want the neighbors to
know how much fucking money I don't want to look like a poor idiot who's getting
a package from like company incorporated and brown cardboard like a vagina and
it should also have the voice box from a tickle me Elmo that says fuck me fuck
me fuck me just going over and over they should deliver it to my house in a
see-through roller backpack that is exactly bedazzled yeah yeah and it says
sex on it yeah and it has a speaker in it that says sex over and over again yeah
that's loud it says ooh you touch my tra la la yeah and I should have to use it
in my backyard exactly okay we pause I gotta get a water okay
I got sludge coffee. I did. I just drank some coffee. Was it like the coffee from Monsters Inc.
that I've always wanted to eat? It did look exactly like that. Dude, there's things like that in movies
that just like stick in my head as like that should be in my mouth. Yeah. Like I
have to have that in my mouth. Absolutely. Like the old man's finger when he's...
sewing woody back up yeah yeah yeah yeah that's the dirt from a bug's life oh my
Oh my god, you know that shit tastes so good.
Oh my god.
When the fat caterpillar eats the blue stuff.
Yeah, I would love to lick that.
Lick that caterpillar all the way down its back.
Ah, boysenberry!
Yeah, boysenberries, by the way, best fruit.
Never had a boysenberry.
Insanely good fruit.
Dude, the three-eyed fish from the Simpsons, oh my god.
Or that big fish from Star Wars Episode I.
Oh, dude, imagine filleting that bad boy.
Taking him out on him.
I don't know, I feel like that thing is probably
I don't know I feel like that thing is probably like dude I also I feel like
it's like a tilapia if you if you put your if you got your thumbs in both of
plow Coons eyes and just kind of like opened him up I feel like it'd be like
candle open there yeah it's good point yeah you know that we know that Kel
doors don't wear the masks or Megan Fox's butthole oh come on that's
disgusting. I would love to, what are they called? What's the Star Wars with the long
thing? A Twi'lek. I feel like you said that way too fast. They're sexy dude. Their whole
thing is that they're like sexy. That's not their whole thing. If you like Fortuna, you
big fortuna is sexy i don't know big fortuna but she sounds hot bib for a big fortuna she's big as
hell no it's the guy she like crushed me with one seat we've totally talked about bib fortuna before
i think we have yeah you know bib fortuna is the guy in java's palace who walks up to 3po and r2
and says day one oh one guy you know i probably wouldn't find him very attractive yeah but the
but the you did this i would love to run that i would i would love to be said it to be turning um
salacious b-crumb around on a spit.
Yeah.
Just eating him?
I want to eat Scrooge's hair. It's so fucking thin. It's so thin.
It's like cotton candy.
It's crazy, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Oh, the animated Jim Carrey.
There's been so many iterations of Scrooge.
Have I told you guys about the time when I was like the most hungover I ever was?
And like, this is like maybe the worst day of my entire life.
It was the day before Thanksgiving, and I forgot that I told Janna's family that I would go with
them to their Thanksgiving thing out of town. It was a two-hour drive. So the night before, I went
out and I was smoking cigars with my friend's dad and drinking full bottles of wine, just getting
insanely fucked up. Woke up the next day, obviously insanely hungover, get in the back of this van,
the back backseat and then oh sorry no this was this was near Christmas but we
go to their Christmas thing and their their tradition is every time they go on
this ride they listen to the audiobook of the the Scrooge thing the Christmas
story. Christmas Carol yeah yeah Christmas Carol so I it's like a
two-and-a-half hour audiobook and I'm in the back right next to the speaker and I
can't tell them like hey turn it down I'm insanely hungover and 17 and I'm
just hearing like "SCROOGE! YOU HAVE DISRESPECTED CHRISTMAS!" It was like one of the worst days
of my entire fucking life. It was so fucked up. Yeah. I mean if I had to hear about Scrooge
for an hour or two, I'd probably lose my shit. Why are you so grumpy? Chill. I have to say
too, I mean if we- Scrooge chill! We're talking about like- Scrooge, smoke this. Food in movies
that looks delicious like some of the kibble from Air Bud just like had my mouth watering.
Some of the food from Chef is actually pretty good.
And Spirited Away.
Oh, I know.
He invented that, you know.
What if they made like a YouTube channel?
Dude, yeah, and anime food.
Or he'd eat the food from movies.
What?
Anime food looks like so good too.
Like in Spirited Away, that giant baby, I know if you roasted him, he would...
Was that Jordan Peterson?
No, Jordan posted that picture of like E.T. on a spit.
Honestly, I'd look at that.
I feel like almost every single like puppet from a movie would taste so good if you roasted
a snow dove.
You would never do that to me.
The main character from the Dark Crystal?
Yeah.
Oh yeah, the Gelflings?
Oh, they would taste like baklava.
No, the only thing that's good about the Gelflings is their essence.
As I've learned.
Well, that's only if you're a Skeksis and you're evil.
Well, I don't know.
You know those giant, what are the big spider things called?
I know those taste like crab.
Those definitely taste like crab.
Oh, the big walker things?
Yeah. No, not the striders.
Not the tall ones? Oh, the striders.
No, the evil ones. The spider things.
I forget what those are called.
I feel like in cartoons,
vomit in a cartoon usually looks pretty good.
Yeah. Oh my god, dude.
It looks like a good green gazpacho verde.
Like the vomit in Family Guy?
Yeah, I would dip a chip into that.
Yeah. You know? A tortilla chip.
Why didn't I just say guacamole?
I don't know.
Green gazpacho.
The uh...
Gazpacho.
Gazpacho vanadate.
When you see like Sylvester the cat like walking around putting pieces of trash on a trash can lid like it's a buffet like that.
Dude a fish, eating a whole fish off the bone like that?
Or just the bone?
Oh my god.
Just a fish bone, a whole fish bone with no meat on it?
Yeah.
That's gonna, can you imagine that getting stuck in your throat?
It'd be so good.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Or a bomb that looks like a cake.
Yeah, that could be good. I would love to fry Tweety Bird, too.
Me, too.
Anything with a wick in it, I think I would eat.
Yeah.
Yeah, pretty much.
Candle.
If they fried her, I'd probably eat the granny from Looney Tunes, too.
Yeah.
Might as well.
She had a big fat ass.
Remember that? They gave her a big fat ass.
Did they?
She walked with a limp, dude.
That was funny back then.
She walked bow-legged.
That was funny back then if someone had a big fat ass.
Granny from Looney Tunes looks like a girl that like Kevin Gates would have sex with.
And like post on his Instagram.
It looks exactly like that.
Yeah.
It is Granny.
Yerr me.
Hey, hello.
My girl Granny, yerr me.
I don't remember what she sounds like.
I don't remember either.
Oh, fuck, I'm Grandma.
Grandma. Oh I'm Tweety Bird's mom. Also you can't be no granny with if you don't got no damn
grandkids. We didn't see those. Tweety Bird. Tweety Bird. The kid is Tweety Bird. Yeah. Who's a guy by the
way did you know that? I did know that. He's not a boy. But he's such a wimp. Yeah that's why I mean
imagine you imagine if you you didn't have any parents you just had a grandmother. Yeah. And
you were a bird and you were bright yellow. Imagine how you might feel then. That's like the most
beautiful lyrics I've ever heard. Imagine you have no parents, imagine you have a granny,
imagine you're a bird and you're yellow.
A bright yellow bird.
Yeah. I mean if Gal Gadot had sung that instead, that would have fixed COVID.
Yeah.
You remember, ah fuck, it feels so long ago, like all the shit from last year, but like,
What was it, that, uh, like in June of last year when all that, all that crap was going on
and all those white celebrities got together and made that video where they were like,
"I take responsibility."
Oh yeah. Remember that shit?
Yeah, the one that sticks in my head from that is the Aaron Paul one.
Yeah.
Where he like, he's like acting way harder than anybody else in the video.
the video so he goes like yeah I yo take the white responsibility responsibility
but he like yeah he like does like prayer hands and like breathing like a lot of
every word it's already been memory hold like it's already been like memory hold
like that's when the CIA deletes it from your memory but what yeah but like that
and then memory what memory hold means is people forgot about it I I was uh I
was thinking about it earlier but aerial pink at the fucking capital rights I
I have not forgot about that.
I think about that every day.
I was listening to Ariel Pink today.
What's his deal?
He just makes weird, like, shitty music.
Yeah.
Sounds cool.
He's a guy who calls himself Ariel Pink.
I think that pretty much explains it.
I was like, I do remember seeing Ariel Pink in the news and being like, "Hmm, Google image
search Ariel Pink."
And being like, "She sounds really hot."
Being pretty disappointed.
The first time I ever heard the name Ariel Pink was in fucking Childish Gambino Freaks
and Geeks.
He says, "I'm in that Ariel Pink" and then I looked up Ariel Pink and I was like, "Oh,
this is just a weird guy.
Like, why would you say that you're inside of him?"
He had some wild lyrics back in the day.
"You know I'm a retard and I'm a fat guy."
That was like every song.
Is that an actual thing or is that you just saying that?
That's off the dome, dude.
I think this is your own song.
I think this is a song you've been writing and you need to get used to it.
You know I'm a retard and I'm a fat guy.
Yeah.
Childish Gambino, yeah I'm a black guy.
That was like his first like eight albums.
Dude that fucking I'm not a rapper mixtape.
Brandon and I were talking about this but it's just like the fucking, he raps over Grizzly
Bear and it's like why the fuck would you ever rap like two weeks by Grizzly Bear you
want to rap over that?
is the most insane shit you could do. You should rap over AC/DC. That would be cool.
That actually, that's some like, that's a Danny Brown move I think. Yeah.
Someone, someone should honestly rap over Aerosmith. Yeah. I think that's... Oh man, could you imagine?
Yeah, I think that'd be a really really good song. And they do a video together. Yeah.
I mean I am such a sucker for when like just a SoundCloud rapper just raps over
a song that is not supposed to be rapped over. That's like the best shit ever. Like
Like when Lil Peep wrapped over Wonderwall, when Cemetery wrapped over Burzum and stuff,
dude it's so tight, it's so awesome.
That sounds cool but like...
I mean literally it doesn't matter what, as long as it's a song that shouldn't be wrapped
over it's awesome when they do it.
But I mean, you know how they invented rap, right?
How did they invent rap?
What tell me.
They took crap and they took off the C.
Oh, 'cause the C was for country.
Mm-hmm.
Country plus rap equals crun...
Crunch...
Crunchy...
Crunchy crap.
Okay, bye everybody!
(laughing)