Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
- Premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Yeah.
Cameron has to pack, 'cause he's going to--
- Iraq.
- I would love to go.
- He's going to Iraq to fight.
- I think it's beautiful there.
- I would love to send him to Iraq.
- I think you'd be easily blown apart.
- I don't think that it's a violent place.
I don't think I'd be blown apart.
I think I might I think I'm on my mind might be blown apart by its natural
beauty and the kindness of those who live there.
Do you know how they pay for everything over there?
How?
By giving each other dinners.
Is that true?
Mm-hmm.
You use dinner as money?
Dinner, yeah.
In the Middle East?
Iraqi dinners.
It's what they're most serious.
This just sounds like a wonderful place.
Uh-huh.
So say like you want like it's like I want a t-shirt that'll cost you 25 Iraqi dinners.
So it's like oh jeez.
25 dinners?
That's why, yeah.
That's, well so what about if you're buying dinner?
What happens then?
happens then? That still costs dinner. Well but here's how they get you. You
think, "Oh dinner, this is gonna be nice steak and something," right? They
come out with a caesian fucking mubarak fucking giant pot of boiling hot lamb
lava and they're like, "Well at least give me a fork and a knife," and they say, "A
what and a what?" You eat that piping hot hand stew with your hand. Yeah. You have to wear
rubber gloves. They say, "No don't worry, we're gonna give you the
thinnest little piece of bread of all time so you can you don't completely third
degree burn you just yes you merely scald your hand and see in season barik or
ever had however the hell you pronounce it he's from Turkey and over there the
only utensils they have you have to if you if you want utensils anywhere in
Turkey they have a guy who spins them around you can't you can't catch him
that's true away imagine you sit you're in Turkey right you've been sitting in
in line for the new iPhone all day long, right?
And then you get up to the Genius Bar,
he says, "Here you go."
You reach out, all of a sudden,
it's in his other fucking hand, right?
You're like, "What the hell?"
There's a false version of the iPhone
that the iPhone was sitting in.
A false case.
They pull the iPhone out every single time.
Every single retail employee,
every single restaurant employee,
every single employee in Turkey has to trick people.
do it when they hand over your grandmother's ashes after she's been
she's been they always use like a grabber they use a grabber yeah spin them
and they hand over a lot of fun then they say side a lot of fun not just they
roll it they roll it down their arms and their shoulders like a Harlem Globetrotter
basketball and an ice cream cone and then they put it in most things are
served in an ice cream yeah so they serve meatballs and shawarma yeah place
near me there's of shawarma she's been shut down forever but a little opening
Avengers reference reopening now reopening now shawarma fi shawarma
shawarma fi all one word like it's an app yeah shawarma fi shawarma there is
sounds less like an app and more like a ray or maybe it's halal if I even more
like a ray yeah a really bad name there is it's either I forget what it's called
but there's some Turkish dish I'll see it every time
I used to know the name.
Dracula's sausages.
No, I think it's intestine or something. I think it's stuffed intestine or something.
A sausage.
Have you ever seen that? I think it's that H.R. Giger painting that Dead Kennedys used for Frankenchrist.
You know the one where it looks like, I think it's H.R. Giger, where it looks like dicks going into pussies.
This is what this food looks like.
Wait, there's an H.R. Giger thing that looks like dicks and pussies?
Yeah.
I don't want to see that.
it's a dead kid they know they call them they call him HR Geiger because the art
store he worked I was always getting sent to HR yeah penises and pussies and
they're gagging when they see that oh my god photo finally watched alien for the
first time the first time what really yeah I thought I'd seen it what I thought
I saw when I was a you've never seen alien no that's crazy yeah you oh you
know what you thought that you had seen alien you had just seen et no you know
penis is a space ball yes you just seen space balls yeah I think I think that was
balls yeah same guy says both it's John Hurt both times John Hurt John Hurt John
Hurt oh my god I didn't he died two years ago he died I feel like didn't he
die longer I don't know who the fuck this is I'm John Hurt oh yeah he's in
- Oh, Popeye.
- No, he wasn't.
- He was an alien.
- I'm gonna give you a Popeye.
- It's actually another part of that
Kid Stays in the Picture documentary
where he's like, he gets--
- Talking about it again.
- It's so good.
- Most boring documentary.
- When you talk about it, it's so boring.
- I was waiting to break this out, but Patrick.
- Oh yeah.
That's the shut up bell.
- The shut up bell?
That was not what I was gonna call it.
- No, I mean, I just, what is this?
- It's the Patrick bell.
- What is the Patrick bell?
Oh, this is a
It's the Patrick Bell.
I've got Patrick's old report card in front of me.
Oh nice.
And I feel like this is maybe instead of having to fill it out and distract me and take notes,
maybe it's like whenever I notice he's being crass or a story that maybe might not have
an ending, I could ring the bell, which wouldn't be disruptive.
You can't do, I think the bell is completely disruptive.
I don't think it's disruptive at all.
All right, well try it Pat. Can we agree to try it just this one episode?
No.
What if we try for the...
Disagreeing.
That's disagreeable. That's disagreeable attitude.
What about for just the next five minutes?
I don't want to hear the bell.
Because it gives you a negative response trigger, right?
I don't like the bell.
Why not?
That's just disagreeable.
I mean that is being disagreeable.
I don't care.
You don't care?
That's fine.
It's okay to not care.
It's okay to not care. It's actually cool to not care.
What if instead we made it maybe a lunchtime bell and we rang it when we got lunch?
What if we make it a funny joke bell and every time someone makes a funny joke.
Truly what happened, this was not, I just, we saw the bell when we were in the hardware
store and I was like we have to buy this bell.
There really is, it can be anything.
Lunch bell.
It's a cool bell.
Do you want to try the bell, Pat?
I don't want to try the bell.
But it's fun.
Press the button.
No.
He got all upset because we rang the bell and now he's fucking, he wanted to try the bell.
I feel bad.
I don't want to try the bell.
He ruined the bell for himself.
You didn't do this.
about a bell. I don't want to try the bell. It's a fun bell. Just ring it. Look at this.
I don't care. You don't even think that that might be kind of fun to touch that bell? No.
Not even a little bit. It's like an easy button but it makes a ringing sound instead of saying
that was easy. If that changes anything. It's a sound board that only has one sound. It
goes ding. I'd prefer if it was an easy button. I don't know why you bought this bell. Because
it was not a hotel it was only where it's an obvious we should be a $40 you
should have got an easy listen to it here I was I was I was arguing with Caleb
about this would this be a cooler Bell if it was the kind of Bell that you hold
with your hand and ring back and forth like this because I wanted to buy that
one and Caleb said no and so we got that words there are more as a cooler Bell
this is another Bell again it's a Patrick Bell just because you called me a
moron and guess what that's a meanness I don't care I'm gonna be rude as hell
this episode for meanness and being rude to me and calling me a moron you got
another and for not caring again I don't care it's okay oh never mind I take
that shit I got the dinner bell but that bell sucks the dinner bell would have
been too loud and you can't just ring it what bells that it should have been too
loud did you have some kind of traumatic hotel experience yes really mm-hmm I
I guess you lived in a hotel.
A Lisa Lamb.
Just that news story.
I remembered it.
I can never see a bell like that again.
Or water.
Have you ever done this?
I lived in a hotel for a year.
Have you ever done this at a hotel, or not even a hotel, anywhere where they have a bell
and it's like ring for service and you ring it?
Yeah.
Does it feel kind of rude?
It's like honking your horn.
It feels really bad.
Yeah, it's rude as hell.
It's not rude.
It feels rude, but it's not rude.
- There's a, I told you about the time the oven was on fire,
right, at the hotel?
- No.
- I don't think so.
- You guys had an oven in your hotel room?
- Yeah, we were at a Town Place Suites.
- That's a hotel area.
- That's an apart motel.
That's a motartment.
- It's a motartment.
- Mm-hmm.
- But I accidentally left a plastic tray in the oven
'cause I thought it was a metal tray.
I don't know why the fuck somebody put that,
it was a plastic tray for the Continental breakfast.
- Oh, what the hell?
- And somebody left it in the oven,
and then I turned the oven on,
the thing melted down the whole tray melted down through the like...
Did it stink everything up?
The whole room smelled like melted plastic that was on fire at the bottom of the oven
and I didn't know what to do because I was like home alone and I ran down to the
lobby and I there was like three people in line ahead of me and I didn't want to
just yell "FIRE!" because I didn't know what...
Yeah.
I didn't know if it was like...
So you waited in line?
I waited in line while the oven was on fire.
(laughing)
And then I finally got up there and I was like,
a tray melted in the oven and it's on fire.
And she's like, okay, there should be like
an extinguisher on your floor.
'Cause I didn't know--
- On the floor?
- On the, like, first floor.
- Oh, yeah, okay, that makes more sense.
- Yeah.
- No, it was on the floor.
- On the floor.
There's probably something on the floor.
- I didn't know whether or not to call the fire department
or--
- They'll handle that.
They'll figure it out.
hotel as their own fire department their own thing going on you have to be if you
have a cruise trip cruise trip do you have to miss Bell I mean this talk now
this could be a really good kind of closed-loop situation I feel like Caleb
could really use the bell on himself and really make him laugh.
Honestly, me and the bell, this might be, I think I might have my own Caleb and the Bell,
Beauty and the Bell might be my new spin-off show. I love the bell. I do like the bell.
It's an instant out of whatever you're talking about. Yeah. You know, and sometimes I just
get a little too off on my own little path. No, hey, and guess what, I can use the bell
also. I tried to take the bell and he grabbed it. Pat is trying to not smile. He's rubbing
Can you believe that? He's rubbing his face.
I hate this thing. He's rubbing his face. Why?
Explain why you hate this.
Caleb is literally monopolizing the bell. It's not okay.
That's fine.
No, you guys were talking down on this.
This adds a whole element of like
disruption.
It adds a bell
sound. I hate when our episodes
are disrupted. Not disrupted
like, for me, personally,
I can't
pay attention if
don't do that. I can't pay attention if there's even a scream upstairs or if
there's water coming from the pipes. I can't. So you're saying the
bell... This already fucks me up so much. You're saying the bell is doing the opposite of
what it... No it's doing exactly the opposite of what it should be doing. What
should it be doing? I shouldn't be doing anything. It shouldn't be here.
Alright give me the bell. Give me the bell. I'll put it somewhere. I'm not gonna
I'm not gonna ring it, it's gonna stay right there. I know you're gonna ring it.
Even looking at it is a problem for him.
Yeah. Yeah. So here's what I'll do.
Here. I'm gonna take it.
We should, if anything, we should leave it.
Well so why, okay, but then.
Let me ask then, so why.
Why is this bell horrible but a hand dinner bell would be okay?
Don't give it to Alex.
Okay, here's my idea. Don't give it to Alex.
We hang it up, we hang it up on the wall
and if Alex and Joe need to talk to us while we're recording, they ring the bell.
(laughing)
- I don't think we, you have to kind of like
reenact that conversation,
'cause there's no way we could hear any of that.
- That wasn't for you guys.
- Well I had an idea for the bell,
and I don't know if you heard it.
- I didn't hear it.
- So we tape it to the wall, where the divider is,
and if Alex and Joe need to talk to us
while we're recording, they ring the bell.
- Why wouldn't they just say, well, you're okay.
All right, yeah, that's fine, I'll take that.
- That's a good use of the bell.
Yeah, no, yeah, no, that's...
Well, he just... I hate this even more.
What do you...
I just heard it. Now we can hear it, and the people listening to the podcast cannot hear it.
From across the room.
I heard it all the way across the fucking office.
See what I mean? It's not good.
Go get it. Go get it. No, it's great when we're in control of it.
You don't ring the bell also.
Alright. Then we're in a good spot.
We're doing well now. Okay.
Okay.
Did you ring it because you needed to ask us something?
thing. He said no. He said no. Yeah. Okay. The Bell's gone guys. That was supposed to
last us at least 45 minutes. Was that a fun five or so minutes of the show? No. Yeah.
I think it was very fun. I thought it was really, really fun. It was not good for me.
I got yelled at by a little person this morning because. You were ringing a bell in their
face. Well yeah. And you were saying dance, dance. I wasn't saying dance. Trying to make
I was trying to make him grow. Yeah? Yeah. I thought it was a miracle grow in their pockets.
Growing bell. Right. I wrote that on it. So I thought it might work. You thought they were
like Tom Hanks in Big? Um, a child? A grown man trapped in a child's body? It wasn't a
child. It was clearly an older woman actually. She said that her, her, um. Why was she yelling
at you? Because Phil peed on her stoop. And I see this lady, there's this lady. I thought
You're gonna say Phil Peeta.
She's not a little, I mean she's not,
(laughing)
I don't think she has dwarfism, but she is a small person.
Yeah.
And she has a son who's her exact same height,
and they walk around and they argue with each other all day.
And she's like maybe 60 years old,
she has crazy makeup on all the time.
It's like Mimi from Drew Carey Show.
I don't know, but I think that's the second Mimi reference
you've had in 24 hours.
Yeah.
Yeah, or maybe not even 24 hours,
probably 16 hours. Well look up a photo
of Mimi and you'll see.
I'll look it up in a bit.
But I see right now that would have been a bell.
That would have been an easy bell.
Ding.
Are you trying to ring a bell?
There's nothing there.
I'm just hitting the table.
Me trying to ring a bell when there's no bell there?
Okay.
She yelled at me.
I don't like that the bell was sabotage.
I don't like that the bell was an ambush on me.
You wish you had known about the bell before.
I wish I knew about the bell.
I was not clued in to the bell at all.
Now you know about it.
Well, maybe somebody left the office early yesterday.
- Because I have to, I'm nursing a stray cat.
- Maybe two friends came up with a funny prank
they thought everyone would enjoy
and it backfired a little bit
and we can all kind of move on from there.
- It was not a nice thing to do.
- It was funny.
- It was a prank.
- It was not a nice prank.
- A prank is not supposed to be nice.
- We immediately changed it
and it became an all around universal bell.
- I would not have called it the shut up bell.
That was all Caleb.
That was very rude of him.
- It was an ambush on me.
It's funny to ambush you.
It's not that funny to ambush me.
Maybe not to you, but to me and to a lot of other people it might be kind of funny to ambush
somebody.
Then why am I here?
So that we can ambush you.
Is that it?
Is that the only reason?
Don't ring the bell.
Don't ring the bell, Alex.
Stop.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Is that the only reason to ambush you?
No.
No, you also sing songs and do stuff like that and that's good.
but it is funny to ring a bell at you every once in a while. It's not funny to
ring a bell. I think with time you will find. I think next episode maybe we can
try a different kind of bell that we're all in. What about a doorbell? But then
that's what I was saying with the bell on the wall. What about a doorbell though
that goes ding dong and then someone comes in and it's a crazy new character
that's every time the doorbell rings. That's pretty good too. Once per minute.
She tried to get me to wash Phil's pee off of her stairs and I said, "Okay, I had a cup
of coffee."
And I was like, "Do you want me to pour coffee on it?"
She was like, "Coffee?
That's even worse!"
And that's my entire story.
Did she sit on the stoop?
No, she was in her car.
She was just watching me do it.
She was like, "Clean it up!"
I was like, "What?"
She was like, "The pee!
Clean it up!
That's my stoop!"
I was like, "I--" It's not her stoop.
It's the landlord's stoop.
And then she was talking to her landlord. The landlord didn't give a fuck, right?
And then she told her landlord--this is just not really a part of the story--but
she told her landlord that her husband has been painting buildings for 45 years
and he would paint the whole place for one month's rent.
Wow.
Paint the whole building.
That's a good deal.
It's a great deal.
That's, yeah.
Yeah.
Wow.
She didn't even say if he was going to paint the building like a special color or anything?
I might have heard something like that.
Yeah?
Yeah, yeah, I might have heard her say that now that you mentioned what color I
think it was gonna be black. Really? I think the building, the brick building in
the middle of a block of other brick buildings. She said I'm gonna
paint it completely Vantablack. Wow! It's gonna be, I'm guess, Vsauce Michael is
gonna, is my husband, and he's gonna paint this completely Vantablack and he
went okay that's fine did you guys ever see Vantablack no they had some dark
black painting in a museum. It's spelled like Dracula saying want a black yeah I
want a black. But they're miss missing spaces. Girlfriend. It's maybe if Dracula's really
excited about that
is either funny bell could be wrong for ivan the black
Okay, it was this thing where they had a hole
And they painted it completely black
And there's no light in there and it looked like an infinite hole because of how they used some special black color
Was a movie extremely darkly black was a movie. I was in a museum. Oh, no, that's a movie - it's called the dark hole
I got confused
So it looked like it went on forever. Yeah, it looked like you're looking into like space or something. It was pretty crazy
I don't think space is that impressive when I look up at it.
The ocean is a little bit more impressive.
I agree.
The ocean, when I look at the ocean, and maybe it's just a matter of perspective, but the
ocean looks bigger than space.
Yeah.
No.
I think so.
The space is all up, it's the whole sky.
The ocean is only the direction, I guess if I was in the middle of the ocean.
But I'm thinking about things on a 2D level where the ocean goes forever that way.
space space is just a space of just a picture that's hanging up there but I
go might as well be a ceiling well it's the same as the oh it's also if you
what's the day I would sooner I think I would sooner believe that there was no
space and that all that the sky was fake then that the earth was flat because the
ocean seems so big that this guy you'd sooner believe the sky was made then
that then the earth was flat yeah I don't sooner believe that it's sooner
Okay, so but those things that you feel like usually go together. Yeah, but I'm
Usually pick one of those. I'm saying I could pick one and that might be that the sky is probably fake chicken little style status
I think that's yeah, I think that's probably the more in chicken little does the sky piece is falling
I'm talking the movie universe. Uh-huh. The sky piece. Is that a
Is that did the aliens build a fake sky or was the sky always fake and it's like a Truman Show thing behind them
the thing behind the sky. Well, I don't know. I think it's a world where maybe
chickens can speak.
Yeah, so when the chicken yeah, so is that why the aliens are making a Truman show? Is because they're like what the fuck?
They're chickens are talking on this world. That's so cool. We should make that a TV show.
I think maybe the whole atom test is an alien experiment.
The only thing I remember about that movie is when the guy breathes into the bag really fast.
And also that intro. Whoever, whatever character does that.
that the duck and my no the fat. I think it's the pig yeah. He goes why the hell
they got a they got two birds and they go and pig
that good point. Why are these why are why are there? Why is it that the world
of words as a as a kid though that duck was hot as fuck the ugly duckling. Oh my
God, dude, she was badder than Jessica rabbit bro. It's in her name. She's ugly
and that's a seriously and that's a kid. I said as a kid as a kid as a kid. Yeah,
I mean nice try you said that that that duck is hot as a kid
But yeah, I did say that you can say that like the kid
Character also a duck you say that the kid characters ugly all day long, but you can't say yeah
You can you guys it as a that I'm you say that ugly duckling is ugly
Yeah, all day long all you want as a kid if you say that ugly duckling is hot
Yeah, first of all that's fucked up. You're betraying the name of this character. No. It's like I say well. She's completely purple
Yeah, wait till she grows up. Yeah, that's what the story is about. Yeah
And she is the ugly duckling turns 18
That's the story. That's what the more of the guy who wrote the ugly duckling was just a pedophile. Yeah, who is that's his rehabilitation
Rehabilitation was like he the judge made him write a story
About a duck that turns 18
I don't know how long ducks live but I feel like probably the ugly duckling turned like
three and got really hot.
Based on...
Bro, are you hearing this?
I'm saying in the story.
Give me that bell back.
He's talking about the pedophile who wrote the ugly duckling is what I'm saying.
Well you said...
You guys are kicking me out of this little world that you're building here.
It's not fair.
You said the ugly duckling.
First of all, he said the ugly duckling hot, then he said it's a kid, and then he said
it's hot as a kid.
you want to badly fuckling with your awesome suckling yeah on this duck. No
you guys are completely misunderstanding me here. I'm saying if I was a pedophile
if I was a pedophile and a duck
and this ugly duckling came up to me, maybe we had you all wrong all along.
I'm starting to understand now that you say that. Yeah. I re-watched Blazing Saddles.
Yeah, couldn't make that today. I think they could make it, I think. I think. But they
would have to be... I think they did make it today. I think they have to do... I think it just came out.
You know who would need to be the new sheriff? Who? Hoody Allen. Steven Yuen. Oh. That
would be a good-ass... So the movie... Blazing Saddles, but it's like maybe this with you
just kind of do a maybe. What if you do Blazing Saddles right? Yeah. Did you say
Blazing Saddles? No. Oh Tiger Woods, get Tiger in there? Dude, Blazing Saddles is such a good idea.
Holy shit. So if you made Blazing Saddles today. That's such a great idea.
Oh fuck, Tiger. We need Tiger. Tiger, just break out roll. That's his 8 mile.
He calls it Blazin' Saddles. It's a pretty good--
Remember how mad everyone got at him for just cheating on his wife?
Yeah, dude, because he's living the most fucking-- they hated him.
I've told you what my grandpa has said about Tiger Woods.
Yeah, he was bringing too much hip-hop to the golf course.
No, no.
That's what I was saying.
My grandpa said one time we were watching--
mean we're just watching golf and Tiger is Tigers up to T and greatest golfer of
all time greatest golfer ball I mean pretty much it's between him Palmer has
a drink between him and there's no drinking a Tiger Woods so he's like the
best golfer of all time was Tyler the Creator
between Tiger and Jack there in his Haley and so he and my grandpa just says
you know the only reason Tiger what is Tiger Woods is famous is because he's
black. It's the greatest goal ever. And my grandpa thinks that he's only famous
because he's a black guy. Yeah. Just crazy dude. Yeah same with Eminem. Yeah. Eminem
only famous because he's white. That's actually true. Eminem's white. I thought Eminem was like Logic.
He's famous because he raps quickly. I thought he was like Logic? Yeah. What do you mean?
Like a lyrical miracle. Oh he is a lyrical miracle. Did you guys see that
that Sauron in the new Lord of the Rings show they released a picture of him a
while ago and he looks exactly like Eminem.
- That makes sense.
- He's like a bleach blonde evil white boy.
- Whoa.
- If you look at the picture.
- Draco Malfoy status?
- Yeah, but he looks--
- I watched that show for like two seconds the other day.
- It sucks dude.
I watched 20 minutes of it and I had to turn it off.
- Yeah.
- It's really not good.
- It's rated PG-13.
- Yeah, well I wouldn't have watched 20 minutes of it
if it was rated PG-13.
- They only do the rating 20 minutes in.
Let me see.
That's Sauron. What the fuck? He just looks ugly. He looks like an ugly...
He's so funny dude. They just made him Eminem. He looks like a fucking deathcore vocalist.
He's supposed to be... He's got the bleached eyebrows too. He's got a bleached buzz cut.
How you doing a buzz cut back then? Is he a child in this? Why does he look so young?
I think he's in disguise. He's in a magical disguise to fool people.
Yeah.
The whole thing of Sauron at the second age is that...
I thought Sauron was some kind of fucked up angel.
No, he's a devilish angel.
He's a sorcerer. So he disguises himself and then he makes the whole kingdom follow him
and then he betrays him.
He's the best friend of a fallen angel guy.
I think he is. I think he is a fallen angel. Wizards are fallen angels in Lord of the Rings
basically. Or they're like, whatever, they're like supernatural creatures.
And dragons are just dragons.
Dragons are dragons, yeah. And then there are also giant spiders, and those are spiders.
There's also werewolves, and you can probably guess what those are.
And clearly hobbits are supposed to be hobbits.
I think hobbits are the Christians, right?
No, hobbits are British people.
No, but hobbits are Christians.
Hobbits are like, love me wife, love me punts of the earl.
Yeah, and the dwarves are Muslim.
Dwarves are Jewish, unfortunately.
Really?
Yeah.
the elves are muslims. I don't know if there are muslims. I think the ancient wisdom shit
going on. I think muslims live longer. The orcs are the mongols. They're mongolians.
Well hey, you can't say that word. What word? That word is just as bad as the r word. Orc?
Mongol. You said it. You said it. I said it to prove a point. It is funny that the word
mongoloid does come from like Mongolian. I think that's not funny it's kind of
fucked up I actually don't like that kind of I think it's funny that it's an
antiquated term. Can we cut out with the racial division?
This isn't racial this is a mental division. Can we leave the mental division in the
past and just thinking about this today I I told you about how I was in like
special needs classes in middle school right yeah I know yeah maybe you didn't
tell me I know just fight figuring out like two weeks ago two three weeks ago
that that math class that I was in where we like learned fractions through
cooking was them training me to become a line cook
yeah they just put all you guys they put us all in a like four of us in a row is
five kids and then one of us moved yeah and then it was four kids in a math
class and one of the things we learned how to cook was churros which was Pam
baking spray over a tortilla covered in you might have been working at a Red
Robin they might have been it might have been a false like a like a studio set of
a classroom yeah actually you were in the kitchen of a Red Robin I just make
- I swear to God. - Making campfire sauce.
- It would make more sense.
- Yeah, I think so.
It's a pretty good idea.
The high school kids are,
I mean, essentially they're free labor.
- Yeah. - Right?
- I remember the--
- They should be making the license plates,
not these poor prisoners.
These prisoners got pushups to do.
- The Chinese class at my high school,
one of their field trips was they went
to a Chinese restaurant and helped them make food.
- Really? - For a while.
Wow.
I think they either, they were like, it was either that they, I think they helped, they
like watched them for like a long time and then like helped them make one type of food
or something.
Yeah.
I used to have to do that growing up.
I used to have to go in and help my mom.
Well, that's not, that wasn't for a class though.
That was because you're helping your mother make food, which is actually like a sacred
and beautiful thing.
That's a kind of class.
That is a class, yeah.
I mean, people who help their mom have class.
I'll say that much.
Imagine if you have to go with your teacher, your teacher's like, you guys have to make
food with these people now yeah you have to speak in only Chinese there's like 25
of you or Mandarin that's too many people that's too many kids in a yeah do you
think that the Chinese restaurant they knew that it was coming where they are
did just 25 kids show up for you yeah okay I don't know I wish I was in that
class I want to see what goes on back there yeah we had a German class my
German class I'd only took it for two years I missed the I didn't have a
language credit going into college so I had to take a language credit at fucking
Emerson and but before that I took two years of German on your third year you
get to go to this German restaurant in like Lee, New Hampshire or something or
like I was pretty far up and you have to speak German the whole day and if you
don't speak in German you can't eat any of the food. That's easy. So if you fuck up one
time you you had to sit there and watch all your classmates eat like a pretzel
no that seems like almost abuse it yeah well it's German class they're the most
strict people in the world to go could you just not talk you probably could but
you probably I think I think probably would ask you a question
from your trauma from trauma the hell because showing for our trauma for out
was for our trauma about to be she was like a 60 year old woman with a bull
cut holy fucking shit and she got mad at me because I didn't learn any other we
would we would do like the we'd have to write two sentences of what we're doing
on the weekend every Friday I bet you were up there doing some Bart Simpson
shit I was I'd say it's not for skiing penis is gawning or something like that
or something like that mm-hmm inglorious my my penis is is niche sir good no it's
not sir good no no did you ever do you ever put up there like inglorious
bastards watch this I think or something so I'm like that we would get extra
credit on tests if we brought in a cultural tidbit
swastika outfit of my grandpa's SS uniform. Yeah, somebody brought in, we watched
that clip in Inglorious Bastards of the German 3. Oh nice. Yeah. I guess there is a 3.
I took like French class. I took French in middle school and
high school and that's like a given where it's like every year you'll
either watch Ratatouille or like Tintin and that's like those are the two things
you only ever watch. I guess I don't know what like as like an like you know at
the end of the year. Yeah. And I guess I can't think of what the go-to German
thing would be besides Ratatouille in German. Really? Yeah. I just remembered that before Christmas.
Before Christmas we watched Ratatouille in German. That's so funny. That's less about the languages and more about the fact that it was a it was a
newer film at the time. Mm-hmm. And it's kind of it's about being worldly.
you know I think we had to watch or maybe we watched a clip from deep rest rumble
the tindrum just like this movie it's just like German movie from like 73
we're like a kid decides that he doesn't want to like age past like four so he
throws himself down his stairs sure decision to make it for you he's born as
a baby genius holy throws himself down the stairs but then he it's like a
Benjamin Button, but if he stays the same age is basically what and then he gets drafted in World War two or whatever
They drafted a four-year-old child. Well, no he ages mentally, but he stays physically for still why would you put this person on the?
Don't remember the movie that well, I do remember one scene where he eats his babysitter out and he's still a four-year-old
Yeah, why is he getting babysat if he's mentally an older person and he's doing why is he and why are you watching an eating?
out movie in class. I think we watched a clip from it because I remember a scene
where a soldier says "Ich liebe die Kartoffel". This is a this is a German
movie. Yeah. Gotcha. So that's the thing yeah like what are you gonna watch in
like German we would watch like all these like short films these German short
films German commercials and then Ratatouille in German.
It's so funny. I pretty much should watch a Shanghai film.
It's just like a man in a language on the DVD.
Yeah, it could be any movie.
I mean, it's probably because the French class already had a DVD of Ratatouille across the hall or something.
Right, just like, "Alright, fuck it, we'll just, whatever."
But I remember we watched this commercial for this supermarket in Germany.
Oh, we also watched, there was this short, this like, you know, the things that are made specifically for like German, like language classes, like the TV shows?
shows. Yeah. Watch this one called Hallo Julia and Christian. No, what it's just
how Germans speak. Her name was Julia. Oh, and this Hallo Julia. Oh, not
Hallelujah. Yeah. Oh, I thought it was Hallelujah in German. There's this
little, there's this kid named Hassan and he was supposed to be representative
of all the big Turkish population in Germany. Is there a big Turkish
population in Germany? Yes, there I those are probably do all those tricks.
they should make a streaming service that just has all of the the language
learning shows, because I would watch the ones where it's like oh this episode he
has to ask to borrow a bicycle from his friend and he has to explain that he
wants to go to the train station. That's the whole episode. Some of those plot
lines are really captivating. My cousin also took German and he remembers
"Hallo Julia" so maybe I'm glad someone else remembers it and I didn't know
there was a possibility that you might be the only one who remembered it. I thought
maybe it was made up for the class. I was in straight Bible study, basically 24 hours. You didn't take a language?
I took Latin. Oh. I had to take Latin. Yeah, which you know what we watched and then my Latin class
went right into my... I'd rather it be Latina class. My Latin class went right into my political science class
which was taught by the same lady, this libertarian lady, so I would go straight from learning Latin
and like watching these like Shakespeare plays that are done in Latin into watching just an hour
of John Stossel videos. It'd just be John Stossel being like "Gay rights should be up to the
states" and that was my political science class.
Stossel's the one with the big mustache?
Yeah, the one and he got punched in the face by a wrestler at one point I think. I don't
remember which one. He's like a piece of shit.
Yeah, Stossel was on PBS, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, it was Stossel and somebody else.
Yeah, he was like a, you know, he's like a kind of Shapiro style dude from but in
the 90s. Yeah, my school had a Latin class too. My school had Latin, French,
Spanish and Chinese and the way it worked is in middle school, in I think
fifth grade, you would take one, you would take a different language every
quarter and then you would decide which one you wanted to take for the rest.
And it was like, I remember I took French because my mom wanted me to, but
the the like it would be like every like they were every quarter. They would try
and convince you to take that language or whatever, and I remember like it's all
like okay french like we'd watch gratitude or whatever spanish. We look
at the show. It's like people are treating stuff and then I remember like
latin was like everyone hated is really boring because there's nothing it's it's
old who cares in the chinese class, the teacher would show his videos of like
buddhist monks getting hit with hammers like chinese people doing like bug
fighting rings where these two bugs are like
that's so did anyone you anyone anyone's mom you knew as a kid ever could like
convert to Buddhism. No, my mom started putting Buddhas around the house,
though that's the kind of I didn't hey, if you don't know someone whose mom
converts to Buddhism, you might be the one you might look at yourself. I that's
Heretical by the way yeah, yeah, she needs to as a Catholic as a strong Catholic
She shouldn't have started looking into bushes. It should it guys fat
He's fat. He's completely
Idol mm-hmm about being skinny like John Mulaney, but you can't be fucking fat as a Catholic. Yep. I'll say there's no
Fat leave that that's for the Protestants. Let us handle being fucking giantly
We all saw father stew for that chapeau episode
It's so funny that he just becomes like like they put Mark Wahlberg in a fucking fat suit. Yeah
Did he was really forget about that and then I think about it and it's fire. Yeah, so funny
Shit, what the hell are you getting a phone call? No, my laundry's done. Oh god
See I could use that as an alarm there's multiple things the bell could have been an alarm
Yeah, well, you could have told me put it off in 40 minutes. I was in there
Yeah, it would have been easy would have been easy would have been easy and
We wouldn't have to rely on technology, which is completely taking over the world. I know I know need to go past week
I noticed technology and AI is starting to take over the earth and I noticed that
Revolution and its consequences have been a disaster for society. I think that we need to go in a backwards direction with technology and
Supplies you have funny as shit. Yeah, I did that was fire. That was fire
I think that we need to go completely backwards with our system society
Yeah, and we need to move from let's get rid of the we like it's like tradition
Let's go away from the iPhones away from the computers. No microwaves
Let's move towards more of a floppy disk record player kind of rotary phone rotary phone, you know pay phone
Whatever, let's get rid of the cars. Okay
Again, yeah, here's Roebuck. That's right. Yep. Sears Roebuck pleated khakis
Wool and how about I'd completely out of wool animals no wait. What's the material that they say is in a rayon?
That makes your balls ruined. I don't know I think it lasted thorns
Yeah, it might be it might be radio. I think it's a razor razor razor razor wire radioactive razor wire. Yeah
Yeah that I guess they're putting in your underwear underwear. Yeah, it's yeah, that's stronger to
Strange side effect yeah that it causes blood to run down your leg
I kind of believe that I kind of believe that all the things that we wear probably make your balls ruined
I think everything is I think everything is is like that my balls might as well be just fucking like prank balls
Yeah, like the you'd buy it us at some kind of gag shop my penis. They're like silica. Yeah, that's what I mean
They're like really have any use for it. It's so useless
It might as well be like like a removable thumb and a magic you should be able to like like with a like with a dog
I should be able to just tie a rubber band around it and just
Yeah, get rid of it ways how they do balls on dog. That's how they do balls in Fight Club. Yeah, really I think
Remember that scene in Fight Club, man. I gotta get what that's when I knew something was up
I'm getting um, you know Fight Club the
Do you know about like what kind of inspired all that is that club the thing the cacophony club or the like suicide club in?
San Francisco no, there's this group of people who
I lived in San Francisco. What's his name?
The what's the name of the guy who wrote Fight Club?
Chuck Palahniuk was a part of this thing that it was basically they would do like
They would just walk around and be and just act weird in San Francisco
And they'd like walk around on the top of a building and like walk on the edge and be like whoa look how fucking cool
This is yeah, and yeah
So pretty much makes sense yeah
So like and then he was like I'm gonna take that and make it actually cool and make a book in a movie out of it
But the real thing was like, oh, we're gonna make,
what if we ate a food that tasted like complete shit?
- Yeah, it was a prank group.
- Yeah, it was like a prank group.
- It's kinda like us.
- It's cool that like, back before the internet,
you could just do shit like that.
Like the only thing to really entertain yourself
was like, oh, we're not gonna fill,
we're just gonna do this just for us.
- Yeah, this is 1980s, there's no movies or books.
- We're gonna make a weird salad.
- That's basically what it was.
As far as I, listen, I haven't done any reading on this club at all, except maybe the first
couple lines of the Wikipedia page. But it seems like they started Burning Man, and so
they started Burning Man because they were like--
They started Burning Man?
Yeah, they were like, "Can we just go be weird in just a different area?"
Wow.
And so they went to the desert in Nevada, and they were like, "This is seriously awesome,
and in 30 years there will be boobs here."
Yeah.
And so they basically did that.
It's so cool that Burning, like, Hoes corrupted it.
I kind of want to go to Burning Man.
mine if they what here's the thing like tech guys love Burning Man I'm gonna go
to bring man I'm addressed up like you us three dress all the burners dress up
like the ho busters right that's kind of a Ghostbusters they'll up dress up like
cops right and then we kill all the women who dress you dress like sluts at
the no I think we're gonna start our a separate a separate festival it's maybe
right next to it yeah so you can see it front you can see left we have a giant
effigy of a of a ho. We'll do a leftist one, it's called Burning Ho.
Burning Ho. Burny Man. Burny Man. We'll do a leftist Burning Man. How about we just
bring, how about a festival, right? It's called Burny Mac.
How about Turning Man? Burny Mac Festival. And it's all
Burny Mac impersonators on stage, each doing different sets.
I will say for Burning Man, it's cool that they do actually have a Burning Man.
How about Furnace Man? And we get a guy who can light it on fire. Most festivals don't have an
Coachella that's a really good and at rolling loud they never roll loud well
there's some people in the crowd it's illegal to do that so they don't do it I
think they do it because it's in its legal state and Woodstock has nothing to
do with peanuts that's a good point yeah that's burning man they're like we know
we know what you want I watch that Woodstock 99 documentary and I learned
and they had no peanuts there. I got mad. It's crazy how they keep making
Woodstock 99 documentaries. I feel like there have been like four in the past
year. Yeah, and they're all so bad. It's been enough time that everyone would
stock no peanuts.
Sorry.
The Bella.
Oh man, you've made my phone fly.
What the fuck?
How did you do that?
Do I ring a bell for myself?
(knocking)
- There you go.
- You're making my computer fly.
- His phone's already breaking.
- I'm sorry.
- What were you saying?
- I'm trying to break it more.
- What were you saying about whatever you were saying?
- I don't even know, I'm so mad about my friend
destroying your property.
- It's fucked up, man.
- I didn't destroy it.
- You destroyed my property?
- Look at the back of his phone right now.
- It already was like that earlier.
You complained about that earlier.
- No, you added that crack.
- Yep, you added that one right there.
- No, you're ganging up on me.
I heard Patrick comment on this crack.
- Yeah, that's called democracy, asshole.
- No, it's not.
Wait, no it's not.
That's called corruption.
You know, if you tap the Apple on the back of your phone three times, you can program
it to do stuff.
Yeah, I made it go to my camera.
Really?
It's two times, I think.
Wait.
Not three.
Watch this.
What did I do?
Check this out.
I think mine is screenshots.
I have to unlock it.
See, I was going to set it to screenshot, but then I was like, I don't want to accidentally
take screenshots.
Mine is really, there we go.
See?
Whoa, mine doesn't do anything.
How did you do that?
You have to go into the settings.
Yeah, you can do that.
I won't be doing that.
It's a little daunting for me.
I mean I can get to the camera way more easily than doing that.
It's not a funny trick.
Why would you do that?
I'd be like a ghost is haunting my phone.
Why would they add that?
Why would they add that feature?
I did that and put my phone to sleep.
But you're still tapping.
For people who have like one arm.
For people who can't like, yeah, swipe or have, it's hard for them, it's easier for
them to tap the back of the phone.
To get to one thing?
Yeah, I mean, or like for example, a screenshot if you can't reach the two buttons.
Oh, if you have one finger or something.
You can program it to do different things.
Oh, yeah, makes sense.
Okay.
Alright, why might I do that?
It doesn't have to be a camera.
also do it for lazy fucking fat guys that's what it's that's what it's used
by yeah lazy fat ass yeah if you hit it three times what does it do made
everything a little bigger okay okay so then you can do this what it you have to
do this podcast is almost getting too good that's called Apple pay I think
that we need to be tested for performance enhancing drugs yeah yeah or
would you submit to a to a urine test Patrick yes and you Cameron sure I won't
be doing it I'll be administering the tests okay well I'll test you after and
I'll administer your test with your mouth yeah well that's how you test it
they drank Roger Clemens pee did you get what to test his blood for PEDs to be
blood for me they drank is Roger Clemens is a pitcher for the Red Sox then he
left for the Yankees they drank his blood and drank his blood and his pee to test
it for performance-enhancing what is it taste actually was on the Astros when
that was tested that what does it taste like PDS PDS tastes like licorice so if
your blood or pee tastes like licorice you've done PDS before in the past mm-hmm
Did you guys ever do you ever have a drug test when you were like in high school or
something? No. You had to do you had to take one of those rehab one of those like
drug test clearing things? I never got I never got drug tested. You never got drug tested?
I think I got drug tested like one time. I can't remember. I feel like in my brain I
can't tell the difference. Why did you get a drug test? It was in Boston for some
reason they were like you have to take a drug test and I was like. Were you
applying there? Yeah. Oh okay. No I was buying. I thought I was like yeah get this
like RTX 2070 you can't you have to pass a drug test. No but they did it but for
because it's a it's a national company or whatever their policy was that you
can't have marijuana in your system to work at micro center so I just did. That's
crazy. Yeah. Isn't that crazy? Yeah that's the stupidest shit. They didn't realize I've have
I had a fucking chronic fucking inflammation at the time for two or
three weeks. I did. Yeah. Chronic inflammation in my fucking boring gland.
I was a damn bored and I need to uninflame it by smoking weed. Come on.
Ding that bell. Yes, sir.
Thank you.
I hate chronic illness. I can't stand the shit when somebody has a chronic
illness. I don't believe in chronic illness. I don't believe in in human
trafficking. None of that is real.
I'm serious. I don't believe in any of that.
I think if somebody puts a zip tie around your car, that just means they like your car.
My car's covered in zip ties, okay?
All my car's covered in zip ties.
It's been graffitied on.
I have a target painted on the top.
What if you... here's an idea for everyone who's worried about zip ties on cars for human
trafficking or whatever.
Put the zip tie on the car yourself so that the human trafficker thinks, "Oh, this is
someone else's bad choice."
Also, they're just giving teenagers funny prank ideas.
I have seen people believe this. I'm just going to start putting fucking plastic
bags and everybody. I mean that a lot of a lot of that stuff is fake, but I did
see there is actually one sign that you can tell if so if you've been marked for
human trafficking. All right, Bill. No, I'm see if you if you walk if you're in
the safe, you're in Wal-Mart and you walk out, you're walking out to
your car and you look at your car and you see on your car, you see a man in a
cloak wearing a sign that says slaver around his neck. Usually you should avoid
your car and you should call the police. Ladies, here's a quick tip on how to spot
if they're trying to human traffic you. I just walked out to my 2006 Ford Focus in
the Walmart parking lot and sitting in the driver's seat you can see there's a
man in a completely black hoodie. He has an evil smile, has completely red eyes. If
you see this, you need to call the police. Do not get in your car. Yeah. Usually
another way to tell is if you're walking down the street and a man starts chasing
you with a burlap sack that's usually a giant butterfly net I went to my car the
or it's a butterfly net you might have been an escaped ape yeah or that person
could be looking for butterflies you ever you look at your car might be a
butterfly you might be a butterfly you might be a butterfly you leave the walmart you start
walking towards your car in the parking lot you start to start to notice as
as you're walking towards it. It's looking a little bit more to D is as
closer to it and behind it, you can see a guy holding up a big cardboard car.
If you notice that your car is within a giant cage and maybe one side of the
cage is propped up by a piece of wood, then if you might be a butter, if
you're coming out of walmart, okay and you get in your car and then you
realize that you're actually not in your car, you're in the back of a van
your wrists and ankles are tied together.
And they've given you a fake steering wheel.
And then you get out of the car and you're in Thailand.
Do you think you probably are on vacation?
Do you think when somebody gets human trafficked like that at a Walmart parking lot, like if
it does happen, do you think they keep the groceries?
I feel like that's a...
That's a tough thing.
You've killed this woman.
That's why they get them from Walmart.
You've killed this woman, you've drank her blood, and then you're like, "Well, there's
there's eggs, there's frozen stuff in here. We can't put it somewhere.
No, it's a bonus because if you, I mean, you put, you grab a woman from
walking on the sidewalk. I mean, sure, you got a new slave, whatever, but you
grab one from Walmart, you got a slave and you got a brand new Blu-ray box set
from the DVD section of Walmart. Also- You ever bought groceries at Walmart?
These guys are- Yeah. You cut into a red onion from Walmart, the middle of that
thing, mold. Why are these the only criminals? I think that might be one red
onion. These are the only criminals- It happened every time I bought a red onion
Walmart. These are the only criminals that aren't telling on themselves on like
Instagram live. Everybody else is like, everybody else is like has video of their
guns or like credit cards they've stolen. You never see somebody like going around
they're like check this out y'all just a bunch of women in shackles in a basement.
You don't see that dude. How are they so good at keeping the secrets? Yeah we're
posted at Walmart we're about to steal a Debra or a Dennis. Yeah. Like they have
that guy is getting human trafficked. Well, because you see they just have
this it's like a picture and it's a guy holding a red sharpie and he's like you
know what it is and there's like a red X drawn on a car. If you know, you know.
Yeah.
Yeah, actually I mean in the Bible that happens, they're marking doors. That's
true, blood of the lamb. Yeah, well that's a thing and maybe that's it's a
blessing if you have the plastic bag, it means your first born son will be
spared and you'll be passed over. When did all of that human trafficking
stuff started. That was when aunties started getting whatsapp.
That's what cave paintings originally were.
If you see an antelope in your cave,
then you need to vacate. You need to go stay with the neighbors.
You need to migrate across the land bridge to America. Yeah, that's why they did it.
I do feel bad for people who do get human traffic though.
Really? Is that true? Because it's very degrading.
It is. It's embarrassing. Yeah. But you don't,
I don't know I don't know anybody who's gotten human trafficked. No, I've never
heard of anybody getting human trafficked, but maybe that's because the
traffickers are so good that they put a decoy. But then all the anytime there's a
missing person, any time there's a missing person there it's always
like it's always like their grandma who's the one who's like yeah they got
human trafficked and they're like I even though they found a skull that has the
exact same proportions as this person. They're wearing the exact same sunglasses.
yeah exactly we're missing yeah same outfit yeah it's in their bed yeah self
and be healthy even though we've got a body that looks almost exactly like it
was a decoy put I don't like a study or something that talks about like all the
human trafficking shit yes there's a well no there's a guy who is it there
because it feels like what's the name of the governor of Minnesota dude Ron Paul
No, the old-- Oh, Al Franken. No, the fucking-- the one who was crazy, the wrestler man. Jesse Ventura?
Jesse Ventura. He was-- he is a proponent of this theory where this guy wrote
this book that is like the secret epidemic of like missing people and
he purports that there's some kind of like crazy like conspiracy where
like 50,000 people go missing every year or whatever. But the statistic of like
50,000 people go missing every year is like to be qualified as missing you can
just be away from nobody saw you for like 24 hours so most of people either
killed themselves or just show back up yeah I mean people I think people get
human trafficked a lot but it's not it's not Walmart it's not it's not Walmart
it's not happening it because there's one video I saw where it's like a woman
is describing her almost getting human trafficked and it's clear that it's just
like a it's a tick-tock it's one of those ones where they like fucking zoom
in on themselves like yeah oh my god you guys and they like the zoom hard zoom
onto their own face so she's gonna do it's clear mind yeah she's got like kind
of like a Spielberg Ian it's kind of take on human trafficking and it's like
clear that she's like like as a dude trying PUA tactics yeah because I guess
the only thing it's a guy different hard monty yeah the only thing different
between the only difference between I guess like human trafficking tactics and
like PUA stuff is violence. Yeah, yeah, and I would say Romania. Yeah, yeah, and
Andrew Tate. You get sent to, I think that's most human traffic
stuff you get sent to Eastern Europe and then you get shipped out and then
you're on a reality TV show. Or you're a crypto gambling host. Yeah, chain to the table. You're
playing craps for people. You go directly to stake.com and you hand operate a slot machine.
Pretty good idea actually. They should be doing, like you know how they have, you know
that one poster of all the Pink Floyd albums on the women's back, you should do
that with slot machines so that there's a human slot machine element. That is genius.
I thought you were saying do that with missing people posters. Oh that's a
good idea. That's also good though. Yeah you should be, I feel like you should have a
naked photo of somebody if they're missing. No not a naked photo of the
person but like the Pink Floyd album cover except if they're not
not album covers, just high profile missing people.
And you hang that up in a college dorm,
so then, who's the most, Gen Z, statistically,
they're the most socially conscious.
So they're gonna see that in a dorm,
they're gonna start a movement
to find all these missing people.
- Speaking of movement and missing people,
I heard in Eastern Europe, all their cars
are like Flintstone cars that are powered
by women from Walmart.
- Yes, which by the way, speaking of return to tradition,
let's go back to those cars.
rid of these electric cars let's go back to it let's go back to that little red and yellow
car.
I want to return to tradition.
Get rid of that little red and yellow car in your neighborhood.
Red and yellow car that runs on feet.
Yeah get rid of this fucking watch on my wrist.
A dinosaur.
They should make a big version of that red and yellow car for adults.
I agree.
I'm so tired.
Don't make me yawn man.
I've been watching this kitten.
Ding ding ding.
Yeah the kitten's taking you out.
He just learned how to climb up the couch.
- Luckily a cat stays inside.
A dog has to go, you have to run with a dog.
You have to go to a place with a dog and go, "Wah!"
- This cat, I found a stray on the street.
I took it home, I nursed it back to health,
and honestly, I wish it stayed sick.
- Basically, it's basically what me and Cam did with you.
- I wish he stayed sick.
He used to stay in one spot of the apartment.
He would use his litter box, he would eat, that was it.
now he's too healthy he's running around the whole place.
He stays up to three in the morning.
We found Patrick in a plastic box on the side of the street.
It was a bin.
There was a lid on.
Tuffs of hair missing.
This kitty.
It turns out we thought someone had left him.
Turns out he got stuck in the box himself.
And I was shaving my head.
We had to take him to the vet, get him all sorts of shots.
We had to teach him English.
They had to mess with his anus a bunch.
Similar to the cat I found, I had an impacted anal gland.
Yeah, well they said they actually...
We were never able to explain it.
Yeah, the vet said it wasn't actually an impacted anal gland.
It was some...
Well, the vet that we took him to.
Yeah, we took him to a vet.
Yeah, obviously.
It's less expensive than a doctor.
I had a lot of hair on me.
It was a lot less expensive.
But the vet said it was something going on with the anus that he'd never seen before.
He didn't know what it was called, the problem.
They said he had avian flu.
Uh-huh.
Yep.
I got it from eating chicken.
I said he had he had a caterpillar AIDS mm-hmm that's true.
I mean like that's a what is that what and he said I don't know I don't know
right now I'm a crazy silly doctor and that's when we ended up going to a
different vet yeah I went to a different vet yeah because he was making stuff up
so that you would pay more yeah yeah yeah and he also charged to wipe your
butt mm-hmm yep dude I got a I gotta go I gotta bring that cat I gotta do stuff
with that cat. What are you gonna do with the cat? I'm gonna make sure he's not...
Dude, his butthole, I took a photo of him I was like oh that's cute he's laying on
his belly. I looked at the photo and you can see his butt is just poking out.
You got a slutty cat? Dude, I don't know. You have a hoe cat? I found him on the street in
front of the office. Yeah. He's about to get hit by cars. That's not very smart of
him. No. So you got an idiot too? He's so dumb. He's so stupid. Phil tries to chase motorcycles. Yeah.
it's pretty stupid yeah you're not gonna win that fight buddy no you're not gonna
win that race I think he could maybe he's getting fast again think about
think about that like the two fat twins who ride the motorcycles hmm I think if
you had the two twins yeah me neither what you ever seen that photo to like
this book of world records for madness
you've seen that photo the fat twins I got a little bad twins on motorcycles I
also wearing overalls and if I just search fat twins on motorcycles do you
think it'll come up? That's an auto-complete, autocompleted, un-sepia-toned photo.
The McGuire twins! Yeah. These fat twins are on a fucking motorcycle.
They're on Billy and Benny Lloyd McCrary. Oh these are okay so they're not it's not
just a motorcycle thing yeah the fattest identical twins in the Guinness World
Records known as the McGuire twins were the fattest to ever walk the planet the
pair performed as tag team wrestlers and weighed more than 100 stone combined
feels kind of rude to talk about a fat person say the fattest person ever walked
the planet like they're a dinosaur. Exactly dude.
That's what I'm thinking. Like they're a fucking brontosaurus.
Yeah it's so fucking rude the fattest who ever fucking roamed the earth.
Walked the planet?
The fattest people who ever roamed the earth.
That's what you say about like a hundred foot long extinct animal.
Yeah that's fucked up.
person that's fucking rude what was their real crime just drink it like being
good at eating hamburgers there are a hundred stone yeah combined which a
hundred stone I mean that's bloody mental yeah that's how I own is that 30 pounds
that's that is it I mean it's a stone what's a I mean a pound I don't how many
pound how many stone is a pound I think it's 30 30 stone is a pound how many
stones is in a pound fuck it's the other way it's the other way how many pounds
in a stone 14 14 14 pounds to the stone 14 pound to a stone so they were weird
well they were they were 14 were weird they were they weighed net near nay
1,400 stone pounds hundred pounds here's my thing a stone should wear one pound I
think you're completely right way one pound okay bye okay bye Halloween show
tickets to Halloween slash shows.
Go check it out.
Halloween night at the Bell House in Brooklyn.
What time?
We don't remember but go check it out on the show website.
It's on the show website.
Swagboot.com/shows.
I'll see you guys on the next one. Bye!