You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[Laughter]
Oh my god, another beautiful Saturday.
Are you recording?
I'm recording.
Okay, are you recording?
Yeah, all three of us are feeling fine and good.
Okay, you ready to take on the day?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm gonna go nuts today.
Yeah, I'm thinking of starting a new club.
- Yeah, what's it gonna be?
- It's just for bad boys and bad asses.
- The Bad Boys Bad Ass Club.
- Yeah, basically it's kind of a bad boy bad ass club.
- You have the word bad in there twice,
you could shorten it to the boys ass club.
- That's not a bad idea, boys ass club.
- Bad boys ass club.
- Yeah, bad boys ass club, and then I could,
yeah, we could have like a t-shirt that says
the boys are back BAC, like boys ass club.
- Yeah, oh, that's pretty good.
you know is a boy's ass club
the boys are
you know what they're
exactly the bad
and the bad
okay the boys asses bad is what you could say
that could be a lot of race
nevermind i'm chained my avenue club that's a fear the furious ass guys
no
why uh... no with the jury is s guys
these boys are
I'm one big furious ass guy.
I'm a furious ass guy, Game of Thrones.
God damn it.
I'm the most, I'm a huge furious ass guy, the guy of time.
Yeah, greatest of time.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's our new club.
Do you guys want to join my club? I just have to write the name on your hand.
It's called the I Love Penis Club.
I'm not going to... yeah, I have to write the acronym for it.
I'm not going to tell you what the different words are,
but the tattoo does have to go somewhere visible,
like the top of a forearm or maybe even your neck.
Your forehead.
It has to go on your forehead.
Yeah.
We should start selling temporary tattoos.
That's not a bad idea. I did think of that.
You did?
First.
So no I thought about it. No I did think of that first. No Patrick didn't think of that first
I did actually I did send you a picture of
Some temporary tattoo website with the the Caleb monkey face on it, and you guys did not
Respond so I don't remember that I don't even I don't even look at exactly you didn't remember it so
Like they put the Caleb monkey face up just independently no
No, I uploaded it to a temporary tattoo website.
Oh, okay.
That's cool.
I honestly didn't know they had temporary tattoo websites.
I should look at the text that you send more often because that's actually cool.
Yeah.
Most of the time if Cam sends it, I know that it's business.
If Pat sends it, I know it's a picture of an old man's balls and penis and I usually
ignore that.
I don't send all business.
i said i sent three pictures in a row that nobody responds to all find a
picture on google that's like
this machine can kill of a rat using nightmares and then i'll send it and
nobody responds to the issue of your answer is a guy who has a
the
and then i would or respond twenty minutes all send something else
and then they'll be response all this year every twenty minutes until somebody
says lol and then i can
kind of continue with my day. I say I say a loyal to most of Cameron's things. Yeah
Patrick's really nice. I'm the only one who's nice. I'm testing you guys right now.
Caleb's the meanest one on the show. Absolutely. Caleb's like the kind of guy
who gets rich and then he he lives in a floating fortress above the earth and he
doesn't let anybody into the fortress. That guy doesn't exist. It's you. It's you.
If you don't think it exists buddy, take a look in the mirror. Yeah take a look
- I'm sending a photo. - Look down, look down right now.
- I'm sending a photo.
- It's your penis. - Nice, nice.
Okay, wow, I really stretched that out.
- What's this photo? - Is anybody gonna respond?
I sent a photo of a big fat woman wearing a shirt
that says, "Riots not diets."
- I respond, "That's crazy."
That's a pretty good response.
That's like kind of a men's response
that men like to use to things.
- Okay, I'm gonna hit you guys with a no LOL question mark.
(laughing)
Not, check this out, not this time.
This is a, this is just a black square.
Oh no, it has a drawing.
Okay, so Patrick sent us a drawing of a penis.
- Of a square-- - And then it evaporated.
- It actually kinda just looks like the crimson shin.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
Yeah, let's do a whole episode of we text each other.
- Of us texting each other.
(laughing)
- Just all of our text messages.
It's not a bad idea.
Simulate what it's like to be in the group chat.
You can smell my fart.
What's it called?
Yeah, it's called You Can Smell My Fart.
You can smell my fart.
Reference to the--
The Chuck Berry sex tape.
Chuck Berry.
Yeah, the classic.
One of the all-timers, dude.
I would say definitely one of the founding texts
of this podcast.
Yeah.
I would say heavily inspired by the Chuck Berry sex tape.
One part of the canon.
Yeah.
It's like, let's see, what else is besides
the Chuck Berry sex tape?
- The acid stuff.
- The acid, oh yeah, yeah, definitely.
(laughing)
Yeah, taking acid with you two.
- That's the only way you can come up with a podcast
this twisted and deep.
- Yeah, yeah.
- 'Cause if you take acid and then come up with the idea,
we're gonna make a podcast where we read lists online
and talk about sucking a poop.
- The entire, the fucked up part was that
we came up with that sober.
We came up with the idea to add Patrick
while we were on X.
We were like, you know what would be so crazy
if we added Patrick.
- Right, and now look at where we are.
- And now look at us, dude.
- Down in the fucking gutter.
- Yeah.
- We're all in the gutter.
- I just remember that was like one of the first times
I really did hang out with you guys.
- That's true, yeah.
- Yeah.
- I'm looking up right now what day Patrick
joined the podcast so we can celebrate Patrick.
- Let's do a friendship history episode.
- Yeah, people love that kind of thing.
- Yeah.
- Patrick. - When did I join?
- I'm looking it up right now. - It's on the Instagram.
- Calm down.
- Sometime in like April or something.
- Yeah, it was after PAX, I know that.
Oh, we went to PAX East together.
- That was huge.
- Let's see, it was-- - I found a Sunday pass
on the ground. - April 4th, 2019.
- Ooh, the April Fool himself has joined the podcast.
- Yeah.
- The April Fool has logged on. - The anniversary
- The podcast itself is Christmas Eve,
which is so funny.
That's the day the first episode came out.
- We could re-release my first episode on April 4th.
- No, it's not a bad idea.
- The one where I was a guest.
- We could.
- You could hear how nervous I was to be on the show.
- You were nervous?
- Not nervous, no, I was nervous that I would slip up
and somebody would get mad at me for something I said.
- You slip up.
Dude, we have like 15 people listening then.
- Yeah, I know.
- And none of them knew you.
- And I was mad that one of those 15 people
would be mad at me.
- Yeah, dude.
We were grinding, dude.
We had like 10 listeners for 30 episodes.
- Yeah, for so long.
- It's so awesome.
- I was one of the listeners.
- Yeah, it's crazy that we just kept going
until it actually worked.
- Yeah, I can't believe we didn't just stop.
- Yeah, dude, any person in their right mind
would have been like, well, nothing.
- Yeah, this is clearly not, this is terrible.
Clearly not working.
- Yeah, we'll just stop now.
- No, we've wasted so much of our lives.
I know we deleted like the first 30.
Yeah, they're not even, yeah, they're not even fucking four months of our life and then just
deleted it.
I mean, that was like, I had nothing better to do then.
I was just like, "Oh, man, this shit."
And just like, drinking all day.
Yeah, and I mean, the thing to remember too is it was at work.
We were literally, we were making money doing it.
True, we probably got paid more then than we do now.
Right.
It's true, per episode technically.
What a fucking life that was, dude.
Now, here we are.
And now it's a different time, so that shows you how time works.
Yeah, and time moves forward.
Yeah, that's kind of crazy.
Yeah.
Who are we going to add next? That's the question.
Yeah, but we've already added patches.
A year from now...
That's true, we did add patches.
He's our employee.
And I hope he never fucking forgets it. That's the goddamn truth.
Exactly.
from now who's going to be the new guy we have to
we say patricks is fourth mike we say that he's fourth mike
we have to add another guy named patrick
as a title
exactly
we've added two fucking patricks
or you've added two patricks
i fuckin i'm one of them
we need a yeah
let me google patricks
neil patrick harris
funny i'm gonna google funniest patricks
that would be good for us
ok patrick star
- Patrick Starr is the top result.
- I cannot compete with him.
I cannot compete with him and you know that.
- That's true.
- Dude, it'd be awesome.
Neil Pond, do you know I can't compete with Patrick Starr?
- That is so funny.
You are just the Patrick Starr of the podcast.
You fill the same role.
- Yeah, and you're Squidward, bitch.
You're a big blue bitch.
- Guess who gets to be SpongeBob then?
- You are not SpongeBob.
- Nobody's Sam Sandy.
- You're SpongeBob because you're gay.
- You're Mr. Krabs.
- I'm not gay.
- Caleb is Mr. Krabs because he's red, bald.
- He has a shell.
I feel like I can't even.
And he's greedy.
He tries to turn everything into a business opportunity.
I get a lot of shit for being red.
You are very red.
I'm not that red.
I'm really not.
I feel like we gotta cut back on the calling each other gay stuff.
We've already done furious ass guys.
We've hit the quota already.
We hit the quota up top.
Think if we got Neil Patrick Harris we could be like, yeah it'd be called furious ass guys.
Hey Neil, what is that?
(laughter)
What would that sound like?
- That's the only thing.
- At any time we'd be like, "Yes, dude, yes."
I'm so glad we added you and killed Patrick.
- Yeah, I can't wait till we get big enough
that we can hire a producer and put out an ad
that says, "We're looking for a producer
"must be named Patrick, but have a different nickname
"than Pat or Patches."
(laughter)
- Cannot speak English.
- Yeah, must be named Patrick, must go by Rick.
- There we go.
- That's our ad.
- Is that it?
Do people go by Rick?
- I mean, that's the only other nickname I can think of.
- My brother's named Eric.
My brother's named Eric
and his friends call him Ricky sometimes.
I think they call him Ricky as a joke, yeah.
- Is Rick the most versatile nickname?
- Let's see here.
- John is.
- Nicknames.
- What is John short for?
- John and Johnson.
- Jim is short for so much shit.
- That's true.
Ed is short for a lot of stuff.
- Yeah.
Ted is also, Ted Cruz's name is Raphael Edward.
- CJ, that's the biggest one.
- Yeah, most abbreviations, yeah, CJ.
It could be, his name is like--
- Big P.
- Big P?
- Yeah.
- What the hell?
All right, listen to this.
Common nicknames--
- That's what my old manager used to call me.
- Diddy.
- These are the top four common nicknames for Patrick
according to dataeyes.com.
- Patty, Pat, Pate, and Peter.
- Pate?
- Peter?
- P-A-T-E.
- That must be some Gaelic spelling.
- Yeah.
- Pate, I think is what you're thinking.
- Yeah, I think you're thinking of food.
- That's actually a food.
- You're thinking of cat food.
You're thinking of cat's food.
- Do cats eat pate?
- Yeah, that I've seen.
- That's a fancy cat!
- Oh, we need a producer.
We need a producer named Patsy.
- Oh, there we go.
- Oh, a girl.
A girl Patrick?
- Yeah.
- We could throw a girl in the mix.
We could get a girl producer.
- Yeah.
- And we could get like, we could set up some--
- No!
- One of us needs like a basement.
(laughing)
One of us needs like a basement where we can set up
like a shitty home studio and put like,
put cameras on us that nobody wants.
- Yeah, and like wizards we all live in different states
so we have to like--
- Yeah, we have to call in still.
- Well no, we could do, we could put a studio in Connecticut.
- I can't have people watch the podcast.
I can't have all these fucking Reddit guys criticizing me.
- Yeah, you think they would criticize you more
if they saw you?
- If they saw me like--
- Well, yeah, no, you can't give them screenshot ammo.
I mean, those-- - Right.
- The subreddit is entirely just people
posting pictures of people
and then just with the name of one of us.
- Yeah.
- It's just like people posting--
- I can't have them.
- Don't appreciate the ones targeted at me.
I don't have a dent in my head.
I don't have Down Syndrome.
I...
Jubio is not a host also.
Jubio is not a host and he doesn't look like Luis Gomez.
No.
Please stop saying this.
That's actually racist for you to say that.
So you know what?
You're getting a negative flare from us.
That's right.
We're going to give you a flare on the Reddit.
We're going to give you a flare that says the most racist guy on the Reddit.
That's what a lot of other podcasts don't understand is you have to become a moderator
of your subreddit.
You have to become a moderator and you have to torment the fans because fuck the fans.
God control you can't let them be autonomous. You need to be you need to be in charge of everything editing every single post
No, but we can't like like the twitch is already too much for me
Like I fuck you know any like I jewel too much and I will make fun of you for trying my face
No, I'm just no now. I don't know now. I've now I've given them the fucking ammo now
I've told them what I'm fucking sensitive about is my tics and shit. You're sensitive about doing drugs. I do
Did you have to your tics I yes, I take see you've made fun of them
You've made fun of my tics before he has all over him. Yeah, I will in the woods. Yeah, I see them
They're building a city on your forehead
I'm looking I'm looking through the comments on the head is not big enough for a city it is it's not it's getting there
Oh, you're hey, you're already there, but no, I don't I I did the smart thing where I eliminated my forehead
There is no there's no evidence that my forehead where my forehead starts or ends
Yeah
So I for you have no clue your forehead goes from your eyebrows
And it goes up over your head all the way back down to your ass exactly which means effectively
I have no forehead no it means you have the biggest forehead in the world
No, my no my forehead is is just between my eyes or my unibrow would be if I had one
But I don't so that's my forehead
Fucking idiots. No, you're an idiot. So stupid we could add Pat Benatar. That's true
Yeah, the barracuda herself
Yeah
I'm
She she's not no no Pat Benatar is not barracuda. I don't care. That's heart
I thought that I thought no heart is an organ
Yeah, you idiot. No
Listen to this. This is a bad trick
I want you to listen to this and tell me if this sounds like your experience with having
the name Patrick, okay?
Okay.
My name is Patrick.
When I have fights or disagreements, people tend to use my name against me.
Apparently the name Patrick is not as great as you all think, because I have grown to
hate it.
In casual or confrontational situations, people don't usually say your name, but I've had
people use my name as a way to make me appear lesser than others, and it is just because
of my name.
like Sean, Matt, Chris, or Kyle, while very average, seem much tougher in comparison.
The name Patrick seems like the title for someone much less tough.
There's been a clip online that was on TV about a guy named Patrick and he was referred
to as a guy who reads and writes poetry and is very emotional.
Hence his title, Emotional Patrick.
There's also Patrick from Spongebob, who is a complete idiot.
And Patricia, a female version used when people are blatantly being disrespectful and trying
to insult or embarrass you. The name is associated with being pathetic, etc. It can be difficult
living with this title at times.
It can be a great name to have when you've been recognized for an accomplishment, but
at other times it can feel like a burden, such as working as a green hand in a hyper-masculine
atmosphere such as construction.
As stated above, people will often form opinions based on your name or nickname and you will
be treated accordingly.
It's not easy to rise to greatness when people don't think you're worth much.
I am constantly doubted and it's rare somebody feels I am worthy of being put in a position
of power or given a great opportunity despite my natural leadership ability and compassionate
nature making me a suitable candidate for leadership roles.
My experience as Patrick has sort of sucked.
No, that's a comment by that guy 27
What does it feel like to be? Well, I don't know I when I was
Actually, I did when I was uh, you are only a 1% owner
Right. No, I'm not you actually do that because that would suck I could see you fucking doing that
That would fucking so bad you would know you would you would be you'd have no tax liability. That's true
Yeah, you would be yeah, then where then I would have to explain that where all my fucking money was coming 1%
Yeah, we are small business owners now, dude, yeah
That's why we got home before the beginning yeah
- Wait, before we move on to the small business,
I just have to, right under that really long,
like, sad comment, the next comment just says,
"It reminds me of that silly character in SpongeBob."
(laughing)
- Yeah, when I was 10, I tried to go by Ed,
I tried to go by Edward, whoa, for a week,
and I wouldn't respond to anybody
if they didn't call me Edward, so.
- I tried to go by Michael,
but my whole family iced me out and wouldn't--
- Yeah, my family iced me out, too.
- We gave you, it is kinda fucked up
You don't get to choose a cool name when you're a kid.
Yeah.
Yeah. I had to choose, I was Pat for a little bit and then I just started going by Patrick recently.
What?
Yeah. I didn't go by, I preferred Pat. Like if a teacher asked, I'd be like,
"Yeah, please call me Pat."
I've never called you anything but Pat, I don't think.
I'm telling you now, you have to stop.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry for all that.
You have to stop it.
No, no.
You have to start calling me Patrick.
Okay, Patrick.
to hate being called cam and then i was just like wait what i have yeah i don't i don't
yeah i don't have any reason to hate being called cam why yeah it's fine well except for the fact
it's a stupid name when i was in when i was in third grade you know caleb is hebrew for dog
but it's you know it's cool you know what you know what's the most loyal creature on planet earth a
dog a bug no no it's not a cricket and it's not a spider it's a dog it's a bug you can't just say
bug there's so many bugs and they're not all loyal some of them are very loyal
but some of them will stab you in the back like a stick but some of them will
kill you for a piece of sand but yeah fucking what's another bug I only know
you know what okay you know a beetle a beetle probably is the most loyal exactly
the most loyal animals a bug or a house plant it's true I met God she's a bug
that would be scary though yeah I just remembered when I started going by Pat
when I was in third grade because it was I couldn't fit Patrick in NBA Street
volume 2. What if... I started going by Pat. It's funny that they didn't have enough letters to fit
like one of the most common names. What if we found out that... Well I couldn't put my full
name if I did Patrick. Oh why'd you put your full name? I don't remember. What if we found out that
the Bible is completely true but it's about bugs? God was a bug and he created bugs in his own
image like so there's no archaeological evidence of anybody's right yes he was a
bug is just a bug people the thing is if you're an archaeologist you're like
looking for dinosaurs and the ark if you find anything else like a fucking if you
find like a beetle you toss it away dragonfly and taste in amber and a food
processor and make some that's why everybody in the Bible they said they
or like 900 years old 'cause to a bug,
being even a day is like 900 years.
- That's true.
- What a difference a day makes to a bug.
- I didn't think about that all the time as a kid,
just like--
- Yeah, bugs that live like one day and then die.
- How bad is that gonna suck, dude?
- No, dude, you get to fuck like an hour after you're born.
- It's true.
- Dream.
(laughing)
Dream life.
- That's the dream right there.
- I come out, I fuck the nurse in the NICU,
and then I die immediately.
My penis gets stuck in her and then I die.
- Yeah, you just shoot out of your mom like a face hugger.
- Like a bug.
- You shoot out of your mom like a bug.
- We should all work like bugs, dude.
You get born, you fight your mom.
If you kill your mom, you get to fuck her sister.
But if you die, she gets to fuck you.
- Yeah, yeah.
- It's pretty sad.
- If you die, you're still a bug.
Doesn't matter.
- If you die, you just die like a normal bug.
- And also you're avoiding giant shoes and hands
everywhere you go.
I think that would make us better people.
- Yeah. - If we were giant bugs.
- I think bugs get reincarnated.
They probably-- - Damn, this conversation
is Kafka-esque.
- Bugs only have, like, there are only so many bug souls
in the world, so they have to keep using them over and over.
So I think bugs get like reincarnated after they die, yeah.
- It's good to kill a bug. - Yeah, like if you kill a bug,
it can just start over again.
- Yeah, I do think that some people were bugs
in like the, not like a previous life,
- But immediately before this life.
- What people?
- Just, you know, just kinds of people.
(laughing)
Not kinds of people, just some people.
Just like, you know.
- Do you mean some famous people?
- Yes, that's what I mean, yeah.
Yeah, I mean, no, but like, yeah, you could just--
- Are you saying, are you, wait.
- You just kinda tell.
- Is this why, wait, is this why you are--
- Like for example, Bebe Netanyahu,
like you know immediately, like--
- Come on.
the bug. We can allude to it. We don't have to go there. I think Caleb is this
why you were asking. I would never go there, okay. Not in a million years would I go there. Is this why you were asking us for
exterminator recommendations, dude? No. No. Yeah, I think I have a men in black
problem. I think there's a, I think my, oh my god, dude. Oh fuck, I forgot about this.
Okay, I hope Jana isn't listening to me through the wall yesterday. So for like
- The past two days, Jana went up on the roof
a couple days ago.
We have roof access, it just has like,
it's not like a door, it's like a ladder
up to a hole in the roof that's covered
by a piece of metal.
And so yesterday, or two days ago,
Jana went up there and then just forgot
to close the piece of metal.
And yesterday, it rained super, super hard
in my neighborhood, and we didn't realize
that that thing was open the entire time.
So then the ceiling on the staircase
just like fell through all over the stairs.
And Jana just like, I was like playing fucking Valorant.
Jana like kept on playing.
- I was playing.
- She was like, you have to, no I was not.
She was like, you have to get off right now.
And I was like, what?
She was like, I can't explain.
(laughing)
You have to be quiet and you have to come with me.
And she just showed me just sheet rock all over the ground.
And I didn't realize my fucking fiance is like a,
she's like a criminal.
Like she was like, we have to clean this up
before anybody sees this.
We can't tell anybody, we wait for one of the other tenants
to report it because I don't want to lose roof access.
So yesterday I had to cover up my wife's crime
so that we could still fucking go smoke cigarettes
on the roof.
- People are gonna report this,
you shouldn't have said this on the podcast.
- I'm gonna send you a picture.
- The fans are here to ruin our lives.
- In the ceiling, it's horrible.
- It's us versus the fans.
- It kind of is, yeah.
- That's why I try and give my address
and my social security number at all points.
Any opportunity I have.
I gave mine out on the Thomas episode.
Your social?
We censored it.
You said that wasn't yours, didn't you?
Why would you ruin the joke for me?
I didn't know it was a joke.
I thought you were just saying something that wasn't true.
Me and Nealey said that was so funny.
Just like stand up in Boston when there's like 30 people in the crowd.
Is something bombs just say your social security number?
It's funny every time.
It truly is.
It's funny that the way the world works is like you have a number that you can't tell
anybody.
Yeah, yeah.
If you tell somebody it will ruin your life forever.
Yeah, like it could very possibly just fuck up everything for you if you tell somebody
this number, this fucking seven digit number.
Yeah.
Or nine digits.
I don't remember how many digits.
A hundred digits.
Mine is a hundred digits.
Yeah, they gave me the longest social security number.
Yeah, they gave me the longest penis in the world.
They knew I was smart enough to remember.
Have you ever seen the movie My Blue Heaven?
No.
Well, first of all, it's a great movie.
Have you seen "I Pooped Kevin"?
We need to talk about Kevin.
"I Pooped Kevin"?
"I Pooped Kevin", yeah.
It's a John C. Reilly movie.
Have you seen that movie "Poop, Where's My Crap"?
[laughter]
Yeah.
Have you seen that movie that's like "Inception"
but it's called "In the Toilet"?
[laughter]
No, I thought that was interstellar.
No, oh yeah, there's two
The same exact names the same director. Yeah, Pistopher Pistopher
Patrick's name my phone is splatter ik toilin. His name is pay pay Rick
Yeah
No, but my blue heaven
So I when I first learned like what I learned what social security numbers were because of that movie
It's a movie where Steve Martin plays like a an Italian mob guy
It's very yeah, it's a very like I
Just realized like my whole perception of like the mafia was warped because of that movie because I've never seen the Godfather
I've seen good fellas like I get it now, but like up until I saw good fellas
I was like yeah, the mafia is just like guys very funny the guy the mafia is just guys like Steve Martin
yeah stealing swordfish out of trucks like yeah they're always going excuse me
an arrow going through their head yeah yeah the mafia is a bunch of guys
playing a Steve Martin special was like this is oh my god ever since I was young
I wanted to be a gangster. My capo is King Tut.
Yeah, the dozen, uh, the cheaper by the dozen family, that's all.
Those are his, uh... That's the five families and one of them,
all of them have 12 kids. Uh-huh. I mean, that's mostly true for...
It is kind of true, actually, yeah, for Italians.
Yeah, we should add Steve Martin as the... We should add Steve Martin.
We should add Steve Martin to the podcast as the next one.
It's not a bad idea, I guess.
He could do some funny stuff, I think.
Oh yeah, but the fucking social security number, he just keeps listing off numbers.
So I thought you just did that to do your social security number.
I thought you just told an FBI agent you're fucking...
What do you mean?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know!
I don't remember.
What?
We can move on.
Wait.
So you...
I'm fuckin scatterbrained as shit today.
Wait what is he doing?
He's just leaving.
No I was trying to look for my jewel.
Alright here's what we're gonna do for the next member of the podcast to be added okay.
If you follow any of us, you are eligible.
Message Caleb your resume, message him and say, "Please let me on your podcast as a guest."
I don't look at my message requests.
Tweet at Caleb, respond to every one of Caleb's tweets for the rest of-
I have my mentions off too.
Okay, find Caleb's address and go to his house and knock on his door.
It's fine.
My address is the only one on the LLC.
Go to Sullivan the Frog Enterprises LLC.
It's out of Delaware.
It's all listed as public record.
- You're gonna give that away?
- I don't care.
I have a gun.
- Oh yeah, that's true.
Yeah, Caleb has a gun in New York.
It's unregistered.
- Yeah, that's how I stop him.
I just tell somebody, I have a gun.
- My address isn't on it, right?
- No, nobody's address but me is on it.
I lied to Delaware and said that you guys live with me.
Which is a funny thought.
- Why would you fucking say that on here?
'cause it doesn't matter.
- God, they're gonna ruin our lives.
- We do live with--
- Delaware's coming after us.
You better move in with Caleb.
You better sleep--
- You move into his house!
- You better sleep in a triple deck or bunk bed.
- Oh, could you imagine?
Oh my God, I wish I could go back.
I wish I could go back to triple deck bunk beds.
- You better get some of those glow in the dark stars
and put 'em on the ceiling in your shared bedroom.
- You guys better play Truth or Dare.
- Yeah, yeah.
- You guys better play a game that involves you
throwing shit off the top of your bed.
- When Ice is coming to see if a marriage
is just for the green card, they're like,
do you guys ever play truth or dare?
- Interesting.
- Dare him right now.
- No, I wanna see it.
I wanna see it.
- Have you ever held a flashlight under your chin
and huddled up in a blanket and told a scary story?
- Interesting.
- So you claim you sleep in the same bed, but.
- And yet.
- Hmm.
- All right.
- We should play some truth or dare right now.
- We should get some triple bunk beds is what I'm thinking.
- I think that would be, honestly,
for all of us at this time in our lives,
that would make the most sense.
- Yeah.
- I miss it, dude.
I had triple bunk beds growing up.
- I never had a bunk bed.
- Is that a break up with Jana?
We just all move into Cam's house?
- Yeah.
- You can move in.
- That might be a cool idea.
- Move into my parents' shed.
- You can move in once I move out.
- The shed on my.
- Yeah.
- That's cool.
Me and Pat just bunking into the basement.
- Shut up, I'm in a process.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- With your mom.
(laughing)
Yeah.
- No, we should definitely get like a,
we should definitely get like one of those TikTok houses.
- Oh my God.
- Dude, that would be so sick.
- That would be great.
- That would be sick.
We get like a, we get an attritionist.
If we get the patron of like,
like $50,000. - A million.
- I mean people, dude, let's just get a house.
- Yeah, why not, dude?
- People, people make fun of that TikTok house thing,
but it's like that's the new American dream right there.
- Right. - Like that's like,
you and a bunch of 13 year olds - That's what every kid
who is 10 fucking smoking weed and playing Xbox.
- Yeah. - Sick.
- Every kid who's like 13 right now is like,
this is what I wanna do when I grow up.
- Yeah, the 13 year olds are teaching like a 27 year old guy
how to do a Fortnite dance.
- Yeah. - And you're there.
- Patrick's there. - It's be awesome.
- I'm there. - Pat's there,
he's the manager. - I'm the guy that,
I'm the guy that they have around to bully.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause they need, they need.
- You're the bodyguard.
- They need to bully somebody.
- It's like that, that TikTok,
like where they like show every person
who lives in the house.
And the last one is like,
and we keep a freak in our basement.
And just have them looking through bars.
(laughing)
- He's the golem.
The golem we keep in the cage.
- This guy's like Gollum from Lord of the Rings,
except his rings is hot dogs.
- Yeah, we feed him cheeseburgers all day.
We feed him the the dollar store microwave
Leave whenever he wants
They have a they have a trap door
So if someone comes to apply to live in the tick-tock house, and they don't like them
They can just drop them right into Patrick's lair
Yeah, be pretty cool. Oh, she just sent me something. Oh, that's cool. Dude a 40 pound
exotic work right now a
A 40 pound exotic pet cat is on the loose in Merrimack, New Hampshire.
That's not too far from me.
Wow.
You might have to go...
This might be the end of the episode.
You might have to go hunting.
I gotta go find that thing.
Oh guys, I just got...
I just got...
Actually, I just got an email from Shudder.
Zachary Quinto returns for Nosferatu Season 2.
Stream now.
Alright, what I said was actually cool.
Now on Shudder.
I can watch it now or add to my list.
Whoa, I just got an email from Bernie Sanders.
Come on.
I did I I tried to have something cool Trump's where from where there's nothing
going on here for me Donald Trump's I need to have something cool this sucks
this sucks you guys play too much I can play $25 to defeat Donald Trump Caleb
plays too much way too much I do play - I'm sick of you guys playing too much I
just started I just made it I'm living a very regimented life now yeah three days
ago I decided to make myself a weekly schedule because if I'm not in school or
have a job I just do nothing all day. Yeah. So now everything is just like I just
live by a I live by a shinobi code now. It's pretty cool. I could honestly
unless my schedule is I wake up and I go to the gym I come back I make breakfast
if we podcast I podcast if not I read and then I go for a run and then I have an
two hours of video games built into my schedule.
(laughing)
- I wish I, honestly I could not,
I could never live by a schedule.
- Yeah, you're too wild.
- Unless I go back on Adderall or something, I could never.
- I've been thinking about,
if anybody in New York sells Adderall.
- Hey, I'll send you some.
- Don't talk to me 'cause I hate drugs.
- Yeah, I don't know, I think I'm gonna get my,
I think I'm gonna get my prescription refilled.
I think I might do that.
I think that's the move for me.
- I'd rather not.
- Get my Addy prescription refilled.
- Get your Addy prescripts, reef, reef, reef.
- I think I'm gonna go to the dentist.
I'm gonna get that shit sorted out.
- That's where you get Adderall.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause you won't sit still in the chair.
- No.
- Yeah.
- I need the prescription.
- Honestly, I honestly have this like,
reoccurring thought that I'm gonna get back on Adderall
and then just immediately the podcast tanks.
(laughing)
because i'm too normal is interrupting every no not even interrupting anything
just kind of just sitting here like
yet yeah i i i i feel like that's not what i don't know if you do
no at no i i mean it because it gives you energy
the the only person who really knew me
when i was on at a row with ben
and i a
he he said i could turned into a completely different person when i stop
taking it
so i'm not cool
I guess, I don't know.
- The Adderall turned me to a monster.
- My first semester at Emerson, I was a very quiet person.
- Yeah. - If you can believe it.
- I can believe that. - I can believe it.
- I feel like you're pretty quiet with new people, right?
- That's true, yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah, before he lets his guard down, you know,
he's like, it's one of those guys where he's like,
where they're like, "Wow, you're pretty quiet."
And he's like, "That's 'cause I don't wanna talk to you."
- Whoa. - Yeah.
- He's like, "Yeah." - Yeah, that's 'cause I'm a freak.
- You should see me with my-- - The things I would say
would scare you. - Yeah.
you just think i'm i'm i need to use it with my friends well
i'm irony poison from online because i use my phone too much all my god is my
phone you might try use my phone and i say f dot s as a as a step shit online
yes somebody in pat's classes like a you you're pretty quiet you don't talk much
and he goes
yeah i don't have anything to say to you
uh... home yeah i don't have anything to say to you
you nor me free
yeah
and you're you're really there is nothing i don't know there's nothing i could say
that you would understand
they haven't understand that i'll try to be broke up a little bit about the
not going to go ahead and even
get that you fucking idiot
use stupid use stupid people alone like that you sign with the other day you know
i hate i hate walking into the room in being the smartest guy every time yeah i
don't bother talking to the site nobody will understand i'm saying i would let's
it like
i love podcasts
yeah nobody gets it. I listen to a messed up podcast and that makes me different from you.
How does that feel? The only movies I like are about time travel. I bet you can't relate.
I bet you can't wrap your tiny mind around that one British one, Primer. You don't know
anything about Primer, okay? Is that movie British? I don't even think it's British.
If you tried to watch Primer, you would even come close to understanding me. Your brain
- You're just explaining me.
- You probably, yeah.
- Even if you did understand it,
you wouldn't even come close.
- I'm sorry, you probably prefer Captain Marvel.
Me, I'm more of a Deadpool kind of guy.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- It's the kind of thing you wouldn't understand.
When Deadpool looks at the camera,
you probably think he can see you for real
and you get scared.
- Yeah, 'cause you're so much dumber than me.
- How a Deadpooly chimichanga through a mask?
(laughing)
It don't make sense.
- It doesn't though.
does he do does not take your mask off if you're gonna eat dead me chongas your
problem I walk into a classroom and I'm like what is this a place of learning or
a house of hogs I walk into a classroom and I died for every escape route that's
right I walk into classroom all I see is targets that's the second I think the
guy that that we're making fun of and then the guy like the second person who's
like oh no we're not making fun of me yeah we're making fun of an idea how this
started no no no okay who's the second guy the second guy is the guy who's like
yeah I look for every escape route as soon as I enter a school yeah guys the
college guy in you can do that in movie theater I get there I do that yeah movie
theaters yeah but like making a point to like say that in I mean I would never
tell anybody it's so embarrassing I'm just like such a baby that like right
It's like being afraid of like being struck by saying that saying that as like a cool guy thing is fucking annoying every time
I walk into a classroom. I make sure I have a vibranium shield in my backpack
Yeah, yeah, every time I walk into a classroom
I make sure to shit my pants and also pee my pants so that yes, so that people disperse around me
Yeah, there's like there's like a circle of students around if you were a mass shooter and a guy shit his pants right next to
Do you still do the shooting or are you like this is a sign?
Yes, today is ruined from the devil or whatever that I think it was gonna smell like poop
Yeah, how am I supposed to aim with all this poop in my nose?
You know, yeah, well, I mean it's like it's like proposing marriage you wouldn't propose to someone if someone
Yeah, a school shooting is just like a proposal. Yeah, I mean it's your proposing to
Everybody yeah
It's an indecent proposal if you uh yeah, what is that movie about it's about a guy
Oh the one where he's like oh, can I fuck your wife for like a million dollars?
Yeah, so if me so fuck you you wife punani one million dollars
That's a movie about charge our pigs offering to fuck your wife
- Fuck your wife.
(laughing)
- And you're like, fuck.
- Oh, moi moi, me fuck your wife.
- That is kind of, yeah, the thing is,
if it's Jar Jar Binks, that's like--
- I would do it, just for the fucking,
I wouldn't even care.
- For the story, yeah, hey babe.
- Hey, she fucked Jar Jar Binks.
- I just got home from work, my boss,
you remember him, Jar Jar Binks?
(laughing)
Yeah, the dog monster, he wants to fuck you
for a million dollars, I said yes,
and if we go back now, it's gonna be embarrassing.
It's gonna be a tough Monday.
I won't have anything to talk about in the fucking links, alright?
You have to get a go and you fuck his gungan ass.
I need to see, I need you to take a picture of his penis for me.
I have some deviant art I need to prove wrong.
Yeah, I need you to wear this GoPro when you fuck Jar Jar Binks, honey.
Please.
Please, for me.
For me, please.
It's called gathering intel.
Okay.
I need you to do this.
Yeah.
He probably has a, can you imagine?
- He probably got a long dick.
- Probably got some, do you think,
can you imagine how much foreskin is on his penis, dude?
- Oh, dude.
- Like how much foreskin does he have on his body?
- It's all foreskin.
- It's completely foreskin.
- His ears are foreskin, too.
His whole body.
- He's just, yeah, he's a foreskin monster.
- Yeah.
Okay, hold up, hold up, who would you rather fuck?
Hold up, who would you rather fuck,
Jar Jar Binks or Big Boss Nass?
I don't know who that is but that sounds like the green guy who's his boss.
Sounds like a Queen Latifah character.
Oh wow, Big Boss Nas.
This guy's awesome.
You would fuck Big Boss Nas?
No, I'm just looking at him.
I haven't answered yet.
He could, yeah, he would.
Let me get a, let me look up a side by side really quick.
He would motorboat your butt.
He does like a, he goes, there's a big scene where he goes.
I bet, okay, the question is, who would I fuck?
not like get a little top it from no no you have to spend like like do it am I
decent proposal style like it's like penthouse loft there's like candles am I
fucking lazy fucking me there's a path of rose petals to his gungan bed I'm
fucking him you're fucking them yeah did these creatures have vaginas that do they
have human look I don't know I don't know which one of them has a huge
I thought NASA's a gun gun. Yeah, he is dude. Look at he's a gun. He doesn't like look like the other like
Please if they had like all the gun guns and then okay. Well, where's the fucking ears?
It says he's a male and Kura gun gun. Okay, so there's different like types of gun gun. That makes sense
You're so stupid. You don't know anything. You're such an idiot
Dude I bet Jar Jar Binks gives some fucking I bet that throat gets sloppy drop, dude. Yeah
- Jar Jar Binks gives sloppy top.
- I mean, also remember how long his tongue is?
- Yeah, he go, he could put--
- Look, there's a picture of him with his mouth open.
- He puts his tongue in your butt,
it's going out your mouth.
- The thing is, I would be really worried about teeth.
- Yeah, no, both Boss Nass and Jar Jar Binks
both have teeth that I wouldn't want.
- Jar Jar Binks has huge teeth.
- Yeah.
- What?
Let me look this up.
- Fucking idiot.
- Oh, wait, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Giant, nasty British teeth.
- Yeah.
You know how I've looked up Jar Jar Binks rule 34 too many times that it...
He's also kind of, yeah he is kind of ripped now that I look at this.
Yeah.
He is kind of sexy.
He has an amazingly human body.
Yeah.
He kind of, he just looks like Steven Tyler.
LOTR fan.
There's a baby Jar Jar Binks here.
That's the one that Patrick wants to fuck.
Nope.
Patrick said I would fuck that.
I said I wouldn't.
You had to fuck any alien from any movie.
So any of them.
who
It needs to be like a true alien.
Well no, she is shapeshifting.
From Star Wars or just any...
No, not shapeshifting, because then you'd be like shapeshifting to Ruth Bader Ginsburg.
Magneto.
Shapeshift into Magneto.
Ruth Bader Ginsburg.
Yeah, the ultimate respect.
You're just moving the goalpost because you're mad I found the right answer.
I'm not that mad, okay?
No, he's pretty mad.
Okay, then I fuck her, then I fuck the aliens from Dude Where's My Car, the sexy Asian one.
Caleb would fuck the aliens from Toy Story.
- Mm, yeah.
(laughing)
- I would.
- All three of them at once.
- Yeah, dude.
That'd be sick.
That'd be so in sync.
- Yeah.
- Twins.
- They'd go, "Wow."
(laughing)
- Wow.
- Yeah.
- That's small penis.
(laughing)
- No.
The balls.
- They would say the claw.
They would say the claw.
- The balls.
- They would say the claw because you have a mandible.
- No, they would say the balls because I have two.
My balls have been so swollen recently.
- Why?
- I don't know, it's been like--
- You're pregnant, dude.
- I might be pregnant.
My balls have just been like, unhideable.
- Yeah.
- No matter what pants I have, people,
like if I, so if I like walked into a wall--
- No matter what pants you have,
people say, "Yo man, nice balls."
- Well, I look at 'em in the mirror.
If I walk into a wall, my balls hit first.
Do you understand how big that is?
- Okay. - Yeah.
- So they're bigger than your penis.
- You've got like a boob out between your legs.
- I don't like the name of this file
just sent us. It's that because I found it. Will you read the name of the file so the listeners
know what you just sent us? Jar Jar. So I found a website called the bok choy which is supposed
to be like a, it's like the onion but it's specifically for, it's supposed to be specifically
for Asian people I guess and it's from an article that says Chinese community to boycott
star wars episode seven
over races jar jar
c_e_o_ banks
character c_-eight c_-eight c_-eight c_-eight minus a bit b
what is i can't do that math can you just say i don't know what i'm not going to
say hit i'm just confused i don't know what you know the young turks we know
you know the answer
okay yeah that guy's name your blank
i think you guys got it
or no blank no i'm sorry
that would be a crazy name
yeah
blank
uygar
yeah how do you say his name
we
chank uygar
chank uygar yeah
okay
i would know i'm a huge fan of the young you are you are a huge fan of the young
- Yeah, you like how young they are.
- Did you watch the Young Turks on YouTube in 2008, Caleb?
I feel like you were there.
- Oh yeah, absolutely.
- I watched it because they would like comment,
I would try to find like Two Girls One Cup on YouTube
because I thought that's where that was.
And then--
- On the Young Turks?
- Yeah, I thought Two Girls One Cup was on the Young Turks.
- You thought it was Anna Kasparian?
- And Cenk Uygur, I thought they were doing the cup.
I thought he was the cup.
But they would like comment on videos
have videos with that in the title so that they would get like clicks and shit
like a fucking clickbait. I mean they still suck but they used to be
awful. I would watch their videos and be like okay where where when when does the
poop stuff happen? That was back when like like the whole thing that was like
the Young Turks was like almost pro Ron Paul. Oh yeah. All those videos that were
like Ron Paul's the only one only one talking about the war and I was like
did Ron Paul swag yeah I remember when reddit was obsessed with Ron Paul
libertarian blocks Ron Paul was my that was my guy and then those newsletters
came out and I was like I think my parents voted for him in 2012 I convinced
my mom to vote for Gary Johnson in 2012 really nice yeah Wow and then actually
- Actually, that makes sense that you were a libertarian guy.
- And then she, well, 'cause it was like my,
you know, I grew up in like a super conservative family,
so that was like, that was like me rebelling
as much as I could.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- It was like, I think gay people should be able
to get married, and drugs should be legal.
- I did the same thing, but I was more socialist.
- Yeah.
- No, I was younger.
- I should be able to kill my uncle
if he engages in aggression against me.
- That's right.
- Stand your ground law against your uncle.
- Yeah.
- That's right.
(laughs)
- Yeah.
- Uncles should be fair game.
- Yeah, if your uncle says something demeaning
about your job at Thanksgiving,
you should be able to tackle him.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- If your uncle calls you a homo,
you should be able to slap his balls off.
- Now that we do this full time.
- If your uncle calls you a homo,
you should be able to say,
"I'll show you a homo," and then get up on him.
- You should say, "I'll show you a home owner,"
and then you point to yourself and you brag.
- I own a house now.
- I own a house.
- Yeah, I just bought a house in Myrtle Beach, South Carolina.
Gary Johnson's most popular policies is that any
anybody whose uncle calls them a homo gets a free house so they can use that
comeback. Exactly.
I would say the funniest video ever is the
thing where he says he's being pro
driver's license. That guy, the one that's like
what's next? Putting a license to put toast in your
damn toaster. That guy lives in Manchester.
i've seen some of the bumper stickers for around there's like there's a little
bit data carvey character yeah only people make fun of you for being read
fucking look at that uh... did and i thought it is so i do it we just go back
a minute
yeah nobody makes money for being read it says i don't know how to read it all
in a cross your face right now
there's not been that's called a camera trick
the
i found that guys face book is in the barrel perry i found his face book yet
that's a good name. Yeah, his name is Jar Jar Binks. He does look like Jar Jar Binks.
He really does. I found his Facebook and I forget what it was. He hit his head on his
bathroom door. I gotta find it. Hold on. No, he hit his head on something really funny.
It wasn't his bathroom door. I think I sent it to Seamus. Let me look. Oh yeah, it was
a big penis. Yeah he got hit in the head by a big penis. He hit his head on a clown nose.
Yeah. Uh huh. And it honked. And it honked and killed him. Oh he stepped on his broom
and the handle hit himself in the forehead. That's what it was. That's way funnier. That's
insane dude. Yeah he sideshow bobbed and then posted a picture of the cut. It's like a freckle.
It's like a freckle.
It's like a sniper dot on his fucking forehead.
It just looks like, exactly.
Yeah, it's not even that big.
No, a sniper dot's too generous.
Yeah, it looked, if I saw that on someone, I would think it was a freckle.
Right.
You don't know anything about sniper dots, dude.
Nah, I do.
No, you don't.
You've never heard of a sniper.
I was in Vietnam.
Yeah, because you're Vietnamese.
Yeah, lots of people are in Vietnam right now, Patrick.
Yeah, this is my friend. He's he was in Vietnam.
He was on vacation.
Going to Vietnam on vacation like last year and being like, yeah, I was in Vietnam.
I remember now.
like smiling and daydreaming and be like man I'm having nom flashbacks right now.
Having nom flashbacks to Sandals Resort. Oh my god it was amazing.
Oh my god I had the most look I had the most amazing banh mi there. I don't know what it
is but it's just better than how they make them in the United States.
Having a nom flashback to a banh mi. Banh mi is Vietnamese right?
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I would know that.
- I think I'm getting sick right now.
- I would know that 'cause I'm so cultured.
- You're so cultured, dude.
I was on the Patrick Travel Show.
Just you going to different,
seeing just what every country's McDonald's is like.
- I mean, we just have to make idiot abroad, dude.
If we make enough money, that's the end goal.
- But it wouldn't be idiot abroad, Pat.
It'd be smart and easy.
- A genius abroad.
(laughing)
We just call it a genius abroad?
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Yeah, we just send you to like,
but we send you to like--
- I just go to the 7-Eleven in Japan, like the big one.
- No, we send you to like Aleppo.
(laughing)
- Why isn't there a Burger King here?
- Yeah, we just give you like skate pads,
we give you like knee pads and elbows and an helmet,
send you to Aleppo, see how long it takes to get shot.
- You could just send me to, there is a program,
there was like a group of people,
i think it's still thing in palestine they have like they teach like uh...
that's a lot of ron
not a program
what hey uh...
a_t_a_o_ is pretty good at it
uh... there is a there's a thing called skater stan
let me look up what it is there's no way program called skaters stand
there is a program called so it's like that that's like a skate brand i would
come up with a bit of a sounds like a it sounds like a level in one year yet it
- It's a non-profit that empowers children
through skateboarding and education
in Afghanistan, Cambodia, and South Africa.
- We should start Skate Korea.
- North Korea has a skate team.
There's videos of it. - Yeah, it's us.
- I gotta, yeah, it's us now.
I gotta find it, but there is like a skate park
in Pyongyang, I think.
- Yeah. - Nice.
We should just go to,
can you still do the thing where you go tour North Korea?
And they just show you like a--
- No.
they show you like a cool hotel yeah that's like unfinished that means that
be so cool to do that would be sick dude I would love to do that you can't I don't
think I'm taking a prank on the tour guide and just getting killed hey making
a joke and getting a chin look at that banana on the ground
an appeal you should check that out did just doing got your nose to it just
seeing just seeing a child walk by in the street and doing got your nose and
just getting killed immediately, just getting knocked down.
- In our country, the United States,
it's actually very impolite if there's a banana peel
to not step on it, so if you wouldn't mind.
Otherwise, I'm gonna go back and I'm gonna tell America
that you guys killed me.
- I'm gonna tell them posthumously that you killed me.
- Yeah, they killed me while I was over there, so.
- Yeah, I think you guys need to drop the nuke.
- Yeah, they just killed me when I was in North Korea,
so you guys don't wanna drop the nuke.
crap you guys, you guys they killed me. I'm serious. I'm serious they freaking killed
me. And here we are with Patrick Doran recently got back from North Korea. He says that he
has a bombshell of a story to share with us. Patrick, tell us what happened? Yes I'm over
there I'm fucking, I'm going where's the McDonald's, where's the McDonald's, why, what is this
food you know I want a hamburger I want a hot dog and then they killed me and I'm
like I'm like hey let me get this straight you're saying that they killed
you ah yeah I'm fucking dead over here I'm like hey why the hell why are you doing this and then they
heard it here first I'm Chanku Gar with the Young Turks yeah I was sitting there I was sitting there and then
Phil Bainette in my back and then the shot goes off. And the title of the video is two girls one cup
real extended cut. Yeah. Dude I love, it's funny that Young Turks is like we're news and
then it's like a Obama selfie? Cenk Uyghur just talking he's like Ruth
Bader Ginsburg's a fucking cunt she's a stupid cunt she should be in jail
fuck you Ron Paul rocks. More like the Young Jerks. Yeah. Yeah. And you guys laugh
- Can we laugh at that one, please?
(laughing)
- We're coming after you, young Turks.
We're coming after you.
- They named their whole thing after Rod Stewart.
Yeah, whoa, there we go.
The dung turds.
- We're splitting the left, dude.
- You guys named yourself after a goddamn Rod Stewart song.
(laughing)
And Anna Craps Turdstian.
- Anna Craps Terranum.
- Craps Terranum.
- Craps very much.
on toilet let's fucking go and Jimmy crap who's that mr. poop yeah yeah you guys
got mr. yeah and that's a little monster you guys got mr. hanky doing stuff for
you yeah Alex fart let's go and count Chuck you
chank which tank wigger and count Chocula are the are coming for you dude we're
taking you downtown what if they what if they what if they send what if he sends
his big nephew to fight us I don't care did as an uncle as an uncle myself I'll
take you down son. I'm scared my nephews are too young to go up against I can't have a
nephew battle that's like I have a level 3 nephew he's got like a level 27 nephew
and he buffed his stats. He's like a super nephew. Yeah he buffed his fucking nephew.
Yeah he slipped potions into his nephew's formula. Dude he's been giving his nephew
rare candies. He made his nephew evil to defeat Chuck Schumer. Yeah. Yeah he's a nephew level
X yeah they're a pedophile who's trying to lure kids into his van with candy but
he accidentally uses rare candies and just gets beaten up by the kids. They just get evolved into
humans. They evolved into an adult because they gave them rare candies. They just went to town on the rare candies I had in my
inventory. We're taking down the Young Turks we're taking down the other the
other stuff too. We're taking down the material report. Sean White. We're taking
down... Stop taking you down, Sean White. We're taking down MSNBC. MSNBC. We're taking down
Boss Nass. MSNBC, what's that stand for? My shit. Hold on. Hold on. What letter are you stuck on?
my shit no bitch crap that's right that's no bitch crap that's no fucking over
x-rays you know fucking old xenophobes there oh that's a good like 2004
that's some good 2004 Bush era shit what no you think faux news is better yeah
- Yeah, oh Fox?
- I'm more clever.
- Yeah, what Fox?
Firefox, where you look up Wikipedia for all your articles
'cause you have no real sources?
- Mm-hmm.
- Fox, how about Falco News?
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- That's what I'm talking about.
- See, that's good, Pat.
- I'm gonna start a network-- - Pay attention.
- Network called Wolf News.
- Yeah.
I'm a genius.
- It's gonna be Evil Fox News.
- What's the other one?
CNN, what's the other one they're saying it for?
Crap New--
- No, no, no, no.
- Crap-- - Crap--
- No, no, no, no. - No, no, no, no.
That's what it stands for.
Owned.
What's the other?
CNBC?
CNBC, crap.
No.
No bull crap.
Bull crap.
ABC stands for...
Crap, no bull crap.
All bull crap.
Awful butt crap.
Awful butt crack.
Yeah.
CBS.
Crap, bring it in.
Seriously.
That's just how it is, dude.
What's the other?
PBS?
Yeah.
PBS.
the comments.
[BLANK_AUDIO]