come back and make a bet
and receive a bite
news huge fucking you know we've been backlogging stuff we finally have what
this one is it was this one really is on we're recording and releasing it
emergency park emergency and we had to get everything yeah this is a
i'd heard this this morning from art associate pierce who's with us today
We want to break the news to everybody back. Yeah. Well everyone already knows I'm sure
But yeah scrap finally ate his little nut
Scrappy his own nuts crack out his acorn slash nut thing. Mm-hmm. He ate it actually
Yeah, he got he gets it every time. Yeah, never actually puts it in his mouth and choose
He usually has your desk thinking that means something else. What did you yeah, I don't even want to say
Nasty.
Low, like he eats it out.
No.
Did you think I was like, what do you mean he eats it out?
He puts it up his butt?
Oh, he got his butt.
That's what he was saying.
Imagine how many, imagine how many nasty ass things he's got on his butt.
He's grabbed his own butt.
Wait, his acorn or you probably thought he's got a gape horn.
Yep.
He's probably way weirder.
He's grabbed his butt in gape horn.
No.
I watched the video.
Me too.
A couple times.
Everybody's watched the video.
seen it but like why does he not eat the top of the nut you don't eat that yeah
that's like the plate if you're hungry that's like eating an oyster shell but if
you're scrat you eat the oyster shell no scrat's like scrat doesn't eat oysters at
all that's why he's mentally disabled he's a mentally could have mentally
disabled squirrel rat marry another squirrel with the same name as him but
with an e at the end gratte it's a really I don't think so could could have
mentally challenged squirrel rat discover scratlantis he didn't really or
could he or could he or could he pilot a UFO and launch deadly meteors at the
earth mm-hmm probably no yeah that's a good really you probably think he's
mentally a wife's his big eyes that twitch sometimes and his yes is weird
yeah we you're all yeah so we are also he can't I mean he's been look even
trying to get a nut for like we said millions of years I'd feel like it's not
Yeah, he's not very good at falling through. Well. Yeah, I was I've been reading a bunch about scrat this morning
Did you know that he there's a big controversy apparently that this woman said that Fox stole the idea for scrat from her yeah
She had this idea first. Yeah, I grow with me. It was
socialite at every party she would
- of him she
character I made she claimed that she created scrat but he was called scrat
because he was a squirrel rat and it was originally she spelled it sqr a t and
then in when I had the idea for a squirrel at a rat first yeah I had the
idea for a sponge bob before they they made yeah yeah well I had spongebob I
didn't have the square pants thing yeah that's fair there was you were what you
are gotta stop there is a sponge bob there is a sponge bob I made but it was
it was just because he was in my sink. I'm not giving you anything. I'm giving you
nothing. I already said the square pits thing and you six year old ADHD in the
middle of it, so you're getting nothing. A guy sneezed really loud outside. And you
stopped. Yeah, you whipped your head around like someone had a gun to your
head. Do you put on a white noise machine at night and just like keep waking up?
up every time there was another green and white. No, what is that? No,
there's rain drops coming from my phone. What is that? There's already enough
white noise in my apartment. Oh, that's right. That's right. That's right. You
guys know that in the DVD commentary, they refer to scrat as the scrat.
Really? Yeah. Yeah. That, does that, well, that's kinda, does that insinuate
that he's the only scrat? Well, it's not though, 'cause there's tons of his
species on scratlantis. I think that they had to change it from the scrat
after they made another scratch. It's probably yeah, probably it could be
it like a Ukraine type thing. Hmm. Or maybe scrap was like you're not
supposed to say you're not supposed to say the scrat. You're not.
You're not supposed to call Ukraine the scrat. No, it's like calling him
the dog. Like his name isn't like his species is scrat. Yeah, is that
your will? Well, you would but then the girl was called scrat a yeah.
I mean later on they figured out that they couldn't name anything but
scrat. They don't need to be funny. Say give him a name. I've got a
Sid the sloth.
Yeah, but no, but like Scrat and Scratay don't say, "I am Scrat, I'm Scratay."
No, they say, "Nyeh-nyeh-nyeh-nyeh."
Yeah, so like I-
Well, the Scratlantis Scrats speak.
Yeah.
So let me see. Can you pull that up?
Okay, yeah.
The Scratlantis Scrats do speak.
I want to see if any of them say that their name is Scrat.
The Scratlantis Scrats are really gonna-
Well, they say, "Welcome to Scratlantis."
They're gonna make the Super Bowl this year.
So he must be a Scrat if they name him.
So he is mentally challenged. He can't speak.
well there at the scrap lantis people are of higher intelligence and most scrap
and it's also i also scrap well i also think that that maybe uh...
you know maybe most sometimes the most intelligent individuals don't need to
speak and i don't want to make a word he's post language exactly uh... is
fully is a senate he has one desire and i was not
the acorn flash not thing
whatever the hell that is the uh...
it looks to me like an acorn yeah but it could be a prehistoric they should have
come up with some awesome scrat like perfect hypostatic union between a nut
and an acorn they actually stole the idea for the acorn from me yeah I had an idea
for a bug that wants an M&M so I think I thought of an ET way long before that
yeah an ET that wants a Reese's piece that's true ET is a scrat or a scrat is
at ET. Scrap flies a UFO. Yeah ET has other interests dressing up like a damn
girl. Scrap hiding in the closet. Drinking cola out the fridge. Uh-huh.
I haven't seen ET in a while. He drinks beer and turns white. He goes nuts. He turns white later.
He turns white not because he drank a beer but because he was in the woods.
He turns white every time he falls down. He falls down in the woods and then turns white.
known about this strange alien species except that they turn white every time
they fall down in the woods. It's so funny to gather like the rules of ET species
based off of his movie like yeah all the people from his planet love drinking
soda and dressing up like girls. And then we watched yesterday the like the ride.
Yeah we go back to the green planet. The fucking planet he just called it the
green planet. Yeah. ET needs your help going back to the green planet. Well Earth is the blue
planet right? Yeah. And Mars is the red planet. And Venus is also sort of...
Is it orange? I feel like I think it's orange. I want to think of Venus as
green because it's like... Greenness. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But I don't think it is.
Well ET's teacher Botanicus. Botanicus. Needs your help. And Botanicus can really...
he's really good at speaking. Yeah. So ET is a Scrat. Hello, welcome to the green. Scrat and ET are the same.
The green planet is Scratlantis.
Oh yeah. It's all a metaphor. There's a lot of parallels.
Well there's also a mushroom that says "Welcome Home."
Where's that fall into the Scrat thing? That's an Alice in Wonderland.
I thought E.T.'s whole thing was that he was like the most retarded guy from his planet but then
you go to his planet and everyone's like
"Doo-wee-wee-boo-boo."
I think we're I can't tell what I know of ET and what I just know from the robot
chicken thing yeah yeah I think he's that well he is I think all of his his
mental like abilities go to his brain I think all everything goes to his healing
finger oh yeah okay you can't see yeah there's so much energy being used to
his rat kind of has that but with his like scratch as I think I think that I
guess that's great like on that nut scratch a co scrat has his acorn and et
acorn would be the boy he's a sport is a boy by that logic was a nice touching
the boy's finger right also et wants to go to his planet so he wants a planet
could be is a corn yeah or a phone home is his not a phone is trapped on earth
and he has to find a phone I guess seeing ET and be like oh yeah no I get it the
the phone was his nut.
(laughter)
Like scrap.
Watching Frankenstein like, oh that girl was his nut?
Where's E.T. the girl E.T.?
True.
That would be E.T.E.
That's because they would...
E.T.
It would be E.T.T.
Extraterrestrial
with tits and ass.
Extra terrestrial with
with tits and ass yeah.
So does, now I'm thinking, now that we're going with a girl whose name is made of letters,
I'm thinking about Wally and Eva or Eve.
Yeah.
And then maybe that that's also maybe the center, the missing link between E.T. and
Scrat.
Wally's nut was fat people.
No Wally's nut was trash.
Trash, it was trash box.
I never saw that movie.
Yeah.
Wally's nut wasn't trash, it was making a box out of trash.
- Scrat is really like the genesis of a lot of different--
- It's like a stock character, you know,
it's an archetype that you can find in whatever.
- Yeah, like the gay villain, or the gay hero,
or the gay dragon.
- I mean, technically, Scrat's nut is a prospector's coin.
(laughing)
So let's keep going back then.
- Well, the prospector, I don't think,
I think it's more interesting gold than coins.
looking for gold. I think everybody wants. I think that's like a human
coin. I think the prospectors gold nugget nugget was a nut is a hue is
the nut and then if you go further prospect humans, no actually because
now I'm thinking about it or perhaps evaluate that because while the cave
man's turkey leg as imagine extra extra the prospector got his. Oh my God
while he's in a proper send off to the gold rush
their own term. He finally got his nugget. Wait, I don't get it. Why does he eat the nugget?
It's like scrat. It's his nut. Yeah. Does he think he bites into the nugget to see if
it's real? No, he does that with the coins to see if they're real. He could do it with
a nugget too. Even a fool's gold would break a man's tooth.
Well, so here's what I'm thinking. I feel like, okay, here, I would like to introduce
a coin. That's eating it. He puts the nugget in his wallet and then it turns into a coin
I want to introduce a new dimension of this which is the prospector he wants a
nugget and he wants a coin this is his dual acorns and if we look at Scrat
Scrat wants his acorn but he also wants Scratay yeah and a family exactly
doesn't he have a son so well that's baby Scrat who he adopted baby Scrat
specter Atlantis that's prosperous Francisco yeah that's El Dorado yeah
Rondo okay so yeah maybe the hollow earth is it the rod
gold the city of gold has no people in robes and our legs pious it's just a
bunch of hairy guys dancing and chewing tobacco.
Everybody's got a golden jug.
They all got a golden jug.
And that makes sense because then the prospector sees El Dorado, the city of gold.
He goes gold crazy like Scrat goes nut crazy when he sees the big nut in Scratlantis.
In Scratlantis, if you guys aren't aware, Scrat sees a big nut.
The Scratlantis guy says, "Don't submit to these base instincts, Scrat.
Be more than a squirrel." And then Scrat goes, "Be more than a Scrat."
And then he, well he says, "Be more than a squirrel." Now I think about it, doesn't he?
Well, he says don't be more than a rodent rodent. That's what he says and
then and then scrap holes would be way too confusing. Yeah, and then he will
yeah be more than squirrel. He's more. She's a squirrel rat. He's already more
than the squirrel. He pulls the nut out of out of the nut holder and it's a
drain and it's a drain that sinks. Gratilantis the prospector goes to El
Prospero and he sees the and he sees the gold. He starts mining it and he
destroys it because he goes crazy and they say right. They say rise up
brother become more than a prospector mm-hmm he's gonna become Jerry yeah yeah
that was his name so who predates the prospector who is the caveman yeah and
what they was also looking for gold coin well caveman I guess was actually was
post-rat though it came in Oh scratch the originator yeah because dinosaurs
didn't want stuff it's like the pre ice age it's like the evolution did want
want volcanoes but not like scrap Eve wanted an apple yeah, but that was
after she was also yeah. I was way before no because that was humans.
That was when humans were created humans came after scrat what's
great was leading alongside each other. No yeah, it's great was already
alive. I think Caleb might be right about this. They lived alongside
each other at the very there's a Neanderthal in the first ice age.
Yeah, but that Neanderthal but so you think Eve was there a baby Eve
is more fully evolved than a Neanderthal though. There's a baby in
one right now if you saw he was a complete was a monkey what they do with
the baby I think the baby gets reunited with his clan at the end yeah so there's
there's there's other he has a nice age right there's one baby in all of ice age
and he also wants a nut yeah there's got to be something that's that bridges the
gap between prospector and and they can't they can't they can't have been no
scrat and just prospector I think there was maybe it was the gist well scrat was
around for a long time that's true we kept getting frozen and
and thought out yeah yeah I mean I think he pretty much carried the torch himself
the entire time yeah I think it was around like just in in all the history
before the Wild West - like he was am I imagining this or in one of the ice ages
wait I can't guess what you're about to say yeah does he cook an acorn over a
fire and it turns into popcorn which begs the question of like what is that
That's what I'm saying, it's a scrat corn.
Scrat coin!
Coin, yeah.
It's a coin!
Acorn is acorn.
Oh my God.
Wait, so yeah, he cooks it and it becomes popcorn.
Are you doing a check on this right now?
I'm doing a check on this.
What were you about to search?
I don't remember that.
I was literally about to search Caleb coin.
Caleb coin!
It comes up.
that's kind of the modern example is Caleb with his coin. Yeah, I always
try to get his coin pretty often. All right, wait, scrap. I was trying to
does he does he like get frozen for like a like millions of years and he
like they have defied in like modern day. There's okay. Now here's what I'm
thinking about. I don't think I've seen. I think I've seen maybe the first
two ice age movies and those were that was a long time ago that I saw those,
but I do remember seeing previews for a movie called Ice Age Dawn of the
dinosaurs and the dawn of the dinosaurs is before the ice age.
Yeah, I sage was post dinosaurs totally so so what's going on
there. I don't know. I think there's like I think maybe they
find a secret island like a Godzilla Island. Oh, yeah. Oh,
yeah, like a world like a leash the dinosaur. Okay, but so also
something that I read about when I was reading so many videos
just called scrap popcorn by the way when I was reading about the
cultural impact of scrat on the Wikipedia page. It does he does
UFO so I think there's a chance that that's right see if the scrat is okay
let's see what's my man this is like a fire the first one so he's cooking a
marshmallow oh he's trying to thaw out the laws out the acorn I see and he's
trying to make sure oh yeah it turns into a popcorn I found a thing here real
life ice age scratch stretches impossibly far for tasty nut okay so
So what year is that from?
This is from 9/11/2018.
That's from maybe...
That photo's from 10 million years ago.
Oh my god, Osama bin Laden!
There's more than one photo here.
Osama bin Laden was a scrat.
That's right.
And his nut was doing a thing to a tower.
He had a nasty, nasty nut.
His nut was a plane.
Well, the towers were like the...
His nut was fear.
No, okay, listen, listen, listen.
Let's be honest.
Get out of view.
the towers were the frozen acorn the plane was the campfire and then the
collapsed towers the popcorn I think that's what I was up you wanted to fly
the plane close enough to the tower that it thawed oh yeah
No, thawing the towers when the plane, it's like when in a movie, the plane flies by a
tower and all the glass windows shatter.
Oh yeah.
You don't want any windows.
Going like a supersonic speed.
Yeah, because windows are like ice.
Because windows, exactly like Rodin in Final Wars, windows look like ice and breaking ice
is thawing it.
Also, the twin towers were frozen in ice.
Yeah.
And he messed up and he popped corn in them.
Only on that day though.
Yeah, they got frozen.
Every other day they were fine.
Yeah.
everybody in the entire building would have gone like oh yeah I wonder if they're
like scratch truthers who are like I'm not wouldn't do that I know wouldn't
become popcorn I think there's no way I'm not wouldn't want to the edge of the
dinosaurs like that it was that yeah that's what I mean is like what the it's
not an acorn wait it's scratt launch the age of the dinosaurs yeah I'm guessing
he's kind of responsible for every bad thing that I know these yeah oh my god
he's gonna start the collision course the collision course is that what it's
called collision that's where it's one movie called collision that's the one
where he flies a UFO and he's yeah meteors at the earth so there's one
called collision course and one called continental drift yeah how are those not
hold up yeah well can we look up a list of I'll look up the list of ice age also
did you say there's a show called scrat tails yeah that's the one that came out
yesterday holy fuck and that's that is what the head the companion piece where
scrat spoiler alert we got it came out yesterday yeah and they immediately shut
down yeah it was their last thing I think okay I sage I sage the meltdown I sage
dawn of the dinosaurs I sage continental drift I sage collision course the ice
age adventures of buck wild buck wild and then I sage scrat tales I don't know
but well rat tails is a and well don't forget the short films gone nutty no time
for nuts surviving Sid, Scrat's Continental Crack-Up, Scrat's Continental Crack-Up Part
2, Cosmic Scrat-tastrophe, Scrat Spaced Out, and The End.
Oh my god.
Oh I think these are the Scrat videos we were talking about.
Yeah, we were talking about the Scrat videos.
Those are the short films that opened Ice Age.
That's another thing that I forgot to mention.
This video, the video of Scrat getting his nut is called, it was uploaded to YouTube under
the name The End by a YouTube channel just called Finale.
Whoa.
I guess they don't have access to the blue sky. Yeah, I guess that's just the video
It's the video of him just walking up eating his nut and then why should put all the finales for everything on that channel?
Yeah, that only makes sense. Yeah, I mean there's no finale quite like this one though. Whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa?
Yeah, don't say that cosmic scratastrophe is a 2015 animated short film directed by Michael Thurmeyer
It was originally released in theaters alongside the Peanuts movie the short once again follows scrat who discovers a front a flying saucer
they're frozen in a block of ice and with a video that isn't a part of ice age.
This is a video that open the hold up and accidentally powers it on and ends
up creating the solar system through a series of mishaps.
Wait, so he so so there's no sun yeah.
He created the solar system, so it is pre eve. Oh my he's God's grad is God
it's got to be oh yeah i was reading someone i was reading theory like
something they say that's right but other people say that the nut is god
that's a good point that
well ok wait i have another huge i have a big development here for the next
scratch video scratch spaced out scratch based out as a short film that compiles
all scratch scenes from ich collision course with a few unique scenes at the
end okay following the events of ice age collision course scrat is heading back
to earth in the saucer an acorn shaped ship appears and pulls the acorn with
scrat holding on to it in the ship three alien squirrels aka scrat zones
finding scrap blasted away from the acorn so he okay so he is like an alien
he's like he's an anunaki he's an alien dude he created the world or no he's a
nephilim he's earthbound he's the one right the one they left behind like a
progenitor yeah yeah scratch zone my god scratch zones
scrat is on oh my god it's a minute sexy dude it's scratch a but she's blue
they send their women oh my god oh geez so the scratch zones are are like an
ancient race of aliens squirrel red alien red oh and they're big like maybe
Yeah, it's like our idea of squirrels and rats kind of came from them. Maybe our cave paintings of Scratz on
Look at how big they are compared to scrap. That's how let me see their size. Oh my god. Their size is immense
They're so huge. So do you think they ever got their nuts?
Scraps on leader hip by mr. Screenshot on TV and
Yeah, you think do you think that maybe
Scraps on sir Scratts who got their nuts. Oh
Oh shit, so he's trying to ascend and maybe he's just maybe he is mentally
challenging. He just it just took him this long. I'll check this out. So I
think if anything,
I don't think so able to resist the temptation for long. How are they
connected to Scratlantis? Because the Scratlantis guys aren't blue. Those are
I guess that's that's what it is. Those are the Nephilim and then the Scrats
on the on and on. What how does Scrat factor into all that then? Because why
is he not in the in Scratlantis? Scrat is just Odysseus. He's just out of
there. He's not a part of this group.
This has to be a deleted scene, right?
That? No, that's in the movie.
That's in the movie?
Oh my god.
This is Scrat.
He's small and he's putting
his leg, his penis in
between Scratazon's
high heels. I like that a lot.
I think that Scrat might be like a
messiah type thing
where he's like, he maybe
he has the he's he's carrying he's he's he needs to bring something about or
something because he even he creates the solar system right yeah he's placed by
the scratch zones to invent popcorn so are we doing another we do a scratch
list is that even possible I think this is a premium episode another scratch is
on here Wow yeah I was also looking up scrap horn before I came and very
important to put the R in there. Yeah, and you're looking at
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
that was good. He's like well, you want something for so long,
you're not
and the picture is of him after having cream pied
rat get cream pie.
And he says, well, you want something for so long, you're
not well.
That's probably what it is.
You know, he's meant to spread the Scratts on kind of DNA
through as many as you want to get any species as possible.
Yeah, yeah, kind of like spread enlightenment or whatever a
genetic memory of being from space from space from space from space. I just I
need I need to like I need like an interview with the with the right. Yeah,
I need a one-on-one with scrap. I need that so badly. Yeah, I really do think
that she I mean wait, what what is scratch? What's her job now? I bet this
woman to me. She's a bus driver now. Wait the woman who created the initially
let me pull it up it said she has to this this be a she's a she was a fashion
designer named Ivy supersonic that's no Ivy she's an alien well that's what I
mean is like the more complicated real name was Ivy Silberstein the more like
fucking insane she has to feel yeah like they stole this and they made it about
God and space yeah yeah truly my shitty idea a rat who's combined with a squirrel
is now the creator of the universe. Listen to this, on February 13th 2002 Ivy
Supersonic filed a lawsuit against Fox claiming that she had created the
character in May 1999 after seeing a squirrel rat hybrid in Skidmore
College's Case Green and intended it to be the next Mickey Mouse. Wow. It is.
It is yeah. How did she, like people who like claimed it. She called her character Scrat and
and pitched it to numerous celebrities and studios from 1999 to 2001. You're
right. It was just like her at parties. Yeah. But listen to this. Although she
was unwilling to accept the $50,000 deal, she was offered by Urban Box Office
Network for a web series, believing the character to be worth seven figures.
Wow. Wait, so somebody actually turned down $50,000. Oh, she's right. They
stole it. Yeah. Yeah. 'Cause no one's gonna be like,
people are gonna know that we stole this this squirrel rat I mean having scrat
having scrat and be like this sticking to your guns and saying it's worth seven
figures she was right she was right yeah but being able to know that yeah I think
getting kind of I think they just brute force scrat and said I don't think
there's anything special about scrat I don't think scrat was supposed to be in
ice age and then they were like we have we have this we need this yeah we stole
We stole this from a woman, we have to use it.
Yeah.
Wait.
I think she definitely grew.
What's Mickey Mouse's nut?
Is it...
Minnie's pussy.
No, come on.
No.
He's kind of a nutless scrat.
He's sort of a nutless scrat.
I guess at first it was a steamboat, but then where did he go from there?
No, he was driving the steamboat.
Yeah, the steamboat was supposed to get to safety.
to safety but he wasn't like so he could kiss me he's not as whistling there we
go voice yeah or big ears crazy gloves it could be something with like it maybe
his nut is just like like Disneyland or like Disney the brain yeah movies oh my
God wait more wizard who's frozen Disney oh my god Walt Disney's the nut oh my
god he has to make pop you're not a ball this may be called frozen mm-hmm and
frozen - right yeah and ice age it doesn't really have to do with this but
but you think about how it's frozen - frozen thing - frozen
- No, we need to turn Walt Disney into popcorn.
- Exactly, his head is the nut, yeah.
- Oh my God.
- Turning him into popcorn will create
the second solar system.
It'll be a reset.
- Yeah, and he needs to go to--
- That will allow the Scratzons to come back in
and fix their flawed creation.
They're the--
- Oh my God, what if his head is just the plug
that sends Disney rocketing to the bottom of the sea, though?
- Yeah. - Damn.
- What if he picks up the head and it's just--
- Oh my God, the Scratlanteans are like the Demiurge
and then the Scradzons are like the Sophia, the creator.
It's Gnosticism.
- Scrad is trying to warn us, dude.
It's really scary.
- It's terrifying.
- And also Scrooge McDuck owns coins.
- He's a guy with a million nuts.
- He's like the prospector.
- He's like the guy who shows you
when you have all the nuts that you want, it doesn't.
- Yeah, and you're still unhappy.
- You're gonna have all the nuts you want,
you still got three bad nephews you gotta take care of.
- And they're going on tails together.
And their dad? Coveting coins and money and it would be awesome like yeah
because millionaires aren't happy with all that money but if money was edible
they probably could get over that feeling of empty like oh I've amassed
all this wealth what am I supposed to you just eat it you eat all the money.
I mean you can still eat a coin but it doesn't make it like a coin is like the
last money. You can eat a dollar. You can put a dollar in a dehydrator and eat it like jerky.
It's just too much money to eat, I guess.
Yeah.
If the money was tinier and it tasted better, I guess then that would be a difference.
They'd get a chocolate coin.
Food used to be money, I guess.
Yeah.
I don't care about food anymore.
Yeah, now you just make food in a lab.
Or your house.
In money.
Yeah.
My house is a lab. I'm a scientist.
Yep.
I call my kitchen my lab.
I call my house my lab. I already said that, so.
You can't call your kitchen your lab, because my whole house is a lab.
The kitchen's the lab.
No.
That's where you make up the food.
I'm the guy with the lab house.
I call my penis my lab.
You know my black lab
No
Like a dog like the dog right, but why did you why did you he said penis and you said black lab?
What what was I gonna chocolate lab no, but just why are you just are you just doing like word?
Association with lab and now you're saying he has a black penis
Interesting
think he might is it darker than your face no you know if it's darker than your
face it means you have cancer
I miss tricking people like that yeah I feel like it you can't get away with
that anymore no yeah probably go to jail it is it's all not hey not to bring this
back to scrap but please Tom and Jerry are kind of like each other's nut that's
true they're kind of a dual system well no Jerry doesn't want Tom Jerry would
no no Jerry wants to trick Jerry loves fucking with Tom that's revenge
really is not a nice he's not and he looks like a little bit
he is the night but he had not he's like if the night jerry can never get to imagine
if the not have a very full of their always rolling all that happens in time
to return to a very calm jerry
tom pretty much gets pretty close though i don't know that i had is not and i
think that's actually
yet i think i'm ready and i didn't want it to the not cycle you can't get it is
technically jerry's always eating his night
which is fucking with tom will his notice cheese
well he's like he's like a okay he's like this kind of like a nut order
it's like everybody has a notion
yes no for another day
that's the only other it's the best thing dot dot like
spike
did to tom is his not but but
no no but i don't know is not know the mom's not is the dog and jerry
but jerry serious smile.
I meant to jerry teams up with spike to what to get Tom. Sometimes your nut can
become your friend.
That's fine. No, no, no, no, because jerry is not spikes. Not Tom is spikes.
Not you already. You said it. You said it right there. Jerry's not the dog is
Jerry's scratay and that's a jerry is jerry's jerry's nut is the cheese. Okay,
that's this huge that it brings up and his scrat a is fucking with Tom and
teaming up with spike
two things and all he's not a scratch a well we're gonna grab a be like is his
scratch it can't be someone's not wouldn't scratch no it's not a great
taste not a study has a every scrat has a nut and a scratch a right but you just
said scratch a is his nut no I did well if I did I didn't mean to that's not
what I'm trying to say. Okay, but you messed up big time. We're not
even saying shit like scratay. Run it back. He said scratay is his nut.
I think you did say scratay is his nut, which just makes no sense.
Okay, then let me start. His scrat has a scratay. His cheese is his
nut and his scratay is fucking with Tom. Yes, but you also said his
cheese is fucking... Wait, hold on. Scratay is his nut. Scratay's not
nuts stop saying that that's not possible wait sorry he's not is cheese
teaming up with Rex and fucking with Tom yeah
You're inventing new characters
Rex is my Tom and Jerry
I made up Rex Rex Rex is an alien. He comes into Tom and Jerry's house
He comes in at Tom and Jerry's house, and yeah, he has his own nut. It's a real nut
He's looking for almonds in the kitchen
And the aliens from science me Jerry was there water was there Jerry
Water with yeah
No Gibson was Tom water was like an anti nut but in Battle, Los Angeles water was
So water is and to it in water is that either your night? It's your Jerry sometimes your scratch a
scratch Jerry ice
No, no, no, he's he's Jerry. No, Tom is his ice is his time
Because he's running around from but sometimes he gets the better of the way, but no, but Jerry Jerry always gets the better of Tom
Yeah, what do you know? It's better the ice
One time and that was that's the end of this Tom's never gonna get Jerry
goodbye time right scratch has no time that's timeless scratch timeless
scratches grad is timeless because he is Tom yes and and his nut is also kind of
his notice is Jerry yeah no the yeah that's what I'm saying is that I fight
spike spike spike yeah Isis is spike what about popcorn popcorn is what is that
Well, popcorn is like when popcorn is what popcorn is like when Jerry drinks
the potion and gets really strong yeah, yeah,
food to coast to the tower yeah exactly yeah and yeah yeah yeah yeah, so then
and then popcorns kind of like the TSA. I guess yeah, I mean I still I'm not you
try to bring a not so old TSA. I'm not sold on that being a one to one Tom and
Jerry to scrat and no, I don't think it is a one to one. I think that Tom and
Jerry is I think Tom and Jerry is a binary scrat system because the nut
never gets the best of scrat. The nut doesn't do any the nuts just a nut man
and I don't rock you can eat and I'm not I'm serious. I'm not convinced. It's
the same nut every time. I don't think it is. I don't think it is because he
turns one of them into popcorn. It can't go back. I think sometimes the nut I
just watched the video of the nut. It got hollowed out and it was a map to
Gratlantis so was that true mm-hmm that's how he founds Gratlantis he was like
trying to not holy scratt scratt on a nut that's crazy you ask he was trying to
eat the nut then I didn't know if he like takes a bite out of the nut and
sees the map inside. He would eat the map. He's holding a hollowed out acorn and it has a map on it. I don't know who did that.
Wait which one like who did that? The whole nut is hollowed out? Yeah. How does he see he looks in it
and there's a map? Yeah it's like the shell of the outside of the nut. Oh the shell or the
which one? Because I saw the video of him eating the nut. He eats the nut shell and all.
Except that neither except he doesn't eat the he doesn't eat the hat. He doesn't eat the hat. He
he doesn't need the hat so it's like he's holding the hat and then there's like a
fingernail shell that comes there's a finger involved there's a fingernail
shaped like a fingernail that comes out of the hat and it's oh okay it's on the
edge so it's only Mario's on that Mario pizza peach is a shared nut for Mario
and Bowser oh and then bow and Mario is Bowser's Jerry but Bowser's Mario's Tom
yeah I can never get Mario unless you lose so it's as if well that's the thing
they're both each other's Tom and Jerry's that means Bowser gets Mario
because you can only win once and then you move on but you lose so many times
to get to that right Bowser actually is Jerry I think that's a new that's
another area and then when Mario defeats Bowser it's like that video where Tom
finally eats yeah and they do a send-off on their own I didn't know you could
share a nut you can share a nut or a Jerry or a cheese I mean cuz he shares
the nut and then yes so Tom so Bowser and Mario are like if Tom also wanted
cheese. Because cheese is cheese. Because they want each other. Yeah. Yeah. So they both have to.
No, you know, maybe they're both, maybe, hmm, maybe they're both like Spike. Or no, you know what?
You know what they are? Bowser has Spikes. No, I got this, dude, I got this. Bowser and Mario are
the alley cats from Tom and Jerry, because those cats hate both Tom and Jerry. Bowser, wait, Bowser
Bowser Mario they both love peach yeah that's like the opposite of hey they
love one things of hating two things well then peach is milk yeah that's true
cuz milk is their nut cheese yeah I think Bowser is spike because he has
spikes yeah that's easy Bowser and Mario and peach or Tom and Jerry no yeah well
Jerry well it depends on the mushroom is a nut so who are the Goombas and the
Koopas the coins are coins those are the alley cats yeah the Goombas and Koopas
those are the alley cats and the Goombas are the cheese what are we
doing is no way is who's the girl who's the the the girl cat Daisy the sexy girl
cat that Tom likes.
Peach.
Oh no because Jerry is...
Her name is also Princess Peach.
Tom's girlfriend is Tom.
But Jerry doesn't like that cat.
Oh right.
He doesn't?
It's like his normal.
No you're thinking of normal.
I think Jerry does like that cat.
No, well Jerry's not like in love with that cat.
Wait.
No Tom loves that cat.
Yeah Tom loves that cat.
Jerry doesn't really care I don't think.
Oh Jerry doesn't even know that cat.
Garfield is a...
Garfield is a scratch.
Lasagna is his nut.
Monday is his ice.
is his ice. Yep. John is Scratay? Spike? No, no, no, wrong. Nermal is Spike. John is his
Jerry. Yeah, John is his Jerry. Or no wait, no, Odie is Spike. Odie is Jerry. No, Odie
is Tom. Jerry is-- Yeah, Garfield is Scratay. Nermal is Jerry's French cousin. Yeah. Yeah,
nibbles the orphan. Yeah. What's the duck? Is that ducker? Donald Duck? No, the little
yellow duck. Oh yeah. That duck is Tweety Bird. That duck, that duck's like the
depressed duck that's like, "I'm going to kill myself!" What is he, where does he fit in?
Wait, that's not from Garfield, is it? That's Tom and Jerry. Oh, right. And then the French
Cousin is normal. I thought you were asking, "Who is the bird in Garfield who wants to kill himself?"
No. That bird... Who is he? In which world? Tom and Jerry. Oh, in Tom and Jerry he's...
John being Tom works perfectly because he's in love with that vet who is the
girl cat. Jennifer Love Hewitt. Who Garfield slash Jerry doesn't know. But
Garfield is in love with Arlene. And this is... Is there a girl mouse that Jerry
likes that's scratch Arlene is gratay right is a girl mouse the Jerry likes
of course there is Alvin in the chipmunk a triple nut or triple scrap I think it's
a triple scrat well there's no there's a there they want there David crosses nuts
yeah that's what I'm saying yeah I think they're triple nuts David crosses scrat
well they also want nuts that they in the beginning of the movie they're
looking for nuts and singing can't be nuts though yeah yeah already has a nut
that is a nut exactly not like food and then music is their nut nuts are their
snack artistry is their nut music is grass is Jerry wait no no snacks the
videos Scooby Scooby's snacks are his nuts yes the gang the mystery gang those
are the Scratlanteans. Oh my god. Oh yeah. But Shaggy is... All the monsters are ice. Shaggy
Scratay. Shaggy has to be Scratay. The monsters are ice. And they're Anunnaki and
Scooby-Doo as well. They are in that one. Scooby-Doo isn't Anunnaki. He is a
Scrat. Yeah. Scooby is a Scrat. He's not a dog. And then there's obviously a Scrat.
He's like way too
Too like spongebob. Oh, but I think it is a scratchy scratchy is is a scrat Lanty or scratch. Oh, it's baby scrat
Yes
But he fucks with scoobies popcorn
He's a popcorn nut yeah
That that's the only way it'll work for scrappy. I'm thinking about could you think we can map this to spongebob?
I think it's fun. I think that's squidward
I'm pretty confident. We have a pretty much 100% success rate.
Yeah, these are like one in one.
SpongeBob is...
SpongeBob is like the mom.
SpongeBob is Sid the Sloth.
No, SpongeBob is Squidward's Nut.
Uh...
No, SpongeBob is Squidward's Ice.
Yeah.
And then Squidward's Nut is the Clarinet.
Or Art.
Squidward's Nut is having a normal day.
Yeah.
Squidward's Nut is dead SpongeBob.
Squidward is Garfield.
Uh-huh.
And his lasagna...
Oh yeah, Squidward's definitely Garfield.
But Garfield is Scrat.
yes he's scrat Garfie scratch but Squidward has no Liz I'm scrat filled
Squidward doesn't have what the clearing playing with clarinet that's his nuts
like yeah yeah yeah but then but that's just something he does every day his
Monday's his Mondays is every day's right yeah well then maybe this is
like we need to shift I think mr. Krabs is scrat money is his night yes
spongebob is the stick he uses to get the yes okay yes we found the scratch
Spongebob's stupidity is the popcorn. Plankton is ice. Yeah. And the nematodes
and the... Plankton is also, no, Plankton is Scrat and the formula is his nut. Oh, yeah.
So this is like a many nuts Scrat. No, no, that's the way it's in. He's tiny, he has one eye. Just like Scrat.
He has one eye bugging out of his head. And Karen, the computer is a Scrat-ay. And everyone, all the other
people are like, all the other characters are the characters of Ice Age. They're
living there well what happens yeah true water he lives in ice yeah with the UFO
right the chum bucket is a UFO oh my god that's a ship yeah that's why it's stuck
in the ground like so is mr. crab is ice or his chair sir Tom mr. Krabs is just
the guy who has the secret formula yeah that's like that's like the tree that
the nut is off but it no cuz he's like he also he's like a talking Harry Potter
is not is a nut and Voldemort is a scrap yeah and the Hermione is scratch no
Hermione is Hermione who does Hermione's my name that doesn't change at all
that's just a change in magic is time and Hermione has a time Turner muggles are
dinosaurs wizards are like rats on setting yeah
Hogwarts is the Ice Age Harry Potter in this situation we're comparing to ice
Casey Dumbledore is gay.
Well, and his nut is is is a guy.
Here's an interesting world, but so so so one snape snape is a guy who
seems like ice, but he turns out to be a snake.
A sherry.
Oh, he's a he's ice.
Yeah, turn out to be Jerry.
Jerry frozen and ice like this thing ice, but he's Jerry.
ice next episode stay best Jerry uh-huh all right Kramer is scrat yes and he's
not walking into Jerry's room he does it too much towards the and Jerry is Jerry
Jerry and Thomas George yeah okay George is not Garfield George's Garfield is
women dating women and George's lasagna George's lasagna is still is something
that you think is funny
Santa a scrat a tom or a Jerry Santa's a saint is the same well Santa think about
Santa's relationship with I know the Grinch is scrat Christmas being granted
is an anti-Skrat. No, he, no, because he wants no Christmas. Skrat is no nut. Skrat doesn't want no nut.
Well, but if he was a Grinch, he would. Exactly. He's anti-Skrat. I think a Grinch is anti-Skrat.
You know why? Because the Skratzons don't want nuts. Yep. Well, yeah. And they're green. So
they're the Grinch. There are different Christmas rules because anyone... This is a season of Joey.
Christmas always has someone who hates Christmas, which is like kind of different than, I guess...
He hates the ice age. Yeah, that's right. So what is Scrat's humbug? Grinch likes the ice because he lives on a mountain.
But Scrat doesn't.
But what is Grinch's nut?
His nut can't be no-grassy.
His nut is Sitty Lou.
He wants to eat her.
Well he's an anti-Scrat who becomes a Scrat.
Yes.
Yeah, I'll give you that.
Wouldn't an anti-Scrat be a Scratazon?
Yeah, but there's
No, because there's a middle ground, because a Scratazon doesn't want anything.
But an Anti-Scrat wants nothing.
Oh no, the Scratazon is Horton.
Oh, okay.
Because he goes to the... they find a little Scrat, because Scrat is small.
Scrat is a who.
Exactly.
And that's why the Grinch is an Anti-Scrat, because the Grinch hates the who's, who are the Scrats.
What if the Grinch is a glum?
Cameron is squeezing my leg really hard right now.
Grinch is a Scrat. He's an anti-Scrat. No, like he, that's like an evolved form of a
Scrat. Oh, you think like he literally comes from Scrat? Because he lives on an ice
mountain. And he's green. Yeah. And he wants... Isn't he from a neighboring town? He's from a
neighboring mountain. That all has Grinch- or Scrats or Grinches? No, he flew
down
but it may not have
scratch
is wrong with you do you think it
who built
it got dogs
that that the
the greatest a scrap it could work
no it's just read as we come to town with their own strategy
i met where they're all gringes at slash you know i think they could be a
different from a time where they're all no issues he's a mutated who
i know i did not lose track of the perfect line for the beginning of this
conversation it's i've kept all the logic in my head out of line is more of a
family tree
yeah yeah
the rat
scratch not is a rat
wait is a squirrel rat?
a rat
a squirrel, wait, Jerry's a mouse
Jerry's a rat
he's a mouse
he's a rodent
and his nut is cheese
and his graté is as well
that's how you can tell a scrat is more of a squirrel
than a rat, because his nut is a nut instead of cheese
ok but who is the ice's
girlfriend?
ice doesn't need a girlfriend
it's the popcorn no no I see his girlfriend is is rocks yeah because
they're both because rocks are meteors that scrat sent towards the planet the
ice planet and he was helping the Atlanteans because they come from earth
but the scrat Lanteans scrat Lanteans Atlanta like this they're the same
they're similar but there's there's a lot of differences it was that we're at
Lanteans where they were they scrat Lanteans they were the edges who hated
hated land. Yeah, their mountain was the ocean and then one day they and their
Christmas was also the ocean. No, they hated the earth and then one day that
they or they hated water and then one day they had a Grinch style switch.
Maybe, maybe an well, Scrat pulled the plug on Scratlantis. Maybe an at pulled
the plug on Atlantis. Oh my God, right at the Apple Eve's app. Yeah, yeah, she
it which was her not from a tree mr. Krabs yeah I'm back to that and then she
drained sin mm-hmm and the snake yep is a dinosaur
it's all a tail yeah I do think the Garden of Eden is probably the best one
what's it that's a dog's nut dog food tail food is always is burying it just
like yeah true it is a bone yeah yeah a cat's nut is catnip cat no catnip is
cat nut well we've already established what a cat's nut is it's a mouse yeah
- A cat's nut is a mouse.
- A cat's nut, to be fair, is a clever mouse.
- Yeah.
- A regular mouse is a cheese.
- A regular mouse is a scrate,
which is something that it gets.
The nut is what it doesn't get until the end,
and the scrate, oh, it gets.
Oh, it gets.
- One day it gets.
- Yeah.
- And then a dog is its dog.
- Borat's nut is America.
- No, Borat's nut is wife.
- It's Pamela Anderson.
- Yeah.
- Borat's wife is, Borat's nut is Pamela Anderson.
- Yeah, so it's actually a clever
version of the nuts grant a formula wait his America is his ice yeah I guess it
is yeah and his bear it's also sort of his hog war well I would say America is
his Hogwarts and Americans are as I yeah and his bear his bear is his Hagrid and
then his ice cream truck is is his ice is his broom is his broom uh-huh and his
wand is the microphone but Mickey's brooms are his ice uh-huh no Mickey's
yes they are yes they are Mickey's mouse is his nut is no no Mickey's brooms are
his campfire where he tries to solve but what to solve a problem with the
campfire but accidentally makes popcorn is the Joker Batman's nut yes yeah
they're each other's nuts they're not Tom and Jerry neither of them get each
other no that's the whole thing neither of them get each other the yeah that's
also Tom and Jerry no Jerry gets to we've been over Jerry gets Tom every
time but but the Joker it keeps getting Batman every time sometimes like with
little tiny thing course Batman and Joker Tom and Jerry and Gotham no they're
hogwarts rat a nut and scrat a nut and the Batmobile is his broom and his
Hagrid is Alfred his Hagrid Hagrid is a no it's a good Batman Hagrid is in Batman
he's not out oh he is out yeah my bad my bad and Wayne Manor is also Hogwarts
yeah we're gonna do the way mirrors hot mr. freezes ice and then the Batcave is
the ice age yeah the back cave is like what no the
back of is the lost world where the dinosaurs are the machines are the
Batman Oh crime is no crime is his nut crime is the Joker and Batman it's both
of their nut they just want to eat it it's a nut scenario damn damn it's all
the same fucking Bowser Mario yeah well it's their peach yeah Batman is Batman
is the Joker's Mario to Joker's Bowser joke is James's giant peach his giant or
or his no that's his hogwarts that's a
song.
Yeah,
and then his spiders his mom, his
parents are is not in ice age.
The ice isn't hogwarts.
It's no,
it's an entity that is the
mountain right now.
And I think earth is yeah,
I'm is hog time is magic.
You said that yeah,
I know,
but I'm repeating because it's
true.
That's a good point.
Yeah,
yeah,
I think we figured it out.
Yeah,
well,
we got you as godzilla's not.
If that's what you're about,
yeah,
okay,
Tokyo yeah well the oceans more of his hog war yeah and then Tokyo is the lost
world with the dinosaurs uh-huh the big dinosaurs that he's I use Godzilla's
cheese what is Jesus killing other monsters yeah or maybe knocking over
buildings because he gets that oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah which one Jerry when
Jerry eats his cheese he becomes shaped like the cheese that's true yeah I've
seen that what's Patrick's not skateboarding maybe maybe that might be
the thing that you like doing yeah the nut is the thing that you get when your
animation studio decides they want to end you on their own terms my nut is
hair yeah yeah my nut is 1 trillion dollars yeah I think that might be mine
You can't have the same nut.
We're not a Mario and Bowser.
Has anybody had anything to do with nuts except Scratch being a nut?
My nut probably is a real nut.
If it's them wanting to kill me,
If it's a hazelnut.
Are you allergic to a hazelnut?
I'm allergic to a hazelnut.
My nut is eating a swan, I think.
You can do that.
No, it's forbidden.
Well, Scratch can just do that.
Is it illegal or is it forbidden?
It's forbidden.
That's one above illegal. Oh wow. Yeah. But you can't just tell him that you can just
do that because you could say that to Scrat too. Eating a nut would seem to be
the easiest task in all of prehistory. I think maybe Scrat just needed to be told that.
I think Scrat maybe needed to just be like, "Yeah, you can eat a nut." Yeah, he wouldn't be
able to understand you. He doesn't speak English. Yeah, he does speak English.
He understands it. He understands it. Because they said, "Welcome to Scratlantis."
Yeah. He probably thought they were saying, "You can have this nut." Yeah, he probably thought they said, "Nut, nut, nut, nut, nut, nut, nut, nut."
not not not yeah it doesn't matter if yeah he thought there was a you can't or
you can't have this nut you know he was gonna spread out either way they said
you can't have this nut and he just leaves
scream people would walk out of the theater I would walk out of the theater
if they played the end by finale at the start of a movie I would walk out of the
theater before yeah well yeah cuz it says the end at the beginning yeah
obviously so that's never gonna be shown in theaters though cuz no it's an
an independent short on you to we should we should screen it. We
should
be read out
we
three now one minute
getting it and then we do and then we do
two more hours of this talking about the cultural impact.
Talking about who Garfield's not it's such a good idea. I wish we'd
done that instead of this
ten thousand dollars renting out the film for
correct. I'm down. This should be called the panel discussion of finale. Yeah. I
mean I'll do we'll do a second one. We'll just do a live one. Yeah. After screening.
Yeah we're gonna do that. That's gonna happen. On tour which you can get tickets at
swagpoop.com/shows. Pierce will be on the shows. Yup. And we're gonna do this we're
gonna do this in every city. Yeah this is the opening act. Philly. Yeah. This is what
Pierce is going to do. Yeah, I wrote this yesterday morning and we all just read it off the charts.
It does kind of seem like that. Yeah. I'm pretty impressed that we talked about that
for an hour. I really thought. Yeah, I thought that was good. I was just excited to talk
about Scrat for ten minutes at the top. And not only, it was very, it was very. Not only
I could keep going. Definitely, I might want to keep going the next episode we're recording
right after this. Calm down dude. We should think of some more examples. We shouldn't release
the next one where we talk about Scrat after. We should wait like three weeks. Well, that's
the way the schedule is shaking, a very complicated backlog schedule. The one that we record right
after this will come out in like two or three weeks. So look forward to...
So you get a little break.
That's kind of, yeah. It'll be a Scrat Gets Us Not retrospective for you, but not for us.
For us it will be a present-spective.
What you should do is you should put the recording on your computer right now and then we can
listen to it and then make...
We should do a director's commentary of the episode.
We do director's commentary and then add like, we're adding footnotes and it's like, what
we meant here was like this and...
It would be so complicated because we did that already.
We were already doing commentary whether or not...
I think it'll sound good.
Alright.
Bye!