You're listening to Patrick's Podcast.
[Patrick's Podcast theme]
Patrick.
Doop-a-doop-boo!
A-doop-a-doop-a-boo!
Oh, no, no, no, no.
I'm not excited for this at all.
Um...
So I have to do Patrick's thoughts too now because Caleb...
Oh shit I have all the Twitch stuff on.
Hold up.
That's gonna...
That'll fuck it up.
Where did I put the...
There we go.
I'll just shut all that off.
Oh boy.
This is gonna be a weird one.
So you wanna see something fucked up?
I'll be open and honest with you guys.
I don't care.
I don't give a shit.
Bless me.
Jesus Christ.
I'm having a day beer because I have to do this.
Check this out.
Bam.
That's all of my laundry and it's as tall as my shelf.
Look at that.
Look at that shit.
Aren't I fucking disgusting?
What the fuck is wrong with me?
Jesus Christ.
Literally like I had the plan to go home and then do all my laundry in New Hampshire and
then bring it back.
But this Omicron shit is, it's, it might, my roommate got it.
So I'm freaking the fuck out obviously.
I had like a big, not a meltdown, but I did panic and spend $84 on snacks just in case
I'm locked in for two weeks.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's shit.
I haven't even bought Christmas presents yet.
Do you, anyone else, like I wait till like the last minute.
Like I got Caleb and Kams because we had planned to do like an episode and then this freaking
Omicron hit and we had planned a Christmas special and now it's like I don't even know
if that's going to happen.
I would love for it to happen but fuck man shit.
Fuck man shit.
I don't know.
This sucks.
This is like the worst time to be alive.
I've been like so, so, so stressed out lately.
Oh dear.
Oh dear, oh dear, oh dear, oh dear, oh dear.
It's basically, it basically sucks.
the
watch
new
I went in there, I was riding this, where did I put it?
It's under my bed somewhere.
My room is such a mess right now.
But you can see the laundry on my bed too.
That's a thing Cameron and I have been doing
to
the
trailer for paymaster. Where's the... yeah here it is. What? Oh. It probably got got
for copyright. Damn. Well anyway. Ok so. Oh I just moved that shit. So I've been riding
this 917 board because one of my boards got waterlogged and riding this 917 board for
those in the know, you know that Max Palmer who rides for limousine now, started limousine
whatever.
So he's at, I go into labor, I'm pregnant, I'm pregnant as hell.
I'm like looking at the shit to make sure that it's like recording and everything and I'm
like looking at myself and realizing like facial tics that I do when I'm nervous and like the
oh god dude this every uh whatever anyway anyway uh um so I go into labor skate shop to buy
new wheels. I'm riding that board 917. There's like beef between Max and Alex Olson who runs
917 or whatever. So I'm riding like an old 917 board while Max Palmer's trying to take
pictures of all the new limousine product at labor. So there's a possible chance that
there's a photo of me holding a 917 board looking at limousine product.
Which none, no one who is subscribed, like probably like 10,
15 people who listen to the premium,
like understand what that like,
understand that that's like like kind of kooky of me and like,
like, Oh shit. Like that's kind of funny. Max took like a,
I'm like in the foreground of a picture,
like looking at his new shit riding like one of like like it's an old Cyrus Bennett board
who also owns limousine and like oh god I've never felt like more like a fucking fool in
my entire life like that that sucked that sucked okay I guess we'll just watch the new limousine
Paymaster is what it's called.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, here it is.
Here it is.
this is a...
Ooh, gotta make me small.
I know for a fact
Cam and Calew find out I'm doing this
they're gonna get so mad.
Hold on, let me...
Jesus.
Might be too quiet now.
It's not like I can get DMCA'd.
I heard that people were complaining that Cyrus Bennett did too many back tails in this.
And it's like, if I could back, what the fuck?
Imagine complaining about a back tail, that is insane.
Oh, they got some Nolan Benfield footage in this, that's so tight.
Haven't seen much of him since like Cosmic Vomit.
Like, like I get being a hater or whatever, I, you know, but like complaining about like
a back tail, especially if you can do him as good as Cyrus, like what the fuck?
to
that
it's
so ADHD and so fucking stupid.
Uhhhh.
Ooh, abandoned skateboard restoration.
That actually looks kinda tight.
Oh, look at that grip job.
It's kinda...
Hold on, Caleb had to reinstall all of his drivers and shit.
It was supposed to be an episode of me and Caleb.
And um, cause Cameron's away.
And uh, I just went ahead and started.
Cause I knew something was gonna be fucked up with Caleb's stuff.
He's either, either something's fucked up or he's lying cause he doesn't wanna do it.
Which I get it.
I get it man, I get it Caleb, it's fine.
You can just tell me you don't want to do it, but I have to tell them I'm recording this
right now.
What kind of trucks are these?
Those look like, there's a C on it.
Those are, the hangers kind of look like thunders.
I don't know, I don't know.
I don't know what they're for.
I don't know.
Is anyone, no one would get any enjoyment out of this.
Like this is also like, cause I'm not thinking about like the people who aren't going to
watch it, you know?
Like no one, I don't know.
We don't do video episodes for that reason.
And now I'm doing a fucking video, oh god dude.
What if I've just ruined the whole show?
What if I've ruined everything and everyone's mad at me?
I hope no one's mad at me for this.
Fuck.
Ugh.
Anyway, what kind of board is this?
Probably some shop deck or something.
It looks like spray painted.
Those look like thunders.
I think those are Thunder Trucks.
This is kind of like...
I guess some...
Oh, dude, just put it on the fucking...
You don't have to take the bearings out like that.
Just put it...
You could have just put it on the hanger.
And look, they literally, on that fucking reflex tool, you can just...
There's a bearing push right there.
You could have just used that thing.
I don't know why he's doing that.
It's like way simpler.
Oh anyway, at labor I bought 58mm wheels.
Which is like crazy big.
I don't think I've ever...
Oh what are those?
Those look like a truck company that just doesn't exist anymore.
The hangers kind of look like thunders though.
I just need to see the base plate again and I'll probably be able to...
Oh fuck.
Are those...
This is ASMR done by somebody with a learning disability.
Uh...
These must be some like
Amazon brand fucking trucks. I can't get a good look
Also like nobody gives a shit no one
No one cares what trucks they are
Nobody cares, but me. I'm I'm the only one I guess I'll have to see once you
But they have that fucking little
Graffiti on them. These are probably some you know what they're probably some European brand. I've never heard of yeah, Crail
It's his Crail on them
The fuck is Crail
I'm sure I'm gonna get some fucking like
Some German guy some German fan of the show is that actually Crail was one of the biggest
one of the biggest skateboard track companies
in in Deutschland
Oh this one time I was with somebody waiting outside of a bar.
I don't know I think I was just like chillin, like having a cigarette and this guy, this
like German guy asks me for a cigarette, it was my last one.
Actually was, I wasn't just being like "yeah I know it was my last one" because I give
out cigarettes like a motherfucker.
I give out cigarettes like way too much.
in
it was a German. But yeah he's like standing there. I tried to guess what part of Germany
he was from though. And I guess northern he was southern and then he's like you don't
hear the Austrian in my voice? And I was like dog I guess German. I didn't say Austrian.
Hitler yeah he's like like talking all that shit and then like my friends like
she was like oh so like what are you like doing after this and he's like oh
you know I could not meet any girls here so I'm probably going to go home and
masturbate I'm gonna go back inside I'm not hanging out with this fucker anymore
more
I bet Crails not even a German truck company too.
I wonder, hold on, let me do a quick look-see at this.
Rod Filmes.
Oh, this is like,
this is like Portuguese or something.
Yo, Brazilian, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, so Crail must be a Brazilian truck company or something.
Gotta say, Brazil?
Crazy ass skaters.
Brazil and Japan fucking smoked us in the Olympics.
It was nuts.
I don't know too much about Brazil.
I've never...
I mean, clearly I've never been to Brazil.
I don't think I've ever left the country.
No, I've never left the country.
I don't mean...
Why did I say I don't think? I don't fucking know.
Whatever.
I got a package in transit.
It's cool.
I think it's a shirt I bought.
But yeah, Brazil, I mean, they got Tiago Lemos and like, oh, who's that guy?
Big Dreadlocks.
Aldemo Jr.
That was his name.
he was sick. He rode for I-Path, hit those giant dreadlocks, he had to cut them off because
he went to jail because his dad like fucked him over for like taxes or something. Shit,
crazy ass story, definitely check that out. I think it was on like, it's like his Nine
Club interview or some shit. No one, no one cares about this. No one... I'm gonna get like
a bunch of people saying like oh like oh it's fine over there blah blah blah also I don't
fucking no one gives a shit dude why am I doing this?
You're not supposed to use WD-40 on bearings.
It's not good for them.
only supposed to use bone speed cream.
Again none of you fucking know what I'm talking about.
This is like, you know what it is, I just came back from skating so now it's like the only
thing I'm thinking about.
And like, it's not like, see it's like now I'm thinking like oh I have to like top the
the
a
twitch stream. You know what, I'll surprise you with an animal that I saw. Nevermind,
I forgot. Woah. This is like the first result. Hold up. What is this video? Woah! What is
Whoa, this is like the first result.
Hold up.
What is this video?
Whoa!
No!
Buddy!
Oh, geez!
Look at how he jumps!
Look at that fucker!
Oh my god.
That is insane.
I can't do like...
The two like most redneck dudes too.
So perfect.
So perfect that it's like, "Oh, you fucking, fucking look at that raccoon, he's on a boat."
Oh man.
Raccoon versus cat.
All right, this looks, this looks very promising.
30 minute video uploaded in 2015.
No audio for some reason.
I'm not doing this one.
Cat attacks raccoon, two minutes, okay.
Just like some backyard footage.
If I had a backyard like this, and a raccoon came in to my backyard, I'd do everything
in my power to domesticate it.
I would let a mama raccoon set up shop in my backyard.
And then, oh there it is, there's the fucker.
Camera glitched out. Only caught the raccoon for a second.
But I'd do everything in my power to let that thing...
Dude, haven't like... Oh my god, like a baby raccoon farm basically and I'm selling them to people?
I sell little baby raccoons to all my neighbors?
That'd be sick.
That'd be like...
Oh, oh, oh!
See, this would be the one problem.
My cat would probably...
If I am in this future where I have
a backyard
and I'm trying to house a baby raccoon farm.
Damn, he's fucking them up.
Orange cats, dude, they're...
vicious as hell.
Oh, dude, look at their... look at the arches on both of their backs.
Nuts.
Whoa.
Whoa!
Is he gonna climb with...
Holy shit.
That is so fucking sick.
Dude, he climbed that thing like fucking Spider-Man!
Holy fuck.
Look at that shit.
Damn.
That is nuts. That is fucking crazy.
Oh, if you're listening to this on your commute,
you're missing out. You gotta look up "Cat Attacks Raccoon"
by Christian Brayden.
Like it's his movie.
Yeah he directed this in June 17th 2021.
Damn. Oh my create my Adobe Creative Cloud has plugin updates.
Cat on ice.
Whoa. Oh come on little dude. Oh he's so little.
Oh he's so scared.
Oh come on little dude.
Oh.
You'll be ok.
Oh man.
Oh he's so confused.
He's never been on ice before.
Look at him.
This is awesome.
Whoa.
Woah!
*snort*
He straight up does not understand.
People are going to be so mad at me for this episode.
This is 10 times worse than the first one.
Because at least the first one I had like 2 days prep.
This is like 12 hours that I have before I have to...
Fuck dude.
Funny cats compilation, most popular part 1.
Absolutely.
This one's a classic.
Oh that cat just took off that woman's bikini, oh hell no.
Oh dear.
Dude, cats fucking, cats love to push things off of...
Oh he's gonna push it anyway.
Yeah, he's gonna do it.
*snort*
Dude, they- the cats fucking love
pushing things off the tables.
I-
I- what?
about that?
Like, why?
Hold on, I'm gonna look that up.
I'm gonna look up- why does cat-
why do cats like to push things off of the table?
Why do cats
knock things over?
Can you even read that?
No, there's no way.
This is PetMD.com
Some of our cat's strange habits can easily be explained.
But this is one habit that leaves us scratching our heads.
It looks like...
It looks like the only explanation is like...
Oh, okay, it's like manipulative...
Cats are little manipulative fuckers.
Damn. I gotta get a cat.
I gotta get another cat real quick.
I'm using... I'm using, uh...
Not my actual YouTube account, because I know...
I know you fuckers would see something in my like recommended videos and make fun of me for it forever.
It's like how to heel flip or something. Like I'm trying to like learn, like skate tricks I'm trying to learn as like a grown man.
Ugh, boy.
Which, I mean, it's fine. It's fine to like try and learn how to skate when you're old, but like...
I don't know.
I don't want anyone to know that I'm fucking...
I don't want anyone to know I can't heel flip.
You know?
Oh hell yeah.
Look at that.
Oh fuck.
I got something in my eye.
I can't even see the video.
There's a really dark shadow.
I'm not even looking.
delicate operation.
You just got one eye open. So that indicates she's five weeks
old. As you can see, she's got a really fat little tummy there.
Oh, she's got a sleeping bag in here. And she's gonna be nice
and cozy in there.
All right, I think my eyes good now.
We're not really well. Just going really fast now.
All right, it's time for a bigger enclosure for
Damn dude, it's so like...
Stode is just British for weasel, right?
Like no one's...
No one can answer me. I'm talking to my fucking self. I'm having... I should have called Leo.
Know what I might do? I might pause this recording and call somebody.
I think that's what I'm gonna do. Everyone was busy.
I couldn't I couldn't call anybody because they were busy
Damn.
Whisper the Stoat?
Stuart Stoat?
Oh God.
I need a Stoat dude.
I need like a little animal.
I need to be a father.
I'm ready to become a father.
If anyone wants to...
If anyone wants to give me a baby...
Please.
Not a human baby.
Like an animal.
Some kind of like snake or...
Like a Charmander.
Like...
like a Charmander like I'm going I'm going completely insane now I don't
think oh geez I spent $84 on snacks because I'm I'm so scared of a second
lockdown not scared of a second lockdown I just don't want to deal with one
one because it will be annoying.
I need to check if this is recorded.
I think it is.
The first half of that I had to stop recording.
I don't know.
Wait!
Ugh.
Anyway, I need like a, I need like a tiny cat.
I need like one of those like cats that they like do like genetic engineering to that makes
it stay kitten-sized forever and it has a million gajillion health problems and it's like, "Oh,
it looks so cute!"
And it's like, "Oh yeah."
It can't shit without bleeding.
It can't shit without bleeding and every morning it wakes up with organ failure and you have
to give it mouth-to-mouth as soon as it wakes up.
That's how you get it awake.
It's like essentially like a toy poodle.
Like all those toy animals riddled with fucking...
Like pugs aren't supposed to look like that.
I feel like pugs are a genetic mutation.
Most dogs are now.
Most like, it's like, oh this dog was bred to hunt foxes and then people just wanted them
as pets and then they just breed out like some kind of like, oh it used to have like a longer
nose like a beagle in like 1901 compared to like a beagle now has like a smaller face
or some bullshit you know?
And it's, ugh, dear.
What we do to animals so that they can like remain cute or like be better house pets is
so fucked up.
It's so fucked up that we play God with dogs.
What the fuck?
What am I doing right now?
I think it's good to have a thing like this every year.
A day where I just audit my own thoughts and think about why I think the way I think.
I don't know why.
I'm glad I have Caleb and Cameron to keep me in check.
If this shit went unchecked, I'd be the worst.
I'd be like the worst guy of all time.
It's not like I'm already...
It's not like I'm the greatest.
*laughs*
What the fuck?
What am I even saying?
I'm just like, just saying like shit
so that you aren't bored.
Oh dear.
Ugh.
Commercials that every 2000s kid knows.
*Zoop house theme*
You know this 2000's kid
I miss Caleb and Cameron already
I'm gonna miss them so much if we go into second lockdown
I'll be able to see them in the park or whatever
are
really good night and uh, just like god damn it I, I love all my friends so much.
I've had so many of those in the past couple weeks and uh, now it's all gone to shit cause
now everyone's getting fucking Omicron and uh, yeah dude it blows.
It blows ass.
Dream skateboard build, all white skateboard setup.
You ever realize what your obsessions are?
And just be like, "Damn, I fucking love watching, I love putting together skateboards.
My dream job would just be to do this."
I don't even, like, if this shit wasn't working out, like if most of this shit in my life
wasn't working.
Have you ever been so down bad that you almost apply to a Zoomies?
Because I have.
I've gone through the application process of Zoomies and then closed the tab.
I got halfway through a Zoomies application in like 2018 and was like, "No."
I thought about it for longer than like the 15 seconds where I'm like, "I just need money
so bad and I just like I was like yeah no I'll just spend my whole day like setting up skateboards
for like shitty kids what the fuck kind of grip tape is that it has no oh okay nevermind
you can tell yeah it's like I don't know it's some kind of blank he's probably spending
like little to no money on this on like Amazon.
Also I love the fucking, what is that like Minecraft like background music?
The soft piano?
He should have worn a white shirt though.
Yeah I almost applied to Zoomies.
I almost worked at a fucking Zoomies.
I didn't almost work there, I almost went through with an application.
I would have been the only fucking core dude working at that Zoomies, you feel me?
I would have been the only one, I would have been the only Zoomies employee that skated
core shit.
I would like go into Zoomies in high school and just to like see if like, oh they're selling
like Spitfires, like if they're selling like Formula Fours or something for like at a discount,
you know like oh well I'll fucking like you know like yeah support your local but like
you know if I can if no one sees me buy like wheels or like bearings at zoomies at a discount
price then it didn't happen so I'd like go in there just to like check out like what
products they had and it always sucked like it was always like like zoomies has like cool
shit like wow don't oh fuck taking that out of context I'm gonna look like such a fucking
idiot. But like, zoomies will have like, you know, like the OG, like, you know, they got
like Baker, they got like all like the big companies, they'll have like cool shit like
that. And then they have just like, the shittiest fucking like, like Goodwood and Superior,
like those fucking graphics. I think my first board was the Goodwood, it was like this Goodwood
major, it said major blazers on it, and it was like a Rasta unicorn with like galaxy,
Like the first board I got when I was getting back into skating when I was like 13 and then
like the first, hold on, the timeline of boards that I've had is like Major Blazers board
when I was 13, 7.5 board, tiny fucking, tiny ass board.
Then when I was like 14 I worked for a landscaping company and I like shoveled like an old folks
home and then I bought this crooked Mark Gonzales team deck, like pink 8.5 board with these
white and blue Thunder 147's.
Why did he spray the...
Why did he spray it?
Anyway, the fucking, yeah, like pink board with white and blue trucks.
it's
I
No one gives a shit about that.
There's ten people who care about-
No, this sucks.
This sucks so much.
God damn it, dude.
Caleb and Cameron are gonna be so mad at me.
But I love them so much.
I love my friends.
I love all my damn friends.
I'm gonna list off all my friends' names.
*laughs*
*claps*
The rest of the episode is me just being like, Caleb, Cameron, Patches, Joe, Alex, Neil.
I'm so sorry to people who are like listening to this in the car.
Oh dear.
I should have just watched it, I should have had a plan going into this.
Cause I don't know, is this like narcissistic of me to like, you know, record myself, like
I'm having a fucking crisis right now.
Like I'm like, like I know we have to put something out and I know that Caleb and Cam
told me to do this.
But it's like, is like, should I do this if I'm not going to be proud of it?
[laughs]
Ugh.
Dios mio.
Dios mio, indeed.
And talk about my skateboard setup.
That's, no, that's very narcissistic.
also no one gives a shit about that.
Truly nobody cares about that.
Except for the one guy who asked.
Forget who, but one of the patrons messaged me.
Asked me about my setup.
I guess I can talk, I don't know.
It's not like I'm not going to get immediate feedback or anything like this.
Like I'm saying it like I'm still on Twitch.
What the fuck are those?
Those... clear bearings?
Those look... those would break in a sec- those are like plastic!
What the fuck?
Oh see, now he uses it!
Oh yeah, the bearing fart.
Never use that thing, always use the truck.
I mean I said earlier, use that, but why put the fucking, I don't know.
I'm not consistent with what I say.
This is psychotic.
this
You can message Jubio and uh, you can tell, you message Jubio and say in the Twitter DM
you say "Dear Jubio, the podcast sucks. I want to kill you because of it. And then we can
report you and then get you banned." Fucker. Fuck you. Ha ha. Fuck you. Uh, I don't know.
I think I'm going to stop it here.
Actually I do want to see how this ends.
Oh here's a quirk I have I can tell you about on my skateboard.
I heard that Ashad Ware does this, so now I do it.
Which is stupid.
Which is stupid for me to be like, "Oh, well no."
Because it's like, "Oh, well that's a good idea."
You get like a fraction of an inch more on your fucking...
I put both the washers on the inside.
like
make me good like a shod if I do that. It doesn't. I bought some big ass wheels though. I bought
some fucking 58mm wheels. I probably already talked about this. I bought some tires dude.
I bought some fucking tires. It's been fun. I get a lot more speed. But you don't care
about that. You wanna hear me do jokes? You wanna hear me be funny? Hey, little funny
man dance for us. If I don't get to go home for Christmas because of Omicron, I'm gonna
kill myself.
Should I even put this out?
We'll find out if I do.
You'll find out if I do.
He fucking it.
He ain't fucking that thing.
Ugh.
There's so much going on in this damn world.
Ugh!
that my roommates hear me and just think I'm I'm I've completely fucking lost it now
everything's scary everything is fucked everybody sucks you don't really know why
but you want to justify sucking someone's dick off funny funny funny gay parody um
I'm gonna finish this video out and then stop.
Oh but yeah my my for the one guy that's interested
yeah I switched to 58 56 millimeter wheels to 48 or 58 millimeter wheels and um
I've got an eight and a quarter uh GX1000 board that's coming in the mail. I bought it straight
from them because I wanted a specific graphic they were making and I couldn't find it at my
I
and a Dr. Pepper.
Speaking of, Dr. Pepper good as fuck.
Dr. Pepper is so good.
I've literally like
not, I stopped drinking Dr. Pepper for a while and then started drinking Dr. Pepper again
because I just like one day remembered like, "Oh yeah, Dr. Pepper, like the can of Dr. Pepper."
Fucking so sick. Dr. Pepper in the can
That's one of the best flavors 23 of them
23 flavors packaged in that beautiful can I'm gonna see you do a front
I want to forbidden 14 only nose and tails on that you scrape one
Fucking
One fraction of the center of the board you throw that thing away I
Don't know too much about the forbidden 14. I know it's a Boston guy. I know it's Dana Erickson
Is that like I have to read the quarter snacks interview about it again
Cuz I tried to do that. I tried to do it. So I only skated like the nose and the
the tail and then I got bored one day and just like did like a
Slappy board slide. I was like alright fuck it. Oh with the white shoes. What are those footprints?
Those are footprints. I'm like gag oh
Dude here's one okay wait
This is a really good one speaking of
Here we go dude this was so this is top 10 moment of 2021 for me
This is a this is an edit
Damn it
okay, so
What happened was I'll explain what it is. I can't just like go in and
Play it out of nowhere
so Joey Brzezinski
Who I mean?
People can have their opinions on him. I don't care. I'm talking about like months old beef now. This is so funny
He runs like footprint
shoes and
Like all they're like marketing is like oh you can drop an egg on these insoles
Then they won't break and it's like all right. Yeah. No. I'm a fucking I'm a rube. I'll buy those I don't oh
Oh, the guys in Cirque du Soleil, they use the Footprint insoles!
Yeah, I'll fuckin' - look, you're selling to guys like me, I'll fuckin' - I'll buy whatever
stupid fuckin' product you're shelling out.
But for some reason he had too many white claws at a Wu-Tang concert, and Footprint
had just did like an ODB collab and those shoes look fucking terrible.
So he's like on, he's off the claws at a Wu-Tang show and took it upon himself to call out
fucking awesome's own Jason Dill, the owner of fucking awesome.
Which you get, you know, fucking awesome puts out some stuff and it's like, yeah, people
People only like it because it's F.A. like I get it, but the stuff they do put out that's
sick is sick.
Like I won't deny that, like F.A. is like a sick fucking, sick art direction and everything,
whatever.
Whatever, I'm fucking, ugh, I'm so stupid.
Uh, anyway, Jesus Christ my voice is, ah shit, did I, I fucking caught it didn't I?
I caught that shit.
Um, yeah I got too drunk at a Wu-Tang show and started doing this.
*Fuck you Dale, what do you have with your fake ass company? F.A.
*Fuck you, you fucking ass, you fucking stupid bitch
*Fuck you, you fucking claiming speech, you ain't speech
*Laughter
Oh man, I fucking, I wish I could find the full, the full fucking rant
Because it's like,
oh dude,
it's, it's, he's like,
dude's off the fucking sauce, like he's
completely fucking gone.
Just yelling like, "Fuck you Dylan,
you're fake ass company!" Paul Hart walks in,
the dude's like a MAGA skater, he like
sucks, um,
he comes in and then like,
there's videos of him for like the rest of the night
and he's like, screaming at like
his friends who like don't want to be in
the video, cause like,
I
a shoe that was similar to Footprint's shoes.
And he's standing there at a Wu-Tang show,
you should be fucking enjoying yourself,
you like got to meet like the Wu-Tang clan and shit.
And he's like, "Man, fuck these guys,
"like our shoes have twice the rebounding technology."
(laughs)
He's talking about his fucking egg drop test
at the fucking Wu-Tang show.
It's so fucking sick, dude.
Oh speaking of, same guy put out a video 10 years ago on his own personal channel, Joey
Brzezinski.
This is a video titled "Joey Brzezinski Gets a BJ".
I've never seen this before.
I know this is going to be fucking comedy gold.
I know this is going to be better than SNL's, this is going to be better than, uh, this
is going to be better, the best comedic mind of all time.
of
this is it. No. Fuck. That used to be, that song used to be the first result when you
looked up like, oh here it is. Yeah. That's so funny. He literally looked up funny 70s
This
- the headphones so the girlfriend will love them
I don't like him. I
Don't like Joey Brzezinski, I
Don't like him. I don't like him at all. I think visual his company sucks. I think team burrito sucks
Footprint sucks. I've skated footprint insoles. My feet hurt so bad after I skated them. I
Don't like him. I
Loo I don't like his vibe. I don't like his tick-tock channel. I don't like I
Don't care I'm gonna say it
I'm starting my first beef
This is it
Patrick's thoughts - ends with me starting my first beef and it's with a guy
Who could fucking destroy me in skate? It's like with a guy who's a ten times better skater than me. He had a pretty good
It's a it's okay. It's like
It's a C- part in
Cliche Bon Voyage, I think that's what it's called. Let me see
Yeah, yeah cliche Bon Voyage he has a he has a C- part in that
But I'm starting my first beef with you motherfucker.
Fuck you.
Fuck you, you little bitch.
I really hope that this doesn't get to him because I'm not actually trying to start a
beef.
I really, I don't want to pull up to a skate park one day and have that dude off the claws
run up to me just like, "Man, fuck you!
Fuck you!
You're talking shit about my rebounding technology, you fucking little bitch!
Little ass bitch!
I'm in the streets, dude!
You're out here claiming straights, fuck you!
Yeah. No, I'm not a fan of that guy.
Anyway, alright. I have to edit this now. This sucks. Okay, bye bye.