commitment
uh... that's that's a story
yeah patrick stems now
that's a good stem
let's discuss stemming
this was a lot of my head about mental health now
Yeah, which is because autism is a mental illness.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, is what Patrick is trying to say.
Yes.
Yeah.
I stim like a... I do excited little hands.
Yeah, I rub myself.
I do.
Anytime that we do a show, I have to go outside for at least 10 minutes and I have to swing my arms like I'm a helicopter and do stretches.
That's because of your...
the physical, like you need to warm up
because of all the tricks and acrobatics
you do during the show.
I don't know if that counts as stimming.
That's more of like a warmup for your like somersaulting.
- That's true.
- Which is a huge part of the live shows,
which I guess, but the time just comes up.
- I do a lot of jumps.
I do a lot of arm swings.
I do a lot of, I did a jump last show we did.
I did a pratfall.
- He did a jump, yeah.
I did a pratfall and then my stomach hurt for like two days.
Yeah, because of what you ate during the pratfall.
All the Jenga pieces hit my chest right here and it's still, there's a bruise.
You fell on the ground and you said you wouldn't get up unless people saw you.
On the inside, there's a bruise.
On the inside.
You keep saying that but that's what a bruise is.
Yeah.
What?
You know when a bruise makes a big bump?
That's scary.
Oh yeah, it's horrifying.
I don't like that.
I got that on my arm, I thought I had a thing.
I gave my brother a concussion once.
Okay.
I was going to say, does he have a bump or bumps are sort of the same.
I gave him a bump but then you started talking.
I feel rude for interrupting.
Anyway, I dropped a knife in my girlfriend's foot and she has a permanent bump.
A permanent bump?
She has a scar and the scar is elevated off of her foot and it hasn't decreased in altitude
since I dropped the knife.
In altitude?
Damn.
Did you drop it like pointy side down?
Yes, Cameron.
Into her foot?
Yes, I dropped it.
I mean, he dropped it like it was hot.
It could have been long, sharp side down.
I was saying, like, did it just like, it was a direct point.
It was a horror movie.
Yeah.
It was frightening.
I threw a, the way, I gave my brother a bump and a concussion, because I threw a can of
Old Spice spray at his head when we were getting into a fight when I was younger.
I fucking just whipped it at him and it just like hit the side of his head and I heard a
you go yeah and I got in a lot of trouble because he got a concussion.
Yeah,
you weren't in trouble until the doctor said that word. Yeah, I think I was
probably fine. Yeah, yeah, that is yeah. You're almost like what sounded to
make that's probably yeah, you're all dressed up like you're in court and
you're sitting in the waiting room at the doctor's office. Yeah, oh my God,
just doing helicopter was told that he can't yeah that's a weird thing about me
like I just get really nervous and like I always have to like swing my arms
around before I go to jail like I get nervous about going to jail yeah just
say straight up yeah I'm not a fan but I always yeah I like have to pace back
and forth and talk to myself like hype myself up in the mirror and stuff before
I go to jail yeah yeah it's gonna be okay in jail you're not gonna be in there for
that long. I guess I was about to say an OCD thing which is turning the lights on
and off. I guess that's stimming if you like the feeling of the
light switch. I guess stimming is something you do. Yeah. It's
like picking your nose and flicking the boogers stimming. What about going to the bathroom?
It depends. Maybe if you roll the booger up into a little ball. But then you keep
rolling. That's when it becomes stimming. Yeah exactly. Yeah. You roll the
a booger up like this and then you're and then people when people ask you like oh,
what are you doing? You just say like oh, no, I'm just playing the world's
tiniest violin to your story.
I'm just rolling to my booger rolling the world's tiniest booger. Oh, you're
sorry. So
yeah,
I was doing a bit where I was doing the excited little hands autism girl, but
she has Havana syndrome and
It's just the same.
When this part of the song comes on, my Havana syndrome goes crazy.
Yeah.
Havana.
What is Havana syndrome?
It's when you get sick.
Deadass, I have that.
They said they were in Havana and they got hit with a stomach ache.
Yeah, it's like a ray that the Cuban government is hitting people with.
It's not real.
It's exactly the same thing that people who are so schizophrenic that they ride the bus
for 12 hours a day say they have yeah yeah a CIA guy in a socialist country
yeah going to experience some stomach yeah yeah it is fun yeah I love the
stomach a gun is probably the funniest like schizophrenic creation to me I also
do just love heart attack gun I love our tech guns great but I think stomach a
gun is like a perfect improvement on the heart attack gun that's like they're not
trying to kill you or even really hurt you. Yeah, they just want you to like be
uncomfortable, maybe poop weird. In reality, they're almost the same gun.
They're just one is a fatal shot and the other shot is in the gut and they're both a
gun that one gun makes you die and the other gun injures you. Imagine the idiot at the CIA
that mixes up the two guns one day. Yeah. Oh my god. Oh yeah. Or he loads the stomachache
bullets into the heart attack gun. I have heartache now. I'm really homesick.
Yeah, I found a guy on Twitter once who believed, who thought he was getting hit
but with the stomachache gun and it was just like a bunch of tweets that were
like, "They are giving me brutal diarrhea. They are causing me pain when I poop." And
just a bunch of stuff like that. Just a guy who doesn't know he's lactose
intolerant. It's exactly what it is, yeah. That's fire. Yeah. That's dead-ass fire.
fire. It's dead ass fire. What did you guys get up to yesterday? I don't even know. I
changed all the light bulbs in my apartment. Really? From what to what? For like most of
the time that we've lived there, it's all recessed lights in there and in the kitchen
there was only one tiny blue light that would work and I replaced all, you've been in my
place you know that like that row of like lights I think right above the stove oh
I replaced all those because they they just weren't working I don't know why I
was like all right today is the day yeah sometimes you just have to pick a day to
do stuff like that yeah but I've been living there for since March I don't
know how many months that is yeah you pretended you're about to count them by
just opening your hand. Yeah. I think it's zero to five. Was it five months? I don't
know. No. Well, you just opened your hand as if you were counting from zero to five.
That was five months. Whoa. Whoa. Damn. I basically did nothing yesterday. I figure you're a genius as long as you're not actually trying to do anything. Yeah.
Yeah, I basically sat on my couch so anyone think that's cool or like funny or watch TV
and one on the computer read a book okay okay food some snacks it's an ice cream
you did not eat ice cream I ate some lactose-free ice cream a were you here
no we all I do we all got each other surprise snacks oh and I got him a
Snickers ice cream bar cuz I was like I don't haven't had a Snickers ice cream
bar in a while but I'm not gonna eat it that'd be a nice thing to give to my
friend and then he looks at me and says no I can't eat that I will shoot diarrhea
everywhere. Well for context it was he it was like five minutes before we recorded
and in any other situation I would eat the ice cream bar and I would take the
diarrhea right I do not want to get diarrhea in the middle of recording. I wasn't giving you diarrhea I was giving you an ice cream bar. That would have given me diarrhea. You have two options. I can tell you for a fact. You can take this ice cream bar or you can take this diarrhea that I found.
What were the other surprise snacks? I'm so curious.
It was also jalapeno cheese curls.
He also said no, he can't eat those.
I didn't say I can't. Again, the really important part of this is that it was right before we recorded.
He turned down every single surprise snack.
That's not true. There are other ones I would have accepted, but they went to other people.
And you know what? I didn't complain. I said it's fine.
I'm sorry for making you guys give me surprise snacks that would give me diarrhea.
And you guys are my best friends and I love you. And then you guys were like, I hate you.
Yeah, we said this.
Yeah.
Well, the bacon, egg, and cheeses yesterday were good.
And you ate that right before, I guess not right before.
Yeah, exactly.
See, that's the thing.
That's what I'm saying.
If it had been any other time than two minutes before I hit record.
You guys all got bacon, egg, and cheeses without me?
Yeah.
You were at the doctor.
He was taking a bacon, egg, and cheese out.
Yeah, it's true.
I was at the doctor.
We were putting them in.
He was removing yours.
Yeah.
I did get Chipotle and I ate it on the train on the way back.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Wait, why is that funny? I don't understand.
Eating a chipotle bowl on the train is...
Isn't that when people say "only in New York"?
Isn't that like one of the...
I guess it's true.
I'm always doing the "only in New York" thing for that day.
Whoever sees me, I'm the guy that people think is the embodiment of the city.
Yeah.
Like what? What are you doing that you're making people say that?
Having a really loud argument with a stranger. Yeah
I think yeah owning a flamethrower owning a flamethrower. Yeah
flying
Rapidly flying rapidly like Superman
Yeah, it's flapping running down the street flapping your arms. Yeah, I think we have I think I
Yeah taking a blonde woman up to the Empire State Building you're swatting down prepare propeller
And then kind of like dry humping the Chrysler building yeah
That's yeah
Uh-huh laying a lot of eggs laying tons of eggs is only in New York. Mm-hmm
digging digging holes becoming a spider in the earth yeah becoming a spider man
yo he's digging holes in the earth only in New York and he's like a week season
hmm like I tweak season no who's that this is a guy that walks around and just
films people and says they're part of the tweak Olympics well are they are they
I can't think of any examples of a good video he makes but they're usually very good.
I thought we were going to end up on a YouTube or Twitter only in New York video when we were
painted completely blue and somebody was filming us out of their car window.
Oh right.
Yeah.
But it never turned up.
So if anyone, I mean it's probably out there on somebody's Twitter or Instagram account
there's a video of us blue and dancing.
Dancingly blue.
I think Caleb was singing Informer by Snow.
Yeah.
That is so funny.
In the blue suit.
We were blue. It was not a suit. It was our skin was blue.
Yeah.
Ugh. Is this episode even working?
I just feel like if Caleb's not here and I'm kind of sleepy,
I'm saying things about New York City. I hate when people do that.
No, you have to say things. You're in New York City now.
Yeah.
So it's like you have to-
here's lives here and his address is is is is is not saying it he's not saying
the answer is address I mean you have to yeah we're doing a full New York
episode yeah where you only talk about New York okay here's an old man or two
energy drinks before I came here I'm I I was fully ready to have a big high
energy episode and then this little sleepy guy comes in I'm very sad to work
York until one am last night after the reason I'm recording this early is
because I have to go back to work at a art department thing. I have to place
and remove stickers off of windows for only in your could that be a job? Yeah,
I actually was thinking that the art job yeah, it was in Cornell Tech on
Roosevelt Island. Well,
one am peeling a huge stickers of a window and I was like this is New York.
I'm always going to remember New York.
I used to go to Times Square as a kid, but this is what it's really about.
It's stickers, yeah. Peeling stickers on an island.
Where's that island? I don't know anything about New York.
Roosevelt Island is the one that you get to on that big ferry thing.
So sad.
Or not the ferry, but the gondola.
So it's an island?
The gondola.
Yes, there's an island on New York City.
Wait, there's an island here?
Yeah, there's an island in between Brooklyn and Manhattan.
I had no idea how similar New York was to Hawaii.
Yes.
Yeah, because I think of them as complete opposites most of the time.
They call Brooklyn the Mahalo City.
No.
Well, it's because in New York, I guess now I think about it in Hawaii everyone's surfboards
and in New York everyone's skateboards.
Right.
Yeah.
And that's why they call it the Mahalo City.
And in Hawaii--
See, Brooklyn is the town and New York is the city.
Hawaii they have Stitch, but New York they have--
Hitch.
hitch hitch hitch or that I mean Hancock
Yeah, every way yeah, it's interchangeable hitching yeah, yeah people understand what you're both superheroes in their own way fuck it
I robot yep. Yeah. Oh my god. I actually did take place here in I robot when he says I'm allergic to bullshit
Do you guys think he was actually allergic to bullshit?
Are you just saying that for the movie what if he said I'm allergic to robots
robots. Sorry, I'm allergic to robots. Yeah, over and over and over supposed to
be a robot himself or he has a robot arm. He has a robot arm. I haven't seen
iRobot since I was young. I just remember he I would love to do a shopper
shot remake of iRobot with all of us play every character. I think that's
If you want every minute of that movie is fucking insane.
Yeah, yeah, I don't remember it that well.
Do you know it's the best one is where Will Smith winks to a guy
and then the the clever robot says what is nice and then he
thinks and then Will Smith goes it's a sign of trust something
a robot.
It's so funny to make that movie out of like that type of book.
yeah it's just such a great yeah yeah exactly
yeah yeah
uh... i had this is a book of by robot about by isaac asimov okay i mean it's
the same thing but it is no that i guess the main difference i guess what i mean
is it's crazy to put will smith in that movie yeah yeah is what i mean by the
trial of boston that to you know plays all the robots
as that shia labeouf
i don't think so
I don't know.
Shia LaBeouf, he gets a robot for his birthday.
You're thinking of Transformers.
He gets a robot for his birthday, then Megan Fox fixes it for him.
Those movies are so good.
Right?
Yeah.
Do you know what we need to-- Will Smith is a big truck, a big red and
blue truck.
Right.
Right, yeah.
I think I remember him now.
I think I remember that.
And the way that Michael Bay does like needle drops in those movies is so
incredible and every movie needs to be doing that just playing the first like
ten seconds of a song just five times throughout the movie is every time like
like I think it's a second or third one where you know I mean every all the
first three have a Linkin Park song. Yeah, I always play everyone knows that
but in the second or third one done not that what I've done what I second one
know what I've done is the first one and then it's new divide and then it's some
some song some newer. I think the when it plays at the at the credits of the
first one incredible
yeah. Oh my God,
but the in either the second or third one, they also they played the intro to
green days, twenty one guns. They play it like three or four times and they
never play the song. They only play the
they just like you start. They always just start to fade it in and then it
like fades out again before the song starts. Remember the guitar solo in 21
guns how it sounds exactly like the full house theme song? Yeah I could have never connected that.
Yeah.
Dude that song bangs though. Oh my god Green Day at their best. They had some song by the
the band him in the Transformers movie and then that when I was a kid that
made me want to see it because I was like whoa yeah whoa that was Michael
Bay has a him song this movie that's fucking awesome and then they don't ever
play it it's just on the soundtrack yeah that was me but for a Megan Fox yeah I
was just giant robots and I remember I used to go see all that because the
Transformers movies would all come out around July fourth. Yeah, it's my
birthday, so i'd always go see them for my birthday and i remember one year one
of them like my friend was like was like like i heard when this move like on the
opening night of this movie when they showed megan fox on in on the screen,
all the men in the audience cheered.
It's like i wonder if that's going to happen again. I really thought that was
going to be like a very obvious lie story. Children tell, but of course that
story is one hundred percent true. It's not even worth lying about the
funniest part of that is like how do you know it like who would have told him
that you know what I mean another boy, but who is there probably is yes yeah
probably is dad says like yeah, I fucking started cheering. I saw boobs
no honey everyone cheered.
It was all the men gonna be a star. I'm when they took out Megan Fox and they
in the strange woman. They put in strange blondie who turned out to be a decepticorn. Yeah, it
was strangely odd, but spoilers much, spoilers much, Pluto TV plays all the first three Transformers
movies basically on loop, like all day, and I've just been catching like just like five
minutes of each movie at a time. The last like three I watched only the Transformers
scenes. Yeah? Yeah. The fifth one is like actually incredible. Yeah. I did not expect it. Is
not expected where they say Harriet Tubman was a auto bot yeah a night of
wit wiki. Okay, actually that might be yeah, no that's the that's the fifth
one that's the one where they have Sir Anthony Hopkins yeah and more
wallberg and he's like I think I found it. You know what mark wallberg some
characters name is
is clark cade yeager. Oh,
and then tj miller gets switch by
yeah, if it is, there's they have like they have like he's they have I
forget there's a super British character is like a really obnoxious British
name to yeah and I can't remember what the name is something like honestly
something like that some and then yeah saying any English name with the
expectation that there's going to be a last name yeah,
but so they have cade yeager the American and this British person and
then there's a and then there's a super there's a French auto button. His
his name is hot rod. There's a French Autobot and his name is Subaru.
The transformer should just be named, should just be named the name of the cars or vehicles.
There's that transformer. There's that one transformer that's like she's a spider woman
and they'd in the cartoons they draw her like like uh...
very scantily clad
I was reading about this. I don't think she's a spider woman, I think that's Arcee and she's just a normal
she's a motorcycle. No, there's a woman who's like... Oh, you're talking about Beast Wars where they
transform into creatures.
I don't know but... Well, just think about it for one second because it's vehicles for the most part
and you probably wouldn't have a spider woman. And then Beast Wars that turn to beasts. There's a spider woman and they one of the...
Are you watching Spider-Man? They took one of the animators to a strip club for
inspiration of that character and then he drew her crazy he drew a crazy nude
holy crap what if this stripper had eight legs like this bug I'm he just keeps
drawing this spider they staring at and they're like no we brought you you can
look at a spider anywhere like this it's a strip club please look around take
inspiration from other it's a house and he draws like a spider a spider again
when it's holding a dollar bill. Yeah, it's a spider hole. I would hate that
I would hate if I went to the strip club pole. Yeah,
there are some transformers that just transform into oh yeah. When the first
movie came out, they made robots that transform into meteors for the first
scene where they're all coming down into space and I remember thing is a
rock. I remember obsessively watching transformers toy reviews of the new
by this guy matrix prime who still does it and I remember him reviewing one of the
ones that transforms into a meteorite he just goes it's a decent toy I can't
imagine a child reaching for this toy in a pile of other toys but it does
transform pretty nicely and the coloring isn't so bad even though it's mostly
gray all right see you next time. How short was the review 30 seconds? No all of his
reviews were eight minutes he would begin by talking about the vehicle form
transform. He would talk about the paint and then he would say,
let's transform. Let's
that's so awesome. I yeah, I there should be more transformers.
There's like a plank of wood. Yeah, a single wheel. Is it
opt of or Megatron used to be a gun? Yeah, I know. That's so
cool on for you guys. I was talking about. Yeah, we probably
talked about transformers before. I have so many maybe I
taught we talked about this one too, but you know the Dracula
transformer. No, there's a transformer who's just Dracula and his name is
Dracula's wow and he's he just has a cape and he looks like Dracula for just
like I'm talking about like ten years of my life. I just would go on the
computer and look at transformers video reviews and go to transformers web like
I remember my parents and I went on a vacation to like Cosmo or Cancun Mexico
and I just stayed no transformers here. I stayed by the hotel pool and just
to the same website which was Star Wars
Transformers.hazbroke.com. Dude, the website
they have like the I remember that one
you could have them like the animated
gifs of them transforming and just like
yeah it's like Darth Vader transforming into the
Death Star or something. There was one
where you could like take the action
figures and put them onto like a
battlefield and they would walk around
in stop-motion I would do that all the
time. So cool. I just looked up the
spider woman and there are two options
here you could either be talking about
about a rack ned or black arachnia. I think it's black arachnia black
arachnia look up. She doesn't like me like she doesn't look like the face
she's
purple on the body and face yeah. She doesn't look like she was drawn from a
strip club. Really it up look it up. I'm looking at her right now. Look up
black arachnia strip club moment
black or a king through the I'm scrolling through the week. He pays for
black arachnia let's see notes yeah I I'm not seeing I guess I didn't roll up
black arachnia stripper moment did you guys ever get like a very like like you
felt disgusting for getting an erection as a child like did you ever become hard
at a very obviously disgusting thing I'll start okay so a story yeah there
was a there was one episode of Futurama where Zoidberg is like kissing his
like another crab and they're like making out and their weird mandibles are just like
slurping it's played for complete disgust like all the other characters are like
"UGH!" I remember getting like an enormous burn. From Zoidberg kissing another woman who
looks like Zoidberg. From two Zoidbergs kissing. Yeah that was one I think I have about two or three more
There was one where I was like 19 years old, like I was an adult at this point and I was
working in Starbucks and I was like extremely, I was in like a very lonely, almost schizophrenic
phase. This was when I was like trying to fight off my genetic predisposition for schizophrenia
and I was just sitting in Starbucks at like 7 a.m. where it's very, very dead at the cash
register not doing any tasks that you're supposed to do when you're waiting for customers to
to come in and a fly flew into my face and I got hard.
Was there any thought to it?
It was a pure reflex or did you think about something when the fly?
So long I hadn't been touched in like ten months by anyone.
That's an exaggeration, but it was a long time since I had been touched by anyone in
a definite way.
And a fly touching you.
And a fly flew into my face.
I won't say that I got hard, but you know how when your penis like pulses yeah,
how it does that little like yeah, like there's a pulse that goes through yeah,
that's what happened to me then in that moment. Oh, and then I think a cat in an
episode of cat dog, an alien blows a fart bubble. I know that one's
I would completely believe that that last one. I don't think it's true. I do
remember thinking, oh my God,
So I do think there is an episode of cat dog where an alien is is threatening to
give cat dog a big sloppy kiss and I thought that doesn't sound so bad. Maybe
that had an accompanying erection. Yeah yeah I remember being really disgusted
by when I was playing what is which game is it I think it's Yoshi's Island some
it's a Yoshi game for the Game Boy and there's a boss fight where a frog
swallow shrinks you down and swallows you and I was like this is the most
disgusting thing I've ever seen. It's like a, the screen goes, it's like a circle of
like the frog's stomach and you have, and it's swallowing stuff and you have to, and
then you have to like turn the stuff it's swallowing into eggs and throw it at the uvula
of the frog and the like whole stomach is like jiggling around and I was like, this is not
okay. Yeah, they need to take this out of the game. I don't know. I don't know anything
that I've ever been really disgusted. Well, like maybe like poop stuff. I've been completely
I mean I'm thinking of stuff of childhood stuff.
Oh, childhood stuff?
I mean, this didn't happen yesterday.
Also, this isn't a story about nasty things, it's a story about...
Well, I'm not sure, I don't really have a catalogue in my brain of what I've got a boner
from that was weird.
You don't have like developmental moment boners?
Not that I...
Maybe meat spin?
I'm sure there were a...
Maybe when I saw meat spin as a kid.
I'm sure there were, I had plenty of Zoidberg moments, but I just don't remember them.
I'm not trying to say I don't have them, but I didn't have them, but I don't, I don't, I
you can't really keep track of the media
i'm not going to have a partner in your brain
mark i was a remember the fact that i have a
uh...
you know you did get a boner at that moment it's like all jesus christ if i
was running away from the t_v_ i guess that makes sense if i look up so i'd
break kissing right now we get a boner again
i mean i i definitely have never revisited it because
way can be as as sexy in my well here's zoidberg kissing a human woman all right
i'm hard completely future on my interspecies kiss zoidberg x mary ann on
deviantart zoidberg kisses uh lobster a good person there's like a girl search
girl zoidberg whoa look at this whoa i bet it's from that episode could be the
episode's called why must i be a crustacean in love whoa look at this
the
the females that were that we're talking about. Oh, no, we're
talking about this one. Look at her. I remember that one. Everyone
look her up. Her name is Edna
and if anyone can find a video of Zoidberg kissing a Zoidberg,
just send it to Pierce. I'm trying to like
like those shock sites that they had as a kid. I never got maybe
like meat spin was so tame compared to all the other ones.
was just poor just a wiener yeah it's just a wiener there's nothing wrong with a
wiener it's barely shocking but in the other ones on the like lol shock website
we're like okay this is this is three guys one hammer there's a guy getting
his face beaten in with a hammer yeah and then this one is a guy putting a jar
in his asshole yeah I don't know maybe attitudes have just changed as I've
gotten older yeah it's not zoidberg kissing lady zoidberg I think it's fry
Fry getting sort of molested by a female void bird.
That's honestly what- He's got like slimy tentacles.
Oh god, ew. Yeah. Yeah, that's not nice.
And Fry is frowning. Frowning Fry.
And he's supposed to be who you're identifying with.
They don't show a close up of his pants stretching with sexual lust.
they show him saying shut up this honestly is making it I I'm not glad I
wish I hadn't seen that because in my brain you you popped a boner literally
just from a close-up of two like tentacle faced lobsters kissing each
other but now that I've seen that it's a fake cartoon woman with lingerie on I
think yeah it's kind of ruined for me also look someone did a fan art of her
Oh my god.
They should have Zoidbergs.
What if they discovered aliens tomorrow and it was Zoidbergs?
If it was Zoidbergs, I'd probably laugh my fucking head off.
Yeah, he has some funny quotes.
I'd probably be like, "Hoh hoh."
Why is my microphone popping?
I don't know.
It's popping?
It's making a pop sound.
Yeah, I can hear it on this.
Oh my gosh, it's crazy.
We got to buy a new XLR. Yeah, we have to buy a bunch of new XLRs. This is the one
that works though, supposedly. Why don't we throw out the ones that don't work? I
mean I put all the ones that don't work in the same place, but then they keep
getting mixed up because other people move them around. I want to sit down and
test them all in a row because I'm also not sure it could be a microphone thing
or a recorder thing. We should just put a piece of tape on it. I basically want to hire a tester to test
everything for me. Interesting. Yeah, that's basically a tester. Do you guys
think you would be do a good job as a poison taste tester? I don't think I
would. No? I don't think I would because I'd probably eat the poison and then I
would die from it. That's a good poison taste tester. That's one who's good at it.
Because then the king won't eat the thing you ate. Anyone else sick of the
fucking king asking you to taste his food? Not me, I don't mind at all. Yeah, we
should politely ask him to stop doing that mm-hmm that'd be awesome if we got
if we maybe I think maybe the king I think maybe instead of asking the king
maybe we just go and cut the middleman out and just ask people to stop putting
poison in the food and aren't you guys sick of the middleman I hate the
fucking middleman and the little man yeah and I remember the medieval man's
the worst man I remember going to Trader Joe's once with my with my mom as a kid
and they had some ad or some sign or branding or something that said like cut
out the middleman on it. That was the first time I had heard that phrase. It's
like who is the middleman? Who is he? What's he doing with the food? What he's
got all the other food at the other grocery stores but at Trader Joe's they
don't have him. Yeah. They don't have the middleman. I don't know what the
middleman does he must increase the food's value somehow. Yeah.
He must be some sort of value increaser. He sprinkles, he puts on special dust
that's worth a lot of money. Yeah, right. Yeah. They say that every time a
product changes hands, it decreases in value, but the middleman is special
because he increases it. Yeah. Imagine getting a job as a middleman and
you're also an eBay real reseller damn him that you're making a shit ton of money
I actually worked as a middleman for a long time yeah yeah it sucks so bad
where's the job and I can't talk about it all cuz I'm still under NDA damn yeah
they don't let you tell anyone what you do to the things to make them different
yeah to make the things different because it's not all food yeah there's
is it and I'm close to violating my NDA here, but it's things not food.
There's all sorts of different things and stuff happens.
Aren't you guys sick of the the Queen and the Princess to I actually hate
them more than the King. I don't know. I think the Princess is okay.
I hate her. He has a crush on the Prince. I don't have a crush on the
Princess. I seriously don't have a crush on the Princess. No, she's just
nice. She's just nice to me and know everyone else is like you're a lowly
serving boy she's nice to everyone she's the princess yes that's why she's cool
if you don't want to marry her but i don't have a crush on her not the
princess sending me secret messages
the princess is sending me very secret nonverbal messages that she wants to
mate with me she wants to have my baby
i'm actually down as fuck with the town hoe
bro the town.
The town harlot, the town,
yeah, oh my God, I mean the town harlot is not for me hub and we get a
tankard of ale
bro and then and then I can't say what happens next on the show. The town,
the town courtesan is not for me because I want my baby to have some kind of
political power. Yeah, yeah, so I have that's why I have a crush on the bro. I
I don't care. I want the town hoe.
(laughter)
Bro, bro, do not even leave me in the same room with the town hoe and take me to jail.
Because we're going to get up to something bad.
Yeah, I'm going to put you guys in jail.
Why?
I don't know.
Because I'm committing adultery with the town hoe.
Are you married?
Yes.
Or is the town hoe married? Who are you married to?
The queen.
(laughter)
Okay, well then can I have your daughter's hand in marriage? No, okay,
but you can if you bring me the town ho as a dowry. If you bring me the town
ho and a tankard of ale
and leave us in a room, well, you leave us for seven minutes in heaven.
I should just marry the town ho yeah. I just want to settle down with the town
Yeah, yeah, why don't you want to settle down town hoe her name is town hoe her
name is it's not that she is the town hoe but also her name is town hoe. I can fix
her. I can fix the town hoe. With a magic spell. I can fix the enchanted witch. Oh
dude the town hoe. Oh my god she's bad. Dude the town hoe just showed me her ankle and
I'm so fucking hard it's it's it's poking my god city belt she showed she just
lifted I heard a dress and I could smell straw I heard a dunk on my metal chastity
belt because I saw the town hose ankle I would seriously go to war for the town
town. Oh the the town caliph is
threatening to make me renounce my God Christ.
Yeah,
the town Viking is wearing a hat with horns on it.
Not the town Viking riding in a boat like a dragon. Oh dude.
The town barbarian is laying waste and siege to my horse. The town Trojan is
about to get... no wait the Trojan... I hear movement in the town Trojan. I hear movement
inside of it. The town Trojan is just a guy with people inside of him. Like a possum. Yeah.
Pasa mommy carries his babies or like a kangaroo. Yeah. Yeah, like a kangaroo. Maybe the town kangaroo is hopping
It's jumping he's hopping pouch Lee
Pouch Lee hopping I would love to live in a town where there's one of everything. Yeah. Yeah, there's a town kangaroo
I do baby Viking Brooklyn true Brooklyn. I do sick all these kangaroos hopping around Brooklyn, New York. Oh
where you get they hop and they got their boxing gloves on and they run up to you
and they try to fight you. They try to, these kangaroos are trying to knock out
people.
They're really good at it.
And they're so good at it. They sit on their tail and they kick you with your
feet.
Yeah.
Like Sheila from Spyro.
A lot of people would think when they see a kangaroo with boxing gloves, they'd be
more scared because they think the kangaroo is about to punch me. I would be
less scared because I know kangaroos without boxing gloves also punch and
they have sharp claws. Yeah, I would actually prefer if they put boxing gloves
on their on their fucking feet.
Mm-hmm. Who was it? So because it doesn't hurt so bad then maybe? Dead ass.
Who is it? It was Mussolini used to like give tigers a bunch of like sleeping
pills or something and then wrestle them. That sounds cool.
I didn't. Am I remembering that correctly? I have no idea. Awesome.
My friend said that his grandfather had a tiger in his attic.
Tigress?
Ooh, a tigress.
Cheetah.
Oh my god, cheetah. Was she in the Wonder Woman movie?
Yeah, played by Kristen Wiig.
Kristen Wiig played cheetah? Was she funny?
I think she might have been a little bit funny.
Was she a funny cheetah woman?
I never saw it.
Oh, no, she wasn't funny. I think she was strange.
She was strange? I didn't see it. I watched a clip and they...
I would have said she was feline or feral.
feral that's what that's the adjective I would have wouldn't she there's like a
scene of her eating a bunch of Doritos or something oh sounds funny to me
there's like a scene of her eating Doritos or sorry maybe I'm just
remembering that there is a Wonder Woman Doritos bag or maybe Wonder Woman had a
collab with Doritos or maybe I was thinking of Doritos and then I thought
of Wonder Woman yeah that must be it or maybe it's because I was thinking cheetah
Dorito like as if it rhymed. Holy fuck. Yeah. If only there was like a cool big
cat with sunglasses whose name rhymed with Doritos. Yeah like
Desta Dorito. Desta? Dustin Dorito. Yeah okay so he's Dustin Dorito.
Dustin Dorito doesn't really rhyme with Dorito. He's not a cheetah.
does Chester doesn't rhyme with Cheeto I thought his name was oh yeah his name is
Chester what did you think it was Cheeto no appears that's the food no that's
actually our 40 50 thinking yeah the okay what's up and Pierce thought that
the food was called Chester's thank you there are bags that say Chester's puffs
I've seen them there are bags that say that yeah yeah big not official bags but
yeah they've written there's at the gym there's bags that say Chester's there is
a bag at my gym that says do not smell do not smell Chester's Chester's smell
and so I'm thinking about Dustin Dorito though I think that's a really have I
think we yeah that is that is big what kind of animal is lying or you know a
lion okay cuz I guess yeah Tony the Tiger is taken yeah Esther Cheeto there's not
really a lion man why is there a lion mascot and plus he's a lion he's the king
of the jungle he could also have a crown made of Doritos
now that would look good yeah a crown made of Doritos is actually really
Dorito the king of Doritos Doritos ever have a mascot he's Dustin Dorito the
king of cheese that's a long name mm-hmm well so that's it's gonna swing
back his wife and his wife darling oh my god his wife Darlene Dorito the the
queen of all the readers mascot
what is it it's a dragon
what's it's a fucked up dragon that looks like a gremlin holy shit
dragon character of the readers his name is just rag and
traces named as trip with the fuck it
yes name is dragon
trading when i was a feeling this is
world okay that's mister corn
why did they have a dragon for jury does because of them
dragon character of the readers is one of the through the though production cases
where every bits of details demands extremely elaborated hard work from
intricate labor of merging plus two wings or nails
teeth are vacuum press now sir three printed we can be proud to declare that
there's maybe no similar one to be compared considering loyalty on original
design and comfort comfort ability of acting this is on mascot dot com the
mascot with a k right let's see is like a polish mascot
Yeah, in Poland they're just making mascots for brands without being asked.
Whoa!
Why are they- what the fuck?
They're assembling the shell and- oh my god, it's a little person!
It's a little person as a Dorito.
Oh my god, because it's a baby dragon.
Yeah, but what does baby dragons have to do with Doritos?
Oh my god.
What?
This is so crazy.
I think-
I really do think that no one asked them to do this and they thought maybe there was a contest or something.
I think maybe this... Okay, I think the dragon is just named Dorito.
Oh, that... Well...
I think this is just a dragon named Dorito.
But what is he the mascot for?
It says, "Dorito's Hot Wave Baby Dragon Mascot."
Interesting. Oh, this music is great.
This is so crazy.
Whoa, look at that other mascot head they have on there.
I want to look at the other mascot.
They look like they just got the shells for like Barney characters.
Look at these diagrams.
Wow.
No, yeah, it is a Doritos mascot.
Look, they have pictures of him with Doritos bags.
Yeah, heat.
Heat burst and heat wave.
I really like this picture of him just holding out his arms.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
This is it.
We should buy this costume.
Can you buy it?
I don't think so.
think any of us are small enough to fit in that cost. We'll figure it out. We'll do
alterations. We should commission this company. To make a Dorito. Maybe we make a
Big Sullivan. That would be so sick. That would be cool. They have really nice
mascots. They made a bunch of mascots. They made mascots for Bonita Bee.
For masks. Oh they made some Masked Singer. Wow the Cobra one's cool.
Orange Fox, Madonna, Professor, Mirror Man. Hillary. They have a cheetah. We could
maybe come to them about about about dusting to read or the king of cheese.
Maybe you should be the king of the jungle of cheese and then he lives in a
jungle of cheese. Jungle of cheese is a jungle made entirely of cheese,
king of the jungle of cheese and through the jungle of cheese is a school
ranch river. Cool ranch river will be sick. I just think the jungle of cheese
is such a good idea. Yeah, yeah, a whole jungle made of cheese and the vines
are string cheese right. The trees are okay. What other Doritos flavors are
there there's the purple flavor spicy sweet chili right that doesn't really
have a cheese angle but no but it does have a chill the what about pepper yes
so what is pepper so what if the peppers are actually peppery Doritos yeah well
what do it maybe penguin pepper the penguin pepper the penguin in a jungle
yeah that's he got he got lost that could be his whole characters thing is he got
lost on the way to the flame penguin to pepper Antarctica oh yeah I guess as
long as creatures are getting lost we could do whatever we want this jungle
well that's yeah that's every every smart writer about pepper the porcupine
that's yeah or what's another door other than those maybe pepper snake a
pepper snake well or we could have a king cobra a corner all in it's all royalty a
a corn snake and it's a corn chip
that's a yeah
according to him
that's perfect okay
what other to read a look at the list of the reader flavors right now and i'm just
trying to think we're getting through the whole list of this cast of
characters what is their time to think about like what what is the actual like
greenery of this forest what it's she's made out of cheese so i think that is
cheese leaves cheese trees yellow or orange or white 3d guy yeah oh they do
have Doritos 3d yeah it can be like a Waldo see graphic Doritos air flame and
hot cool ranch yeah that doesn't make much sense to me well I think those are
you know these are like tertiary Dorito care so just to get the main ones out of
the way I mean I'm just on the Doritos products scroll down scroll down and I
don't want to talk about 3d crunch so I think the staples are cool ranch cheese
and spicy sweet chili. Ooh, the dinamita. That's interesting. Those must be sort of the trunks. Oh, and spicy nacho. Yeah.
See, and they have simply organic white cheddar flavored tortilla chips.
I think that that, maybe that is like, um, though. Well, the main, the main cast of characters here is, is. Maybe that's like an airplane.
No, but I have a good idea for a side character for the simply organic white cheddar flavored tortilla chips.
Maybe it's a Karen. It's like, it's like a, yeah, it's a British guy. Okay. It's like a Brit,
it's a Jane Goodall type came to the jungle of cheese to research it and he
goes it's simply organic that is awesome British and he's and it's he's made he
got covered in white cheddar right and I guess the white cheddar and his name is
basil cheddar oh okay so this is good he's like a animatronic in like a sort
of Disney ride and yeah that's welcome to the jungle of cheese simply organic
simply organic yeah. We began with a simply organic chip and yeah,
you want to everyone in the everyone in the ride gets a little so it's a right
now. I thought this was like a brand world character is doing a brand to
work. Yeah, no, I just thought we were until you said that a character is
saying something that there's a commercial and what do you mean is
there commercials and stuff right like Tony the Tiger says it's great. That
doesn't mean he has to be a ride.
So look you're you're on a ride and everyone gets a
one. This is Doritos the right
it
to move it in the cheese
and by the end of a custom chip, just like yeah, because it's
just like in disney's star wars lightsaber.
You start with like a chip base. You choose a chip base from you
can either you can get that from the corn chip snake or the
tortilla chip right right you have to on rails so that every
stop you get a choice and then it's one corner in one of three dips and then you
also get the powder at the end right it should all be it should all be powder
yeah I think I think it's a chip powder yeah did I tell you guys about the time
that I got a bag of chips in my cafeteria and we were all touching it
because it felt gooey on the inside it was Doritos so we didn't open it and
like everyone was like what it was like heavier than a normal bag of Doritos and
it felt really good on the inside and then we opened it and it was two chips
and just a ton of dust like all flavor dust and two chips.
Whoa, that's incredible.
You should have saved the dust.
I have a really good, I have a mix and match idea.
What's that?
Um, that we, this factories, it's a factory idea for any factory owners.
Switch out, switch out, switch out the dust between Doritos and Sour Patch Kids and see
what happens.
Yeah, they should have a mix up at the two factories.
A mix up.
why why did Doritos cool rancher look like why are they green when I think of
ranch I don't think of that color it's the jungle it's due to the jungle it's
the ranch River the ranch the river rancher is it's for the green color is
from algae in the ranch oh my god and the red is from the blood of the enemies
the enemies of the red is from the lipstick from the queen of the
jungle yeah that's like that that's the plot twist as you get you get to a
clearing and and the like trees the cheese trees kind of part as you're
turning the corner and it's a giant castle yeah they should just call the
trees palm cheese there we go yeah yeah what's a jungle. I don't think they
necessarily be palm she oh in the desert. Oh that's what do you get the
dry Dorito that's hot and the dust is sand yeah. Oh my God. This is a spin
off ride. Yeah, you can either go in the jungle of cheese or the desert of
desolation. Yeah, and it's the hottest desert on Earth and you dip it in the
sand, which is really all the sand is flavor third degree burn. Yeah, spice
cactus. Calvin Cactus Calvin is your guide there and he says it's simply
organic. He's the brother of of basil. Yeah, see I'm wondering
because okay, so we've got Dustin Dorito, the king of the
jungle of cheese, the king of the jungle of cheese, then we
have his wife,
Darlene, the town, ho the town, ho of cool Ranch River, yeah,
and then the the king Cobra is the we didn't think of his name.
- Pepper the King Cobra, spicy sweet chili.
- King Cornbra.
- The corn chips, and then he has that whole title
in parenthesis, a corn chip snake.
- A corn chip snake.
- I really want to get that in there.
- Yeah, he is just venom flavored.
- Yeah, there's one thing that you do,
if you dip it in, it will poison your chip and you will die.
So do not, and the ride, they're like,
watch out for the King Cobra,
don't dip your chip in his bowl.
yeah only mean boys eat poison chips.
They feed it to their sisters and a few yeah a few times a year. People are like
they're probably i'm going to be nasty i'm going to dip my chip in the king
cobra's bowl is a bowl yeah is a bowl you get a bowl yeah you get a bowl for
your chips
with a regular salsa yeah and then at the end you don't get to eat your chip,
you get to buy a picture of it at a
kiosk. Yeah, you get to take a picture
that's a safety measure in case the any
of the poison gets onto the chip.
You don't want people seeing you.
I remember this kid at my high school
posted a picture of just like Doritos
covered in cheese in his microwave
and he just with the caption,
"I'm a fucking genius!"
We need to carve out some space at this
entirely Doritos themed theme park
for a Taco Bell area where they have
the Doritos Locos Tacos.
wait oh the Doritos the Taco Bell area should be like a Taco Bell when you're
done with the ride you can go to go to Taco Bell get a drink oh my god when you
order at the Taco Bell in a bell so you don't get to eat your chip at the
end of the ride you get your picture printed out of the chip when you order a
Taco Bell you hand them the picture of the chip you designed and they can make
that into a shell for your time make that a specialized taco yeah it has a
there's a code on the back that they scan with a code reader. Yep, they
have a code reader at the Taco Bell. This scans the chip code and that
way they can also protect against poison getting in the food right. I
guess I would like maybe every fast food restaurant to be in the jungle
yeah, and it has different. They you can eat each one of you have to
choose where you're taking your chip basically right like I can go to
mcdonald's and I could give them and they'll make my chip into a fry
I make it into a whole Doritos Locos Taco or you can eat it turns it into
well. You get multiple come on come on. Obviously, you get multiple fries
right. You get a whole order of fries. It's a batch. Yeah, Burger King also a
fry a chicken fry when these you also get a fry right as I'm just thinking of
like you know in the box a taco taco. Yeah, five guys is a fry five guys is a
a fry yeah del taco is a fry inside a
burrito yep a California style burrito
yep. I hop you can't you can't use it
there. No you can't know you do that you
think it would be a so maybe you would
think it would be a hash brown or a fry
at I hop, but they don't accept it. It's
something with their contract. They say
we don't say we don't have want to buy a
code scanner at I we're kind of keeping
costs low. We don't really like having
code scanners around at I hop and then you can swim in a cheese river yeah yeah
and you get to see it's a blue it's like a pool where they instead of dying it
blue they die yellow oh it's a lazy river it's a circular lazy river it's
filled completely with liquid cheese it's really hot you get in you're covered
in cheese you're like okay that was a fun novelty thing to do they have showers
there I'm gonna go shower the showers are also cheese mm-hmm and you can never get
get clean and then you when you're trying to leave when you try to leave the
theme park. They say you can't leave because you're taking our cheese with
you. You have to leave the cheese at the door and you're like well. Can I rinse
the cheese off and they're like no, then yeah, give you a chip. They give you one
just to scrape it off yeah yeah to spray it off to scrape it. That's the worst
thing about going to like an amusement park as a kid or as an adult, ripping
cheese off your body. It's scraping all the cheese off. Yeah. When you go to an amusement
park as an adult or like a, I don't know, like a great wolf lodge and then you realize
like oh yeah, there's like, it's just kind of depressing here. Yeah. It's not as magical
as it was when I was a kid. So maybe this park can have a lot of stuff for, like awesome
stuff for adults. Yeah, maybe a beer ride build your own beer.
My God,
I want to go to be your world and you can pick you pick the
liquid and then you pick the bubbles.
You get to pick any beer.
Yeah, there's a lot of picture taken with the Rolling Rock
horse. Oh my God. Yeah, that's something we're going to have to figure out is if
the beer animals can coexist with the chips animals in the jungle or if we
need to kind of coordinate off. It does beer world have its own separate place.
It's the same theme park, but it has two entrances based on if you're going with
your family or not. Okay, so if you're taking your kids, you can trick them
into thinking you're going to only Doritos, Doritos Dominion. But if you
Doritos Dominion!
Wow!
Holy crap!
It's Justin Dorito!
The king of the jungle of cheese!
And his wife, the town hoe!
Wow! Dorito!
Yeah, but they have a hotel there too.
The town hoe-tel!
yeah oh it's the town hotel yeah yeah it's themed after the time you get
fucking yeah it's a cock sucking hotel they have a harlot in every room when
you're renting TV Harlote and pay to not watch porn on that hotel TV damn I gotta
to pay you to watch the news and their continental breakfast. Okay, they have
they have baked hotatoes and they have chicken brothel.
Those are the only foods that they serve. They have hard boner eggs.
Yeah, it's like when you your boner hits her. Yeah, and you dip those and come
and yes firms are here are they did that completely in jesus are you have
parkman that's gonna sexy
uh...
yeah i don't know if you have a little bit of this really quick and then they
and then they have
and then they have and then they have and then if you leave the food on you get
sperm germs
right always
uh... i think when i get sperm germs are they get sperm germs and you get to
is
your toe yeah and then you leave her your wife full or wife, wife, which is a
waffle
yeah. Don't tell your wife. Oh, don't tell your Belgian wife.
It's your Belgian wife that you are having a secret affair, a fair ground
yeah all's fair in a fairground hotel.
Tell no wife
all's fair in glove a glove used to eat the food, which is in glove and warm
applesauce right warm applesauce to meet with a glove. Yes, that well the town
was going to town on your whole shit on your whole dick
uh... no
okay well that's the town hotel
that's the town hotel and that's the end of the episode that's the end of
sausage sausage
yeah
yeah um that's that alright bye
bye