You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
Yeah, yeah, take another bite of the sandwich that made you run out of the room.
Yeah, do that.
Pierce got a gas station sandwich and right before we started,
He turned into Darth Vader voice and had to leave the room because the sandwich was attacking
him.
The sandwich was punching out at him like a xenomorph.
Every single time I eat, I take really big bites, I don't chew and then I start to chew.
Nice.
You need to relearn how to eat.
It's so funny to identify that as a thing that happens every time you eat and do nothing
about it.
I'm always so hungry.
Have you ever tried?
I'm always so hungry to eat.
How long do you wait between meals?
Have you tried chewing before?
It's only breakfast.
It's only when I - it's like when I sleep in until -
Wait, it's only breakfast?
Oh, I'm kind of the same way.
That's like why I don't like breakfast.
It's only breakfast.
Breakfast for some reason your brain can't think of taking smaller bites.
I'm so hungry in the morning.
Because you've been working up an appetite all night.
Exactly.
I sleep in until noon.
Do you like - are you like hiking?
I sleep in until noon and then I have like a fried chicken lunch for my first meal.
to me and I eat such big pieces of fried chicken mmm I'm drinking oh yeah what
time is it over there it's like 11 let's do that again
Pierce just dreams all night of running on a treadmill I dream of being chased
by my high school drama teacher dreams of a doctor taking all the food out of
of his stomach surgically and then he wakes up and he's like, "Fuck, I'm so empty."
Better not chew.
Mm-hmm.
I'm chewing now.
Do you sleep in late normally?
Like when do you wake up today?
I kept waking up, I probably like got up at around 9 or 10.
And is that early or late for you?
It's fine for me.
That's fine.
It's normal.
Yeah, that's okay for you.
I've been waking up at like 630 every day. No control over it. Yeah. Yeah, that was happening for me to me for a while
I was waking up at 7 and then just showering and
Playing video games through three hours before I started my day. Yeah, I felt like I was smarter than everyone else
Yeah, when you wake up early you are like, oh I fucking rock like even if you do nothing, you're just like, oh, I
Want to know this is free. Yeah, you just get some extra hours
Being a lot I used to I woke up at like 4 a.m. Every day. I think the parts do
Wow, that's how we have man. Yeah
Before before the Sun comes up exactly before homeroom. That's awesome, dude
A15 you walk and you walk onto the school bus and people could just tell yeah
There's an air because you're wearing a goofy costume
Sword
Receipt of your ps3 trophy
Yeah, and he was mad yeah, and to get back at you he dropped you off at school
To get back at you he drank
If you if you're applying to be a school bus driver that you have to hate kids because you have to hate them enough to
Take them to school, which is like the worst
There's a citizenship they give you a they give you a test it's like there's 30 kids on your bus. Where do you take?
They give you like a doll and then whatever you do to the doll that's how they hire
Yeah, if you take him to school, you're the bus driver. Yeah, what do you mean? That's how they hire you
Like if you fuck the doll they fuck you back
That's the job well, yeah, so if you hire the doll you hire the doll
They give you a doll and you drive it to school.
It's in your blood.
Like a bus driver.
Yeah.
They have someone waiting at the school with a sign that says you're hired.
But if you take the doll to the trampoline park, they hire you as cool uncle.
Yeah, they give you some nephew.
you yeah you cigarettes if you suck the dolls dick do they suck your dick or do
they make you suck their that's sort of the old - that's why they had to stop the
program because people figured out that one way to play it safe is to is to 69
the doll you get you get your dick a little wet exactly just a little bit
that's you also get hired as a bus driver if you 69 because you're a problem
solver yeah but a city bus driver not a school bus driver I never rode on a bus
that was never I only know like weird charter schools growing up so I never
had a bus yeah I just walked I went to weird charter schools too and I was
always on the short bus nice I was the only one they had right mm-hmm there was
no big well yeah well the bus the bus would take me back to daycare when
school was over and that was a short bus oh yeah short bus I was a that was a the
kiss of death in elementary school if a kid got picked up for like the girls and
boys club doesn't matter as long as it's a short bus I'm gonna get you yeah yeah
yeah you're fucked yeah you're absolutely just yeah it doesn't even mean that the
short bus is the downs bus it's just that it's shorter than my bus exactly
look at my long bus yeah look at my big long bus I do remember think I remember
thinking like the girls and boys club that sounds like paradise and then I
I don't know what that is.
Girls and Boys Club is like this, it's like a thing for, it's like an after school care
thing for like kids whose parents work like 24 hours a day.
And so they would pick up like six kids from my school and take them and I was always so
jealous and I told my teacher, I was like, "Yeah, I wish I could go to the Boys and Girls
Club."
And she was like, "No, you don't because that would mean you were very poor."
(laughing)
- Okay, I guess I didn't make the cut.
- Yeah, you didn't think it through?
- No.
- Yeah, you just thought it was gonna be nasty poet.
- Yeah, yeah, I was like, "Girls and, wait,
"girls and boys?"
- Yeah, that's what's up.
- "In the same bus?"
- One time my friend's mom was giving me a ride somewhere
and it was just me and her,
and I had just gotten back from summer camp,
and she was like, "She's dead now."
- Nice. - That doesn't matter.
She was like, "Was it a co-ed camp?" and I didn't know what that meant so I just went,
"I think so."
And she was like, "It means boys and girls."
And then I was like, "Yeah, well, you know, you never know with these girls."
I don't know what I was - I don't know what I was -
I have so many memories of any time I was in the car, like as a 10 or 11 year old with
like an adult woman at some point I would think during the ride like we will have
sex. I remember going on a field trip and it was there was like not enough room in
the bus for me I so I had to ride with the teacher my teacher Miss Sullivan.
That's just what they told you dude. They just didn't want you on the bus. All the other kids on the bus
had a petition do not let Caleb ride on this bus. They all had a petition that said
Let's get Caleb Wade by the hottest teacher in school.
- But we were right, it was like to the aquarium.
And I do have a, my teacher turned on
Paralyzer by Finger Eleven.
I was like--
- That's some I'm gonna fuck.
- Yeah, yeah, and I was like,
I'm going to get my dick sucked in this car by my teacher.
I'm 11 years old.
- I had a, there was this thing
in my TV production class in high school.
we had uh...
we had to do a video for the fifth graders at one of the elementary school
like we set up a news station for them
and they all went up and they did like uh...
like their stories
and apparently they complained
uh... because it was like low quality but we were shooting it at the school
like the access center
like the town's local access center so we had to go to the school
and apologize to them because like for some reason
the
yeah they thought we were making fun of them so we had to go there and do like a big apology
thing and uh the there was like the security guard her name was terry oh she was also a
medals teacher but she drove us there and like we were talking on the bus and i guess
she like knew why we were going to the school and one of us was like laughing at something
that someone said and she just like freaked the fuck out on us like she was like screaming
something about like you know what you
fucking did you you're not supposed to be like
having fun going to this drink this
thing and then we got there and they
just complained but all the little kids
complained that it was just like low
quality they were like yeah no we didn't
really like um it was just low quality I
don't know why you guys are apologizing
this is the craziest you had to go to another school to
apologize for standard definition video
to
Well, because we, so they didn't tell us like the whole thing.
So we get there and then they tell us like, oh, the video was just kind of low
quality. And then my teacher, like once we got back, she was like,
yeah, I'm sorry guys. I don't know why we had to do that. Oh my God. Oh,
there was, so there was two video production class.
There was the juniors and the seniors. This happened when I was a junior,
my brother, Paul, who's a, he's a patron. He's going to hear this.
We can ask him his story. Yeah, we'll ask him. Yeah, we'll definitely, yeah.
But yeah, we can call him right now.
- Okay. - Yeah, I need to know.
- Get him, get him, I had to call him.
I'm gonna make sure he's not in there.
- No, I just remembered, I just remembered this
'cause like, I guess--
- No, call him, call him. - This is such an outlandish
story. - No, call him.
- I have to call him.
- I have to have-- - No, no, no, 'cause it is.
All right, so they, there was one kid named Joe.
There was one kid named Joe, and as soon as Joe walked--
- Call Joe! - Yeah, 'cause--
- Joe walked into the cafeteria.
- Where's Joe?
- As soon as Joe walked into the cafeteria,
they started chanting his name.
and he like kinda like went in like a wrestler it was very strange
he went in like a wrestler?
he went in like a wrestler
yeah like they went like
JOE!
and he walked in like high fived the kids
what?
aw man
what are you talking about?
why did I miss the end of that story?
I don't know
he high fived the kids
he high fived all the kids
I'm gonna write
like he was a wrestler
I'm gonna need to hear from Zell and Paul on this one
he's a wrestler walking out to the ring
yeah we gotta ask Paul about this
call Paul no I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm with a dog I'm with my new dog I'm treating
it like a wrestler yeah I'm teaching my new dog wrestling I was on the student
announcement team in middle school and
there's this student announcement like we
would do the morning announcement on the
TV I thought you might just announce
things to the school and you all the
announcements were like they were they
wanted to make it like its own cool
program so I got to do my own little
stand-up segments at the end where I
would like played an old it was I was
like an eighth grade and there was this
guy mr. Toto was like he walked up to me
one time at the water fountain like
during like free period and he was like
"Pierce, I just want to know what ticks you off."
You should do a show called "What Bothers Pierce"
or "What Pierce's Pierce."
(laughs)
I was like, "Okay, yeah."
- I'm just watching the Daily Show on his phone.
- You should make this at my house.
- Literally.
- You should make this show at my house with me.
Don't tell anyone.
- Yeah, and we're gonna find out what bothers you.
I'm just gonna do stuff to you
until you say this bothers me.
- We're gonna find out what ticks you off.
We're gonna work our way up until I take you off.
Yeah.
And then we'll turn the video off.
Say uncle!
Um, yeah.
Then we'll turn the video off, yeah.
But I did one like bit about how the Santa story is stupid and then like everyone on
the - all the teachers that ran the program were like, "Do you think there's any middle
schoolers who still believe in Santa?"
And I was like, "No."
And like five parents called in and were like, "Yeah, my seventh grader didn't know."
And Pierce ruined Santa.
When you say they call into your show, they call things like Morning Zoo Radio.
"Hey, first time, long time listener, first time caller, you broke into my son, Bradley,
that Santa's a real."
You said, "Fuck you."
And then I said, "Why don't you straddle your speakers and turn the bass all the way up?"
(laughter)
- Yeah.
- I wish an Opie and Anthony style talk show
in middle school would have been perfect for me.
It would have given me an outlet.
We didn't have any sort of AV program
at any schools that I went to.
They were all too poor.
We didn't have a playground,
we just had like a,
there was always a parking lot behind the school
that they would put a,
they would draw a four square.
Square.
- Awesome.
- You could play jump over the glass.
Yeah, so I, yeah.
You know, it's just how I grew up, it's not.
You play wall ball at all?
We played wall ball, we played ball wall,
we played Paul Wall, the rapper.
Yeah. Paul Walker.
We played Paul Walker until the game died.
(laughing)
Yeah.
Until the game crashed, exactly.
It's my birthday.
Woo!
It's my favorite birthday.
here is a that will do this comes out of the yesterday or the birthday
yesterday i think it would be your birthday
but just can't stop telling people it's my birthday
uh... could very excited about it
twenty three
michael jordan number
you do anything fun
non no
now a chick fil a
and in this today
and i have a lot of other how you asked me when
a chick fil a a
- Oh yeah, I'm sorry.
(laughing)
Whoops.
But no, I'm hanging out.
- Haven't you seen Super Size Me Too?
- Yeah, I actually did watch Super Size Me Too.
- You did?
- Yeah, it's so sad.
- And you still got Chick-fil-A?
- It's so sad 'cause it's just like he's just--
- Are you serious, dude?
- The first one was interesting because--
(laughing)
The first one was interesting because it was just like,
it was like, okay, yeah, people I guess don't know how--
Like, shit, that's--
How many 5,000 calories a day will actually make you kind of fat?
Eating McDonald's is bad?
Yeah, I mean that was definitely surprising at the time.
That was before people knew.
He's like, "Oh, whatever."
Everyone thought it was healthy.
There definitely wasn't the same sort of health conscious movement.
Nobody saw a fat guy say, "Meat on me hurts!"
Yeah, people thought that fat guys were just nerds back then.
Before that, they had never had a real fat guy in a movie.
It was all people acting fat.
Yeah, they had Eddie Murphy play all the fat people.
Exactly.
Yeah.
It's similar to Borat.
They never saw a documentary where someone said, "Oh my god, my stomach."
That was the first time somebody threw up on camera.
"I drank too much root beer and now my stomach hurts."
They should do Super Size Me, but just with the drinks.
You just peed a lot.
Super Coca-Cola Me.
Yeah, yours was worse.
Drink me.
Super Power Me.
Before Borat, no one found out that if you talk in a silly voice you turn into a gay guy.
Yeah.
But not until the second movie.
That's when you get it.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
You turn into a gay guy.
Bruno is like the chicken super size.
Yeah, exactly.
He's really depressed and really gay.
These people already knew about a guy who talks funny, but they didn't know about a
gay guy.
And so they made Bruno.
I haven't seen Bruno in so long.
the
together to simulate a stick hole opening.
Yeah, he goes, "Bruno."
Bruno.
I've never seen Bruno.
You gotta see it, dude.
It's really good.
It's on my computer.
Yeah, it's on Caleb's computer.
You come watch it on my computer.
Alright, I'll hack in.
Do you have my computer?
I'm gonna hack into it.
Go for it.
I dare you, I have so many firewalls.
I know how to get past firewalls, really easy.
How?
Water.
You didn't think of that, did you?
Fine.
how water they're useless now yeah I use water programming it's where I pour
water onto my computer and I'm able to access any file I want if you if you if
you hold on to a frayed wire poking out of your computer and then pour water all
over it you can see whatever file you want in your head yeah you become part
computer yeah yeah you cry you climb into your bathtub holding your giant CRT
computer plugged in and you experience the files
experience your files in three-dimensional it's a real computer
into the bathtub and open a file and then just let that boy fly if you want
to know if you want to see Wolfenstein 3d in real life yeah put your yeah if you
want to see it in 3d yeah yeah yeah they say it's 3d but they say you activate
3d once you put it in the tub. Have you any of you guys been contacted by the
Secret Service about your tweets? No no I don't think mine doesn't have a keywords
in it so I think I'm fine. Mine I think I'm I think I'm waiting I think they're
probably building up a bigger case against me honestly yeah yeah cuz I had
I had like three people DM me and they were like,
"Hey, I just like posted the lyrics from this
"and a guy knocked on my dad's door."
- Holy shit.
- Yeah, so I mean I think it's probably not a big deal.
And if you guys are listening, I'm just joking.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- I really, yeah, it doesn't matter.
It's just like right now,
I don't want anybody coming to my house.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Well, the thing is,
the reason I'm bringing it up is 'cause I got a call
the secret service about the Mechagodzilla tweet.
What was it?
They called me and they were like, it was the one where it's about Mechagodzilla using his
finger missiles and it also has to do with his brain.
I'm not going to say the whole syntax because they told me I shouldn't say it again.
Gotcha.
But yeah, they called me and they were like, is your account CRM?
Is your refrigerator back?
There were two of them, one was like training the other one, but they were calling from Boston
'cause that was the last address that they had of me, I guess.
And I guess they're making calls because of COVID, they're not knocking on doors so much lately.
Oh, that's good to know. Alright, I'm gonna kick it up a notch then.
[laughter]
What are you gonna do, call me?
I just won't pick up, bitch.
I said that I was gonna pick up [censored] and swing him like a bat.
Yeah, you also said you were gonna go Travis mode on him.
yeah i don't know if you can i said it's really a i think i i i i i said i was
going to go to our national disaster
yeah he's gonna repeat your face off
yeah
yes i think it's a good thing to trick is just to say jill
as people get it
that's a young interviewed me for like forty five minutes well um... what all
did they have to do for you later you are you ready to argue that uh... yeah i
think so they asked me like if i've ever been suicidal if i've ever shot a
firearm if I've ever been to a rally for a political protectee before. They asked me
if I was a member of any groups and I was like, "Like what?" And then he listed like
three very avant-garde white supremacist groups that I've never heard of. I was like, "How
do you know all these groups?" He was like, "You wouldn't believe me if I told you." I
don't know what that means. I think how he knows is that he's a secret servant. Yeah,
Of course, of course.
Yeah, he should have just said that.
Yeah, that's because it's my whole job.
Uh-huh.
Um, it ended pretty strangely because I was, like, the whole time I was trying to make
them laugh to prove to them that I was funny and not insane.
I also, like, before the interview even started, I was just like, "How did you know, did you
guys already know the Godzilla monsters or did you have to look it up?"
And one of them was like, "I'm 51, I know all the Godzilla monsters."
But it ended with, "Yeah, yeah man, you wouldn't believe the kind of shit we hear.
We just had to make sure that Mechagodzilla wasn't code for you or something.
I heard one guy say that the devil talked to him on the TV and told him that he needed
to kill Barack Obama."
I was like, "Yeah, that sounds pretty normal."
And then he was like, "Well, anyway, we just had to make sure that you weren't gonna, you
know, travel across the country to do anything to hurt poor d**k."
And I laughed so hard.
I was like, "Did you say poor d**k?"
And then he was like, yeah, poor [beep]
[Laughter]
It was insane.
He really had a joke.
I was like, what is his home address by the way?
I'm kidding.
I'm more than - I'd welcome a call.
I would love to talk -
It was pretty nice to talk to them.
I would love to talk to them just because it would keep me from like - like every time
I get like a phone call or something, I'm just like, oh my God, here it is.
But it's always capital one.
It's always a worse phone call.
Manchester, New Hampshire. I don't know if that's the Secret Service though. I've been
hanging up on them. Yeah, the thing is most phone calls I hang up on, I don't answer a
lot of stuff. The only phone calls I get ever are just some, are like a pre-recorded message
of a woman speaking Chinese. Oh, that might be, that might be from when I signed you up.
That might be the Secret Service. That might be from when I signed you up for Scientology
in Chinese. Yeah, I think that is what it is, but I get them like, that's literally the only
phone calls I get. Nobody else calls me.
Yeah, Scientology wants your Chinese ass.
Yeah.
They're gonna get your Chinese ass, Cam.
You watch out.
I don't know if I can help it.
Have you been, Piers, have you been to the
psychiatry industry of Death Museum?
Mm-hmm. I went there on like my first week
in LA.
Man, it's good. I think I did too.
I think it was my first or second week.
I was gonna go with Alex, but he was a coward.
He didn't want to go.
It's so scary. It's like a haunted house.
I walked in with a group of friends and we all gave
fake names and then, you guys know Mike Palladino?
Yeah
Yeah, he literally just walked out and you waited outside for us
We were in there for like an hour the whole time
He was just stressed out on the street corner of the psychiatry
When I went it was completely empty. I went with David Potashnik
the
Boston comic and we just yeah, we just moved through there's nobody in there except there was like two
Beautiful like the most beautiful like French couple I've ever seen
And I've seen a lot of French couples and they were just looking at everything and they seemed
so convinced that I couldn't help but think that they were - they just like - they lived
there and like that's their whole job.
And then when we were leaving, a guy who looked exactly like Shaggy like walked in and it
was like the most crazy scripted shit I've ever seen.
The guy walked in and he was like, "Hey, I just wanted to come check this place out because
this is the Scientology Museum, right?"
the guy behind the counter was like no we are not affiliated in any way with any
religious organization we are an activist group and a museum and he was
like awesome thank you so much and then he left but it was scary you got it they
have cameras. Scientology stuff in LA is so makes you so paranoid when I
walked when we walked about when I walked by the the I walked by the the
Psychiatry Museum like a few times and just there were all there always just
like people standing like right like there were construction workers just like
standing there like not like yeah just like you know just standing next to it
and it's like oh you got your cat calling
cuz yeah they have all those like front businesses around the media center right
that guy David he he lived right he lived in like let's feel as right near
they're like media production center and there's this there's a string of shops
that surround the media production center that they don't they aren't real
They're just like owned by Scientology. It's like a dry cleaner and a mechanic and you walk in and you're like, "Hey, I need my car worked on."
And they're like, "Oh, we can't. We don't actually do that."
And they're just there to serve as like a buffer between the media center and like people who want to like record,
you know, going clear to or whatever.
Yeah. Jesus Christ.
People like watching you over the counter.
It fucking rocks, man. It's awesome.
It's so cool.
It's so funny. They just let it happen.
scariest thing I saw other than the giant vampire that I walked by the giant
vampire I shit myself yeah yeah vampire of LA Pierce no his name is Dracula he
lives in the Hollywood sign hmm he lives in the name is Dracula yeah he lives in
the D it's Dracula. We were guessing it's Dracula. Okay he hasn't said it. No just L. Ron Hubbard's
Winter Wonderland. Oh my god I forgot about that. That was so fucking weird. Yeah in like
in Hollywood. I was like a little bit away from the Ripley's Believe It or Not Museum
though. Yeah. So like. So I don't know if I believe it or not. Yeah I don't know I thought
it was just one of those things. They had a Scientology themed like like Santa Christmas
Park yeah and it just had like a quote from L Ron Hubbard that was like like
they hadn't opened it yet it was a very Christmas presents it was like and all
the little children of the world their Christmas goodies it's a part of a
larger work on Christmas yeah it fucking it was it was awesome definitely one of
highlights of walking through that godforsaken place. Oh my god, Hollywood, whatever that
thing was, that strip we walked on. Yeah, it's a nightmare dude. It's the worst place in America.
It sucks. I can't believe you're there, Pierce. It makes no sense. Yeah, I mean I can't be
here for much longer. Yeah, we gotta get, we're gonna, I'm gonna get you out of there.
I'm gonna get you. I'm gonna pick you up. Put me out of my misery, man. Yeah, I'm coming.
So you're gonna move across the country?
Yep.
Yeah.
Well, I'm gonna move across the country, get him, and then he's gonna move across the country
again.
Yeah.
Well, now he can't come across the country because the Secret Service is blocking him.
Yeah, that's what I was saying.
Yeah.
I think, oh, god damn.
You're right.
Yeah, I think I'm gonna move to Delaware.
And I'm gonna, yeah, hey guys, do you guys mind if I wear this Mechagodzilla costume
on the plane?
*laughter*
Yeah, fuck.
Yeah, that's all Pierce can say.
Fuck.
Yeah, I'm not allowed to comment on that.
You do not have the liberty to say anything else. You can just say fuck.
No, no.
That's the Secret Service.
You're allowed to say fuck.
Yeah.
The Secret Service called me because I was using curse words.
*laughter*
Have you been saying the F word and even the C word?
disturbing the people in the government, okay?
It's been really upsetting them.
You've been using disturbing language recently.
Like the F word or the S word or even damn and hell.
We heard you say
F Trump
and honestly I, we have to take up
every threat. You wouldn't, you wouldn't believe
the kind of stuff I hear. Sometimes I hear
I hear F Trump, F Nancy Pelosi
F this, F that.
It's disgusting. Sometimes I've heard I want to
F Trump and that to me
is just a bridge too far.
or
this month's rent it's exactly this month's rent nice dude
congrats i can't get uh... unemployment or
uh... stimulus
i quit my job in december
and yeah that's right
yeah fuck you pat fuck you you're a bitch dude
broke bitch where's your money at
we get your money out that's why we need everyone to up their pay grade
we need someone to up their pledge to the filipino mr bean tier
yeah
filipino mr. beantier is i think three thousand dollars
we had somebody up their pledge like forty dollars a month
yeah that was insane
yeah such a mistake
what do you get for filipino mr. beantier?
I think we set it to be you don't even get the premium episodes
you don't get anything
yeah so if you want the episode it's three thousand five dollars because you have to subscribe
You just unlock every episode, you guys say "Thank you Filipino Mr. Bean" and you don't even say a name.
No, they know who they are.
I think if somebody's dropping $3,000 on the Filipino Mr. Bean tier,
they probably want to be anonymous anyway.
You don't want that coming up when you search your name.
Yeah.
Yeah, an employer is like, "It says here you're a Filipino Mr. Bean."
It says here you're subscribed, you pay $3,000 a month to a podcast so that they call you
you Filipino Mr. Bean, is this correct? Yes. Congratulations, you're a school bus driver.
Oh fuck. I'm so fucking tired. You're tired? Yeah. You should get on that NOS shit like
young Pierce. I was gonna get a Monster Zero for this but I didn't. But I don't know, I
went to bed at like 11 last night, I woke up at 5, fed the cats, and then went back to bed
and feel like, well...
- Wow. - That's awesome, man.
Let's call Paul and confirm.
(laughing)
- Let's call Paul, let's see what Paul has to say.
- I never, for some reason, I still have little kid brain,
and on my birthday and Christmas,
the night before, I can never sleep.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I can't fall asleep until like 3 a.m.
on my birthday and Christmas.
I haven't done anything today.
Yeah, I'm just sitting, I'm giggling like a little girl
in my bed, going, "He he he he, it's my birthday!"
And then it turns 12 o'clock and I, and then I get more excited.
Yeah.
You start jumping up and down.
I'm, I'm gonna, I'm gonna read the poem that I wrote for Caleb's birthday now.
This is one of the sweetest things ever.
This poem is called the King Caleb.
Yes.
And it's for Caleb's 23rd birthday.
I'm going to sit back.
King Caleb is so funny and he has a lot of money.
Don't interrupt.
Okay.
I'm going to start over.
It's called King Caleb.
King Caleb is so funny.
And he has a lot of money.
He is handsome too, except his head looks like it's been stretched on the x-axis by three inches.
Going viral with his challenges, Caleb has advantages.
Like being...
Like...
Like being good at basketball.
And having the strength, speed, cunning, group skills, and head of a hammerhead shark.
King Caleb has a wife and fame, but what is up with Caleb's name?
You may not- you may think it's nothing special, but the etymology of Caleb can actually be
traced to "caliber", meaning the diameter of any circular body, as in, "Caleb's
skull is of a grossly wide caliber", as well as "caliper", as in, "I am going
to use a caliper to measure the width of Caleb's ear to his other ear", and the Arabic word
"Kalib" meaning mold, as in Caleb's mom's pussyhole is shaped like a rectangle, resulting in a
wide berth, no pun intended, in the mold, or "kalib", of Caleb's head.
Patrick is a prince, and Cameron is a royal clown, but today Caleb is the king of town.
So put on your kingly crown, the whole of which is shaped like a rectangle.
Wow. Happy birthday, Caleb. Thank you, Pierce. That was beautiful. I do have a big head.
Yeah, you look like a bald-headed baby. I do. One time, a friend of mine
had his barber went to the same gym as me and I guess his barber one day was
talking about, he was like, "This is fucking little white boy with the
biggest damn head I've ever seen in my gym.
*laughter*
And my friend was like,
"Is his name Caleb?"
And he was like, "I'll ask next time."
And he came up to me at the gym, he was like, "Is your name Caleb?"
*laughter*
And I was like, "Yeah." And he was like, "Okay."
And that was it. And I didn't know him for like
six months.
Fuck, in my gym.
In my gym, yeah, in my own gym.
Caleb's gym. Fuck. I was attacked in my own
gym for my head's shape and size.
Is that the gym you worked at in?
No, this was back, this was years ago.
This was when I had an even smaller body so my head looked even bigger.
Did I tell you when I applied to work at the gym that you quit, your boss said that you
did improv?
Yes, that's awesome dude.
Your boss was like, "Well, I know you probably know Caleb through improv or something."
Yeah, that guy, he managed a gym and he had been, he used to be a UFC fighter, like, not
a UFC, just like a low level MMA fighter.
He used to be a UCB fighter, that's what he kept talking about.
He got punched in the face so many times that sometimes, he briefed me on this when I interviewed
there, he was like, "Sometimes I'll just be talking to you and I'll just start drooling
and not be able to hear what you're saying for a little bit.
So just bear with me.
And it would happen every day.
He'd be like, "Did you fold the towels?"
And then he'd just look at me like.
(laughing)
- Oh my God.
- For like 10 seconds.
And I'd have to be like, "Hey man, you there?"
He'd be like, "Yeah, sorry, I zoned out."
He called it zoning out.
(laughing)
- Those are called non-epileptic,
or no, yeah, they're called non-epileptic seizures, I think.
- Is that what that, oh yeah.
So I have talked about this on the podcast,
but I think it was very similar to the kid
who I went to school with that would,
when he laughed, he would have a non-epileptic seizure,
and I would just spend all day
trying to make him have a seizure
until they had to separate me from him.
It was similar, but his was just like,
if he had to remember where the laundry detergent was,
he would just start drooling.
- Thinking longer than a three-word sentence.
- Yeah, he would just absolutely lose his brain.
It was awesome dude.
He would have to trick his brain into thinking about numbers.
Yeah, he was a math genius somehow.
You should have worked there Pat.
You would have continued the long line of fat people working at the front desk.
No, I tanked the interview so bad.
What'd you say?
He said something and then I said like, "I'm not going to tell you I'm going to be the
best employee in the world."
God, you suck dude.
Dude, I can't do job interviews.
What is wrong with you?
I don't know.
I'm going to ask you something you said.
Well, you know, when I was 13, I screen printed this thing and all the teachers, you just
started telling a story.
Yeah, I'll just say right now, I love to jack off at work.
Yeah.
It's just like one of my perks.
Straight up.
If I see a fat person in this gym, I'm going to call him a fatty.
It's one of my call of duty perks is I can jack off at work.
It's in my load out.
And I will not switch my load out for you.
And I will not switch my load out.
It is very tactical.
I'm gonna take my loadout on your towels.
[Laughter]
Yeah, my two perks is I jack off at work and I steal money whenever I see it, no matter what.
Because I'm trying to buy a new loadout.
Yeah, that means that I can't take any cigarette breaks.
That's one of the perks that I'm choosing not to use.
So you're welcome.
And I also won't hit on any customers.
I roll up the dollar like a cigarette and I smoke it in the gym.
There was a, at that gym there was a panic button under the desk.
You had a man hour button?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it would lock all the doors.
No it would just call the police basically.
It was in central square, it was right down the street, like the police station.
And there was this one girl who every time a homeless person came in asking to use the
bathroom she would press the panic button.
And the cops would just come in every day and just be like, "Please, just let him use the
bathroom or tell him to leave."
To be like, "I was scared.
I was scared for my life.
He's asking me to use the bathroom."
Yeah.
Well, I mean, what else would you do?
Just shoot him in the head.
"I can't.
Can I use the bathroom?"
That's the other button.
It activates the turret.
That's the real panic button.
The century gun.
The hobo turret.
It shoots the sandwich out the door.
That's our bum laser.
*laughter*
Yeah, there's like ten buttons for just different weapons.
Yeah, it just slices him in different layers like Resident Evil.
Is that a bum or a hobo? I don't know if he's the bum laser or the hobo grenade launcher.
Sir, please identify yourself so I know which weapon to dispatch you with.
Are you a bum or a hobo?
Did you get here via boxcar?
We need to know.
Or you just ugly
We have a big we have a big makeup
But there's no cure for what you have
You doing inside ciggies is that what this is like I live alone I get to do this
Your landlord says okay
He don't know. He don't know. What he don't know, he don't know.
Yeah, weird. Now he does. Patrick's your landlord.
Yeah. That's right. That's right.
Oh my god.
Cut that. Don't.
I'll cut that. Yeah.
I knew a guy who had his landlord as his Snapchat username.
That's funny. Yeah. Pretty good.
That is good.
I'm not going to say it.
Why not say it?
Come on.
Let's all add him on Snapchat.
No.
Why not?
I used to have a crazy, when I was a kid, we had a crazy Greek landlord, this old lady,
she would walk in while we were there, she would just walk in unannounced and start telling
us our house was dirty and sometimes she would just use the bathroom.
She sucked, man.
She sounds awful.
She was one of the worst landlords I've had.
She would use the bathroom.
Yeah, one time my landlord came in to use my bathroom and it was when a friend was staying
with me and the place was just absolutely fucked.
Just trash and ash everywhere.
And he was like, "I had some coffee and it went right through me.
Can I use your bathroom?"
He used my bathroom and then a day later he called me and he was like, "I raised the rent
on everyone by $25 but you are still paying me the old rent and I was like
you didn't tell me he was like I put mail in everyone's mailbox I don't know
how you didn't get it and also Pierce there is no maids we don't have maids
you have to take good care of your apartment I thought that was going in
the direction of him saying like well you don't have to pay the new price
because you let me demolish your toilet no no he roasted me for having a messy
apartment. God damn it. He had the guts to shit in your toilet and tell you off? Yeah.
To do a coffee shit? Yeah he did a coffee run. Oh my god he did a coffee run in my toilet.
God damn dude. That sucks. That sucks right guys? That's seriously shit. That's ass. I'm
just gonna say it. So what have you been doing all day Pierce? I know I've talked to you
But what have you just been stuck inside? Are you're not doing any any work anymore?
No, I I know I'm not doing any work anymore
Playing a lot of Metal Gear and then hanging out with my girlfriend
Nice. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Metal Gear is so good guys you play it. Is it? No, what is it for PC?
Yeah, how do you know are you playing it on the emulator emulators for like PlayStation is so confusing and annoying. Yeah
That's a simulator
Yeah, I got a special edition Metal Gear Solid 4 ps3 from the mall
Well, I bought it. I bought it with my truth point check
Just been playing the legacy collection of the Metal Gear games the legacy of metal is it all of them
Yeah, it's all of them. It's all it's all of them
What is there isn't there a new one that you're not you're not snake or something you're just like four guys
That's like you're looking at her be in the amazing final fantasy. Yeah
They're all the same game to me any PlayStation. I've been playing death stranding
It's pretty good. Yeah, it doesn't seem fun
It's it's got a fun story and like it's just a nice like zone out game. I mean like yeah for me
I can't imagine picking it back up again after beating it, but it was it was good to play. Yeah, it's not it's good
I gotta get it.
It's a good game for a guy who's like bad at games and likes movies, which is me.
Yeah.
I'm the opposite.
I hate movies.
And you're great at games.
I'm great at games.
Yeah, you wouldn't like Death Stranding if you don't like movies.
It's just like all cutscenes and then walking.
I love those games.
I love like Heavy Rain.
Yeah, you would not play it.
And what's the horror one?
Until Dawn.
That's a good game.
It's great.
I'm human.
I really like Heavy Rain.
Heavy Rain is really good.
uh... idea i i like
i like games that are
i'd like to have any game that's like a uh...
come a mediocre story which i think every rain is good but like all of those
walking simulators from a two thousand thirteen
where you like have to go you are like walking through your old school
and like picking up uh... letters that people
wrote to you
i love all of that she really anyone who has a nice on home is one of them
uh...
in my dear dear ester
uh... fire watch postal those are all games like that postal to postal yeah
that's how you have to pick up those letters from gary kent
yeah you have to pick up the fart gun
it's a big deal
man i gotta i have postal 2 on my computer
i gotta play more games on my pc
all i play is xbox
shut up dude
my favorite game i think my favorite game of all time is still gmod i don't know why
you know it's pretty much you know it's all going on and i don't know how to
consider your energy monster
and you know i don't have any of the textures everything's that pink and
black that's your own you know i think that says texture
yeah i don't know how to do it
it's going to get the the valve you to wait for the summer sale get the
complete like
it away till the summer
yeah please
you know inside
at all summer playing g_-mod
so that
That's how Steam tricks you.
They get you on the computer.
With their sales.
That's true.
I'm trying to figure out a way to just download illegally all of my games.
But I think I have to purchase some sort of--
All of your games?
All of my games that I've made.
Caleb's games?
Yeah.
Like Baby Simulator?
No, it's not a game I have, or made.
Yeah, that's a game that you play every day.
I'm not modeled after--
Bald Baby's Adventure.
No, it's not a game.
The Tall Baby's Quest.
what would bald babies it'd be
uh... was a huge no i have told me i'm not a little bit of the game is you're
having trouble sleeping to its your birthday the next day
no yeah and i don't know how to get the other hand and you go on a bloody
road in the game is i lost my rattle fuck no it's not that's not what you
have a little bit of this now the game doesn't exist so there's no open again
doesn't get your life
no already
on their plate you play baby they can't make the game until you die because they
one of the ending of the game. It has to be based on a true story.
Uh huh. No, it started out as a baby. They should make games that are based on a true
story and you can't deviate at all from what happened. So...
That's kind of like the JFK. The what?
Have you ever played that? No.
The JFK reloaded? Are you JFK or are you the shooter?
You're Lee Harvey Oswald and you have to recreate the JFK assassination as...
Then that's not based on a true story because that's not how it happens.
Yeah, you have to do it as accurate as possible.
Do you think Lee Harvey Oswald got New Game+ from doing that?
Yeah, he hit him in the head and it said "Achievement Unlocked" on the bottom of the screen.
Yeah, and he started with infinite ammo as some other guy.
Pretty good.
That was his New Game+.
He upgraded in every sense.
Chris Dorn was the new Z-Ball version.
New skin unlocked.
And then he didn't get a new one though.
And he won't.
He doesn't get another chance.
Jack Ruby got Kingslayer.
Yeah.
Didn't they kill Jack Ruby too?
Yeah, they killed Jack Ruby in Prisoner of Jail or something.
Dude, they absolutely killed everyone!
They killed everybody in that shit, dude.
It was fucked, dude.
They killed, uh...
They killed MLK, they killed JFK, they killed Ruby Tuesday, they killed...
They got 'em all.
They killed, uh, BFG.
Yeah, they killed the big fucking giant.
Yeah.
No, he's friendly.
With a BFG.
Yeah, they killed...
Wow, I'm killing the BFG with the BFG, and I'm at... I'm at BFG.
BFJangs.
*laughter*
Eating BF Wangs
Yeah
That's a good item
They should put BF Wangs
BF Wangs
*laughter*
Big fuckin' thing
At PF Changs
They should serve BF Wangs
Uh huh
What is it?
Buffalo Wangs
*laughter*
You're right, they should serve that with a Z at the end.
Uh-huh.
[Laughter]
I only had P.F. Chang's once and I vomited.
Was it the one in Boston?
You used to work there? No, it was in Charlotte.
Yeah, I worked at the Boston one.
Oh, did you? The one in Seaport?
Yeah, that's a P.F. Chang's, right?
Yeah, it's the one with the big horse statue outside where they modeled half the penis.
Wait, yeah, that P.F. Chang's is a P.F. Chang's, right?
Yeah, that one is, yeah.
They all have horses. That's the way.
No, they're lions. They model half...
Oh, no, there's a horse.
Yeah, there's a horse.
There's always a horse.
And they have half of the penis modeled.
It goes half the shaft up.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, it's pretty funny.
I gotta check that out.
It's not quite the Denver Airport thing.
It's penis 50% Chang's.
Have you guys seen
what the Denver Airport is doing?
Like, in the, I don't know if
it was a news story or whatever, but they
The inside of the Denver Airport like they have a bunch of posters and shit that talk about the conspiracy
Like pictures of the underground tunnels, and it's just like you know 3,000 miles of underground tunnels
Investigate the conspiracy go to dia.com and it's inside the airport
Yeah, there's like capitalizing on all the conspiracy stuff, and they're like crazy the mystery of the horse go to dia.com
- That's crazy. - That's crazy.
- It's fucked up.
Not cool.
- One weird multicultural mural.
- Yeah, there is one weird one.
- Yeah.
- I think the same artist, whoever did that mural,
I saw a painting from him once,
like a print of a painting from him
in a skate shop for some reason.
And I remember it was the Denver Airport muralist
'cause I looked up the signature
'cause it was so insane to me.
But it was a person, it was a body
in like a lotus stance.
And then it was all of the person's chakras were identified.
And for each chakra,
there was like a little vignette next to it.
And I don't remember all of them,
but one of them obviously was Bob Marley.
One of them was 9/11.
And then one of them was just a family watching TV.
- So sick.
- It was like $600.
- Did I ever talk about that crazy statue I saw in the mall
near Christmas of like it was like so it's like a bunch of people peeing no it
was but you're paying into a no no like that it was uh this it was there's a
restaurant in Harvard Square that is a bunch of babies peeing statues just all
over the restaurant but this is different it was in a mall and I was on
like the upper level like looking over the balcony and there's like this this
sculpture on the on the floor of the mall that's like just a big like cooking
pot thing with a bunch of like children in it like with their elbows like leaning
out of this cooking pot and we're like it's like what the fuck is that and I
went down and looked and it was like Christmas time so they right next to it
they had like the like take a picture with Santa thing and I was like what is
this sculpture and I went to look closer and just taped like on like a piece of
like printer paper taped on the side of the cooking pot there it was just a star
of David and said happy Hanukkah. Thank you for not taking a picture of that.
I yeah I really should have taken a picture of that.
No, no you shouldn't have. No you don't want that. That's bad news.
Yeah you don't want that on your phone when the Secret Service calls you.
Exactly yeah. Once the Secret Service goes poking around
your phone and asks you to explain all your pictures.
exactly what's with this version of the Yankee with no brim video yeah a bunch of
like varying stages of face app do where you just pictures of me is it with my
monkey yeah and they're just like who is this this is genetic this is the most
powerful image we've ever seen they're like how to find out about this phone how
did you find out about our hybrid experiments yeah our monkey people were
We're trying to send to the Middle East.
How'd you get a picture of our super soldier?
I hope so.
You hope you're the super soldier?
I am the super soldier.
You're not the super soldier dude.
You're the diaper soldier.
No.
You're super focused.
No, I have abilities.
Yeah, like wearing diapers.
Yeah, like wearing diapers and going into them.
That's a skill.
I have abilities.
Yeah.
Yeah, the ability to cry.
The ability to crack your diaper.
Yeah, cry and crap.
You're to the two Cs, cry and crap.
Backflip.
Crapping, cry and Caleb.
No, gainer, front flip.
Gainer?
I can do a gainer.
The gamer?
No, gainer.
I can do a backflip where I run.
You said you're a gainer.
You gain more poop in your--
No, you've been doing a gainer
for the last three years, buddy.
Yeah, you gain poop in your diaper.
No, you gain weight from Fritos.
I don't, I hate Fritos.
How dare you?
Now you do, because you've had some.
No, that's, I, that I take, no, no, uh uh.
Yeah.
No, he's not saying I eat Fritos.
I am saying you eat Fritos.
That's where I draw a fucking line.
Yeah.
No.
You get a, you get one bean out of the chili and then you cover it in Fritos.
I don't cover anything in Fritos.
You do.
You cover your bed in Fritos.
I do not eat Fritos.
I don't eat Fritos.
Yeah, you love the twist, you love the barbecue twists too.
No, I, no, I hate those.
You love the scoops.
I throw up from them.
I hate all Fritos.
I eat, I eat Tostitos.
I eat Tostitos.
Please don't.
Please no.
I've already said it.
we had a whole episode where i did voice- oh it's that one again
patrick never says the names of programs twice that's his thing
it's unnecessary
at that point you're just bragging that you have it
you get it too i do respect the restraint of not using it until there's
five minutes left
thank you for that i was expecting you to break it out much earlier
you're welcome bitch
nice that one sucks you're not even using a good one
sounds like a walkie talkie that's the counters break
use a cool one please
okay i guess i was in place it is a little bit of a lot of the pedophiles
probably
do not have something to do and
yet
terrorist
the failure of the year to uh... zoom display name
now
you know
the
kato's you know the e
a look at the e
at a file
the
I don't know what this one is. What does this one do?
That's just hazard voice.
That one's me.
This one, it says it has ambient effect.
Does it?
Yeah, there's a lullaby.
Twinkle, twinkle little star is playing.
It's just my voice.
It's rockabye baby.
You're right.
It's rockabye Caleb.
Yeah.
That song's about Caleb being in a tree top like a monkey baby.
Caleb sits in a tree house.
It's in the treehouse. No, what is this one sound like?
I'm ready. I go walkie-talkie. There's a beeping semtex in the background. Oh
Now you're okay. Yeah. Oh, okay. Oh
Do the do the Grinch you're an idiot I'm an idiot routine you're an idiot
No, you know do it your normal way
No, but then you have a normal voice the response yeah, okay, I'm a Grinch
He says I'm an idiot and echo says you're an idiot do it I just got killed to say I'm an idiot no
Yeah!
Woo!
Yeah baby!
This is the worst birthday party of my life.
Yeah the Austin Powers voice!
It sounds like Austin Powers.
Say do I make you horny.
Do I make you Austin Powers?
Do I make you horny baby?
Say do I make you Austin Powers.
Do I make you Austin Powers baby?
Do the teeth too.
Yeah.
Austin's teeth and his face.
Austin's teeth in his face.
Yeah.
It's good.
I like that.
Do I make you Austin Powers, baby?
Oh my god.
No.
Cause then he's talking to you, "That is a baby."
Oh, I get it.
It's a baby voice with a lullaby.
But it's not a baby voice.
It's a low pitch, yeah.
Maybe it's the father voice.
That's the deep voice?
That's the bedroom invader.
It's father.
That's Austin's room.
what is this one is called I don't know what this you say it's called punk
no oh it's like okay and then this one is called central central yeah all these
names are stupid yeah we should rename these I think I should buy this I think
I should just bite the bullet by this thing you're gonna spit you just said
you have you can't get unemployment you can't get a stimulus check yeah but I
think it's only I think it's only you're gonna buy the 60 premium voices I think
it's only a dollar oh what it is a $32 lifetime subscription oh hmm well how
long are you planning on living but look it's got like Thanos look it's got
It's got Power Rangers and all of my favorite characters.
You can make yourself sound like Harry Potter.
Oh, there's a cop chase?
Children to adult?
Children to adult.
Oh, damn.
Damn, I could have, uh...
Damn.
I could have sang you "Happy Birthday."
There's one called "Birthday Reggae."
Yeah.
We'll press it.
Birthday Reggae.
I don't have $32 to buy it.
Press play.
$32.
Okay, wait.
great don't buy it.
Happy Birthday to Caleb.
Yeah.
(bell rings)
- Thank you.
- How was that?
- I think that was as good a place to end the episode
as any.
- All right, Pierce, do you have anything you wanna plug?
- No.
- No, all right, we'll follow Pierce on Twitter.
- Pierce is making very funny videos.
Follow Pierce and Will online.
- Yeah, follow Pierce and Will.
- Yeah, follow Will.
I'll plug Will.
Follow Wheelie Duncan.
- Wheelie Duncan, follow him.
He's very, very good.
- Follow Wheelie Duncan, follow Cringe_Genius,
and follow, if you're the Secret Service,
follow Pierce with a black van.
yet
the company with a black and and yeah right
drive the van into his house parking in his bathroom i won't notice he doesn't
go to the bathroom tickets the label
haha
because it was
are
thanks for calling us
so i had no problem
armory
you know
nice
and more
who
who's who's
Welcome to the new age.
To the new age.
Oh oh oh.
I'm radioactive.
Radioactive.
Oh oh oh.