Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
- Premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
(laughing)
- All right, here we are.
- Wow, dude.
- Very exciting.
- First time in a studio.
- In a real studio.
- In a studio.
- What's the name of the studio?
- What do you call it?
- Davida Studios.
- We're here with Matt Davida.
- Yes.
- Titular Matt Davida.
How are you? What would you say your title is?
I've been trying to come up with one for years. I really don't know.
Renaissance Man?
I've been trying to
shrink what I do to just one or two
words. What's your best shot right now?
Let's just say All Things Audio Video. All Things Audio Video. Pretty much.
When it comes to production. Okay. So we're in the All Things Audio Video Studio.
audio video production I mean right now yeah yeah I say I say you say video like
I don't do TVs really no no I mean it looks like you do well you got a lot of
them in here yeah they look cool they do look really cool dude there are
there are this is like the kind of place that like when I was a kid I wanted like
a treehouse it looked like this I would live in here yeah it is my home away
from home yeah like like Star Wars shit I have have my memorabilia stuff
yeah I mean yeah there's that Cartman fella he's a little bastard. He keeps an eye on the studio while I'm gone.
yeah yeah yeah I wouldn't want to catch his eye. No he'd chop you up in a bowl of
chili. Yeah he's a piece of crap. Make your parents eat you. Yeah that's so true.
Or make you eat your parents I think is what he did. Did he do that? In an episode yeah.
yeah
killed his parents
yeah, Scott Tenderman, remember?
yeah
cartman
you're eating your parents, dude
it's gotta be illegal
um
thank you
yeah
the reason we wanted to talk to you is 'cause we, we have, we've gotten an itch for the paranormal as of late
no, why? I mean, just
it's, it's October
it is October, that's true
well, besides that though, was it before that?
I mean, I've always been super interested in that kind of stuff
I'm big into, you know, the, the paranormal and conspiracy stuff, all that type of thing
sure
I'm very fascinated by that.
So I thought it would be very fun to talk to you and like, you know, you have like hands-on
experience with a lot of that stuff.
Per se.
Per se?
So they say.
Do you like conspiracy stuff at all?
Or are you more just like ghosts or?
I dabble in a little bit of everything.
And I don't necessarily believe in all of it, but whether I believe it or not, I find
it, most of it, interesting.
Absolutely, right, especially if you are a critical thinker, you know, which which are my paranormal group is yeah, we are
What do they call it? We're capers soul seekers out of Wilmington, North Carolina. Cool. So what?
What what got you into that whole like line of work? I used to own a bar, you know
I've been in the music and film industry for over 35 years here in Wilmington, North Carolina home of Screen Gym Studios
Most people don't know that so that's where that studio is. Anyway, I got a plug them. But anyway, um
I used to own a bar, it was a legendary bar here on the East Coast called Bessie's.
It's called Orton's now. Actually I don't think it's open anymore.
Yeah, they closed it. It's very sad.
Yeah, it sucks. It was a great place.
And I kind of didn't really believe... a couple of these shows were coming out about the time I owned it.
this was, I don't know, 2000 early, you know, somewhere around in there. Like, Ghost Hunters
was big. Oh yeah, my mom was real big into that. That's about when they came out. Yeah.
And I was kind of like, whatever, you know, I didn't really, I thought they were kind of,
you know, BS-ish, I guess. Yeah. So, but then I bought Bessies and things happened
that I couldn't explain. Yeah. Like, I had, and I knew it's got a huge history of being haunted.
It's got a resident spirit. His name's William. And people have seen...
It has its own special spirit?
Yeah. So, Bessie's used to be a hotel. It was a five-star hotel in like the early 1900s.
And it burned to the ground. And people died during the fire.
And one particular person named William.
There was a few others that supposedly and/or possibly died,
but they didn't have any identification.
William's the only one they can account for.
And he's, you know, many people believe he's there
and I've had multiple experiences when I was there that,
you know, and about the same time,
me and a friend of mine were kind of watching the shows
And then I sold Bessie's.
And after that, me and a friend of mine were hanging out.
And he said, "Didn't you have some experiences
"when you owned Bessie's?"
And I said, "Yeah."
He said, "Well, why don't we go in there
"and see if we can't poke around?"
- After you'd already sold it.
- After I sold it.
- So you kind of pawned to the ghost off on the next owner.
- I guess, but they knew going into it
that it had a history.
But so we were able to get in there as we weren't even we didn't even have a name.
We were just a couple dudes, you know, with some recorders and some cameras, you know,
and we had seen a couple of the shows and we didn't think, you know, I knew I had
experiences that I could explain, but I still wasn't completely convinced, you know,
until we did our thing.
Really? And we caught some what they call EVP, which is electronic voice phenomena,
which best way I can explain EVP is,
you know how a dog can hear a dog whistle,
but we can't, same thing, same concept,
just a different frequency.
Everything has a frequency, I'm sure you all,
you know, this mic has a frequency.
- So spirits communicate on a specific frequency?
- That certain electronics can pick up, but we can't hear.
- And it all has, according to paranormal enthusiasts,
and scientists, the electromagnetic field has a big to do with the paranormal world.
Some say it's a barrier between our world and the next.
When you pick up, when either you see a possible spirit or you pick up an EVP, you are, and
the field fluctuates all around the world.
You know, and it moves.
It's not stationary.
Like China, the big huge reactor that they just built.
Have you guys heard about this?
- No, I haven't heard of it.
- You need to look into it.
It's huge.
It's supposed to be hotter than the sun.
- Oh yeah, the artificial sun.
- Yes, the artificial sun.
- Okay, in China.
- So you know how they got that?
They tapped into the electromagnetic field for its power.
Now--
- Trouble.
I mean, you know.
I'm sorry, go ahead.
Playing with ghost stuff in China?
To start a huge reactor. I mean, I'm telling you.
You think they're funneling souls into the...
Hey, I didn't say that.
Whoa, but you kind of did imply it, I would say.
But, you know, I mean, you know, it's interesting to...
You know, they're China, they're gonna, I guess, do whatever they want.
That's true. Very true. China doesn't give a f--
They don't give a-- they really don't.
Yeah, to back up, you said you had experiences you couldn't explain in Bessie's. What was the
first-- like what happened there? So I'm good. I'm good on time. I don't want to--
Oh, yeah. We're just chilling. There's no stress on time.
So my first night after I bought Bessie's, me and a friend of mine were checking inventory
or doing an inventory log and just I was counting all the you know liquor and beer and stuff and
and he was in the back um just doing inventory of of bar stools and this kind of stuff you know
yada yada yada so i'm sitting there behind the bar and i'm underneath count you know my inventory
sheet just also the jukebox comes on and it starts playing running with the devil
I'm not lying I'm not I'm telling I'm not yeah right it just came on Anna in the
middle or like the start it at the very beginning oh just came on popped on oh
like the oh man familiar with the song how does it go with the devil van Halen
- Yeah, but you know like the intro,
it has like that, like the, it's like the beats
and then it like gets into the guitar part.
- Yeah, so it's a ghostly song.
- I mean, it's not a song--
- It's called Running With The Devil.
- It's just the title, you know,
running with the devil.
- So it's like if a ghost was looking through a jukebox,
it might choose--
- It'd go on, bam, right.
- He'd say, hey, I'm gonna let you know I'm here
by selecting this song.
- It's like, well, I choose Jump Around.
I like jumping around.
- So it gets, jump around, that's good.
So it gets, so Sean comes around running around outside.
Did you turn, scared the shit out of him.
Did you turn, did you box off blah, blah, blah.
I'm like, I've been behind the bar.
I don't know how it happened, right?
So he was, I was just like, just let it roll.
We'll gotta keep working.
You know, it's probably just a fluke
or a credit that was on there.
And it was just probably a coincidence there.
Of course, I don't believe in coincidences either,
but that's what I told him.
So we kept working. The next song that came on, another song came on and it was
Hell's Bells by AC/DC. I'm not making this up.
Something's fishy.
Something's going on.
So it's Hell's Bells, Sean comes running back on and he's like, "If it plays one more
fucked-up song, dude, I am out of here."
Right? That's the quote. That's what he said.
And then, happy birthday.
Yeah, yeah. Right, right.
you know? So I said, "Man, we got to get this done. Let's just hang tight."
Because he knew Bessie's was haunted. He did not want to be in there.
He was a downtowner. He knew all the stories before we had
bought it, or before I bought it. So when they sold you the place, I'm
curious about this, when they sold you the place, did they like tell you anything
thing about that where they like oh yeah oh here's the kitchen here's the bar
there's Williams over there. That's the thing when someone sells you something
that's haunted they love to tell you about it like I don't know if it's the same.
Was it one eyed GMC who sold it to you? No. I bought it from a couple named John and Laurie Butler they
were big into the Wilmington music scene and film scene and and I'd also used to
I used to have you know DaVita Studios that were the band DaVita rehearsal
studios back then where all the bands practice so which is pyramid studios now
but anyway so I got I got a calm down and I got him to go back you know to work
and the last song one more song came on I guess it had three credits on there I'm
guessing but because it didn't play anymore after that but it was a it's the
end of the world as we know it. Oh my god. I will say. If that's not a sign. Hilarious
bookend. Yeah yeah I mean those were the three songs. To go from Running with the Devil to
It's the End of the World. That's right. You know the ghost is like kind of losing
the thread at the end. He's like hell hell end of the I don't know hanging out
at the end of the world. I'm still not getting their attention damn it. Yeah.
Singing so fast they got to pay attention to that. Yeah. So did you let
the songs. Did you let them play or did you turn them off? Well this was the
where the plot thickened. So Sean and I were standing in the middle of the bar,
I mean middle of the bar basically. And Sean looked at me and said,
"I wonder if it's plugged in." Oh man, no way. That's what he said. I was like, "You son of a bitch, you had to go there, didn't you?"
And so we walked over, we walked over like, you know, like we were watching a scary movie, you know.
Like Scooby-Doo.
And it was kind of comical to see, you know, grown men walking over to this jukebox, you know.
Anyway, so we get there and we kind of argued about who's going to look first.
He's like, "You're the owner, you look!" So I got looked around and sure enough it was
plugged in. Oh, okay. It was plugged in. I just want to sweat off my brow. But still, that was like the first
of many weird, you know, I left one night. We always used, there was a
bell that they had mounted, and as tradition you were always supposed to
tell William goodnight and ring the bell. Really? Last one to leave. Wow. And if he
didn't he'd let you know and I forgot to ring the bell one night and I'm locking
the door and as I'm start- it was downstairs it's a downstairs bar. Yeah
it's like a basement. And it's got a lot of- Oh is that the one by the parking garage that we
walked by? No no it's the one that I pointed out and I was like this is a
pool is a great pool hall. William Mosconi set a world record there.
And Tom Berringer used to own Longstreet's which I have Bessie's and Longstreet's. I own both
but but as I'm walking out of the Bessie's side I turn around start going
upstairs all of a sudden jiggle jiggle jiggle somebody was jiggling on the door.
Wow yeah. So would you say that William was or he's
probably still there yeah. You know it's tough to say because in my personal
experience over doing this for over 15 years now and I've been almost everywhere
on the you know from like North Carolina down to Florida you know some spirits
move on yeah you know I don't know that all of them do but at some point. Do you
have any any theories as to why? Possibly they have done what they needed to do
yeah you know and William needed to play music and jiggle doors. He finally found the song he wanted.
Well he did a lot more than that. I mean people have seen him, people have spoken to him.
Damn. Yeah, like you've been in Bessie's. You know that the back door part of Bessie's
uh-huh back with it turns back into the brick little patio thing yeah yeah
they've seen him there was a girl one night out on a patio part back there by
the back door someone saw this girl talking to nothing whoa all right and
we thought she was having an episode or something and she turned around said
what's wrong he's like you tell me and she said who he what were you doing is
like I was talking to this guy and she described he's like no he didn't see
anybody was he what did she describe him as like he's wearing like weird leather
clothes and shit that time that out yeah those time yeah she thought it was a
little odd he was wearing clothes that were from the 19 yeah yeah but Wow yeah
so she saw full apparition right yeah you ever seen a full one a couple of
times really really whoa what's the scariest one I want to yeah my home when
I lived in a Vassa really my house and yeah so years ago we did an
investigation with Port City paranormal which are good friends of ours on the
battleship and the battleship for people don't know is an old it's a battleship
battleship docked in North Carolina and Wilmington and very haunted yeah super
mega that makes sense yeah yeah I feel like that's probably one of the number
one places to be haunted right battleships yeah anything with that kind
of talked about terrible tour you know it could could possibly horrible endings
could possibly you know yeah yeah yeah have some sort of energy you know
residing in in yeah and or where it used to be so yeah but uh and I that's just a
word to the to the wise to people interested in this stuff careful what
you wish for. You know, the TV, things I don't like about the TV shows, I'll tell
the battleship real quick, but I just, I'm leading in, you know, the, what
they don't talk to you about enough in my opinion on these shows is, you know, this
this stuff is real, okay? I mean, it's, careful what you go looking for. You
might not like what you, and you might not be able to get rid of what you find.
Yeah. So in other words I'm a big, you know, I preach on spirit attachment all
the time and that's why, you know, people say "I want to go ghost hunt with you"
and I hate the term ghost hunters too by the way. We're not
hunters. I don't have proton packs. Spiritician? We're paranormal
investigators. We're just paranormal investigators. Investigator sounds a lot
less bad than Hunter. Yeah, well you're walking around like Elmer Fudd. Yeah, I mean, you know, we're just...
Looking for a ghost. Yeah, it just... the shows have done some good things for paranormal investigators,
but also have done, you know, it's like a double-edged sword kind of.
Do you, are you... what's your opinion on Zach Bagans?
I better be careful because I have a lot of followers. That's true.
I guess we all know each other. I mean, I've been in this for a long time and I don't want to...
Right. Well, yeah, we don't have to get you in trouble. Yeah, we don't. Yeah, don't worry. Yeah,
I appreciate that. Let's hear the battleship story. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Off, off. I'll tell you later.
Okay, I'm excited to hear that.
Sorry y'all, sorry for the disappointing, but I know too many people in this field and I can't publicly, you know, I just don't feel like going there.
But, and y'all know, I'm not, it's cool, you know.
That's a whole different, that's a whole different segment.
But we don't operate that way. How about that? We don't operate anywhere close to
how he does. Our group is. Sure, yeah. And each to their own. Each to their own when it
comes to that. But we're not at all about that type of approach.
Yeah. How about that? That sounds right. Yeah, middle of the road. Thank you. Perfect. Well done. Thank you. I had to think about that for a minute.
But I had a one of the I personally feel one of the soldiers from the
battleship attached itself to me after our investigation. Really? And followed me
home. To Nevada. One morning I'm laying in bed it's about I don't know 630 in the
morning right when the sunrise was coming up and I'm on the side of my bed in my
room and I look up and I'm awake you know and there's a figure standing right next
to my bed. Oh man. He was dressed in the white tees and blue you know. Yeah.
Yeah blonde hair. Blonde? And he was kind of kind of there but kind of not. Mm-hmm.
Yeah. And I just, I had, the only thing I could think about, I wasn't scared really.
It's kind of funny because the only thing I could think about was, I stayed still,
you know, and he was just kind of there over, you know, just kind of like, "Hey."
Yeah. Right? I mean, it wasn't scary. He wasn't like,
you know, any of that, you know, it was just like, it was just kind of
looking out yeah chilling right and I'm sitting there going I wish he would leave
cuz I got to be so bad yeah real paranormal so it was clear that it was
not a real man that you were like what the fuck you doing my house bro no no no
it was not like that because it was not a it was not solid yeah yeah it was
there and I've seen anything from anomalies to shadow spirits to you know
partial apparitions to full full-blown apparitions. Would you make a distinction
between ghosts and demons? It's really difficult because demons from what the
knowledge of I have of them can present themselves to you in any form. So yeah
It's very difficult for me to go, "That's a demon and that's not."
Plus, demons are notoriously tricky.
Absolutely.
And do I feel I've ever come across one?
Quite possibly.
Yeah, right.
I can answer that as well.
Most of the time, typically, and I don't even know if it's necessarily a demon as we know
what a demon is.
usually if you come across what we call a foul spirit you know there's usually a
distinct smell. Is it sulfur? Yes absolutely it's it's like raw eggs yeah
it's sulfur mix right and and that's usually when we have bad shit happen
yeah yeah I mean I mean not the fun you know. Have you ever heard of someone
getting like actually hurt? Me. Really? You got hurt? I've got pushed more than once.
Really? Oh yeah. What's the worst you've been hurt? I got pushed pretty good at
the Rusty Nail. Oh yeah? Yeah. You're not going there tonight. There was a great place.
It's my favorite place. It's one of my favorite places. I didn't realize it was haunted. We played there about a month ago.
Wait a minute. No, it's been longer than that now. July. End of July. But it's haunted?
Barry. Really? With an aggressive ghost? Well... Tough to say. Again I'm gonna stay diplomatic on that.
my first rodeo there was a murder there in the 70s and in the ironic to the
wrong place called the rusty nail by a rusty nail right that would be you know
know. Pretty funny. Yeah, that happened to me and I was the ghost, I just want to tell
people. Yeah. You know, it's named after me. That's right. Isn't that crazy? I died here.
It was the nail. It was called the rusty nail and I died from a nail. Got shanked. But he,
I got pushed where the guy died. Whoa. Right where in front of the bar. So you've been
Yeah, yeah, of course. You know the little partition is to deal with behind the bar. Yeah.
You know like if you're facing that to the right, a couple of barsicles down.
And I was right there and I got pushed into that pole.
Damn. Yeah, like I'm talking like... Like shoulder check. Yeah, yeah.
Or you know how you're in a club and boom, somebody just... Yeah. It was like that.
But there's, you know...
Why do you think he pushed you did you like see a mugshot I gotta kill them? No just because we were there
He might not have been pissed. He might have just been I might have just been his in his way
Yeah, it might not have been out of aggression necessarily was he was that a sulfur smeller? No, no
No, I don't think that's that kind of out of
Experiences we've had there. We've been there up to three times
There's some places. I can't tell what we've gone. Yeah publicly confidentiality
People probably aren't too keen on telling the world that their restaurant is haunted.
We've done fire departments, we've done hospitals, or what used to be hospitals.
Wow, yeah.
So, because of our reputation. And us, and Port City's Paranormal is the same way.
So they hire you and they keep it a secret?
Yeah, we can't, you know, yeah.
Wow.
They make you sign stuff, or no?
We just, you know, we got a good rep.
Yeah, of course, don't fuck it up.
Yeah, that's where we are, you know.
So we, you know, and that's why people keep calling either us or them, you know.
How often does somebody ask you to come out because they think that something's going on and it's just a whole lot of nothing?
Most of the time.
Really?
It's not like the TV shows.
Yeah.
90% of the time it's nothing.
But I say nothing.
It's all in how you look at it or perspective.
I've done this for so long that to me meeting the people I meet, finding out history that's
not in the books of hand-me-down stories, you know, where I'm at in my age in life,
to me that's all part of helping people whether we find something or not.
It's all part of it.
my opinion you know if you're if you're in it just to get scared or find a ghost
per se you're you're missing the bigger picture. Your hearts not in the right place. You're missing the bigger
picture. Are there people who are paranormal investigators who they want to get
scared? Of course there are. Really? They think it's like a haunted house? Look at Zach.
Oh he slipped in. I'm gonna cut him off again.
That's as far as I'm gonna go with that.
He's blown over dude.
People who are just like out there, they prank the ghosts until they scream at them.
Thrill jockeys.
Or just, yeah, thrill seekers.
That's a good word.
Thrill seekers, thrill jockeys.
You know, and they're missing, a lot of them maybe or could possibly miss the whole bigger
picture of history.
The connection you're making with people.
You know, the peace of mind you could possibly be giving someone if it's not haunted, you
know, so they could sleep better at night.
Those kind of things.
you say is the most common sign that there's some kind of paranormal activity?
Is it the... talk to me about spirit orbs. Is that a real thing? I'm not a big fan of orbs.
Yeah. Now I believe... Can I quote you on that? Yeah. I'm just... I'm not... I personally am not a big
fan of orbs. Right, yeah. No, but there is a difference between an orb and what they
call an anomaly. Yeah. Similar in shape, but nine times out of ten when you see an
It's dust. Yeah, it really is. Absolutely, yeah. I agree. But an anomaly, I saw one on the
battleship. Mm-hmm. It was about three inches by three inches in diameter and
it was, I thought it was a reflection because it was in a mirror. I thought it
was a reflection off my IR light from my camera when I walked in. I turned the light on
because I was like, I gotta find out what this is. So I turned the light on and it's
still in the mirror just kind of waffle right and I'm like what the fuck is that
allows yeah okay yeah yeah you can curse cool I say pretty much anything all
right pretty much anything I just said
And then it was almost like it knew I was in there.
Right?
'Cause about, as I started to kind of,
curiosity kills the cat, you know,
I started walking to it, it jumped out of the mirror,
still on the wall, didn't come out at me,
but just, it was weird.
And then it just, and it shot,
and just kind of, not like, not like Ghostbusters.
- Yeah.
- But it just, like before, it almost looked like
it just, you know, as it was going towards the next wall, it looked like it dissipated
before it got to the wall.
Yeah.
No sliming, though?
No, nothing like that.
It was, it was, and it was fast.
It was super fast.
Have you ever seen slime?
Any ectoplasm?
No, but, you know, they say, I've run into spider webs, but never found any spider webs.
Okay.
So, that's what, in the paranormal field, to my knowledge, if you ever have that feeling
Like a sticky slime or something?
Yeah, like there's some spider webs or something.
Spirit slime going all over you.
But it's not, you don't have anything.
Yeah, but you feel like you're just completely covered in it.
Yeah, but there's nothing really there.
Just getting globbed all over.
But more just, it's more like running into a spider, like a spider web.
Really, that's the feeling.
Yeah, but there's no webbing.
Not like someone pouring like Nickelodeon slime.
No, not, I mean, I'm not saying that there's not.
Just my experience.
And I've been doing this over 15 years now.
So we've been at it a lot.
My team's kind of spread out.
We got about eight or 10 members.
- How big is your team?
- About 10 members strong.
- Okay.
- But only about three active.
COVID, you know, changed a lot of our, you know, approaches.
- Doing less investigations now?
- Yeah, and not necessarily less investigations,
but with less people, including wherever we go, you know.
And we try to, like, you know,
how far you and I are together,
six, eight feet. Like if my team goes somewhere, usually it's just two or three of us now.
And we stay at least eight feet apart.
Do you ever get called out to investigate anything like
physical, like any cryptid stuff, or like aliens?
I'm a UFOlogist. I can't even say it. A UFOlogist as well.
Oh really? You consider yourself one?
Is that a more recent thing? About three or four years. But the group I work with out of Southport
that's also on the Cape for Soul Seekers, we do UFO investigations too.
Really? So what do those look like? Somebody tells you that they like see a
UFO in an area and you camp out? Same thing, same kind of thing. They call,
they, this group I work with been doing it for a while and they get a call and
ask me if I want to go. We'll pack up. Usually it's just a, you're looking at
stars all night, hanging out. Yeah. What do you think as a UFOlogist of the,
there was all that like declassified info yeah I was highly disappointed yeah I
was too I was so late I really thought yeah that this was gonna be you know had
over 200 some odd pages and they only released like what yeah it was nothing
nine yeah and it basically says like we have seen things in the sky that we
don't know what they are they they claim to have equipment they mean Pentagon you
know that is off world that their quotes not of this world mm-hmm in our
possessions what more do you want yeah you know what I mean I mean what what
yeah you know I mean and and and the Navy just released a bunch of stuff yeah you
know yeah and and and and has publicly stated that that you know they don't
know what it was they were chasing you know what's your what's your your
version of aliens like what would you anything that Hollywood has ever
produced no yeah I believe in the greys or like green well maybe if anything I
would lean towards great the greys you know the aliens supposedly there's about
six or seven maybe even more different type of species sure typically the
According to my intel, the graves are more of the scientific ones.
They're here to just observe.
Those are the kidnappers who fucking put stuff in here?
Lights are flickering.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Look at the studio.
Oh God.
Oh wow.
They are.
Oh man.
That's pretty cool.
They know we're here.
They heard you talking.
Have you ever had any spiritual thing here?
Yeah, I stage a studio about
twice a quarter.
Really? About every three months I stage it.
How far out are we from the last stage?
Well, let's see how much more the lights flicker, that'll tell us.
But you know, we're also in a storage facility, so it's not necessarily the best.
Yeah.
So for what it is I've made it, you know, yeah, have you seen a bunch of UFOs?
Look, let's not forget UFO means unidentified flight logic, right?
Have you seen anything that you think is like alien origin?
Absolutely, but a lot of people forget this. Yeah, they get wrapped up in the moment,
right? Yeah. And a UFO doesn't mean it's an alien ship, right? It's just something you don't know
what it is. We don't know what it is. We can't figure out what you know, they get so excited.
the same thing with spirits and you know 90% of the stuff we we do we deep we
debunk you know we're big on on a scientific approach about everything you
know very similar to taps you know ghost hunter folks you know we operate very
similar to them as far as trying to disprove stuff you know and but but I
have seen some things in my last one I did was probably about a year ago but we
called sky watches. We were down at the north, south end of Oak Island and just
sure enough these weird orb things it was a kind of a cloudy night. It looked
kind of looked like a drone. I thought it was a drone. But drones don't just, same
thing with the, like the anomaly. It just, it just disappeared. It was there and then it wasn't.
It was there and then it wasn't. Yeah. You know and I've seen those a couple of
times.
Sure.
So you've seen the same type of UFO multiple times would you say?
Yes.
I have.
Now there's different types.
Now the group I go with, they've seen different types.
The one they see the most is either the spherical one or the triangle one.
There's a triangle shaped that appears down in the...
I don't know if you know this but Southport...
I don't even know if I should say this live.
Or I mean on recording.
We can cut it out if you decide you don't want to.
Southport has a reason, if I'm not going to, we're good, I'm not going to say exactly,
I'll bounce around it, but there's a reason, in my opinion, there's a huge reason for,
I'll just say a huge reason military-wise, for that type of activity to be there,
you know i mean the interest
if i was an alien
uh... right now i want to check it out pretty regularly yeah so that makes and
the zoo to approach that uh... as well as an alien and look up southport
military
you'll sure i'll tell you all later yeah yeah yeah yeah i was listening to military
if you had to break your guess what's in area fifty one
hunting area fifty one the distraction
really my think everything's in a result of the two or fifty three really moving
they just win one up? Yeah, oh yeah. Not only that, there's miles and miles and
miles of tunnels all around that place and I think if there's anything that
is really there, it's gonna be in those tunnels. Yeah. So a friend of mine, I
can't mention his name, but one of my best friends, his grandfather or great
grandfather, grandfather, was at the area, was at the Roswell crash site. Wow.
- Oh wow, that's tight.
- He can't say anything, he's never been able to say
other than, and my friend, he never said anything,
you see my quotations, but he could tell by his mannerisms
when they were talking about it that--
- There's, yeah, something was up.
- Yeah, something was there.
Material that, a material that they--
- He's talking to his grandpa, his grandpa.
I didn't see anything there.
- Except for alien.
(laughing)
Or dry and early.
I mean, there's just all kinds of, there's, you know, to say that we're alone in this multiverse
or whatever you want to, you know, with infinite, infinite, infinite systems, you know, an alien
could be, I was just talking about this to somebody a couple days ago, you know, and
when I was doing the Cape for Soul Seekers show, we talked about this a lot, you know,
And we, you know, if it's a microscopic organism.
True, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's an alien, you know, by default.
You know.
Yeah, don't really think about that too much.
You're not alone.
A lot of people don't.
We brought stuff like that up on the show.
Most of our followers, you know, new people would be like, "Holy cow, I never thought
of that."
Yeah.
Because you're brainwashed by Hollywood to think otherwise, you know.
Yeah, like Mars attacks and all that.
Yeah, which is a hilarious movie.
Oh yeah, it's great.
Paul, you seen that one? The alien smokes weed. Yeah, I gotta watch that.
They do that in real life. Where is it at? Where can I watch it?
You know, is it on DVD? I saw it on DVD. Yeah, it's a good place to watch it.
Yeah, strong DVD release. I'll check it out.
Probably on Amazon I guess. Yeah, something like that. I'm curious, you should
- What are you guys discussing about?
- Yeah, I was gonna, yeah.
- Your favorite.
- What do you think, I wanna hear what,
your take on Nibiru, on Planet X.
- Whew, man, y'all are getting in deep, aren't ya?
- Dude, this guy's got the heaters.
This is why I wanted to link you two.
- Do you know the guy about the Venus guy too, by the way?
- The Venus guy?
I don't know.
- I can't remember the guy's name right off the top of my head.
This supposedly happened, the guy came,
said he was from Venus, came down.
- What?
- He was gonna give us all the technology.
- Oh, maybe.
- Look at, look at, look at, I can't,
- Was his name Billy something?
- I'm sure some of your followers will probably know it.
- Sure.
- There was a guy from Venus named Billy?
- There was, no, the Billy guy's different.
That was a different, that guy was--
- I cannot remember the guy's name.
- That was a guy, I forget what the whole thing was,
but that was a guy who, he said he was a space prophet
and he said that a virus was coming called the wolf
that was going to destroy Earth's population.
And a virus did come.
- Well this--
- And he's called the wolf 19.
Yeah, well, and a lot of other kind of variations.
But this guy was supposed to give all of his technology
and our government just turned him away or something.
Or no, I think they were gonna help each other out,
but they got all the information and then made him leave.
Or something, you know, but none of that would surprise me.
But Nubaru or Planet X,
Planet X is one of my favorite bands.
But, um, uh, you know, people have claimed to see it.
You know?
The planet itself?
Yeah.
Um, I, I, I'm not opposed to the idea of it.
Right.
Because we don't understand dimensions.
Or we, some of us understand them more than others, how dimensions work.
You know?
Um, it could be any number of things.
things. It could be not a space station but of space station origin, you know, like
like and it could be able to jump in and out of dimensions if it exists. But I am
open to the possibilities of it. Right. You know. Yeah and like have you you like
what about like Nephilim kind of stuff like ancient aliens, angel, angel hybrid.
- Is it the Anunnaki's?
- Yeah, Anunnaki, yeah.
- So, I don't wanna get in trouble.
- Okay, well, yeah, we don't wanna get you in trouble.
- But I'm gonna try to say it.
- Is, in trouble with who, the Anunnaki?
- Well, whoever might be, might hear this broadcast
because of everything else going on.
There are, I'm not gonna say it's me.
How about that?
- Sure.
- There are people that, 'cause this is a touchy subject.
- Okay, yeah.
- It's a touchy subject where I'm gonna,
and all the recent latest events
and you probably are
figure out what i'm talking about
you know
you know i a m
people for home listeners
the hell you know i think that a lot of the time you have a very good
uh... sure they're all used to it and maybe you guys could still could put it
in
sure it's later you know different yes but
believe this is all preparation
for the in a keys return
uh...
it has nothing to do with population
no no no no i don't i'm not saying this is my opinion but yes people are saying
i am saying in the paranormal world and in in in the alien world i have seen
this on website chatter
uh... maybe some kind of tool of control
the return of the uh... not right okay which is a very good like it could be
be like a categorization thing. Yes. Yeah like like you like putting a barcode.
Or maybe you have to have that whatever is in that to be able to be in the
presence of them. I mean for yeah you know any number of any number of reasons.
It could be a test, could be a categorization. It could give you superpowers on their planet.
who knows? Or be able to just carry on, you know, there could be voice translations in
that. Yeah. You know, because it's nanotechnology. Right? So, or what I'm told.
Well, does it depend on which one you got? What's that?
Does it depend on which one you got? I hope not.
Well, yeah, one of them, the Anunnaki see you and they're like, "This is my best friend.
If you got the other one, they'd kill you on sight."
- Yeah, right.
- You're screwed.
- One of them gets you pregnant.
- Yeah.
- I'd give you that one.
(laughing)
I mean, I don't know.
I have no--
- Yeah, right.
- Who does, right?
- Nobody does.
- We're just open talking here.
- Exactly.
- And I have sources and some of these people
are firm believers in this.
- Yeah.
- Everything we've just mentioned, but you know,
I do feel that there is, going back to what we were talking
about earlier about Area 51 and stuff,
I do feel that there is technology that we have that's not of this world.
And I'm a firm believer.
Now, 51, again, I think it's just a...
It's so...
I think it's just a distraction.
Really?
I mean, we all know where it is now.
Are you serious?
Exactly.
It's the pop culture.
Right.
Do I think that they probably do some sort of testing there?
Probably so, but not near as much as.
- Right.
- The only testing that they do there
is the stuff they want us to know about.
- Exactly. - That they think
we don't know about.
- It's like Count Dracula,
how he hides the existence of a real vampire.
- Yeah, yeah.
- It's more like a pop culture.
- Absolutely. - Yeah.
- Absolutely, same concept. - Exactly, yeah.
- Oh, oh, let's talk,
do you believe in any cryptid, anything?
- So the group I work with out of South--
- We love cryptids.
I had no idea.
Yeah, I love cryptos.
It's awesome.
The group I work with is called, I think it's Atlantic Cryptoid Investigations, I think.
I can't remember.
I can't remember hardly anything these days, but they're big on cryptoid investigations.
I think, you know, some, yes, they're really big on Bigfoot.
Really?
We believe that, or I say we, they, and I somewhat believe that if Bigfoot was real, he would
probably be capable, could be capable of interdimensional travel.
Yeah, well yeah, he's gotta be staying hidden somehow.
Because he is the best hide and seek player.
Absolutely.
So they think that he's more than just an animal?
think he's a some sort of alien descent you know I think he's something I think
he's something spiritual yeah I think some kind of like elemental type type
or or possible last of the Giants yeah have you ever heard in a theory that
he's Kane whoo yeah you guys all his days throwing it out there pretty sick
fucking theory yeah yeah that would be the coolest shit ever yeah if you
especially we caught him he's like yeah it's just me
we're like he's on TV on the Bible you know hey bull he's got we mean your
brother Abel he was awesome wait wait what the question would be is if that
was true look how able Kane is true yeah what if I just threw this mic through
window. I'm sorry. You're turning my mic off now. What do you think about werewolves?
You know, we kind of feel that there's a
possible relations between werewolves, Bigfoot, and the Chupacabra.
Right. Yeah, I'll feel that there some way I feel like werewolves in Bigfoot, especially that feels to me like yeah
So there's a link there. Yeah, there's some sort of you know, and again could be hand-me-down from Giants. Yeah and or experimentation
From the Giants. Well speaking in Nephilim. Do you that that is like, you know, biblical? Yeah
It's a biblical giant ballistic Giants. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's an interesting
I think that you know, it feels like that makes sense over the yeah
Did you hear about the giant they killed in Kandahar the Marines they killed?
Yeah
And in China, they're finding they're digging up graves that were they're huge. Yeah, you know, really? Yeah, great
Yeah, like I mean a huge huge bones. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, holy god in China, yeah in China this happened a couple years ago or recently
Yeah, but you know as things progress we're getting
less and less information from
Yeah. You know, for all kinds of reasons. Maybe they're building their sun. Yeah, yeah, as they're building their sun, exactly.
But, you know, same, we've covered a lot of things, you know, same thing with pyramids, you know, a lot of us feel that pyramids are a distraction for bigger things.
Right. You know. What do you mean by that? The Sphinx.
communications. So what would be distracting? It's there to cover up.
There's something under it? Either under it or more about it that we'll
never know until it's too late. Yeah. Until there's the right time and the
right, you know, a lot of people think that there's gonna be, I thought, yeah,
the end of times come, aliens return, a beam of light's gonna come out at the top of
the... That's what I've always heard about pyramids is that they're energy
conductors yeah yeah for signaling well yeah so beacons or if I was an if I was
like an alien trying to do some shit like that like I would just make every
all this shit that I put on earth I just make it invisible right who's to say
there's not I mean we could be in an invisible pyramid right now um good
point you know we've talked about so you know just like with with travel you know
everybody's I say everybody so many people are brainwashed to think that it
all has to do with the ship right when it comes to alien technology you know if
they're that advanced why would they need they may not even need a ship they
could just have a suit yeah right and and it could be a like a jump drive yeah
suit jump from dimension to dimension well that's interesting so what how so
you you seem to have mentioned a distaste for Hollywood and like
brainwashing Hollywood shit a couple not everything they do yeah but not
everything but like what what do you think in Hollywood right now is a like
almost like a surely an op I like the X-Files yeah but what is what do you see
on TV that is like like TV or movies where you see it and you're like this is
clearly funded by the military this is a cover I got you something oh lord try to
me a little bit I'm not falling for that's uh that's a great question um like Glee
they're all aliens everybody yeah yeah well and that goes back to I don't know
if any X-Files fans in the house but remember the episode when Babe Ruth
they thought anybody that was extra great at something it's like sports yeah
Babe Ruth was an alien. Yeah. I totally believe that. Yeah. I mean I
Give me what it was. Yeah, what's the threshold for how great are we talking like who?
Yeah, if they name a disease after them like Lou Gehrig, okay, okay, okay
Tom Brady is an alien sure
He does not understand human custody. You know what father-son relation?
I wouldn't surprise me in the least if he goes hey, by the way, I'm from Nubaru
There was a there was a got milk ad
He did and he said that he puts crushed ice in his milk
In the ad in the milk and they aired that on television. It was on Sports Illustrated
Look, the man is whether you like milk
He has done things that no other quarterback has ever done. It's true. It's my mom in the history of sports
I got you know, he's they call him the gopher. I mean, but
That alone cuz you didn't human. That's right. Exactly. I mean, you know, I mean
It's just there's all kinds of or anything
Any anybody I don't want to talk Tony Hawk's either, but you know nobody cares
Here can can come can come arise above
And do a great thing
When they were predicted to never be great. Yeah in my opinion could possibly
Yeah, AOC
You went you went there. I was gonna go somewhere else for sure. Why not?
I think AOC is shape-shifting. I mean she could be. I think Hillary's for sure. Do you think reptilian? Reptoid.
Absolutely. Reptoid. Yeah, yeah, she could be.
Well, I mean, you know, we're worth going out there. I mean, that's just
Again I don't know. I'm just yeah. Yeah, I liked the X-Files episode where they were talking about. Oh, yeah
like anybody in the Olympics really right like
sports a little bit musicians even healing to be an alien for all we know
that is guitar players ever
yeah you know it would be like we're not
it's true it's been a fact that you see
you see on you to now people are just doing extraordinary things yeah
with instruments
you know i think it could be a thing of what i really really any of those
millions
alienated on the uh... it could be the idea of you know and
we could go back to
to see what happens with recent
things right yeah sir things any different yeah
you know it could be d_n_a_ in their things certain sharp widely distributed
and i think that i have a lot of shit that's right
that's right
but i mean you know
uh... again i don't know if you're here and i have no clue yet but none of it
now i mean as you know we're just your talking to your final surprise me though
like none of my i don't know what you know
you know never never never built that a black
yeah we first find out about and he's like and they're watching the t_v_ and
he sees his old teacher
yeah is that there is he was an alien i don't know if she was an alien that's
so so speaking of like so let's leave the
the uh...
extra normal world for a second i'm curious what
what like kind of plain
uh... uh... terrestrial conspiracies do you
kind of hold to be true?
Well, I believe in spirits.
Yeah. You know, and look, whether you're religious or not,
you know, a lot of folks don't talk about this in church, but spirits are mentioned
more than once in the Bible.
Yeah, holy ghosts.
The horse that got stopped by the spirit,
I can't remember what book that's in. I thought it was Job, but I was wrong
because my mom told me it's not Job.
So I don't want to say the wrong Bible, book, or chapter,
but a horse stops, gets stopped, and saves the horse
and the guy riding it from crossing this bridge.
- Right.
- Right, so how can you not, you know,
believe that there are spirits in the world,
or not in the world, necessarily the world,
but that come in and out from time to time
when it's in the Bible.
- Yeah.
- So that's, you know,
to me that's affirmation enough.
- Yeah, sure.
Yeah, that makes sense.
- So that, as far as that goes, I feel, you know.
- But like, so like JFK, what's your take on JFK?
You think they capped him?
the cap him
absolutely kept the idea
he was getting ready to spill the beans
on everything really a yeah
well yeah he was going to spill though he's going to tell everybody
everything about aliens
in in the capital
and this was back then yeah
yeah you know even trump
was supposedly gonna spill the beans yeah i'm gonna get him with the stupid
ray yes yet but he will he had
he was going to play
like his last beach one of the land he was gonna
- Really? - Yeah.
- Yeah.
- I feel like that's why they declassified
as little as they did. - What they did.
- Yeah. - 'Cause he was getting ready
from what I know from all of my connections and sources,
they've all said the same thing.
He was getting, and he got,
he had no idea how deep the deep state is.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Nobody does.
- They, in my opinion, they think they do,
but there's this and the deep state could be alien
yeah in nature
yeah you know
and and do you really want to go there yeah you know what i mean
speaking of deep state i'm curious what's your take on uh... like Q
i'm more into anonymous
yeah yeah
you don't think like john podesta was executed by military tribunal and
they have a clone walking around
look anything's possible yeah it is you know it's like 60/40 bro you know what I
I used to be a lot I'm in I stay in touch with politics enough to know what's
going on yeah right we all should it was no matter what side you're on you should
all at least be aware of you know things definitely right um and and I stopped I
am unaffiliated when it comes to politics though 9/11 changed everything
from me, right? And for whatever reasons, but if we... I believe our government is
capable of anything we could possibly imagine.
Absolutely. Yeah, definitely. Especially now. Yeah, yeah. The technology that we have right now.
Yeah. Do you ever kind of think about what if they got real lazy and just did
9/11 again? You'd be like yeah like of course you guys fucking...
What you could do with the towers or... How do you know that's not in the works right now?
Probably is. Probably is. I mean I'm just saying with all that's going on... But like come up with another
thing Jesus Christ. Yeah. You know? Yeah. Did you think on the 20th
anniversary did you think something big was happening? I was still in the fire
department then so we were all on calls and we they didn't know what was gonna
happen. Oh yeah. They set off a counting-wide pager on our pagers. Oh really?
2001 yeah yeah and and we all those that could you know yeah reported to the
station you know yeah did you wait firefighters here started heading in to
New York just we had a county-wide page and you know cuz they didn't know what's
gonna if there was gonna be attacks well cuz we have oh yeah yeah kinds of stuff
around here so yeah they just said those that could go flaming Amy's what if they
took that one out that'd be tough that'd be an actual tragedy a
a gastro strophic explosion
now i was going to have a nice clean i want to know
i hope we're getting close the end of the i want to i want to a lightning round
okay i was one ask you what you think about some stuff on was sold
you know just
brief and and yet here i i got one
uh... have you ever been uh... talk to a ghost didn't speak english
i've gotten e_v_p_ has wasn't english really what language
We never were able to get an interpretator to come in,
but we thought it was German.
- Okay.
- Ah, cool.
- Do you think there is a portal to hell
in the Large Hadron Collider at CERN?
- I think there's a portal to multiple places.
- Okay.
- You just gotta be able to, you know.
- Not just, yeah.
- You gotta, you know, again,
be careful what you look for.
- Yeah, yeah.
- You know, I think vortexes are possible portals.
- Mm-hmm.
Do you think the heart attack gun is real?
- The what?
attack gun the CIA do you think the CIA has a gun that can that can give you a
heart attack going back to an earlier statement yeah yeah yeah I believe yeah
I believe you're hurt a Havana syndrome I have not oh it's like all these like
like us like spies and fucking government workers and shit go to Cuba
and they come back they all get a stomachache it's pretty weird right it's
the food. Probably. They're big on spices. They're not used to cupanos and plantains over there.
Now it could be government related because of the food. You think they make the food
spicy to weed out all the whitey spies? I think it's funny imagining a white guy pretending
to be a Cuban spy. They're not going to let a softy be a spy. Yeah, definitely not. Do
Do you think Atlantis exists?
I believe in, maybe not Atlantis like we know Atlantis, but I believe that there is possibly
something.
Some lost continent.
Yeah.
How about like the Tartarian Empire?
Do you think that we developed technology in the past that was further than what we
have now and then something wiped it out?
I think we had help.
Yeah, okay.
I mean, we were, some believe in cavemen and some don't, but if there were cavemen, we
went from cavemen mentality to where we are.
We skipped, yeah.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
Now, help, how did we help?
Could have been mind through thought or premonitions, projected, astral projection, all kinds of
different ways, but I think we had help.
Oh, I have one. So what do you think of the theory, it's like a common debunking theory,
that most ghost sightings are sleep paralysis?
Absolutely. I wouldn't say most, but a lot.
But a lot of them are.
We've actually had a case and we were able to prove that it was sleep paralysis.
We put cameras and recorders in this lady's room and watched her for a period of time.
and she popped up and her eyes were open
and she popped up out of bed and her eyes were wide open.
- Yeah.
- And she kept-- - Oh man.
- But she was asleep.
- Okay, yeah.
- Right?
And she kept having a recurring dream
that there was a ghost at the foot of her bed.
- Yeah.
- She was just--
- Yeah, yeah.
Do you think there are artificial structures on the moon?
Do you think there's aliens or anything up there?
- Buzz Aldrin does.
Buzz Aldrin does.
- Really, he does?
- Have you seen his,
you need to look up his video on YouTube
about the moon, the dark side, you know.
I think it was Buzz Aldrin.
Astronaut claims that the aliens told them
to stay away from the dark side of the moon.
- Yeah.
- I don't know if you've, it's on YouTube.
Or they might have taken it down.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- How about remote viewing?
You believe in remote, like ESP?
- Absolutely.
- Yeah. - Telekinetics, all of that.
- Have you met anyone who could do remote viewing?
- I've known a couple of people
that were really into studying astro,
was it astro?
- Astral projection?
- Yeah, astral projections.
- I used to try to do that.
- Did you really?
- Yeah, in high school I used to try to do it
you know remember that comedian Sinbad yeah yeah he used to talk about it and I
was like that's so fucking cool man it is cool I mean I don't have enough time to
these days to wanna of course I wanted to do it I mean it's hideous man what
you know oh yeah I wanted to do it and then go to the you know watch movies for
free my big plan dodging demons to fucking watch the new Fast and Furious
probably would be a bad thing if I could do it yeah it's true who knows what
Sinister plans I would yeah, I was able to yeah, you guys have any other questions
Oh, it's okay. So the big one I've been into recently see monsters
Okay
You think you think so Nessie's definitely really uh, it's something similar
- I mean, look. - Think it's a dinosaur
or a monster?
- We don't, I think it's its own species.
- Really? - Yeah.
- Yeah.
- I don't think it's necessarily related to,
if it's, you know, to me,
and or there might, I feel like there's more than one.
- Yeah.
- I don't think they're seeing the same.
No, there's gotta be tons of them.
- Yeah. - That's what I think.
- Look, we know very little about deep sea anything.
- So little. - Yeah.
- Yeah. - Oh yeah, that's the--
We want to go to space and we know hardly jack crap about the ocean.
Speaking of lizard people, where do you land on Elon?
That's hilarious.
You think he's a lizard?
You're not the only one that has talked to me about this recently.
Really?
I like Elon.
Oh you do?
I mean I like some of the things.
Yeah? You don't think he's a controlled opposition for the people who want to keep us from space?
Um, I like that he does his own thing, because he can.
See what he named his damn kid?
No.
You didn't see it?
That's messed up.
You know in cartoons...
Can't be any worse than Blanket.
No, it's worse.
Oh, it's really.
You know in comic books when someone says the F word and they do F and then pound, sign, exclamation point.
That's what he named his kid.
Pretty much, man.
much man. Well I like him a little less now. But I mean I like I like his vision. Yeah.
You know what I mean? I think his vision is is genuine. You think CIA ever uses
self-driving cars to like assassinate people? Goes back to the whatever the
government. What do you think about zombies? I think I'm prepared. Yeah.
yeah really yeah I'm a gun owner so yeah and a sword owner so nice the sword is
how you get them yeah broadly what I know they said lightning round but there's
just so much shit to talk about right and we could do another yeah I would love to
of course but what is when if you if you when do you think the apocalypse is
coming like do you think we're inching towards you think we're getting close I
I don't think we'll know. I mean a lot of people seem to think it. Here's what I got to say about
and again I hate sound like I'm picking on China but I feel like they're
trigger-happy right now. Yeah. They're harvesting souls dude. That's true. I feel like
they could just snap. China have nothing against the Chinese people. Yeah.
Beautiful culture. Yeah absolutely. Love them. But I feel like their
government has lost its mind. Yeah. I'm just saying. Yeah. I mean I feel like
they have just and they're gonna if if anybody's gonna swing first think it's
gonna be China I think it's gonna be China or or North Korea. US I mean always
been cool hand Luke about that kind of stuff right? What you know with how crazy
look I've even talked we've even talked about this you know on our shows you
know when 2019 some a lot of people feel that this whole universe went into a
different dimension really our whole 2015 2019 2019 okay yeah we're still there
something yeah really like how would that work like the how would we not notice
that we slipped into something different that's you haven't noticed look at how
crazy everything is right now all over across the world right I mean Elon
Musk he named his baby though I mean or McDonald dud yeah yeah yeah true I mean
it's just it's just crazy so but I feel like if I don't feel that we would
strike first I feel like China or Russia but I feel like China's you know lost
it's just lost you think that's how we go out though nuclear war it's not gonna be
some kind of fucking alien planet devourer yeah yeah just go like this one
day maybe do we just blink out of existence could be it could be in
relations they could be in relations and they want it you know want an
apocalypse to come in and take over so that goes back to the terraforming
yeah the soul star that's right building yeah yeah I guess it makes sense yeah
right so this could be all part of somebody else's exactly and it's all
leading it's all leading towards something project blue beam right is that
what it is project blue beam oh really yep fake the the fake second coming of
of the fake messiah holographic
mark it a beast
some believe it's happening right now
yeah could be
very scary
you know if you read the bible
whatever there's
you know god
if you believe in god
supposedly made our bodies
perfect the way they are
and doesn't want anything
that's in there
in their it doesn't want anything artificial in our you know
you know i mean the any sort of technologies
but we're putting them in their
so these damn smart for you know are we are parts of the are we closer to the
end of times quite possibly
yeah i guess that makes sense because of
not just one thing
a lot of double-edged yet on across the globe
yeah yeah you know
i mean even so it's not even a letter even stuff like like glasses and stuff
if that can be like, I feel like,
that you know, it just--
- Tattoos. - All incrementally.
Tattoo, yeah, you know, incrementally.
- Yeah.
Nothing is out of our government's grasp at this point.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Nothing. - Yeah.
- You know, the sky's the limit, you know?
- Yeah.
Well, I feel like we should probably wrap this up,
but I do, I am curious,
what do you think happens when you die?
'Cause I know you,
what do you think the experience of dying is like?
- Oh, well, if you have to use the bathroom.
- Yeah. (laughing)
- I had heard that.
That's the answer is you shit yourself. You would absolutely shit yourself.
Oh yeah, we watched like the whale explosion videos the other day.
Strong point. Yeah, I think that happens to us. You think you explode?
Well, I think that's our version of that.
This could be a whole other topic on whether you're spiritual or not.
I believe we ascend to somewhere.
Now, I don't necessarily, this is my personal
opinion or whatever it's worth, I believe some may ascend directly to somewhere and some
may not so much, just depending on how - not necessarily whether they lived a good life
or a bad life, but whether or not whoever the creator is may have something more for
that particular person to do still even after the ascension or in the process of ascension.
- Yeah, that makes sense.
- That makes a lot of sense.
- And that's why we see or have,
you know, like I think as Catholic,
they believe in purgatory.
- Yeah.
- Right, and I don't necessarily believe in,
they believe in purgatory, I think,
as a more long-term, I'm not necessarily sold on that.
- Wait, actually, I have one more question for you.
Do you think there's,
would you be surprised if you died and became a ghost?
- I would love it.
(laughing)
- You would love it?
- Oh, yeah.
love I mean the things that I could do you just love it you just people I would
torment your bit of a prankster who's on your list oh gosh I don't want to get in
trouble
family members possibly you know so yeah a little brother you know there's a few
things that I would you know I'd scare the shit out of uncle chip I would
probably irritate the shit out of my sister.
(laughter)
- Yeah, easy to do.
- You know, I mean, I'll just prank her constantly.
- Real petty stuff when you're a ghost.
- Absolutely.
- All right, good to know.
- These keys are gonna go in this room.
- Yeah, yeah.
- You know?
- Yeah, I think that's the right idea.
- Nothing detrimental, just a little--
- No, no murder or pushing.
- No, no, nothing like that.
- Maybe, but no.
- No.
- Depends on who I'm stuck with.
- Yeah, true.
- Yeah.
- Depends on who I'm stuck with.
- All right.
- You know, you could possibly be assigned a person
and not have any, you know, not have a choice.
- That's true, true, yeah.
- All right, well thank you so much, man.
What do you want to plug?
Like what should people check out?
- Capeford Soul Seekers on Facebook, our site's down.
Hopefully soon we'll have
the Capeford Soul Seekers show back up.
We've got some episodes on YouTube,
Capeford Soul Seekers show.
And we got a couple episodes on Twitch,
but the audio's not great on 'em.
Go to YouTube, Capeford Soul Seekers show.
- All right, awesome.
- Thank you so much for coming on, man.
- It was awesome, yeah, thank you.
Thank you guys for having me.
Bye y'all.