Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
Okay.
Ooh.
Alright.
They told me I fell off.
I needed that.
Yeah.
To fell off what?
Humpty Tumpty's wall.
Caleb's sick again.
Still.
Still faking it.
He's on a ventilator.
But he's still sick.
He's still sick.
but he's yeah yeah he's faking he he found out that there are paintings of
cartoon characters in the the children's ward at the hospital and he pretended to
be a seven-year-old with kovat yeah he had fond memories of watching his
watching the VHS tape with a nebulizer as a child and he's trying to return to
tradition. So he's so he got put on a ventilator.
What's that like purple disc of asthma medicine?
Adver, you guys are. Oh, yeah, yeah.
Yeah. It's giving you the CD roms.
Yeah, my kid can't breathe too good, but he's well, 10,000 hours.
They're giving you Pokemon TMS.
Yeah. Yeah.
I remember just huffing toys like if ever there was like a nozzle in a toy,
like even just like a Lego piece.
If there's like a hollow hole in it,
I would just suck it in and just get a
little tiny note of the factory.
Yeah, yeah, smelling toys.
Great smelling stuff in general.
Awesome Caleb lost that experience.
Oh yeah, he can't smell shit right now.
You can't smell or taste smell.
We get to smell.
Even smell actual shit.
Yeah, I texted him.
I'm this.
What is that?
I can smell this right now.
Diddycon coin from a wonder ball.
Mm. Oh, I found this at my
friend's house.
I never had a wonder ball of toys.
And what's a wonder ball with like sweets in it?
Yeah, you get it.
Your dad is probably in like the side.
Yeah, it's probably the side of the box.
It's like a knockoff Kinder Egg.
Yeah. Yeah, it's what it's what we're allowed to have.
Pop Wonder Balls.
Now I have two crazy coins.
See, this is so sick.
This was a crazy coin.
It's a really good.
Yeah. Why?
Mike Pence in front of Trump.
This is the Pence commemorative coin.
Oh I see.
And then on the back it's got Indiana.
The place where he fucked his wife.
Yeah the place.
That's what it's commemorating.
We should get challenge coins made.
That would actually be so sick to have his merch fucking challenge coins.
What's challenge coins?
I was just agreeing because I want some coins. I want some more coins.
Yeah, any type of coin.
Those like special coins that they make.
All coins are special.
I don't know why they're called challenge coins, but it's like the like, you know, if you like.
It's a challenge not to eat them.
But no, you know, like they'll make them for the police and it'll have like a.
Oh yeah.
Punisher skull on it or something.
Yeah.
Oh, you leave them on dead bodies.
on their eyes. You put the challenge coins over a dog's eyes.
Yeah. Yes. The only challenge coin, the only time I've ever... There's that video of Korn
performing at a USO show or whatever for a bunch of military people. And then at the end, this guy
shakes the hand and is like, "Now, I don't do this for a lot of people, but I'm going to give you my
coin." And like, "Here's a special coin for performing." And I want to be able to do that.
I want to have a bag of coins that I carry around. And if someone like, if someone treats me well,
like a, like a fairy tale, genie, like if someone I'm asking for help to cross the street. And if
someone helps me, I give them my coin, give them a coin. And if they don't frogs and snakes will
spill forth from their mouth, whenever they open it again for the rest of their life,
their mouth. Oh, okay.
No, it's when they open anything.
That'd be a cool superpower if you open anything frogs and snakes come out.
Yeah, I guess you need some definitional criteria about what you can sell.
No, if you open a web page it's always frogsandsnakes.com.
A digital... I was gonna say a digital frog hops across the screen,
You can't get rid of it.
Yeah. Frogs and snakes dot com.
You're a lot better.
No matter what you type into the URL bar, you'll go to frogs and snakes.
Yeah, you can't open your hand, I guess, to grasp anything.
There's no frog. Yeah.
Frog pops out of the middle of your hand.
Do you ever
you ever see this movie called The Electric Grandmother?
No, it's based off of icing the body electric,
which I think is like red Bradbury's like.
I think it's a Twilight Zone episode, too, but there's like a grandmother
that comes from space.
She's like a robot.
And the kids love her because she's the best grandmother ever.
And the reason she's the best grandmother ever is because she can shoot
orange juice out of one finger and milk out of the other.
And the kids go fucking bananas.
They love her super grandma.
That was it.
Was it like she was it was it like a situation where they had a
normal grandmother and she like replaced.
Yes, grandmother.
They're like, oh, you're so much better by a car and then the
new grandmother came from outer space.
That's that that's that.
No, no, I think it was like what came from outer space was like
a jigsaw puzzle.
That's like a steel heart and then when they put the pieces
together, it's like an invitation to go to like this Willy
Wonka Factory and they assemble their grandmother, like they walk around and they get to make their
grandmother from different parts. That's that beautiful biting social commentary that Ray
Bradbury is known for. What if a grandma? Yeah. Is crazy. And such, yeah. Yeah. Before I sit down
and write every book I think to myself. Basically grandmas are beverage slaves.
Those aren't even, come on, it's a grandmother, they should be shooting hot cocoa out of one.
Yeah, I agree. They should be shooting it. And you know what else? They poop lasagna.
That's really good, yeah. They poop a whole lasagna for you.
Yeah, and when it's their time of the month, a gingerbread slides out of a slot.
A little gingerbread man. A whole gingerbread house.
Once a woman hits menopause, a uterine lining is replaced with a little ginger snap cookie for the grandkids.
Yeah.
They don't need any eggs anymore, so it's just like, well, how else am I going to provide?
It's just actual eggs. It's just little hard-boiled eggs.
[laughter]
that uh I think it was at yes Cumberland Farms I saw they have buffalo eggs which
was a like you know like you know when they like make like a soy egg or
whatever or like raw egg hmm you heard of a boy egg virgin no egg we can talk
about that after yeah we'll get into that later but it was a like they make
like a soy egg just like yeah they like they marinate the the hard-boiled egg in
soy sauce and it just like sucks up the soy sauce but they did it with buffalo sauce.
So it's just this like bright orange egg in a bag.
Cheeto egg.
Yeah.
That's good when you put like a...
You soak an egg in like maple syrup or something? What is it?
Or like not maple syrup. What is the substance that you soak an egg in and it like grows really big?
We did an experiment in my science class.
I think it's vinegar.
It might be vinegar.
Vinegar make egg big. Google images.
Yep.
This is the first.
This is the first picture.
I googled vinegar make egg big
and then this is the first result.
[Laughter]
Oh, have you seen that video?
No, what is this?
It's just a picture of two eggs and one is bigger.
It's like one of those.
Remember those like, it was on
like Facebook videos that like the I think this is like blossom or whatever
one of those fucking like like life hack companies this is presented as like a
life hack to make your egg bigger
we should be doing this in my science class
this will solve world hunger pretty quick
why you should put vinegar in eggs the times of India and then they have a
picture of like they have a picture of an egg but the focus and the pixelation
makes it look like it's just a cloud in a bowl. The Times of India has a lot of
really good articles. Times of India is a great website. Look at this picture of this egg. Like it literally looks like a miasma.
Yeah, it focused on the wrong part of the egg. I think it focused on the bowl rather than the egg.
Jesus Christ. Yeah, it's like it's focusing on one little reflection on the
surface of the egg and then everything else looks like someone washed it in
Photoshop. In the article the caption of this photo is "make naked eggs"
okay but anyway. There's something else you can soak an egg in that like
peels away or like makes the skin or the shell like you can just take the shell
off and then the egg is like it's not cooked but it's just like there's a very
very thin jelly surface underneath the shell.
Hydrochloric acid.
It might be, it might be shell remover.
Shell be gone.
You ever put that hard chocolate shell on your ice creams?
Oh yeah!
Oh that shit was so good, they had the Reese's, the Reese's flavor one.
Peanut butter chip shell.
That one was so good.
It's actually not that, I think it is just a clever little science experiment, but I don't
I don't think it makes ice cream taste any better.
No, but like cracking into it and then eating the ice cream out of it.
If you're right, you crack is so cool.
Yeah, we've we've literally we're so autistic now
that like every other tick tock video is just cracking something open.
But the thing you're cracking open is just something that you've made
to be cracked open.
Yeah, I would love to get to a point in society where, yeah, those like little
hammers that they have on like dessert cooking shows, you know,
like that that's just like a normal place setting like it's like fork knife spoon hammer
that should just be part of it the little like crab shards yeah the crab uh if you have nothing
to crack if you have nothing to crack open in your dinner you can use it on your plate
when you're done crack a plate when you're still hungry yeah you crack your teeth yeah
but i want to go back to virgin boy egg because have you not heard of a virgin boy egg pat
No, I haven't.
You're gonna really like this dish.
Yeah?
You're gonna make a lot of money with your piss once you find out about virgin-
I'm reading- I'll read from Wikipedia for you for virgin boy egg.
"Virgin boy eggs are a traditional dish of Dongyang, Zhejiang, China,
in which the eggs are boiled in the urine of young boys who are presumably peasants,
preferably under the age of ten."
What?
"The dish translates literally to 'boy egg' and is a springtime tradition of the city
where the urine is collected from prepubescent peasant boys."
Why did they do that?
It protects you. It protects you and it cures you.
Oh, well, you didn't tell me it protects me.
It's like medicine.
Well, you know, I had some qualms, but now that it offers protection, I mean,
I'm... Virgin boy piss is like such a hot little commodity pretty much everywhere.
Yeah. I just the fact that there is a food that's actually called a virgin boy egg is...
Yeah, that's messed up. It's incredible.
I love it. Yeah, I mean, the fact that virgin isn't in the actual
child, like just you, you know, it's a virgin boy.
Any boy egg.
Any boy egg, huh?
This says even a boy who fucks you can you could battle true.
Listen to this.
Listen to this virgin boy eggs are widely accepted as a time-honored
tradition of the city rather than considered taboo as they are
most other cultures boy egg vendors go to elementary schools
in the city where they collect urine from young boys, preferably
under the age of 10. The children, having been raised in the city and its culture, are used
to the practice. As young boys would in schools from many other cultures, they excuse themselves
from class when they feel the urge to urinate. However, instead of going to the restroom,
they relieve themselves in the basin that the vendors place in the hallways. Some vendors
go as far as to wait with containers in parks or public restrooms for a parent who is willing
to let their child offer urine.
Can you piss directly into the cloaca of a hen to make a boy egg instead of pissing into
a basin and then yeah, ferment it in the reproductive system.
Go, yeah, go right to the source. Yeah, that could be an efficient way. We can maybe make
a factory like sexual. Maybe that's like a penetration. Yeah, that does make it sexual.
Yeah, there I if I'm if I'm eating an egg, I don't want to think about sex.
No, no, never. Well, that's another thing that you can try it too,
is like a fertilized chicken egg, like an egg with a little
with the baby in it embryo in it. Yeah.
Yeah.
Yes.
And I know they don't come on.
Yeah, they're cool.
Oh, yeah, it's just been around for forever.
They preserve it in like clay and it turns like green and brown
and looks like a gemstone.
Yuck. Yeah, I'm century eggs and gross when the boys go to collect their urine in the basin.
Does that mean that like boy eggs are like, it's like a hundred different boys piss, like in one sort of ground beef mix.
Like you don't know which animal.
It's like the Fiesta mix.
I don't know which is more perverse is like having a boy egg that came from one boy.
Yeah, or from like a thousand.
I think I think the thousand boys is worse unless you want the the single one because of who the boy is.
Yeah, you know him if you know the one boy, if you know, that's like a million times worse.
I think it's also I think it's less perverse if the if you're related to the boy,
if it's one boy, because then it's like it's a family favor.
Right. But if it's like if it is someone in your neighborhood who you like see on his bike every
day. I don't think you can pick at all. I think you're not allowed to pick. You're definitely
not allowed to pick. I think the best case scenario for the virgin boy egg is it's like
a raffle and you get a random boy. What if you get a really awful boy? What if you get a stinky
nasty boy? What if you get a little troublemaker? A Dennis the Menace type. If you're going to eat
a virgin boy egg and you find out who the boy is and you're like I don't want this anymore
that also is really bad you can't be doing that they'll make you eat it if you say true
because that means that you're thinking more about the boy than the egg
yeah yeah what if you do get some like little Dennis the menace little fucking rascal type
and he's like uh he replaces his pee with like dr pepper yeah like yeah what if what if you get like
a drug addict kid. Yeah, and then you can't get enough of his boy eggs. You want to keep
going back to the source. You're like, sorry, we don't do repeats. You lucky enough to win
the raffle twice in a row. And then they should also make an at home test kit. Like if there's
no boys in your area, you should end like, let's say you don't want to eat a boy egg
right now, but you do want one in a week.
You should be able to buy a little vat of piss to do it. That's what everyone in China,
in China gets that for Christmas instead of an air fryer.
[Laughter]
They get a boy egger.
And if they've been naughty, they get a century egg.
Yeah.
They get a shit egg.
That's the other part of the raffle.
First you draw a boy's name and then you draw out a piece of paper and it's either yellow or brown.
Uh, no, I got brown this year.
Fuck.
Yeah.
And then if you've been really good, you get a girl egg.
Like really good.
Yeah, like, like only the emperor gets that.
I would eat a girl egg.
Would you?
Boy egg sounds kind of nasty, but.
Boy egg?
That sounds sus.
Yeah.
I feel like boy egg should just be an urban dictionary term for poop.
I think that that's what boys lay.
Yeah.
Boys lay poop as eggs.
Oh man.
Yuck.
Now I'm thinking about poop instead of...
Instead of delicious eggs.
We don't do that on this show.
We don't talk about eating poop or poop in general.
Yeah. No, no way.
I feel like we know.
So maybe just let me know if we have talked to us before.
If you got COVID and you couldn't taste you, you got to eat
a piece of poop, right?
So I was talking to this guy.
Ask Caleb.
I guess you guys know Matthew.
I was talking to him about New Year's and he was like, yeah, me and my friends were all
sitting around and watching this woman who eats her own shit.
And she like has this whole she's like a mother.
YouTube or I don't think it's on YouTube.
It must be on her own fucking website or something.
Yeah, she eats her own shit.
She like takes herself around shit and she like talks about her philosophy of shit eating
that it's like it's the only product that you can really create.
And then he was like, yeah.
And then we looked at the clock and it was 10 minutes past midnight.
Like we completely missed.
That's I don't think I could do that.
I don't I really don't think I could watch somebody their own shit, even on video without vomiting.
And he was like, yeah, like a video guy.
I feel like maybe you would be able to.
I was like, no, I don't.
Video.
Yeah, I don't think you I think it would probably make me sick.
I don't be able to watch.
I think that would be pretty gross to me.
What it what if you if you if you watch the video like he wanted to do it
He was saying like someone was trying to talk him into doing it like as like the first post-ironic
Shit eating performance are like doing it, you know sort of
cringe way
Then he was like, yeah, I was like doing research about how to like ice your taste buds that you don't taste it
I'm just like I will break up with you. I can't believe you would choose eating your own shit over being with me
and you're like, "well, I don't know."
I'm an artist, so...
Damn.
That's fucking crazy.
I would never eat a poop.
Let me go on record.
I think there's a timeline someday in my life
where I try it.
Like a, like a, like a, like a
Terminator type timeline, though.
Like a very bad one.
Yeah, like something has to go very wrong
on
honor when the robot war is over. Yeah, if I was if the only way I could defeat the robots
was by eating poo, maybe. Yeah, maybe. Or maybe if like maybe I could fight alongside
the robots, but they they make me eat my own poop before. Yeah. The only scenario is if
like I was like, like disguised as like a guy that everybody hates. And I did it on
live TV. That would be cool. Like you're you're in like a like a mission impossible. Which
Which one is that?
Three?
Two?
You're in one of those masks that looks very realistic and you're like, "Hey guys!
It's me, Jimmy Stewart!
I'm back from the dead!
I'm here to eat poop!
I'm here to eat poop on TV!"
Imagine they finally get the Jurassic Park technology all fitted up for humans and shit
Yeah, like there are five a bunch of dead presidents, but there's some like there's some some
Glitch in the system and franklin becomes addicted to shit. Yeah, they all just crave they
They just crave eating poop constantly
It's wonderful you've put me on the 100 bill. Can I use this to buy poop to eat?
Like they're like how many turds can I buy with this 100 bill i'll sign it
they unveil like these intellectual giants from the past that they've resurrected like Einstein is there
and then they like yeah they're they're televised again they just all just walk into the bathroom
they're still mic'd up and he does here yeah this is amazing
This is delicious!
Like when Tom Cruise runs out of the Oprah studio to talk to Katie Holmes, but they're
just running to get food for their speech.
And it's not even a situation where it's like some like animalistic like dog desire got
created in their brain.
Like they just think it's awesome.
Yeah!
That's what the future is!
For some reason they're like, "Oh, thank God!
We always dreamed about the future where everyone could eat poop all the time without getting
worried about getting sick. Yeah. So sick. So nasty. So nasty. I've been thinking, I
mean, I kind of lost my sense of smell, but I think that, uh, I hate it. I think it's
so disgusting when people talk about like a fart or a shit and they talk about what
food. It smells like that specific smell. That to me is so, I want a fart or a shit
to like, I want people to talk about what person it came out of. Like your farts and your shits
always smell like this, even though that's not true. But to me, it's so nasty to think about
what diet led to the specific smell. Why? It's simply an equation.
Why? Do you fear mathematics? Yeah. Gordita plus my dad equals...
Yeah, yeah, I think I, you know, I might ruffle a few feathers here, but I'm going to go. I think that
farts and poops are nasty, no matter what they come from. And I'm not afraid to say it.
I think they're funny as soon as you bring up the food that creates.
Yeah.
I think they're funny and playful. But as soon as you say like, yeah, noodles, I want to,
I want to fucking vomit.
Okay. So if you saw, if you saw a video.
I think it's funny to blame the food.
I can't explain it, but I think it's grotesque.
Yes, if you saw a video of someone eating poop, okay, and you vomited from seeing the video,
and then you found out immediately after you vomited that it was completely fake,
would you feel cheated?
I just eat the puke.
Would you feel, would it like shatter your worldview?
I'd eat the puke.
I don't think so. I think I get sick from like, or I get queasy from watching Peter Griffin and
his family vomit. That sort of makes me feel a little bit ill.
Yeah, specifically them.
Yeah. And I also get a boner when I see like Jessica Rabbit. I don't feel cheated.
I don't feel cheated after I come in my pants spontaneously after seeing a picture of
Scooby-Doo's girlfriend from the alien
God oh my oh, oh wow
Christ
Yeah
Yeah to me that's real
Even as soon as as soon as my body has a response to something it is it is it is a sacrament. It's real
That's very true like I salivate when I see you know
Yeah, Patrick get off the computer. I
I'm done waiting 20 minutes to bring it up. I'm gonna start bringing up first five minutes from now on
Yeah, you have to read out loud what is on your screen right now
Top to be buck answer 5mu
on white ice cream FW 7 505 men's shoes size 11
frogs and snakes calm forever
Now do you have a guy who needs that fucking curse I do I I need to get back on adderall or something
It's like we've been recording on zoom and it has been so hard for me not to just like look at shit while we're recording
That seems like that seems like you should do some work on yourself. Yeah, you should get what you need is you need like horse blinders
Yeah, maybe cuz my monitors right here. So don't look at the what's that?
Oh
What my meeting will end in 10 minutes
Dangling keys in front of me did they turn off my oh, they definitely did dude
They turned off my zoom premium down now today. Oh, it makes it cuz it's the new year. Oh fuck
No, but it still says I'm licensed. What the fuck? Oh
All right, ah
Wow, well
over
10 more minutes of every group
Okay, what the fuck this is gonna are we gonna have to buy our own zoom? That's all right
You guys gotta pay us that you guys have to pay us way. I'm not paying for zoom zoom sucks. Yeah
Period in this episode where each of us is in our own separate void before we reconvene. Yeah
We'll call it out when it's about to happen. Yeah, so don't stop your recording or anything. We'll just count it down like New Year's
Yeah, cuz it shows
Is that so much pressure to this episode that I could see a countdown to the top my screen where everything's gonna fall apart
Patrick just started looking at pictures of fucking shoes again
What do you think? You think I didn't just shift monitors?
Yes.
I'm putting it on the other monitor now.
That's your mission impossible is moving one fucking brush window to the other monitor.
One chrome tab.
And it takes him two movies to finish the art.
Oh man. Oh man. This is scary now. Oh, this is the scariest shit of all time. Let's think
of an eight minute thing to do. All right. Let's think of a seven, seven and a half second
thing to do. I've got an idea. What's your idea? Doo-wop song. Doo-wop song? Go ahead.
Okay, do you know any
No, yes
I haven't had an idea. It doesn't mean I had a song
Well, you're the one who said song
Okay
Bought a bottle by a baby
blue
You guys didn't fucking what the fuck it's you it's we have eight minutes to kill you they were gonna jump in
*Badly singing the Blue Moon theme*
I don't know what to do.
One of you has to do the
*Badly singing the Blue Moon theme*
You guys don't know?
God damn it dude. This sucks.
We've been trying to start a doo-wop band out of the podcast for years.
And now we finally get the opportunity and we don't even fucking take it
I'm looking at we could use of virgin boy eggs. Yeah, did you know that seems better than a do-up song?
They're supposed to prevent heatstroke. That's one of the really health benefits. Yeah, how does it prevent heatstroke? That's like
That's because of the boy pee
All right. Well, you didn't say that's the effect of the boy pee duh. Mm-hmm
There is I searched with quotes yummy boy egg, and it says no results
I
Guess they don't taste good
Boy egg, there's no I there's no universe where a boy egg is good. You know
At least this is so fucked
It's the end of a school day in the eastern Chinese city of Dongyang and eager parents collect their children after a hectic day of
primary school. But that's just the start of busy times for
dozens of egg vendors across the city deep in coastal Zhejiang
province who ready themselves to cook up a unique springtime
snack favor by local residents basins and buckets of boys
urine are collected from primary school toilets. That sentence
should get you shouldn't be able to have a website if you
read that sentence. Didn't you didn't you just read that? Well,
no, that was like not basins and buckets basins and buckets
are and also collected from the
toilets is this one.
Buckets of boys.
Brown.
Yeah, it's also also part of the most.
I think one of the most fucked up
parts of this this food is that
it's a street food.
Yeah, yeah.
You don't go to a restaurant
and order hot dogs.
There's just a guy outside
who's selling you it.
Yeah, it's like getting a special
or religious about it.
It's like getting a pretzel
in Central Park.
Yeah, it's like getting a quick snack on the way to work.
Yeah, and they charge like you can dunk it in your coffee.
Probably could.
Yeah. Yeah.
That's like that's what that's that's Chinese coffee instead of Irish coffee.
A splash of boys urine.
There's really not any interesting reviews of boy eggs, unfortunately.
You'd think there would be.
I thought there would be.
Wait, Kinder Eggs in Korea...
Yeah, Boy Eggs were... that was originally a knockoff of a Kinder Egg.
It was a Kindergarten Egg.
And if you would crack it open, there would be a little pouch of Kindergarten Boy Urine.
Damn, that's not true.
I don't know what a... I guess in Korea there are Boy Eggs and Girl Eggs, but those refer to different kinds of Kinder Eggs.
This is a lot of egg talk this episode. This is the egg-isode.
Oh, have I ever told you guys about Flottie? The website Flottie?
No. What's that?
What the fuck, dude? Okay, hold up. Wait, wait. Before we do this,
I'm on a Paleo blog, this post about virgin boy eggs, and this woman is, she has pictures
of her sons holding up beakers of urine. Are they smiling or are they crying?
not really smiling but they're not unhappy. Listen to this. First we had to collect enough
of the double O's wee wee to cover six pastured eggs in a medium saucepan. For a couple of
days we had them piddle outside into a Tupperware container that we kept sealed in the fridge.
We did our best to collect the urine first thing in the morning so that it would be super
concentrated with nutrients. When we collected enough bubbly piss, we poured it in a medium
saucepan and gently dunked in a half dozen eggs. What the hell?
Here's what you do.
Bring the eggs to a roiling boil before removing them
from the steaming hot piss with a strainer.
Roiling boil.
All right, you guys got to go to flotty.com.
OK, how do you spell that?
It's e-e-posted. No, I just posted it in the link.
Flotty.
What is flotty?
They're just egg products that are in a bag.
There's Floddy Baby. Floddy Baby are the first eggs of young, alive hens that have just begun to lay eggs.
Although they are smaller than other eggs, their taste and quality is very special.
Consume Floddy Baby that we put up for sale in 4-egg and 8-egg packs with real pleasure.
Floddy Sports?
Yeah, Floddy Sports. They're sports eggs.
Sports eggs!
The sport of an active life requires vitamins and minerals more than normal.
The egg is one of the foods that you can get the required nutrients in the purest and most
natural form.
Consume Flauti Sports with great pleasure for an organic life.
Sports eggs.
God damn, dude.
And then you can satisfy your curiosity on the FAQ.
What is the difference of Flauti Sports from other eggs?
Sports eggs, dude.
I'm not going to get over that.
Sports eggs is really, really good.
They have an Instagram account.
Let's see what's going on here.
Nothing interesting, just a bunch of pictures of eggs.
This is a... what is this company?
They're an egg company.
Yeah, but like what's the...
I guess they're Turkish.
Yeah, they're Turkish.
All right, less than a minute before the bomb goes off.
Oh, it says 1/24 for me.
What does yours say?
Mine just says less than a minute.
Mine says 119.
Okay. Dude, this is so stressful.
Yeah.
Alright, well.
I'm gonna quickly try to read.
Why are your packages in paper bag shape?
By doing so, we use less papers and ink, different from other types of packaging,
in order not to harm the nature.
You can also use our packages as a real paper bag.
You can make a major contribution to recycling in nature
with flotty packages.
Oh, that's good.
By putting your little accessories in it.
It would be stylish.
Okay, now it says less than one minute on mine.
It's just gonna end randomly.
Yeah, we don't even have a countdown now.
Oh my god, this is true.
This is the worst egg-isode ever.
Yeah, ruining the egg-isode.
Yeah, I guess we just we do.
We do have to just keep talking when it ends.
I don't know.
Do we all just have individual monologues that overlap and ruin the episode?
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, I think it's going to end 2, 1, and I think it ends now.
Oh, no, it didn't end.
It got to 45 minutes, but it didn't end.
Is it just not going to end?
Mine still says less than a minute, but it's been saying that for a minute.
Is it now it's going to live in fear that it's going to end the whole time?
God!
I'm just, don't stop recording your audacity.
I'll sync it up.
It's going to suck to edit and it's going to be horrible to listen to.
This egg-isode.
This egg-isode is horrible.
What were you guys talking about in the dark?
I'm about to buy these shoes.
I was apologizing and I was, I Googled "Buy Boy Egg Shift from China"
and I found a bag of realistic chicken eggs, toy food playset.
What did you talk about, Pierce?
I just talked about how stressed out and sweaty I was.
I really thought that I gave out the zoom
room code and the
In the password, that's fine. I found I just found a big something great that we could buy for only $10 on eBay
What is it mythic eggs bundle of 25?
whoa
This is a virtual in-game. I what's a mythic egg. I don't know. Okay, what is this?
mythical egg.
25 mythical egg.
Mythic egg.
From seller Dream Egg.
What is this?
They sell egg bundles.
They sell eggs from dreams.
They have 132 egg bundles for sale.
What game is this?
Eggs the game.
Eggs bundles of 25.
Oh there's so many.
Mythic eggs, ocean eggs, fossil eggs, ox boxes.
You've never played.
Ox boxes.
What's an ox box?
Ox box?
They sell them in bundles of 25.
Wow! Do you guys want to buy ox boxes?
Is this for Animal Crossing?
It could be.
I just got the Red Ring of Death on my ox box.
Heyo!
Oh dude, ox boxes are so cool.
That's when my co-waker is in flames.
Red Ring of Death on an ox box.
What the fuck is it? What is an ox box?
I don't know. I think it's an item.
It's an item.
Oh, it's still in the video game.
I get it.
Yeah.
I really wish it wasn't.
Oxbox.
Oxbox is a really good phrase, though.
Do you guys ever played Billy Hatcher and the Giant Egg on GameCube?
I never played it, but my friend brought it in for show and tell in the first grade.
Dude, it is such an autistic kid totem to have that game.
Just like, come over and, you know, you get bored of playing Melee, and now you gotta
watch your friend play Billy Hatcher.
Hmm.
Just that was around an egg.
My
game for Gamecube was
a
I played a
Star Wars Rogue Squadron 2
Good game.
I never had a Gamecube.
I went over to my friend's house who had a Gamecube
and I played one of the Crash Bandicoot games.
I thought it was so cool.
Was that on Gamecube or was that a different system?
I think you're lying.
I truly, I mean I never, I have no idea.
Yeah, that's true.
I forgot you were a no video games kid.
I wasn't a no video games kid, I was a no consoles kid.
I had like a Gameboy.
Oh, okay.
But I didn't have any.
Did you play the Godzilla games on Gameboy Color?
Did I play what?
The Godzilla, like the animated series, Godzilla games.
I played Godzilla Domination.
For Gameboy.
a
19. Damn. Yeah. That's insane that they **** it was the worst
game ever dude. Yeah. Dude, it's cool. It's cool how much
shovelware was on the DS. Yeah, the DS is the **** best
platform for all of just the most insane DS and the Wii.
Yeah. For some reason, they like Nintendo is just like,
alright, **** it. Throw whatever you can at it but I
guess that's a good way to like test like cuz I think that
that was probably like the first time, like the Wii, was like the first time they had
that technology.
So I think that's a good way to test it, but they had some fucked up...
Darts Championship 2008?
There was Godzilla on the Wii too, and you had to like shake the Wiimote to do any fucking
attack.
Damn.
PDC World Championship Darts for 2008 for Wii.
I remember I bought some like my uh...
I just bought this for cam.
What?
P-P-P-D-C.
I don't have a- I don't have a Wii.
I didn't actually buy it for you man, I'm just playing around.
I uh...
I- my- my dad likes like uh...
Like old planes.
What are you- can you-
Can you shut the fuck up dude?
You're in a fucking online shop.
Piece of shit dude.
I'm buying something for you.
My dad, my dad was really into like, uh, like old planes, like
old, like fighter planes.
And so I found this, like, I forget what store is that, but
I found like a game for like a dollar for the, we like a used
game.
That was like a dog fighting game with a bunch of old planes.
And I was like, Oh, my dad will think this is cool.
And like, I bought it, loved those fucking games.
And I, Oh, I bought it.
And it would be like, it was like, it's so similar.
Like it, the render distance was so tiny that it was just like
fog.
You couldn't see any other planes. It was dude. It was and you had to like hold it like it was it was the worst
My dad would play any piece of shit flying game. It was so awesome to watch him play
Yeah, any fucking like a game where you have to land on a fucking
Aircraft carrier four times in a row just we you just did whatever the fucking game told him to do
He was like, well, I don't care if the game is bad. I have to do what it's telling me. Yeah, that's the thing
Yeah, they're good at following instructions
Yeah, yeah, I'd love to get really into flight simulators
That would be cool like you know those
If you like dreams and you were doing impossible maneuvers, that's the thing those those none of them are cool like this never
The missions are never like do a loop-de-loop through it like
No, yeah, it's just like yeah wait for six hours
That's this mission. Did Star Wars squadrons I could get like a full fucking I get the VR headset
I could get all the like the peripheral like flight stuff and then I do it all in a TIE fighter
Yeah, I remember playing battlefront 2 at
There was this place called the nerve center where I grew up and it was like a LAN party. Oh, yeah, those were sick
Maybe I've talked about this was it even Gillian themes?
No, but it was spelled like nerf in a Vangelion
But I would do my birthday parties there and there was also like a room where you could like play
Xbox or ps3 like guitar hero rooms
But like the main thing was like a room with like 40 different computers and you can have a LAN party
So we would always play battlefront 2 you guys ever do the space battles and battlefront 2
Yeah, take the carrier and like put your it may be so nauseous. Yeah. Yeah
But I would always be the one who drives the the gunship and anytime someone else would do it
I'll be like you're fuck you can't do it. You're so bad. It turns out. It's the easiest thing in that game to do
Oh, yeah, it's so easy
Dude
the best the best move is taking the taking the gunship into the other like base and then like parking it there and it's kind of
Like having a couple people guard it and then because then you can spawn into their fucking ship
That's what I would do. I played so much battlefront 2 in high school
I think I let me let me look at how many hours I have played cuz it I definitely have like 800 hours
Yeah, there it was like my parents had this like shitty like Dell like
You know, there's like PCs that like it's like the Dell all-in-one
So it's just like the monitor and then like the back of it is like the whole computer
Yeah, it could only run like games up until
Because it it had six gigs of RAM which is like
There's the craziest about like you can't get anything done with that. No. Yeah, you can you can run battle
Yeah, yeah
So much fucking sport. I'd never have been like three times in my
childhood and adolescence where I like made my parents buy me a PC and
There they knew that the only reason I wanted to buy a PC was to play one video game at a time
I made them buy me a PC just so I could play Spore.
I played so much Spore.
That was one of my best childhood gifts ever, is my grandpa.
Because I wouldn't stop just talking about Spore.
About everybody.
Because I would just watch the videos of them and be like, "On Spore you can create a creature!"
And he got me the Galactic Edition of Spore, which has the box and an art book and shit.
I was so fucking obsessed. I brought the art book to school and I was showing my friends.
Dude, I remember bringing like the the instruction manual for war of the monsters into the bath with
me all the time. Into the bath? Yeah, just look at pictures of the monsters in the tub. Yeah,
no, that I would print out the Wikipedia page for sound wave from transformers and just read
it in the bath. I was so obsessed with just holding... holding...
The bath specifically? Well that's where I got to be alone and just
sort of be a cool... I definitely, I also printed out Wikipedia
pages but I did not read them in the bath like a freak. I would print out a Wikipedia
page of something I thought was really cool and read it one time and then just put it in
my backpack and it would just stay in there until it like rotted because I also left applesauce
in there by accident or something. I'd only print like pictures out. I thought like I'd make stuff
in like Photoshop and then like print it out. I remember using PowerPoint all the time on
the family computer. Oh yeah. Just to write the word Godzilla in WordArt.
Just find the one that looks like, yeah, the Godzilla 2000 font and just make that over.
I was like, I'm going to make a slideshow about Godzilla, but I would just work on the title page
for like three hours. Dude, PowerPoint was the fucking best. I would go on PowerPoint in the
school library after school for like hours at a time to make like video games where it would just
be like you click on, you either click on like the circle or the X and it like takes you to
different like slides based on that. Awesome. Dude, it is so sick. Yeah, you could do all the
animations and stuff. Man. Yeah. I'm gonna get back into PowerPoint. I'm gonna do a lot of pivot
stick figure animator to oh dude pivot was so sick pivot was tight yeah i was 100 129.6 hours in
battlefront 2 that's not very much time that's not no i have like i definitely have a video game not
really but in like team fortress 2 i have close to 800 or something yeah i also wasted so much
fucking time in TF2 I would just play engineer in 2fort like what the fuck
yeah I was just in the 2fort is so sick everyone hates 2fort and I would just be the engineer in
the fucking intel room yeah for hours just camping I would just I would just be on a I would just yeah
I would just be on a skype call with like my like with like like not the nine other kids in my school
who like knew what TF2 was and just like yeah just get killed like a hundred
times in a row and just yell at each other.
Yeah I remember there were like so many times where I would like not be in the
Skype voice chat just talking to no one camping in the Intel room as an engineer.
It's a miracle that I'm not fucking schizophrenic. I remember my parents got
us laptops for Christmas one year when I was like when I was like 13. My parents
got his laptops and I was like, telling like my friends online
like, like, oh, I finally like got my own like PC. And they're
like, Oh, yeah, what's like, what's up with it? And I like
told them it was like, dude, it was a fucking it was like a
compact laptop from 2001. That had this like, card that like
you did like the only way it could connect to the internet was
this wifi card that you had to put into the side and I told them it ran Windows XP and
they fucking died laughing at me.
They were like, "How the fuck, like, tell me like the specs of it right now!"
They had like, fucking, they had like one gig of RAM and like, it was like, I thought it
was so sick that I had a laptop.
Look how it's still making you laugh.
Yeah, I know, I don't understand this story at all.
Yeah, what's funny is just this shitty computer
that makes people die laughing.
It's making you die laughing.
It's a poorly made computer.
It's just so old.
Dude, it was so bad.
It like didn't even turn on.
No, the first day I got it,
it was like this refurbished computer.
So the first day I got it,
I accidentally, I tried to hook it up
to an external monitor
so I could like do shit with it.
No.
No!
...do shit with it.
Hold on, this actually gets funny.
It actually gets funny.
Let me continue.
*laughing*
Okay.
So, it, like, I hooked shit up to this monitor and then forgot that I, like, I got a bod-
Like, my mom gave me mouthwash in my stocking, and I hooked it up to the monitor, and then, like, tried to move it.
You hooked the mouthwash up to the monitor?
No, no, no the monitor I hooked the computer up to the monitor and then the mouthwash was behind the computer and it
Broke onto the laptop and all the mouthwash spilled into the keyboard
Wait, this is the only part of the story just happened
It broke onto the computer?
Yes
The mouthwash cap broke and the mouthwash spilled
How? Spontaneously?
The monitor toppled onto it
Okay, how did that happen?
I don't remember how, but the monitor fell onto the mouthwash and it broke into the keyboard
and it spilled all over the keyboard.
And it like, I had to...
And then what?
My dad had to go get it.
My dad had to go back to the Showtime computers in Nashua and go get it fixed.
And they were like, "All right, well, it runs, so it must just be the keyboard that doesn't
work."
So they were like, all right, so what's like the what's like the password my dad had to call my mom am I?
Hold on hold on
The passwords the password was very bum liquor
Because it was really long and no one would guess it. I think I I think I saw it somewhere
I think I saw that phrase somewhere else too. So I
Check this out. Hold on. Hold on. Check. So no way no way. Hold on
My dad had to sit there. Patrick, listen to me right now. One time my computer broke and
my mom had to tell the computer fixer guys the password was "Fairybumlicker".
Okay, hold on. So he's standing there. No, no, no. You think.
Because it was really long and no one can guess it.
That's a good password.
It is a good password.
But so is every other password.
Not true.
Password 123 is not a good password.
Yeah.
It's a bad password.
So my dad and the computer guy went back and forth for like 10 minutes
because he kept like typing it in and it's like, "Oh, that's not the right password."
And then my dad had to call my mom back and be like, "What the fuck is the password?
He's not...
It's not...
That.
I just had to fuckin' say "fairy" or "hairy bum liquor" to the guy.
He thought it was "hairy bum liquor".
But it was "fairy bum liquor".
And my dad had to say "hairy bum liquor" to the computer guy.
Look, I thought that-
You really- You really- You-
My mom tells the story better.
That was all in the-
*laughter*
We did that whole thing in the middle!
And you're sorry-
It's more difficult for you to tell a story that someone else has already told
than to tell a story from scratch.
I can't...
I had a Mac in middle school
and I didn't have a PC
and I really wanted a PC because
you can do more stuff on a PC than a Mac.
And I remember my grandma died
and I got her old PC
and I was so happy because I could finally make custom Magic the Gathering cards
without using the wine converter thing. And that was very big for me.
I remember going on Google Video before YouTube was a thing. I probably talked about this too,
but I would just Google "aliens or predator" pretty much every day. And there was this one
home movie that was an AVP parody, and I would just watch it three times a day. Stupid eight
8 minute video of just friends playing around in the woods.
The Predator was just a kid in an airsoft helmet.
I feel like you've shown me the video before or something.
I can't find it.
Maybe tell me about it.
Dude, Google Video was so sick.
I found so much crazy shit on there.
They should bring back Google Plus.
That would be huge.
That could get the zoomers back into that style of social media.
There could be a Google Plus. I don't think anyone has fond memories of Google Plus like
they do MySpace.
Yeah, Google Plus is so funny. It showed up, it didn't do anything. Nobody cared about
it at all.
Yeah.
And it went away.
I really wanted one. I really was looking forward to getting the invite.
Yeah.
I had one.
I think I had one. Do you remember Google Buzz?
No.
That was Google's fake Twitter thing. That was Google for weeks.
It was like... It was Google. It was like... That's the one that nobody remembers, dude.
But that was fucking... That was like you would just post and people would comment on your post.
That's all it was. And it was tied into... It was sick, dude. Me and my friends used it so much,
and I was so mad when it went away. It was literally... It was just...
Look at... Oh, and I'm looking at pictures of it on Google Images. This is bringing back
such memories dude. You never used Google Buzz? No. Dude it was so awesome.
Did I ever tell you? Yeah I talked about it. Sparktop.org. What's that? No, I don't know what that is.
That was the forum I found in a Sports Illustrated for Kids magazine. That was for kids with ADHD.
It's called Sparktop? Sparktop.org and I would go on there and I would talk to other kids.
That should be like a slur for kids with ADHD.
Yeah, spark talk. I think it was. I think it was for kids with like ADHD and kids on like the autism
spectrum and that's where I would go and talk to other kids. I was like looking around on it at
first and I was like, "Oh, this is kind of lame." And then I looked up CKY.
To get kids with autism, ADHD all in the same room with no supervision.
Right. A forum. That's where I learned about like insane clown posse.
Tight. Yeah.
Because I looked up like CKY and stuff like that and I looked up like skateboarding and then like
found like kids like in their bios like had like favorite bands like Tool, Insane Clown Posse,
Linkin Park. I remember my Myspace page just had a personality quiz about how well you know me.
That was the only thing on it. The background image was like a xenomorph and the questions
were like, "Who is my favorite character in Smash Brothers?" And the answer was all of the above.
It's funny that this website was sold to you as something for kids with ADHD,
because I looked it up, and it's a forum dedicated to helping kids with learning disabilities.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's learning disabilities specifically.
They sold it. It's different now.
Well, it doesn't exist anymore. Here's the top...
I'm on common sense media looking at it. So, you know, they have like parents and kids reviews.
There's only this. So this is the only parent review for Sparked Up from April 9th, 2008,
written by netbug009. Five stars, five stars. What a great idea. This is a great site for
the mentally challenged, but you don't have to be to enjoy yourself. Check it out. Oh, God.
You gotta get back on there, bro.
Yeah, dude.
This is a great site for the mentally challenged, but you don't have to be to enjoy yourself.
Dude, I mean, it taught me what ICP was.
Yeah. No, any site that teaches you what ICP was is a good, a good site.
Dude, I just remember, I remember the other day, my mom let me have MySpace when I was nine,
but like I could only add like people that like she knew. So like, I had like all of her friends
from her restaurant, like all of her coworkers and like my neighbors. And my mom got pissed
off at me because like in my bio I said I was 13 when I was really 10. And she was like,
"You're not 13. Stop trying to pretend to be 13." But I was like, "If I say that I'm not 13,
I'm going to get kicked off of there." Yeah.
Because I thought that they would like kick me. I thought they would ban me immediately for not...
They should have. I've often done the exact same thing. I think 13 is the age to be on MySpace.
Yeah, same with Facebook. That was what it was like when people were getting Facebooks.
Do you remember they had the, you could, like, there was something that you could like put like
your own play, like, you would get like the one song on MySpace, but then there was also like
some embedded like player you could add. I did that once, but like the laptop, my dad's laptop,
like the sound driver just like didn't work or something like the audio wasn't working and I put a bunch of songs on it but couldn't hear them
until I used the other like computer in the house and then like realized that like all of the songs were the wrong songs or they were that fucking like that
LimeWire like Bill Clinton thing if you remember that?
No, what's that?
The LimeWire Bill Clinton thing was so funny, you would download a song and be like, "Oh
shit, that took really quick."
And then it was like a 15 second MP3 of a guy doing a Bill Clinton impression where he's
like, "I didn't have sexual relations with that woman, but I did go to ifreeclub.com.
iPods, MP3 players, and laptops absolutely free."
We need that back in our society.
That's like an ARG.
I've heard it so I've heard the iFreeClub thing so many times in my life.
That's one of my favorite ARGs is the free RayBans ARG.
Oh yeah.
It's such a crazy web adventure.
RayBans20percentIndia.ru
Yeah, one of my favorite ARGs I found recently is actually this great ARG where basically it's
where you can win three free stethoscopes if you follow this Indian doctor on Instagram.
Have you guys played the like it's the lore is insane and it like starts out
with this really cryptic video where it says you will not last 10 seconds.
You basically go down this insane rabbit hole. My favorite my favorite ARG has been on this
website pirates.com. Oh my god there's this ARG called the Badger song.
crazy. Yeah. All right. Pierce, plug your thingy. You guys want to see my thingy?
Just plug your thingy in. If you live in LA on the 23rd, I'm doing a anthology thing at
the Elysian Theater and Matthew Golden's gonna be on it. And I don't know. Yeah,
It might not be so funny, but it will be kind of cool.
Yeah, you're gonna go if you live there.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know. I don't give a shit. I don't give a shit.
Okay, you're not gonna go.
Yeah, there you go.
Yeah.
Pierce isn't gonna be there.
All right.
Yeah, I might get cold feet because of this COVID, this pandemic.
It might be a no-show situation.
So.
Yeah.
Don't buy tickets. But it's a great opportunity to meet people and to network.
Definitely. If you're COVID positive, go to this event.
It's a networking event for people who have COVID.
Yeah. Give Matthew and Pierce COVID. And basically just spit everywhere. You can spit everywhere
like it's a Texas roadhouse. You can eat peanuts. You can spit everywhere.
Is it Texas Roadhouse that does peanuts? Bye, everybody.
Bye. Sorry.
Bye, guys.
Sorry!