you're listening to Israel's number one podcast
this is premium content
if you are not a premium subscriber
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately
*laughs*
okay so
let me get my mic into my hand
there we go
my mic arm doesn't come in till tomorrow
he's a genius
so like a week or two ago I bought Patrick a scammed
like stolen minecraft account for him to use
oh yeah
from like eBay for like two bucks and the username and password they sent didn't
work so I asked for a replacement and I got the replacement and in Patrick's new
Minecraft account the password contains the n-word. Yeah, the password for my new...
You can't change it. I can't change it at all. Say it, what is it? It's n-word and one.
Like the basketball shorts?
Like the basketball shorts, exactly.
Fuck, dude.
So he has to type that in every time he wants to play Minecraft.
Oh my god, that's almost, that is almost worth paying another five dollars to get a new one.
It was a, yeah.
That's not just green, dude.
If it was 99 cents, it'd be a no-brainer, but it being, how much is it?
I think it might have been like a dollar or two dollars.
I could have just bought, I could have just bought it.
Just get a new one, dude.
You don't wanna, and from a different supplier, you don't wanna give that guy more money.
Yeah.
[Laughter]
Yeah, that's true.
I think, I think I might just, I mean I got, I got a refund.
That's why, if you want, if you want one that has a password that isn't a racial slur, it costs $10.
Yeah.
[Laughter]
I, um, I did get a refund for the Microsoft one I bought.
So, I could just buy a new Minecraft.
When I bought one for my little brother and then I had issues with the password and so I
talked to the guy on eBay and I was like, "I need a new one." And his response was,
"I'm so sorry, me Chinese." And then he was like, "I know confusing." And then he sent me a new one.
That's very nice of him.
It was pretty nice of him. "Me Chinese." I was like, "Say no more. Say no more. I've
I've already got my money out of you.
- I got my money's worth.
- That's fine.
- I drank a rain energy earlier.
- You drank rain water?
- Mm-hmm.
- You thought it was a new energy drink?
You went to the Rainforest Cafe.
- I did and I got the blue,
I got the strawberry lemonade from the Rainforest Cafe.
- Yeah and you drank it like a frog would drink.
- Uh-huh, but I got a rain energy that it's like bang
but it's not made by, it's not, yeah, it's not made by Hitler.
- Is Bang Israeli, is that the problem?
- No, Bang has donated like a shit ton of money
to the Trump campaign, so it's one of those situations
where it's like a huge-- - Bang is actually,
they named it Bang-- - A huge drink bag,
you're Republican.
- They named it Bang after the master of rocketry
and explosive, Werner Von Braun, so.
- Oh, gotcha. - Yeah, that's why
people don't like it. - Oh, okay.
yeah makes sense that yeah we should know about bang
i drink a rain
the star blast flavor actually don't want to know what star they're blasting
uh...
as you know
has a good uh... yeah
related
and i i i i i that's a funny it's funny a boycott bang because of political
reasons and not because it's
actual poison. Yeah, it's like acid.
Yeah, literal.
I'm boycotting drinking battery acid because the people
who make it are from Israel.
Is it? Are they from Israel?
Yeah, they're from Israel.
I know they have a really fucked up
I know that bank has a really fucked up
influencer program.
What's fucked up about it?
They do, so like
their influencers have to pay
for all their products
and shit. It's so clear that
- I heard that Patrick only knows about this
because he was trying to become a Bang influencer
at one point.
- So?
- It would make perfect sense.
- He applied to the Institute of Bang Instagram posting.
- No, but the rules are really fucked up.
I watched a video on it.
- How long was the video?
- It's about like 10 minutes.
It's a pretty good watch.
- What were the rules?
- Yeah, what kind of, what do you mean by fucked up?
- I don't remember.
Hold on, let me look it up.
- You can't have sex.
You have to remain.
You cannot have sex. You have to wear a bang chastity belt.
And the only person who has the key is the CEO of bang.
The bang ambassador.
The bang ambassador. I'm a bang ambassador. Holy shit, look at their fucking CEO, dude.
I'm looking up right now. I gotta see this.
Bang energy CEO. Is it like the Abercrombie and Fitch guy? No, do you remember?
He looks like one fucked up dentist.
Oh my god.
He kinda looks like Stallone in Spy Kids 3D.
Yeah, yeah.
The toy maker.
So, I guess like...
God, what?
Jack O'Walk.
Yeah, Jack O'Walk.
That's him.
Jack O'Walk.
That sounds like a Bart Simpson prank name.
He has in his Twitter bio says "Inventor of Bang Energy."
I'm an inventor.
I invented this energy drink.
I'm like a Thomas Edison style inventor.
I invented putting 300mg of caffeine in Sprite.
I'm pretty smart.
If only if it was just Sprite with a lot of caffeine.
What is it?
I think I've only had it once or twice.
I've had it, I only have it if I need it.
Bang is insane.
I drank Bang like two semesters ago pretty regularly and it's just like, it's crazy.
It's just, it's not.
Because of your beliefs.
It's yeah, it was because of my beliefs at the time that I chose to drink it, but that
has changed.
Now I just drink it for the taste.
It's like it's very clearly just a chemical like it's not meant to be ingested.
Oh yeah.
Like there's no pretense of flavor.
It's just like we're gonna make this like caustic like
like chemical that just goes into your body and fucks everything up.
Like you can tell it's not giving like the way you know.
Oh yeah, you don't feel good when you drink it.
You can tell the like the way it's just like beating up your brain like to give you energy.
It's just like squeezing your fucking.
They didn't realize it's just a carbonated version of the slime they inject dogs with to kill them. Yeah
Where where as rain rain energy is made by my name is from the earth
It's from the earth's month. Oh my gosh. I'm made by monster nice so you can trust it
Yeah, I'm reading about Jack o'clock right now, and it says earlier in Jack o'clock's career. He was a high school science teacher
No
Dude, he did like a Walter White
He did dude
Disciplines along with English health and ran internal suspension over a period of nine years
There was a Jesse Pinkman kid in his class who just loved caffeine
Yeah, and he recruited him and he was like, what do you want? And he just a duct tape two monsters together
Yeah, and he was like, what about this? Yeah, he's like, I can figure out how to make that a can
He just poured Monster into an empty gas tank and then siphoned it back out and that's bang.
That's how you make bang energy.
You just shake it around in a used gas can.
Yeah.
Fucking...
He Jack-a-wok.
Jack-a-wok.
He's actually...
He had a side job where he had a dance group called the Jack-a-wokies.
Nice.
Okay.
Alright.
- It took me a while to get there.
- Yeah, no, it took a second.
- Wait, a little bit.
- I think I may have breathed over that.
Can we get a clean take?
- No.
- I need to read you guys this paragraph really quick
from Jack O'Walk's journey to become CEO, okay?
He was working with like proteins and stuff.
He was trying to create weight loss,
like chemicals or whatever.
Listen to this.
Things went from bad to worse.
Shortly thereafter, his best friend
was playing professional basketball.
He was highly allergic to milk protein.
With all the trust in the world,
Jack's best friend requested he recommends the purest milk protein free
supplement and sends it to him.
Jack sent him MedSport egg protein.
Upon consuming this protein he asphyxiated in the shower.
Suffocating and near death he pounded on the shower doors. His wife rescued him
and immediately transported him to the hospital where the medical staff saved
his life.
What the fuck?
No, Jack-a-woke
killed his friend. Jack-a-woke almost killed his friend.
making bang with eggs yeah god damn yeah you don't you don't make bang without
cracking a few eggs we gotta we gotta write the jack o'walk
enraged with anger at the corruption dishonesty and utter tomfoolery in the
supplement industry a walk was set on an unwavering war path
is this on the website he's just banging on the front door of
fucking nos yeah this is on a website called magster
Magster. He's at GNC just like, he's outside of GNC with a molotov. With a bang. He just has a bang.
He has a bang. Because you can use a bang is so flammable you can use it like a molotov cocktail.
There's a bang flavor called nitro jack. I'm lighting my, I'm lighting up my affliction t-shirt
and stuffing it in my bang energy and throwing it at the White House. What is the bang revolution?
"The bang revolution is fueled by experiential marketing
"that we do to create content all around the world."
If you ain't banging, you ain't hanging.
This is a universal truth that banksters live by
and competitors lose sleep over.
- Whoa.
- Hell yeah.
- I mean, the truth is like with energy drinks,
it is just like, yeah,
if you, whatever drink has the most caffeine,
you're like winning, you know?
- Yeah.
- You're like the apple of energy drinks.
- Damn, you can get a 18 karat gold-plated
bang energy charm for 20 bucks.
- That's good, dude.
- And you can get a bang energy float
and a bang beach towel.
We should become bang ambassadors.
- Absolutely.
- I would love to be a bangster.
- We just spent the last 10 minutes talking about this
just so that you could recruit us
'cause that's part of the ambassador program.
- Yeah, it's one of the rules you didn't get to.
- It's like you have to get two friends.
- Yeah.
- And you have to convince them to also be bang ambassadors.
- It's like Scientology.
The special bangster box.
(laughing)
- The bangster box.
- The bangster box, what does it come with?
- The special bangster box.
- Oh, oh, it's a subscription box.
- Oh, so it's like a loot crate.
- Yeah, the bangster.
- Yeah, exactly.
It's like dropping Superstore and you get a bang energy.
- Yeah.
I would love a bang, I feel like there would be
a Bang Energy Fortnite tie-in.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
That makes sense.
I would expect that.
Yeah.
It does seem like a very dystopian energy drink.
No, yeah.
It is like an idiocracy ad.
Yeah.
It does, I mean, there's a crosshair
over the earth in the bee.
(laughing)
That is so funny.
Oh no, that's not the Earth.
That's just a radar.
Yeah.
Bang is so powerful.
It gives you the energy to destroy the world.
Hey, shoot the fucking Earth.
Who cares?
Yeah, I got hyped up on Bang and I started blowing my 12 gauge at the moon.
Yeah.
I just started just wailing.
Just wailing on my kid.
Wailing on my kid.
Bang is dad fuel.
fuel.
Yeah.
Yeah, bang is fuel for big daddy when the kiddies get out of line.
There's a whole section on the store for bang called goals.
Yeah.
So you click on goals and it's just fitness goals and then all it is is like 12 pack of
bang, bang keto coffee.
These are the, these are bangs goals.
These are the goals.
The goals?
Eradicate the Romani people.
Bang.
Bang energy.
This is a graham cracker supplement.
They have a graham cracker supplement?
Yeah, you're a cracker named Graham.
Yeah, you are.
Uh, yeah, you are.
You're a cracker named, you're a cracker who buys a graham, yeah, for a million dollars.
You buy a graham for one million dollars.
No.
- Jackalwok is a Gemini, guys.
- I'm starting to crash.
- You're Dr. Weedville.
- Oh no.
- He seriously has, he's starting--
- You're Dr. Weedville and you buy a grant
for one billion dollars. - Jackalwok has serious
Gemini energy.
- Absolutely. - No, he doesn't.
- He has serious Gemini energy.
- No, you have serious Jackalwok interview.
- You have Jackalwok interview where you--
- We should interview Jackalwok.
- You know who he looks like?
- Jackalwok has serious bang energy.
- You know who he looks like? - We should send him an email
that's like, we're looking to understand
your billionaire mindset and we wanna change the world.
- We should get him and Gnome on,
we should host a debate with him and Gnome Jockey.
- That's a good idea.
- Yeah, we have both their emails,
let's just get into contact.
- They disagree with each other perfectly.
Gnome is like, "No, I know this guy, I love him."
- Yeah, surprisingly, Jackalock is very anti-US imperialism.
- Why do you think Gnome looks like that?
He's been drinking my fucking juice.
- Yeah, Jackalock's like, "Well, you can, you can,
our greatest misstep was creating a villain
out of Muammar Gaddafi."
And Gnome Jockey's like, "Really? Okay."
(laughing)
- All right, let me give you a sip of that, come on.
- Yeah, maybe I'm gonna try that shit.
- Yeah, maybe you're right.
- Man, that's so funny that being Qaddafid
was a whole meme from Tosh.0.
- What, having something in your ass?
- Yeah, getting a knife up your ass.
- I thought they put a pole in his ass.
- Yeah, well, I don't know, but either way,
Daniel Tosh showed the video on Tosh.0,
and then he showed the video on Tosh.0
and then was like, oh, so I went around my office
Kadophying my coworkers.
- God, that is.
- Send in your Kadophy videos.
- That's so awesome. - That's so awesome, dude.
- Yeah, that's badass.
- God damn it, dude. - So crazy.
- I misstandard, is he still doing that show?
- He is still doing Tosh.0, yeah.
So epic dude.
- Yeah, what kind of stuff are they watching now?
- They're just watching live leaks.
- Yeah.
I bet they're watching videos of people.
- And he's recreating them around the office.
- Yeah, he's like, "Watch these."
- We grabbed our co-worker and his son
and we did the Muhammad Al-Durra incident to them.
As they cowered behind a wall,
we destroyed them with gunfire.
- It's been on for like 10 years.
It's been on for longer than that, right?
Yeah, dude, March 17th was its 12th season.
Yeah, it's been on forever.
It's like, and it's basically the Tonight Show.
Yeah.
Daniel Tosh is the new Johnny Carson.
That's true.
Who was the new Jack Parr.
Mm-hmm.
Who was the new Abraham Lincoln.
Yeah.
Back in the day, FDR invented the late night talk show
with his fireside chat. - He did, with the fireside.
- Yeah, and he used to do monologue jokes
about Sammy Davis Jr.
And then-- - And we can't repeat
any of 'em. - We definitely, no,
absolutely not. - We definitely cannot
repeat any of them. - But what we can say
is they were funny.
Just objectively, pretty funny stuff.
And then Jack Parr started doing it,
and then Johnny Carson started doing it,
but then Sammy Davis Jr. died,
and so we needed something else to make fun of.
Luckily a little man named George W. Bush came around.
- Mm-hmm.
- And we still lampoon that foolish monkey to this day.
- Yep. - Absolutely.
- Yep, George Bush is a great--
- You guys remember when he said fool me once
and fool me twice?
- Yeah, remember when that guy hit him with a shoe?
- That was some cool shit, honestly.
- Yeah, I wish someone would do that to me.
- Yeah, hit you with a shoe. - I would love a shoe.
I would love to have a shoe right now.
- I would love a shoe so bad.
George Bush was kinda ungrateful, he got a free shoe.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's also crazy 'cause it was a Jordan,
it was a off-white Jordan bread one,
it was worth almost $2,000.
The problem was it wasn't his size.
That's why he was so mad.
Yeah, that's why he was upset.
If it was his size, I think--
The insult there was that it was a woman's shoe.
Yeah, it was a woman's size shoe.
And I think if it wasn't a woman's shoe,
I think we would've established a democracy
over there sooner. I agree that that guy he got thrown into prison because he
disrespected him. He broke the Geneva Convention. You're not allowed to give a
man a female shoe. Yeah. It's one of the especially not a world leader. Yeah
especially not especially not the leader of the skull and bones. Yeah especially
not the Texas rider himself. Yeah. Yeah. The beautiful the beautiful Texas
the Texas Beast the Texas yeah the Texas Ranger the Texas Ranger himself George
HW Hitler George H Hitler George Hill Bush yeah he had a complicated family history
the bushes yeah because his uncles were fighting all the time when he was a kid
did you ever see the Josh Brolin Bush movie? No I remember seeing the
poster for it at the video update in my hometown I saw the TV cut of it it's
just so epic what was it what's it called just it's like it's like it was
like right when I think it was like 2008 it came I think it's just called Bush I
I think it was 2006. I think it was earlier than that.
Personally I think it was 1985.
Yeah, it actually came out in one.
It came out year one.
It came out the same time as year one with Jack Black and Miles Cera.
Oh, it was 2008.
Okay, so it was...
But it's basically just like
them making like a snarky movie
where... I mean, yeah, it's basically
like a Will Ferrell comedy with Josh Brolin
and George W. Bush
and he just walks around and they're like
But what are you gonna do about the Middle East? And he's like, I'm gonna take a poop.
Yeah, funny. Yeah, you know, we need we need one of those right now for Donald Trump. Oh,
my God. So we need to make fun of this guy. We need Funny or Die to partner with Netflix
and make a real take down. We need a Funny or Die Raytheon partnership to come together and
make a scathing Donald Trump. Oh, and Michael Moore. And we need all three of them. Michael
more Raytheon funnier die and bang energy and bang energy yeah I was gonna say
that bang energy and they and Barack Obama and yep
Verner Barack Obama's Netflix deal Barack Obama has a cameo where he walks out of
the of the bathroom while Donald Trump is tweeting on the toilet yeah or there he
walks into the bathroom while Donald Trump is tweeting on the toilet and he
says miss me yet and the crowd cheers yeah the crowd in the movie there's an applause
break in the middle of the movie yeah and there's uh actually obama plays a lot of characters
obama goes norbit in the movie yeah and he plays every character that donald trump has
to has to interact with including melania yeah at the end of every line that he says
he pulls off whatever like prosthetic he has on and goes "miss me yet?" and there's a pause.
Yeah. Barack Obama plays the girls that the Wayans brothers play in White Chicks
and they are as Stormy Daniels and his mission to fuck Donald Trump.
Right? Yeah. So Donald Trump comes in he's like "I wanna be on you" and then Barack Obama as
the white chick is like, "This, uh, you suck."
You know, something like that.
Yeah, let me be clear.
I'm telling you.
Let me be clear.
You are, I'm gonna pee on you.
I'm gonna pee on you.
And I'm gonna make fun of your penis.
And he records it with the, uh, or the white chick, Barack Obama records it,
with a little Sony camcorder, right?
and then and then there's a like an hour-long sequence of him trying to
figure out how to edit the video down yeah
that's the rest of the movie he's on sony vegas 6
and he's just trying to figure out how to find the razor tool
and he's doing it and he's doing it in funny or die headquarters
okay problem you know who's looking over his shoulder point showing him how to do
it will ferrell oh my god and also played
by barack obama keeping him focused what bang energy bang energy uh-huh and the
The problem is the reason that the rest of the movie is them trying to use Sony Vegas 6 to edit the movie is
That the video and the audio got unlinked and they don't remember what button they pressed
What they pressed to link it back together and so anytime that they import it's an AVI file
So anytime that they import it, they're like, well, where did the video go and they're like, I don't know
Yeah, so and then they figure that out
Then there's a review in the newspaper of the movie and it's this is like in real life not in the movie
the reviews come out and they're like this is a stunning mind-twisting rendition of
real events combining reality with fiction in a way you can see the movie
being created in front of you on the screen in Sony Vegas 6 this yeah this is
four and a half stars out of five this is Donald Trump's Frost Nixon yeah this is
a worthy successor to Charlie Kaufman's adaptation mr. Farrell I need your help
the text that says hot I cannot get it to change the text from saying hot and now
there's a cool and and then and then Will Ferrell says if you ain't first you're
last yeah and then he leaves yeah yeah cuz it's also a NASCAR partnership yeah
yeah that's the other part yeah so they're in the they're in the NASCAR car
and they have a drive-in the whole time
back because it's also serves as stuber as the second stuber movie yeah it's all
the Carol and Barack Obama the computer is powered by the by how many RPMs the
car does like speed yeah so they have to go really fast yeah and John wick is
there John wick from speed and it's really one of the Avengers uh-huh and
black Adam it's really hard it's really hard because the car has to make a pit
stop so anytime that they have to make a pit stop the quantitized to frames button
shuts off and then the clips get really small he's accidentally because the car
is going so fast he's moving the mouse but then the clips get too small and it
does that like YouTube poop stuttering effect where it goes like also and then
they get an idea to just make a YouTube poop yeah so that they try to make a
YouTube poop of the Donald Trump sex tape yeah that they've made also this
movie is filmed over the course of 15 years like boyhood yeah yeah and in the
middle there's a part where the entire cast of the movie which is again Barack
Obama Norbit it up as white people is be there being driven through a Taco Bell
drive-thru and Barack it gets frustrated trying to take everybody's orders yeah
Yeah, because Donald Trump's like, "I want a black bean chalupa."
And then Barack is like, "I'm getting a 24-pack of beef tacos."
And Donald Trump is, "I recently went vegetarian and I need the black bean chalupa."
"This is the only fast food place where I can get a vegetarian option."
What about the Beyond Burger?
It's 2009, we don't have that yet.
Yeah, it's Donald Trump in 2009.
2009. Yeah, it's 2009 Donald Trump still doing The Apprentice.
Yeah. And he's still hanging out with Epstein. He is preparing for his
Comedy Central roast where he announced his presidency and he's talking to Mike
the Situation and he's giving him all of his material for the show.
And we recreate the Mike the Situation Donald Trump roast but instead of
of Mike the Situation he's played by Michael Shannon. Yeah, Mike the Shannonation.
Mike's the Shannonation and it's Michael Shannon being like Anthony
Jizzleneck I love your jokes I told them to a model when I was having sex with her
at my apartment on a stack of money. That roast is so incredible. Dude it is one of
the best. It's so great and then at the very end when he's like Donald Trump I
I think you should run for president.
Yeah, I think you should run for president, man.
When did the roast get bad?
I think it's the James Franco roast.
Oh, yeah.
'Cause, no, no, no, 'cause it was technically
like a funny one, but they had too many people
who were like alt comics and shit
who broke the format, and so the original format
is just not funny anymore.
Yeah, so the--
'Cause like Anthony-- I remember--
- Or fucking Sandberg did that thing that was like,
- Boom roasted!
- Yeah, yeah.
And it's just like, as soon as you do that
on the Comedy Central roast,
you can't go back to Liza Minnelli,
like being made fun of for having--
- Liza Minnelli?
- I mean, no, Liza.
(laughing)
What's her fucking name?
- Yeah, they're gonna make the Comedy Central--
- Lisa Stramboli, what's her fucking name?
- Lisa Lampanelli?
- Lisa Lampanelli.
You can't go back to just making fun of her
for like having sex with a black guy,
which is the first 30 roasts.
Oh yeah, every roast is just Greg Giraldo being like,
the limousine, that's what they call
Lisa Lampanelli's pussy.
Yeah, it's awesome dude.
But you can, I mean, those old ones in the 2000s
were so funny, but they'll never be back.
Dude, Aziz Ansari went up and just went like,
he did like a fucking woke, like,
yeah, I'm actually not gonna tell any jokes.
He did like an annet.
Did he?
I don't even remember.
Did you see, he annetted the roast?
Yeah, he annetted the roast.
He knew it was coming.
Do you know that roast of Bob Saget where Gilbert Gottfried goes up and just keeps saying over
and over, "Bob Saget raped and killed a girl in 1990"?
He just says that over and over.
That's one of the all- that's probably the all-time best I would say is Bob Saget.
And then the Norm one too.
I thought that was the one where he did the Aristocrats.
I don't think so.
I mean I don't know anything about-
He was on so many of them.
Yeah, that's true.
Like that, those old ones with Geraldo and Godfried.
- Nah, I'm just imagining Gilbert Godfried
trying to do it as like an alt,
like the new alt comic roast shit.
So I have anxiety.
I have anxiety because I was molested as a kid.
(laughing)
- That's his version of like revelation.
- He has an epiphany on stage.
(laughing)
He just stares into the camera.
"Oh shit!"
"I said too much!"
"I didn't realize I was gonna have a breakthrough at the roast!"
Yeah, his eyes finally open.
He just stares directly into a mirror.
I can see my reflection in the lens!
I hate the man I've become!
Every morning I wake up in a malaise!
I am a coward!
I need serious...
You just start screaming?
I need serious help!
*laughter*
Please! Somebody help me!
Somebody stop me!
*laughter*
I found the mask backstage!
Gilbert Gottfried, Son of the Mask?
*laughter*
Yeah, I'm thinking I'm producing that movie.
I put on this mask and fucked my wife!
Let's see what happens!
You know he's doing TikToks now?
Yeah, he's doing TikToks where he reads tweets.
Wow.
You know, he's a very frugal man.
You know, he takes the megabus out.
This sounds like a roast joke.
Gilbert Gottfried is a very frugal man.
He wants...
He wants what?
- Come on, do it. - Oh man.
- Say it.
- It's hard to do that style without--
- Yeah, what do I do? - Without something
that we have to edit out.
- Exactly.
(laughing)
Exactly.
- No, you have to finish this.
We're not editing anything out.
- No, I'm gonna go 2018 roast.
- Okay, do it.
- He's so frugal.
He had the--
- He had the?
- He had the--
- The best part.
- The greatest intro to any punchline, he had the.
(laughing)
- He had the,
mega, he had--
- He had the mega.
- The mega.
- He had the mega bus driver.
He's so frugal he had the mega bus driver.
- Just like Moshi Kasha wrote it up for ya.
- Is that the end of the sentence?
- He had the mega bus driver.
- He's so frugal he had the mega bus driver.
- Okay, well we gotta workshop this together.
- No.
- Yeah, all right, well we already are committed,
we already are locked into he had the mega bus driver.
- Yeah, you have to continue with that.
- How about he had the Megabus driver give him a dollar.
(laughing)
- There we go.
- He uses mail-in rebate on a gumball.
How about that?
(laughing)
That's pretty good.
- He had the Megabus driver use his mail-in rebate.
- He had the Megabus driver, there we go.
- Use his mail-in rebate.
he had a medium ball for a megabus driver
yeah gilbert gottfried is so frugal issued yet don't say she hit that
he's he put a god stopper on layaway
uh... here we go to see a yeltsin loves canada
yeah
yet gilbert gottfried so frugal he p
put it he made a nurse wrote
uh...
fuck he stole a nerds rope
he made a nerds rope last three weeks
yeah that's kinda just impressive
yeah gilbert godfried is so frugal
for dinner every night he licks a gobstopper
and it lasts him a whole week
that's good dude that's really good
I think I should try these out.
We need to do, yeah.
Let's write some more roast jokes about it.
But again, we gotta keep it PG.
Gilbert Godfrey.
Yeah.
Gilbert Godfrey is so frugal and he loves candy so much that when he bought a candy
bar and it had Willy Wonka's golden ticket in it, he used the golden ticket to buy 1,000
more candy bars.
Which is way more than the golden ticket was worth.
That's true.
In the first place.
Because of inflation.
of the because of how frugal he was. And then you would go from here and you would say, "Speaking
of inflation, uh, Lisa Lippinelli is here." I want to see Gilbert Gottfried inflated.
I want to see a little baby kicking around upside of him. Yeah. Speaking of inflation,
I want to put a Yankee candle under his ass and ride him like a hot air balloon. Speaking
of inflation, I'm looking out in the audience right now and I'm imagining every one of you
naked and puffed up like a bouncing balloon. Yeah. That's right. I'm turning the roast on
the audience this time around.
Speaking of inflation, I have a bee in my pocket and I'm going to give it to Bob Saget, who's
deathly allergic to bees.
Genius.
Speaking of bees, I'm a bee.
Patrice O'Neil is here.
Patrice, I thought you died in 2011.
See, that'd be a good one, right?
Greg Giraldo is here.
Hey, Greg.
I thought you died before that.
Hey, Greg, you died earlier than Patrice.
He died in 2009.
And speaking of, Warren Sapp is here from the Tampa Bay Buccaneers.
Warren Sapp, they call you, they call you, no, you weren't the refrigerator.
Phil Hartman's here.
Hey Phil, how's your wife?
Hey Phil, you died way earlier than all of them.
Hey, how's your wife? Did she kill you?
Andy Dick is here. Hey, what did you do to Phil Hartman's wife?
[laughter]
Hey, Ralphie Mays here. Hey, you're also dead.
Who else is dead?
Hey, Alexander the Great is here. I thought you died a really long time ago.
Hey Jesus Christ is here he's alive in all of us.
The theater is filled with freaking dinosaurs I thought we got rid of those
things. Yeah speaking of dinosaurs Larry King is here. See that'd be a good one.
Yeah. I could definitely write the segues. Yeah. You just saying all of those
just into the microphone one after another and they're just trying to pull
you offstage. Yeah you're not even like there's no connecting joke it's just the
segues. Speaking of dinosaurs George Burns is still alive for the purpose of this joke.
So now the security guards are trying to drag me offstage.
What is this? Speaking of security guards. What am I a terrorist?
The Mandalay Bay incident could have never... Yeah speaking of candy Eminem is here.
what what up that's what I would yeah come on up here man yeah you yeah you talk
come in and so did Eminem ever do a roast I know Snoop Dogg Snoop Dogg was on all
of them Snoop Dogg was at the Donald Trump roast and all of his were all he
only I only remember his Lisa Lampanelli stuff and it was always like Lisa you
got the stankiest pussy I ever ate girl and then they would play like music
behind him. His own music. Yeah. It's cool. Yeah it was cool. Yeah. Yeah. I miss him dude.
I'm so glad he died. Donald Trump has a casino. Hey Donald Trump is here. Speaking of Las Vegas,
Stephen Paddock is here. Yeah Stephen Paddock is here at the roast. Hey Stephen Paddock
How'd you fire 52 consecutive ARs?
Stephen Paddock is here from... he's at the hotel adjacent to the roast.
Everybody look out.
Yeah, Stephen Paddock and Jason Aldean are here.
Or James Aldean.
I feel the tension in the room.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's like at the Grammys where they sit exes next to each other.
Yeah, they said James L Dean and and Steve static
The comedy central roast I don't think we've gone a single episode without mentioning Stephen Paddock at least I know we have
Or they'll not in the past few weeks. I think we've had like a
Streak. Oh, yeah, we should not talk about your knowledge. No, they didn't tell they didn't even it was so late
They fucking they called me. I guess I got a couple mixed missed calls from the couple mixed calls from the
Boston Police Department and
And they, I answered and it was like a four minute phone call.
They, for one second, they were like,
"Do you know why we're calling you today?"
And I was like, "No sir, I have no idea."
Just smiling so slyly.
- Yeah.
- And he was like, "Did you post on Facebook?"
And I just said, I was like, "No."
(laughing)
And he's like, "I'm sorry, no Facebook.
"Twitter.com, did you post something about
"I'm making the United States Army military surrender to you"
"Kind of a... making the US Army surrender"
And I was like, "Yes I did, yes that was me"
And he was like "Okay son, you can't, I mean"
"I'm not gonna tell you what you can do with your life, but just be careful what you post online"
And I was like "Is that it?"
They didn't even ask me if I was serious
it down there just like just be careful because there's filters out there and they see something
like surrender US Army or I want to declare war on the United States military and they
get you know and now I got to give you a phone call and you know you're doing me a big favor
by just not posting stuff like that son so just be careful.
It's so funny how big of like a file they have of you.
You don't even live there anymore.
For like brought up same with the Secret Service guys they brought up they were like, oh the next door
They make posts in 2018 on an application called next door
And I was like, yeah
He's like did you post on the application next door that you were looking for people in your neighborhood to commit crimes with?
Yeah, and they're like did you also make a post
Asking if there was an if there was an old man
wandering around, who had gotten stuck in your apartment and was making pancakes.
I forgot about the old man.
Yeah, I made two posts on the next door app.
Who was that a photoshop or like a face app of?
It was some random face app of like this very low quality image of an old man.
And I made a post on the next door app.
Oh, I thought it was one of us.
I was like, this guy walked into my apartment, made himself lunch,
and now he's just sitting on the couch smiling like this.
(laughing)
And I was like, I don't wanna kick him out
and I don't wanna call the police,
but can someone come retrieve him?
And I had a bunch of people, they were like,
you need to call the police right now.
He could've escaped from a senior home.
And I was like, no, I don't think so.
We're playing a game now.
(laughing)
And then, yeah, and then I just had one other one,
'cause every single post on that app is just like,
especially in Boston, it's just like,
you're wearing a do-rag yeah yeah just saw a man walking his dog in his backyard
just yeah and could be in disguise shoot him yeah and so I just made a post I was
like yeah mailman just walked up mailman just walked up my front steps
and put something in my mind mailman just woke up oh he bring me I like what
Didn't you tell the cops that it was Neal setting you up?
I got a call in the middle of a class, in an art class.
Art class?
In an art class that I was taking.
Finger painting?
I was finger painting.
You were taking finger painting?
I was making a turkey with my hand.
Intro to finger painting?
And the Boston Police Department called me a couple years ago and they were like, "Yeah,
Did you make a post saying that you were looking for people in your neighborhood to commit
various crimes with?"
And I was like, "No, I actually think that was this guy who's obsessed with me and he
has my number and he's always doing shit like this.
His name is Neil."
And then they gave him a call and he had no idea what was happening.
And then he called me and he was like, "Did you tell the police that I did a...
I committed a crime.
I was like, no, dude, they're after you, dude.
Oh my God.
Imagine he gets like pulled over one day.
We have a warrant for your arrest in Boston, Massachusetts.
I mean, it rocked it.
I love, I love the hanging out with the police on the phone.
That's why I do this is you and I just want them to call me.
It's because you could never join the force, but you want to join.
Hang out you want to be with the God them so bad. Yeah, that's exactly it. Why do you guys keep calling me?
You guys
So what's up you guys see you guys do my address
I'm like
Six burgers do you guys need a physical description of me? Do you guys need to know what I'm wearing right now?
Do you guys need to come over? I'm sorry if you do sir. Can you tell us what you look like a six and a half?
cut that's all you'll need to know yeah I mean I I've ascertained there might be
some poisoned hamburgers on the grill in my backyard and I want you and your
friends to come over and help me investigate them and test them yeah I've
ascertained that there's a strange hole in my bathroom wall there's a strange
hole in my butt I'd really like you to look at mouth in front of it I need
somebody yeah it's holding the stall in the the bar on the corner near my
apartment it has this weird taste to it and I think it might be poison I need
somebody to come taste test it can you please get some taste testers down here
some of your finest taste testing on a taste tester for the police department
yeah now that's a job job that's what we're gonna transform the police
department into just up in full that's like a bomb full bomb squad gear except
there's a cutout where your tongue is yeah a full like biohazard suit yeah with
just a tongue hole. Yeah, that's what I'm talking about. Hey, I think there might be a glitch
in my Mortal Kombat game. I need you guys to come take a look at it. Can you guys come
game test my game? I think someone's committing a crime in Grand Theft Auto. I'm going to
need you to come and watch me play it. Yeah, I'm going to need, I actually, just straight
up you guys, we only have one Xbox, but we have six people trying to play Halo Kombat
evolved we need you guys to bring over another Xbox two extra controllers and
an Ethernet cable so we can land party this bitch how's that sound yeah you
guys pick up a couple of cores lights yes everyone here is around 12 or 13
- but they're cool they won't tell anyone just bring it over okay come on
we're still two cigarettes from Tom's dad and we're basically gonna have the
wildest night ever yeah we might even call a couple girls over play truth or
- We're gonna go on Uvu with a couple of girls later.
- It's gonna be pretty awesome.
- They're using, I'm old enough to have Uvu premiums,
so all the kids are.
- Hey, cops, listen, two of my friends are playing
gay chicken and they're actually getting really,
really close to each other's penises.
So if you wouldn't mind coming and putting an end
to this nonsense.
- Yeah.
We're gonna have the perfect night.
- They're way too young to be playing gay chicken.
- All that's missing is four or five heroes
to protect this country.
(laughing)
- Yeah, and a--
- We need more heroes at this party.
- And a blockbuster rental of My Bloody Valentine 3D.
So if you guys could bring that over on the way.
- Hey, do you guys have any good stories
you can come tell to my friends?
I've been telling stories to my friends all night,
but I work in retail, so it's all really boring stories.
I need some really good stories.
Do you guys kill anybody?
Can you guys come kill someone at my party
so I can tell a story about it next week?
- How many, do you guys have any more heroic tales?
We also, we pulled enough money to get a red box, so.
(laughing)
Maybe even a Blu-ray.
- Me and my friends are planning to go as cops for Halloween,
so could we borrow some stuff from you?
- We got, we got Lego City on Switch,
and there's some cop stuff in this game
that we're trying to figure out, but we don't know.
- Yeah, can you come look at this cop stuff in Lego City
and tell us if it's accurate?
- I need to figure out if these Lego cops
are telling the truth.
- We need a fifth for pick up basketball
and I know you guys love being filmed doing shit like that.
So you wanna come down and get your ankles broken?
- Yeah, my little brother just ran away.
No, no, I don't need you to come look for him.
Can you just come be my little brother?
(laughing)
- You come replace him.
- Yeah, can I actually get a bunch of you guys?
- One thing my little brother loved to do is jack me off.
So if you're gonna be a good little brother.
- Yeah, you kinda have to, you know.
- It's kind of in your job now.
- Yeah, and it's actually super dry.
It needs something wet in it.
- It needs cop wet.
- You should put your cop juice on me.
- Yeah, I need some cop sweat.
- I actually stashed a big bag of cocaine up in my penis.
- Yeah, and you need to fish it out.
- There's a crime going on in my ass.
- My ass has a tiny city in it,
and I need you to inspect the investigation.
- 9/11 just happened in the tiny city in my ass,
So I need you to go save everybody.
- Yeah, I need you to respond first.
- Yeah.
- Firstly.
- First of all, I need you to respond.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- That's what they said as soon as the plane
hit the second tower.
- Yeah.
- Wow, someone needs to respond to this right now.
- For 911, what's your emergency?
First of all, you need to respond now.
- Do you have any response for what just happened
in midtown Manhattan?
Oh shit!
Alright, thanks, I'll see you later!
That's the response we needed.
Yeah.
No.
The response we didn't need?
The Iraq War.
Whoa.
Eww.
So uh...
He's got a point.
Yeah, I'll be headlining Giggles in Boston, Massachusetts doing stuff like that.
It's in Saugus.
in Saugus, Massachusetts, doing stuff like that,
doing kind of awesome.
- Awesome David Cross jokes.
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna be going and doing David Cross's jokes
in Saugus, Massachusetts.
- I'm gonna be reenacting David Cross's first line
in the Dalai Lama sketch from Mr. Show season four.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
I'm gonna be performing that sketch
they just pulled from With Bob and David.
word yeah it's my that yeah they just pulled it oh that's so funny yeah yeah
it's a good sketch yeah it was a good sketch it was a very good sketch it's so
funny that they just like like the Tina Fey pulling the 30 rock episodes is so
funny oh I know like literally like I didn't make that yeah I didn't I
definitely didn't write all that yeah no what and like all of the the the stuff
in Kimmy Schmidt where Titus is in like yellow face like that. Did they call that too? No that's still
up. Yeah I didn't watch Unbreakable Kimmy Schmidt because I'm not a girl but that just might be me.
I mean I don't know about you guys I guess. I watched it I think I watched the first season.
Yeah I watched. But then I realized that that was a girl and not like a not like a rock fan
with long hair. That's what I thought. I was like this metal head is very funny. I thought it was
I thought it was Mark Wahlberg's character in Rockstar.
Yeah, unfortunately.
Which is why I thought she was okay with the yellow face.
Yeah.
No, that shit, they pulled the Always Sunny episodes too, right?
Really?
Yeah.
I think that's much funnier than the 30 Rock thing, though.
Yeah, I mean that sucks.
We're pulling all these documentaries about Hitler because Hitler, he does bad stuff in
them so yeah it can't be on Netflix yeah yeah yeah this is like like oh you just
can't you can't see this like yeah so dumb yeah what are we in communist China
I can't watch someone do blackface anymore on Netflix we're in China now
this people are so I just it it just it blows my mind all the time just how how
many people are just like oh if something's on TV that means that they
think it's good yeah that means like right it's so crazy how can you I just I
don't understand anything that happens in a movie happens because people think
it's good yeah in a movie every character is good there's no such thing
as a bad character American Psycho yeah he's very good we're taking it
as he's a job man exactly creates job fine that's fine that's why he can do
all that shit is cuz he makes jobs. But those scumbags in Always Sunny, those leeches who
work a job at a bar like an absolute fucking degenerates. Yeah, exactly. You can't see it
but my head's shaking so hard right now. Yeah it is. My head's shaking so hard. He's gonna
make himself dizzy. I did. I did make myself dizzy. It doesn't take much to make you dizzy.
I'm very I have a lot of low amounts of blood. I'm
I blame Disney for everything. Yeah, um, I pretty much I'm just becoming that guy. Yeah, it's true
Yeah, just people they control everything and they have absolutely no stomach for anything did you see
Do you see mouse actually is evil the thing that was like evil in it the NBA like
Like oh, yeah, well, we'll see the security. Yeah, Walt Disney security is gonna be trolling the NBA like seating or whatever
you know that they're having they're just doing the rest of the NBA season in Disney World because
That's the because they don't want players to leave so they have to do it somewhere where the players can be entertained
Yeah, and it's like they make two hundred million dollars a year
I think yeah, I can like like they don't have to play golf every day. Well, they can live in the princess
Yeah, and plus if you're doing like the rest of the NBA season, like Splash Mountain's gonna get fucking boring after a while, you know?
Not anymore, no, because they're turning it into Princess and the Frog.
Oh, right, Princess and the Frog Mountain.
Yeah, exactly.
Which, famously, that movie had a lot of mountains.
That's true, yeah,
the beautiful mountains of New Orleans.
Beautiful mountains of New Orleans.
Yeah.
Take me home, country roads.
The only, like,
like, IP
they could think of that had like black people in it was Princess and the Frog.
Disney's been woke for like eight years. Yeah it's true. Yeah when Obama got
reelected they were like all right, Song of the South, we're gonna stop doing a new
release of Song of the South every 15 weeks. Right. Disney was like oh well just
like Walt Disney like froze his brain so that like the Jews couldn't get it and
now it's like well we we made we made Moana now so yeah they're just good just
they're they're just trying to freak him out as much as possible when they
unthaw him yeah once they unthawed yeah we made we made splash mountain it's
It's Schindler's List theme now.
(laughing)
What on earth?
Oh my God!
What happened to my idea for the
Protocols of the Elders of Zion ride?
Yeah, we had to scrap that, Walt.
Yeah, no, people didn't like that idea.
People were being super weird about it.
Yeah, people were being so weird.
I mean, you're alive now, you can talk to them about it.
I'm sure you can convince them, but--
Here, let's get you set up with a Twitter account.
we're gonna go first all right well Walt Disney has been taken so Walt Disney
1480 nope that's been taken too.
yeah why is it why is your at Walt Disney 1488 well I think Disney properties
should be as accessible to 14 year olds as 88 year olds.
So that's pretty much why.
Oh, okay.
We believe you.
Yeah, I tried every number from 1 to 1487.
I swear.
I'm sorry.
This was just the first one that worked.
What is our CEO's last name?
He better be a scientist.
Yeah. He, uh...
When they saw it at Disney, it's just like me.
He finds out about Marvel and he gets really excited when he's watching the first Captain
America movie, and then he's like, "Oh, man. I totally misread that."
They did what to the Red Skull?
Yeah.
How are you going to kill the protagonist in the first movie?
(laughing)
- Interesting to do an anti-hero movie.
Black Panther, hmm.
(laughing)
- Oh, well, that's not the wasp I was thinking, but.
I didn't know it was gonna be so literal.
- It's never a good idea to unthaw anybody.
- No. - Yeah, leave 'em,
leave 'em froze.
Austin power you should have kept in the thing dude. Yeah, it's too horny
Yeah, yeah, they're gonna cancel Austin Powers pretty soon. God. He makes - he makes women too Randy, baby
Yeah
Here's my story of how my ex Austin Powers actually abused me by making me too Randy all the time
thread one of 60 one of 69 fuck
See that's his fault. Yeah. Yeah, I can't stop thinking about 69. I can't stop thinking about 69 in Austin Powers. Oh
Oh my god. Oh my god. I went to shock therapy to stop thinking about it. Yeah
Yeah
Walt Disney wakes up and he sees the Star Wars franchise and he sees
He sees like just reading really slowly and he sees the last Jedi and he's like the last I like where this is going
(laughter)
- Oh, fuck.
Oh, God, that was good.
- We have fun.
- We're talking about Walt Disney.
Disney is not gonna be happy with this episode.
- Yeah, that's the real reason we should keep him frozen.
- Yeah.
yeah we're actually getting bought out by disney
i know it i don't see mergers next
is it
i've been a reality happens at the time of this record a we're getting bought out
by uh... e_s_p_n_
uh... we have to support
here we are technically a sports show
they want to see if they want us to have a little bit of a station i choose i
think you're in the improv yet instead of the emperor we used to be seen as a
- Stand Up, they pushed, for some reason,
they're censoring us from the Stand Up charts.
- Really?
- Yeah, I think they listened and they were like,
"This is not a Stand Up podcast."
- Damn. - So they took us out of it.
It's kinda fucked.
- Yeah. - They moved us to improv?
- No, I moved us to improv because we'd stopped
charting in Stand Up.
We used to always be like six or seven on Stand Up,
but then they just kicked us off.
- That's true, yeah.
- It's pretty fucked up, you know.
- Yeah, and now we have to--
- Now we have to do improv every episode.
- Put us in the rapist category, come on.
(laughing)
- Why'd they go and do that?
- It's pretty fucked up.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I don't love it.
- Yeah, I'm not a fan.
I think they should have a category called lists.
- Yeah, I've been saying this for--
- They should have a category called podcast about list.
- Yeah, they should.
- We're charting all the time.
- It's okay, we're just charting the normal comedy now.
We've been charting for--
- Which rate us five stars.
- Yeah, we do need, yeah, let's get to number,
let's beat Joe Rogan.
- Uh-huh.
Let's beat Joe Dogan.
We could beat Joe Dogan.
We could beat James Dogan.
We could beat Shane Dogan for sure.
We could beat Shane Hogan.
Uh huh.
Shane Dogan.
Yeah, well I'm not going to say his real name.
We could beat up Shane Hogan.
Yep.
And Shane, if you're listening to this, I could beat you up, buddy.
I want you to know that.
You try to send me that picture.
Yeah, you try to kill me with your funny gun.
Yeah, nobody knows what we're talking about.
Okay, there's a comedian with a funny gun in Boston.
Yeah. We've definitely talked about it before. I think we have probably, but he has a pistol with a sniper scope on it.
Yeah. We've used that picture for so many things. There used to be a time when you looked up podcast about list on Google images that that was one of the first.
That was like the only thing that came up. Yeah. Yeah. That's awesome.
That's so good. Yeah. We should all get guns. I miss those days where we just had like... I miss Boston Comedy, dude.
It's all just Facebook posts now.
Yeah.
It's all like, "Oh, my Zoom show."
There was this whole thing where some girl tried to do, she was like, "Yeah, I'm going
to do a Zoom show for Black Lives Matter charity where I show my tits."
And then it was like a thousand comments from guys who would definitely pay to see that,
just like, "This is in very poor taste."
So awesome, dude.
So cool.
You gotta love it, dude.
You gotta love it, I miss it.
I'm moving back.
Well, that's the double standard.
And it sucks that they didn't let you do your Zoom show.
Yeah, it is pretty sad.
Yeah, that's why I have to wear these tank tops now.
It's as close as I can get.
Yeah, they didn't let us do Caleb's Comedy Club.
And let me tell you, those aren't C's.
Yeah.
(laughing)
You know what, we should plug, because this will be out.
The stream that we're going on will still be going.
Oh, true!
Yeah, so if you're listening to this,
right when it comes out I think the kimono friendzone goes until it's going
to tomorrow yeah today noon on the day this guy's out twitch.tv slash kimono
friendzone or check out a sample wave or Sam underscore Chris on on Twitter we're
gonna be yeah I'm gonna be on and off on that stream. 24 hour Tony Hawk so check it out.
Do we get to play the game or do we just watch the stream? I don't really know we're just gonna find out.
We're gonna do it right now. I wish I wish
Well if we play thug pro I could play. Oh, yeah, we can just also just separately play thug pro kind of for fun
While we're on it. Yeah, we'll just do that idea. All right. Yeah, I'm smart. All right. Bye. Bye everybody. Bye everybody
Bye, everybody.