you're listening to Israel's number one pod.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[laughter]
[explosion]
So we found a condom in my room.
Yeah.
It's probably decades old.
Hell yeah.
That condom's been sitting in Tom's wallet forever.
Yeah.
Tom Wilder.
Tom, you know the vibes.
has it been being in uh... college again
on you fell out uh... honestly it sucks med school sucks i can imagine
why do you know why are you living in a dorm
i'm looking at the top of the fact that the public
it's like
that i'm literally i'm like the cheapest rent
now how how are you
honestly patrick's not a at home is to get mugged
yeah i live in a bad part of town for you and i just
i'm a skateboard with me i can't send my son i think we have a place that i can
- You can impress him with a kick flip until they leave.
- Yeah, as he's stabbing you to death for 75 cents.
- Right, exactly.
- That was great, so Patrick--
- I got paid yesterday.
- You got paid yesterday?
Oh yeah, you got your refund too?
- Nice, dude.
- You got a refund?
I said a refund from Subway.
- Oh, yeah, a Subway refund.
- Yeah, for the finger that was in your sandwich.
But point is, Patrick came to the dorm
and he hung out with a bunch of my fellow med students.
- Yeah, and then Tom left me in the room.
- I left him in the room for like 20 minutes
'cause I was talking to one of my friends in the hallway
and I was really nervous about what I was gonna come back to.
(laughing)
Patrick alone.
- Patrick alone in a dorm.
- Yeah, just drooling. - With med students, yeah.
That I don't know.
- Yeah, so do you live with other people in this dorm?
- Yeah, so I have a single, I have this one other dude.
- Congrats.
- Jean-Luc who's pretty cool.
- Jean-Luc Picard.
- Jean-Luc, I'm not gonna say his last name.
I don't know. - No, say it.
(laughing)
- He has a Patreon, they gotta pay for it.
- Yeah, yeah, that's whatever.
- Actually, you know what, if it's Patreon,
it's people who look him up. - Literally, so he's
this cool dude. - True.
- He literally looks exactly like Steve Harrington
from Stranger Things.
- Oh, my brother met him.
- He's very handsome. - Exactly like who?
- Oh, it is 50 Hours.
- Steve Harrington from Stranger Things.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I know.
- Yeah, I've had a couple drinks, so you know.
This might not come up clean.
- You can tell me what part of town you're living in.
- So I live in technically the South End.
- The South End-y, baby.
- No, I live by Boston Medical Center.
- South End is the nicest part of the city, I feel like.
- Yeah, well it turns real quick,
'cause it does turn into like basically--
- At night it's a whole different place.
- Are you saying the part by the trains is the bad part?
- Yeah, I mean like, yeah.
I wouldn't call it, yeah.
- This is awesome.
I will, safe isn't the first word.
- What stop are you closest to on the orange line?
- Mass Ave, probably.
- Oh, yeah, okay.
Come on, I can, yeah.
- But you're like a mile away from Mass Ave.
- Oh, word, okay.
- Just Patrick kick-flipping his way.
- Yeah.
- I am actually neighbors with Lloyd now.
- Oh, yeah. - I see Lloyd all the time.
- Really? - Oh, we have--
- Yeah, yeah, the-- - We should have Lloyd on
when I get back.
- Honestly, it would rule.
- Oh, it'd be so good.
- It would be so fucking good, dude.
- I'd love that, man.
- I wanna ask him about his gloves.
He wears finger, he's a Boston comedian,
wears fingerless gloves everywhere he goes.
- I wanna see him do karaoke.
He does like, so he does comedy, he also does--
- Yeah, he's a Michael Jackson impersonator.
- Yeah, he does like, basically,
he's basically a Michael Jackson impersonator.
And he's probably like,
he's too nice to be in Boston comedy.
- Right.
- Yeah.
It's not great.
- You gotta be hard, you gotta be hard
to be in Boston comedy.
- Patrick, shut up.
- You gotta be horny.
- Gales, how's LA?
You look thin.
You've lost weight. - Thanks, buddy.
I have lost weight.
LA's a never-ending nightmare.
- Oh, big announcement for the listeners.
Yeah, I think I'm going out to LA.
- Woo!
- Yeah. - Yeah, baby.
- I gotta talk to my work,
I gotta talk to my manager about getting those days off.
- Nice. - But yeah.
I saved up enough money.
- $26.
$26 and it's all thanks to you to the work. Mm-hmm. Shout out to the the patreon who is
Chunk of it. Do you just have numbers on the patreon or do you have like end of it? Do you know who yeah
We know we know who's subscribing we have like we did shout outs. That's pretty crazy. Yeah, who subscribes besides like
black retard and
fat asshole and
It's black and fat retard. Oh, it's fat fucking reach
Hot agent that's a real one. Yeah, it's odd agent. Yeah. Yeah, so we do know who subscribes
I don't know if they're aware that we get their name, but we do right $5 a month. It's five bucks a month
Yeah, probably do we have to pitch you our patreon right now?
You said that you would probably subscribe three times tonight
I mean, I listen to every single one of the podcasts.
Not every.
You told me in the lift here.
You're not going to fucking listen to this one.
I'm not going to listen to this one.
You told me in the lift here, you're like, "Oh, five bucks a month, I can do that."
And then 20 minutes ago, you were like, "Yeah, I'm not going to fucking pay five bucks a month."
Yeah, yeah, yeah. But I mean, I will. I will.
Pick a side, stupid.
No, pick a side, stupid.
Nice.
You know, you know, it's funny we we make like we make like $30 more a month on our patreon than they really
Yeah, I mean what are you gonna do yeah
Sean Carter BTF
Yeah, John Carter fucking owned did it rocks because like he put Brian Sullivan in the gauntlet round of his one of his shows
It's just like Brian Sullivan's the best comedian you could ever touch Sean Connery
I'm drinking an awful sour beer that I got for free. What is it? Yeah. Yeah, what is that shit?
I like a modello. No, it's a
smokey rain
grand crew
Flemish sour ale that sounds bad. It's really bad. I was I was drinking this and listening to even flow right before I call
Even flows a such a good song. I forgot how good that song
made of concrete.
I think I've been thinking about that line.
drive Tom has one of those little like wine tumblers and they're pouring him a
shot and then Tom takes the bottle and then pours fucking four shots worth of
alcohol into the thing and they everybody at once like once they noticed
they were all like what are you doing people are taking shots of rum at
medical school yeah I never want to go to the fucking wasteland shots of rum
don't go to the dentist already ruining I'm so depressed yeah I can imagine
yeah you look terrible I was thinking I was thinking on the way over here how
funny it is that like you like at the end of this will like plug your Twitter
account and then it'll just be like 10 more strangers who follow you as you just tweet
like another day in hell.
Like every 16 minutes.
I love being Irish.
Just oscillating between like I'm getting drunk right now and then I got too drunk and I'm
thinking about dead people I used to know.
Honestly it rules because it's like I feel like every once in a while like a couple people
that I've known like you guys or like other people online will like retweet me
and I'll pick up like 10 followers and then I'll tweet something like "oh went
on this date with this girl didn't go well gonna kill myself later" and then
I'll just lose them immediately. As it should work. People are like "oh maybe this guy's funny" and I'm just like "no."
Because you don't you don't even put jokes online. It's just people who only
know me intimately might enjoy. Yeah exactly yeah it's more theater than
anything else. Theater of the mind. I would describe myself as an artist and I have.
He did five minutes ago. Yeah some girl was like I'm upset you guys aren't coming out
with us to Fabrico which is just like a yeah a club in Cambridge and there's like
you're not coming out that's upsetting I'm like I'm sorry we're artists we have
the podcast. Yeah this is art baby. Yeah just the fact that there's just a
woman's titties over your right shoulder is beautiful. It's called a pinup, Tom.
It rocks, honestly it rocks because it's just like I know the reason it's there.
This is your brother's room? This is, for the last time, this is the office in his
house. You wanna know why I love that? Because it's your brother's too cheap to
buy internet to have porn. So you can just...
Yeah, I'm not connected to the internet right now.
So you can just jack off.
Caleb's talking to us on a hotspot.
No, yeah, I mean, I assumed you're on a landline.
Yeah, I'm plugged in. The thing is, it is, she is very beautiful and she's eating a Pringle,
it looks like.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, that's Selma Hayek.
Selma Hayek's famous Pringle picture from Playboy.
I'm intimately familiar with that photo.
(laughing)
- Is that, now I'm like, I'm gonna check it.
- So what do you do for work out there, Caleb?
- Let's talk about Caleb's detailed job.
- I knew that this is what this episode was gonna turn into.
It's just me and Tom catching up.
- I know, I really miss Caleb.
- Yeah, I miss you too, Tom.
I miss you so much.
I work at a pool place.
- Okay.
- Yeah, I install pool tables.
- You don't wanna talk about it on,
- Oh, you sell pool tables?
- Yeah.
- Are you sharking out there?
Are you like fucking hustling?
Are you hustling?
- No, I only lose money on pool.
- Oh, hell yeah.
- Yeah, no, I play Filipino eight year olds
and they beat my ass for $15.
Yeah, it's really cool.
- That's cool, man.
- But I mostly, I just sell like pool sticks
to just like cranked out fucking maniacs in Santa Clarita.
That's pretty cool.
- Yeah, just looking at what you're gonna be like.
Yeah, just tiny little chicken legs, giant fucking veiny forearms, and a constantly runny
nose asking about where they can get the new--
Just a grown man who maybe has two weeks left.
Right.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, there are people who come into the shop who have done so much meth that their
hearts are blue.
Jesus.
And you can see it bumping out of their chest.
they're like what kind of sticks you got yeah yeah this poplar yeah what is this
you just saw a guitar and there's like it'll shoot good there is a guy who
comes in and looks like a like a juiced-out ghoul I swear to God he looks
like a 250 ghoul. Hell yeah. Yeah and he sounds like that too. Yeah. He's always
saying smooth skin. He's always saying smooth skin. I only have three options of
dialogue when I talk to him. If your charisma goes up any higher you may unlock a fourth. I get a
fourth one that says in brackets charisma. Yeah. I can use my charisma points to say
"Fuck you, man."
(laughing)
And he'll go, "I like the sound of you.
"I like your style, kid.
"I respect you."
Yeah, man, it's awesome.
I'm gonna buy out the whole store.
We, did I already talk about the guy who tried to sell,
or tried to buy a pool table
with a stolen credit card on here?
Oh, you might know, I think this is good for Patreon.
What a king, what a king.
True, yeah, so we got--
Can you drop the credit card number also?
(laughing)
Yeah, I don't care. I don't think I have the credit card. I do have the guy's, uh, the fake
I do here. I'll just so yeah, the guy called one day and he was like, um, he sounded like
like that like old clips of like Woody Allen stand up. He's like, um, excuse me, do you
have a pool table available? And I was like, yeah, man. Yeah, we sell pool tables. And
He was like good. I want to buy one for my son. He lives in Santa Clarita
I live in New York City as you can imagine and
And I'll because I am Woody Allen. Yeah, he's really just hamming it. Yeah, Woody Allen. Yeah
And he so basically I was just like yeah, we have pool tables for sale
But like he was like, yeah, I want to buy one today
I want to buy it today and normally you have to like buy a pool table then schedule a time for us to come deliver
it and set it up and shit and he was like no I just I'll have somebody come pick it
up and so already I'm like okay that's weird cuz like you have you need somebody
who like knows how to install a pool table and but he did seem to not care
and I talked to my boss my boss was like if he just wants to buy the pool table
whatever it's like less work for us so he he we go to I like take his car wearing
What is this guy wearing? To me he's a phone. He called.
Oh he called. Oh wow, I really missed that.
Yeah, that's a whole part of the story.
He called from New York City. He called from New York City.
He called from New York City and then so he gives me a credit card and I
put the credit card in. It's like a $4,000 pool table. And I put the
credit card in and I'm like what's a zip code and he gives me a Chicago zip code
and I'm like okay so your son's in Santa Clarita, you're in New York and you have
a Chicago zip code on your credit card. I don't care because I get a
commission on all the sales so I'm really pushing for this to not be a scam.
So then it doesn't go through and he's like okay I have to go to the bank and
and um put some money into the bank today and i was like i was like okay yeah man that makes perfect
sense to go to the bank yeah i was like yeah dude that you're right you need to go to the bank if uh
because the the the charge is declining the only problem is that it's sunday and there's no banks
open right now and he was like oh no my bank's open on sundays and i was like okay what fuck
Yeah, yeah, it was a Chase card, but Chase is not open on Sundays. But again, I want
that $30 so bad. Also, it's a credit card. Right. What do you mean you have to put money in?
It makes no sense. So then he tells me, then he calls back like an hour and a
half later and he's like, "Hey, I, um, I'm sorry. Hey, I need you to run it on two
separate charges okay so half and half so I do one charge $2,000 the other one
$2,000 and it goes through and my boss is like okay just get a picture of his ID
for the for because we need to we need to have an ID for a sale this big like
over the phone so he sends me a picture of his ID and it's a Pennsylvania ID for
a guy named Robert Schwarzman and I'm like, "Sure, again, like I need
$30 so badly." But so then he's like, "Okay, I'm sending like a group of guys to
come pick it up in about an hour." But so the group of guys, so the shop
closes, the shop closes because it's like and my boss comes over to the shop to
like basically do the the handoff of the table but I leave because I have to go
to a pool league because we close at 5 they were the guys were coming at like
545 or whatever I leave the shop and start driving to pool league and my boss
tells me he's like he's testing me in text and he's like that that that ID
photo that he sent you you have that right and I'm like yeah and he's like
okay it's a live photo I want you to press play on the live photo so then I
I open up the live photo and I press, I like hold it down and so it's a picture
of an ID and then the picture moves up and it's a guy like
it's clearly a black guy's voice saying "I gotta make a couple runs real quick"
and then my boss two seconds later sends me a screenshot from Square that says
like you have used a stolen credit card. This credit card was just reported stolen. I was
like dude fuck yes dude. Here's the best part I still got the commission because my boss
paid me before I left. What a king. What a king. Hell yeah. But yeah man it's Santa Cruz
Paradise. That's LA. That's LA baby. That's not even LA that's north of LA. That's like
This is where that mass shooting happened the other day.
- Oh Jesus. - Oh yeah, that's right.
- All right, did you mark yourself as safe on Facebook?
- I did, yeah, I had to.
- Yeah, yeah. - That kid--
- I was not a student at the high school, but the kid--
(laughing)
- Yeah, weirdly I was at the high school for other reasons
on the day, but I'm safe, everybody.
- I remember, yeah, I was at work and you fucking texted me
and I had to deal with all these fucking rich people.
Like, I was like, "Oh, it's not a gluten allergy,
"but it's a sensitivity."
And I was like, hey, my friend--
- Don't you serve coffee?
- No, we don't just do coffee, we do food.
And I was like, hey, my friend is near a mass shooting.
- Yeah, my friend's visiting his girlfriend
at the Santa Cruz High School.
(laughing)
I don't know if he's safe.
- Yeah, that's right, she's the guidance counselor.
Okay, and she actually, she lives for those fucking kids.
Thank you very much.
She's teaching them about Shakespeare,
but she's doing it in a way in which they can understand.
So she's a--
- It's almost like peer learning.
- She's saying like, yeah, did you know
that Shakespeare was the OG rapper?
(laughing)
The kid who did the shooting, he was--
- I don't know anything about the kid.
I don't know anything about this situation.
What was his vibe?
- What was his vibe?
(laughing)
- That's Tom asking what race he was.
- He lived down the street from my brother.
- Damn.
- Like, yeah, like 10 houses down.
- Yeah, that's his house right here.
- Every night he poked his head in the window.
- Did he have like a manifesto or anything?
- No, that's the cool thing about him
is that he kinda did it.
- That's the cool thing?
(laughing)
- He did it for the lulz.
- It's true.
- That's so sad, god damn it.
- Yeah.
- That's wild.
- I was hoping he would have a cool manifesto
that like mentioned my brother, you know.
- There's this guy.
- Yeah.
- Who has this absolutely gorgeous.
- And I can't get over it.
- Absolutely gorgeous painting at his office.
- She's good looking, dude.
She's really pretty.
- Who was the incel, not shooter, but the guy.
- Elliot Rodger?
yeah he's like an LA guy yeah I mean some of that stuff that he said not great
not great some of it was so it's definitely one of the funniest shooters
of all time yeah no that was that was at Santa Barbara
okay which is yeah which is oh yeah yeah he he he clapped on Santa Barbara big
time he was just like the he was the og in cell yeah I think he yeah a lot of
of them like look up to him yeah yeah a lot of them not us so not we I don't
look up to that guy at all no you guys both have you know I look up to you
perfect jawline Keats heats Keats Keats Oscar Wilde nice nice John Paul Sartre
ah yes yeah Charlie Chapman Charlie Chaplin Wow none of these people women
interesting oh oh and and and girl Charlie Chaplin yeah yeah Bunny dresses
up like a girl that yeah that's my favorite female comedian the only female
comedian I know is girl Bugs Bunny and I only like her cuz she's hot she doesn't
you know what I like she doesn't talk about her pussy she doesn't exactly just
seducing Elmer Fudd.
It's so funny.
I wish I could do it.
Cale, when are you coming back to Mooyahs?
Not to do like a show, but to do the open mic.
Not to Boston, to Mooyah.
I will be back in Boston.
I'm doing, beginning of December, me, Neil, and Gus V,
are all--
we're doing a tour back to Boston.
Wow.
Beginning of Dece-- like after the 14th, or?
Yeah, yeah.
I think--
Are you staying in Boston, or?
So on the 15th, we're leaving.
I think we're doing like--
- So what does a tour back to Boston look like?
What does that mean?
- I think we're doing Flagstaff, Albuquerque.
- Oh, that's what that text was.
- Yeah, I think we're doing the Dallas Improv
somewhere in Atlanta and DC.
And then on the 22nd, we have like a two-hour spot
at the Comedy Studio in Boston.
- You have a two-hour spot at the Comedy Studio?
- Wow. - Hell yeah.
- So that'll be-- - You each get two hours?
- Yeah, yeah, me and, I'm doing an hour 45
and then Gus and Neil can split the rest.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, it's gonna be great.
But I think that's only 20 seconds, so.
Oh, and we're doing one in my hometown in Wilmington.
- Are you staying in Boston or?
- Yes, I'm coming back to Boston.
Then I'm leaving, it's basically the day
after I get to Boston, I'm leaving to North Carolina
for Christmas and then I will be back and living.
- It's like a full time back.
- Hell yeah, he's coming back.
- Nice.
Oh what can you still go to the show me the body show?
Where is that? That's at the Paradise on the 22nd or the 21st. I will not be in
Boston on the 21st. God damn. Alright then I'm gonna bring Cameron. That makes sense
you should do that. Yeah on the 22nd. That's more of a me and Cameron thing. Come on.
Come on, dude.
That's a me and Cameron thing.
I love fucking music, man.
Music's my life.
I just told you I listen to Evenflo right before you called me.
Come on, dude.
I was imagining playing Guitar Hero while I listened to it.
Yeah.
What Guitar Hero was that?
That was Three.
That was Guitar Hero 3.
That was Legends of Rock.
Yeah.
That was one of the first sets.
That was the one with the guy with the giant chin.
Yeah.
And he wears the leather wristband.
That guy did more for music than anybody.
He was sexy dude.
I liked when it would accidentally make him have girl vocals.
Yeah, like when they did Hit Me With Your Best Shot.
Yeah, and you'd be like, "This kid has range."
Yeah, he's got an amazing falsetto.
He can do Hit Me With Your Best Shot, he can also do Jack Black in Tenacious D.
He can go, "Rick-a-cake-cake-cake-cake-cake-cake."
My favorite part about Guitar Hero is that they always made the girl songs be in the
shitty backyard show that you do.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. And then any male vocalist is in Madison Square Garden.
That's not entirely true. Guitar Hero World Tour, they had a Hayley Williams from Paramore.
Shut up! Shut up! Literally.
Jesus Christ. Shut the fuck up.
I'm just saying, Hayley Williams from Paramore was in Guitar Hero World Tour,
the one with Steely Dan, Do It Again.
Steely, okay, we're talking specifically Guitar Hero 3.
Yeah.
Do you have a fact for that now?
Guitar Hero Steely Jay?
I just feel like I never knew how to use my pinky
until I started playing Guitar Hero.
Yeah, I can still play on medium, but I think that's it.
Really?
What was the one where it was like a...
I went up to... what's the one before Expert?
Why am I talking about it?
Hard. There's easy, medium, hard, Expert.
Yeah.
And then I could do hard for a little bit.
And then I stopped playing because I turned 11.
Okay.
And people said that it was gay.
- It is gay, yeah, Guitar Hero is a gay CIA psy-op
to convince, or to teach.
- I played Guitar Hero well into my 15s.
- Damn, you know what it was?
- Your 15s?
- I sold my penis too.
That was a crazy year for me, honestly, wild year for me.
I like went to high school, it was crazy.
- Yeah, Tom is like two years older than us.
- Yeah, he's old.
- So when you were playing Guitar Hero, I was 11,
so it was probably the same time.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- When people were calling me gay.
- And you know what?
It is gay to play guitar here. I guess it is a CIA psyop to teach young men how to do gay stuff like finger pussies on expert mode.
Someone's been listening to Red Scare.
It's a clit over here. You're wiggling a big clit.
We know you're a Red Scare guy.
I think I am subscribed to the Red Scare Patreon.
You've explicitly told me that fact.
That's true. Yeah, I remember you telling me that.
I thought I unsubscribed.
- Like, perfect.
- The what?
- The People's Republic.
- That's where I told you that?
- The bar?
- Yeah, remember we went there one time?
We had that great night.
- Yeah, with Colin, that was fun.
- Dude, that night ruled.
- Yeah, I wasn't there.
- Not yet, you weren't invited.
- People's Republic is a great bar.
- I was living in Revere, I couldn't go anywhere.
- That's so, it's so funny that I like hung out
with you guys like as often as I did.
And like, I was losing so much money
every time I came to hang out.
- The last half of every hang with Patrick
was him stressing about how to get home.
- Yeah. - He was just trying to walk.
- And you just being like, "Hey man, it's gonna be okay.
"You do it every time, somehow."
- Just Patrick walking through the Ted Williams tunnel.
- Right. (laughing)
- Trying to skateboard through the Ted Williams.
- Yeah, on a skateboard.
I'm at that fucking, what's it called?
What's the, what's that highway in, it goes to Revere?
- 93?
- Route one, I'm on route one.
- This is what the people have always wanted
from this podcast.
- Talking about gene-graphical locations.
- Yeah, this is what fat whatever, fat fucker, whoever.
- Fat fucker, yeah.
- That's Tom trying his hardest not to say retard on my--
(laughing)
- We'll just name him Fat Fucker.
- He's in medical school now.
- Dude, I lived off of Route 1.
- You lived off of Route 1?
- Yeah. - That's disgusting.
- I know, I lived pretty close to Kowloon.
- That's so disgusting.
- I know.
I think I'm right you're gonna new cat. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah, talk about that fucker - baby
Fuck where I don't think we're gonna call the fucker the fucker anymore cuz they're gonna watch elective the fuckers
That's a sellout. Yeah. Yeah, I'm not into it. I'm not into it, but
but I
Do have to show you a pretty good video the video honestly Caleb video rules. Yes, what's the video?
It's Dom introducing the two cats to each other and one of them just runs into a wall.
Yeah, I can't tell which one is which but one freaks out and just runs into a wall and fucks his shit up.
Can you tell which one is which?
Yeah, well they look exactly the same except the fucker is an inch shorter than Yoda
and Yoda has blue eyes.
You should just put like a sharpie thing on the side of it.
- You should, yeah, yeah.
- I should.
- Yeah.
- I might.
(laughing)
Just like a cool, do a super S.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, the Stussy logo.
That'd be cool.
- If he did that, and they had the lines,
like the three lines.
- Yeah, the three lines and the three lines,
and do it with the Jester's hat.
- Yeah.
- That would be cool.
- Patrick's texting his girlfriend right now as well.
- Yeah.
- I will say, Caleb, honestly,
I'm looking past my computer right now
and there's a jar of peanut butter
and I'm going to go to town on that tonight.
I'm gonna finish that bad boy.
You're gonna fucking K. Love butter. Well, I mean
There's a huge hole in the peanut butter, yeah, I mean I've obviously already fucked it but like, you know, come on
Yeah, you just gotta fuck the peanut butter. Yeah when you see it
It happens. Hey Ben, dude, you look good. Thanks, man. I've been up in
I've been pretty shitty. I mean LA just sucks so bad. Yeah, it sounds terrible Neal
Yeah, as a man is Oh Neil is Neil is killing it
- Yeah, dude.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, man.
- I haven't, yeah, I haven't really,
I think it's mostly just 'cause I'm like,
if we didn't have this podcast,
I'd probably like, would just like,
you would come back to Boston and I'd be like--
- Patrick's shouting right now.
- What?
- I'm shouting?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Oh.
- He was just shouting so much.
- Well, if we didn't have this podcast,
I probably would like, not see you guys
for the entire duration of you guys being there,
and then you come back and then I catch up with you.
- Yeah, odd.
- I realize, being out here has made me realize
that I have no ability to maintain friendships.
I don't call anybody ever.
- Me neither.
- It's so stupid.
- I text Neil out of the blue,
and then we'll say something,
and then I'll get distracted by something else,
and then I won't respond to him.
And then I'll just send him another text two weeks later.
- I feel like you and I have a good thing going.
I'll text you every once in a while.
- Right, yeah. - If something happens.
- Right. - I'll hit you up.
- Yeah, or we're going to the same thing.
- I'll pretend to be friends with Anjan.
(laughing)
- Patreon, baby.
- I'm just trying to talk to Caleb and Theo.
- That's true, yeah, yeah, in our group chat.
- Yeah. - Yeah, about Sam Hyde.
- Sam Hyde.
We did have that conversation about Sam Hyde recently.
- Yeah, that's for the Patreon only.
- Yeah. - The Sam Hyde.
Unlock the Sam Hyde conversation and see me and Tom's opinions.
I'm not telling.
Yeah, I'm not telling.
I'm not telling who's pro, who's against.
Yeah.
Both pro.
(laughing)
Both pro. Shut up.
Like violently pro.
Yeah, weirdly pro.
It's so funny how like many of--
Yeah, we use the word genius too much.
Yeah.
(laughing)
Hyper genius.
Tortured genius.
Yeah.
It's so funny how many of like Sam Hyde's fans,
like you fucking, when you tweeted that thing
that was like something about like inherent racism
and like, oh, you can't, yeah,
like no amount of class consciousness will ever like,
I don't remember what the fucking tweet was,
but then someone said some like diehard--
- Basically people from New England are racist.
- Yeah, yeah, that's the gist of it.
And then some like diehard Sam Hyde fan was like,
oh yeah, big words make you smart.
And it's like-- - Fucking owned.
- For like, for a group of people who were like, oh--
- A grown man whose Twitter account is called Brain Getter.
- Right, yeah.
(laughing)
- We were like, we were engaging.
For a group of people who were like,
"Oh, you just don't get Sam Hyde," or whatever,
it was like, "Oh, well you don't get other things,
"'cause you're so deeply involved into this one guy."
- I mean, the TED Talk ruled.
- Oh, no, I'm not saying--
- Did you show up to a TED Talk lying your way into it
and just planting for the first 10 minutes?
- He was like, "Other stuff is bad."
I'm not saying I'm not one of those people who's like--
- As Patrick says as he crosses his legs with a pink sock.
this is the this is the this is a media criticism Patrick using a bubble pipe I
will say I will say Patrick asked if it was okay if he hit his jewel and my
friends I'm very polite whoa that is polite I am very okay if I hit this and
like yeah Pat it's fine you've changed Pat Pat used to come over and sit on my
bed and fart for an hour while we recorded the podcast that's true yeah
- Yeah, 'cause I would go to McDonald's or the Middle East.
- Yeah, and just get loaded up.
- Dude, I run by the Middle East
like probably like three times a week
and I think about you every time.
- That's a long run.
- I went to Veggie Galaxy with Dom the other day
and fucking just walking past 35, I was like, ah.
- It's like, fuck.
- Old times.
- My boy.
- My UCB teacher, he used to live in 35.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Wait, so what are you doing at the UCB?
Are you taking classes there?
No, I'm taking a class through college that is a UCB class, but at the UCB I am a...
I gotta stop telling people this. I know.
It's the most embarrassing thing. It's just for another month. Nobody can get me...
Patreon challenge, get me fired from the UCB in the next month. It won't be that hard.
How do you get fired from taking a class? I know.
No, no, no, no, no. So I work front desk at the UCB.
Okay.
Yeah.
So you let Aaron Glazer in.
Yes, exactly.
I put a stamp on his hand.
Tap him off and you're like, "Hey, what's up, homie?"
Yeah.
What's up, dog?
You're my best friend.
You're my best friend here.
Hey, hey.
I don't believe a word they say.
You just tap him off.
Look, I haven't heard anything about it, but you seem like a good guy.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Cool.
Yeah, he's funny.
Yeah.
He does his thing.
He was great in Wolf of Wall Street, baby.
He was in Wolf of Wall Street?
Yeah, he was really good.
Damn.
He played Jonah Hill. No, he played the other guy. He played Jonah Hill's brother. He played Leonardo DiCaprio
Yeah, he played Leo. He played the other guys one time
Do this but like I was with my friends who were all taking acid. I've never done acid
It's fun too much of a coward
Caleb and I did acid and then we watched Wolf of Wall Street and
Then they just like as we finished I was like babysitting. Yeah, like as we finished there's like let's play it again
again. And then finished again, they're like, one more time.
We watched nine hours of Wolf of Wall Street.
Three and a half hour long movie.
God damn. Jesus Christ.
That's the whole fucking trip pretty much.
I went from hammered to like drunk to hungover over the course of the movie.
When me and Pat did Abso together, we just watched Awesome Powers.
and you know what really you hit Neil in the head with a shovel no no that was a
different time Neil got really Neil got really bad vibes from Austin Powers
no Toy Story it's Toy Story 2 oh is that what he got yeah it was so easy but it
was the scene where I feel bad talking about this it's not the Woody getting
fixed scene it's like the two scenes before that where it's like what he has
that like dream where he's like oh and he's gonna throw me away and then like I
I understand where Neil's coming from here.
Oh, that is a scary part of that movie, yeah.
Yeah, that is a very scary part of that movie.
That's a great movie, though.
Yeah.
Played by Wayne Knight.
And then we walked, and then we did a, we took a long walk to a, just a part of, it was like around a lake, it was where we were staying.
Dude, I wore fucking, I wore a pair of like, chucks.
And I walked through.
- Hell yeah.
- I walked through like two inch deep like snow.
Not even like, no that wasn't two inches,
I'm fucking bad at math.
- Yeah, it was more than that.
- Yeah, it was like, it was at least a foot of snow
that I walked through in caves
and I didn't feel anything. - Just so wet.
- Yeah, it was fun.
I wanna do it again next time I'm back.
- Yeah. - Or when I'm back.
I guess I am moving back, I keep forgetting that.
- Yeah. - It's gonna be weird.
I think I'm gonna be working at a children's museum.
- Really?
The children's museum?
- The one on the water?
- I don't know.
- Did I love that name? - It's just a name of science.
- Did your girlfriend get you that job?
- I fucking wish.
No, it was, I think Gus.
I think Gus is, Gus told me his mom runs some--
- Gus was on camera the other night.
- Yeah, I saw that. - It was cool.
He was super pumped.
- Yeah, he really did enjoy that.
- Yeah, he wore that shirt for quite a while.
- Like a whole week?
- Oh wow, that's a bad look.
You know, it was cool. It was cool.
As much as I wanted to make fun of him for it, it was like, yeah, you have it.
You're the first person I know with a TV credit.
And then when we were planning the tour
and like sending bios to people,
he put like, "Featured on Jimmy Kimmel Live."
I mean, he's not wrong.
No, it's technically true. He just got molested by Ray Romano on stage.
Yeah, I guess they-- Get over here.
Get over here, Gus. Get over here, Gus. I'm gonna touch you.
You're not my fucking son. You're not my son Gus. Yeah, that was it. They should not have played. I love you though. I
Love you more than my own son Gus get over here. You feel better than my son. Raymond Raymond. That's not your son
Hey you do a good that guy yeah, I know that guy rocks man. I had no idea remember he had those seven up commercials
Yeah, where it's like Brad you're a grump dress seven up
They're just like people that you see in show business and you're just like how do you have a career right look how yeah?
Yeah, like you yeah, exactly dang looking why don't you?
God damn, I'm good. I'm on fire tonight the sour beer is hitting my pineal gland in such a way that is making me sour
Listen, I'm here. I'm doing your podcast
it I
Appreciate it actually Patrick is there that's you you're at home
right now yeah I honestly when I turned back into that dorm after I'd left
Patrick there with my med students friends for like probably about a solid
20 minutes yeah like I'm nervous I don't know what I left do you think Patrick is
a wild card right I mean yeah what the fuck do you think no no in that context
absolutely because yeah really yeah it's a very hypersensitive thing dude I'm
literally like the least I fucking hate medical students I'm the least fucking
worried worrier person yeah you were just what have you had come back and
they were doing gastric bypass surgery
gonna happen. They're just pinning him against the wall. It's like, "You need it!"
"I'm not that big!" "But you will be!" Patrick just hitting his jewel on there too.
My guts are out. People are just so rude. It sucks. There was this kid, I was walking
across, I was trying to cross Mass Ave a couple days ago and I saw this kid who I go to school
with this like other like med student with his girlfriend he was holding her
hand and we were crossing in the crosswalk and I was like hey man like
what's up like it was so excited like excitedly being like hey how's it going
man it's like it was like outside of school and then he was just like I had
sunglasses on and I guess I was like a partly cloudy day he just goes
sunglasses really well and then him and his girlfriend just start cackling at me
And I was so humiliated so that is a white microaggression
One of a white man for having sunglasses on on a cloudy day, that's our culture, buddy
And I was in the middle of a fucking intersection. I could I had no response. I just I
Just ran out
I was I was weeping I was weeping damn damn cold. So that's so that's why you've been so depressed
Yeah, yeah, it's because a guy said, the guy acknowledged you had sunglasses on.
A guy and his girlfriend made fun of me.
God, dude, medical school sounds tough, man.
It sucks that in three years you're going to be a millionaire.
God, what a nightmare.
Yeah, and Caleb and I are going to be interns at like fucking, some shit.
I can't wait to cut you open for whatever surgery you need.
And then like, we get into your guts and it's just like, "Oh, I'm going to have to cut you
and he's just like, "Oh my God, he's had seven 7-Eleven hot dogs
the past 48 hours."
We specifically asked him not to eat.
I get bottom surgery just to get a new asshole.
You get another stomach where your penis would be.
You remove your penis to make room for another stomach.
Yeah, my girlfriend really doesn't like it, but uh...
I've been just pounding on it.
My body, my choice.
Patrick asked for his stomach lining to be replaced with Teflon.
(laughing)
- Yeah, he has to be replaced.
He has to be replaced with fruit roll-ups.
(laughing)
Stitch together fruit roll-up.
- Hell yeah.
- The only thing that can withstand
all the fruit roll-ups that you eat.
(laughing)
- In six years, I mean.
- I already tweeted this, but.
- Yeah, tweet it, talk about it.
- Yeah, I was at work, I had to leave the,
It was really busy, we had like four lunch rushes today.
It was fucked.
And we were like so busy.
- Patrick has pink socks on,
I can't take him seriously.
- But we,
I left the register to go in the back
'cause I was laughing.
'Cause there was like this,
there's just like this dude,
like this type of dude that comes in,
he doesn't take his AirPods out.
Like there was a dude I had the other day
He was on a very important business call
and his car, the internet shut down
so all the pin pads weren't working.
And I was trying to take his order to just get him a coffee.
And he was like, hold on, I need to call you back.
What's going on?
And I was just imagining just a guy
with that same attitude just walking up
to the register stand and just being like,
yeah, let me get a fruit roll-up.
- Fine, fruit by the foot, whatever.
- Whatever. - You don't have,
oh hold on, let me call you back.
And he just takes out like the one AirPod
and he's like, oh, you don't have,
what do you got, Gushers?
(laughing)
You got Gushers or something?
You got like fruit leather?
- Just like a Starbucks or wherever.
- Yeah, well, oh, this is an organic place.
You guys got fruit leathers, you got fuckin'.
(laughing)
You got the apricot fruit leathers from Whole Foods.
- Shit's nasty. - One's on the counter
for 79 cents.
- I don't want that bullshit, man.
- So does your brother know the person
whose titties are on that photo,
or like what is that?
Is that like-- - That's actually his brother.
- Is this the first time you've seen a naked woman, Tom?
You seem obsessed.
- Honestly, it might be.
- First time in a while, I'm guessing.
- First time in a while, dude.
- I gotta tell you, this is a drawing.
- Someone drew that?
Pull that off the wall, bring that closer, baby.
- Yeah, bring it here. - Okay, hold on.
- Yeah, bring that shit over here.
- Describe the image. - Come on, come on, come on.
- He's got the headphones out,
he can't hear us talking shit.
- Caleb, he looks so handsome.
I'm gonna talk shit, he's so beautiful.
- He looks like normal.
- Listen, I love Caleb a lot, and I miss him.
- Caleb looks normal.
- Well, no, okay.
- Okay. - That's a drawing?
Oof, my run.
- You didn't even say that Italian word right.
- I mean, goddamn, dude.
- Who's the, show me, yeah, show me the,
I wanna analyze the-- - Nice.
- Let's see if we can get an angle where her vagina--
- Who's that artist?
Who's that artist?
- Says 19-- - Alberto Vargas.
- Alberto Vargas.
- Alberto Vargas, 1928.
He drew that in 1928.
That's all they had, dude.
- Yeah.
- Wow.
- Damn.
- Imagine if you had to draw your own porn.
I would suck.
- People do that still.
People have to draw their own porn still.
Like furries and shit.
- Furries?
- Furries are like people who are really into Overwatch.
- Yeah.
- Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I know one of them.
Yeah.
- You know one of them?
- Dwo.
- Yeah, what do you mean?
- Who?
- Well, I would refer to her as those people.
- Her?
- But--
- Damn, okay.
girl who jacks off to overwatch porn absolutely she's definitely subscribe to
our patreon she's hearing this right now absolutely respect how you doing Alex I
guess it's been like a thing cuz like they just released new skins for the
game and like people are like they released new skin yeah awesome it's so
funny talking to Tom about video games.
Because he's so clueless.
I played Call of Duty.
I played Red Dead.
I feel like Tom stopped playing video games.
Tom, you're not a true gamer.
You're not a gamer, Tom.
I played Red Dead.
Red Dead 2?
I have a PS4, dude.
I feel like,
it's just like the skins,
they're making new skins for Overwatch,
but then there's one that they released that's very similar
to an Overwatch porn video.
And I didn't understand it.
I had to read all the replies in the thread.
- Interesting, interesting.
- And they didn't even link to the video.
- Yeah, did you have to go find the video?
- I didn't find it.
- I mean, I can find it for you.
I promise you I can find it.
Yeah, I mean, yeah.
- The weirdest part about that is probably like
how many of them are just like,
oh, I would like to see Mercy, the medic,
with a just a gigantic penis
with the uh... was that it was mercy woman yet just like
uh... have you ever a huge b_n_a_'s there there in the ads
i mean yeah i've obviously dabbled in the uh... cartoons in the dark arts
parker
the truck
just referred to click
simpsons for a half-part the dark arts
drawing more simpsons
Eiffel Tower Bush.
Marge Simpson with just a 12 foot penis.
Yeah, yeah, I've obviously like, you know, sometimes, you know, things are getting desperate,
you aren't getting there, you just gotta, you gotta, you gotta push on.
Sometimes there's no more human porn to watch.
Exactly.
Once you've, once you've run through it all.
There have been, truly been some times where I'm like, I've seen every video that I'm going
over and it's, it's disgusting.
And you go, and then, and then what's your next move after that?
Well, I just hit up grinder
People see what happens just try it out, you know, yeah, you know, yeah. Yeah, not even
I'm just messaging just to feel something. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I'm just
Jacked off - I jacked off - the song shallow the other night, which one?
The Lady Gaga bro. No, it's only I was thinking of my bloody Valentine. No, I jacked off
That's a song you edge to.
No, no, no.
You edge to My Bloody Valentine.
Yeah.
You come to Rihanna's S&M.
No, no you don't.
Yeah, yeah you do.
You come to Shallow by Bradley Cooper.
It's so funny that that song is just like played
in like Roach Brothers now.
Well no, so what you do is you come to Shallow
by Bradley Cooper and Lady Gaga.
At the part where it's like,
♪ I'm off the deep end ♪
Yeah, you come right there and then the post-cum song
is the I'll Never Love Again,
after Bradley Cooper's already killed himself.
Okay, yeah, whoa I haven't seen that movie so thanks for the spoiler Tom. It's been remade four times
Yeah, I only anytime I listen to even flow. I'm jacking off. Yeah, yeah, try the jacks off to Jeremy. It's weird. Yeah
Even concrete pillow is what I call when I come in my pillow sheets and let it dry
You really made a concrete
Yeah
Concrete yeah, that's about me fucking
Where are you gonna live when you come back? Yeah
Can you give out your address? Yeah, let's hear it. I'm gonna be living in Brighton. Oh
Word boo. I can just fucking go down the street and hang out. Yeah, man
It's like a 10 or 15 minute walk to your place. Yeah, it's not even right by Cityside
Yeah, oh, yeah, very close to Cityside. I miss Cityside man. They've they've been doing really good shows
I like Cityside and hideout. They got Peppetown the other day. Yeah, they did which is like salute that got Pepe the frog
- They got Pepe the Frog.
- They got Pepe the Frog to come headline.
- They did get Pepe the Frog.
- They got Pepe the Frog to headline a hideout.
It's crazy.
- That's nuts.
- Shout out to--
(laughing)
- She has her--
- Shout out to King.
I keep DMing him and I'm just like,
damn man, you gotta lose weight, but I love you.
- I've never met, I have not met anyone in Boston comedy
that hasn't done mooyahs.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Pretty awesome.
- I don't, I don't go to Mike's.
- No, we talked to Janet though at that show that we did.
- Oh yeah, she, yeah.
J.M. Actionary?
I mean she's probably going to win Boston Comedy Festival.
Oh, she's so funny dude.
She rocks.
Yeah.
She literally walks, she's kind of an asshole, but she's just rules.
It's like she's an asshole in the best way.
Yeah, she went up on a whole thing about how she doesn't tip at like restaurants at the,
like the restaurant that I work at.
Honestly, she's like, just like one of the wilder people I've ever talked to and I loved
it.
It's just because she's an asshole.
You know she was on American Idol?
Yeah.
- She rolled up to this show and we were standing outside
the fashion show or whatever, there's a fucking--
- Oh yeah, I was--
- Big window and she was--
- Was that before or after we were sharing the 40?
- That was before.
I think you were literally on stage,
or about to go on stage.
I rolled up and she was like--
- I was drinking, I drank two White Claw Tallboys
before I went up and then I just did the worst set
I've ever done.
- Nice, dude.
- Honestly--
- I did fairly well, they have a video of it
and I'm gonna tell them not to post it.
I mean I thought yeah, yeah Tom immediately crushed
He's a comic
Yeah, Janet walked up and like someone outside was just like is this a good show and she's like absolutely not
I'm the only person on here with the TV credit
For American Idol, yeah for being like ironic on American, that's awesome
Yeah, probably when Boston Comedy Festival, it's gonna win American Idol. She's she's going back for a redemption episode
She's doing she's doing a web redemption. I love it
You watch that American Idol episode and she's like, yeah, I was on American Idol and it's like, oh, yeah
You're on American Idol in 1999
I'm gonna make my wife do a web redemption for the video that I have of her fucking the milkman
That's gonna cost you a web redemption for giving birth to your first son. Yeah. Yeah
- I love it. - I mean, I'm gonna
videotape your wife giving birth to your first son.
- Thanks, buddy.
You will be there.
Well, you'll be the doctor who delivers the baby.
(laughing)
There's pretty good odds.
- Just, I bring my medical degree
into whatever operating room here.
It's just like, free.
- I'm supposed to be here.
What is the, what kind of doctor are you becoming?
- I don't know.
I honestly don't know.
I have to decide that at some point.
- You're like a free-range doctor?
- Yeah, I don't know.
Honestly, we'll figure it out.
- If you're a free agent, you can just pick one.
- You do your first couple years and then you decide.
- Look, I'm not trying to become a specialist.
I'm just trying to learn the basics of everything.
And then just kind of like, it's like,
oh, you need an OBGYN, I'm right here.
- I'm not gonna be an OBGYN.
- Be the master of none.
- Dude, honestly.
- Tom wants to be an OBGYN.
- It's so weird.
- Something just fell off of your head, Tom.
- There are dudes that roll in and they're just like--
- Tom wants to be the first male OBGYN.
- Thank you, I mean, dudes in school who are just gung-ho
on OB-GYN, just red flag.
- Yeah.
- I don't--
- Yeah, I would say the most obvious red flag
in the world, maybe.
- In the world, dude, it's so uncomfortable.
- It's like, you remember Good Luck Chuck?
- Yeah, that's literally--
- Yeah.
- It's like the guy who's like,
"Oh, I'm a breast augmentation doctor."
- Yeah.
- It's the guy from Fantastic Beasts.
- Yeah, it's literally Dane Cook.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, those are those guys.
- Dane Cook and his best friend.
- His brother who stole all that money from him.
Yeah, and made him and then made him date that 17 year old.
If you want the money back you have to fuck a 14 year old.
Dude, my bloated face King.
Can you imagine having sex with Dane Cook?
It'd be so tiring.
Jesus.
I'm over here now.
Yeah.
Get over here.
Yeah, he's very screaming into your ass.
I mean, he just literally had one good bit about like being nice to
someone who might shoot up an office.
- Yeah.
- He had good--
- I really liked his bit as a kid about people,
about the drive-thru.
- Oh, that was good.
- BK Lounge?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- That's like one of the first things
I downloaded on LimeWire.
- Yeah, man.
- I was a big Dane Cook guy back in the day.
- Oh, yeah, when I was nine?
- Yeah, when I was like a child.
- I was big into Dane Cook and Carlos Mencia.
- Oh, dude.
- It's probably, it's because like--
- Because you're a thief.
- Yeah.
No, it's 'cause just like, they were on TV,
So I was like, these are the coolest guys.
- Yeah, and then Gabriel Iglesias was another big,
I was big into Gabriel Iglesias,
into Fluffy when I was a kid.
- Yeah.
- Remember how they had Carlos Mencia
on the first two episodes of "Bernie Mac"
and then they took him out like immediately?
- Yeah, they did, yeah, yeah.
- Yeah.
- Damn dude, "Bernie Mac" RIP, what a king.
- I have such a distinct memory of watching "Bernie Mac's"
is like that Apollo set where he does the dance.
Yeah.
- Yes.
- That, because it was on Comedy Central,
like they would just play like 90s standup,
just all day, every day on Comedy Central.
- Yeah, I heard of it. - In like 2005.
- I saw a big Jay Oakerson thing at 4 a.m.
when I was like 12.
- Nice, and you were like, I wanna look like that guy.
- I wanna look exactly like him.
- Just honestly, being 12 years old
and being up at 4 a.m., like what?
- Yeah, yeah, what was your life like?
- I was gaming.
- True. - I was gaming, yeah.
- What were you gaming?
- I got really big into Gmod and TF2.
- Oh my God. - Did you guys play RuneScape?
- Yeah, of course I played RuneScape.
Come on, dude. - I didn't play RuneScape.
- I had a level 102 main.
- Dude, I fucking love RuneScape.
- I had 98 wood cutting.
- I didn't get into it, I didn't get it.
- So I have a funny story about RuneScape.
Before I got into it, my neighbor,
who was a couple years older than me,
like introduced me to it.
And he like, he waited for me to get like a couple months in.
I like built up my like stockpile and shit.
And I was like gaining stuff.
And he was like, yo, come with me.
We gotta go on this quest.
And he like took me out to that part of the woods
where you could just assault people
and steal all their shit.
- The wilderness.
- Yeah, he took me out into the wilderness
and he was like, yo dude,
there's like a fucking dragon out here.
We're gonna get all this money.
And he took me out there and just beat the shit out of me
and stole me and robbed me for everything.
- Damn.
- And I saw him the next day at the bus stop
And he was like, "Welcome to the real world, asshole."
(laughing)
I was like crying.
I was like, "Why would you rob me, Tyler?"
- I had an account and played for a long time,
and then when I was like 13, I just decided,
I was like, "You know what, I'm done playing this game.
"I've put enough time into this."
And then I gave my account to some neighborhood kid.
And then like a year later, I was like,
"You know what, I kinda wanna start playing RuneScape again."
And then just logged in and changed the password
so he couldn't get back on it.
Just stole the account back.
Yeah, and then just like for quite a while
would message his friends and be like,
"Hey man, I'm gonna kill myself."
(laughing)
And they thought it was still him.
- Caleb, you were truly a monster.
- I know, I know.
- Caleb child story is like some insane shit.
- I love your story about you and your brothers
where it's just like, yeah, if we had a younger brother,
we'd just kick the shit out of him
and like make him wanna die.
- Yeah.
- That's pretty much how it went, yeah.
- That's my older brother.
- Here, you bullied your older brother?
- Yeah, me and Eric bullied Paul.
- Damn.
- We like, so Paul and I had to share a room,
and then one day we just got into a small fight,
and then he left, I think he had football practice,
and Eric and I just moved all of his stuff upstairs,
and just didn't tell him.
like had to come home.
He kept all, he stole a shopping cart from Walmart
and then kept all of his clothes in a shopping cart.
So Eric and I had to carry the shopping cart
from the basement to the upstairs like part of the house.
- Just like imagine someone's sharing blood with Patrick
who played football in high school.
- Right, yeah.
- It's wonderful.
- They both did. - Patrick is a,
- They both played football. - Patrick's a skater.
- That's an athletic, he's an athlete.
- Honestly, Patrick, you should leave
before the trains close.
- Oh yeah, what time is it?
- It's 11.40.
- Oh no.
- Yeah, I might be late.
- Yeah, goddamn, what are we at?
- We're at an hour, that's fine.
- Oh, cool.
- Okay, we're at hell, yeah.
Honestly, Caleb, I miss you so much.
- Yeah, I miss you too, buddy.
- And every day without you here is a nightmare.
- I'll be back in a month.
- I'm so happy to see you.
You look thin, you look handsome.
- Thank you, you as well.
- Yeah, you should look into hair plugs before you come back.
(laughing)
- Thanks, thanks.
Thanks.
Yeah, I will.
You look healthy though.
You should look into SSRIs maybe.
(laughing)
Honestly, salute dude.
Couldn't be me.
All right.
Follow Tom on Twitter at--
Doer, D-O-E-R-I-F-I-T.
That is not how you spell it.
You already fucked it up.
Doer of it.
Yeah.
It looks like Doryo fit.
Which would be a cooler way to read it.
Yeah.
Caleb, I love you.
Love you too, buddy.
Yeah.