You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
You're a monster.
(explosion)
Let's fucking go.
Woo!
Let's go.
Oh my God, he's drinking a Ray in the can.
Oh my God.
What's up Thomas, how we doing buddy?
Pretty good, how are you guys?
Not bad.
I'm good man, I always am shocked by your eyebrows
when I see you.
They're awesome dude.
I mean, it's insane.
- As somebody, as someone who also has gigantic eyebrows.
- No, I think you have gigantic eyebrows until I see Tom.
- Yeah, no, compared to yours, mine are just terrible.
- You don't fill those in at all?
- Me?
- No, no, I've trimmed them back some,
but I can't really stop them from--
- You can't contain them.
- Yeah, I kind of gave up a couple years ago,
'cause I used to just shave this middle part.
- Do you have a, you got a uni?
- I've got a slight one on there.
I thought your forehead cast a shadow. I thought it was like offset an inch.
My nephew's head does that. Was he like just born? Did he have a weird
vagina? Otis.
Yeah, my nephew's name is Otis. Why are you saying your nephew's name on the
show? Yeah, we'll bleep it out.
He's gonna
Head looks like that
That you were asking about
Did you just get distracted in the middle of in the middle of talking about yeah your cousin with the weird head
It's not my cousin. It's my nephew cousin nephews or a cousin. He doesn't have a weird head. He just he looks normal
It's just his forehead.
If his forehead comes out an inch off his fucking head.
It doesn't come out an inch.
Yeah, dude, it just has...
That's what you just said!
No, it looks like his...
I don't know, it looks like he has a unibrow sometimes.
No, dude, he just has a pterodactyl beak and the horn thing on the back of his head, but
it's like normal.
It just looks like that, alright?
It's cuz he's Irish.
It's cuz his name.
Oh.
But yeah, we're here with young Thomas.
He's looking good.
He's got the eyebrows.
He clearly just got his beard trimmed.
Do you trim your own beard or do you have a guy do it?
I shaved my beard off like four or five days ago.
And it just grows in like that?
Yeah.
That's like a perfect black guy beard.
Yeah, it doesn't like fill in in the cheeks at all.
It's just a chin strip.
I thought that was a style that you were choosing.
Whoa, yeah, that looks very, very clean.
It's incredible, dude.
Every piece of hair on your face is perfect.
I'm gonna take your hair.
Sven is also pointing out different things about Thomas' appearance.
Yeah, over on an audio show.
Yeah, we're gonna do this for an hour.
No one can see.
This is, uh, this entire episode is gonna be me just, like, slowly trying to convince him to, like, donate follicles to me.
Yeah.
For a transplant.
I would love to get just, like, my shitty...
I could give you some of mine.
My shitty, wiry, Italian hair in the back, and then right where I'm going bald, just like Thomas's eyebrows just stacked on top of each other like an equal sign.
That would look good, dude.
Yeah.
So, what's life like in Texas right now?
It's... I mean, it's not too bad. Like, it's hot everywhere else, but it's not like hotter than usual here, you know?
Yeah, I meant the weather. That's what I meant.
Yeah.
Yeah, I was getting to the weather, yeah. So it's hot there.
Cool. Yeah.
Nothing else going on. It's just nice and...
Yeah, so there's cowboys.
Is that Texas heat?
Yeah.
Yeah, what is it like having to... You already... COVID is one thing, but having to battle Indians
every day, does that get annoying?
Yeah.
Which side did you take in the cowboy Indian war?
I would love to be an Indian and just wear paint all over myself. I assume they still
do that.
Yeah.
You should try to rub your eyebrows off thinking they were face paint.
Bone Tomahawk was based off the life of Thomas.
It was originally called Bone Thomas Hawk, but they had to change the name because it
was going to suit him.
That's his Indian name.
It was a very different movie.
It was called Bone Thomas.
Bone Thomas.
Yeah.
It was a completely different movie and then they rewrote the script to make it not a porno.
They still had the scene where the guy holds the guy by his legs upside down and pulls
them apart but it ended a completely different way.
The original version.
Thomas, has anyone asked you to do porn yet?
Uh, no.
Have people asked you, Caleb?
You mean considering the proposition?
People have asked me to do...
Yeah, yeah.
People have asked me to do OnlyFans quite a lot, actually.
Well, that, yeah, but...
I consider that porn.
On 50.
Yeah, I guess.
That's what I think porn is.
Yeah, my problem with that is that I only have a gaming chair in my room, so like, in terms
of poses and stuff like that, like I...
You're relegated to sitting in a chair as you pose.
I'm not doing that standing up, I mean, come on now.
Nah, it's about, you gotta work the angles.
You want me to exercise for a living now?
Geez.
Yeah, I feel like you could make a good chunk of change on OnlyFans, but you, the thing is
you give away too much on the on the Twitter you give away too much you have
to be shirtless photos already yeah people got that free I've got the whole
other in though to work with I guess I guess that's the only thing I could get
offer really Michael Rappaport could start a and only fans with that
penis I've been I still got it saved absolutely it sits on his fucking
ceiling it's the first thing he sees when he wakes up yeah he looks at it every
morning he's got a dartboard in his garage that just has he has that right
now throw darts he's in his bathroom battle rapping that photo right now he
prayed out Thomas's penis you suck and then you can't rhyme you look like a
fucking idiot what the fuck is wrong with you he's got the shook ones
instrumental going in his garage at all times you can just go in there and just
start whenever he feels like it. Yeah, basically this is my freestyle room.
I have Shook Ones. I have a freestyle room. DJ Premier is here at all times.
I hired him from my the money I got off a Bill Simmons podcast appearance
and he just plays Shook Ones non-stop and I battle rap Thomas's penis.
He printed out like 20 copies of the of the penis photo and put him in
envelopes and was like giving to his family and was like if I
ever die you mail this to all the media but he didn't realize the envelopes were
the ones with those windows over it like the bill in the club so he's given his
mom
yeah dude he definitely has it he has a you know that only that on it yeah for
when you finally kill him yeah yeah have you guys had any other interactions since
done? Um, no, but I didn't really fully detail the interactions at the time just
because... We meant to have you on that week, but we had Felix on. I think I asked you. I
don't remember. My internet ended up crashing that afternoon and then I sort
of found some other stuff out. Dude, you got DDoS'd by Rampaport. But he had like a burner account on
Instagram. Oh my god. It was clearly, it was like some college girl in a bikini and she
kept replying to like all my posts like Rappaport has your photo and he's gonna
send it to them I was like it's clearly it's clearly you I mean yo Rappaport has
your photo homie yeah oh no Ashley from University of Oklahoma is gonna get me
I'm pretty worried about that god damn dude that fucking rocks you just sent it
to him kind of because he was being mean to Emma, right?
Emily, yeah.
Well, I introduced it like I had dirt on her.
That's how I got her to talk.
I didn't realize that's how you got it.
Yeah.
So I said I used to, I told him that I used to work at a restaurant with her and he was
like, "Okay, I'm listening."
And I was like
I was like well, I mean she was
You're gonna you're gonna be glad to hear this
I just kept leading him on and then I was just sitting in my bed and I mean it's hard to you know
Explain over audio, but I send it and I was like well cuz before I send it
I was like, I just have one question so that I can trust you and he was like, what is it?
And I was like how far down your throat do you think you could fit this?
*laughter*
Dick pic?
We're not gonna reveal all the tricks and tricks
that's right here
(laughter)
Mom walks in on you jacking off
You're like, "No, you don't understand, I'm doing this for my grab report"
I'm trying to take a photo of my dick
The guy, the guy from the
War at Home, uh, he wants to
he, he, he's
asking you for a photo. No, Mom, I'm protecting my
friend online, okay?
You told me to stick up for my friends always
I'm getting famous I'm getting famous for you I'm dueling the producer of the a
tribe called quest documentary mom yeah when Michael Rappaport looks at this
photo and just instantly turns to ash I get his inheritance mom and I'm gonna
buy you the biggest house and the biggest car so who are you gonna sit are
you gonna send a penis picture to next which which which white guy who's on the
list. Yeah, what's on, who's on your hit list? I feel like you're plugging rain
every time you drink a sip of this. Rain? You mean the delicious energy drink that
leaves me not fatigued at all and just with a delicious rush? No, everybody knows
that about rain and bang. It's just a pure crisp high, no calm down at all.
Yeah. There's no, there's no like you sitting in your bedroom just kind of
looking at the ceiling. Yeah. Because you drank it on a day where you didn't work
out or anything and you never like you never vibrate free of the third
dimension and like see something that sees you back and just keeps following
you for the rest of your life just because you never there's a guy in your
house because you heard like the door in the apartment next to you unlock yeah
for me then the entire time I drink like a high energy or high like caffeine
content energy drink it's just me thinking I have to shit and then going
to the bathroom and then just like farting and pissing yeah oh no I'm
I'm actually it actually this actually raised my vibrational levels high enough that I can perceive the ghost that's fucking my ass right now
Yeah, it's doing it all the time
But the only time you can tell is when you have enough energy to notice it when you raise your raise your energy signature high
enough
What'd you guys do if you were ghost man?
I asked this earlier if you were if you were God would you go to the girls locker room and like take a peek?
Because also the thing is if you're God everything that you do is is fine. Yeah, you know
So it wouldn't even be morally wrong at that point
It'd be like looking at a sandwich you made
in the sandwich locker room
If your sandwiches were alive
Yeah, if you're beautiful pussies and big fat titties and they were barely 18
Would you go look at the sandwiches in the pantry?
It's just a question
It's a theological question.
Pat, you're so afraid of sex.
It's about Christ.
You're so afraid of sex.
That's why I had sex positive icon Thomas on.
We're trying to fix you, man.
You're too much of a Puritan, dude.
Thomas, your video where you were pretending like you were eating pussy was making me laugh
so hard.
So I pulled it, I was looking at it and I just couldn't stop laughing.
Do you have any tips, man?
You really don't want to think about it too much.
You just try and don't look her in the eyes or anything like that.
Yeah.
Because that's going to mess you up.
You just pretend it's like a Krabby Patty or something.
Like the little candy versions.
Like the gummy ones?
Yeah, the gummy ones.
You got to stay in the pocket.
Yeah.
Just know your place, you know.
Lose yourself.
Yeah.
And also use your nose to hit the clay.
I try and make it good for either one of you.
Just get it over with.
Yeah, it's basically, just set a timer.
You might as well just be sitting next to her.
It's just, there's 10 minutes,
there's 10 minutes before you can come
and you have to just do something.
It's like watching a movie, you know?
Yeah. Yeah.
What I like to do is I like to, with one hand,
I have like a two-handed technique.
With one hand, I do a little, you know,
a little top of the, top of the,
I do some clit action with my left hand.
With my right hand, I show her a video on my phone
to distract her from how bad I am at this.
You know?
- Yeah, look close. - I'm like, check this out.
Look, this kid puts a remote in his ass and screams
'cause he's so mad.
Isn't that funny?
- No, this is the part.
Look, look right here.
- Okay, your turn.
(laughing)
- Look, this is-- - That's the ultimate,
that's God's ultimate trick.
Eating pussy, always bad for both of you.
Having your dick sucked is never bad.
'Cause it's always kinda funny.
It's a trick of sound.
'Cause I was like, "I have my dick in a face right now.
"That's kinda funny."
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm basically a master of sex.
Yeah, I'm always imagining that my dick is a microphone
and that the girl is doing a stand-up show.
And the girl is Howard Stern.
Yeah.
And I'm Robin.
And I'm the audio engineer.
Goddamn, I wish Howard Stern would suck me off.
Yeah, I got some private parts for you
to put in your mouth Howard. How's that? Did you see his dick in that movie? I don't
think you do. No? Kind of false advertising. Yeah kind of a misleading. I'm suing
I'm suing Howard Stern for false advertising. I'm suing the the Empire State
Building for covering his penis on the cover of private parts. Not enough private
parts in that movie. Yeah I agree. Thomas are you a you a Stern guy or an
opiate
like to pretend a forty years old
and i've heard either of those
nice to listen up in any
i never
and i never did be an anthony i would always
i was so does the list of the opiate
it opiates
now there's a note there's a rose emoji display name right there
now that's that's a pretty funny
opiate opiate opiate anthony
yeah c_n_n_
k_c_ anything and i think now we're getting somewhere
never tell you never tell you guys
and i don't know if i've talked about on the pod but uh... there's like a house
show
for uh...
did i awesome
there's a show like a great next story
there's a house shows like a fundraiser for that's that show cameron and i were
on at emerson
promoting rain again
Well I got too fucked up that night and I grabbed the microphone from the band and I said, "Casey
Anthony's innocent!"
And uh, yeah.
Nice.
That's a wild story.
Was there like a reaction to it?
I don't remember the rest of it.
Yeah, no, a lot of people were very mad.
Like a lot of like the kids, like the house show kids did not like me after that.
Yeah.
"Now she's locked!"
that that list that was that's been going around of all those DIY bands but then
Patrick's name is on there and it just says thanks Casey Anthony is innocent
something I think I said Casey Anthony innocent free the Menendez brothers
something I love about every Patrick story is that it follows the Joseph
Campbell like myth outline yeah pattern you know where it's like a hero's
journey you know there's a clear beginning middle and end yeah there's a
there's a climax, it ends on a strong note.
- Yeah.
Well yeah, you gotta--
- Some guy always appreciates you as a storyteller.
- It's like that book--
- You should go on The Moth and tell stories.
(laughing)
- What's The Moth?
- Moth is like this show, it's like a storytelling show
where everybody talks about their dead daughter,
or the one video I saw.
And it would just be you going up and you'd be like,
man, my brother has a bike and--
(laughing)
He actually fell on it twice.
Yeah, and then I said what the hell are you doing? And then you be like, sorry man. I had I had six bud bud heavies
Which is exactly how you do stand up yeah
I'm so sorry guys. Oh my god. I'm so sorry. I'm
Apologize when I do stand up you apologize after you record a podcast episode or a stream
Then where you get drunk or in the middle? Yeah, you'll be like, oh my god. I'm so sorry guys. I have a headache
I had half an Advil four days ago, and it's just like really messed up my brain. Yeah
Yeah, I tried to eat before 1 p.m.. And it really fucked me up
And now the only thing I can think about is which video game cartridges I played when I was 9 years old sorry guys
Yeah, I
Never I bet if you start eating breakfast
It'll like restore your memory, and you'll have some you'll be able to like add ends to your stories and stuff
Maybe I don't Patrick eats breakfast once gets a perfectly square
Today I did breakfast sandwich was on it. Yeah, let's hear it lunch food. I bet it was a spaghetti breakfast
It was just egg and beyond sausage sandwich. I'm eating so yeah
Dude, that's why that's why everything's fucked up in your head. Yeah, so that's so it's why you went twisted
Well, I counter I counterbalanced it by eating a bunch of peppered beef jerky. So
Wow, yin and yang dude.
Yeah.
Incredible.
What's your diet been like Thomas?
Yeah, what have you been eating?
Well, I just got a George Foreman grill.
Oh, I saw that tilapia you grilled.
That's huge.
Did you guys ever...
Hey Cameron, you want to steal my next story too?
Yeah, dude, no, go ahead, start it.
Let's do it.
I've been just eating normal for the most part.
I thought I had coronavirus for like a week and then my test came back negative.
Nice.
That's a bummer, dude.
Yeah, dude, I'd already told like 200 people I had it.
You're already bragging.
Yeah.
You're already like, "Dude, that's the thing about that test.
You take the test because you only take it thinking you have it.
And then for the two days that you wait, you're just telling everybody like, "Yeah, I pretty
much have it and I'm fine and I'm surviving."
And then you're like in the middle of watching like eight hours of movies and then you get
the test back and it's like you don't even have this thing.
Yeah.
And you're like, "What have I been doing for two days?"
Yeah, man.
Near the beginning of all this, I was having like a ton of trouble breathing and it turned
out I just have trouble breathing.
I thought I had corona when we went to New York.
Yeah, I've been having erectile dysfunction and I think it's probably from the coronavirus.
Yeah, I'm gonna need you to stick one of those swabs up my pee hole though to test for it.
I think this is a new type.
Did you guys ever get into that growing up?
Exploring your body and putting pencil lead in your penis?
No.
No?
I can't say I did.
I read that Chuck Palahniuk story, Guts.
And he talks about putting pencil lead in his dick and jacking off with it.
And so I was like, you know what, I like to try, I'm an adventurer, I'm like Andrew Zimmer
from the Food Network show.
So I like-
You're an alcoholic?
So I like put, I tried putting pencil lead in the tip of my penis and it's like the worst
pain I ever felt.
Why would you put that pencil- I mean I got like a quarter of a centimeter in and I was
like that Chuck motherfucker's weird.
Yeah, that's one crazy phrase.
I just threw it away.
Actually no, I remember I put the pencil lead back in the pencil.
It was like a mechanical pencil.
Nice dude.
Yeah, I don't know if it ever saw the light of day.
What a crazy moment for me when I was a kid like getting sent to fight club and then I
I find out the guy who wrote Fight Club is gay puts a whole new spin on the whole book.
Yeah, it's like yeah, maybe they weren't fighting each other after all maybe that was a metaphor
Exactly. Yeah, no wonder he had Brad Pitt in the movie
It's a good. Yeah. No. Yeah, there's two guys are the main character. Oh my god, dude
It's it's like at the end. It's the exact same storyline, but at the end he puts the gun to his head
And it's a pink gun instead
Exactly, yeah
I'm trying to think. I used to, there was a period where I loved like all those like
those like gross out short stories growing up. Man I love Chuck Palahniuk
still. I'll go to bat for him. I think he's a really good writer.
I'll go to bat with you. My favorite gross out short story is Chuck Berry's
The transcript of Chuck Berry's sex tape. Chuck Berry's sex tape transcript.
Sec tape. Sec tape. Sec tape. Where he says you can smell my fart. Are you wise to this Thomas?
Have you seen that?
No, is it the same Chuck Berry who like filmed women in the bathroom?
Yeah.
And sang rock and roll?
Yeah, I was listening to rock and roll.
The Chuck Berry sex tape, he farts in a girl's face and he says, "You're gonna smell my fart."
No, no, no, he doesn't fart in her face.
His penis is like an inch from her face and he's peeing on her.
And then he farts and he's like, "You like that, bitch?"
And she's like, "Yeah, I love that."
Because you can't just stop there, you're getting your face pissed on.
Like, it'd be crazy to draw the line.
Well, there's another...
I would leave the room.
I would say no.
I would say no, I don't like that.
You would get to that point, though.
You would get to the point where Chuck Berry's pissing on your face.
Of course I would, but I would say, if I didn't like it, I would say so.
But you gotta be honest.
You're not gonna do anything about it, but you are gonna be honest about the fact...
This man's saying my dingaling, so...
That's true, man.
You're gonna let him pee on you.
I can't wait to get to that point, dude.
What? To say where you sing my ding-a-ling?
Where I can fucking fart on a woman.
You can? Like, pretty much?
I can, no.
No, that's an expensive... that's either like the most expensive prostitute or the cheapest prostitute in the world. We'll let you do that.
No, you can just fart on a woman on the train and not...
Oh, I've done that, yeah.
I do remember one time, like, farting on the train and there was a guy... a guy was like...
Like I was standing and he was sitting down and he was eating a sandwich and I like basically
farted on his sandwich.
He loved it dude.
He was like, "There's something about this sandwich."
He smells it and it's amazing.
I think my sandwich just leveled up.
He had a subway sub and he's just standing there and then he smells it and then he just
like deep throats the whole sub.
Just immediately.
Just eats it like Scooby Doo.
Yeah man.
But uh, yeah I like having sex basically.
That's what I'm saying.
Even with Chuck Berry.
Couldn't be me.
Yeah.
Hey man.
You're too tough.
I'm too tough.
Couldn't be me.
Show that kind of vulnerability.
You're like Ryan Gosling from Drive.
Yeah.
Dude I wish.
Autistic.
Did you know that song.
Completely non-verbal.
You're right.
you're right you know that song the song in that movie where there's where it's
like a real hero a real human being do you know that's about that's only
someone's song what yeah somebody said that or that's true like the I mean I
mean I'll look it up now I saw somebody saying it's the band that did that song they
say they did like a genius verified yeah I'm googling it right now you guys talk
about how autistic I am more. I was googling a song in the middle of the episode. I feel
like that's a pretty cool case. Yeah, I just googled it. It is about Sully's Burger.
This is the guy from Monsters Inc. Yeah. He was a hero in that movie. Yeah, but he was
not a real human being. You know who was not a hero? Randall. What a mean... That guy was
a real rascal. He's a monster. Oh my god, wait. He was a monster. I think that might be why
they called him Monsters Inc. is because of how evil he was, that one character. No, it
was, he's, his monster's pink because he's the pink monster. Yeah. He's purple though.
No. Yeah. You're colorblind. He has like a thousand legs too, you guys notice that? He's
got one, he's got two legs. The other one's blue and furry? What the hell's going on on
this movie make the monsters look the same they can't be the same thing thing
monsters if they're look yeah that's true what what if there is the same
variance in humans well I guess it kind of is like me and Thomas don't look like
the same species no no we aren't no we're completely did we have like just a
different genome yeah Thomas looks like if if you combined all three of us but
not like take the average just like overlaid each of us just Thomas looks
like a fucking like like three guys in one I mean it look he looks like pieces
of like magazines cut out to make a guy's face like a show yeah yeah I look
like Jim Carrey yeah you look exactly I've said this for a very long time you
looks so much like Jim Carrey. And Cam looks like Jim Carrey's girlfriend.
No. We're gonna see what happens when we put you in a room together.
We put Jim Carrey and a girl in a bottle of pills in a room. Here's what happens.
I bet he would make some crazy faces. Oh my god.
Pat, what the hell are you eating? Nothing.
I can hear that you're crinkling up your bag. Put it down.
it down. What are you eating? Cheese-its? You can't eat cheese-its while we're recording.
You can't go 30 more minutes without eating cheese-its? I didn't eat lunch. Me neither.
Oh my god. Oh fuck. Are you still working Thomas? Not really. Every now and then I'll get a
landscaping gig but I just yesterday worked for the first time in like a month. Nice,
How did it feel to be out there again?
It actually kind of sucked because it was...
Landscaping sucked?
Oh yeah, dude.
I had to do it like...
This flower bed had been flooded for like six months so it was like sewer water basically.
You had to do it all out.
It was fun.
You had to suck it up with a big straw?
Yeah.
That's what happened.
Did you use some of your techniques?
Yeah.
He uses landscape techniques.
Yeah, he uses landscape techniques when he eats pussy too.
Yeah, hold up, let me get my straw.
He goes both ways.
Hold on, I need a tiny shovel.
Yeah, let me get the weed whacker.
Shorty, I'm gonna destroy that pussy.
Let me get a weed whacker.
This pussy's been flooded for six months.
It's full of seawater.
Is that the sound a weed whacker makes?
I'm gonna have to extract it.
was like sounds like this yeah sounds like Thomas I think you did that so loud
that the audio just cut in the zoo that's what it's like yeah hmm but I'm
glad so you're you're back to work so Texas how are the parents I don't know
anything about your life I know that you have a job you're like one of the guys
I
I've never been a landscaper. I used to work for a structure.
Yeah, I didn't know that either.
I assumed you'd mowed a yard before.
I never have actually.
I had a...
I had a fucking push mower at my house.
One of those ones from like cartoons.
My stepdad at some point got into like
owning a scythe.
Dude, I had one of those too at my house.
You could use it to cut the weeds.
You hit the weeds out of the ground with it.
Sick as fuck.
Was he like the angel of death or something?
Yeah, my stepdad's actually the angel of death.
It always sucked growing up having him around.
There was always like a low hum every time he walked into a room.
It sucked, man.
It was a bummer.
We had like a scythe and then he was like, "This is too hard. Let me get one of those push mowers that have no gas and don't work."
Yeah, man.
You know?
Sounds like we had pretty similar lawn mowing experiences.
Sounds like we had the same stepdad.
Yeah, we might have.
Now that I think about it, my stepdad said he was the Grim Reaper.
And I think I thought it was a different person than the Angel of Death, but you know, I'm thinking it might be the same guy.
Might be the same.
You show the big ass leg.
Oh, you have a lawnmower tattoo.
I always forget I have a lawnmower tattoo on my leg, and then I'll go to tie my shoes and I'm like, "Oh, it's a lawnmower."
It's always such a bummer when I see the tattoos that I have that suck.
And it's only ever when I'm naked, because they're all on my ass and around my dick.
And I'm like, "Why do I have like a...
Why do I have this swastika on my penis?"
It's a poor decision.
I have like a ghost on my ass cheek.
I have a...
Somebody tried to write the word Satan on me once while I was like passed out drunk
but then turned it into a flower but you still see the S and the A.
So I'm just reminding...
It's like Stana.
Yeah, it's San Antonio.
Nah man, I'm covered in terrible tattoos, so...
what's what's next trying to get
now you know what would you have not been trying to get one well tell me we get
people know you said a thousand times yesterday's dad's tattoo to make fun of
it and it's been a step to
you need to get his penis tattooed on you yet
now my dad and i have a rose that's been a sliver of the rose next to his penis
that's cool
you know i mean
it's going up and it's a little bit with a tattoo of
of his dad's penis on his forehead and being like "look at this dad, I got you good dude!"
I got you, you fucking loser.
Hey, nice dick, dad!
Now everyone knows what your dick looks like, dad.
Yeah.
Well, time to go to work!
Time to go back to the bank.
Time to go.
Yep.
I'm in line at Chili's.
My, my, somebody got my, somebody got my brother's initials tattooed on, on them when they were
like teenagers with a crown on top they were like best friends because he died
and he did not die but they now they like now they hate each other so this guy has
my brother's initials on him with a crown tattooed on him forever but the
best part is that my brother's initials are JAP so this guy has on his arm
Jap with a crown on it. How do you, do you think he's covered it up at this point?
No I saw him recently because he works at the same burrito place in my hometown.
But wouldn't you just get JP? Yeah because I, because he needs to make sure
that no one thinks he's talking about Jamaica Plain. Yeah the neighborhood in
Boston that's a good point. Yeah or Jeff Bridges. So he had to get the A.
Oh, people would think that it was a giant penis.
Or Japanese people.
Yeah, exactly.
He wanted to make sure that people didn't think he was talking about Japanese people.
Yeah, exactly. JP, Japanese people.
But now he does, since he hates my brother, they had a big falling out.
He does have to just make something up.
For what they fall out of.
They fell out of a plane together.
Yeah, they went skydiving.
That's a little too clever for us.
We'd like to go for more lowbrow stuff.
more lowbrow stuff. Can you tone it down dude? You're doing some NPR shit. Come on David Sedaris,
we just fucking, we just cool it. If there's a line I'm gonna cross it you know that. Just
like Sedaris. Sedaris is basically the king of sting, you know? In the humorous world.
Yeah. Dude that guy's nasty. That guy. You don't want to get on his bad side. No. Nah
He's a sharpshooter. He's like Geraldo, Patrice, David Sedaris.
Geraldo, Patrice, David Sedaris, Mo Rocca.
David Sedaris would have been so funny on the roasts, dude.
Dude, yeah. I mean, you just gotta watch out because he's gonna...
If you cross him, he's gonna write a 30-page story about his childhood
where something awkward happened.
And he's gonna add you in as a character for one paragraph.
Yeah, he's gonna own you.
Yeah, dude.
It would have been great in like the new style of roasts where nobody actually does any jokes
and they just all do the same bit where they like say "fuck it"
Roasts are weird.
Yeah, so annoying.
Yeah, so roasts are weird.
Back in the day it used to be like, I mean, yeah, Lisa Lampanelli just being like absurdly racist
and now you have Andy Samberg going, I'd be like "nooo, this is so weird"
*weird noises*
I get the song, Sandberg!
And that's in order.
Yeah.
Z's walking around, roasting all the women with his hands.
Tiny, tiny hands.
The only fun part of the roasts at this point is just seeing how bad Jeff Ross can look.
Yeah. It's just worse every time.
I mean, I think it's better, dude.
It's crazy that he went from like, he had like giant braids to just like the baldest guy in the world.
the world. I think what's actually going on is they're making a boyhood style
remake of the fly where they're following him around in his life.
Just over the course of years. Yeah Jeff Ross is just like a like a puddle of
ectoplasmic goo by the next rose. Yeah they're like we need another Jeff to
play a fly. I think they actually I think Jeff doesn't go on anymore I
I think he was labeled too mean.
Too much like a fly.
Too fly looking.
I think, or too easy maybe.
They were just like, yeah, it's distracting to have him in the audience.
In like five years he's just like a gray puddle with box braids.
The first day I moved here to New Hampshire I saw a white kid with box braids in his car.
So sick dude.
it's like fine yeah I wouldn't in New Hampshire I would never care about
something like that you busy battling the outlaws who are trying to steal my
son yeah yeah yeah I'm a white person with dreads in New Hampshire that's just
your teacher yeah that's like that's like them there's like the most woke guy
in New Hampshire yeah yeah and every New Hampshire town there's at least three
people three like just different people who live on opposite sides of town that
look exactly like a borderland psycho.
- Yeah. (laughing)
There's a dude who has a bunker in the woods.
He has a picket fence that's the size of his house.
And he's got a keep out sign on the front of it.
It's so sick, I wanna see what his house looks like.
- We should definitely come up and shoot some guns soon.
- Yeah, that'd be cool.
- That'd be fun.
Thomas, do you own a gun?
Uh, no.
That's what I like to hear.
No, I've never owned one.
Nice.
If you did own one, what kind would it be?
Probably a Mossberg 12 gauge and a 30/30 lever action.
Nice.
I'd probably have like a giant laser beam gun.
I would get the Spartan laser personally.
I'd have a cooler gun than that one.
I would actually, I would probably train the Devastator from Transformers Revenge of the
Fallen to kind of be my pet and my like attack dog, but it's, you know, it's all, it's
kind of to each their own, you know, if you just want like a...
I'd probably get guns implanted in my arms.
Yeah, I'd probably just become Superman, so...
I'd get Liberty Prime's laser.
Probably use my car like a gun.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'd probably have a giant gun that shoots cars, but you know, it's no big deal.
Whoa.
Yeah.
And never mind, I'd choose Cameron's gun.
I'd probably have a Swiss Army knife, that's all I'd need.
Yeah, I'd actually just need one long... I'd need a shark tooth.
I could actually do it with a single hair. I could actually kill any intruder
with one strand of hair. A dental floss, even if you tie
my hands around my back with a dental floss, I'll still kill anybody.
I pretty much just need some air, if I blow the air in the right way, it works like a bullet.
That's pretty much all I'd need. I just need a big frying pan and a dress.
and I can chase him in and out of my house over and over again whenever the clock strikes
the hour.
I don't know.
It's just easy for me.
Did I ever tell you guys about my...
No, I feel like I've talked about this.
My grandpa just guns...
I'm talking about my guns.
I'm talking about...
Not my guns.
I don't have any guns.
Talking about guns made me think about my grandpa who is just obsessed with destroying
ISIS.
Have I talked about him before?
No, I don't think so.
My grandpa, he pitched me, when he found out that I was like working in like entertainment
as far as he knows, he was like, "Well, I got a movie pitch for you."
He's from New Jersey.
He was like, "Yeah, I got a movie pitch for you."
So basically, it would be like a team of guys, right?
And they would basically be retaliating against ISIS by going into Afghanistan and killing
every single person they see.
Through whatever it is, car bombs, IEDs, crossbows, they basically kill every single person in
every member of ISIS's family, extended as well, everyone in their hometowns, and it
would be like, that's how they stop terrorism.
And I was just like, Grant, you just pitched ISIS to me.
You just pitched doing the exact same thing.
Good ISIS.
Yeah, but just like with no like not even like a political motivation.
Yeah.
It's just like still mad about 9/11.
It's just like get over it, you know what I mean?
Yeah.
Well, he was there when it happened.
Yeah, that's true.
No, he wasn't.
He was there when 9/11 happened, dude.
He fell off the guard tower.
Let's fucking go!
Let's go!
Yeah, he is in ISIS.
I mean it would be so funny for me to come home and be a white Muslim to him.
Like I wonder like what he would do.
Your head's so bald but you have like Arabic tattooed all over it.
Yeah I mean literally I mean I can just wear like... Caleb mathematics.
Khaleeb mathematics.
People do spell my name Khaleeb sometimes.
They'll do K-A-L-I-B on the Grubhub order
and then I get there and they're like, "Ah this is..." Hold on.
When you see that, that's the best feeling that you have in your life.
It's amazing. Yeah, I'm like, "You're right, I am Khalid."
You know, his name used to be just DJ Caleb before he made it big.
Yeah, Jedi Mind Caleb.
No, I would love to do that, man. I might be like a white t-shirt,
like white Muslim guy. I would just wear like a triple XL, white tee, shave my head completely
bald get like some like terrible script tattoos and just have like a very young
girlfriend I feel like it would work for me yeah yeah start a patreon just for me
yeah start messages start privately messaging all of the fans of the
podcast me like delete your pledge to the pod I need to make my trip to Mecca
I have to make my trip to Mecca.
Yeah.
I don't know, I think it would work.
Yeah dude.
You just show up to your ISIS grandpa's house and you're wearing just like a burqa.
Yeah.
You're wearing like the wrong outfit.
Hey guess what grandpa, I'm also a girl now so try that one on for size.
I'm trans and Muslim.
God dude, I mean he would have a...
You'd just give your grandpa a heart attack.
It wouldn't be a heart attack dude.
It wouldn't be hard, his head would explode like scanners.
Yeah.
Like that's exactly what would happen.
I would walk in, he would see me, even if he didn't know it was me, his head would explode.
Just seeing like a Muslim woman, his shit would be completely rocked.
Yeah, dude.
Yeah.
I don't know, I definitely want to change religions though.
Yeah?
What religion are you right now?
Bahai.
It's getting expensive.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, which one would you choose?
I mean, I know you were talking about going Catholic before.
I was never, no, I mean--
No, you were.
Catholic is too many rules.
I would need basically,
I would basically start a new religion, I think.
All right, let's hear it.
Yeah, so I'm God,
and that would be it.
So you'd be starting Branch Calebians.
Yes.
Is that what happened?
Did David start the Branch Davidians?
Was it a guy named David?
I don't think he started them,
But yeah, there's all their like Messiah is always named David or something like that.
Well, David's from the Bible. I think that yeah.
David's from-
His name was Branch and then he just started-
I've talked about this, but there is a guy in my hometown named Branch.
His name is Branch Leevold.
The only path for a guy named Branch in life is to start like a murder cult.
Like that's the only thing you can do.
Like you'll just get laughed out of any career.
Or you become a white rapper named Twiggy.
That's true.
In the case of the guy who lives in my hometown named Branch Leaf Olive.
That's such an easy name to find, too.
So anyone who listens can go find that guy.
It's so funny.
I mean, they've tried.
I remember we talked about him before and people couldn't find him.
People found like a different guy named...
Dude, his name is Branch Leaf Olive.
You think he's on the grid?
No, dude, he's living in a tree somewhere.
That guy is not in the fucking, in the yellow pages.
The government doesn't know he exists.
Yeah.
They saw his name on the NSA spreadsheet and they're like, "Oh, looks like we got another
error. This must be anonymous. This is a placeholder name. We'll fill that in later.
Oh no, the census taker accidentally just looked at a tree again and thought it was a person.
Yeah man, I think he had like heroin addict parents or something, turned Christian,
and they were like, yeah we're just gonna name our kid the coolest thing of all time.
Yeah, what's the most beautiful name? Noah's Flood. That would be a good name
for a christian kid. What about what about genesis bible? Yeah what about jesus christ?
What's the deal? There's a lot a lot of like mexican catholics name their kid
jesus. Isn't that like is that cool? Absolutely. I think it's one of the coolest things. I mean
it's definitely cool it's definitely cool but is it like is that allowed? Is that allowed with uh
the pope? I think they have a different pope. They have a they have el pope. It's just Gabriel Iglesias.
He wears a different... He does have disciples. He has like a... You know Gabriel Iglesias
has like a like a like a group of fat guys that are only do stand up with him
that tour with him and they all just talk about being fat Mexicans. He just walked into a warehouse one day and everyone who worked there just started following him around.
yeah just like 50 fat Mexican dudes all doing jokes about their sister named
Maria before he goes out yeah talks about food his one rules he's like don't talk
about food don't trample my shit or that maybe they do I don't know I've never
seen it maybe they do like a burlesque act to warm up the crowd I hope they do
I hope it's burlesque they're like they're like juggling like plates on
sticks like spinning them but all the plates have like a full meal.
Like a whole roast turkey.
Yeah but yeah man I think Pat you should definitely you might be able to glom on dude.
I might be able to join I don't think I'm fluffy enough.
No you're definitely not but that could be your thing you could be the skinny guy in the
fluffy gang.
That's true.
Right they can call you skinny P. Yeah.
I had a manager that only referred to me as Diddy,
'cause my initials were P.D.
So that turned, it went P.D., P. Diddy, then Diddy,
and then I quit.
- It's like the exact thing that happened to the real Diddy.
- I know.
(laughing)
He never went Puff Daddy though, I'm kinda mad.
- No, yeah, that's, which is the coolest one.
- Yeah, absolutely. - Any name with Puff in it,
you're like, people think I smoke, man.
- Racy's Puffs.
- Yeah.
- Puff Thomas, it's got a nice ring to it.
Puff Tommy. You should rebrand. Yeah, Puff Tommy. Puff T.
Have you ever gone by Tommy? Um, no, because uh, I don't know. I didn't really realize you could
like pick your own nickname if you wanted to. I was like, I didn't think about it until I was like 17
and then I was already Thomas by then. So it's kind of late now. There was a like two weeks where
I decided, I decided to go by my middle name. Yeah, I did that too. I was like, yeah, I'm Michael.
yeah i was like fuck you do you know yeah i call that is a thing insane
realization as your kid when your kid really communicate it goes by the mail
name is like
holy shit
yet my best friend i don't know by the way i mean
his name is john but he went by alex
my name is uh... mohammed laura croft and third grade
i had a friend in middle school whose name was michael but everyone called him
bob and that was not as middle name i have no clue why they call them that
I don't even think he chose to go by it, I think everyone just called him that.
There was a point in middle school where I was like, "Yeah, I'm gonna be the guy who
gives people nicknames."
Yeah.
And I only got one off.
There was a guy named Duncan, and I got him, everybody called him "Dunkos" because of me.
There's a kid who I'm-
Yeah, he's just like a nerdy little kid.
There's a kid who in middle school, his name is Jack, and everyone called him "Muffin" in
middle school.
I don't know what the story behind that one was, but it like stuck around until high school
and he got really mad.
Oh shit, no, there was this kid at like the like the homeschool co-op
I went to in like ninth grade
Who his name was Samuel and he's just like really dorky little like loser who got into like Bitcoin
When like 2011 so he's probably rich now
He probably buy me but he his name was Samuel and I started calling him Sammy and then one day
I just called him sausage and then everybody there
So I started calling him sausage and then like the principal sent out like an email
There's like please stop referring to Samuel as sausage
And his mom teachers have to get involved with that. It's so funny there that happened at my school, too
With the kid whose name was Alex, but everyone called him Nubby
Eventually got so fucking mad after like oh, yeah, oh, I just there's a kid
There's two there's two kids who are the same name
There's two kids named Alex Augusto at our school and one of them was like really first and last name
Yeah, same first and last name.
That happened twice at my school.
There was two kids named Alex Augusto.
I think you had a glitch in the matrix there, dude.
Two kids named Alex Augusto and then two other kids in the same grade named Seamus Rio.
What the fuck?
Which that's not fucking common.
That is not a fucking common name.
Neither is Augusto.
Yeah, but one of them was very tall and dark Italian.
I think he was probably Sicilian.
He finishes. Say he was handsome.
He was just very, he had just very dark skin and he was Italian and-
So that's not handsome to you?
*laughter*
Yeah, is that a problem?
No, he was busted.
But-
He was busted?
Oh my god.
Then the other Alex Augusta was like very short and fat and one day on the bus he was
going over someone else's house and like an older kid, this kid Hunter was trying to
get his attention and he was like, "What's his name, Alex?"
So he's screaming Alex for like three minutes and he went, "Hey Alex, there's a jar of mayonnaise in the back of the bus!"
And he looked.
And then he, we just called him Mayonnaise for the rest of time.
God, dude. It's so cruel what little thing can make you...
I know.
Dude, I just remember my favorite...
Yo, Chris took a poop. He's poop now.
What up, poop?
He started to embrace Mayonnaise, so then we stopped calling him it.
The best nickname story.
Yeah, when a kid is like, "Yeah, I'm my nickname for sure and I love it."
Um, there's this kid at my school, um, whose name was Steven.
And, um, in the high school yearbook, um, yeah, no, I know.
No way.
In the high school yearbook, they had like a picture of him that was labeled Steven.
And then next to it, they had a different picture of him.
Like, it was just some glitch in the yearbook.
It was a different picture of him, but like the name under it was, was Steeniuiu.
like it was like s t e e n i o u i o u
as we would call him steenu all the time
it was i might still have a copy of that yearbook it's like the funniest thing i've ever seen in my life
god damn dude
yeah yearbook kids fuck everything up
like someone just fell asleep on the keyboard
there's another time my friend for con
they printed his name in the yearbook as boy
That's a pretty funny nickname already.
He just didn't even want to bother getting his name correct.
I, the yearbook, the girl who did the yearbook, my like senior quote was some like, that Harris
Whittles joke about like wheat thiccs.
Oh yeah.
You know that joke, like wheat thins call me when they're wheat thiccs.
I was like a big Harris Whittles fan in high school.
And she messed it up so bad that my yearbook quote ended up being, "I love wheat thins."
(laughter)
- This is a suck dude.
It's like everybody's just gonna think I like wheat thins.
(laughter)
- Not good.
- I love wheat thins.
Imagine liking wheat thins enough,
you're like, yeah this is my senior quote.
- Also it being a quote from somebody else.
- Yeah.
- It's not that I love wheat thins,
it's that Harris Whittles, the dead comedian,
loves wheat thins.
Just terrible dude.
Did they put Harris Whittles at the end of the quote?
I love Wheat Thins, Harris Whittles.
Yeah, it said, "I love Wheat Thins, Harris Whittles."
It's like it was his final, it was like his last words.
Yeah, my final will and testament, I love Wheat Thins.
Yeah, man, that was a serious yearbook snafu.
If I had been a chartered yearbook, I would have crushed it.
I would have given, I would have been amazing.
I would have put so many Wheat Leaves.
I would have hidden so many weed leaves in the back of the photos, dude.
I would have done mustaches, devil horns.
Yeah.
Yeah, nothing else.
Super ass.
You know.
It would have been good.
I don't know.
Did you, uh, you went to high school, right, Thomas?
Yes, I did.
How did you know?
That's awesome, dude.
You just had, you seem like an educated man.
Yep.
And I'd like to give you a job.
Yeah.
Do you go to a bank?
Did you go to a big ass Texas high school when I was one of those 15,000 kids?
No, my graduating class was 80.
Whoa.
Is that because all the other 15,000 dropped out?
Yeah.
Yeah, we just had a terrible school.
Like a 99% dropout rate.
It was insane.
I went to a wayside school.
It was a bummer.
Everything was sideways.
Yeah, dude.
They turned me into apples.
Yeah, they turned me into apples.
It was just missing floor.
I mean, Apples is just missing floor.
Yeah.
Not cool.
I went to the MKUltra High School, so I did experiments on my mind the whole time.
Is that why you're so weird?
Yeah, dude.
That's why I'm all messed up.
Every time you look at me, I get a headache.
You're doing powerful shit.
It's so fucking funny that the government for like 10 years was like, "Yeah, we're gonna
give people mind powers."
Yeah.
We gotta do it.
It's the sickest shit of all time.
Yeah.
billions of dollars. Yeah. No, the best... Can we just pitch anything to...
Hello, Mr. President, I'm gonna make cartoons real. And it's like the fun, the
best part of it is like, oh you know what the way that they're like, you know what
the way we're gonna give them mind powers is? Alright, here we go. We're gonna
put them in a big pool, we're gonna put a helmet on their head, and we're gonna play
a tape that says, "You have mind powers" for a week and not feed them at all and
they're gonna get mind powers. And then we're just gonna give them like a drug
Like me that makes you drop out of high school. Yep, and then we're gonna cut open their stomach
Yeah, cuz why not just sick, dude
Yeah, we're doing we're doing dark dark mind experiments to figure out. What does the stomach look like when you cut it open?
I'd probably be pretty creepy
Yeah, we're just gonna be kind of weird now. Yeah, we're doing weird experiments
We wanted to make like a hundred and fifty very weird guys. Yeah, what would happen if you combine?
What would happen if you combine waffles and pancakes that was one of the big
MKUltra things that got covered up. Can we make it rain tacos? Sir we have we have
collected 150 of the most random people we could find to do raw RxD
experiments on. Sir what's the square root of dinosaur? Neapolitan ice cream?
You're in. Yeah it's crazy. It's crazy. After just a week one of our
specimens was able to translate the dinosaur word for love. For "I love you."
They walk by like a testing chamber and they just see like a Tumblr teen trying
to bend a spork with her mind. Yeah. Wow this is so bacon. Sir we have three
bacon, tier bacon operators ready to go. Ready to attack Vietnam at any point in
time it appears that these specimens have have developed a fixation for Bill Murray
yeah they saw Bill Murray on the street and he said tell nobody Wow sir I'm
afraid hallucinating Bill Murray sir I'm afraid the experiments were a failure
doctor, all three of the subjects still like twilight.
Oh, fuck, dude. Yeah.
Fail blog. The operation was a fail blog, doctor.
Yeah. Yeah, we could definitely design something
like that for the government.
You're walking around the grocery store and you see some emaciated test subject who escaped
who's just like in Stranger Things style, in a hospital gown and stuff.
They walk up to you and they're like, "Excuse me, can I has cheeseburger?"
Yeah, the code was like, "Quick, Edison or Tesla?"
Tesla.
Yeah, you're in.
Identity confirmed.
Yeah, man.
I think I'm going to go into the military now.
I think I could change it.
Yeah.
What branch would you go for?
I would basically go to the Marines.
Yeah.
I think I would be a Navy SEAL.
I think I would be probably whatever's on top of the Navy SEAL. I would be a space marine, but you know
Yeah, I'd be a I'd be a general. I'd be a Jedi so
I'd be a Jedi Sentinel in the army. Yeah, yeah, and I would basically my plan is to go over to ISIS and basically kill all their families
The thing is you if you pitch that like, you know, like Pompeo or whatever would be like, yeah
Why didn't we think of that before? Of course?
He's like I'm in
(laughter)
- Yeah.
- John Krasinski proposing a crossover
between Jack Ryan and Star Wars.
(laughter)
What if we revealed they're in the same universe?
- Yeah, in real life.
Yeah, the Jedi and the CIA and Jim from The Office
are all in the same universe as ISIS.
- Dude, imagine if in--
- And I'm gonna take them down.
- Imagine if in Star Wars 10,
like the cliffhanger at the end,
like they're like, "Oh my God,
a new powerful Sith Lord has risen and he turns around and it's Osama Bin Laden.
[Laughter]
And that's the reveal that it's all been in our universe all along.
It'd be even crazier if he was a Jedi.
He's the last Jedi.
Holy crap.
I mean, think about it. He was in a cave.
That's what Rian Johnson wanted to do. They wouldn't let him.
He was in a cave, right?
Yeah.
I mean, that's some Jedi shit right there.
That's all you need.
He was surrounded by 13 year olds.
He could use the force.
Very Jedi-esque.
He could use the force, yeah.
Yeah, nobody was piloting the planes.
Yeah.
Osama used his force powers.
He destroyed a large structure
by targeting its weak point.
Oh my God.
Very Jedi-esque.
Yeah.
He wore a dress.
He did wear a dress like a Jedi.
He believed in the divine power of Allah,
which is a Jedi attribute.
It is a Jedi trait.
Yeah, that's part of the Jedi code.
The Iron Code of the Shinobi.
He loved, he had a ton of porn on his laptop.
Yeah.
Very Jedi.
I mean, how embarrassing for him.
Do you guys think that the SEAL Team 6 like planted all that shit on his laptop, like
all the movies and stuff?
I think one of them left his laptop there.
Yeah, and they were like, "Oh, look at all this gay shit."
He's like, "Yeah, this probably belonged to Osama Bin Laden."
Yeah.
Yeah, these are probably Osama's things.
Um, anyway.
Geoff, is this your laptop?
No.
Anyway, that was Osama's laptop.
That was here when we got here.
Osama loved Evangelion and Naruto.
Oh, how embarrassing.
He had a bunch of naked pictures of me and my friends.
This is us.
Yeah.
He was trying to extort us.
That's why we killed him.
Wow.
He had this naked photo of me grilling.
Yeah, he knew he was onto us, dude.
He was gonna leak this to the press.
That's why we had to kill him.
check out his joking bookmarks do this is so sad
has an entire folder on chrome is joking website
all my god and he wrote my name on the bottom of the computer to try and frame
me
yet yet says what is the other day over the day open up the laptop it's like
password required in the ages like wait guys i'm a master hacker i didn't tell
you that i have a couple but i think that's the best part of the one track
yeah i'm guessing it's mario with big boobs one
so far into osama's mind i was able to extract the password
we did some deep research on him and what his password would be
yeah turns out it's SEALTEAM6
yeah
i wish i'd been there dude
If I was there it would have gone different.
He would have killed me.
Yep.
Yeah.
Osama would have killed me and all my friends so easy if I had been there.
God damn it.
If only.
Fuck.
Alright I gotta piss.
Yeah me too man.
We need to wrap up.
I've had to pee for like 40 minutes.
Thomas thank you so much for coming on.
Thank you Thomas.
Do you have anything you want to talk about?
Tell the people about?
Not really.
Maybe next time though.
What about like a landscape?
Do you have like a business card for your landscaping company?
yet we'll get there. Thanks for having me on. Yeah of course. Subscribe to Thomas' Hats Patreon.
Oh yeah. Oh yeah. Let's get into it. How much you pulling down from the Hats page? I think like
9,500 a month. We're gonna get that to a thousand pal. You say 9,500 a month? 9,500 a month yes.
Oh my god let's get it to 10k. Yeah. Thank you Thomas. I appreciate it. Y'all take care.
See you buddy. Bye.