come back and make a bet
and receive a bite
so
on the way on the way
into the
the office
i've been is we got like some kind of
all men are cursed
was placed on us
your deterred your mic off again what do you do that the second before record
I don't know. What? It was on and then you turned it off. I don't think I've ever done that.
You do that a lot. Is it working now? You don't do it anymore. You just did it again. What?
Is it working now? Yeah. Am I working?
Yeah. Okay.
How about now? Why do you turn it? It sounds horrible. It makes a click noise. It makes like an electrical
click noise.
It's not a funny bit because nobody can hear what you're saying when it's off. So when you say
"Is it working?" it doesn't like translate at all in the audio. Does it pick up on your mic?
I don't know.
That probably does if you're yelling, yeah.
- I quit.
- Yeah.
- I'd knock you off. - That was a good one.
So-- - Carmichael!
- What?
- What's that?
- I said his name wrong.
And no one at home will know I said it wrong.
Well, you yelled it.
I said if you yell it, so you yelled it.
- Well, I'll just say you said Carmichael,
you didn't say Cameron.
- And you yelled it too, so it's loud.
Get on with your curse story.
I was walking in here, I was walking up to the office,
and in front of the office there's a car
they're like like double parked in the street people in it as I walked by a
lady got out of the car. She's holding a crow in her hand now and she placed it.
You know how there's like a the like tree with like a little grassy area
around it. She put the crow in the grass at the tree in front of the office and
it just started pecking around as I walked in a pitch black of a black bird,
a crow. I did see that our double parked. She got out of the car. I swear to God,
not an April Fool's joke. I really saw that and it's I think that something bad
is going to happen and then I walked in here and you guys tried to scare me and
I walked in and I was like I was feeling weird cuz I was like I just saw a lady
put a spell on me and like I walked in and all the lights were off but
everything like the coffee maker was on and doors were open and stuff and I
really thought I was being haunted for a second. What if you had found that me and Patrick
had been slaughtered to death? Yeah. Would you have felt anything? Yeah. What if our
rib cages had been ripped open by a dead space monster. I don't understand.
What if I was in here, what if you walked in here and you saw me eating ribs?
Would you be sad if me and him both died and there was blood covering everything
including you? If you were covered in blood, would you like it or not like it?
If I was covered in sauce, would you wipe me down? If you saw your whole family die, would you
cry or smile? Cry? Because of laughter or sadness? There's a right answer. There is a
a right answer. Sadness. Sadness because you're because you're crying or because
your family died? Both. Okay. All right. You got it. These are all the right answers. You solved the puzzle.
If you walked in here and I was eating a rack of ribs. That would honestly piss
me off so bad. I know. Yeah. I would be annihilated if I walked in
and you were eating like a full 12 rack of ribs,
barbecue sauce all over your face.
- Why?
- It would just annoy me.
- It would be a nasty thing to do.
- Especially if I saw you pour more barbecue sauce
on the ribs.
(laughing)
I think that that might finally make me fucking kill you.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, if I saw you pour stubs on the ribs.
- Would be stubs, stubs is a cooking.
You put stubs, you don't put more.
- Dude, I'm like tearing up thinking about this.
This is like, I would be so pissed off.
Stubbs is too liquidy for me.
Even this is getting too close to me.
Stubbs is not thick enough.
Because now I know that you're imagining the ribs, and I know that they would be short
ribs.
He's going to put chocolate syrup on them.
Is there the exception?
Are you baby back or beef ribs?
I think I'm baby back.
Yeah, okay.
That's better.
That's a little better.
But what if, I think the exception to this, barbecue spare ribs from a Chinese place.
No.
Not boneless, like bone-in spare ribs, like Chinese style.
That's not a rack of ribs though, that doesn't bother me.
What if I make it that, like I put a smoker outside?
If you put a smoker outside I think I would maybe forgive you for eating a humongous serving
of ribs in front of me.
Because I would give you something.
Because I would be like, "I'll give you a smoker."
Regardless, you guys come in, I'm eating ribs.
I'm giving you like one rib.
I don't want to eat a rib, dude, because I know that you're sitting here and you've already
touched every last one of them.
I know you've touched every rib. You're picking them. "Oh, which one do I want?"
Squeezing them, trying to see which one is the softest, because you have no teeth.
You can gum them down harder.
I have teeth. You don't have teeth.
You don't have teeth. In this scenario, I have no teeth.
Yeah, you're eating ribs with no teeth.
(laughter)
They have to be very tender. You're just chewing into them with gum.
Yeah, oh my God, and you're wearing a bib.
You're wearing a bib, and like, you're wearing like, you're wearing like a, like...
Why did we stop wearing bibs when we grow up?
You're wearing like a hazmat suit made out of grocery bags.
Here's the thing, man.
So the fanciest thing that you can eat
is lobster. You wear a bib.
But then the least fancy thing you need is baby food.
And you wear a bib.
It's horseshoe theory.
It all comes down back around.
It's horseradish theory.
You dip in one of those.
So what's in the middle?
What's the exact bib?
Lollipop.
is much closer to baby. It's a fancy versus not. Let's take the horseshoe
right now. Okay, okay, so it is least fit. Okay, yeah, least fancy baby food
cat food.
Yeah, next, yeah,
but you could wear a bib where eating. Yeah, that's like, yeah, ribs has got
to be right above cat food, then because you can wear a baby. No, ribs is on
the lobster side. Yeah, ribs is on the lobster side. You can get surf and
turf
ribs
turf and turf. That's barbeque ribs on a lobster. And fish ribs. True. Gills. Barbeque gills.
Yeah. Yeah. Fish ribs. Wait, no that's the. Disgusting. What are you picking up? I was
going to make the horseshoe. I was going to. We don't need to draw anything. We can use
the theater of the mind. We have a highly imaginative audience. So first imagine a letter
C. Rotate it 90 degrees. And then put all those. I think I have them dots all over them.
Yeah, what's that about? You ever heard about those are fleas from the horse? I have okay. Okay, so like
baby food cat food horse meat
Horse meat is pretty fancy
To me the definition of a salad in a can definition of fancy if you go into a restaurant and you ask for it and they
Don't have it. That's fancy
That logic you go into I don't know like nope, no, what's uh, what's the fancy restaurant?
I say a fan okay obviously a fancy restaurant has fancy food and if you ask
if you go to a fancy restaurant you ask if they have food and they say no then
that's not fancy. I don't think Lucien's fancy. In my brain the fanciest
restaurant you can go to is Ruth's Chris and those are in hotels. They just have
like steak but I honestly I'm like that's the fanciest. If you go to Peter Luger, so by that logic if you go to like Peter Luger and ask for a
Crunchwrap Supreme that's what I'm saying. That makes it fancy? No because Peter Luger is
fancy so if you go to a non fancy restaurant and you ask for something and
they don't have it it's fancy but if you go to a fancy restaurant and ask for
something I don't know it I think the middle here uh-huh the direct center of
the horseshoe is Taco Bell it could be between lobster and baby food yeah I
think that actually is right I think you might actually be on yeah I think that
you would never ever wear a bib and Taco Bell no you would be removed you would
you'd be on the news if you showed up.
- You would be at Taco Bell.
- If you sat down at Taco Bell with a Crunchwrap Supreme
and a Chipotle chicken burrito,
and you wrapped a bib around your neck.
- You would be on the news.
- Yeah, you'd be, because I would kill you.
- Exactly.
- There's a gun under the register.
- Yeah, exactly.
- And they whip it out when someone comes in with a bib.
- There's a button they have that's in case of bib.
- It's like a Matt Lauer button.
It locks all the doors in the restaurant.
The storm shutters come down.
And then check this out, on either side of Taco Bell, slightly more bib-worthy, non-fancy
side McDonald's, fancy side Five Guys.
Yep, because them burgers is cheesy as a motherfucker.
And greasy too.
No grease in Taco Bell, or cheese.
You're not going to go to jail for wearing a bib there, but it's still a bit of a faux
pas.
You won't be killed.
If you wear a bib at Five Guys or McDonald's, and McDonald's people are going to assume you're
doing a prank.
I feel like wearing a bib at Five Guys, I could see a hipster doing that.
Well I could definitely see a hipster doing basically anything morally wrong.
Probably a plaid bib.
And hipsters would eat both ends of the fancy and non-fancy spectrum because they would
eat fancy because you can't afford it and they would eat baby food because they're like
what you think it's not good?
But then also the bib is going to confuse them because they think that it's some kind
of scarf.
Yeah that's true.
My infinity bib.
Yeah.
My infinity bib got sauce on it.
It goes around on my back too so if I hold my food behind the back of my head and it
my drips. I'm safe. Yeah, I won't get it on my way. Yep,
I won't get it on my my cafe latte americano. Yeah, I don't get anything in
my there. I'm not going to get any of my rib sauce in my cafe. Oh, no, yeah, or
my or my pointed devil tail.
Yeah, exactly, because the devil is a damn hipster. Yeah, and I left I left
before it was cool. Yep, yep, that's true. That's what the devil said. And you know
he likes rock. Uh-huh. I hate that rock shit. You know what God listens to? What?
Iron and Wine. He loves that crap. He loves that boom bap ho hey stuff. You know
what he loves? God loves Lumineers, the devil. He loves the, he loves Jet, Are You
Gonna Be My Girl? That's his favorite song. Jesus Christ favorite song is that
that song like paper and fire paper and fire living on the airstream baby that
one fact you should talk to my dad David yeah yeah I think you guys might really
get along what's that song it's called paper and fire did you make it up did
you know it I don't know my dad might have originally recorded that and put it
on his iPod you know it'd be so funny if that song is like a like royalty-free
free song.
My dad just listens to the royalty free music all day. These are just the
these are the most like the true
garage man like in music. It's by this. It's by this like crazy, like like
Indy garage rock guy. His name is Kevin MacLeod. He makes like crazy punk
stuff. I've always
Leoed yeah me too yeah and then you and then you realize it's but yeah, it's
cloud the fucked up this fucked up guy mm-hmm strange strange guy strange fruit
what do you wrote that - yeah really yeah it's royalty free yeah oh that's cool
that's a very poignant royalty free song yeah a lot of them are good yeah what
else did he write I like scheming weasel you know that one no that's the song
it's like Turner Turner you know that the one you know the one I know that one
Why did Evanescence become a free music that you could use on YouTube?
Well you could use, I think it was UMG or something, there was some licensing
agreement between YouTube and some record company
and that's why all of those you could like put. Evanescence and then like
Finger Eleven Paralyzer and then 009 Sound System.
That's too loud you have to stop. Yeah. Let's sing that for the rest of the
episode they should have one they should have bought out the Lonely Island yep
yeah it would have been awesome it was so she would like the first like when
YouTube would get like you get copyright strikes for music and shit and you would
have to like replace the that was when they did it manually though which so is
easier to get away with it if you as long as your video didn't have a lot of
views you could post whatever you wanted yeah but like yeah when they would they
would give you to be like hey we took all the audio out of your thing so then
And then there'll be like a 50 minute fucking tutorial
on how to load OS 10 onto a computer,
and then the guy's just like mouthing the words
and you just hear,
♪ How can you see through my eyes ♪
It was awesome, dude.
- That's what they do with skate videos still.
Like the first, what's that movie,
Foundation, that's like the intro
is a 21st century schizoid man.
It has no sound, and then it goes to the first part,
and then there's music, and you like,
"Oh, well just why not just like take the fucking video down?"
You know?
- Dude, these fucking, these drug addicts
who are in charge of all the music
and you get shot in the head and killed.
- Yeah, copyright.
It's all about copyright nowadays.
- I genuinely believe--
- I actually call it copy white.
- Yeah, these fat cats, these big cheeses,
they just wanna line their pockets
with TMs and Cs in circles.
- I genuinely believe that's a copyright
last thing Hitler invented.
you think that was right before he died
he was like
and also he was like i'm gonna kill myself
yeah he was like nobody else can do this
oh yeah
and copyrighted
it's actually copyrighted short from the german word "kopieriten"
if i i i would actually
i'd be pretty happy if if if he copyrighted all that bullshit he did no
one else could ever do it again yeah that's actually might be the most brave
thing that he could do yeah it's not really brave it's just that he wanted all
the credit for it. If he could copyright the Holocaust so that nobody could ever
do it again. Yeah exactly. I'll take that. He was originally Copy Reich. Yeah that was
his idea. Yeah and there's one guy who's trying to Copy Reich.
Donald Trump. Well I don't know if it's him I think it's probably Brandon. That's what Saturday Night Live said.
If you ask me it's actually all the Democrats. Yeah Brandon and his lackeys.
Yep. Yeah. The EmoCrips and I don't know maybe the Rebloodlikens. No the Rebloodlikens
are actually cool. No yeah they're cool-likens. Yeah. I'm gonna go ahead and say...
Republic Kings. It is a freeing feeling that Spotify has already given us the
COVID-19 misinfo thing. Yeah. Now we can just say whatever we want.
Now we can just say, let's just admit it, COVID's fake. It's fucking fake dude.
fake I'm trying to I want to say this for years it's not real if they if they if
Spotify gives us that warning I'm gonna you best believe I'm never wearing a mask
again yeah dude like I you're put you're giving us no option here Spotify you put
the warning on every episode you put the warning on episodes that are like about
a frog yeah they're like from before yeah it existed yeah yeah before it was
created in a lab by the Spotify guy exactly and by before Cove it existed I
mean right now. Damn. All of our episodes are pre-covid. Who's Spotify's little fat Swedish
founder? You. No. Yep. Kim Dotcom or something. What? No, Kim Dotcom made Mega. Oh. And now
he gambles with trainwrecks TV. Oh true. Yeah. He's awesome dude. I love him. Yeah, I think
Covid was created by Spotify. Look at the genome of Covid. Look at the Spotify logo. They look
similar. They're both green. That's true. I think Covid was created by the NBA to try
to give LeChina more rings. It's true. Yeah. You got a ring in the bubble. You know what
else has rings? The Olympics. Yep. And where were the Olympics held one time? LeChina.
LeChina. LeBron. They were held in LeBron James. Yep. You know who was in the Olympics?
Who? LeBron James. Played for the skiing team. Played for the skiing team. USA skiing team.
You know what color medal people try to get in the Olympics? Gold. And do you know what
color of covid is green. Yep. This is not you know what you wipe your snot with a
tissue golden gold foil and listen to this gold green gold green gold 5g's.
Wow that means 5g that's fucking insane. Yeah. How many rings in the Olympics
seven or seven seven or eight or something add two to five that's seven
at two of that nine then eleven then thirteen fifteen seventeen number thirteen nineteen
twenty twenty one what happened in twenty twenty one
coveted happened to it happened a year before yep yeah it had been one year since coveted
yeah twenty one uh-huh add two more years 2023 23 michael jordan but then also 23 and
me lebron 23 and the mirror d and dna dna sequencing and the gene says i'm chinese
Mm-hmm. I'm the I'm LeBron China. Mm-hmm. Yeah, and then
Quarter a quarter is money. It costs money to get the vaccine. Yeah. Yep. At least it should yeah
It's just cost money to get the vaccine. Yeah to pay to get you should have to pay right?
There's no such thing as a free lunch vaccine Maxine
Maxine Max period women are trying to control the world. Mm-hmm period period
Yeah, think about that the last the last thing in a sentence is a period the last thing a woman sees at the end of the
Month the last thing that a man the last word a man hears before he never has sex again is period. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Three periods in a row that's an ellipsis. Mm-hmm
Eclipses Donald Trump looked at the moon lips. It's the moon controls my periods
Yeah
And what does the moon look like the moon?
Dot it looks like a dot which is a giant period dot damage over time
Mm-hmm Cove or it could be an egg and what goes in and what comes what dies?
At the end of the month for a woman chicken a child a child that comes from an egg every
Period is an abortion. Yep. Yeah. Yeah, go ahead and put that as a warning on your fucking Spotify music
you're gonna go up and what is and what is a sperm what does that look like a
balloon frog a balloon tadpole a balloon when do I get balloons my birthday on my
zero with birthday what was I a sperm yep and also it also it looks like a
tadpole and what is that what a sperm tastes like salt and what is salt where
to salt go on the road on the road and why be to melt go back to melt to go
faster to get all to create friction with the snails on the road there's too
many snails there's too many that's what we're trying to get at in New York there
are too many snails on the ground and dr. dr. Martin Luther Eric Adams needs to do
something about these damn snails oh my god snails snips and snails and puppy dog
tails mm-hmm what does that make a good stew a boy that's right what and what is
a girl made out of sugar and spice and chemical and everything spite mm-hmm
yeah if they did Rugrats nowadays it'd probably be like it's named out of
boogers and rice and everything everything lice cuz the girls decide to
be disgusting of armpit hair oh we got a pause now because Patrick has to get
laundry all right fine okay we're like Warren Buffett right now he's got a
beautiful bikini model george i don't know who that is
you look like warren buffett
when you go to the buffet that you gotta issue a warning
s
saturday incoming
hide all of the the cheese
and the fruit is in the what do you have a buffet
that she has a very nice cereal
hide it all this is a good thing to have don't cut the news that you have a
continental breakfast is a buffet. We're not thinking about a buffet.
Patrick alert at the buffet warning.
I'm going to drink all the orange juice.
It's just like it's just like a hundred people running down the aisle like
like a Godzilla movie.
Yeah, it's all Japanese businessmen fleeing the buffet.
Just not giant just normal size, but walking real slow like a giant into
the buffet and then getting all the orange juice and all the milk.
It's continental breakfast you're describing.
It's not a buffet.
And you're sitting there slowly, slow motion,
turning a waffle at the buffet.
No, you go to a buffet and you only get orange juice and milk.
And the waffle buffet--
(imitates trumpet)
The waffle maker.
He wants the milk!
He's getting 1%!
And now he's at the 2%!
You're still, you're just screaming like Godzilla.
You're just going, "Ehhh!"
This is a buffet warning.
he's moved on to the buffet waffle maker it is making it a little awful and that
that's it's pissing me off you just do it is getting a single-serve
uh... individually package now here you're going back now he's going back to
his room
he's going back to his buffet room
war room warning is patrick is going back to the buffet really slowly walking like
godzilla or king kong
now he's watching shark tank like godzilla i lived in a i lived in a hotel
for like a couple months yet they give those warnings everyday
Yeah. Did I ever tell you about that? I accidentally... so you'd get like the
continental breakfast tray, you could bring it back to your room
and someone put that in the oven and didn't tell me.
Someone put that in the oven and didn't tell me. So I looked in and I was like, oh
that's just like a cookie sheet that we had.
And I turned the oven on. You melted one? I melted a continental breakfast tray.
I melted a continental breakfast tray and like
the plastic was melting down onto like the oven itself.
Why didn't, wait, why didn't you take it out?
I thought it was a cookie.
Either way, why not just take it out?
Yeah, but why not take it out?
It's just funnier to just let it in there.
No, if you leave the tray in there, then you can put your
Elio's pizza on top of the tray.
Oh, okay. And then it's already hot.
Alright. And it makes the crust...
You know you're supposed to heat up a pizza stone?
Yeah. If you do that
with an Elio's pizza...
He doesn't know about a pizza stone.
If you had to guess what a pizza stone was,
you fucking honky bitch what would you say?
- A magical stone.
- Yep, you nailed it first try.
Great, you're a genius, awesome, cool.
I look like a dickhead.
- So the plastic melted down onto the bottom of the oven
and then like was catching fire
and I didn't know what to do.
And I didn't want to, I didn't think it warranted me
getting the fire extinguisher,
so I went down to the front desk of the hotel.
- You told them there was a fire in your room?
- I had to wait in line to tell them
'cause I was so nervous.
I just didn't want to like, 'cause if I went,
there's a fire in my room like that would be way worse than me just being like the
oven something's going on with the oven you know like I couldn't just be like oh
fire fire I think there's a middle ground between those two things I don't
I was 17 dude I don't know so I'm pretty - man singing upstairs that's all I got to
say that story man suffering suck it you know and that situation I think you just
climb into the oven over you join them yourself you think would your skin
plastic made like a big goo thing like a big like I would just roll around in oil
and spices and I just climb into the oven and everything nice yeah yeah I'd
cover myself in za'atar and then spin around in the oven yeah what is that tar
is it weed za'atar is like sumac and like sesame seeds poison ivy nettles
hair or milk we a lot of birds mm-hmm in the in Zatar yes and mm-hmm that sounds
about when you're in the sandbox as a kid yeah and it's like moons and why do you
keep looking to the other it's literally I hear what nobody else can hear it's
it's so quiet all right good it's somebody talking like a man who
apartments over look at like it's like an asshole talking too loud on the phone
at a restaurant yeah he's at his house right now you know he's in his home it's
so quiet. I can't even hear him. I'm singing. You can sing in your house. I was
in my- I was literally in my house. We come in here every day and we scream at the
top- well you scream at the top of your lungs. I was in my house so loudly this
morning taking a shower singing Diary of Jane by Breaking Benjamin. Diary of Jane.
I called you in the shower today. I sort of showed you my butt cheeks. Yeah, you
showed me your butt farting. Yep. He FaceTimed me and I showed him my butt and farted on it. I
I couldn't pick that call up because I was beating the Elden. I'm glad you didn't.
You would have seen my butthole. Yeah. Yeah. He showed me, Joe and Alex.
You were the only one who wasn't on the phone. I realized I was fighting the
Elden beast. That's a good point. My butt looks like a girl's butt on a FaceTime
call. Yeah, dude. I have a Hank Hill ass. Really? Yeah. You have a tiny little...
Dude, if I clench my cheeks, it literally looks like Hank Hill's. Damn.
Yeah. I got some serious fucking... I got a package back there. I have no ass. Damn. You
you would think I would with all the jumping I do you
that's how you get around
think I'd have a strong ass. No, it's all on my thighs. My ask gets nothing.
You're a hopper. Yeah, I am jumping constantly. I never really thought about
it. I do jump a lot. No, you don't yeah. I do. I don't know that I've ever seen
jump on skateboard that's not jumping it's pretty much that's all that's called
loitering yeah that's crying yeah yeah I really wish you would stop killing
yourself with that bullshit okay you're hurting your body you're hurting your
soul you're hurting your family and your friends - good okay well that's when you
get taken before my devourer and he weighs your heart against the feather
you're going your soul is being devoured mm-hmm my soul against a feather mm-hmm I
I think they weigh the same.
No.
Your soul doesn't weigh anything.
Again Pat is doing...
Your heart is...
There's a kid screaming this time.
Your heart is filled with sin.
Your YouTube reaction faces.
Huh?
His heart is filled with sin.
Yeah, so it weighs more than a feather.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
How much does sin weigh?
A lot.
A lot?
Yeah.
Are you getting ready to throw something at me?
No.
Are you...
You promise me.
it's a fidget thing that I need to do. You need to do that? Yeah, so I can pay
attention. A skateboard is basically just like the opposite of
like the tablet with the Ten Commandments. It's like the evil tablet.
It's like if you put it upside down. Yeah, it's instead of the Ten Commandments it has
a dragon. Yeah, it's the RDS logo. The Red Dragon skateboard.
That actually sounds pretty cool. Yeah. Have they put the Ten Commandments on
the bottom of the skateboard? That would be pretty cool. I think, okay, so there's a skater
Brian Sumner he was like born-again Christian and he made this like God like
this like Christian skateboard company and like there's a shit ton of like
sick born-again Christians are so fast because it's like I don't want it like I
don't want to stop doing this one thing that I do like Christian metal Christian
rock and then you become a Christian and you have to like somehow put the things
that you like into Christianity yeah yeah it's so funny that the members of
of corn are gradually one by one becoming born again. I remember the first one did
yeah first one was yeah. I remember reading I because I was you know my
family super Christian and I was at my dentist's office who he was a he went to
my church yeah and they own the only like magazines I had were like Christian
ones and one of them was an interview with corn yeah I was like oh this would
be cool. He'll probably talk about fucking drugs. Yeah, I'm open it up and
he was just like Jesus is it love is yeah. He left corn and he made a solo
album a Christian new metal album that's yeah he was on Huckabee uh-huh and then
he played bass with Huckabee dude it's so sick Huckabee that video yeah that
video is tight dude Mike Huckabee what does he says like well the music may not
sound that great but this man loves God it's so funny to still go by head and
become Christian yeah yeah I'm head you know his real name Brian Welch Brian
head welch brian head welch was he a was he a good part of the band or yeah he's
basically the the band like after he left they they don't sound like corn anymore
but then he came back we are not saying about getting molested he very clearly
no I don't think he I mean is there room where he could maybe work on him I
definitely I think they will turn event - I mean two out of five maybe I don't
that's like enough that is like they will all eventually. I feel like if one of them
does it and then another one does it years later. How many corn songs are about
Jonathan Davis getting molested as a kid or whatever? Most of them. Most of them?
Almost all of them. That'd be so funny for him to go to like the one establishment.
He's gonna become Protestant, he's not gonna become a Catholic.
Maybe. You don't become, there's no born-again Catholics. I'm born-again Catholic.
Catholic. That's not true. Well except for the the one small slice of people in this
city, the worst city in the entire world. Yeah. With the worst kind of people. Those
are, you really have to be a true piece of shit to become a born-again Catholic.
Born-again Christians are just people who fucked up. Yeah. Yeah. People who fucked up
and just need, they just need something. They just need, honestly they just need
new movies. Another really good Christian. They just need access to new movies. The born-again
Catholics do it because it's like oh I'm a piece of shit I need to pay for my
being a piece of shit by getting whipped and stuff. They do it so they can take
pictures. That's true. Yeah. Take pictures with the rosary. Yeah.
There's another really good Christian new metal band. That's like
probably I think the funniest combination. Like the funniest music to
be Christian is like new metal. Yeah. Where it's like hip-hop and metal combined.
Demon Hunter. That's another really good one. P.O.D. is fucking sick.
Didn't P.O.D. have a song in Grind? I don't know. I'm thinking it's a click click boom.
click-click boom is sick yeah is that pod or is that no that's saliva yes that's
not yeah that is a cool song yeah pod is we are we are the youth of a nation that
song you remember that remember that now yeah that's a good-ass song what's the
other pod song though it might I don't know I don't know much much pod that's
the main song I know pod a bo utl is team
pod you last oh you ever heard of them fire that does a lot of stuff about
clowning pod Dallas by gelato I forgot the last I was gonna look up pod to see
what other song it is I forgot the last thing I did today was joined pants dudes
discord is it mostly people who are fans it's yeah it's so funny like the like
genuine Oh alive that's the pod oh yeah so alive the pants dude discord is a lot
of people like I did consider like yeah totally people jack off to him what do
you mean yeah no yeah most well no guys I thought I thought it was so funny that I
I never like thought like yes of course people are jacking off to this dude he
is he is the giantest magic is dick yeah and the world is a perfectly upright he
is he penis yeah that's probably I wish my dick looked like that thing is big I
wish mine looked like that but it does not pop out like this well that's the
curse yeah that's the curse that's what you have a perfect penis but it pops out
at the worst times like when you're ordering at Subway or when you're
studying at Hogwarts. And also every pair of pants you have comes with a perfect
ripped seam. Yeah. That's just fails at the worst time. No I wouldn't do that. I would
do it dude. Because also like if you have a big ass fucking perfect. Yeah it'd be more
embarrassing if my thing was little. Yeah. Okay if we're not living in like a
fantasy world you're gonna go to jail. No you're you have to explain. You don't go to jail
for an accident. They're not gonna send you to fucking. You're gonna be killed.
You know who didn't go to jail for an accident?
We're not going to send you to Azkaban just because your pants flew off at the park.
Is a middle school or an elementary school.
Yeah dude, you're there too. You're in elementary school.
She's an adult. He's an adult.
You know who didn't go to jail for an accident? Casey Anthony.
True. She's still walking around.
And she had one of the worst accidents.
You would have a hundred accidents a day.
Are you calling her child an accident?
Yes. She didn't want, she wanted to stay partying.
You're right.
Honestly, I think she was dragging her down.
did I call her crazy Anthony? Wow. I call her crazy momthany. Yeah crazy momthany. I call her Carmelo.
I hear like you I say like oh you remember that that stuff in the news with crazy?
I call her Carmelo Anthony. Because she's because she uh loves twos but she hates threes.
She never sees threes but she sees twos and never threes. Sees threes. She sees ones and twos but
but she can't be out there with the threes.
- Yep.
- 'Cause her kid dies before she turns three.
- Yeah.
Remember the Nancy Grace,
did you guys watch that with your mom or was it just me?
- No, my mom, I think that--
- My mom loved Nancy Grace.
- My mom didn't know who Casey Anthony was.
- What?
- I like was talking, I brought up Casey Anthony
to my mom the other day. - That's crazy.
- And she was like, "Who's that?"
I was like, "What are you talking about?"
- That's insane.
- Isn't that crazy?
- My mom was obsessed with that case.
- I know, I feel like--
Like everyone's mom at least had an opinion.
That's crazy.
- Yeah, she literally had no idea who it was.
She had to look it up.
- Like everyone's mom at least said like,
well, I don't know.
- We were a little busy.
My mom was a little busy fighting Obama.
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah, doing spiritual warfare against Barack Obama.
- Yeah, my mom was like,
'cause I would come home and I would hear like,
innocent taught Kaylee Slane in the pool
at the back of her house.
- What year was that?
What year did that happen?
2007, 2009. Something like that.
Yeah, my mom was a little busy thinking about all of the kids and not just one kid
being put in FEMA camps because of the H1N1 virus.
Yeah, kids being torn apart and used for drumsticks.
My mom did think for a while that, she was like, "God gave me a vision. Obama's going to use swine flu to put Christians in FEMA camps."
And I was like, "Okay, sounds fun."
go to camp? Camp? That's badass dude, let's go. We get to go to camp for free? Is there
jet skis? I didn't get to go to camp as a kid, did you guys go to like any kind of
summer camp? I went to a church camp for three days, it was supposed to be a week
long, I went for three days because I was vegan and I could, they, they did not have
any food that was not like pizza. Yeah, you were vegan in the south. Yeah, so I ate for
three days, all I ate was pickles and Sun Chips. It was the only thing in the entire
camp I could eat. And then I started like vomiting like black bile and I left the camp.
I went to camp for a few years and I hated it so much I made my parents stop sending
me. My parents couldn't afford it. I used to run around in the summer. Yeah, running
around in the summer is good. Summer run around is very fun. I would not wear, when I was
from the age of like 6 to like 9, I would not wear shoes outside. I would just run outside
like hobbit feet. I got sent to this summer camp, it was like a tennis camp, but it was
like the high school. So we play tennis outside for like an hour or two or
whatever. And then we go inside to like inside the high school cafeteria to eat
lunch. And they'd like put a movie on like a tiny TV. And then it would just
be like, we just sit in the cafeteria for the rest of the day. You could draw
or you could watch the movie or you could eat your lunch and that's it.
Yeah, I fucking like my my younger brother used to not like we just
wouldn't wear shoes, me and Eric, and like, it would,
it got, he did wear shoes one time, he had this pair of DCs,
and there's that video of him breaking his arm.
They had to take his shoes off for some reason
in the room when he was like, you know,
they were checking out his arm.
- Pervy nurse, to smell his feet.
- Pervy nurse, yep.
- Yeah.
- We gotta take your shoes off.
- Dude, they threw his shoes out.
- They threw them out?
- They threw them out, I think they took them off
or something. - Like a gunshot victim?
- They took them off, or they like,
- They took him off. - Cut him off his body.
- Yeah, they took him off and like smelled him.
They went like, I could smell them.
And they're just like, Jesus Christ.
And just threw them out and he had to go home
in like little like slippers.
- Damn. - Whoa.
- They were DC Mantecas too. - That's disrespectful.
- They were my DC Mantecas that he was wearing.
And they had like, they were DC Mantecas
with like the panels and shit.
Had like little graffiti writing on them.
- And how old were you?
- I was nine.
- So you've always been like this?
- What?
shoes and shit. You remember the shoes you had when you were nine years old?
It's so funny. Dude, I don't remember.
Dude, my best pair of shoes I had. I don't remember a pair of shoes that were
on my feet until maybe three years ago. I had Vans Bucky Lasix. I think they were
Vans Bucky Lasix 5. Are you hearing this? This is crazy. As a nine year old, you were
aware of the shoes that you had. Black leather Bucky Lasix with like a gray
accent and after that right gray swoop the swoosh the van stripe and then after
that I got audio they weren't the BAMS which I was kind of bummed out about I
think their audio Kenny reads fucking nine I think they're Kenny reads yeah
yeah yeah they're black audios wait you just said was that from the ages of 5 to
nine you did not wear shoes and then you immediately went into to skating so I
do like no like like like I also have my friend Anson gave me a pair of the
at knees low cuts and then another Cali cuts you should wear shoes in the summer
but like once I started skating I paid attention to shoes and shit you should
have been out there fucking catching frogs in your mouth and shit I was with
wearing specific shoes. No, no. Then I started skating and then I stopped
running around. These are not compatible. One of these is a lie. Yeah, the devil did grab. You made a deal with the
devil. He said, "Do you want to be... do you want to have knowledge of all shoes?"
And the trade-off is knowledge of nothing but all shoes. Maybe. And he said
yeah. And he signed it with your tail that you had. Dude, I had like little
hobbit feet. It was so gross. You still have hobbit feet. Yeah, I do. I can pick things up
with them. Everyone can do that. Everyone learned how to turn on the TV with their remote.
I can write my name with my foot. Yeah, so can I. I can
actually jump. With your feet? I can actually jump off the ground.
What? That is sick. I can do a somersault.
I can do two somersaults in a row. You can't do a somersault.
Whoa, you got really close to your desk.
That's not a somersault. In what world is that a somersault?
That was a somersault.
Are you guys stupid?
What would you call a somersault?
That was a roll.
You rolled.
What's the difference between a roll and a somersault?
You have to jump onto your hands
and then dismount onto your feet for it to be a somersault.
That's a cartwheel.
No, a cartwheel is sideways.
A somersault is a forward cartwheel.
No.
You can't just roll on the ground and call it a somersault.
That's definitely what a somersault is.
You guys are stupid.
No.
You guys are not.
Well, you know a lot about gymnastics?
Yeah.
I used to go to tons of gymnastics birthday parties.
- Cheerleader. - I'm not a cheerleader.
- Cheerleader. - I'm like the big parachute
that they'd put you under.
- Oh, you know what else? - Cheerleader.
- 'Cause sometimes I would imagine me and the gym teacher
getting stuck in there.
- The Bucky Lazics, I had checkered laces.
- What?
Oh, that's cool.
That's really cool. - They had to distract you
from being mean.
- I was being mean?
- I threw a wrench at you.
- The definition of somersault verb,
to perform a somersault or make a similar movement
accidentally.
(laughing)
- I'll call it an accidental somersault.
If it wasn't a somersault, I didn't make a similar movement.
It was a similar movement.
Is that not what he did?
This is exactly what you did.
You did not do that.
You're literally stupid.
He didn't use his hands.
He just rolled on his head.
I used my hands.
I put my hands down before my head.
You just don't know what you're talking about.
You're not a gymnast like me.
I used to do tons of gymnastic stuff.
You're talking to me and the king of parkour.
I had a monkey ability.
I was into parkour way before you guys.
does not true still I was using to parkour no cameras really in the water
pro I was conging I Cameron on that video I would Kong I've seen his videos can't
jump I haven't I have he hasn't seen the other ones I would walk he's only got
the unlisted ones he watched he watched the one that you had that has the most
views and then denim is just yeah I've seen I mean a lot of them I can't put out
because it would just like skew the scene and a lot of people be mad at me
like there's a bunch of records I can't really break because I feel bad for like
the people to him climbing that I came up with you know he's so cool to watch
you see my 100 times flip off the Empire State Building probably not okay I can't
release that one cuz spider-man will get pissed off at me yeah you didn't do a
hundred times I know yeah I did a 100 times how's that even possible how'd you
see my 100 times pizza eat video oh dude his pizza videos are just as popular as
his parkour videos I have seen no piece I've seen the parkour but not any of the
pizza stuff. I haven't seen it. I haven't seen the pizza material you're
by now. You're doing a choking video for me right now in real life choked on
water.
It's thinking about delicious pizza.
He tried to bite it.
Dude, if you drink water and think about pizza while you're drinking it, it
will taste like yeah. That's a like water with your left hand. You feel like
a fish. Yeah,
that's true. I heard that yeah. I heard that sit on your throat before you
drink water.
It feels like someone else is drinking the water.
If you sit on your entire body for a while and then do anything, you feel like a ghost.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
That's why they call it the ghost.
If you sit on your phone for a little bit and then smell it, it smells like your butt.
I forgot that I put my mask in my back pocket.
Dude, that happened to me so many times.
I would put my mask in my back pocket and then have to put it on to go on the bus or
something and just--
And then smell your butt?
It's just toxic.
Yeah.
Really?
I would never put that in my back pocket.
thinking. Do you ever just smell the fart zone of your pants before you put them on to see
if they smell like the farts that you've been throwing in all day? Yeah. I love that. I
do that. I mean, you know. I love that so much, man. It gets me high. You don't love
that. It doesn't get you high. I love to smell my own farts. I love, the first sniff, you
weirdo. The first sniff of your own fart is great, but I do not want to sit in a room
that's filled with farts. I sit in my room. I hate the smell of my own farts. Dude, you
need to go get that checked out because you're supposed to be the smell of all
farts I sit in my room and I fart all day and I keep the door closed so they stay
in there so I'm just like even if the most beautiful woman farted near me I
would say what I hate other people's farts but my farts are like seriously
like dessert to me if a beautiful woman farted near me I'd say P you it's like
when you rub your hands all over your balls and then put them in your mouth
mouth yeah your balls not your hand oh it's tastes like hand my nasty ass hands
been touching doorknobs all day I wanted my balls man my hit my balls smell like
why do balls smell so bad I use I touch so much because it's just my hands it's
the sweat building up in the taint area plus the the butt juices are rolling
down to the taint area the butt juice is coming off the butt but my balls are
like the butt juice. It's like the center. It's like the central hub of a sewer area
where you fight like a slime monster. Yeah, so all my poop is your thigh. It's
the smell of your also the sweat from your thighs smell from your feet goes up
your pant leg. True. And into your balls. All smells travel. Every smell in your
body travels to your balls. It's like Delta Airlines in Atlanta. Yeah. Okay.
All right, now I get it. It's like a hub.
Yeah. All smells on your body can be linked back to your balls or vagina.
Vaginas don't smell that bad.
Vaginas smell horrible.
No, they taste and look and feel horrible. They smell okay.
They smell and the feeling and the look.
They're putrid. Vaginas are useless.
Yeah, they're pretty much...
Why does anybody ever want to...
Pretty much non-functional.
...do anything with a disgusting vagina?
Especially, you know how sometimes girls you can see their vagina from their from the back?
It's like that's I think it's a but it looks like a butthole. Yep. That's disgusting if I saw a vagina from the back
It's disgusting
It's next to your butt
It's like you have oh my god horrible. It's like I have two but I mean I got I have half a mind to pull out
A measuring tape and show you just how close it is and maybe you'll understand
I'm gonna pull out a square foot of sheetrock and close that puppy up.
I'm going down there with spackle.
Yeah, I'm gonna close it like John Taffer.
I'm condemning this disgusting...
This is how people get sick!
(laughter)
Shut it down! Shut it all down!
Look at this! You can see it from the back!
It looks like a second butt!
Look at this! There's old food in here!
I'm putting a manhole cover on it.
Dude, I fucking love John Taffer.
I love John Taffer.
I'm putting, um...
I've been getting back into Bar Rescue.
I just have been watching all the videos.
Yeah, dude.
There was one where there was a bar,
I told you there was an episode called
12 Beers a Slave.
Dude, so good.
Such a good name.
But then I was watching another one
that was about a bar where all the bartenders
were just like, had their titties and asses out,
and one of the bartenders was named Cheeks.
Mm-hmm, okay.
And she was getting her...
Dude, they ran a marathon on Paramount.
shots out of her butthole. Whoa. And I was like and there and he was like we have to
fix this bar. I was like that's the best bar ever. Dude some of the bars you go into. They seem awesome.
Yeah some of them on the show it's like like yeah like the food and shit is
nasty but like they'll have like some drink special that's like. And also a good
bartender is drunk as hell and gives you free stuff. Yeah. A good bartender is the
drunkest person in the entire bar. I don't want to go to a bar and have
somebody who's like worried about making their boss money. Yeah. Somebody if I go
to a bar and the person is like like oh yeah I know how to make like I know how
to make a vodka Lewis what the fuck is a vodka Lewis I just made that up. He always goes in there he
always sends Maria Menouonos in there and she gets like an like a Manhattan or an
old-fashioned yeah it's like these are all places that all they have is well
you get a gin and tonic. Why are you there? You don't get a Manhattan there. No.
They have Campari there to weed out people. Not to bring it back but that's like going to a baby food store and
ordering a lobster. Exactly, it makes no sense. Well that actually makes more sense
than going to a Taco Bell and ordering baby food because of the bib situation.
They have a kids menu. That's true. That actually makes pretty... yeah. You would go to a
baby food store, see the bib section. Yeah. Oh yeah. It must be a lobster store.
Yeah, but you'd still be wrong though. Yeah. You, they could... it's just an
understandable mistake. You could put lobster biscuit in a baby food jar. You
could put anything in a baby food jar. You could feed a baby a whole lobster. You
could feed a baby and he has been keeping up with Leon the lobster Leon the
lobster of the pet yeah no have you who's that just molted he molted oh
that's huge yeah it's pretty disgusting yeah I bet have you have you guys ever
do you guys follow the Instagram page world of snake no no it's a bunch of
videos of snakes and there are a bunch of like like little girls who have like
pet snakes in other countries and it'll be like a video of like just a giant
snake like not like a bow constrictor just like a big snake like not like a
thick one but just a normal snake yeah and it'll just be like just sitting on
their bed and there are a bunch of videos where you know how if they like
try to slither on some like surfaces they just they can't move forward so
they'll just be sitting on the bed and they'll just be going like they'll just
be wiggling just like going like and just completely just completely in place
on like a bed or a floor rug teach a snake to be cute and adorable you can
put a bow on around you wrap a bow around a snake's head. Snakes look pretty cute if
you look at a snake's just its face not its disgusting long body. Yeah. But just
its little eyes. They look kind of smiley. Yeah and they could make us if they could
put a snake's head on a frog. They're the same they're the same kind of cute that
like a mouse is I think. Yeah. They're fake they just have like they kind of
they have like like pink mouths. But then when they move around you're like yeah
yeah. Well not if they if they they're dancing on a bed that's pretty cool. That
is cool yeah yeah I'm gonna see if I can find we should have a snake in a basket
here we oh dude we need to get we need a snake a basket in a flute yeah and a guy
who can play the flute I can play this I'm not learning no I it's not what's
more of like a it's a recorder yeah recorder yeah I can play the recorder I
think we all can I can definitely play a recorder yeah press record yeah playing
one right now I want to play a comb whistle see that as me playing the
quarter that was not I want to play a comb whistle so bad cone whistle comb
whistle comb yeah comb all wet and you put a piece of paper on it check this out
you think this a cute snake with a bow on it right yeah I told you you can put a
bow on it that's like a sexy snake like why is it like why is that snake so sexy
to but like why do they put like a lacy bow on it that's her name
lacy lacy bow see that's like a stripper name yeah are they dressing up this
snake like a Frenchman. Wait, wait, like a strip club? They're like, all right, you know
her, you love her, coming next to the stage, Lacey Bow, and just a snake comes out.
It's like a big, like a basilisk. Basilisk comes out from the back. No, it's better if it's like a
rattlesnake. Yeah, it's a normal rattlesnake. Oh, a basilisk is not dangerous, okay. Well, it's not, I
guess it is dangerous, but it can be, but that wouldn't happen because a basilisk
isn't real unless you mean the lizard they're not in America yeah they're in
and they're definitely not gonna find a bad at Hogwarts in Magic City you're not
gonna find a basilisk in Magic City no Hogwarts yeah checkmate bitch yeah I've
been to Magic City the Hogwarts at Universal Studios yeah it's awesome uh-huh
I want to find this video so bad but I can't. I want to see the snake on the bed. I have had it with this
goddamn snake on my wife's bed. He says motherfucking snake. Not in the
fucking wife's bed. Not in the TV edit. Yep. I'm doing this. I've had it with these snake snake.
Whoa. Damn. Damn he got some fangs on him. That's not cute. He has some fangs on him if you ask me.
What is it? I got bit by a snakes thing. I just found out that frogs don't have cocks
Yeah, what does a snake have a dick? No, no, they have they have like a I
Think they have a thing where it like it like pops out like they have like a yeah
They all have like this
It looks the same from the outside
But then like the male snakes can like open it up and shoot their wiener out or something
See frogs basically just have an area that drops come they have a cloaca. Yeah
I felt I held a frog once and it peed on me or toad actually it came I want to oh
Yeah, I was trying to fertilize your hand. Yeah, maybe your hand looks very frog like yeah
Oh were you holding frog eggs while you were holding him?
He always had that might be he was holding them and I mean around like nuts and popping them into his mouth
It tastes you the caviar I I do think like that's the ideal sexual organ
Right is just what like being able to just like all that drops
- You know, just dump, like, any time,
like, you never have to jack off or have sex,
you just dump out cum whenever you want.
- Turtles, sea turtles can breathe through their cloaca.
- What?
- Yeah, you can through practice.
You don't have a cloaca.
No, no, you can breathe through your butt through practice.
- Really?
Try it out for me.
- Cagle exercises.
- Getting one, having one hold of poop, pee,
lay eggs, cum, and breathe.
- Why do I even need eyes, then?
It's like, just fucking, just make me,
I mean, we've done this. - Just make my whole body
the
they just have a lot of what I okay here if I think whoever so okay Elon Musk or
whatever yeah needs to build basically a giant like underground city that is
everything in in that city is designed like it will kill you if you're not
cube-shaped it will kill you if you poop and pee like you know it has to be like
like it has to be artificial evolution we have to whittle down the population so
only the people who are most like cloaca cubes survive yeah people have kids
generations after generations then well eventually have a cloaca like we just
need you know what I mean we need somebody we need to do we need to do
unnatural selection to design a cube that poops and pees and comes and breathes
and looks out of one no little arms no legs no eyes no mouth no you just
thoughts and and not even thoughts no need just just liquids and fluids and
semi fluids basically a piece of plastic a plastic cube filled with blood and a
hole on the top yeah it's kind of ideal yeah and well in glasses too if you need
them. Yeah, if you wear glasses, yeah.
Glasses to show he's a nerd.
And a jacket and a letterman jacket.
A monocle over the
cloaca part.
But yeah, like a perfect,
can somebody draw this up? A perfect
fleshy cube with just like a
receding
volcanic hole. And it has, it's like
skin, like it's not like a
gelatinous cube, like it's not like
from like D&D, it's not like slime.
It's flesh. It is skin.
Yeah, yeah, it's made out of skin. It's a cube, but it has right angles and points and like yeah parts of that
But as one clutters a single hole on the front yeah, and it looks weird
It looks weird. Yeah, but it would look it would look normal in the future
And I also if we're halfway through like some people are cloaca cubes and some people are still people
Yeah, what's it like a cube a flannel?
- Yeah, we'll get to like a cube with arms and legs.
- A flesh cube with flesh arms
and the front of the cube is a face.
- Yeah.
- But on the back of the cube,
that'll be like a missing link.
- That'll be like a missing link.
- That's like Bigfoot to them.
- And then when you can practice tattooing on the cubes.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause they won't, what are they gonna say?
- You can put a--
- You can do it any way you want.
- You could put more dots on other sides
and use them as a human dice.
- You could put a lyrist to holy diver
on the top of the cube.
- Yeah, just in case you forget them.
- Yeah.
you could pack your lunch in their brain. Yeah. Oh my God, you could put stuff in
them. Yeah. Oh my God, it can be like a Pez. Yeah, you could just put all your
stuff in. We need to trick everybody else to become in cloaca cube so that we
just have boxes we can use when we need to move. Uh-huh. Yeah. Or if we wanna do
holy diver karaoke with no backing track. Exactly. Yeah. And with no lyric
sheet. Yeah. 'Cause normally I'm like, holy something. You've been out too long.
me. Oh, what's not right,
but then if you had a right, the right, you get something you something
something holy diver
that song so good yeah dude that's like the best song ever is dead yeah such a
bummer yeah. He looked like a lunch lady. I like that he's in the tenacious d
movie, but he's so old, but he's like on his like poster, but like an old poster,
he's like really fucking old he's like 75. The thing about that song too that I
love is it's like it's so courageous to write just like the best song ever and
then give it one minute interrupts just silence yeah just just nothing so cool
oh yeah just make it annoying. Did Dio just make one good song? No no no no. What else did he do?
Like a rainbow in the dark. Invisible from that album is really good.
- Dude, Dio's Sabbath is good.
- Yeah.
- Dude, are you kidding me?
- Oh, I forgot he replaced--
- Yeah, you replaced Ozzy.
- Ozzy, yeah.
Yeah, Dio's good.
- Yeah, Dio is so sick.
- That album cover, sick too.
- Yeah, I wanna get--
- Is Ozzy a giant demon with chains?
- I wanna get that. - Is Ozzy alive?
- I wanna get that in my house.
- Definitely.
- Not like a poster, not like a painting.
Like, I want that demon in my house.
- Why did we lose Ozzy Osbourne as a cultural touchstone?
- He's probably, I mean, you--
Coronavirus, dude. People don't like eating bats anymore.
*unintelligable*
I miss it, dude. It was funny.
And then, oh, his daughter did become the view, though.
Although, did she get kicked off?
She said the thing... oh, that was so funny.
It was a sad news thing. Someone's dating his daughter now.
Right. Then who is gonna clean my trousers?
Oh, yeah. She said, "Oh, you wanna get rid of Mexican people?"
Who's gonna clean up all the bathrooms? Yeah, he's gonna clean up my disgusting farts and shit
He's gonna clean up my poop and fart people if you get rid of all the Mexicans
Who's gonna?
She's dating Sid Wilson from Slipknot. That's who it is. She's doing the DJ from Slipknot. Go DJ
Toxin in hotties crazy. Really? Yeah, he's like be jock. Yeah. Yeah, that's tight. It's really I'll show you a video after it's
There's a really good episode of the Osbournes where Jason Dill shows up
And he's like just just so zonked out of his mind
You just can't like like it's him like interacting with Ozzy, and he's like leaving stuff everywhere and Sharon's like
He's just like I don't I don't fucking I don't I don't know man
It's an awesome, awesome show.
Yeah.
It's like what if we got a guy who has Alzheimer's.
A guy who did like coke from like a fucking, like a guy who like drank cocaine.
A guy who's actively just dying in front of you.
What if we put him and his family and get this in their house?
In their house, their mansion where they have a tiny dog.
It's not like fish.
Dogs that shit everywhere.
There's no fish out of water aspect.
It's them just at the house.
chilling at the crib
yeah pomeranians that shit all over the floor yeah like
"I WANTED A POOPING ON THE FLOOR AGAIN"
I wonder if they if the the people the producers were just like
cuz they definitely weren't at the house like oh this will be great they just
saw him and they're like yeah I bet your house sucks
have you heard the
Jessica Simpson Ozzy Osbourne Christmas
the Jesse Jessica Simpson Ozzy Osbourne baby it's cold outside
No, I bet it's... I bet he really...
Dude, it is... it is fucking fire.
I bet he was chasing her around the studio.
But baby, it's cold outside!
That's beautiful.
You know how like later Ozzy, like,
it kind of... that kind of he's like Melodyne on his voice and you can totally tell.
Yeah.
The Melodyne... because he sings in one... he sings one note.
And like he's singing all that. It's like Jessica Simpson and then he's going like,
baby it's bad out there so sick you know they said melodyne to him and he would try to inject
it into his arm just just you you already were making a whining voice while i was doing ozzy's
voice i know you were pat you said something funny i just you know oh you don't get to hear
melodyne was a drug you got it you nailed it you would have heard it the first time if you
you were going wow how about that what's not just a song guess the song what do
it again for me I'm the man war pigs
sabba is that a sabaton song that is a reggaeton song okay is it is daddy
the Yankee? Reggaeton is my favorite war metal band. The Swedish war metal band.
It's called Reggaeton. Sabaton is sick. It's cool they just make songs about
like boats. Yeah. They just make songs about boats with cannons. You know what's sick
is Blind Guardian. They just all their songs are just about Lord of the Rings
and they're just like power metal so they're just they're still singing like
like just like all songs like that. It's like if Zeppelin was good. Sabaton has a song that
talks about specific giant ships that are in Germany or whatever and just how cool
they are. Yeah it's like they heard the wreck of the Edmund Fitzgerald and they're like yep this is
what music's about. They call it the beast of the seven seas. It's just been sitting in a dock
for 50 years and they're like that thing's fucking it's cool so. It's the coolest thing ever. The
music videos like the music the music video is actually an ad for world of
tanks
oh really yeah that's really fucking cool that's I mean that was that was the that
was the the sponsorship they were aiming for absolutely yeah world of yeah it's
either like yeah world of tanks or like that the the Nazi memorabilia museum
yeah some like rightist front thing
Some website.
Somebody left like the MTV like Pluto channel on and
I just heard like Alex and Neil just fucking dying in the living room
I was like I want to know what the fuck like I was like what the hell's going on here
I get up and I like went out and looked they were just watching a ghost music video
Dude, ghost sucks so bad. Yeah, that's the gayest shit of all time. I cannot believe people let go
like that goes I like I like I heard like
I'm not fan and blind Guardian fan ghost
is like that's like dire is ghost they
they the guy dresses up like a like a
zombie Pope and they sing like it's so
it's that actually sounds cool no if
you heard the music is it bad I've never
heard their music and I've seen like
their suits and shit I was like that
looks kind of cool and then I heard I
love things I like wear masks and stuff
but their music is just like yeah they
are dog shit I was like the worst band
ever yeah I was watching Miss Murder the music video this one I was so sick so
fuck I when I was a kid I thought music video I thought that Davey Havoc was
Marilyn Manson Davey Havoc looks so shitty in that music video he has like
so much makeup on I looked him up now he looks like a normal guy but he looked
terrible yeah he did not look good he has so much makeup on set a fi song from
pros do that fight before yeah before Miss Murder they were like a punk band
they were so cool I mean Miss murders it is murder so this murder is tight yeah
Halloween the the the AFI album cover from that song from the pro skater 3
song that shit goes crazy hard it looks like Halloween we see a start a band man
we need to you know we need to start up we need to start a pumpkin thing a thing
with pumpkins yeah okay what we do like a pumpkin we need to do we need to do a
pumpkin carving contest in the office I literally fucking destroy you know
probably would not know what I'm pretty good at carving a pony you're not you're
shit at it I'm actually not and you have a pumpkin carving contest next week guess
who's gonna have the better Walter White pumpkin me all right well you think so
I'm gonna get mad up though so you're gonna be pissed yeah well you get my
team fortress to pumpkins gonna destroy both of you I don't think so no I think
I think you guys are really going to like my myzoids. It's not any character from
TF2, it just says TF2.
In sharpie.
I'm going to do a Lena Paul pumpkin and everyone's going to love it.
Whoa.
Yeah.
Actually, I'm thinking about that now.
Tour tickets are at swagpoop.com/shows.
Is Lena Paul?
You mean Lena Dunham?
Nope.
That's who I was thinking of.
No, me too.
and
go to try to check out of the tour and uh... by yourself ticket is got a bunch
of cities on their budget gains as well but also our friends at home planet
about a year out fifteen feet away just started a picture and uh... where they
are posting go check it out show patriot dot com slash home planet the whole
planet show
the home planet very good very fun you'll ever say i don't believe me here
is a man
yes it is a somebody in this room and one of the three i was it was it
some guy with long hair.
Somebody!
The one who looks the most like a girl!
You're not, didn't I kill?
Bye!