you're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content!
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately!
[explosion]
Doth the beauty...
Oh, we need to write a poem.
Doth the beautiful beauty...
Doth the beer tea...
Doth the beer tea hath drinking of...
Homer...
Of lovely yellow Homer,
and sweet thy...
thy son Bart be him ever so mischievous.
And behested upon Marge is a gargantuan blue head of hair and
there was a child named Maggie.
Ah, the saxophone.
Avast ye, ye Homer.
The saxophone of Lisa doth play all night and all day.
Then sweet tunes echo through the halls of Moe's Tavern.
An ode to Homer.
Oh Homer, betwixt thy two hairs upon thine head, thy yellow
head sits on thy shoulders.
Yes.
Thy big fat stupid shoulders.
Oh Homer.
Thine, thine, thine duff doth flow.
- Let the duff flow and the--
- Donuts grow.
- Comic book guy is oh so fat.
And Linney, oh Linney the dark friend.
- Professor Frank, always he think.
- Yes, yes.
Dr. Nick doth scam the town's only man, Homer. Homer, you yellow bastard.
You yellow-bellied and rest of your body bastard. You have drank your
last duff. Oh, how... And now you will be... Now your life is enough.
And as the sun sets on the lovely land of Springfield, the Simpsons clan retreats to their couch.
That was beautiful.
We've all been standing like it was the Pledge of Allegiance for this whole thing.
We have a conga drum in the corner of the room, but we haven't been playing it.
That's what people do at Poetry Slams. They snap after poems.
I don't know.
I don't know how you do it.
You snap it back.
Don't don't snap like that. Why? I think you go like this. You snap like in someone's face.
You can't shake. No, you're doing a face with it too. I think a lot of people...
What's wrong with that? A lot of people after they hear a poem too will like
snap in the other person's face and go, "Excuse me!" Really? Yeah, that's kind of a
thing people do at Poetry Slams too. We should go to a Poetry Slam tonight and be the best, do the best etiquette of all time.
Well, we don't have to go to a Poetry Slam tonight because we got one right here right now.
Yeah, that's a really good point. Yeah. I feel like we need like a... we do... we should have
brought a fucking just like a snare drum. That's what I was saying, we have a conga drum in
the corner but it's broken. It's broken because we were playing with the butterfly knife over
the conga drum. It happens. And both times we hit both drums. Yeah and it popped my ear
drums out. Yeah. I can't hear much. Thine ear drums. Thine ear drums shall be popped.
Oh poetry I love it so. Poetry is kind of like my one true love in this world. I'm basically
poetry all the time even when I'm at the deli and I'll say cigarettes I can have
like yoga I might it's kind of like talking I'm gonna have an early night
yeah I did on my first chopped cheese today
liked it. How was that chopped cheese? It sparkled for my stomach like a star
possessed. Ahoy matey!
God, I love poetry. There once was a chopped cheese from Bodega and it was
delicious.
I say yeah. Damn, I'm gonna call you. I'm gonna call you William Steaksbeard.
had inside it had cheese and ingredients please.
Hey, Ock, let me get a chopped cheese with the ingredients on it.
And that was the chopped cheese Ock made, yeah.
Wow, you're a veritable Shel Silverstein.
Yeah, my specialization in poetry is mostly limericks.
You know how like in like Hogwarts you can do all the different types?
I went to poetry school and I chose limericks.
You're a dimwit.
No.
I wouldn't say that.
Okay, never mind.
Sorry, I don't have a specialization.
Thy insults fail thee, my dim-witted friend, with his head so shiny and his brain so small
and a smelly hiney and tiny balls.
See, you and smelly balls.
I don't have tiny balls.
They're humongous.
I don't know about that.
It's like a walnut in the shell.
All right.
Well, let's get in.
Speaking of balls and such, I'll kick off our poetry slam here.
Oh yeah.
This is a very special...
Oh, I shared mine with you because there's some photos that I think you need to see.
You can...
Here, it'll be easier if you do it from your phone, if that's okay, I think.
Yeah, I'll just show the...
Yeah.
Okay, so this is a website called allpoetry.com and these are some just brilliant poems that
people have written that we wanted to share with you guys today on our very special premium
episode. This is a poem by Magic Light named "A Wiener in Winter" and this is, I
mean, this is simply enchanting. I'm trying to think of where this could go.
Let me, let me, let me read this to you guys. I see so many welders, they're busy
as can be, helping the brass monkeys. It's as cold as it can be. With record snows
and chilling winds blowing from the east. It's coming from Siberia, they're calling
it the beast. Wieners just don't like it, as every man will tell, for they retract and
disappear like a snail into its shell. All shriveled up, it hides away, won't raise its
ugly head. The cowardly little worm-like thing looks like he's fucking dead. He's not so brave
and hard now, 'cause the weather's really cold. Won't stand up to attention, even when
he's fucking told. He's curled up in my Calvin Klein's, he's really lacking guts. Just like
a squirrel, he hibernates and clinging to my nuts. I've even tried to coax him out with
of Pornhub we would view.
He keeps his one eye firmly closed.
Now that is something new.
I'll check the weather forecast to see how long this lasts
'cause I can't have a wiener that's afraid of chilly blasts.
I pray that soon a thaw will come and melt away the snow
with a sigh of great relief.
They don't want us to read this.
- They're trying to shut it down already
'cause the poetry could change the world and they know it.
- True.
I pray that soon a thaw will come and melt away the snow
with a sigh of great relief.
I'll watch my wiener grow.
No longer I'm embarrassed as he often looked deceased.
I've now nicknamed him Lazarus.
He has risen.
He's the beast.
- Whoa. - Damn.
- Mm-hmm. - Stop.
- What? - Stop doing that.
- No, it's disrespectful to say mm-hmm after a poem.
You just snap. - Why?
- You just don't. - It's just the etiquette.
- Have you been to a poetry slam?
- No. - What?
- God damn it, you just don't know etiquette, I guess.
- That's what I do after I eat something good, too.
- Really? - Yeah, I go to Allgarden.
- I've never seen you do that.
- I get a pasta fagioli.
I haven't seen you do that either.
You haven't seen me do that?
No.
Well, it's good I never swallow when I'm around you guys.
Sure, yeah.
Yeah, you spit into a napkin.
Well, I just like, yeah, I just like chew with my mouth open and let it all kind of
fall out.
That is true.
Whenever we eat at a restaurant also, you do also ask us to go to the bathroom after
we're finished eating.
Yeah, not me go to the bathroom.
I ask you guys to go to the bathroom.
Yeah, exactly.
I mean, I like doing stuff for my friends, so I always do it.
And then I kind of spit my food out and put it in different places and like kind of curl
napkins up to make it look like I ate all of it.
Yeah.
I push my belly out like I'm pretending to be pregnant.
I actually, I usually bring a pillow with me.
I put the pillow under my shirt and I say,
oh, mm-hmm, I'm so full.
- All right, who's reading the next poem here?
- I have a poem here.
This is a poem by Shannon Norman.
And Shannon Norman has a very specific style of poetry
where she finds Halloween costumes on Google Images.
Okay. And writes poems about Halloween costumes. I mean, inspiration can come from
anywhere. That's the beautiful thing about poetry. So this poem by Shannon is called
Popeye's Sexy Sister. All right. She's a sailor, sexy smart with a mouth that'll
make you blush. Wearing those tight shorts with stilettos, not an ordinary
lush. That sailor hat is just too cute. Worn with a nice striped blouse, you won't
have to scrub the deck you're an ace that's in the house Wow
stars indeed 64.99
sexy Papa that's where the thing about thing about cum cum per dollar though
yeah that's a high ratio that one that one was kind of short but she also has
another poem here it's okay the same vein yeah this one is sexy pirate gal I love
I love the titles, they're so evocative.
"Careful where you aim that pistol, sexy pirate gal.
Some will like your badass look and call you a great pal.
I think your boots are thick and slick and I dig your hat.
That pirate garb has sex appeal, but everyone knows that."
True.
Wow.
Well, that one hit me.
Yeah, that one hit me right in my soul.
I'm crying a little bit.
I'm drooling.
I'm crying because I don't know what is happening to me.
Yeah.
My body.
It's like, I mean.
Sweating a lot too.
I mean, you weren't sweaty at all when you walked in, but you're soaked.
I'm crying from my body.
One of your arms is really red.
Yeah.
That's a reaction.
Which one?
I see like a Hulk vein popping out on your arm too.
Yeah, the other one was green.
Now I see it.
So I found this guy, I'm gonna read a few of this dude.
Yeah, of course.
Because this is kind of telling this whole story I would say.
So I was looking for weed palms and this guy has a, his name is Joe Fetick.
What are you honking at?
I'm in here.
You know where I am.
Fuck dude, stop.
I'm trying to read.
Alright, I'm just gonna, we're gonna pretend that's a nice drum line in the back.
It's just, you know.
It's atmosphere.
the tone. This is Joe Fettig and his, let me see if I can read his bio for you guys real
quick. He's kind of the man I was looking, oh yeah, okay. I'm a self-published writer
from Redmond, Oregon. I've self-published six books so far. If you enjoy reading my poems,
feel free to follow. I write poetry to express my thoughts and express my emotions about
various mini-subjects. If you find my poetry interesting, you can buy the books on Amazon.
So here's the books that he has listed.
The Red Pill eBook, True Patriot eBook, True Patriot Paperback, Ghostwriter Self Publish
eBook and Paperback in Large Print, Dark Ages Self Publish eBook, Dark Soul Poetry.
So I found his poem about weed.
Here it is.
It's called Old School Stoner.
Okay.
I'm an old school stoner.
I remember wearing tie-dye shirts back in the day.
Smoking out of a metal pipe then, I would listen to some reggae.
Those were the days I would only buy an eighth of weed.
Smoke it up that night, that was all I need.
Things have changed now.
I can go to the dispensary and buy one ounce.
Buy the top shelf quality weed, then bounce.
Everything is legal now.
Oregon is a green state.
Let's go smoke a bowl now.
Time to medicate.
So that was the first thing I found.
That's really beautiful.
And I found another just beautiful poem from him.
This is called Asian Beauty.
(laughing)
- Wait, did I show you guys a picture of this guy?
- Yeah, let's see here.
- All right, he's there.
- Oh yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
- He's wearing a thin blue line shirt
that says, "Men going their own way."
- Oh, wow.
That's awesome. - Yeah, he's awesome.
- It's one of the coolest--
- Hold on, can you find that shirt for me?
- I might try.
This is Asian Beauty, five months ago.
"She was an Asian beauty.
"I couldn't help it, I just fell in love.
"Tired of going my own way sometimes.
"Deep inside my heart, I wanna find true love.
She is so soft-spoken, elegant and sweet.
She's girlfriend material.
It's time I turn up the heat.
Romance is in the air as the sushi flies off the plate.
[Laughter]
I just wanna be with you.
Let me take you on a date.
I can teach you the way of love.
All you have to do is open your heart.
You're the woman I need in my life.
You're my sweetheart.
I see you looking at me.
Come closer to me when you look into my eyes.
Let me kiss you out of the blue.
Give you a sweet surprise.
I want to get you to know you more. One day you could be my wife. The power of love, the
lessons we learn in life." Okay, so then this is where it takes, unfortunately...
Everyone can relate to that.
Yeah, I mean everyone's been there. So tell me if you can relate to this one. This one's
called "I also am one blowjob away." This seems a little more aggressive, so I'm going
to give it something here.
Okay.
"I am one blowjob away from leaving the plantation. Men go in their own ways, growing across the
the nation. Feminism has destroyed relationships. How the fuck am I going to date? You have become
so toxic and masculine I can't even call you my soulmate. You can't even give me a blow job. You're
supposed to do it every day. That's why you can't keep a man. I'm gonna leave you. I'm not gonna
stay. You're so focused on your money and your career. I don't care about your success. You just
want to ride the cock carousel until you're 40 then expect someone to save your mess. I'm not
I'm not going to marry you and risk to lose half my shit.
I'm just going to end our relationship,
then call me a hypocrite.
You want me to make all the sacrifices
while you haven't changed, you have made none.
You're too busy playing with your phone on social media,
talking to other guys while I'm done.
I'm just one blow job away from leaving the dating scene.
I need to focus on myself more,
become a money making machine.
If she is not giving you a blow job,
tell her it's required on the first date.
If she refuses and doesn't submit to you,
break up with her and set her straight.
- By Joe Fatigue.
- God damn, Joe.
- Ooh, Joe.
- I mean, there is, there is,
I'll read this one later.
- Okay.
- I'll read, all right, yeah,
we'll go around once and then I'll read another one.
- I'm gonna, I have some collections
of some really talented poet.
Oh, this mic just stopped working for a second.
I have some collections of some really talented poets
that I also found, but I'm gonna read just a one-off here.
This one, I think, is, this is another thing
It's an issue I think a lot of people have dealt with in their life.
So I was wanting to help Trinity0513 speak some truth to power here.
So this is a poem entitled Spanish Teacher.
I absolutely hate my Spanish class, the reason why I'm about to amass.
At first I enjoyed it, there was nothing wrong, until a new teacher came along, one by the
name of Vivian Docobo.
I'm convinced she's actually loco assigning us work. I'll do in an hour.
Her expression is always dour only giving certain kids extra credit
something good. She will never say it. She says she treats everyone the
same. Honestly, she brings this whole school to shame project to sign
day after day and active caring. She will never display. She's white
not even Hispanic and frankly, she's rather satanic doesn't even
have an accent. It always says y'all just being in her class makes
me ball. I'm going to stop now before I say too much. If you want
want to keep listening to me rant, I'll be sure to keep in touch. All I have to say
is don't take my words for granted. Hopefully, your knowledge has expanded.
Learning about my bad Spanish teacher, I bet now you don't like her either. I
don't like Mrs. Dokebo. Mrs. Dookiebo? Oh, Mrs. Dookiebo. I do actually. I forgot.
This person does this. I'm, you know, I'm, I'll just read one more by this
person. Oh, yeah. 'Cause this is a similar topic here. Pate math teacher. I thought
my teacher would be great, but instead, it was Pate. This woman fills me with
Her breast smells horrible and this woman should obliterate.
I'm shocked she isn't overweight.
Have you seen how much she's ate?
The bell rings and she tells us to wait.
Like bitch, I'm not about to be late.
And then they repeat it.
If you don't get it, just let me restate.
This one is kind of bars.
Yeah, it is.
You know, this one's kind of a little bit bars.
I agree.
I think that's kind of what poetry is about, is bars.
I mean, yeah.
Poetry is kind of, yeah, poetry is bars.
William Shakespeare had bars.
Yeah.
That's what my teacher told me at my inner city school.
- When he came, when he taught there for two weeks?
- Yeah. - The substitute.
- Substitute, yeah.
- Yeah, well you went to the school of rap.
- Yeah, I did. - Yeah.
With blackjack.
(laughing)
Oh my god, dude. That's like, that's the modern like, the starving games that we need.
That's the new like, parody at the school.
Blackjack.
Oh fuck, I'm so good sometimes.
Okay.
I have a poem here from, this is a poem from Demon Lover.
Oh god.
And let me show you guys his photo real quick. That is Demon Lover.
Oh my god, he's got full Darth Maul makeup.
Yeah, he's in a... well, it's like a reverse Darth Maul,
'cause he's like red with black on his face.
He's like the insidious monster.
This is his bio.
"Hello, I am Mike Leap. I'm 22 years old. I live in Pittsburgh.
I'm engaged to my beautiful wife, Cherise.
We've been together for four years and still counting.
I already had an account on here, but I created this one
because I can't remember my password and username.
But yes, if you want to know more about me, please go ahead and message me.
I'm very easygoing and friendly.
And oh, my profile picture is my face painted from Halloween this year.
Here's his poem.
Yeah, an angel and a demon forbid in love.
Okay.
Yeah.
I mean, you only imagine right?
Yeah, I am a demon from the depths of hell, but you have captured me in your
spell.
You are an angel that fell from the sky.
I have caught you and help you to fly.
You are an angel with all your beauty, for I will protect you because it is my duty.
I am a demon with my dark charm.
You have helped and held my arm.
I am a demon with wings like a bat, and have dark eyes almost like a cat.
You are an angel with beautiful white wings, shining so bright like a diamond in rings.
We glide through the sky and through the clouds, past the sun and all the crowds.
Our love is said to be forbidden, but we shall not be hidden.
An angel and a demon that we are, but our love for each other will take us far.
There is one more thing before I go, for I know our hearts will forever glow.
So I think a lot of his things are demon-themed.
Yeah, well that was gorgeous.
I mean I could tell you were I mean captured by fits of emotion even halfway
through the poem. I was crying. You know when you see someone doing some kind of poetry and they're like
like between the whole lines right? They're like...
We need to do that. Yeah. I have actually you know I have some emotional ones
coming up. Really? I don't know if you... I have another one from the demon lover here.
I'd love to hear more from demon lover though. Because this is uh... It's interesting that he is a
demon but he's... He's a demon and a lover. Yeah. So he doesn't love demons he is a
demon. He's a demon lover. Oh. And this next poem, this next poem will, yeah, like
like he's a demon who has sex. This next poem really, really illustrates it. Okay.
Really gets the point across. Yeah, let's hear it. It's called "Love is my drug."
They can get high smoking what the will, maybe even pop a pill, cut some lines and
then snort them up, or maybe even take a syringe and shoot it up, but love is my
drug. They can drink a few beers and have a good time but all I will ever need is
for you to remain mine. They can laugh and shout and do what they want but love
is my drug. They can do any drug that they may see but all I can ask for you is to
stay with me. Love will never kill you it will make you want more but that's not
bad for without love in the world I would be sad love is my drug that I take and it
will never be a mistake for I can take as much as I please just like the air that
I breathe love is my drug I think I'm coming out of my writer's block now so
yeah tell me what you think I mean that's good dude it's yeah clear than
I mean that's how he feels you know and that's what the important part of poetry is.
Absolutely.
Talking about how you feel.
Yeah.
So speaking of, so this is one last one by Joe Fettig.
Okay.
Yeah.
So the last one was One Blowjob Away.
You guys remember that?
Oh I remember it.
So this one is Two Blowjobs Away.
You ready?
There's a sequel?
I'm ready.
Two Blowjobs Away.
Or is this a prequel?
It came out after so it is a sequel.
But it has to be a prequel. Yeah, unless he yeah, you're right. He's yelled out. Does that make sense?
I am to blow jobs away from leaving the plantation does she spit or swallow?
I am the dominant one so you need to get on your knees and follow
Why have one blowjob a day when you could have to?
She needs to suck that dick until her face turns blue
She wants to be loved but is she swallowing the sperm sucking fuck every day
We can make this relationship long-term get your ass butt naked
I'm gonna smash that pussy in between the sheets you better submit to me
Or I will throw your ass back in the streets you dream about having romance and love
I just want sex I pull your hair and bid your ass over then I put on the latex
Smashing that ass I'm making you moan loving that good dick. I'm gonna make you sweat all night
You are an obedient side chick. I pull out then you start sucking my dick waiting for that eruption of joy
Swallow my sperm. I know you're a freak. I am your fuck boy
I am to blow jobs away from taking the red pill hookers are cheaper than girlfriends. That's the power of free will
damn
Wow, dude, why I mean why I have two jobs or why have one blowjob a day when you can have to I think he wrote
One is a job
To blow job
Fuck I'm lowballing here. I got a
Yeah, two blowjobs is three times better than one blowjob
Yeah, that was very powerful. I yeah, I mean also how you can you disagree with that right really?
Is better than one and it's better than zero, you know to blow jobs and it's worse than three. It's much worse
It's three. I'm gonna be walking around exhausted all day
Like I just come I come three times a day all out of me
I might as well just eating Thanksgiving dinner
Like I'm just walking around just like holding my body. Yeah, just like oh
I just sit down. I don't even watch football sit down on a couch fall asleep watching football
That's what I have absolutely have to walk around with my belt loosened like yeah
I'm unbuttoning the top button and shit
That's a I mean coming three times a day is just that's too much. It's just gonna bad zone. It's way too much
much. I have two poems here that I'd like to share in a row. They're by different
authors, but I feel like they make good companion pieces.
Okay.
This first one is by the user Angel of the Shadows, who I'll just read their bio
for you. I think it's a really... The bio is kind of a poem in itself.
Oh, okay.
I am a dark being. Most people do not know me because they are afraid. Just one
little tip, do not try and hurt me or my family without knowing what I'm capable
of. And this poem is called Phantom, and this is an acrostic poem where the first
the letter of each line spells something out. So you know it
doesn't say like the let all just like I'll say like P is for
you know, but it doesn't say that in the poem just so you
know, so everyone at home can understand what's going on here.
P is for painful moans be whale H is for haunts torment a is for
awful tragedies mumble and is for nameless horrors. Howell t
is for threatening yells shout. Oh is for observant phantoms
own and M is for major scares bother
and then this this other one I'd like to read
the title is poem is breakfast by blue moon boy. He looks like a very nice
young. He looks really sweet
and I believe these poems are kind of like a yin and yang. They show the two
sides of life. Can you read his bio? Yeah, hi there. I am blue moon boy and I
love to write and read. I live in the country India and I'm an 11 year old
kid. So here's breakfast by Blue Moon Boy
hot fresh pancakes drizzled with maple syrup with warm white milk served in a
long large cup
a scrumptious cheese sandwich and finally at last to yummy tasty biscuit
is my idea for breakfast
then his comments prompt is "what do you mean by breakfast?" right in the comments
yeah he I mean he's very talented yeah he's kind of a prodigy yeah oh yeah I
think that's the phantom or the demon what's his name angel of... he needs to
take... angel of darkness needs to take him under or Blue Moon Boys needs to take angel of
darkness under his wing. I think they could both teach each other a little bit
about my demonic breakfast. Two evil eggs served hell side up. It has to spell
something. Bacon deep-fried. That's true. Imagine if that poem had spelled breakfast. In lava.
One cup of blood orange juice and two pieces of toast and they're burnt too.
That was a poem by me. That was beautiful. You should be the Hell Breakfast Boy.
The Hell Breakfast Boy. I have another, I have a poem here. This is another person who
just looks at like a photo and then writes their poem based on the photo.
A picture is worth a thousand poems. That's what people say.
It's a gift. Poems are terrible. Let me read her bio first.
Actually, I don't need to read this bio. It's not that good. There is just like a bunch of
photos. Oh that's beautiful. Yeah it's a very beautiful, there's a picture of a butterfly.
Oh look how beautiful that is. Yeah, but the photo that this is a, this is a kind of a raunchy
poem it's called XXX Wham Bam Thank You Lamb and the inspiration for this poem was a gif
of Kermit the Frog fucking a lamb puppet. And let me just get right into this. Intraspecies
coitus never results in a foetus. I'm just trying to make the rhyme work.
It's a fetus. Yeah. So it saves sex in at least one way and it's got to make for
unique play but you got to watch which species you choose and the precautions
that you use. So there's this horny frog his dick was feeling like a log. I mean
that hopping boner would just not go away he'd been hanging at his pad but he got
to feeling bad so he went out for some so he went out looking for some illicit
intercourse he spelled illicit wrong with dick in hand he sailed forth and soon
came upon a horse but he found out that he couldn't hop that high so reluctantly
he turned away by telling the horsey bye-bye swinging his head his way and
that as his boner grew more fat. He almost settled on a big disgusting sow then his
eyes lit up and he shouted, "Oh wow!" He had spied a sweet little lamb. He grabbed it
and then bam bam wham wham bam with a sigh he pulled out saying, "Thank you lamb."
and the comment prompt is what do you think that's pretty good that's
disgusting you it was a good it was a good story that says a man I don't know
I'll applaud just for the pic poems good too so this is from so there's this
this person pink fairy 5 on here uh-huh and I was looking at her profile and she
has like probably a thousand. I did see this person. Really? Yeah, every section you
look at this person's all over the website. It's crazy. Yeah, power user. She has
like a thousand poems and a large chunk of them are about her husband walking up
behind her and grabbing her 44 double D breasts. Like there's like probably
30 different poems and they're all super super long. Yeah. So I didn't pick them
out because it's really just it's just like my husband grabbed my breasts and
just kept holding them so this is one that she has that was between so it was
sandwiched on her profile between two of those it's called not always a symbol of
evil mm-hmm the swastika was not always a symbol of evil but once it became one
there was no turning back that's the entire
And she immediately right after wrote another one about her husband grabbing, this one was
he was pretending she had a tick on her breast and then he grabbed it and then she started
holding her.
That's really something.
Kind of a beautiful relationship.
It kind of is.
Because poetry is about love but it also is just love.
Yeah absolutely.
Now that one was kind of silly.
I do want to read a more serious one if you guys are down with that.
A little bit sad.
This one's called At The Gas Station Pumps.
Oh, okay.
By Brian Shaw.
Across from me, she looked at me like I was a ghost or something.
I know I look different with long hair.
I'm skin and bones and lost at least 20 pounds, but can you stop staring at me, please?
It seems like you're looking right through me, even though three years ago we were sharing
a bed together watching the world crumble to pieces in the movie Idiocracy on Netflix.
where the hell were you when my world was crumbling all around me? She had all my
social media, my phone number. I'm sure she heard all about my long battle with
COVID. Everyone in this community has. The least she could have done was said
something, waved, talk to me, but some things are too hard these days.
That's kind of written like a tool song right there. It's like the...
yet it is a beautiful like the way that it is a nice to look at you know
it's very gorgeous it is a gorgeous one ninety ninety spoken word poet
uh... poem here this is by uh...
by cats meow
uh... in the title is madonna's at it again
and uh...
the c cats now doesn't have a bio but he's a he's an old man from england
nice of the u_k_
And this poem is, Madonna's at it again.
I see Madonna is ranting again and being bitchy.
No wonder her 20 husbands have pissed off, including Guy Ritchie.
Saying that she'd like to blow up the new president in the White House.
She's used to blowing off men in the wrinkly old shite house.
You should see her scream and shout.
Does she want the publicity because she's got a crappy album coming out?
With her champagne lifestyle, she thinks herself smart.
But she has all the eloquence of a horse's fart.
Oh my god, don't go there.
Inspiring. Very funny, Michael.
Whenever I see her, now, it will be a horse fart.
Alright, I'm going to do this one and then I just remembered one that I'm going to try to find here in a minute
that I think you guys will really like. Speaking of old British men. Okay. But this one is
this one is actually because like we talked about like like rap is poetry. Absolutely. It is a kind
of poetry. So this one is by Papa Mama Jama. Okay. And this is called rap. Okay.
Hola Papa Mama Jama the great alpha wolf lyrical gangster, alma chocolate maestro extraordinaire,
Mastering the art of oratorial cornucopia
Charismatic syntax, lethal friction
Hot, sweet, and rolling off the tongue
The celebrity of dictation and sight deliberation
In the prefrontal cortex region (head)
And until they pass him oratorium, banning oral
He got them shaking and gyrating, begging for more
Verbal ambrosia, from sea to shining shore
He's giving love to the wannabes who don't want yore from yore
He was it, Shakespeare who said
They tryna muddy the motherfucking water
To make their shit rhymes sound deeper
know my mistake that could have been Eminem or Tupac who said that anyway
it's something remotivally relevant don't just squawk and grab your vacuous
ball sack. I want to read after reading that rap I would like to read his bio
absolutely let's hear it oh wait where yeah okay let's see I find poetry
sites inspiring for the most part it can be hard to stay motivated to write
reading helps and feedback is always welcome site for me I've posted over 250
poems on another site and I promise to not renter old poems as I want to keep
motivated to write new ones I'm looking forward to being on here and I'm open to
criticism for my work very open to suggestions so please don't be shy I
consider myself a student who very much wants to learn and get much better
looking forward to meeting the great artists on here cheers to all of you
they kind of got two sides yeah you got the rhythm and then you got the poetry
yeah I've got I've got some with two sides here too actually this is from user
Better not be Dr. Jekyll.
Whatever666.
Which, check out this profile picture.
Oh my god.
Man, he really doesn't give a fuck.
He's fucking scary, bro.
She's fucking scary.
I'll read this.
I have two poems I'll read from Whatever666 to kind of showcase her two sides.
This one is called "Am I Still Yours?"
I'll be found in the fraggle tube.
My curly smarkle laugh is gone.
Toot-a-roo, we never said again.
Thought we'd go to Farklip.
Didn't even make it to Snoodleflurp.
go to woozen fart split in whamper slip. We're in our
booble right full of a mess. It's a shame of Humper Wump from the
Uzi Wuzi. I had though. I'm dead. Am I still your girl?
So that's that's am I still yours by whatever 666 and then I
like to segue immediately into don't ask questions. If you
can't stand the truth in poetic form. Okay, here we go. This
one's a little bit long, but I think you're gonna I think it's
worth it. If I could kill someone and get away with it, yes, without a doubt. If I had the
chance to change anything in my past, I would charge up to my birth father and yell, "Fuck
you," to his face. Is there a God? Yes, I believe there is, but we've shut him out of our daily
lives. Then wonder why God's not there when we want him to be. As for what I think the
afterlife life is like, peaceful bliss, belonging. As for my opinion on the meaning of life,
live it to the fullest. Do what others say you can't to push the envelope without being
illegal. Am I pro or anti-gun? And why pro-gun? Because I want to be able to defend myself.
Secondly, it's our right to bear arms.
In the event of martial law, I would go off the grid.
The government keeps screwing things up
while murders get out of jail free.
Would I cheat on my other half if could?
I don't have to worry because I'm never, never,
never, ever going to get a boyfriend or get married.
If my soul was mirror, would I like what I saw?
Probably not.
I don't even like what I see in an everyday mirror.
For the poor pedestrian I hit on that deserted road,
I told not just whoever may read these words,
but also the authorities on the next town I entered.
As for parallel universes, yes, I believe in them.
As for what they're like,
Well in this universe you might be fat, so in the parallel world you're thin, yet in another
you might be all muscle, you might be rich or a bum.
If I've ever seen a ghost or experienced a supernatural event, well, I used to live in
a haunted duplex in Waterloo, Iowa, the ghost was cool, picture frames would be moved back
the way they were before they were dusted.
As for what I would do if I had five minutes left to live, that's easy, I'd write my will
with slop job handwriting, leaving it for the family and friends to decipher.
If the cost of one thousand strangers lasted to delay my own death or a loved one's life,
No, I would rather die on that day of my death than to sacrifice others
And no, I'd rather have to say goodbye to my loved one than one thousand strangers
No, I haven't ever experienced true love
In order to know it was true love, I'd have to be in love
And not just asked out on a prank or wanted just to have sex
When asked if I believe animals have souls, I invariably answer
Yes, just look into their eyes and you'll see there's unconditional love
If reincarnation is true, I think I was a woman who was murdered for being a smartass to the men
And I think I will be even more of a smartass in the next life
As for believing in aliens, yes I do
There's so much space that we can't explore due to radiation that will kill us outside Earth's atmosphere
And when asked how corrupt is our government, it's very corrupt.
Why else does money talk as bullshit walks?
I'll do those bastards in office.
At last, love is like a vampire, drains the life right out of you.
Oh my fucking God Almighty, dude.
I love that she threw in that she hit a pedestrian with a car.
Well, just yeah, like, yeah, she was so wracked with guilt that she had to tell somebody
and she was like, I'll sandwich it between this shit.
Very smart to put it in the middle of the poem
so that people who are just skimming it wouldn't notice it. Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, no it was very, it was beautiful. I have a poem here. This is somebody
that I found. Her name is Miss Sexy. You found her? Yeah, I found Miss Sexy. Damn.
And her profile picture is a photo of her with the word sexy on top of it, like kind of like Kendrick
Lamar "Damn." Oh yeah, it does look like that. She is sexy. Yeah. She's got platinum hair. And
And here's a poem by Miss Sexy called,
I have two poems by Miss Sexy,
one of them's very short,
and this one is more of an introduction to Miss Sexy.
So these are Miss Sexy's icebreaker poems.
This one is She's So Sexy by Miss Sexy.
She's absolutely marvelous.
The way she talks is just so unique.
Her words are like chocolate, so creamy and sweet.
She's so sexy from her head to her feet.
perfection she's good enough to eat miss sexy is her name absolute is what I
called her if given a chance I would pamper and love her damn she's so sexy
she's so fine a work of art so pure and divine I wrote this poem from the depths
of my mind so pardon me if it doesn't rhyme but damn she's just so sexy damn
dude that's fucking me up you know podcast about list this is a list
that she wrote my top five number one sex don't you know me by now number two
money always trying to make a dollar number three my babies what mother
doesn't number four my man want sex there's no punctuation there so I don't
know if that's like like a got milk yeah like right and number five you always on
my mind. Damn. Does her man know about that list? I hope her man doesn't know about number
five. She sent her man a poem that was called my top four. So I found this guy, his name
is Grey Wolf 1957. Ah, chapel fan. Yeah. And his, he has 1800 poems on here. Wow. He's
a metal worker. He lives in the UK. He says that he's been a slave for 20 years and
that he's going to keep being a slave until he dies. And this is one of his...
this is one called "Love is a Fragile Flower Opening to the Warmth of Spring."
Okay, I already like this. This is a short one. "That warmth turning into fiery
flames, strong emotions that weave overwhelming joy, that amazing moment
when it dawns upon you, when your heart begins to collect what it yearns for,
happiness beginning to contour adding dimension that love that lingers even
when you are apart like that fragile flower opening to the warmth of spring
love is blossoming and love is the only way so that's very pretty that is very
beautiful I I wanted to see what this guy was all about he has a bunch of links in
his bio one of them is a link to a YouTube channel that has him reading
every single one of his poems and also hot sauce challenges. So here's another
poem by him okay this one is called the Reaper. I have tried so many
different peppers, some delicately flavored, others hot as hell. There were
those that made me laugh and cry, each one with its own unique smell. The simple
jalapeno was the start of the chili madness I was in, followed by ghost
I just knew I had to win so many chili challenges out there with warnings of what laid within the chocolate
Boudjiello Kia was an insane type of pepper sin the scorpion chili was the next to fall
This one really made me sweat a burn like I had never experienced before I had to do it as I had made a bet
Even my tears were scorching hot the hiccups wouldn't go away
I put the toilet roll in the fridge as ring sting would be there that day then in one moment of pure madness
Carolina Reaper was there in my sight.
Oh my god.
I psyched myself up to eat it.
I had one hell of a night.
My tears once again were burning, my urine became molten in heat,
my mouth burned like the fires of hell,
in the morning I would be in for a treat.
Never before had a ring sting been so intense.
I heard sounds like I shouldn't have oughta.
Then I realized it was just my sphincter going down to drink some water.
[laughter]
So...
That was beautiful.
He's bea- he also- I found him from a poem called "Grandma Fart Attack".
This guy does not this guy shouldn't be a slave he we should free he's I mean he
he's like one of the most like masters of all time right like this guy should be
this guy should be the top of the top should be well you know what they say is
like good art comes from pain and that that ring-sting sounds like it really
hurt that's why he makes such beautiful shit yeah yeah yeah from his ass come on
his damn asshole oh yeah something I forgot to mention about whatever 666 is
is that most of her poems in the inspiration section,
she just attaches Tom McDonald raps.
- Oh, sick.
- Yeah, so I wanna share another user that I found here.
This is The Devil's Wife.
- Whoa, what?
- I'm scared.
- Her profile picture is an impact font meme
of a lion made of fire that says,
"Don't take my kindness for weakness.
"The beast in me is sleeping, not dead."
And she basically, she writes poems and raps.
So I have a selection here of a poem and then a few raps for you.
Okay, cool.
Perfect.
Yeah, so this is The Dark Side to Me by Devil's Wife.
Imagine liking solitude to the point you become colder than ice.
Imagine having a rage that's darker than all the powers of hell.
Imagine being full of life and giving life one day, having no desire to live or see things
live the next.
Imagine being a being of light, but that light is nothing but darkness.
That is the dark side of an empath.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Now wait till you hear this rap by Devil's Wife called 911 Rap.
Okay.
Yeah, put your hands in the air.
I'm gonna show you unfair.
Watch me take this beat to the street.
I'm about to make you taste defeat.
I'm the Jack back in black, diamond ring Pontiac and Cadillac.
From this madness, there is no coping.
On shooting stars, I'll have you hoping.
I'll show you how to go pro once I set the stage with my fiery flow.
Whoa.
I'm about to call 911.
I think that's why it's called nine one rap and now I would like to read this
other rap by the devil's wife called this to Mr. Tom McDonald. Whoa okay,
this one there's no line breaks. So it's kind of hard to read yeah yeah yeah.
Yeah, I heard every one of your videos dude go ahead. Call me out and say that
I am rude. I know you probably don't care about my diss. I know that you
hate hip hop and you are seemingly a troll. So my favorite message to you is
what goes around comes around. You say you are unafraid, then when Illuminati
showed up you act all scared. If it takes words to battle you, hell, I am more than prepared.
To stand my ground and not back down, I decided to troll the troll. Go ahead, hate me because
I make my haters' heads roll. And yeah, for the millions of death threats being ghost stories
when you logged in every day, I know that you are not a white boy. Your soul is as black
as they come. And I know if you were black, you would probably look for a reason to state
that I was politically incorrect on my diss track to you. But hey, dude, we all have buttholes.
You stated that yourself, and I know that you are not the only corny artist in the game.
You just met a female who loves how you play the game only to tell you that she thinks
that your playing has lost its aim.
So yeah my feet are not glued.
I do know what I'm saying and yes that more than one million times you say people are
so stupid dude.
I am sure you are a person too but hey I could be wrong.
You could just be a clone of you.
Damn.
That's fire.
Think the Illuminati clone Tom McDonald?
Could be.
That's what I'm thinking.
It could.
That actually is kind of what that points to isn't it?
That would make a lot of sense.
Yeah.
of
companion song I don't know if you guys play the dip dip dip mm-hmm Wow
this one is called funny bunny okay oh that mr. Bugs bunny so quintessentially
funny he tickles my old cranium he's better than a bonbon saying what's up
Doc cracks me up not much how about you what's up crunching carrots by the dozen
would taste more yummy honey baked in the oven gotta love Bugs Bunny he's much
the wiser escaping dangers on far horizons in 2030 he'll turn 100 still
yooks looks young still turning heads damn you know honestly I think I think
nowadays like writing poetry like that takes a lot more courage than writing
writing like dark empath poetry.
I agree and also like nobody cares that you like, like you like someone died in your life.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, I care a lot more about Bugs Bunny.
Yeah, like Bugs Bunny like, like there's a reason why like your mom was never famous.
Bugs Bunny's like one of the most famous people ever.
Absolutely.
You know, like just shut up about your like brother who drowned.
Like I don't.
It doesn't matter.
Bugs Bunny, he literally like eats a carrot the whole world laughs.
Do you know another comedian who has that ability?
No.
No, nobody.
No, there's nobody who can do that.
Yeah, that's like I mean it's fucking it's insane to say it work. So this next poem speaking of Bugs Bunny
Yeah, you said it as a companion song. Yeah, that song is Harlem nocturne by the Viscounts. Okay, let me look this up. Mm-hmm
Give me a second here. Yeah, Harlem. How are you slapping my knee? No, just a dead air, you know, yeah
Okay, here we go. Single version. All right. Okay, here we go. I'm playing it. I
Can't hear it
One crazy night at the wet and wild Looney Tunes Conventional
Things got out of hand when the cartoon characters became
unconventional
For instance Sheriff Ricochet Rabbit grabbed a hold of Bugs Bunny and really let him have it
Because the sheriff knew Bugs Bunny's single-bend ear was code for he likes taking it up the rear
now while those two
Sick puppies of bunnies got down on their got down to their rodent man-on-man
rodent jollies
Daffy Duck plucked off all of his feathers because he likes to strip then strap on some S&M leathers
Oh, you should have seen it when he cornered Elmer J. Fudd whipped him silly then smoked some really good bud
After that Daffy became loose as taffy then sent out his sights on none other than Miss Minnie
But Mickey Mouse wasn't having any of that. He then let Daffy have it with his baseball bat.
And so when this drunken stone mallard finally came to,
he sang a different ballard.
Ballad.
Daffy chilled out then dug this wild convention scene. That's when he realized what really happens
behind the scenes.
He saw Porky the Pig
getting blown by Yosemite Sam.
But whoever knew yo had taste for chewing that kind of ham
Now the next sight was certainly from another level as Sylvester the cat was riding the Tasmanian devil
He also saw something foul upon which his shocked eyes happened to gawk
foghorn lechhorn fucking tweety bird
Cuz old foggy's a goddamn chicken hawk what does that mean I hope that's not a slur no it's a
Then there was a Jessica rabbit
Turning up turning some special order tricks pulled hairs out her ass so the bitch got paid
cleaning herself of tics
At one point Jessica's tight little rabbit hole
Became very loose
Yep, you guessed it. She fucked Bullwinkle
That hung like a horse moose
The dirty bitch even gave Pepe Le Pew some deep-throated head.
That's when Daffy saw her ruby earrings so bright and alluringly red. He knew he...
That's how it's written.
He knew he had to have them, but was shocked to see her blowing a skunk.
Then thought to himself, if I scare Pepe, he'd spray the whole place with funk.
So while on Jessica Rabbit, Bullwinkle, and Pepe did run a train.
Daffy sneaked, sneakily pulled the fire alarm and the sprinklers started to rain.
It scared the shit out of that just about to come skunk, causing him to rip loose with
his famously foul funk.
Jessica hurled carrot chunks all over Pepe's dick and that most certainly ended up doing
a trick.
Daffy then stole the ruby earrings and ran all the way to the desert saying it's mine
mine mine.
Got there and saw something that totally blew his mind.
The Road Runner was finally captured by the Coyote and was being force-fed
Spoonfuls of some wacky peyote.
Daffy couldn't believe his eyes.
An hour later, the Road Runner was beyond stone.
That poor fucking bird got bent way over as the Coyote finally got his bone.
Daffy heard him say while stroking away,
"In all this time, you thought I just wanted to cook you.
Well, I still do, but first,
"I'd like to super silly fuck and then eat you."
Daffy was appalled and thought to save the Roadrunner, so he came up with a plan which is a hell of a humdinger.
He ran over to them and then said to the Coyote in mid-stroke as he was still fucking the Roadrunner while giving his neck a little love choke.
"I'm sorry to interrupt, but I'm here to mention you both missed out on the Looney Tunes convention."
The Coyote stopped from choking his fucking chicken.
Then said to Daffy, "Now you had just better listen.
"I hope you don't say anything about what you just fucking saw, because trust me-"
And then BAM! Without warning, Daffy broke the coyote's jaw.
Daffy helped the Roadrunner heal, and they both grin as the coyote began to squeal.
An hour later, the Daffy- Daffy says,
"You know, the coyote wasn't that tough, but I did enjoy eating him."
"Even though dog meat can be a bit rough."
The Roadrunner falls over giggling with hysterical laughter as Daffy screams aloud,
his cry echoing across the canyon's rafter.
Let it be known if you come at me, bring plenty of luck, because I'm Taffy Duck and I don't give a damn fuck. End of part two.
Imagine just somebody showing up to a poetry slam and just saying that for like 20 minutes straight.
How fucking long was that?
I got really, really stuck on Porky the Pig blowing Yosemite Sam.
That is... No, I think it was the other way around.
No, no.
No, he said he didn't know that yo like that kind of ham.
Oh, I assume that that meant that Yosemite was eating the hand.
I do like that there was a song companion to that.
Yeah, the song companion added a lot. It played two times.
It was a long...
The song, it helped so much.
It did, yeah.
It felt like you were in L.A. Noire.
Yeah.
I was recounting it.
The worst story ever.
His name is Daffy Duck.
Maybe I should have read it like that.
Yeah, you should have.
Yeah, that would have been funny.
I didn't listen to the song beforehand.
So I have, I'm gonna do, I have two here. Sure and then I have one we can finish it off
with. Oh let me do all three of these. Okay. All right.
This is a really, there's two really quick ones here. Okay. A filthy dog ate a
maggot lunch on my ball sack. Who in their right mind would allow my stink in
public that's the end it's called the ball sack wars and then you know what
I'll just do I'll skip that one and we'll just do this one for my last one
this one's called so this one's called South Park okay home by two more going
down south to listen to Cartman's big mouth see his friend Kyle be pissed all
while Kenny doesn't have a penny but he is friendly among many Stan is a normal
boy partially because his father was a man they also can afford much more than
Kenny can come on down south and we'll meet some friends of mine
it's a four years old that for you I think that's a pitch for the new theme
song yeah it's yeah there was like a million South Park poems really so yeah
A lot of people have a lot of stuff to say.
So I do.
I have a short one and a long one and then a good finisher one.
We have like five minutes left.
I don't know if anybody else has any more that they want to read.
If we have five minutes left, I'll read this one.
This one is called "My Bad Boy Earl" by Goombas Girl.
Dedicated to Earl, R.I.P.
His name is Earl, I have to say.
I will fuck him hard every day.
All tied up, his dick hangs low.
Cock in my mouth, now he explodes.
I spank him hard, it pains himself.
Four fingers in, I play with myself.
Nipple claps, ball spreaders too.
Deep in your ass, more you plead, so I do.
Now that you came, it's my turn now.
Hurry, please go, oh, I wonder how.
One finger, two finger, three fingers, four.
My cunt is filled, but I want more.
Pound my ass, I beg you please.
On the floor, I'm on all knees.
Cock jammed in, you fuck me strong.
Go Earl, go on, you cannot go wrong.
Deep in my hole, how I love your huge cock.
Back and forth, I rock and rock.
As my body shakes, I finally come.
It's your turn again.
you better run 12 years ago. R. I. P. Earl.
That's the, maybe the best ending line for that poem.
All right. So I'll, I'll finish off with these three then.
This first one is by Andrew Kel and it's called a sound coming from Ross's
bedroom. Is this Ross Geller? No, I don't think so.
Unfortunately. I mean, it could be, okay. You know, actually we don't know.
doesn't have a last name in here. So if you want to imagine this is Ross
Geller, that's fine. Okay, let me just read this.
Well, everyone else in the pool continued splashing to keep cool. Debbie
went inside for a drink before she heard a sound coming from Ross's bedroom and
start peeking on him, drill his rod in the pink taco of and who was on top of
Sarah just before a pop came from Ross's own dude, piston dink.
Dude, piston dink.
Wow.
Really beautiful, right?
That was written a day ago it says?
Holy shit.
I'm amazed at how, honestly like, I'm amazed at how much shit like this is on this website.
It's insane.
There's so much.
And also when you sign up, it says that if you're under the age of 17, it turns off explicit
things.
Yeah, and I put my birthday in.
This website hasn't been, I don't think it's been, no, the thing has been updated.
No, you have to go into the settings and change it.
I put my birthday in 1997 and then it said you were 17. What? Yeah, it said you're
under 17. I said I was born in 1926. Yeah, what did I, you have to make a website on,
an account on this website to view the poems. What user name did you
guys go with? Dr. Pepper 2. I think I'm, let me check. I went with Juice World.
world. Yeah, Juice WRLD is really good. That's my go-to. Mine is Mr. Dookie. Alright, here
we go. Let me read. This is our second to last one here. This is kind of long, but it's
called Ping Pong, a poem written by Big Verge. Okay. This is from 2020. Now when I was young,
athletic and strong. I really did love a good game of ping pong or that's right
table tennis. But I say this to preface this poetic message. Do I need a ping to
say I'm infectious pings that now sting like this Corona menace that now will
send endless pings that now pong when their message is wrong. I mean, what's
going on? Do all these pings belong in a world where it's said that we're now
seeing less of this need to inject or a need to prolong distancing measures as
lockdowns are lessened because of a drop in the rate of infections. And because
of these apps that can chart and can map infections before you know that you've caught a variant
form of this corona force? Have the tables now turned so corona gets burned and no longer
fills urns or are we being served a whole load of spin about all these pings when PMs
refuse to start isolating because I'm confused by reports in the news where their tables now
show that corona has slowed because these pings know where it is people go because of
our phones and now know who it is we've been in contact with so can trace virus strains
that are in people's veins? Doesn't it seem insane that we have to track and trace all
all over the place, but still have to wear masks to cover our
face or okay.
Yes, our mouths.
Does the logic seem sound profound and thought out or something
thrown around just like circus clowns to keep people tied down
controlled and now bound like some kind of bad hound.
Are all these pings correct or a way to direct people to inject
because of the threat of a quarantine bed or being jobless
because of a ping that tells you to stay away from working and
earning a wage.
The table's not straight like these government names and their
government games.
Are we all being played and forced to vaccinate because of
these pings. Surely something must give in people's thinking when tech like this gives
us bad messages that claim to predict when we will become sick. It's a form of sickness
that clearly is linked to making us live in a world that restricts because of these pings
that come from our phones because it isn't a joke to be told stay at home by an app that
now tracks and apparently can diagnose better than these people in labs who still don't
seem sure of how variants form. So our saying be warned because these vaccines don't cure
or stop us from getting corona infected because you've had shots, they're singing dud songs
things unlike what's going on and do not seem able to stop telling fables. It
feels like a game where we're being played because of false claims about the
flu strain. I wish I could say that things will be okay, but something seems
off because Corona's not gone or taking a break and going away, which brings me
right back to the days of my youth when things weren't so bad and filled with
this flu that's causing problems for us in multitudes. I just wish I could go
back to those days when I was in school and saw nothing wrong with hearing the
sounds of a game of ping pong.
This guy has like so many that are all about like coronavirus and all are this long.
It does it all.
Written in this style.
It's a fake.
Yeah.
Talking about what it's going to be.
It gets you. It gets you hooked in.
I was like, oh, it's going to be ping pong. It's going to be sick.
All the like paragraphs to end with like four exclamation points or a bunch of
exclamation points and question marks.
Yeah. Well, it also is the exact flow of The Way I Am by Eminem.
It's like literally the exact same thing.
Yeah.
All right. I got one more to close it out for this poetry.
So imagine like you know the lights go low everybody people it's like you know people are ready to go home
This is yeah, you can't get Ginsburg. Oh, yeah, this is by NJ Towers. I'm not gonna read the title yet
Seen it yeah
They found nothing in his pockets, but lint and knives
controlling bats and taking lives
He changes the tides with nine words
Some people just want to watch the world burn Wow
A killer clown with a chilling laugh?
The letter A is a craft.
You say he's insidious.
He asks, "Why so serious?"
Is there no one that sees the joke?
For everything to go up in smoke?
He's a mad dog chasing its tail.
His master plans will never fail.
That was the title, "Why So Serious?" by N.J. Towers.
is beautiful. Wow. Yeah. Thank you, everybody. Thank you for coming to the Poetry Slam. We'll
see you at the next one. Bye!