you're listening to Israel's number one pod
this is premium content
if you are not a premium subscriber
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately
*laughs*
ohhh
I need a boner yesterday
oh man I need a boner sooooo bad
oh is it what is it boner o'clock?
oh look at my watch
it says boner here I got this special watch
*laughs*
It only says boner at like 3 p.m.
Look at that, it's boner, oh, and look at that, it's 5 minutes later, it says nap time.
Like it's a complete, like the face of the clock is completely white except for boner
and then like 3, 15, nap time.
12, 1, 2, boner, nap time, 4.
And after that, daddy needs his wine.
A little boner and Moscato, ain't you?
Oh my god, dude.
It's obvious now, Thomas is on the show.
Yeah, we got Thomas here to replace Caleb permanently.
Which we haven't told Thomas yet.
How do you feel about that?
I haven't been told yet, so I don't have an opinion on it.
Yeah, fair.
Good point.
Yeah, we'll tell you later.
I appreciate it.
Yeah, we're all...
big day today
yet that's patrick's birthday yeah according on patrick organism we're
given escort yet
his first escort or organ watches
finally the only
that i mean
every year my fucking birthday gets ruined by cameron
and now it's become a big thing where now everybody
ruins my birthday for me
head with
because cameron decided one year to lie about my birthday i'd sit on my birthday
What was the original thing was on my birthday? I said happy birthday to you, and then that's spiral out of control
Yeah, now everyone tells me happy birthday whenever they want. It's not my fault
I was I was dude. I was ruining my own birthday the birthday police. Yeah
Oh you get to tell everybody when your birthday is yeah come on man. Dude it sucks
My birthday is so ruined every year by Cameron. I can't wait to hear you complaining about this in like 17 years
years yeah great I turned 41 and everybody doesn't even care anymore
because of Cameron everybody thought I turned 41 a week ago the pot has not
been going for like 10 years. Caleb and me are both dead. Cameron's joke once again my
kids didn't tell me happy birthday cuz he messed up the date thanks a lot
This sucks.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, the guy at the grocery store did not say happy birthday to me and it's because
of fucking Cameron.
Is this a chocolate cake?
This is a chocolate cake?
Fucking Cameron, dude.
He ruined everything.
He gave me the wrong flavor cake.
All because he said happy birthday to me that one time.
I don't like cake.
Yeah?
Let me just, let me say this.
What's your favorite?
favorite sweet delight
uh... flock lollipops put me on the spot
are you really like i can i a i look at your face that's a lollipop faces i don't
like what you got a you got a lollipop smile
yeah he does
a stick at your time
or is it
it's not blue it's a little more easily be studied and he barely suck it up but
it was really a little fluid but only on the tip of the air
there is something else
yeah you look lollipop just for the two
no it's not gay
exactly i got the navi flashlight
i've been looking at that
been practicing
you know i got that blue raspberry
oh my god
now that sprint is t-mobile swap out your sim card to experience the bigger
combined network it's easy and free
watch this short video then check with your primary account holder to make it
happen damn i didn't know you guys had that kind of ad reads now
here you've got that text so we're doing every told me it's a great is a great
his birthday ever for me i could switch my spot by sim card out at t-mobile
this is great do you know the thing is he's like a paperclip
yeah i did i know how to do it but i gotta go get the sim card
now no do you know he's got a piece of paper you're at sim on it
okay it'll work right up to right now yeah
i don't want to do it and i'm scared
uh... you know it's in court is backwards right
dragness
this is a great result of the holy shit
yeah that's what like
yeah it's a field the only president is a bite on the neck yeah
and so santa coming down the
jimmy it's a
yeah that's a bad
it's just a
straight yet
as a victory
it's a bad
it's a bit yeah
instead of a slay with them
a bunch of reindeer
it's a bad being pulled by a bunch of other
he tested another pat
instead of
rudolph the red-nosed reindeer
it's bad off the bat knows that
that
c_e_o_
you're going to go to the middle of the little player bats for battle
That's a different guy actually yeah, I don't know what that was oh the North Pole you mean the bat bat
We're all really tired
I'm so hungover. I like just kept drinking Jameson. It's like
You you put that shit in for that shit. It's a type of juice, so I'm gonna drink it right. Yeah
It's a type of juice uh-huh
Jameson is a type of juice. It's a type of juice if you put it in front of him, he's gonna drink it.
You tell me a juice drank this Jameson?
Hell yeah.
So you just can't control yourself around juice? It's true. Yeah, I put it in a sippy cup.
Yeah, you got a little straw. You have like a sippy cup, a juice box sized straw.
Yeah, you get spit yeah, you they try to give you a normal stride you go no no no no they should do they have Capri
Sun at bars they should
That I mean, that's the next thing I mean
They have like barcades or you could pretend there's a good
Parties people used to get Capri Suns and like get like a syringe thing and like put rum in there. Oh
That's a good idea. It seems like high effort. Yeah, I'm just drink. Well. Yeah, but you can do it
I mean what if you got to go to the airport, but it's nice you get
point yet
you can't
all of the tasty taste of that rummy rum
people would say that at parties people would say that
i love the delectable taste of a delicious rum drink
uh... this rum is decadent people would say that all the time
oh my god it's yo ho ho it tastes like candy combined with rum
Yo ho ho, I love this rum.
Hip hip hooray, I do love an extravagant taste of a wonderful delicious drink of rum.
Pip pip, this rum's scrumptious.
I want to go on like a Food Network show and just like have an aneurysm.
Dude, I want so bad to be, as a guy who like doesn't like food that much, I want to be a judge on like a cooking show so bad.
Just be like, "Yeah, I don't really like this."
I don't like any of this stuff.
You know, I'm not very hungry.
I took a bite, you know.
Don't like the texture.
It's weird.
This is giving me a stomach ache.
Yeah, my stomach really hurts.
I'd rather just eat it like if you guys had a Tootsie Roll.
I would really like that.
I mean, you have the whole grocery store, it's like guys' grocery games.
You have the whole grocery store in front of you and none of you brought back a thing
of saltines for me.
That's all I wanted was saltines.
I don't want to try your Korean fusion hot dog.
I just want one saltine with a saltine in the middle.
Yeah, one saltine, no salt, please.
The salt is way too spicy for me.
Do you guys have anything that a horse could eat?
I've never met one.
Like eating the napkin and be like, "Oh, this is really good.
You guys did a great job."
My compliments to the chef.
The balance of flavor and paper in this dish.
The balance of flavor and taste is just immense.
Oh my god, and the smell.
It's like I'm being on a food show.
Yeah, well it tastes really good, but it smells amazing.
Oh my god, I love the smell even more than the taste.
And it feels so great on my fingers.
(laughter)
- You're just crumbling it into a ball.
- Oh my god, I would love to feel this between my toes.
- Are you an inventor?
(laughter)
- Man, those, I mean, guys, grocery games,
there was like that week where Julio was here
and we were just watching that at Caleb's.
There's so many like--
- Ninja was on there.
- Oh, was he?
- Yeah, I saw a clip.
- I didn't know that.
somebody posted a clip of ninja on guys yeah you must have thought it was guys
grocery gaming yeah he must have thought that maybe instead of guys grocery games
yeah he probably looked at that and he said what is this guys grocery gaming
he was probably like guy like the guy from fortnight yeah what he said grocery
more like fortnight probably said that he probably thought it was a guy who did
say a guy fortnight gaming do you think he did the I do that I don't know I
I think he, you know what it was?
He was security.
So he was like going around on a Segway and yelling at people.
He was the, that was his thing on there.
I would love, it's funny that like every person that goes on there is like, I like, it's either
like I was like a chef in the military and I worked on a Navy ship and I, I did that for
11 years and now I'm here.
And then the other one is like just some, just a fucking, I am the most bisexual guy
alive.
Yeah, it's a guy, a fat guy with a bow tie and like little glasses.
Yeah, he's wearing, he's wearing bifocals and he's like flipping in the lenses to
detect different flavors of pop.
Yeah.
I mean, if as a podcast, as podcasters, we should be able to just appear on any
reality show, we want reality or game show.
It should, that should just be like, that is, I think the thing that I want most in
life right now is just, I want to be, I want to be on family feud.
i want to be on the i would love to go and i want to be a guest judge on cutthroat
kitchen
i want to be a cutthroat kitchen i want to be a beautiful lady on deal or no deal
i want to go on monopoly
i would be one of the squares you know what i want to do so bad
i can't wait to go to slurple swan you know my ultimate goal
i want to be the bachelor what's that name?
slurple
what are you talking about?
is for both of these not on the bachelor now
now that that that
chocolate guy who lives in the the resort his name was like gloppy
lobby
i was a little mister gong or something i don't think that was great
i want to be the bachelor and i just want to be able to say like
he has a little on i'm on the computer right now that i'm gonna you'd be like
can you guys call me mister bachelor
whole time. You can't know my first name because no one at my work can know I'm doing this.
All the girls are like, "Please don't advance me to the next round."
Every single one of the dates is just them watching me play Fortnite for 30 minutes until
I get bored and say, "I'm going to watch a movie and go into the other room and close
the door."
I'm mostly sedentary. My bones are made out of pretzel material. I can't smell anything.
I don't want to.
I have 15 jobs and I'm busy and I don't have time for these women.
Have you ever heard of anime?
I'm looking for a light-skinned shawty to ruin my life.
That's what I need from this competition.
And you know Jessica, you do not fit the bill.
I'm going to have to send you to the bathroom.
That's where I think you go.
It's a bachelor where the guy thinks if he doesn't pick the woman they get killed.
He's like crying as he picks.
He's like, "I'm so sorry."
"I can't believe I have to do this to you!"
"I just don't see us having a future.
It's not..."
Oh god.
Oh god no!
It's like the bad, the like, the narrator's like, "And Cameron had a, was in for a difficult
day."
And it's just like a video of like the outside of the door and it's just going, "Oh my stomach!
I ate the rose!
*laughter*
I ate the whole rose with the thorns!
Oh my god!
My stomach is bleeding from the thorns and the rose!
It's sucking!
Oh my god!
I need all of the women to rub my belly!
*laughter*
It's the only way to make it feel better!
I need an ultrasound!
They do an x-ray and it's like a whole rose with the stem, like completely unshoot.
Perfectly preserved. It's like the fucking Beauty and the Beast thing.
They have to do surgery because it's like...
The medics like run in, like they have like the...
They like completely cut you down the middle and like sew you back up.
Yeah, like just chin the dandruff all the way, way too much.
Damn. Do you remember, I think I've talked about it before, but on Rock of Love,
of
on our levels are off the charts.
- Yeah.
- That's that guy's dream job.
He was growing up and he's like,
"I wanna be a doctor.
"I wanna be a boner doctor."
And everyone's like, "You'll never make it."
- It's just like Dead Ringers.
- "I wanna be a boner doctor on TV."
And they're like, "That's not a job.
"You're not gonna get that job."
- It's like Dead Ringers, he's got a twin brother.
He's like, "Oh, I do all the work for you."
- Instruments to inspect mutant boners.
- Imagine being a mad boner scientist.
You're in the lab and the evil guy's like,
I need it done tomorrow and he's like I don't have time.
I don't have time. He like turns the electricity thing like all the way up
and the guy's boner just like it's like 20 feet long all of a sudden.
It's too much. It's too much for him. We gotta take him down.
Oh god he's gone. Bigger.
We're losing him. I need it bigger.
Yeah it's still just Igor in there too.
they said measuring Igor's boner Frankenstein's penis it's actually
Frankenstein's monsters yeah yeah no I'm saying instead of his monster be his
dead penis like he's gonna he's gonna have a monster when he's done with it
he's like trying to bring his dick back to life like putting together different
guys like balls and stuff he's trying to bring his dick back to life and you're
like he conducts lighting and it just explodes.
(laughing)
Oh yeah, I shouldn't have tried this.
- Oh boy.
- Oh, Patrick's tired.
- How's your New York adventure so far, Tom?
- This has been the worst week of my life.
(laughing)
- This is your first time here, right?
- Second, but the first time I was just a kid.
So I just saw like, I was mostly in DC,
like I saw like monuments and shit, but it wasn't like--
Yeah, well DC is not in New York.
Yeah man, I'm gonna fucking kill you with like a gun.
I looked and I didn't know how I was gonna get around before and I was looking at like
if there were like ATV rentals around here.
Cause I was like it'd be badass if I just got like a dirt bike for like a week and I
just fucking rode it out.
But yeah, they don't have that here.
They have the city bike, they have electric city bikes.
Yeah, it's not the same.
I want like a four-wheeler.
That'd be sick.
I could just take down Grand Central and just *roar*
People do that though, they do have like the, have you seen the dudes on the ATVs?
Like riding through, they ride on like Myrtle Ave and shit
Just like around there, dudes on like dirt bikes and shit, they're all doing wheelies
Yeah, it's so cool. Speaking of ATV, I was at the zoo
last week, and there was a little kid
who was on like a kid ATV who was riding
riding through the zoo on it.
It was so funny because he was just like,
he was there. - You were just jealous of him.
- It was so cool.
He was there with his mom and the thing was so slow.
His mom was just walking next to him
and like holding his hand and like helping him steer.
And we were just like walking
to all the different like animals.
And it was like insanely slow,
but also just like the loudest thing ever.
So we'd just be looking at the animals
and we'd just hear coming up like,
(imitates car engine roaring)
just like this tiny ATV with this little kid.
So sick.
You should get one of those Thomas.
Yeah.
I'm going to get a, I'm going to like sell my truck and just get like a fucking.
You can get two ATVs for the price of a truck I think.
No, they're pretty expensive.
Well, I don't know much about ATVs.
Like well, I mean dirt bikes too can get real expensive, but like you can, you can get a
cheap one, but it's still like probably like 2,500 or something.
Yeah.
Which is like not an insane amount of money, but like.
Right.
I mean, but it is an all terrain vehicle, so you are getting a lot of money.
You can ride that on the subway.
You can take it on the interstate if you want.
That's one thing that's interesting about New York is there's no highways, there's no roads
apparently.
It's all just brick pathways.
And people, they've got donkeys, they've got poodles, they've got their carts.
Brick shows.
Yeah, and it's interesting.
People ride camels here.
Yeah, it's like a melting pot.
I've seen people like I thought died from my life just walking around.
I saw a guy riding on an ogre's back.
I saw myself in like 10 years.
And that was just at my house.
I saw myself from age 1 to 30 walking in a line together.
I saw how you guys are going to die.
New York's crazy.
How?
How does Cameron die?
I didn't. I forgot. I wasn't paying attention. I just saw it. I was trying to look at my phone
and I kept having these like
you know like
like prophecies would come to me and I'd be like dude fuck off I'm like
I'm looking at boobs dude. I just want to see boobs I don't want to see. Oh my god
I'm so close to beating my high score in bubble bobble. Yeah
I'm playing the boob game dude. I just remember this the other day
when I had class with Caleb and
there's one class we'd always just be our laptop if you play bubble bubble the
entire
class like the game like
the game where you like shoot bubbles on the like a spit like
the worst game of all time. I played that at the arcade the other night.
it's a horrible game
it's the worst arcade game. I went to a barcade.
yo! Actually we could probably go back I have so many tokens. You guys want to go to the
barcade today?
I'm down
so like do they have gun games there? They do. So I
I went back on whenever I built my PC I got back on Steam
uh... and I hadn't really used it for like a year or whatever but I'd forgotten
that whenever I was like at like a university or whatever and like
completely burn out I would go to class open up my laptop and play this like
mafia wars game
that it was so stupid dude like
two thousand ten level like
it hadn't been up to date. Those are the best games to play. It was like
gang wars or whatever where you'd like buy like
properties to money launder from and like
you'd buy like guns and cars and shit but none of the economics on it really
made sense
and i thought like oh how many hours do i have in that probably like twenty
but i used to play it like everyday in class and i would just be like barred out
or drunk or whatever and i'd be like this game fucking rocks i had like two
hundred hours on that game
I was like, "What the fuck, man?"
It was my most played game by, like, a lot.
Like, it was the main game I had played.
That's sick.
Yeah, dude, I'm glad that Bloons doesn't tell you how much time you played, because I played
that a ton.
Dude, I probably, in middle school, had like a thousand hours on Temple Run 2.
I was like, I had a Kindle Fire, and I was like, "I'm going to be the best in my whole
school with this game."
Yeah, playing on a Kindle 2 is really funny.
It's really hard on the Kindle.
Yeah, I've got to play it on a bigger screen.
I think I got like, I hit like 18 million on that game.
Ooh.
Am I lying to us?
No.
You're not?
I saved up my gems for a long time.
Okay.
Anyway, this now, keep in mind, this was not a time in which I had really any friends,
but you know, like, sometimes you gotta know when to grind and when to shine.
When to run through the mines.
i was in our city other day i think it's fucked up that they have like
like fruit ninja arcade machines like a like doodle jump arcade machine or
whatever like
they should have been all be like
it should all be aliens fireteam or whatever it shall be house of the dead
that's not a lot of your case it all begins for you kill
dear zombies are humans those are the three types of games it should be an
archive saw and one pinball machine yet with a sexy lady or pinball pinball is
my favorite me a break
of course symbols your favorite you know pinball of course
is so good the gun games are better to get to see the only pinballs the best
much every game is gumball you just put a quarter in a year
haha
does that
uh... lost again
uh... because of the dropping the gumball on the ground i keep trying to reach
into the glass yeah
uh... damage
uh... i was playing this one game i think i talked about this area don't know
but i was playing this one game uh...
at this place the kings in the
was that winfield
movement and uh...
it's like a
but you're shooting down in the future but i get a little bit yeah oh yeah we
did talk about it
yes i clear that it was like i mean all of the way it's like d_-day
it's like
how do you have a better set the air
all our team a_t_m_ imperialist side exactly all i think it should have some
kind of
that's right
You should have some kind of like, just like...
Some guy who doesn't know who was involved in D-Day.
Yeah, we were trying to invade Normandy.
Who... what did they ever do to us?
Yeah.
What did they...
I mean, that's France, too.
The Normandans.
What did France ever do to us?
The Norman... the Normandides.
I mean, they were all speaking Normandese at us.
They were innocent Native Americans over there.
And we came in trying to wreck their shit.
I'm glad we got our shit wrecked, dude.
We deserved it trying to invade Normandy.
[Laughter]
Yeah, they were communist.
Yeah.
[Laughter]
So stupid.
But yeah, every arcade game should have some kind of either weapon or vehicle that is like
attached to the machine.
Like you should either be holding a big gun or sitting on a fake bicycle, like motorcycle.
No, you should have two flippers.
No, dude, that's lame.
That's lame as hell.
You could play that on a keyboard.
Every arcade game.
I do.
Exactly.
That's why it shouldn't be an arcade game.
You should play that at home.
You know what?
The Pirates of the Caribbean machine sucks.
Okay.
I'm going to say it right now.
The Pirates of the Caribbean machine I played the other night, do not play.
Okay.
That's my official.
But the Star Wars one, it's from the 80s.
It's very cool.
I bet you you saw you saw Keira Knightley on there and you started blushing and he
Started squinting your eyes and you couldn't see the game you lost
You suck here nightly and you put all your tokens in it didn't play here a nightly back in the day
She was
She was mine dude when I was like three years old. I thought she was so fucking hot
I wanted to just like you know, I don't know what I want. I didn't really want to do anything
I wanted to give her a flower.
I just wanted to follow her around, I think.
Maybe like hold the back of her dress when she got married so it wouldn't get caught in
somebody's feet.
Maybe be the ring bearer at her wedding.
Pirates of the Caribbean and Pride and Prejudice, dude.
You just watched Pride and Prejudice because of Keira Knightley?
No, my sisters watched it.
I was a kid so I didn't get to.
There weren't a whole lot of movies we got to watch, but for some reason those two were...
They were watching Pride and Prejudice, you were just standing in the door in the back
of the room just going "Hrrr!"
We had some family friends, we had some family friends who their family wasn't allowed to
watch Pride and Prejudice because some of the dresses showed cleavage.
Damn.
Yeah.
Ooh, hold on, what's this movie called?
Yeah!
Ooh!
Oh my god!
More like, uh...
Let me get that shit on DVD.
I'm probably having sex with this.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
Oh, God!
Hell yeah.
Y'all brought me on for the fucking heat.
Yeah.
Damn.
We are on our A game today.
Dude, a pride release prejudice?
Yeah, more like why I'm wedging this open and then I'm putting my fucking rock hard
fucking cock and stroking it and I'm fucking sliding it in, spitting on it, getting it wet
and rubbing it down, lubricating it, hitting it from the back, and flipping it over, and
grunting and I'm sweating and I'm staring at the wall so I don't bust too quick, and
I'm, I'm, uh, edginess.
Yeah, Pride and Prejudice is more like slide my penis in.
Yeah, it is more like that.
It is that.
It's a lot more like that.
That's what I would call it if I wrote it.
Yeah, Pride and Prejudice, what is that?
doesn't mean anything uh...
does a bunch of random words we give you two
perfectly good titles here
here's a better name
wise my hard target that's a cool yeah
they should call it that
right bridges alien versus predator that's a cool name should call it that
was my head and shit
i will have a look at the district
yeah
uh...
Guys I'm sorry
Dude pirates of the Caribbean trying to make something that rhymes all that is like
More like try it's a barely peeing
Try to shit while I'm barely being it's no more like pilots and I'm scarily I'm being
flyest in the very
if
Yeah, more like penis of the crazy peep yeah more like vaginas that I'm very be in
Yeah
More like trying to put my scary pee in
My shit's scary as hell. Oh my god, man
It's straight up has a ghost feeling shot. He got my dairy spleens
*laughing*
Oh my god my magic wiggler
It's raining oh my god, I'm meeting
Oh my god, I'm about to blors it's about to get hanky
Oh no, it's getting weird!
My Winkle's weird!
My weirdy!
Oh god!
My binky!
Yeah, she's sucked my weirdy all night.
Oh dude, my winky just made chowder!
Shawty you wanna slobber on that slonker?
Get that gribble wet?
Ooh, how about you come over here and chew on my bristle?
Oh man, my thing just coughed up chunky Arizona.
*laughter*
What the fuck?
I'm making-
Oh my god I'm boiling over.
The snake grits are coming out.
Oh my god my gumbo.
*laughter*
There's porridge on the ground.
My gumbo fell off my shorts.
Oh my god.
Oh no!
Shit I just made a dungeon puddle everywhere.
*laughter*
Dungeon fight, what the fuck does that mean?
I just let out the sloth!
*laughter*
Oh my god, my white jello.
My white jello rolled down my leg.
*laughter*
White jello, that's so gross.
Oh my god, dude.
I mean, it's like a tapioca sprinkler.
*laughter*
the
It's so gross.
It's horrible.
Oh my, my...
CUM!
Yeah, my jizz.
Yeah.
It just busts you freaking low!
Oh my god.
Oh my god!
I just shot a cum out!
As soon as like you're about to bust, you're just like...
Eeeh, oh I'm gonna bust!
I like, you like make her look at it after...
That's, that's fucking cum!
That's disgusting!
Can you believe that? That's the first time it's happened to me.
Look what I did!
What the hell did you do?
I could make a can if I put it in you.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
Oh, I just sprayed cum, oh my god!
What the hell?
You see that? That happens every time I have sex.
Why'd I do that?
What did I do? Oh, I...
I didn't even mean to show them that.
Plan equals ruined.
Oh, I hate that I just did that.
Just saying now your turn you do something like that. I want us to do that
I bet you always yours look like that. It was but it was way more
Yeah, you can't do that at all I'm the only guy who can do that what if that was in you soaking you were soaking it
it up.
I can't believe it.
Oh, alright, I'm going to go get you a sponge.
You're like with your wife of like three years or whatever and she's like, "Okay, you could
just do it like in me or whatever."
And you're like, "Okay."
And then you like cup your hands and like bust into your hands and like try and scoop it
into her.
I'm trying.
I don't know why would I...
You said you wanted it in there and I'm trying to put it in there.
Oh my god, it's just a funnel.
*laughter*
It's normal, I don't have good aim.
I'm not going in there.
*laughter*
I'm scared, I don't like it in there.
I can't see the bottom.
It's weird to me.
I don't like your trap door.
I don't like it.
I didn't know you had that.
Keep it closed.
Look, every time I see it, it pisses me off.
It makes me- I turn red.
Why don't you look like a poly pocket?
pocket
i was i thought you would be like a poly pocket
sex is is just crazy it's just gross as hell
sometimes i think i know too much about it yeah absolutely i'm like sometimes i'm
like too good at it yeah i'm telling everyone on the train about it i'm like
hey have you heard of this
have you heard about how how do you know that i'm a good apparently it gets
pregnant when you get p_m_ the girls
you know what i know it's your mom and dad did
yet you
and i thought it was a good idea i was there the night you were born
yeah so i don't know that apparently if you put your mouth on someone's thing it
can can make p_m_
yeah i mean do you
did you ever seen our dogs will there's something like that on boys
and it goes it goes into a but i don't know
so some men have buns on them some got them taken off
uh... great
that's what pirates do
i was seeing a lot there's some there's cia
you you can walk the plank if you want and don't do that because there's a
shortage
yeah pirate
they'll say they want to split your gold with you and that they take all the gold
because they're stealers. You hop in an Uber and don't even have the door closed. It's not
your Uber by the way. You'd never walk the plank ride. Don't ever do that. There's a crocodile
that makes clock noises down the water. You've been in New York a lot, right? There's a lot
of water. There's so many pirates in New York. Have you ever done an Uber ride for a pirate
on a ship? They have cannons on there too, which is you can use a match that you go boom.
I wouldn't mind walking the plank if it was longer.
Maybe it connects to another boat.
Maybe if it went to land and then I could just go there.
And I hate being in the brig.
I don't like it when they put me down there.
It smells bad and there's a guy with one arm and he tried to eat me.
I want to be an anchor.
I want to be the mermaid on the front of the boat.
I want all the boys that...
I want to be in the nest up there.
Yeah, me and my friends, we're thinking of moving to Brooklyn. I think we're all going to buy a pirate ship together.
We're all going to live in the...
I've been getting really into pillaging lately.
Yeah.
What's that fucking...
Is it the Gowanus River?
Gowanus Canal?
Where's the...
Why are you asking me?
Yeah, I think that might be what I'm thinking of the Panama Canal.
I was just saying that because it's something connected.
I'm just thinking about like a pirate ship in Brooklyn.
That's...
The Panama Canal is not in Brooklyn.
I was fucking with you.
No, it's here.
I mean, he believed you.
What is the closest bywire? Amazon River?
The Panama Canal is right here, right next to the Statue of Liberty.
Don't you see that?
It's not the same.
Yeah, I heard that sharks are big and scary,
But there's a little fish called piranha.
There's a thing here.
If there's blood in the water, don't even get in there.
There's a thing called the buttermilk channel.
Yeah, it's called where you tune in to my freaking wife's pussy.
That shit creaming like a motherfucker.
Yeah, I got off the pirate ship.
I found a treasure chest in my dad's closet, but he just had his gun in there.
So I played with that for a while.
I looked for a parrot and they all got mad at me.
me. I wanted him to get on my shoulder. Come on! I just called them all Smee, they didn't
like that. I saw a guy with one leg and he was he was taking he was holding a bridge
hostage. Would you please get out of the car, man? We can't we can't drive away until you
get out. You're not part of this ride. We're not UberPool. I'm just gonna drive with you
you
hitting a telephone pole because you're hanging out the door.
It's like you keep hitting fucking shit.
Yeah.
Yeah, there's Davy Jones and there's a bootstrap bill and he's got barnacles on his face.
Yeah, they're not pirates but I heard there's some turtles down in the sewers too.
They like pizza too.
So.
Oh, where am I headed to?
You probably hear this a lot.
Anywhere but Davy Jones' locker.
Yeah.
Oh man, time to go.
(coughing)
Oh man, Thomas got me back on cigarettes and I've just been like...
Yeah, I've been trying to...
The thing is, I don't really smoke cigarettes usually, but since I got here I've been smoking
like half a pack a day.
Yeah, man, it's New York.
You gotta smoke in New York.
Absolutely.
In New York!
Concrete jungle where cigarettes were from!
They were made here!
That's where they came from!
New York!
Now I smoke Newport!
Yeah, there we go.
Yeah, I got a pack of camels last night.
Yeah, really?
What do you feed them?
Oh my god!
Oh shit!
Probably water and maybe oats.
I haven't smoked like a normal cigarette.
Or like, you know.
Like not a light or something?
Yeah.
Like a real man's cigarette?
Yeah, because I would only smoke camel blue.
Yeah.
And uh...
Are those like the, what's it called, like the Turkish...
the Turkish ones just like the plain like the six dollar ones in New Hampshire.
Yeah but is it similar blend wise or is it like a parliament or?
There's like the Turkish ones like there's like the red pack.
In terms of the blue camels like what are they similar to?
Probably red camels.
Yeah red camels.
Interesting.
They kind of taste stale which is why I like them.
i like uh...
but they are true but i think it's a
turkish any of all this
stuff is like a turkish thing
so i don't want to know anything about cigarettes on those people funnel
you know they come in different colors on a mini blow it out to suck in your
puffing it
blow the house down
we should get leather jackets before we should we should get the uh... eight ball
jacket
you know the one
we should it's like the red jacket we should get a ball in the back and see
We should get monster costumes and prank our friends into thinking we're monsters.
There was a Halloween store in the Lower East Side that got shut down and it's right next to-
They saw a real monster in there.
Yeah.
They had to shut it down.
Probably got shut down because it's July.
No, like COVID shut it down. It was like a costume store.
Oh, like year-round?
Yeah. And it's right next to a place that's like, it's called like a goth- it says gothic
on the front and it's like a place that sells like like trip pants and like
chain mail and shit yeah yeah I wanted to go there really bad I want chain mail
oh dude we should get chain mail I need I need to be dressed like a Lord of the
Rigs I'm more of a like a bronze yeah I think I might wear like an elven cloak
maybe yeah that might be more my I use really thin leather I'm killed pretty
easily yeah it's a little bit of leather maybe no not even studded oh well yeah
What weapons are you rolling with?
I usually use elephant tranquilizer and then I'll do charisma rolls.
And so I'll inject the elephant tranquilizer and I can't feel anything.
I can't do any attacks.
I wake up and I have to do the elephant tranquilizer again and I'm pretty useless as a character.
like a problem now is that all the drugs in the city all have elephant tranquilizer in
them.
It's mostly because of Thomas.
That's why all the white rhinos died is because they were smoking on that shit.
My loadout, I got an elephant cloak, I got a chainmail speedo, and I'm walking around
with the flail.
Here's a special trick no one will tell you.
If you hold the flail by the spiky ball part and hit him with the handle, it hurts more.
It's because there's a piece of metal at the end of the handle.
It hurts.
It hurts really bad.
It's longer than the ball.
What about like a...
I mean if you got hit in the head with a basketball, that doesn't hurt that much.
You get hit in the head with a baseball bat, that's going to hurt really bad.
So it just makes sense.
Just a tip for any flail heads out there.
Is there like a double-ended flail?
Like a Darth Maul flail?
I've definitely seen pictures of it, but that's just...
I mean that's essentially a shotgun that's pointing the wrong way.
on
by accident right away. That's why they had the helmets. Just caving your skull in, yeah.
So they could get hit in the head by the flail. Yeah.
Yeah. That's why I bought mine. My doctor said you gotta get one because you're gonna...
Yeah. You gotta get one. Yeah. I was prescribed a flail. Yeah.
I hated that doctor. Yeah. He always had this huge iron gate.
Yeah, oh and his keep was just impregnable. It's so yeah, dude. Oh, it's like great now. I have to talk to har goth
at the front desk and he's always like
And i'm like great dude
What else what's my yeah? I'm trying to like see i'm trying to schedule my follow-up appointment. They're like on the third moon
From now i'm like dude. I need to see this guy in a fortnight. Yeah, please
and it's like
prices of i have newt or just going up absolutely i_q_ it's like it's just
because i have a fucking even get like over the counter like bizarre lately is
like yeah
good luck i mean when i'm paying this many gold coins they should just be
doing merlin's charm of making on the immediately and say yeah like i don't
need to have to do that brother
yet mean
fucking last time i was in there
was trying to get a anurad
prescription
at a lie and tell them that i'm a i'm afraid of
uh... the other exit ninety-eight
have you really afraid of flying on the backs of the eagles so
which uh... apothecary d_c_'s
uh...
johnson johnson yeah
i think that's a fact
it
the
i went to this which doctor is a most
he was okay
yeah i mean
and i you know what also it
i hate dragons so god
i they've grown on me
I just, I don't like them. I don't like them but they've grown on me.
I don't like getting burned by fire.
Don't walk around with some gold in your pockets around a dragon is what I'll say.
Whoa!
They eat that shit right out of your pocket.
Yeah, you can't walk around with gold in your pockets, period.
Around here.
What?
What's that?
It's heavy.
you can wear a belt
it's a good excuse
period of the year satchel
yeah or your back
he's can't trust people to make good belts anymore no absolutely sure yes
i mean i don't think it's the same guy making all the belts i don't know
but
and where we at
yes we have fifteen minutes left are really
what is the only fucking talking to me don't you know i'm just i'm really
hungry
and his really little
my name and they've been in the month warm you are
i want to go to red lobster so that's the i can we go to where lobster
please it's my birthday and i think that we will i can't wait to go to red
lobster in times square dude
all my god i got a red lobster in times square
we might we do
well as well as one lobster so bad
i was a lobster on my birthday
well no it would be a guy i really believe it's a lot of stuff she pushes
you know
you know i have somebody's got thirty dollars and a z is crazy here it like
you know the thing out you originally was like prison food yes lady like
is just like a bug and was like it should be this to prisoners and they're like
weight actually is gonna be the rich person food now
the prisoners really are no i a all got it so i don't know who is
butter all my god i hate lemon butter of its day when you have any napkins oh
yeah that was that was the other there you know they were chained to the wall
you know they do shackle bibbs
yeah
man i put that by keep the bibs
uh...
yeah when you're not sure i keep the bit i just don't know i have a lot of the
i guess the juices are like sunflower seeds and i crack it with my teeth and i
spit out the bones yeah
they've got so many bones inside them struet most of the thing i realize about
lobsters like most of it is inevitable
yeah it's it's kinda like a rotisserie chicken you have to throw most of the
way yeah
like
yeah exactly i think you just take the heart out yet
like that green shit on their but you know you only get all that you can only
you like the toes and you know yeah
and you gotta like
it's like a bag of ice
you gotta
bounce on the ground
yeah
yeah in the parking lot you just slap it
and you see if it's
yeah i mean the way i
yeah i i i love i love killing the lobster but i hate eating it
i love i love it it's so crazy like the first time i teach him how to swim
the first time you ever eat lobster i remember being a kid
and like my mom bringing home lobsters and being like
like it's like
okay we can like put it on the floor and like play with it for ten minutes before we kill it
it's like the most horrible thing ever. That's like how Vietnamese people like
bring a fish home and like keep it in the bathtub for a little bit
yeah I didn't know that. Yeah they'll swim with it
in the tub? Yeah. Is it true?
no that part's not but
you know it's like your baby son and it's like
it's like a three-foot long fish and you're like alright you have a good bath
Yeah, no.
Just leave the room.
Yeah.
I mean, fuckin' ... Hearing a lobster scream the first time.
Yeah, scream is insane.
Yeah.
It's so crazy that they scream.
'Cause like some people just like don't do the cut.
Yeah.
But I don't know if the ... Someone told, like I just found out the other day 'cause Caleb
told me and I just didn't say it.
Like I wasn't like, "Oh, like that's why they scream?"
It's like the pressure leaving the shell.
Yeah.
But
It's probably more humane.
Maybe.
I mean, I'd rather have my brain chopped in half than be boiled in a pot.
I think.
I feel like we should just not eat lobsters.
It's just too much hassle.
And also, don't they live super long?
Yeah, they're biologically immortal.
They only die when they don't have the energy to molt anymore.
Like, they don't die from old age or whatever.
The most expensive lobster probably lived for 300 years or something.
That's probably true.
Yeah.
I feel like every science museum I've gone to is like...
That's how crazy you are.
You just, "Oh great, you're gonna eat that like a damn hamburger."
Every science museum I've been to has had a lobster in a case that says, "This is the
biggest lobster in the world!"
I feel like...
They're big.
They move it around the location so you can see it.
Yeah, they know I'm coming.
They know I'll want to see it.
museum they know that Cameron yeah great I love seeing a giant lobster.
I'd love to see big things in museums. Remember when Walmart used to
have the lobsters like swimming around in the oh the tank yeah those were the days
I used to touch them wasn't supposed to. Yeah I put my whole upper body in the
tank. Yeah it is weird that like remember when we used to get kicked out of
Walmart for fingering the lobsters oh my god dude sixth grade was a movie yeah
Remember we used to eat out those lobsters at the grocery store?
Yeah, I used to put my penis in there and make it swim.
And they'd all come up and suck it like a dick.
Yeah, I'd say, "Look guys, it's a fishy, look, it's a fishy!"
And all the workers at the seafood counter would clap.
Yeah, I would have sex doggie style with the lobsters in the bathroom.
Hey, you buy the lobster, you can do whatever you want.
Your mom brings home a lobster and she's like,
"Alright kids, you got ten minutes."
yeah you like to you like it like surreptitiously like take it into the
bathroom and then later when they're boiling it they're like what's this like
white stuff that's coming out of the back of the lobster? Whenever you hear that
screaming it's actually the lobster having a wicked orgasm.
I mean it's like a water jet to them. The bubbles, they're getting it
everywhere dude. Man I need lobster so bad. We'll get you some lobster tonight.
Oh, I need lobsters so bad, I'm so hungry.
Oh my god, I need a two pound lobster, I'm so hungry.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, I need roast goose.
My blood sugar is low right now, I need a roast goose.
I need mutton, now!
Oh my god, I need a seven layer wedding cake, I'm so hungry.
you just have a little bit of creme brulee, I need it so bad right now.
So, so, so, can we please go get duckling?
Oh my god, I need tortured veal.
Yeah, walking into the bodega, I'd just be like,
yeah let me get like a roast goose and cheese.
a little bit of a uh... there's going to the bedroom and i would like to land
the newborn
yes straight out of the womb fucking credits and you are you are let me get
the state are tar
the extra hot
but you know i don't remember torturers
yeah let me get the
let me get the the the tormented for a graph please
you know let me get a four-hour role yet
i want a full chicken i want to see pain in its eyes it
I do have you walked by any of the
yeah the chicken stores there's like we gotta take Thomas
yeah we're getting the head I'm sure you may like kill it in the store
like full to it like that poultry stores here that it is like murder animals in
yeah I mean it's like a butcher no live chicken
and you pick out the chiggy think which is killed dead animals
they don't keep like a thing is chickens in the back I don't have any
to
most meat is like, like if you buy meat at the store it was like run through you know
one of those lines.
It was ran through.
Yo that cow's ran through.
Have you ever seen like the videos where it's like they basically like have a cylinder thing
it's like a gun and it goes.
Oh yeah the bolt gun dude.
Yeah.
That happened to me.
And then they put the electric shock and all my blood came out and I said ewwwww.
Guys I'm feeling faint.
I'm gonna faint from seeing all this blood.
Yeah.
Do you think the cows when they're in line to get bullgunned, they're like, "Oh my god,
we're finally in line at Disneyland."
I hope not.
Imagine it's the most terrifying moment of your life and the only noise you can make
is like, "Moooooo!"
Yeah.
I'm so much smarter than a cow.
Imagine like two reactions a cow can have to anything is is say moo and squirt milk
Those are the two imagine like you're watching the assembly line
You like work in the factory and there's one like the cow is just about to get like it's next in line
And the rest of cows like whoa ruin you just hear one. It's like fuck
And then the gun hits it and you never knew like
That was like the one cow that could talk
Yeah, shit. Well, we can't bring it back
You're like yeah
Fuck gotta wait another hundred years to fucking see this thing
First it's first words to
*laughter*
Who do you learn that from?
He just goes like, "Noooooo!"
"Don't! No, no, no, no, no!"
"Ah, shit!"
"Oh, damn!"
"Hell no!"
It's like, "Well, that cow was racist."
"Good riddance."
the
inside a cow and then talk.
- And then get killed.
He's like, no, it's like fully automated.
There's no one there.
You just get killed.
- You guys in a cow costume.
- Yeah, you're like in a two part cow costume.
- He's gonna be such a good friend, this fucking guy.
- You get processed and somehow like the ground beef
or whatever, like you can see your entire face in it.
Didn't get shredded.
- Yeah.
- My throat's killing me.
- Yeah, dude.
- You yelled too much last night.
- I yelled and.
like
and I looked at it and I was like, "This isn't going to be good."
They had a bin to put it in and all the rest were clear, light yellow,
and mine was like, "It looked like scotch."
And I was like, "Yeah, this is probably fine."
And the doctor didn't even say anything about it, it was just on the report.
It was like, "Yeah, this shit's fucked up. Whatever, it's not what we're worried about right now."
"Tastes horrible."
"Smell like piss, dude."
I thought it was gonna be whiskey.
Yeah.
I'm fuckin'
Worst apple juice of my entire doctor life.
That's the doctor that you have, it's just like
"Uhhh, eee, eee"
I go to that
"I don't wanna, I'm nervous about hitting your funny bones"
I go to that like fake doctor who just like pretended to be one for like
Oh yeah, yeah.
Eight months, yeah.
I go to that gynecologist, yeah.
Yeah.
Was he pretending to be a gynecologist?
yeah that's so fucking for the it'd be funny if i
you do that you like a version of time you like find out you're gay that way
you know i i don't think i like
this is how well but i have to do it
because i think the hippocratic oath yeah
now you did honestly don't like
i understand there's a new but i mean i didn't the idea that like most
male gynecologist go in to be like a creeper something is fine because you
just see like
pussy at its worst. It's like, man, I want to see some like stinky, fucked up, like,
prolapses and shit. Metal tongs holding it open.
I mean, the trick is, if you're a male gynecologist, you have to make sure, just to make sure your
patients are comfortable, you have to, whenever you're looking at a woman's pussy, you have
to go, "Ugh, I hate this!" I've always thought it'd be funny to like, see how long you get
away with this. You pee with that thing? That's disgusting. You're like at some point in the
examination quietly enough and like without much emphasis. Nice. Yeah I mean even a female
gynecologist you can't like say anything you know. Your pussy looks great it's really pink
yeah i don't know what it's the uh... fantastic yet works great
uh...
now
do anything
uh... i didn't do anything you know saying to you
i didn't i didn't do anything
uh...
on my god it's beautiful
just wow
that was just like a do you mind if you might like sketch it
i'm making an art book
i actually have a sculpture at home that looks just like this
yeah my look at my looks just like this actually. gynecologists be weird and nasty. dude they
be weird and nasty as hell
why would you choose to study that? yeah. yeah. why don't you study... why don't you be like
a dinosaur scientist? why don't you be a cock doctor like a man?
they don't have those. this thing is normal. yeah. you can be like a...
a prostate guy or whatever right? yeah you can be a prostate guy but no one
inspects the penis. that's not a doctor that's just a prostate guy
you got balls. yeah but your doctor just kinda gives him a squeeze. i think your prostate... it doesn't need to look at
your balls yeah but no there's no like
did your prostate guy fondle your balls not my prostate guy isn't there a penis
doctor though I don't know there's a guy who knocked on the door of your
apartment
So this is let me preface I was not molested but I there's so I had to get a
physical for this job and I hadn't had a physical since like sixth grade
basketball or something and so I'd done most of it and then it was like this
Indian doctor and he was like instead of being like okay if you could like you
know scoot he was like show me your penis and I was like what and he was
like for the uh you know whatever i was like oh okay yeah you can see it or whatever
and the weirdest one i've had for a physical is this guy just like uh he like drop him
oh i was like my i went to the same doctor and he like fucking so usually they like
they do they go like up here yeah yeah and they have you cough he like fucking like
He briefly like grabbed my balls.
That's what my doctor would do.
And then it's where they'll like hold him and they like
Yeah, they check for a lump.
They put like a blindfold over you.
[laughter]
They're supposed to do that.
They put something wet all over it.
And you have to sign like so many documents.
[laughter]
And then you find out you're starring in a movie.
I hate doc--
[laughter]
Our healthcare system is messed up
but it just turns out he like got molested by his doctor.
I have great health insurance, but this system, man, there's just something about it.
Don't you guys all agree?
I had a doctor, the doctor I went to from, I've only seen one doctor my whole life, from
the age of like 6 to like 20.
They're all over.
You've probably seen another.
Probably on the train.
But he like, every time he had to do it at the physical, like touch my balls or whatever,
You just go like, "Okay?"
(laughter)
He's like, preparing like, "Okay, you know I don't want to do this."
- Yeah.
- Then you'd just be like, "Turn your head and cough.
Turn your head and cough again.
Okay, now get hard."
(laughter)
- In sixth grade, whenever I had to get one,
it was this girl who was in our grade,
Her mom was a nurse and she did all the physicals.
So all us guys, as like 12 year olds, we're like, "Yeah, she's probably gonna see who
had the biggest soft dick and tell her daughter."
That's probably how it's gonna work.
So maybe fluff it up a little bit before.
All right.
Listen to Pendejo Time.
Yeah.
And subscribe to Pendejo Time.
We just put our first video episode out if you want to check that out on YouTube.
If not, I'll go fuck myself.
That's right.
Alright, peace.