Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
*Badass music*
second and I'm gonna let you know it's not gonna happen. You do have some Grinch
in you I think. My spirit is low! Yeah you have a little Grinch penis in you.
Yeah do you want a little bit of one? Yeah do you want some more of one? Yeah.
Hey you have a little bit of my penis in your face. Do you want more of it?
Would you like a little bit more? Not a lot. Do you want my second one? Do you
want my other? Do you mean the balls Cameron? Can I blow my nose in you?
blow my nose in between your butt. Can I blow my nose in your meaty tissue? You look like
you have a little bit of my finger in your belly button. Merry Christmas. I'll say Merry
Christmas after that. Merry Christmas. Yeah, why would you say Merry Christmas after that?
Can I sneeze in you? Merry Christmas. Are you guys excited for Christmas? It diffuses
the situation. If they're really grossed out when you ask, then you immediately say Merry
Christmas. They just get excited for Christmas. You can say Merry Christmas in any situation.
I would say Merry Christmas is like one of the best things
you can say if you're getting mugged.
Yeah.
You know, 'cause most people who commit crimes
are really are like stupid, right?
Like you're pretty low IQ to commit a crime.
So if you say like, "Hey, Merry Christmas,"
maybe they'll get confused and then out of the,
kind of, you know, reason for the season style,
they just, they stop mugging you.
Yeah.
I feel like that's not a bad strategy.
I mean it works better if you have a gift for them I guess.
Yeah, I would let most people mug me if they said Merry Christmas before it.
You could also say Merry Christmas as you-
If they said it was going for a toy for tots.
You could say Merry Christmas, I got you my phone and then you don't have to tell your
wife that you got mugged when you get home.
Yeah, well you could also say Merry Christmas, I got you this phone but you can't have it
till Christmas morning.
Yeah.
so i i have to go and rally telling your mother telling her mother your address
so that they can come to your head when i was about to ask you a question i don't
have anything on the air now that i think it is another day
could you come to my house yeah oh what about christmas
number twenty-fifth you come to my house i i'll fix and then the plate we're
having a coffee cake
news that you have any rash you can you do home alone at your house
doing
we do this thing every year we we kind of approximate what who has to taste like
and then uh... we eat that and we're gonna have a big play for you so do you
want this phone
or do you want to taste who has
or would rather have joy
phone now or joy later one of the toughest questions
sooner
ronnie was a rather have my phone or would you rather have a hug as it looks
like you're going to
come here
bring it in
I mean, okay, you could either, listen,
I could give you my phone now,
or you go to dinner with me and we talk about money moves
so you don't have to rob anymore.
- I gotta say, yeah, an hour with me at dinner
is worth a million phones, okay?
'Cause I'm Jay Z, and I'm gonna teach you
how to make Rock-A-Wear and make the biggest clothes
in the world, so you're gonna really regret
taking my phone. - Oh, what is this?
Oh, oh, you're already wearing Rock-A-Wear?
Yeah, that's my company.
- Yeah, I'm Jay Z. - Yeah, so how about
you give me your clothes instead of me give your phone for you for you mm-hmm
and then you know that's my closet on yourself for Christmas I want to get
something you say Mary get some old rock aware so bad get some Juvio got a rock
aware jacket while he was here I don't think he knew what it was he just said
it was a denim jacket that that's Sean John yeah I don't know where like all the
old like all the like mid-2000s like rapper brand yeah Sean John's sick you
You would be I think you should get some Oshkosh Bagosh.
Oh, dude.
Yeah.
Well, he's been so much time in the store already.
Yeah I got Caleb Granimals for Christmas.
They named the store after Patrick hanging out in there because he watches the changing
rooms and goes Oshkosh my gosh.
No, I don't.
I got Caleb Granimals for Christmas.
I don't know what Granimals is.
Then you never had a nephew.
I don't have enough here. Is this short for green animals?
Yes. If so, I've seen one before.
Lizard. Frog.
Chameleon, half of the time. Keep guessing, keep guessing.
Sick dog. Green bird.
A parrot. Parrots are green, right?
Sometimes. Keep guessing though.
Keep guessing green animals. Grass, grass.
Grass is an animal. A green snail.
I'll tell you it does eat grass.
A cow.
I got you a green cow.
You mean it?
I would love to have a cow, man.
I would love to have a cow.
Don't have a cow.
Okay.
Yo!
Don't have a cow, we'll get you your cow.
We got it so good.
Is this on Christmas Eve you're doing this to me?
Yep, that's true.
It's Christmas Eve.
In the anniversary of our marriage.
It's the third anniversary of the podcast.
It's not Patrick's third anniversary.
We'll have to calculate what that is and have a different.
third anniversary
tori's pat would call it basically
i think that the jokes are good
yet
you know
like i hate the good jokes
uh... yeah i don't know about all the other ones but i stand by that one
that was a good one
The only reason I don't get mad at them is because I don't want to ruin your fun.
You ruined a lot of other people's fun.
Yeah.
They'll never have fun again.
All the people I gave COVID to.
Yeah.
Yeah, you have been walking around flailing your arms like an inflatable outside of a
used car dealership.
I've gone to the movies every day since finding this out.
Why wouldn't you?
Yeah, he was accidentally pretending it's too dark and sitting on people's laps and going,
"Oh, oh, I'm sorry, it's so dark in here."
"Yeah, I couldn't see you.
I couldn't see you."
"WHOA!
Yeah.
You also have been putting your mouth around the popcorn butter machine like a weird kid
at a water fountain.
Walking up and down the aisle playing a tuba, like spitting into a...
Any brass instruments.
A bassoon.
I'm playing Kenny G, uh, fuckin'
Kenny G, fuckin'
Songburn, Songburn, de, Songburn
Kenny G has to be one of the masters of sex, right?
Oh, yeah
That guy's gotta be so fuckin' good at sex
Dude, he's made so many NPR guys have sex in their life
I know
Like, he's made, like, so many NPR women horny
Dude, I would fuckin' s- I'd fuck Kenny G
Yeah?
Yeah
he's got long hair that's about all the bags in the 90s probably oh dude sucked
him up whole oblivion shit bro he was yeah did he was seeing moleg all he was
seeing it dude they they these these women with tote bags in the 90s they
sucked him so hard he went to Mehrunes he saw Mehrunes Dagon he was he was talking
the machine elves as he came yeah he was leaving his body him and Mehrunes Dagon
We're playing we're playing songbird to all the imps and oblivion
It'd be funny if Kenny G like smoked DMT and he saw the machine elves and they were just like you have to stop playing the saxophone
You don't have any you don't have any like
Knowledge to pass out. No, just stop. You just gotta stop bro. Imagine how awkward it would be if
If you guys suck so hard that you had like a near-death experience and you like saw heaven for a minute and you saw
Hell where can I sign up for that?
You saw your parents and they're so excited to see you and they're like son
You're finally you're finally uniting with us. Like how do you why are you here?
And then you come back and then immediately yeah suck on that. You're just with some woman. Yeah
Not mom and dad. Yeah, I miss my mom and dad. I miss my mom and dad. I have to go back
I have to go back!
Suck me again!
Yeah, it's like Star Trek Generations when fucking Malcolm McDowell's freaking out on
the ship.
And he tries to blow up the sun.
You like, "It's like Star Trek Generations with Malcolm McDowell!"
I think you know for a fact that neither of us would know what was going on with that.
I thought you would at least, Cameron.
No.
Fuck.
I've never watched Star Trek in my life.
I'm not a fucking nerd.
You should get on that, dude.
love it you should get on that don't you love it you would actually know you were
a Star Trek fan me yeah you didn't know that about me he's getting out you see
like Star Wars he's mixing up how he likes true I like I like wharf what and
Captain Sisko what are you doing what is it okay that's a phone company
Odo and nog and quark I'm not sure and shut up shut the fuck up what is that
even you're just saying nothing man the USS defiant you like the USSR are you
communist piece of fucking dog shit yeah uh-huh
commie piece of shit you don't like Christmas cuz you're communist yeah you
said don't you know that Christmas is actually founded on the genocide of
natives no it wasn't found on the genocide of natives actually it's
supposed to be called trees day now mm-hmm we call it trees day yeah what are
you calling it? Christmas. Reason for the season baby. I call it Christ-mas. You don't call
it Happy Holidays Day? No. I bet you do. You fucking- I do! I say happy- I have an LED light
that I put- and this is gonna piss Caleb off- and it says happy happy holidays day? It says
happy happy holidays day. It's a big LED light- LED like screen. It's on the side of my Prius.
yeah and I'm gonna come knock all the letters off till it just says hard so it
says you're gonna know it so it says Honda I think I'm driving a gas-guzzling
Honda that's right I love your I love your festivus shirt yeah it's no it's not
a shirt it's a it's it's a shirt well it's an ugly sweater it's an ugly
festivus sweater and has a picture of the festivus pole I love the cartoon on
the back that's like it's an it's supposed to be about Easter but it shows
Jesus as a zombie and it's like Jesus came back to life and he's like eating
people and there's like it's like really cool. I have a I have a Festivus sweater
that's just like it's a sweater that's just the entirety of the Kramer Laugh
Factory. Pat says it all man. Happy Holidays, fucking happy zombie Jesus day.
That would actually be such a sick sweater. It's like one of those you know those like
embroidered sweaters I have like of the like the dog. That you have? Yeah you know
like the one that I have that's like the dog catching the the ducks like the
dog going after the ducks I was just well it's like an embroidered sweater like
that but it's just like Kramer on stage at the laugh factory and it's like the
knit of the sweater is supposed to look like the stage but then it's like a fully embroidered Kramer.
Why did you need to describe the sweater you own for that example you could say a sweater with Kramer on it.
You say, "You know the sweater that I own that has the picture of the dogs on it?"
Yeah, I wanted you to think about that specific one.
I don't want to think about your clothes.
The sweater itself looks like...
The only thing that looks like a thing is the embroidered shirt.
It looks like a shirt. It looks like a tuxedo, but it's a shirt.
You know how I have shirts?
You know how I have that one shirt with the Nirvana logo on it?
It's like that, but it's a tuxedo.
Oh man, I'm literally at my worst right now.
You're at your worst?
Yeah.
We can go lower.
over the brain fog the covid brain fog plus you said you said a hundred times you feel
nothing you can't get out of it excuses the brain fog now like it's been a couple days
now oh it just came in as soon as i said that sweater thing oh the brain fog just rolled
in and i said that stupid sweater thing oh this damn covid and i also don't i didn't
have any caffeine today sorry this isn't in the spirit of the season we have to get back
to christmas everyone's gonna god everyone's so mad at me already yeah and the only way
that they won't be mad is if we cover this beautiful Christmas website that I
discovered that I'm so excited to share with everybody. Yeah, covering what?
Hmm? Yep. What? Yeah, covering what? MyJelly? Okay. This is a beautiful website called
ClawsNet.com. That's right. Today we're looking at the beautiful forum on ClawsNet,
the Santa Claus Network. This is a forum for Santa Clauses. And it wasn't easy to get in here,
by the way. No, it was so hard. Okay, so I yeah, I discovered this website because I was trying
to find a Santa Claus for him because I thought that might be funny. I found this literally
the most beautiful homepage I've ever seen. It has all the different sections of the forums.
I go to click on and it's like, oh, you need an account to view the forums. I'm like, okay,
fine. I make my account Santa Toprak pretty beautiful name convincing, right? I seem like
a Santa and they said I have to get my account manually approved. It took like two days before
they let me look at the forums but I'm in now and I'm ready to infiltrate and mock
the the beautiful tradition of portraying Santa Claus. I'm not ready. These people
disgust me. I actually, now that you've told me about this I'm backing out of
the episode I don't think I want to make fun of Santa. That's because you are
clearly a future Santa Claus at a mall. Yep. Yeah. So this website could, oh that's
going to be I want to read here that I talk to Santa himself the about section
on Claus net there's this this section title entitled about this about the
Claus net Santa Claus Network so the Santa so it says launched in 2007 the
Claus net Santa Claus Network is the premier online community for men and
women actors dedicated to their traditions and faithful portrayal of
Santa Claus mrs. Claus elves reindeer handlers breeders reindeer handlers
slash breeders are also welcome to join.
KlausNet.com is the internet's largest resource
for the Santa Claus community for the purpose
of sharing stories, advice, news, and information.
Most importantly, KlausNet brings people together
to build friendships that help spread happiness
to the true believers of Santa Claus,
the child inside of us.
- Well, that could have been our in.
We didn't have to pretend to be a Santa.
- What?
- There are a couple guys on here--
- Reindeer breeders?
- Who do not seem like they're trying to be Santa at all.
- No. - Yeah, dude, we could have
just gone in-- - There are a few elves
on here that I've run into.
there are people who have elves. We could have pretended to be elves, we could have pretended
to be reindeer breeders. Or reindeer. True. So the thing about this website, almost every
single user of this website has the word Santa in their username. They're all named like
Santa Jim, Santa Jeff, Big Man Santa, stuff like that. Their profile pictures are all
Santa Claus. It's really incredible. They have on the homepage, they show kind of a cross
section of some of these accounts. We have on the homepage, we have Santa Brad, Tyler
Santa. I'm looking at a Santa here named Santa Ray J. That's pretty good. Here's Santa Castor.
And it's not the guy from the video. Santa Edmonton. Richard Ganey. Sinter Noel. Papa
Christmas 59 Santa Jared Kevin vast Tampa Santa Santa Mario Raylor Santa
Robbie big Adam on bass Felix Estridge Black Hills Santa Santa Steve KL seen a
lot of this guy is like the shittiest he's a bald guy he has the shittiest
beard I've ever seen and his name is Santa Bob Ford. Santa Bob of Tulsa. His beard is
like a white but it's the length of Pat's. That's very funny. Timothy Allen Adams. He's
not a Santa, he's a supporter. Niceville Santa. Do we want to go over the beautiful welcome
that you got on this website, Cam? Yeah. So that's the other thing. So the other, even
Even once they manually approved my account, I still couldn't view the forums.
And I was like, "What's up with this?
It turns out you have to make a welcome post and have people welcome you before you're
allowed in."
So they have a very elaborate permission to view the forums here on ClauseNet.
But so I posted, "Hello, my name is Toprak, and I'm very excited to be part of your forum.
Thank you for accepting me, and I love Santa very much, and I hope to portray him faithfully
and bring joy to Christmas."
I mean, that's beautiful.
You have a real Santa's mind.
Thank you.
Yeah, I had to kind of wear the skin of a Santa here to get into character.
You couldn't just put on the suit?
No, the skin isn't very important.
I guess it's true.
The first person who welcomed me here is Santa Timothy SC who said welcome to Claws Net and
posted a beautiful gif of Santa waving.
The thing I love about this forum too is so everybody's name is Santa, everybody's profile
picture is is them as Santa and that everybody also in there like under their
profile picture it has an interest section and they all say Santa Christmas
with just like it's like random other things added in and then it says and of
course Christmas which is there they're all like you don't like Christmas 98
98% the same person yeah I'm looking at it I'm looking at a Santa right here
Santa ed K no Santa in his bio no I don't think he likes it we want to read
out what he does have. Coin collecting, sports, and reading.
Yep. Those are classic Santa pastimes. Yeah, so Santa Bill Ryler, interests hunting, fishing,
camping, outdoor cooking, sandblasting bottles, and Santa. Black Hills Santa goes all in,
interests study of Santa Claus and Saint Nicholas, the study of religion, lots of time with family,
and good literature Wow South Carolina Santa retired interests retired college
soccer coach soccer referee woodworking painting landscapes and murals scenic
lighting and design and acting hey I think referee might be a the ideal
second job for yeah it's like I imagine there's a you're fucking playing soccer
there's a bad call you didn't foul the guy you're about to yell at the ref you
look up Santa Claus right I'm relaxed dude yeah you can't say shit I go aww as
a soccer ref? Do you mean it Santa? As a soccer player dude imagine imagine getting put it
getting a red card from him getting put on the naughty list from Santa oh
exactly people are gonna be on their best behavior exactly no one's gonna get a
red card that you know no dude Santa's playing not gonna be a single foul the
The only red card I want is one with a picture of my friend's family.
That's right.
Who's unmarried.
Put it up on my fridge.
Yup, hang it on a string.
Oh, I love Christmas cards.
I accidentally close mine myself when I run to the tree Christmas morning.
I love Christmas cards.
I love walking up to eat, to go get leftover mac and cheese out of my fridge and going,
"Oh yeah, these are the people that I know."
Right.
It's so beautiful.
The only red card I want, red lobster gift card from Santa.
He's gonna hook you up.
He's gonna hook you up this year.
I know he's gonna hook you up, bro.
50 bucks me yeah you two guys I put in a good word I pay for my half of the meal
with the gift card and you guys pay for yourself
sounds good sounds good yeah I'm gonna go to my loft Santa Mike UK interests
town crier wedding toast master speaker run my murder mystery business and
portraying Father Christmas Wow that guy's right here collectic who is this
This is another really good one.
Yeah, Town Crier.
You guys didn't have a Town Crier growing up?
No.
Well, he's Mike UK.
Really?
He lives in the UK.
How'd you know if Thunder was rolling in?
We just got scared.
Oh.
We just got scared of the Thunder.
We always had a heads up.
If I was under my bed, then I'd realize, "Oh, there's probably Thunder."
And that's why I got under here.
How did you know if enemy troops were afoot?
Oh, that, well, I mean, with the internet, I think the internet kind of destroyed the
Town Crier business.
Yeah.
sensor for me. Nowadays they have email, we used to have the town crier. Yeah. Santa Steve
KL uh interests Christmas pre-1840s reenactment martial arts. Oh man. Why that specific? Pre-18.
Yeah. Santa's saying he likes pre-18s. That's a little scary. I was thinking of a Civil War thing.
I think it's bad to put a specific date on the...
Yeah, it's dangerous.
Yeah.
Historical reenactor, 1940 to 1944.
[laughter]
Not specifying anything else.
And I live in Hamburg.
[laughter]
Um, so yeah, that's the welcome post.
Okay.
I have a really quick one from Sinter Noel.
He has no replies on this, okay?
And he says, "I've just signed up with Gig Salad and we'll sign up with Gig Masters
next week but I was wondering if you all know any malls in or near Atlanta or
southeast Alabama that might need a big backup black Santa.
Big backup black Santa. A big backup black Santa.
Big backup black Santa. That's a Christmas... And I'm looking at his photo. His backup is big.
I'm looking at his photo on here and he looks very white to me.
yeah yeah maybe he's looking for a friend i actually have i actually do have a
follow-up to that we're talking about a white black santa
uh... i'm
dreaming of a white black santa
just like the one i used to know
you lied with that afro
elf hermie is an rss bot that just auto posts christmas news
to this forum and Elfhermy has posted the topic "Christmas episode of The Office quickly edited
to remove blackface. A classic Christmas episode of The Office has been edited to delete a scene
showing an actor in blackface depicting Zwart Piet or Black Peter of Netherlands fame. The
revised version has been distributed to Netflix and other various streaming read more." And
the only response here is from Santa Craig Maxwell who says "Thanks for keeping up with
this stuff and reporting your research to us. This is disturbing, but we need to be informed.
Hopefully by being informed and ready with our responses, we won't get blindsided in
compromising situations. Keep it coming.
Woah, dude.
There's a funny bit to a bot too, it's so funny.
That's sick. He's a Santa and a fucking culture war operator.
Yeah.
"Interest Christmas caroling with the guitar and all things Claus."
Hmm I found a I found a post here very ominous title in the post just says well
I finally convinced her dot dot dot but then the post just says yep I finally
convinced my wife to dress as mrs. Claus and a couple of events this year and it's
just all other Santa's talking about convincing their wives to be mrs. Claus
I don't think I've ever seen a Mrs. Claus.
There's Santa Mike E from North Carolina, Caleb.
Well, shout out, raise your shirt up.
You might know him.
Do you?
Hold on, hold on, 'cause I think your interests align.
Okay.
Public speaking.
Gardening.
Oh, yeah.
Ham radio.
Love ham radio.
And Christmas.
That honestly, yeah, no, that lines up perfectly.
Yeah.
Does it say what part of North Carolina he's from?
Let me look at his website here, mrsclausplussanta.com.
- Is he from the 910?
Dromington, Kilmington?
- Triangle Park.
- Oh, he's a triangle kid.
- Well, hold on, hold on.
Sorry, I read it wrong.
He's available for hire in Cary, Raleigh,
Holly Springs, Apex, Morrisville,
Fuck, what does that say?
Fuckway, Varina, Garner, what?
- Fuquay, Varina?
What?
What is that?
Fuquay Farina?
What?
It sounds like someone with a speech impediment saying "Fuck my vagina."
There's also a place in North Carolina called Bolivia.
Really?
Yeah.
That's cool.
It's beautiful.
Oh, and then he says, "Pittsburgh and Research Triangle Park."
What the fuck?
Hold on.
Why are these North Carolina places named?
This isn't about
This isn't about North Carolina. This is about Santa and
And he says yeah, sorry. Let me just read this thing that Mikey said
I'm afraid that my wife will resist stepping into the role of mrs. Claus for quite a while
She's 10 years younger than me and I'm five to seven years from retirement
Hopefully someday let me get a couple more years of Santa under my belt and I'll be in a better position to persuade her
Also, it'd be kind of I will say be a little bit compromising
To Santa's image if like, you know, the mall Santa's all get their wives to do it and then you go see Santa and there's like a
22 year old mrs. Claus, right? Yeah, throw me off a little bit. Yeah, that would be that would be
Confusing to me. I wouldn't understand what was going on. Yeah. Yeah. Is this an elf?
Yeah, this is this daughter
Santa's daughter Brittany, Brittany
Hey there Mrs. Clogs. I want to read another Elf Hermie thing here.
This news bot. So this is something that I found. This news bot usually
posts stuff like, "New article, what are the best electric cars for ten-year-olds
to drive?" Stuff like, "Mall Santa spotted giving to a homeless
person" or something, you know? Stuff like that. And then here's one
Here's one news post that it made on January 15th 2008
An enraged water buffalo went on an hour-long rampage in northern Vietnam
Going for people and destroying food stalls before being shot to death by police officials said Tuesday
That's pretty cool. That's the whole post. Yeah, it's awesome. I wonder what it what makes it choose certain headlines. I don't know
Maybe there's something article where like the person just said like also I love Christmas
(laughter)
- The water buffalo destroyed my Christmas tree
which was still up in January,
which was very disappointing to me.
- If I was an editor of like a big magazine,
I'd put I love Christmas at the end of every article.
Just so it ends up on here.
- That's what I'd give that on notes
for novels that people submit.
It doesn't say you love Christmas in the acknowledgements.
Do you did be so funny if the like like what like storm front or something or
like like info wars puts I love Christmas at the end of every article so it gets
sent to this website so they can get army of Santas those people these I will say
a lot of these Santas would really like that yeah from what I've seen well if
you're listening um yeah I mean I can't even I can read one here for I would
love to hear this this is a this is a post called Santa security by Texas Santa
whose interests are Christ family military families and special needs
children I was reading through the forums and happened across a couple of posts
regarding security of Santa it reminded me of a time when I went to an event
that was deep in the hood there were many warnings for this event did not
happen mainly from the gang leaders sure enough the day of the event rolls around
Santa in the hood?
the neighborhood. While my team was setting up, even more police arrived. At the event
start time, we all entered the site and prepared for the worst. No problems, no concerns, just
hundreds of children that were relieved that Santa had kept his word. We hurriedly packed
and moved off to a secure location to properly put everything away, when even more police
showed up. Word came to me later that the gangs had all declared their hatred for each
other and were ready to have a bit of a tussle, but they could not be sure Santa and his elves
would not be hurt. They feared the judgment of their children if something happened. Sadly,
We have never been able to go back to that neighborhood.
I believe it would be wrong for Santa to carry a firearm.
Yes, I am constantly busy traveling to homes and sites that are an hour away from any type
of law enforcement support, but I still rely on my common sense and my capabilities to
not be seen on TV news as a stereotyped bad Santa.
I believe that if you are in an area that is a soft target and you fear for your safety,
you should not be there.
The primary insurance provider for the Mahler site would probably also have issues with an
armed Santa as well as most of the parents.
In my opinion, on-site weapons are a liability that runs afoul of Santa.
Wow.
Yes, sir.
Talk that talk.
Santa Marty replies.
There's some really good replies here.
Santa Marty replies, "It would just seem to me that we, as Santa, in a static location
like a mall, would be a very soft target.
Some social, religious, or economic fanatic could sure make an impactful statement in
a hurry."
God damn, dude.
I just love that Texas Santa, like everyone else on here is like, "Look at Santa Marty
be
was like no I have to let everyone know everything like like my interests
helping the special needs I'm the best Santa on this fucking site whoa I'm
better than all these other Santa's all these Santas think about themselves I'm
the only Santa thinking about the other the real world yeah okay thinking about
fire there's still more replies here - that are very good yeah this is from
Santa Caris.
Oh, let me read his interests real quick.
Yeah, go ahead.
I really love this.
"Interests, beekeeping, motorcycles, camping, traveling, grandchildren!
Last but not least, my Mrs. Claus."
While I've never been armed as Santa at any event ever, I find it hard to trust my safety
to mall security.
I am disappointed as Santa that this even has to be considered, but I'm not the one
that started jihadist terrorist attacks.
I'm sure the mall administration would have a problem with an armed SC, Santa Claus, but
just not sure that other than my family, many tears would be shed at my demise by that same
administration.
I am 99% sure that I will not be armed as Santa, but you can be 100% I will be vigilante.
You know, I'm fuckin, I'm pretty upset with the kid that wished for jihadist attacks on
mall Santas.
it sucks that the kid was good and they had to give him the present I know yeah
well he was you know now he did it shores he went to bed on time
destroyed wished it was Texas Santa Texas Santa was like please please please
Santa give me give me one jihadist terrorist attack so I can use my firearm
in the mall. I have this guy Big Adam on bass okay his only interest is Freemasonry.
He's the Santa that's recruiting all the other Santas into the Illuminati.
Which is an interesting mix I would say as Santa Claus but I he made a post asked to
play Bad Santa.
While I have mixed emotions on this, I thought I should turn to you all.
I have turned down this event but want to know what is your thought on playing a Bad Santa
for an adult party.
I feel that if the word got out to the wrong people, that's it.
Your time as Santa is done.
And then Santa TJS replies, "Pictures taken by adults on cell phones will haunt you for
the rest of your days."
And then people just are telling him, "Yeah, it's a bad idea to play a bad Santa."
It seems like the real Santas are very opposed to it.
You made the right decision.
They don't want a quality Santa, but a raw comic in a cheap Santa costume.
It's not worth it.
How does this fit into your idea of Christmas and the image of Santa Claus?
They're very, very concerned with the image of Santa Claus.
I found another post that I didn't save it, but there was a guy who was saying he never
drinks any liquid like he doesn't even drink water when he's a Santa costume
because one time somebody took a picture of him in the Santa costume drinking
water and said Santa drinking vodka and he thought that was disrespectful.
That is disrespectful. Yeah. I like it's kind of heartwarming that there's so
many old weird men who are so invested in the image of Santa Claus. In the
section of how to portray Santa they have like a guide yeah they have
something called the five-second rule which is when you enter the presence of
your audience you have five seconds to make people believe you are the real
Santa it's kind of a they kind of take it very seriously yeah they have you
know they do oh well we I was I just said you said old old men are very
concerned with the image of Santa Claus and speaking of old men and images I
I have a topic here by Santa Craig called pregnant belly photos
Pray tell
That'll transition good into this next one that I found but go on yeah
This is I was surfing on Facebook just now came across a friend's link to some studio sessions featuring women who have had high-end
Photos done with their husbands or by themselves with their pregnant bellies exposed
Well, this is certainly not my cup of tea. Some people feel the need for these fad pictures
I honestly do not see how or why anyone would want these photos hanging on the wall, but I digress
And there are a lot of replies here
and
There's oh there was one. I was I was trying to find one second. I have to contrary it is from Santa Dawn
whose interests
interests are
bachelors and master's degree in Santa Claus from the iusc special advanced training and special events in portrait video and portrait studio and
and Santa Dawn says, "I think pregnant women are the most beautiful thing God ever placed on this earth.
When my wife was pregnant with our three kids, I just loved to look at her.
There's nothing like the way a tummy full of baby feels, and I must admit,
I usually ask if I can touch the tummy of pregnant girls I teach with.
Now having said all that, I would not be comfortable touching pregnant tummies of Santa,
let alone taking photos. Kinda just feels wrong."
Why does he... he asks the women he works with if he can touch their bellies but he can't
touch it.
It's like in Santa it's like no that's a different guy.
Yeah if you're Santa that's a cross that's over the line.
If you ask in plainclothes that's fine.
Santa doesn't have a pregnant woman fetish.
Yeah but Stelter does.
Don?
Yes sir.
This is a storytelling Santa.
Oh, hold on, I got a, I got one here. I said I was gonna read. Oh yeah, go for it.
Attack of the Flirt by Charlie Claus. Reoccurring experience, I was wondering if
how everyone else handled it. Single mothers tend to want to flirt with Santa.
I've tried to ignore them in the past but tonight something was different. That
something different was that my wife was present. I agreed to be Santa at my
daughter's Christmas banquet at the Votek. She's in culinary arts program. My entire
family was in attendance and everything was going well. I was making my way
around the cafeteria visiting each table and spending a few extra minutes at with
any table that had children. When this mother in her mid to late 30s began
flirting with Santa, at first it was rather subtle but it quickly escalated to
her getting up and rubbing against me as she squeezed past me in the closed
quarters at this point I made my exit I had already visited with all the kids
there and I was getting very uncomfortable the argument with the
missus afterwards well I can get through that I was wondering how you guys have
dealt with or stopped these kinds of advances is there some sort of repellent
I mean I get it I'm a short fat bald guy with a beard what's not to love
somebody help I mean did Santa's Santa's pole did yeah are you kidding me put your
girl in a room with Santa, she don't fold.
Dude, girls treat you different when you're in the Santa costume.
Bro, plus you pull back the lapel on your fucking, on your Santa coat, burberry.
Damn, dude, Santa's got it like that?
I guess he's giving himself gifts.
Damn, look at you, Santa.
Santa with the Gucci belt? Okay.
Santa with the red bottoms? What?
Dude, yeah.
I just want to read a post title really quick.
Yeah, go ahead.
the prayer request section which is a prayer request for our brothers and
sisters in red and all others in need and I just want to read this title this is
very short this is by SC Santa who's the the retired soccer coach down to eight
fingers but the show must go on.
Damn.
No, dude.
Wow.
Does he say what happened?
Fireworks accident.
He says,
"An accident at work back in 1996
left me missing an index finger and part of
my thumb on my right hand. Last Saturday
night I lost a fight with a jagged piece
of steel hardware on the middle finger of my right
hand and despite my hope that it was just a
deep laceration, removing the bandage Sunday
morning proved otherwise and I had to go to the ER."
So he's missing two and a half fingers.
Wait, he's fucking shit, dude.
Imagine losing a finger in 1996 and then 2019 being like, just the dread of like, "Oh, I made it work with nine for so long."
"Now I gotta readjust again."
Also, how fucked up would that be to be a kid sitting on Santa's lap? He's missing fingers.
In the meantime, I have a major musical that opens on Friday, and I still have all the artistic painting, the lights, and the sound to finish.
Damn.
Um, this is from Storytelling Santa. This says, "You won't believe this request."
Okay. Posted November 17, 2011.
"This is a legitimate request that came through Gig Salad today. I'm gonna pass. I cannot believe they would expect Santa to soil his good name."
Here's the request having a nice size meet-and-greet for about 200 plus couples in the swinging lifestyle. It is a public club
We'll be holding this event in so just a meet-and-greet is all
Looking for a Santa for some of the nice naughty ladies so that they can get their Christmas wish
And a lot everybody's just dogging this dude
people say
That will accept this guy this guy says sounds like a great way for some Santa to get one of the many gifts that keep on
giving
Whoa and this guy this guy's cake wrinkle this fellow's disgusted by it
He says to each their own, but I would pass on this
Actually, it kind of turns my stomach to think that Santa would do this
These people hate say I have another
Santa in a sexual Santa
Thread here dude sexual Santa. He should never be these people. Yeah, there's they're very anti-sexual Santa, which I think Santa
Should get it no I agree
Why I think you should be blowing backs out and getting his foot back no now
I think you should be I think you should be lying on his back jiggling like jelly while some elf gives it to him
Wait wait so Santa gets fucked by an elf I know he should be taking it
I think he should be taking it and giving it to everybody he can
Also, this guy's got you know those back shots my like peppermint
*laughter*
This guy says, "In the words of Bart Simpson, I carumba.
We live in a day and age of cooties, and now I want to risk my life over some fetish?
Where's a lump of coal when you need one?
When I played Santa for my cousin or friends last year,
at least one of the ladies commented on me being a handsome Santa
and snuggled up a little close for the picture while holding my hand."
In the words, in the famous words, the immortal words of Bart Simpson.
Ay caramba.
Absolutely.
I'm still reading the attack of the flirt comments here.
Here's a comment from Santa Cori B.
It just says, "Yeah, if it gets rough, you can mention something about an elf hit squad that she has watching you."
so woman flirting with the interest that i have a bunch of else you have sniper
rifles pointed at you right now
you back the fuck up
uh...
yeah i have another sexual center post here
christmas and porn
by noro
you
when tracy interests writer coach in courage ur
why do people watch holiday themed porn
maybe this thread will
no i won't
uh...
I just blocked a Christmas person, maybe a Santa, on Facebook, because he is posting
a site to visit where you create titles with porn movie names as a takeoff of hit movies.
Even if you are into porn, someone who claims to represent Christmas or a Santa should not
be posting it or being associated with it.
Santas have enough trouble with not being accused of sexual harassment without putting
it out there on Facebook where 30% of internet users are on.
He doesn't use his photo just to cartoon, nor does he use his name.
This is very upsetting and disappointing.
I have seen this in Michigan with clowning, where a perverted clown gave all clowns a
bad name.
No, it is not funny or cute as one said it was.
This is one very upset Mrs. Claus.
I don't think clowns have as pristine of an image as Santa Claus.
The phrase "a perverted clown gave all clowns a bad name" is so funny.
It's true though.
Santa Danny says, "Nora, I have deleted two Santas in the last few days from Facebook for
posting inappropriate content."
I agree.
to deal with this Santa without having Santas posting soft porn on Facebook.
I too have deleted a couple, this is from Santa Spice, who also is interested in Freemasonry.
Christmas, Alaska, and Freemasonry.
I too have deleted a couple in the last week.
For the reasons Nora listed, I also deleted one Mrs. Claus because I looked at her groups
and she had several on S&M, Bondage, etc.
Which if she likes it, I am fine with it, but not with a picture of Santa related items.
So she got the boot too.
It is like us not smoking or drinking in public.
We must be careful.
I hope I am not a prude, but some things just don't go together.
Dude, there's a, um, sorry, this is...
If you just look like Santa...
Well, yeah, there's plenty of guys who look like Santa who are like addicted to...
Like smoke and drink.
Yeah, if you're addicted to porn, you just look like Santa.
Your name's Santa Tim.
Yeah, it's not your fault.
That shouldn't come down on you.
We're red everywhere.
Yeah.
You're not bringing a giving Santa bad. It's your parents fault really right for naming
You know what you look like he's like yes, I know Santa Claus and yeah, my name is Santa. Yeah
But I don't I'm not Santa though, and I love poor. Yeah, and yeah, I'm addicted to porn. Yeah and junk food
This is a smoke in public and I rub up on women
This is from Michael Riley. This is a this is an important. This is important. This is
Grinches on the rise. Oh, yes. This is a good one. How many of you have noticed an increase in Grinch performers?
So it seems like this is a problem
It's a big problem
And this guy says seen a few of them
They inevitably make their way to me and I try to play it off and not make a big deal of it
I've got another issue. I had a jack wagon show up in a horrible Santa costume trying to make a splash
Some fake Santa's showing up.
But the Grinch is, I guess a Grinch, like that's a surefire way to ruin them all, Santa.
Yeah, the Santas here hate, hate the Grinches.
I mean, who, who likes the Grinch?
Besides that fucking bitch Cindy Lou Who.
That's true.
She likes him a little too much.
Listen, toots, he's never gonna change.
Here's a comment from Felix Estridge on that post that says, "Yes, and have you seen the
videos of them scaring the bee Jesus out of the children intentionally?
Here's one from Santa Joe. I guess this don't real- I guess they don't realize this is a
copyright infringement.
Last year the Grinch was a co-feature during one of my Santa bookings. Only on one occasion.
Whilst he played the part very well, I didn't much like it. Took away a little bit of the
magic. I think they have a similar session this season and I shall Grinch and bear it.
LOL.
Good. Here's Santa Hill. Santa Hill interests Christmas, Santa, movie makeup, and flight simulation.
Actually, they started cracking down on freelance Grinches in my area. None of the princess party
business are allowed to have one. I think an attorney from Universal sent out cease and
desist letters and it made the news. Good on them. Good on Universal.
This is a...
Universal fighting the good fight. Keeping the Grinch in their prison.
Yeah, the Grinch Prison. This is that last post I read about the Grinch and Barret guy,
Santa Rob Thompson, his interests here. The Great Outdoors, charity fundraiser,
trombone my grandson otherwise known as boy.
My grandson otherwise known as boy.
The way that it's written.
Yeah, oh my interest, I'm into boy.
Trombone my grandson.
I miss my grandson.
If you don't know him, he's my grandson.
This guy says, "The Grinch became a jackass tonight at first intermission.
I departed to another part of the ice arena and went on my way."
Santa Fred, New York says, "I work with the Grinch in my event.
Dave the Grinch is a wonderful actor who I've known for many years working at the Haunt
Attraction."
Dave the Grinch!
Dave the Grinch.
That guy's born to play the role.
Yeah.
I have had guys try to crash my gigs at public events. The poor dopes. They have no
idea who they're dealing with. I make sure the police immediately escort any
Santa imposter off the premises. That's right. That's right. That's right. Get the
cops involved. Yeah. Honestly just shoot the Grinch in the head. If you show up dressed up like the
Grinch or you show up in some shitty like dollar store, Party City, Santa
outfit and you try to sit on Santa's lap, Santa is allowed to fire a bullet in your head.
Absolutely.
Here's the thing, I open up the news and it says "Cops shoot unarmed men" and I go "Oh
dear God."
But then I see that he was a Grinch.
It's like, how many lives have these police officers saved today?
Here's a short one.
This is a topic by Michael Riley.
How do you answer this question?
Where are your reindeer?
So this is a this is in a section where you you they talk about how to answer
questions that the children ask them when they're sitting on their laps. So most
people are giving answers like oh I tell the kids like the reindeer how they're
at the North Pole they have to rest up for their big trip but you know like
stuff like that but then Santa Joel has a different tactic here that he details
he says I don't know if this is a good answer or not but the one time I had
kids ask me I told them that since it was hunting season I had to keep them
hidden so they wouldn't get shot. Probably not the best answer, but it seemed to make
sense to them.
Dude, I would. I would love to eat a... Is it a reindeer or just a caribou?
I think so.
I would love to eat a caribou.
Oh, it'd be delicious.
Let's see. We got... Here's another prayer request.
Prayers for Santa Tim by Big Man.
As you all have heard, Santa Tim is in a new movie. I am putting in a request that the
movie does really well and that Santa Tim gets lots of recognition from this.
What's the movie?
They don't say.
Wait, he's in a movie?
What?
But Felix Esdrich responds and says, "I know that Tim is one of the last people who portray
Santa that do it for recognition.
He keeps his ego in check.
Let's pray that this is a very successful venture, of course, but not that Tim is lauded
or his ego boosted.
Ego is the last thing that Saint Nicholas was about."
Mm-hmm.
Facts.
What are you- what- that's bullshit, dude.
Santa's a fu- Santa's like the biggest fucking attention whore in the world.
He is.
Are you kidding me? This guy demands that you fucking, that you write him a letter every year?
Why can't- he's magic.
Well how else is he gonna know?
He's fucking friends with God! He can read your mind.
He's not friends with him, he's his brother.
He's not God's brother.
What?
It's not like-
What church did you go to growing up, idiot?
It's not like Greek, like, titans. It's not like God and Santa.
No, it is.
No, he's just a, he's a, he's a German guy, right?
Mm.
No.
They're brothers.
They're not, he's not brothers with, so what,
Jesus is Santa's nephew?
And he spends, and he celebrates his birthday by working?
Yes.
Yeah, this makes no, you have the most,
you always do this, you always ruin Christmas.
You are trying to ruin Christmas really hard.
I'm not trying to ruin Christmas,
I'm just telling you what I was taught.
You are trying extremely hard.
Here's someone else who tried to ruin Christmas.
Mall Santa gets 15 to 30 years for molesting young girl.
Oh.
Well that's really, what do people, are they pro him or against him?
Well here's a comment from Santa Marty, Honolulu, Hawaii.
Frankly, I don't see the fact that this criminal was also a mall Santa to be newsworthy.
The crimes that were perpetrated were not committed while he was a Santa actor.
Adding that this criminal was a Santa to the news story points out to me that the reporter,
editor, or manager of the media outlet has an underlying agenda.
[laughter]
They have an agenda against Santa.
It's an anti-Santa media agenda.
I mean, maybe the guy said he was Santa. I mean, he looks like Santa all the time.
Yeah.
He could have played it off like he was plain-clothed Santa when he did disgusting things.
Yeah. That's true.
Santa's should be on duty all the time you know like yeah well that's kind of I
would say that's a big part of what these people are campaigning for right it's
like if you look if you are looking at all like Santa don't do anything bad
because you might fuck it up for though I mean it's really a gang do they else
really is they should have a violent gang on every plane yeah is there a Santa on
the plane just this young boy has a wish yeah in case something like that or like
you know terrorist attack like they're trying to bring the plane down you know
what shows up this young child is having a savior lay under the plane oh yeah
he some kid wished for a big magnet for Christmas this year he puts a magnet
under or I mean I'll also just put put fucking 16 reindeer in the cargo hold
right yeah the engines start going yeah drop them absolutely you know yeah this
one I definitely want to hit this one before we finish up the Pat you you found
this one too this is what is the last thing you ate yeah this is a really good
this is a really good one this is a thread that's been going on for years
since July 15th 2007 is when I started yeah let me send you I mean I guess if
there is anybody in if there's any group of people that ate a lot yeah so that's
why it's very fun right so Michael Riley starts off okay this will be fun post
what was your last meal snack or drink? I'll start. Salami and cheese on potato bread sandwich,
ice green tea, smiley face. We got Sean Riley, I assume related to Michael Riley.
They gotta be, right?
Pretzlies and rice crackers.
This guy, wait, this guy Allison says, "Marmalade on whole meal with a cup of tea."
And then the next day, posting this thread again, "More whole meal toast with marmalade and tea."
I'm starting to see a pattern here.
So Sean Reilly also posted again, but on the same day, didn't even wait, Doritos X 13D.
Wait, and then he said the next day, "Hot dog on a bun."
And also, yeah, Michael Reilly posted the next day, "Coke Zero."
And then the next day he says, "Cheeseburger and hot dog."
I'm looking at Santa Bill Claus right now. He had an all meat Subway sandwich.
Dude, Sean Reilly is dominating this thread. A month later he says, "A hermit."
A hermit? He ate a hermit crab?
And then two months after that he says, "Buffalo chicken salad."
Santa Oliver had barbecue chicken and fried potatoes. Yummy.
I'm still on Sean Reilly two days later.
A slice of pepperoni pizza.
And the same day, cheesecake.
Oh, oh, I know.
The Godfather.
Oh, he's replying to something.
Santa Bill Claus here.
This is written in size 24 font.
Vegetarian casserole.
Ginny Claus had homemade turkey soup on October 9th, 2007.
Um, yeah, I mean this is, this is just...
- This, how long is this thread still active? - There's so many people just come back here
over and over again to say what they ate.
- Kona... - Santa Bill Claws had a salad last night with a Thousand Island dressing.
On April 30th, Kona says "Orange."
Guest Claws with a Claws says "Cheese."
Santa, Santa Buchan had Pop-Tart.
Santa Marty had Trail Mix.
Michael Reilly, "Hot Dog."
- Hot Dog seemed to be a... - Santa Buchan...
Santa Buccia in the same day after Pop-Tart says, "My lunch, a ham roll and crisps."
I mean, I, I, I, you know what I gotta say?
Severe lack of milk and cookies on this list.
Oh, and Santa had cookies.
Kona, this is one of my favorite signatures on the list.
Kona's really good.
Kona just says, "Rice."
Kona's interest, motorcycles and anything that goes fast, photography and all things
Christmas, and then here's his signature.
Kona, the Klan Klaus Society, founder and chairman, chieftain of Klan Kennedy, knight of St. Nicholas,
the sovereign military order of the Temple of Jerusalem Knights Templar, KlausNet member
of the month, May 2008.
Damn.
Uh, let's see.
A Santa-sized plate of spaghetti and homemade red sauce.
Spam.
Back to yogurt.
And then Santa Marty, Santa Leonard said Spam.
Marty says, "What variety did you have?" and then posts a picture of every spam that exists
and he just- and Santa Leonard replies, "Regular spam."
Holy shit dude, this is Carlo, Clem, and Kona going back to back like the clips.
Yogurt again, banana, spaghetti, rice pudding, pancakes.
This is all fucking Kona dude.
Kona came back the same day as Rice and said "Mint ice cream" and then the next day just posted "Orange".
Orange. Watermelon.
Cereal. The same day.
I need... "McD Hamburger Fries Apple Pie" says Kona.
"Salmon Patties with Coleslaw Jello".
Dude, Kona... Oh shit! Here we go, Kona. This is what I like.
Big glass of milk and a donut.
What... what... page number are you guys on? I'm not seeing any Kona.
6. Kona says a not so buzzshot. At some point Kona leaves. Dude what?
Kona posted in a really big font on May 2nd, pasta salad.
This guy June 2nd Kona says walnut brown. David Dixon a lunch prepared by the
youth at church. Dude Kona literally is just doing every meal he's ever eaten.
a hundred and forty three pages on this topic i'm gonna skip to page ninety nine
uh... a little more modern to see how the other ninety nine is only up to twenty
thirteen
holy fuck dude
do you think i would have to wait
i don't i hope not s_c_-santa had banana
leftover pork roast
there yet they still need to go everyday stew and rice from sales it was it was
kona's birthday on november twenty third you know it's the best thing about this
this forum maybe we should find out the forum that this is hosted on because
this is Kona's page looks like a myspace page can I I just want to read you on
Santa Marty's just just just read through his post on this page because he
was he was he's wilding out so November 19th turkey sandwich and chips same day
stew and rice same day cherry pie next day baked chicken white rice and string
beans same day banana same day like right after trail mix same day
cereals and skim milk same day sandwich and chips same next day
mandu soup mandu soup yes you do same day bagel spelled wrong yeah and he did the
same day roast turkey same day chocolate Cheerios I guess a peanut butter
Sandwich what what month is this?
November same day. Oh, dude. He's getting ready for Christmas, bro. He's trying to get as big as fucking possible next day Cheerios
Bagel this guy said hold on. Let me find this when he said probably one of the most disgusting sounding meals I've ever yeah
Okay, so he made it. This is Santa Bill Claus
Okay, Bill Crosby. He made it in the largest possible font he can and
Put it in pink and he says
Burger and noodles with Mexican cheese on top laced with some herbs and seasons. Oh
good
Santa Bill Claus I
have I have
Another Santa Marta Santa Marty as it approached Christmas in 2013 on December 15th. He wrote a little Christmas poem here for his meal
No, no quiet no, I just introduced it chill
You are a Grinch you are stealing from other you're Grinching mute yourself Rob Thomas had a hobnob
This is the Santa Marty's rhyming couplet on December 15th 2013 pork and rice posted via a mobile device
Wow oh my god
That is so beautiful. What a beautiful Christmas poem. Yeah, and something I forgot about this that I wanted to cover that
I just want to throw in here before we we finish
Is that they do on this website have a Santa Claus oath?
That you can take you can sign and take by proxy and I wanted to read it here
But the creator of the of the Santa Claus oath
Michael Riley
It's very specifically states that there that it is copyrighted and you cannot read it or post it anywhere
Well, and I do not want to get in trouble with them. So but just imagine a really fun Santa Claus oath
Yeah, I also I have one I think this should be the last one we read because this is
This I'm gonna link this to you guys. We're gonna we're gonna take this one at a time
This is I think a perfect beautiful ending to Christmas. Wait, we're not reading the Santa Claus oath. Are we no we're not
I'm sending you something. I just said we weren't you are a Grinch. You're going out eating it, bro
It's copyrighted. I don't give a fuck. I didn't read this. I'm not we're ending with I'm not getting this is tell a story
Three words at a time by Holly Claus and I'll start out. We're gonna we're gonna take turns
It's a 204 page. We're gonna read the first page
Cameron then me then Pat. Okay. Are you ready? Yeah. Mm-hmm one stormy night
long time ago
before you were
able to remember a
child born in
Bethlehem town to save mankind
took his cross
Saved our sins died for us
Rose for us walks on water
And he wondered at their disbelief
He healed many
By his stripes, we are saved.
We are saved?
We'll come again, not soon enough.
On eagles' wings?
Above the clouds, trumpets will sound.
Angels will sing.
Rain drops begin falling.
On my head, sits a crown of many thorns.
At his feet, which did bleed.
bleed by his blood we are saved clean as snow pure as gold wise men did kneel
praise the child wait hold on look at that fuckers picture yeah okay praise the
child of love in life born in Bethlehem Oh Holy Night stars brightly shining Oh
night divine plus
Thrill of hope I think we have lost the storyline. I think we can end there
Isn't that a beautiful Christmas story that was the most amazing thing I've ever heard except for Santa DBC fucking everything
Yeah, but it's all right. Merry Christmas
All and to all all good
Christmas Christmas, what were you gonna say Christmas? All right. Bye. I said mine
*Christmas bells*
Ho ho ho ho!
Feliz Navidad!
Ho Ho