Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
- Premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- All right, we're recording.
Oh, the sun is shining right in my eye.
- There's a lot of things going wrong today.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah.
- This is a bad, this is gonna be a bad one, everybody.
- Yeah, this is gonna be really, really bad.
- This is gonna be a really bad one.
Maybe the worst ever.
- I tried to get something to eat on the way here.
I tried to get a protein bar at CVS, didn't even scan.
The lady was like, "It's just not scanning."
- So you can't have it? - She's like, "You can't have it."
Like, you fucking, it's CVS.
- It's free if it doesn't scan.
- Get your shit together. - That's right.
It should be free if it doesn't scan.
- She tried to scan it with the gun,
tried to scan it at every register,
tried to scan it with her phone.
Well, that was the problem.
She shot a hole through it.
And I was like, "I don't want no hole in my damn Clif Bar."
- Yosemite Sam has fallen on hard times.
starting to work at CVS. I did get a varmint bar.
I was also just at CVS and I got my my COVID booster and my flu shot at the same time.
Well, that's what I'll say is like, yeah, I just got my COVID booster and I really have to say that
Microsoft devices be hitting different gifts this year.
What do you think of the Surface Pro?
I was just like yeah, I mean the thing about it is innovative and it's kind of like it's between a tablet and a laptop
But just something you don't see so true
Yeah, and I mean I can't speak for everyone
But everyone in my family would be over the moon to see one of those under the tree this year
My question is just under the menorah does Microsoft likes both does it come in different colors? No
Really the screen stays black until you turn it on
You know what I'm getting?
That's a good point.
I didn't think about that.
You know what I'm getting my family this year?
What?
One year of Microsoft Office.
Oh my gosh, that's another great gift.
I mean, that's a gift that lasts a whole year.
Microsoft 365.
Microsoft Surface, you can only use it one time.
Unless you charge it.
Damn.
I tried to use my pen on it.
And it was actually, I used a Sharpie.
And I couldn't get that stuff off the screen.
No.
great gift sharpies. I think I'm smelling.
Staples do be hitting different in the holidays season ever since.
They do be smelling amazing when you put them in your nose.
Yup. And they color the inside of your nose a different color than it could be otherwise.
Do you remember they used to have like scented markers and shit?
I loved smelling those. Those are the best.
They smelled so good. Those are honestly some of the best smells.
Have you ever smelled a vanilla marker? What?
A vanilla scented marker? Yes dude.
A scented marker? Have you ever smelled a vanilla one?
There was a vanilla smelling one that smelled just like vanilla.
Dude, the grape one?
I'm not kidding.
The grape one?
They had these little ones.
These kids in my class in like fifth grade, they were like this big and there was like
a vanilla one that someone had that looked like vanilla ice cream or something.
It was like supposed to, it had like a cone and you know what I mean?
And it smelled just like vanilla.
I have a money scented incense that I'm afraid to burn.
Yeah?
I'm afraid that it's going to actually affect my life.
Probably is.
Someone gave it to Janna for her birthday, so it was like a serious gift.
It was like, "This is going to bring you money."
Yeah.
I don't know how much more money I can take that makes so damn much money.
That's true.
I haven't burned any incense in my life yet because I'm waiting for the best one.
Someday they're going to have to, I mean, someday they're going to, you know, there's
incense that's like, "Oh, this one will bring you good luck.
This one will bring you money.
I just want to bring you love. I mean, I feel like it's only a matter of time before they
design one that's just all this stuff.
Yeah.
I would be--
It still smells like everything.
I'm worried about--
But nothing at the same time.
--going to get some incense because I see one and I go, "Oh, lime incense. This is going
to be pretty good." Go home, light it. Oh, shit. Crime incense. I accidentally got the
crime incense.
Yeah.
All of a sudden--
The smell is a beacon for criminals. They smell it wafting out of your window.
It's not like yeah money one you burn that money one a criminal smells that is gonna start climbing up your window. Yeah money
It's true a lot of ones that correct creme that could be yeah, they're gonna French for crime. Yeah, yeah
Grime mm-hmm bobbery for apples
Accidentally got robbery. Yeah, I could be products. I could be a my apple products. Yeah, yeah
Yeah, there's a lot of there's a lot of different instances that bring our city car Cinti
I accidentally got larceny.
Whoops.
Yeah, ooh, this delicious melanie smelling incense is actually a felony.
Yeah, whoops, I brought a felony power to my house.
Oh great, now I'm arrested.
Great, I just got arrested because I lit the wrong incense.
Burning a felony incense counts as committing a felony.
Yeah, if you burn it all the way down.
Well, it's because it's worth $500.
Yeah.
So if you burn the stick, you're destroying the property.
True, yeah.
I got a battery scented incense turns out is a different type of battery
But no I got somebody came into my house beat the fuck out of me that taste when you put that 9-volt on your tongue
Oh, it's impressed your brother. It's pretty good taste. Yeah. Yeah, I love the taste of you
Know when you leave a battery in the attic for a while and it makes white foam. Yeah. Mm-hmm. So cool. Yeah
I thought if I touched that stuff I would die.
Would you die?
I was so afraid of touching the white battery foam when I was a kid.
Really?
Yeah.
I would find, I would be like, "Oh, I forgot I had an RC car in the attic."
And I'd pull it out and it made rabies out of the battery box.
I wasn't afraid.
I would put that shit right in a plastic bag and put it outside.
How do you dispose, aren't you supposed to dispose of batteries a specific way?
You're supposed to recycle batteries.
You're supposed to put them in the trash but in a plastic bag first.
Really?
That's how we did it in my household.
That's sick.
I usually just flush them down the toilet.
Yeah.
You're supposed to throw them out the window as far as you can.
Get them as far away from you as possible.
Yeah.
I've never thought about the environmental damage a battery does.
Yeah, because that's where lightning comes from.
You just throw it away when you're done.
True.
Yeah, they say lightning actually comes from the ground to the clouds.
That's because it comes from batteries.
Do you remember the battery from Toy Story 2 in the beginning?
Yeah.
I wanted to eat that thing so bad.
- It looked delicious, man.
- It looked so good.
- Yeah.
- I wanted to eat it.
- Oh my God, it's so special.
- I would eat like a Halo Shield battery.
- Oh yeah.
- Yeah.
- That'd be good.
- That'd be a good battery to eat.
- I wanna eat one of the needles from the Needler.
- Oh those would be so sour.
- You know that shit would be pink limited.
- Yeah, sour rock candy.
- Yeah, that's all my dope.
- You know that shit would be pink limited.
- What other ammo from video games would taste good?
(laughing)
- I mean, any of the plasma grenade,
putting that in your mouth.
Blue plasma probably tastes so good that it's the best.
- Though I bet like, I feel like a rocket,
like rocket ammo from like Fortnite,
I feel like you could screw it open
and have some kind of really good powder.
- All the Fortnite stuff looks like candy.
- Yeah, not the ammo though.
- Yeah, the ammo doesn't.
- Most of those look like bullets, except for the rockets.
- It could be a damn cake.
- Yeah, hey, the Fortnite shield potion.
I would literally drink that every single day of my life.
- I wish I could drink a choke jug.
- I don't drink soda or energy drinks,
but I would drink shield potion.
What's that soda slurp?
Oh yeah, that's Chug.
Chug.
I think you're talking about the real life one.
Surge.
Which Surge looks like a battery.
Yo, the Minecraft dirt block though.
Oh, jeez.
They should get Benjamin Babish on the Minecraft dirt block.
He should be doing that crap.
That might be busted.
It might actually be really good, we don't know.
Who knows, man.
He wouldn't make it with real dirt, he'd make it with chocolate pudding and Oreo crumbs.
- Man up and eat the dirt.
- Make some real dirt.
- Just eat the dirt.
- Yeah, a big dirt block in your house.
- I'll do it myself.
- Dude, I also, I feel like if you could cook
a Koopa Troopa in its shell.
- Oh, man.
- Oh, fucking wow.
- The only problem would be the underwear,
the boxer shorts.
- That's just mo soup for me.
- Koopa soupa?
- Kinda wanna eat a turtle.
- Yeah.
- Never eaten a turtle?
- I saw a video.
is a video of a turtle being prepared.
- I saw a video of a turtle being prepared
in Cannibal Holocaust.
That made me unhappy to see.
- Yeah, maybe I have to see that
because they were putting like star anise
and like chilies on it.
- In Cannibal Holocaust,
they just like crack the shell off it
and it's disgusting and they wanna throw it.
- The thing is about a turtle is that
it made me less interested in eating them
is that their shell is not like--
- The shell is the body.
- It's not like a rock they're stuck in.
- Yeah, no, it's like they're a part of them.
You think because you learn about hermit crabs in your kid, you think a turtle is the same
situation.
No, they can feel every time you touch a shell.
Yeah.
So like, yeah.
The nerve endings on a shell, that's crazy.
Oh, dude, I bet they cum so hard when you touch the shell.
I'd love to have a shell.
It's like a hoof on top of them.
It's like their foreskin.
It's not like their foreskin.
It's exactly like their foreskin.
And then shave it off.
They don't need it.
It's my uncut turtle.
Yeah.
(laughing)
- Yeah, I circumcise turtles for a living.
- I think scientists should stop trying to clone sheep
or clone mammoths or whatever and work on just like
genetically modifying a turtle with no shell.
'Cause I think that would be one of the best looking animals.
- There is a soft shell turtle.
- Not a soft shell, no shell.
- Yeah, it looks like it has no shell.
- I'm not talking about looks like it has no shell.
- Turtle arms, turtle legs, turtle head, man's white body.
(laughing)
That's what you want?
- I thought you were going with like a Rayman thing there.
it's like a turtle, pretty much all composed together except the arms are floating.
We don't know. I mean, there could be gravity involved.
That'd be so cool to have a floating limbs, like Plock or Rayman.
How scary is it to fight Rayman?
We don't know where that arm's going.
Exactly. And also, how can I even kill? Are you even killable?
I feel like if I walked between Rayman's arm and his hand and his body, I would get cancer.
and die. Definitely yeah. Your hand is already. He just has to move his hand next to you and
I think you would. Yeah. Yeah his hand around you. Yeah exactly. Like he throws his arm. Yeah
just he does a circle around. That's what, that's what, Ray is radioactive man. Yeah. Whoa. Whoa.
Whoa. We cracked the case. I may be, I may be just, that might be a. And the rabbits must have,
the rabbits have birth defects from the radiation. That's why they're like that. Oh my fucking god.
That's why they're so annoying. You're kind of like a real life rabbit. Yeah a little bit. How? Just I hate you
And you're white
You don't hate me. I'm not white you like this
I don't have that my teeth are small
That's one of your defects
Yeah. Yeah
I didn't I didn't know I had your short until cameron called them small one time and I went home and I was really
Self-conscious holding up a vanity mirror
And I was like, "Yeah, I guess they are kind of small."
(laughter)
I always thought I had big teeth.
That's funny.
(laughter)
I didn't know that.
Yeah, I guess you do.
Somebody said I had a big nose the other day.
You don't have a big nose.
I don't have a big nose at all, but then I got self-conscious about it.
And then I started looking at my side profile and I was like, "No."
I think I don't even, I didn't even notice you had small teeth
until you showed me that picture of you as a kid
where your teeth are like dots.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, you do.
Well, that's because I used to grind my teeth so much in my sleep that they like...
Your rice teeth.
Yeah, I shaved them down to like little rice...
Yeah, you got Bobby Peru teeth.
Who's that?
From that one movie.
What's the movie called?
Bobby Peru?
What movie is that?
It's a David Lynch movie.
They're like fish teeth.
Yeah.
Yeah, they're like goose teeth.
The ones he has.
Yeah, the goose, exactly.
Yeah.
The little bumps.
I don't have fish teeth.
You used to, I'm saying.
Oh.
Now you have big fish teeth.
Yeah.
teeth are kind of, I mean, you know. I wish I had shark teeth. I have some British in me.
I don't have to, I don't have to get into that. Yeah, you want some? I already have it. I don't
need any more. Yeah, you want a little. I wish I could expunge all of it. Do you have a little
wild at heart? Oh, okay. Willem Dafoe. Oh, I did have little Bobby Peru teeth. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, when I was like six years old, I had Bobby Peru teeth. Yeah. But my gums were normal.
They didn't look like that.
I don't know.
Let's go to the fact checker.
I think you might have done what Bobby Perut did in that movie.
Fact checker just saying no.
Fact checker just saying you're lying.
There's some kind of gum disease.
Periodontitis.
I'm glad we hired a fact checker.
Yeah, it's great to have.
Yeah.
You got us all hooked up to a lie detector.
Well we don't bother using him anymore for the rest of the episode though.
Yeah.
Just that.
So if you loved that, sorry.
If you loved that incredible.
We're not making it into a bit.
It's not going to happen for 10 minutes.
No sir.
Nope.
Right fact checker?
Silence.
Yep.
He's died.
He died right now.
He passed away.
He's already decomposing.
It's like that video of that fox.
He swelled up and then he burst with maggots.
Things are just eating him off of the forest floor.
We're in the forest.
Speaking of maggots, have you ever seen those videos of people and they get maggots in them?
Oh yeah.
What's that called?
And they pop the maggots out like it's a big zit.
But then you see it start like moving.
The ones, they just have like big holes on their body.
Yep.
That's so cool, man.
I saw a video of like a stray dog in a...
And the guy that they're removing them from is always just like, just sitting there.
Like there's just maggots coming out of his head.
Yeah.
That the guy is taking out with a scalpel and he's just like kind of smiling.
I feel like if...
Well, it's probably...
I would be kind of smiling if the maggots were being removed.
first. Well, I would just be finally. That's probably the first good day of his life. I'd
probably be walking around. That's probably like the best day he's ever lived. His best
day still ends up with like a bunch of fucking holes in the back of his head. Yeah. That's
sucks. At least the maggots blocked the holes from the elements. That's true. Because they
like, you know, these people live in. The elements do be trying to get into the holes
in his head. And these are the kind of people who get maggots in their head, they live in
the elements. Yeah, the elemental plane. Yeah. They live in the element store in Universal
exactly yeah they sell you surfboards and shit yeah oh don't mind my head oh yeah don't mind
this big one giant maggot out the top what are they called something bug bugs maggot
heads but what are you asking there's a word for the there is a word for when you have
maggots in you it starts with an m i'm pretty sure yeah maggot maggot in flesh word oh it's
It's myiasis.
M-Y-I-A-S-I-S.
That's what it is.
Myiasis.
Stinky.
That's right.
That's true.
Yup.
Yes, sir.
Imagine how much more beautiful the rest of your body looks when your head has maggots
in it.
Yeah.
You could probably seduce so many women.
Dude, like the...
I saw a video of a stray dog at the vet and they're like popping the maggots out of the
dog like it's a zit.
Fuck that, bro.
Yeah.
I gotta stop looking up weird shit.
You always will be hanging out and you'll be like and you'll just suddenly look at your
phone and instantly just go "Ugh!" and I'll be like "What's wrong Patrick?" and you're
like "I just saw a guy made into a sandwich."
Yeah and we're like "Oh was it like a surprise video?" and you're like "No it was called
'Guy Made Into Sandwich' and I clicked on it."
Yeah, I don't know I'm in like fucking some group chat where they send gross shit.
There was like Rex last night in the car was just watching that video. Those guys got shot a million times.
He was like, "Oh my god! Oh god!"
He just stalled it over.
And then there was like a long pause and you could hear him just start the video over to watch it again.
That's so funny.
I was like, "What is wrong with you, man?"
Well, that's the thing.
He's darkly twisted.
Trainwreck stuff like that, like, I think I look at it just so it's like, you know, it doesn't,
Not so it desensitizes me, but it just keeps me grounded.
You know what I mean?
What?
Like, looking at crazy shit, I feel like it keeps you...
You're getting a little too big for your britches, you think?
And you gotta watch how the fucking ice is going to cavitate on there.
Well, that's why I eat rotten dookie once a month, because it's like...
Rotten dookie.
Yeah, well, because it's like, you know, like...
How does it look?
You gotta make a difference.
It's actually way different from fresh.
I immediately knew as you...
On the walk over here, I saw some rotten dookie that had been sitting there so long
long that it developed a skin. Yeah, it looked like a brown banana. I remember
back in our apartment in Boston on from the walk from the apartment to the car
there was like human shit that was literally there for like more than a
month and there was a rainstorm and it did not wash away. Whoa. It was literally
like a pile of shit so big and so so I saw that in a parking garage in LA. Yeah. Yeah, I was like skating around.
We saw some human shit on the boardwalk last night.
Did we?
Yeah, maybe you didn't.
I didn't.
You left it.
He dropped out of his pants and he just kept going.
Whoa, what's that?
That's crazy.
I didn't see that.
Yeah.
I'm still kind of bummed that the Rainforest Cafe didn't let us in.
Yeah, that was fucked.
It would have just been a long wait.
Fuck that, man.
I've never been, but it was.
I truly didn't know there were any still open, though.
I know.
That's why I got so excited.
I was excited, too.
- If we go to AC, we definitely gotta get a reservation.
- We'll make a reservation.
- We'll make a reservation for the Reinforce Cafe.
- Oh, dude.
- 'Cause like, out of nowhere, there'll be like,
thunder and shit, and then you'll hear like,
gorilla sounds while you're eating.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- That's the best.
- That would scare me.
- Yeah.
Oh, we gotta go.
- Yeah, we can go next week.
- Dude, that'd be awesome.
- I feel terrible today.
I just didn't even drink anything.
I just had that gambling hangover.
- I feel horrible.
- I got home and forgot that drunk me, two nights ago,
I bought a 4 Loko Gold.
Don't tell me you drank that at 2 in the morning last night.
I drank a 4 Loko Gold at 11 when I got home.
What the fuck is wrong with you man?
I don't know.
What's the gold version mean?
14% ABV.
Wow.
And how much caffeine is in that?
None.
There's no more caffeine in 4 Loko.
Oh really?
Yeah.
I've never had one.
Me neither.
You haven't?
No.
There was a period in my life where I was just drinking 4 Loko's.
Yo, you gotta.
It's not it's like more expenses in a tall boy. No, it's the same price as a tall boy
Really and it's taller than most tall boys
How tall in feet probably it's probably 25 ounces. It's like a foot tall. It's like the same as a natty daddy
Though that's if you drink this shit natty daddies is a problem. Yeah, dude. There was a guy at the world
It was fun. There's a guy at the liquor store who would come in
pretty much every day and he would get he would
you would get like six Natty Daddies and
Tall Pans?
Yeah and you would get like
Yeah Natty Daddies are a boy
I think it was like two like blueberry Smirnoff nips and then a pack of
Parlaments, Parlaments of the hundreds and he would come in and he would
never order, he would come in and you just get that stuff for him and he
would always be like, "Oh yeah, you have to remember my order because it's all
blue."
(laughing)
- The blue man.
Was he blue?
That's how you prep for the blue man group.
(laughing)
- Yeah, that's the hazing in the blue man group.
- Yeah, they got me drinking all these blue drinks.
- Are they allowed to talk to each other, you think?
- No.
- They don't know each other.
They don't know who each other are.
- True.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, 'cause they're blue.
- Yeah, I'm sure.
- You can't recognize a blue man.
- They don't know each other off stage.
Do you think they have hair?
No. Those are bald caps?
They have secret identities though. They do. Superman, Batman, Green Lantern.
They just gotta let out some steam every once in a while. How do you think that started the Blue Man Group?
Probably a lot of gay sex.
Probably a lot of sex between a bunch of guys together.
I just can't imagine like... Yeah, the idea process is very...
It's hard to follow that train of thought.
It seems very simple, but also there's probably some really complex reason as to why.
I don't think it seems that simple. I think it's a very weird combination.
We're going to be blue, not talk, and drum.
Well, which order do you think they came in?
I think it was probably drumming, and then they were like, "We need a twist on this. What if we were all blue?"
And we can't talk.
Well, they just hate each other. That wasn't even a rule.
The Beatles didn't talk much either.
yeah that whole that new Peter Jackson 40 40 minutes of silence mm-hmm 40 hours of
silence 4,000 hours of silence actually that's why that's what I wish would come
out from the Beatles oh my god yes hey Beatles you're on notice that's right
yeah you know I were coming for the rest of you you know what my main experience
with the Beatles is what is the Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band movie
with the Bee Gees in it. Alice Cooper sings "Because". I liked that. I thought that movie was sick.
I liked the Help movie. Oh, the Help movie's fun. Yeah. Hard Day's Night also very fun.
The one with the Dookie Pie? I don't remember. The Help? No. The Dookie Pie movie?
Help, the Beatles movie. Oh, I don't know that. I was like, I don't think the Beatles were in the Help.
I'm sure they were listening to them. True. They were listening to the
Beatles every day on that set. Yeah. But yeah the Sgt. Pepper's movie. Steve
Martin sings Maxwell's Silver Hammer. That's a fun one. It's a cool movie, dude.
Yeah. The Beatles movies are all pretty cool.
What movies? The Beatles movies are all pretty cool. Yeah.
Apparently everyone hated the Sgt. Pepper's movie.
Yeah. Yeah. Which I was like dude it was sick when I was fucking 12. I'm sure
on a rewatch you'd understand why yeah probably yeah yeah is there nudity in it
no yeah literally no good yeah it's a Frampton's beautiful body oh he is good
looking he in that movie yeah nice looking good and all the BG's - don't
even see one dong from the BG's no don't even see Robins Gibb come on now come on
Come on. Down low. Down low. What? Down low. Down low. Oh, okay. I just forgot. You forgot
to put your hand up. You said down low without holding your hand. I forgot that you have
to do that. I thought you could just say down low and something's cool. Yeah. Up top, down
low, too slow. Hey, high five. In the middle. Say that. High five. Don't touch my pickle.
You got really close to the pickle right there. I did. I did almost get some pickle there.
Yeah, remember it was kind of strange.
Oh no, wait, you guys weren't with me.
When you touched a pickle?
No, I went to this diner, the place that I found the Hamburger Delight, and I ordered
a sandwich because I thought like, "Oh, it's going to come with fries, coleslaw, and a
pickle."
First of all, they didn't even put any tzatziki on the gyro, which is fucked up.
That's fucked up.
to put like if I'm getting a gyro, it's got to be like two globs of tzatziki on that thing.
Globs.
Globs, yeah.
A glob I feel like is not very big.
No.
In terms of a sauce.
No, that's the perfect amount in a gyro.
In a sauce.
You also can't glob every sauce.
But a tzatziki.
Tzatziki you can glob.
That's a globby sauce.
But like a chipotle mayo can't be globbed.
No, no, no, no.
No, it's too runny.
- Mm-hmm, but yeah, I didn't even get the coleslaw
or the pickle with that, and there was not even,
there were no tzatziki on the gyro.
And I forget what this diner's called, but steer clear.
- Yeah, stay away from diners.
- Was that literally the whole story?
- Yes.
- And you, not only did you bring it up,
but you were like, oh, you guys weren't with me.
- Yeah.
- Like, we would've remembered that if we were with you?
I would have complained about not getting a pickle, yes.
Well, 'cause a diner pickle's fuckin' awesome.
Just ask for the pickle, you fuckin' weirdo.
No, it said it, it was on the menu,
it said it comes with a pickle.
Yes, it said, "I didn't get my coleslaw
"and I didn't get my pickle."
Not gonna do that.
Why?
Why not?
'Cause it seems rude.
You think it's rude to not give you a pickle?
That's true.
I think honestly, wait staff--
You literally let them bend you over and fuck you.
Nobody is more predatory than people
in the service industry.
Yeah, they're literally to take advantage of you literally at every single every
opportunity because they literally all they're doing while they're like I need
to get home and I need to do drugs. Yeah, or I need to get back in the back and I
know I need to die so soon. Oh, I need to go home and die in my bathroom. I have
to go home and kill myself. I need to make sure that this shift gets over soon
so I can go home and kill myself. Shut up. Give me my pickle. I need to exploit
as many people as possible today. That's what they say. Oh yeah, diner pickle
That's good.
You want to get this pickle on the side of the sandwich?
You shouldn't feel bad telling me these.
One pickle next to the sandwich?
If you're a waiter or a waitress, you're like...
It's that half pickle.
Literally, I'm not even kidding, you're like subhuman to me.
You're like complete dirt.
Why?
Why not?
Why not say that?
I don't know.
Why are you...
Is my mommy's one?
Yeah, case and point.
Because you're talking about my mommy?
Case and point.
Yeah.
That's messed up.
You don't talk about my mommy like that.
Your mommy is...
She subs on my human.
(laughing)
- Nope.
Nope.
- Yeah, I showed her my human sub.
(laughing)
- Speaking of diners too.
- She served me, no wait.
- 50's diner, nuh-uh.
- She let me have breakfast all day.
- Yeah, I dined on her 50.
Doesn't make any sense.
(laughing)
- I hate 50's themed diners.
- Yeah, I got in a race car booth.
- Unless it has a race car booth.
the hollywood bk dude we still haven't made the trip stop trying to distract us
from your mom's vagina yeah i rocketed my johnny in her
stop it okay stop it now i'm all in her milkshake listen to this i gave her an egg cream
but we gotta go to the hollywood bk yeah i still haven't been yeah we gotta sit i've never been
either i'd be down to go you've never i can't go today you're longer than me i walk yeah burger
Burger King's not on my list of things usually.
- Yeah, but you look in there and you see that it's got
like cardboard, so you don't walk in.
- I do, every time I walk by there,
I feel like an orphan walking by a Christmas store.
(laughing)
I want it so bad. - In the cold.
- Dude, it's just pictures of Denzel Washington
on the wall, and Mike Myers.
- I feel like there's a very little difference
between seeing it and being inside of it eating.
- Being inside of it is so depressing.
- But then if I go inside, I have to eat Burger King.
- It's awesome.
- And I gotta deal with, like I said,
those pieces of shit who work there.
yeah
here's my thing to get a cat who do you can't tip good europe
the up automated already i wasn't gonna anyway
yeah you just be basically just removed me put putting a lot of tips section of
the receipt
i wish you could i wish i said it was couldn't see them cooking your food back
in the back as they're so damn ugly
speaking of art
all your right we'll talk about this about
Yeah, I accidentally robbed a homeless man. He robbed him blind. He really stole what?
I thought he was giving me a nice gift because it was Christmas and he was in the giving spirit
and uh no I just walked away with a with a this guy came up to us and I see a homeless guy and
he handed uh he handed Patrick a Christmas card and he said I don't like to just ask for money
I like to give people something in return. I didn't hear that. So if you could spare any money here's a
through a megaphone yeah yeah and Patrick said sorry I don't have any
money and then walk and then ran away and ran away holding the Christmas card
I forgot to give it back to him yeah I didn't run away you ran away going
did yeah I ran away I said sorry sir and he's going to the CEO you did you heard
him. He had closed captions on. He had words floating in front of him. He had a little LED
necklace. That said everything. Just to fight that excuse. And you ran away with his thing.
That's so sick. A person with closed captions. That's so fucking sick. That'd be so... They
should have that on... A whole screen and you wear it around your neck like it's a Flavor
Flav chain and it just says ever it's got a little yeah yeah Mike oh my god that
before I speech man to you each to text read yeah yeah but uh son yeah I
genuinely for a so much your chair move for God's sake where am I a move to just
a move close sons in your I can't just spin around just look the other way yeah
I want to look at your ass anyway that's the most guilt I felt because I genuinely
We did not, no.
I can't believe he's talking.
I was not paying attention to this.
Just put a visor on.
You had a hat on earlier.
You can't put a hat over his headphones.
That's true.
You can put it under the headphones.
I'm thieved up.
I don't feel good.
Dude, I hope the, I wonder if the booster is going to be as bad as the second shot.
I got a booster and flu shot at the same time.
Oh, god.
So you were a madman.
Yeah, well I had to get them both.
I don't want like two different days of feeling like shit.
How many microchips can one man have in his body?
I mean I already have a lot.
I mean he already had so many.
Yeah.
The human computer this guy.
That's what we call him.
Because I look up porn on him.
I can google search anything in my mind.
Okay.
Try it.
Alexis Texas in butt woman.
Wow.
Yep.
Looking good.
I searched it and I saw it.
Nice.
August Ames, date of death.
Wow, this is interesting.
3564 AD.
I knew they were lying.
I knew they were fucking lying, dude.
That was a heartbreaker.
I think Ben told me, he had a co-worker that was like, he was like, "Hey man, how you doing?"
He's like, "Oh, not too good.
My favorite porn star just died."
That's sick.
Dude, that's so funny.
You know who's from my hometown?
Just being like a small town guy is just like...
Your family?
My family.
And Stoya.
Really?
From my hometown.
Wow.
Yep.
Who's that?
I don't know.
I think she might be a athlete. She sounds like a musician to me. I think she is a
musician yeah. She's the one that she's like she dated Marilyn Manson. I don't know.
You're thinking, that's how I know about it. You're thinking of the Bride of Frankenstein.
Oh yeah. Yeah you're thinking of a skeleton in a wig. Yeah and the wolf woman.
yeah yeah wolf woman yeah that's a bad lot in life the wolf woman dated marilyn
manson wolf man you can get away with i'm turkish wolf woman tough no i mean wolf
man could get away with it by saying oh i'm simply a balkan man okay yeah i don't know
why i thought you were telling me you were turkish you look like turkish from snatch
and that's a compliment. Thank you for saying that. I appreciate you. It's very sweet. I don't think
his name is Turkish. Yeah, it is. Is it? Jason Statham's character's name is Turkish. Oh,
I thought you just were talking about Turk. No, it's Turk from Scrubs who you also look like.
Yeah. Turk from Scrubs, that's cool. That's pretty fucking cool. You know,
Jason Statham's like almost 60 years old yeah it's crazy five or something you
finding out Jerry Seinfeld was like 60 when I was in like high school I was
like blown away but then I was like no that makes perfect sense yeah he just
says the hair dye on line yeah yeah most facts I learned actually make perfect
sense to me yeah well most facts are they make perfect sense yeah yeah yeah
What's a fact that blew your mind recently?
Get this
Die hard not a Christmas movie really I think it is my friend. I think it's kind of the only
You just said it was a fact that it wasn't prove it
No takes place on Halloween. That's can't be true. It's true. If you look at the behind-the-scenes photo
It's actually a Halloween party where everyone was weren't dressed as
Santa Christmas party
Exactly Santa was a Halloween costume. Oh, dude. I didn't even think about
That we're gonna be seeing that this month what Santa bar crawl Santa con?
Yeah, I think Santa comes probably this weekend actually. Oh fuck me dude. I'm afraid of Santa Santa con sucks
Santa con is not he's not gonna come to fucking Brooklyn Santa cons like a Manhattan thing
I don't want to see him. You don't have to see Santa if you don't want to
What is your deal? Why are you afraid of Santa Claus?
I sat down on his lap as a kid and he said, "Shut up."
He said shut up?
He said shut up.
What did you say when he said shut up before?
What made him say shut up to you?
I was crying because I had to sit on his lap.
Yeah.
If I was Santa Claus and your mom handed me fucking you as a six year old, I would have
punted you like a football.
I feel like small Santas should be allowed to hit kids and like the parents aren't allowed
to but the mall Santa once a year.
It's like a sorting hat.
Well, yeah, if the kid mall Santa's to get hit. Yeah, exactly
It's like if your kid if yeah, your kid has that you like goes up to mall Santa
It's like I want I want a fortnight gift card
Yeah, no, no more video game if Santa can you see it's like like you get a bunch of empaths to be mall Santas
So they can tell when the parents are annoyed with the kids. I think you should get a bunch of a paths
Yeah, hey, who'd want to destroy the kid? What's an a path just die?
hate. Psychopath. An antipath. An antipath. I'm one of those. Yeah me too I hate
everything. I use psionic energy to attack people. Here, tell me something about your life Pat.
My best friend is Caleb. I don't care. Wait it is? Maybe I'm not an antipath.
Mm-hmm. Maybe I'm pathing. Yeah. Yeah. There's a pretty good picture of me and my
family with a mall Santa. It's like a Polaroid. It's cool. My... There's a pretty
good picture of me and your family. No, actually there is a pretty nice picture
of you meeting my mom and dad for the first time. Yeah, it's in the MoMA.
The title is The Aristocrats. But it's my little brother's crying. I have my fists
up like I'm about to fight Santa. My brother's yawning and like my sister's
just like not looking in the picture. So if you, you know, if you were that mall
Santa I can really say it in my head I completely agree with you yeah the Santa
should have hit me that's gonna be a bad job I wonder if you get paid well that's
probably that's one of the closest jobs to slavery yeah it's being a mall Santa
absolutely as you also can literally only do it if you're like a yeah I wonder
if anybody's ever like kind of 80% there and they're like well I need a job I got
time to go time to go fucking Christian Bale and prepare for the role, you know, eating
doughnuts and girl. Yeah, who wants to be a mall Santa? I think it's something I think
it's something you fall into one day. Yeah, you wake up after like a bender. The eight
ball bag is like on your forehead and you look in the mirror and you're like fuck I
look like exactly. Yeah, I have to fuck I need to just unemployment check. Last night
was so crazy. I turned into Santa. Yeah, exactly. I feel like it's like the squid game where
where they scout you, they pull you into a world,
an underworld of intrigue.
- I feel like when you're old,
you'll have a Santa thing going on.
- Me? - Yeah.
- 'Cause you'll keep your hair and you're tall.
And I feel like you might be able to get real fat
if you want to.
- I could probably get fat if I wanted to.
- We're gonna stuff you.
- Don't stuff me.
- We're gonna stuff you like a turkey.
- I think that I wouldn't want to be Santa.
- We're gonna be feeding you nothing but gravy
for the rest of your days.
is
was thinking of the real center of the world or
the couple
like i was really a lie
yeah you know it's gonna hit me like over the course of this but it's really
kind of waves like i am here
i'm sweating
i'm saying it
He's sticking right now?
I'm sticking right now!
He starts like singing.
That's such a great video.
Another episode where we talk about a video we saw.
Just a guy freaking out.
People like that.
People like to find the videos.
People like talking about videos.
You know what I learned recently is people don't
just sit around and watch YouTube videos with their friends.
I think that's just an us thing I've learned.
I've learned. Maybe we just have weird some of the top curators. I don't think that's
true. I think a lot of people watch YouTube. I think that's really common. I think you
probably met one person who said that was weird. Yeah, yeah. That's probably. My friend
group's like we're low-key like weird. We watch videos together. Yeah, yeah. We like
like YouTube. Sorry, yeah. We watch a daily dose of internet on the couch together. Who
cares? Yeah, we do. I'll fuck. I love that kid. This is a dog that has a scarecrow. I
that has a skateboard.
Yeah.
I wish Daily Dose of Internet would have a daily overdose of internet.
I hope that guy dies.
Yeah, I hope he gets a daily dose of Fintanelt.
Fintanet.
Finternel.
Finternelt.
Yeah, I hope he gets a one-time dose.
Yeah.
Of Fintanent.
Of Flinternet.
are meant and it sounds like a toothpaste though I hope that guy chokes on his
toothpaste and I hope it's spicy toothpaste and it hurts his throat when
I show you that spicy I hate a spicy toothpaste to stop making that spicy
toothpaste oh y'all I ate a Reese's Cup the other day it was spicy as hell you
better make a sweet to face or that would be so good though what like a
Reese's Cup a Reese's Cup no like a Reese's Cup with like chili powder in it
I know that's what you meant, but I couldn't resist.
Because they have that, like, the Lindt chocolate chili one, and that one goes crazy.
Yeah, you might enjoy Mexico.
Yeah.
They got all kinds of freaky, spicy chocolate crickets and shit.
What are they called?
Gozos?
Dude, I had...
Every piece of that Mexican candy he gave us was disgusting.
I ate a piece today, it's like the caramel kind of thing, and it's not very big, it's
probably like this big.
I was like, I just want like a little piece of candy and I add it in two or three bites.
And then I looked at the nutritional facts. It's like 450 calories for like two bites of candy.
It's like it defied the laws of physics. Yeah, that's all like the dulce de leche stuff.
Yeah. Yeah.
Is that one again?
Those little...
Dulce de leche.
Those those ones with the nuts on it, the dulce de leche nuts thing. You know, like the little
like it's like the toffee bar but it has like almonds and shit on it.
I don't fuck with- Those went crazy.
Stop putting vegetables in my candy bro.
Nuts is not candy.
That's what I'm saying.
Nuts is not vegetables.
Tell that to the ground where they're from.
Yeah.
Fucking moron.
What about peanut butter?
That's vegetables.
You don't like peanut butter chocolate?
Of course I love peanut butter but I don't- I mean-
That's mostly the butter work in there.
Well you gotta try this candy bar out. It's chocolate and celery.
That doesn't sound very good. That sounds very vegetal.
Too crunchy.
Yeah. Check this out.
That's too crunchy for my white ass.
My teeth will break.
Here's a crazy combo I just thought of.
Okay.
Celery.
Yep.
Put peanut butter in the shoot.
Okay.
The shoot.
And then you put raisins on top of it.
Okay. Well, what are we going to call it?
Probably dookies on a log.
Yeah.
Little turds on a brown thing.
Turds on a turd river.
Turds on a turd on a celery.
No, I call it a--
Two turds on celery.
I call it a green and brown.
yeah no you don't yeah that's an Irish thing yeah yeah come out you green and
come out you green and browns come and take me to the ground want you to beat
my ass till I am green and brown what is that song about come out you black and
tans yeah so who are the black and tan black and tans are like the British mmm
why I don't remember I don't know yeah obviously yeah that song is just like
saying like fuck you black and tans mmm yeah yeah you don't like the blacks and
the tans listen Eric Clapton what a rant in his concert about black and tans and
you have a rant in your life about black and I have a rant in my notes app I keep
about blacks and tans. Tans. I'm sick of all these people coming out of the fucking tanning
booths. Check out these greenos. These greenos and the tans. Oh dude, the Jersey Shore cast,
I'm so sick of them. I thought they were called greenos when I was a kid. Yeah. Yeah. But
um. What are they talking about? Blacks and tans, now you don't care much for that. Yeah.
Oh yeah, there's a drink, the black and tan.
Yep.
There's another one, Sprite.
It's messed up.
Sprite, pretty good.
Lemon and lime.
A combination I would have never thought of.
I had a drink earlier that was...
I would have thought lemon and lime was going to be pretty redundant.
Turns out it's...
They're a compliment to each other.
They're kind of crazy good together.
See, that's the thing, like lemon and lime works, but if you have like a orange and lemon,
it's not that good.
It's not as good as lemon.
Or like if you have like lemon and poo.
It usually isn't true.
- What the hell?
Okay. - They're together.
- I would like to honestly go the other way on this.
I think that poop would be greatly,
greatly improved with lemon juice all over it.
- But lemon would be dragged down.
- But lemon on the other hand,
lemon's like, I don't know if you've ever
put a lemon in your mouth.
It's not great to begin with.
But to have kind of,
something about if you added poop to lemon,
you'd be like, oh, this sucks.
But if you added lemon to poop, it'd be a bit of a relief.
You squeeze a lemon over it like it's a shrimp?
Yeah, exactly.
And it's curled like a shrimp.
And you've got to de-vein it like a shrimp.
Well, yeah, that's the best part about poop.
It's all the shrimp's vein.
I love eating the shrimp veins.
Just collect all the veins and give them to me.
There's something about them.
I love eating shrimp so much.
I'd be down to get some seafood this weekend.
- Oh fuck yeah, dude.
- I haven't had it in a while.
- We should get some safe food.
- You know what, I've never been to one of those places
where they just give you like a fucked up bag
and you pour it on the table.
- Yep.
- I've never done that.
- I wanna do that shit.
- Yeah, I wanna do that shit.
- Yeah, dude, I wanna get like a,
dude, I've said it before, but I can eat 80 shrimp.
80 shrimp, one sitting.
- I thought you said any shrimp.
- Let's do it.
- 80 shrimp?
- I can eat 80 shrimp in one sitting.
- Let's do it.
- I'd like to see you try.
- Let's film it.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
be hard for me yeah 80 shrimp 80 shrimp not hard for me shrimp get fucking gross
after 10 no yeah not for me dude there's this fucked up we're making a video we're
gonna record you eating 80 shrimp okay you can't spare the room for the cocktail
sauce at that point no I can how big is your big belly pretty big can you slab
it twice that might be able to hold that might might have the capacity for a
truant I've done the math how about okay okay no that's what I say can we try a
hundred cuz that's like that's a way more that's a click baity number yeah
that's like we could we could make it big with like like well okay it all
depends on your shrimp size 100 shrimp that could be like the biggest video on
YouTube we can get like one of those the shrimp rings at Costco that have like a
a hundred shrimp you don't get to pick the type of shrimp that you eat you don't
get where they come from no no no no no no this shrimp shrimp also come in
varying sizes what kind of shrimp are we the ones that come in the rings okay
fried jumbo shrimp yeah a hundred king shrimp fried shrimp I could probably eat
probably 25 for I could I could eat your go here going a hundred fries I could
I could eat 80 pieces of popcorn but I might throw up.
I might get so full.
What size popcorn?
Little. Unpopped.
Kernels.
That's pretty easy I would say.
Dude, we've been talking about it. I think we've had this conversation twice this week, but half popped kernel.
Oh yeah, if they could somehow figure out a way to sell half popped kernel popcorn.
That'd be perfect.
That'd be so...
You like those?
Oh, those are the best.
Those are the best.
Because it's like eating a nut, but like, it's like a nut, like a microwave popcorn.
Have you ever tried eating raw popcorn?
Just the kernels?
No.
Well, what if you might like it?
No, that's not the same.
If you like the half popped, you might like it.
It's too hard, right?
It's too hard.
Yeah.
It's not the same.
Okay.
I just like that extra chew, you know?
Yeah.
Because it like, you bite down into it and it's just like the burst of like the butter flavor.
It's like a buckwheat popcorn.
Yeah.
It's got a little more bite to it.
It's got umami.
Oh mommy, when I'm with you mommy.
Nope.
I knew it.
I say oh mommy.
I knew it was going there.
Oh mommy.
Fuck, fuck.
Yep, you got the right idea.
She's popping my kernel, halfway.
I'll be popping the kernel.
She slurred special Sanders.
You'll be popping her kernel?
I'll be popping the kernel Sanders.
I eat a double down every day.
You'll be popping your own mom's kernel?
What the hell are you talking about?
I'm not talking about my mom, I'm talking about KFC.
You treat your mom like a chicken breast?
No.
What's wrong with you?
Yeah, I got your mom's thigh pieces though.
Finger licking.
Yeah.
She gave me the original recipe.
Do they still sell the double down?
Fucked her a million.
I don't know.
I haven't been to KFC in a while.
I think KFC has pretty, I think KFC might be underrated though.
Yeah.
Chicken style.
I think I've still only been to KFC two times.
Maybe one.
Oh yeah.
We all know about the first time.
Two.
- We should do, we'll do shrimp, we'll do KFC.
- Not on the same day, are you kidding?
You're a madman.
- Same day.
- Jesus Christ, this shot, this booster's making him go crazy.
- You might actually get iodine poisoning
if you eat 80 shrimp.
- No.
- Yep.
- I'd be fine.
- Nope.
You would die.
- I'm saying we're gonna take a video.
- I've literally eaten you.
- Imagine if he goes to the hospital
at the end of the video.
- We should do is we should hire an EMS
to check his vitals on site.
- Yeah, just like, yeah, to have him hooked up
to a bunch of machines as he--
just see his blood pressure go up as he eats shrimp?
Yeah.
That'd be awesome, dude.
That'd be so tight.
How do you fix iodine poisoning?
That'd be one of the coolest videos of all time.
What's the opposite of iodine?
Myodine.
So you have to sip myo and dine on it.
Yeah.
Yeah, if there, I mean, I didn't think about that until you said it.
Now you're scared and you're never going to eat a piece of shrimp again.
No, I'm going to do it.
I'm going to do it.
I just like, you know, if there's like a pill that I could take, like Imodium or whatever,
Some kind of pill that reverse iodine poisoning.
You need to get yourself a sody.
Yum.
True.
Man, hopefully a doctor listens to this and tells me exactly what.
If you can eat 80 shrimp.
Exactly what.
Yeah, somebody is listening, tell us something.
Somebody stop him.
No.
Nobody stop him.
Please somebody stop him.
Do the opposite of stop him.
I could eat.
Have you guys ever done a food challenge before?
Which one?
Every food is a challenge.
(laughter)
- Hot chip challenge.
- That doesn't fucking count.
At a restaurant.
- Oh, at a restaurant.
No.
- Oh, I did the blazing challenge at Buffalo Wild Wings.
- I did the burger challenge in Persona 5.
It was really hard, I threw up.
- I'm still on one of the walls
of Buffalo Wild Wings in North Carolina.
- We should've, why didn't you take us there?
- I should've, yeah.
I had the, at one point I was the youngest person
to ever do the Blazin' Challenge.
- Damn.
- Yeah.
- I was like--
- You use that on your, like, if you get booked on like a
show.
- I was like nine years old.
- You get booked on a show and your credit is Buffalo
Wild Wings.
- I remember that was like--
- So I go, writer for Patriot Act.
- That was probably--
(laughing)
That was probably like the first time I like had like a
like thought about killing myself.
- Yeah.
- Was I was like nine years old and I did the Blazin'
Challenge and then the next two days I was just like on
the toilet just like oh yeah spewing shit now if there if I could kill myself
painlessly right now I would yeah yeah I have to go pee so bad
okay we can pause okay we're back what we're back after a long time I ate a
sneeze he said he sneezed out poop into my bed yeah no it did what the fuck do
you what it smelled like it's ah dude I had to go I wish I had my mask it's no
really bad that's right next to the bedroom my girl is in there good that's
That's horrible.
It stinks up your whole house.
I think you guys violated the Geneva Conventions.
You always be coming to my house dropping bombs in my bathroom before you leave, bro.
You always be recording, you go, "Oh, my stomach hurts.
I gotta take a shit before I leave."
Then I walk in there and it smells like a dog.
It smells like an animal's fur.
So I'm going blow for blow with you now from now on.
I'm just glad you guys don't like coming to my house.
You have the most disgusting, fucked up bathroom I've ever seen.
Your bathroom looks like it's in like, like the toilet looks like a scary toilet from a
Resident Evil game.
Yeah.
It looks like you, oh reach into the toilet and grab a key.
It looks like a, this toilet from Saw.
Saw toilet, yeah.
It's bad dude.
Because my hair is on it.
No, it's because it's got yellow shit and piss streaks that are like fossilized around
the bowl.
I gotta get one of those blue things in there.
What?
Just scrub it.
Just wash it.
no. What do you mean? It flushes water that means it's cleaning it so I don't have to
do that. That's true. And you don't have to clean the shower either. Think about how
much of that stuff is is whenever you drop a huge log and it's bombs away
think about how much of that water is splashing up and getting on your legs
and your butt. Oh damn yeah good point. I've never thought about that. You probably have the most
fucked up stinky butt. Let me smell it. You're not doing that to me. Why? Just a
with
you want to take your pants off my shirt to do this to me because he told
everybody on the last premium that his wife did that to him
no she's checked my but to see if i had a c_e_o_ here and i want to check your
but like a baby and i try to do it to me i don't want to see if you're what i
want to see if you smell through your pants
well these are all but now that there's a there's a lot of variables here these
old pants. He's already hedging his bets. Old pants shouldn't smell like poop though.
You gotta skate it in these. Did you skate it through poop? Skate it through a dookie
field? New York baby. It's New York, you gotta skate through it. This is, you are proving
the fact that you won't let me smell your butt. You're fine, come here. Can I take a
picture of you smelling his butt Caleb? Yeah. I'm not happy to report this, cause it's funnier
if it smells like poop. Smells like fresh out of the laundry.
Wow.
Yeah. Smells really good. That's why I took a couple, I took a little extra.
Yeah.
I took it, I went back for seconds.
Yeah, that was decent.
Yeah, that was very decent of you to let me do that.
If there's one thing about me, I'm not, I'm probably not clean in any other sense.
But that butt is smelly.
You got to keep your ass clean. You got to wash your ass.
You got to wash your ass.
I've heard that.
shower technique my shower technique I'd be like I pretty much fist myself every
time I'm in the shower yeah you gotta get up in there you got clean it it's worth
worse I've been getting in I've been getting in I've been taking baths more
often recently and so like well Jana will walk in and I'm like it looks like
I'm doing fucking live jasmine in my fucking bathtub just like shoving a
fucking like doing this and just shoving it in my ass yeah I have but I do use a
a washcloth. I got a loofah thing. You have a butt washcloth? Not a loofah but a squishy
thing. You put it into your butt? You know what I'm talking about? Of course. You get
one for your face and one for your ass and your body. I don't even care about that. I
use the same thing for everything. That's some white people shit. Yes sir. I have the
squishy. Yeah, a loofah. That is a loofah? No, because a loofah is like different. A
- The aloofa's the one that has the--
- No. - Has ribbons.
- Yeah.
- No, the aloofa's different from the squishy.
- Are you talking about a sponge right now?
- I just described what a aloofa is.
- It's not a sponge.
- But it is squishy and porous?
- It's like the--
- Aloofa looks like a sea creature.
- Well, yeah, aloofa's like a plant, right?
- I don't think so.
- What?
- Well, here's a fact that'll blow your mind.
- I think aloofa-- - What?
You say aloofa's a plant? - Hold on, yeah.
I thought like aloofa's like, hold on.
What the fuck are you talking about, man?
Yeah.
Yeah, luffa is a tropical, yeah, and it's used--
- Let me see it.
That's not even how you spell luffa.
- Look, it says it right there, a shower luffa.
There might be a-- - The luffa often spelled
luffa with two O's. - There might be a plant
called luffa, but this is-- - This is not a luffa.
- Yes, it is. - The shower luffa
that you get at Target, search shower luffa.
do this is the yeah
this is the well yeah bathroom loofah sponge
right there that's not what i'm talking about all yeah that exactly that's what
i'm saying you talking about this one
this is what i think of when i think of a little while when i think of lupo i
think of the plant
the i'm looking at all right now that no i don't have this
i have that you search our lupo this is all it comes up
This is all the top images. They're all this.
Now I believe you've never washed your ass.
And you've never taken a shower.
That's why I smell so good. It's my body's natural oils.
It's covering itself up. You're cocooning.
But yeah, that's a...
There's the plant one and there's the synthetic one.
So you use that?
Yeah. Okay, so you do use aloofa.
Yeah, but I didn't think that was called aloofa. I just bought it because I was like,
oh that thing's from the shower. I don't like I think loofahs are probably even
more dirty than a you know because a rag. Yeah it's a plant. I wash my rags like every time I
take a shower every other time. Yeah. But the like a loofah just no one's ever
washed a loofah. Yeah I use a toothbrush to wash my whole body. And my teeth. Yeah I have a
toothbrush that I use to wash my ass with and it's electric. Yeah. Are you guys on the
tip of you you like always close the toilet lid when you flush the toilet? No.
Yeah, I am.
Which it makes me, I'm not like a germaphobe at all, but yeah, my toilet lid broke off and
it makes me very...
That's my bed.
Yeah, it actually...
I go in there and I kick that thing.
It'd be funny if it was your bed.
I really wish it was.
Well, for weeks that thing was like...
It's been fucked up for a long time.
It's been fucked up since you moved in.
Yeah, but the lid completely broke off though recently and it makes me like, yeah, getting
in the shower and knowing that the toilet seat is open like it's like some it's
gonna the steam is gonna fly in there and then fly back into my face it's a good
point your toothbrush you're worried about the steam flying out of the shower
yeah it's like that's what I'm not really it's like it's like a supernatural
like like kind of like you know you're opening it's like a miasma fear spirit
see I would never think to fuck I also am worried sometimes that stuff will fall
off the sink and into the toilet. Oh yeah. I've had toothbrushes do that man. Have
you ever dropped your phone in the toilet before? I had a phone. Have I? The first
phone I ever had I took an insanely like crazy diarrhea and then I dropped my
phone in. Oh my god. And then I like tried to wash it out but there was and I
didn't I didn't have like money for another phone so I just had to like put
it in rice and then like oh fucking like you keep using the phone and I remember
there was like a black spot under the screen and I swear it was do do oh yeah
the screen was cracked also yeah yeah the dookie got into the phone oh my god
you put this is a dookie cyborg I was using that's so cool I kept it for a
long time yeah that'd be cool if your phone like grew a spore because of a
dookie that was in it yeah it's a sport but it's a child of mine a silo side
mushroom yeah exactly silo side bin mushrooms come from poop right yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, my mom was telling me that they used to find them in the
Like all the farms kids in North Carolina. Damn. Yeah, that's cool. It looks at no terror farm
I said, would you you've done mushrooms? I haven't done much. Yeah, I've done a
I wanted like I was gonna do a time this year. Yeah, cuz it's just food poisoning, right?
Well, you put on a poison yourself in the way that every like psychedelic drug is true and alcohol to every
Every drug in the world is actually poison.
If alcohol was poison, how would it clean things?
Pretty crazy to think about.
It didn't clean your stinky ass.
Oh wait, yeah it did.
That's why!
Oh my god, you have so much fucking alcohol running through your butt that it just keeps
it perfectly sanitized.
That's why my ass smells like gain.
He poops white.
And that's why your dick is blue at the tip.
His poop is transparent.
It's the same consistency, but it's completely see-through.
You know what they find like the like it's like oh, this is like a pink lobster that we found
That's what happens in my body every day. I'm shooting one pink lobster out of my ass
every day
Yeah, mushrooms is me. They do make your stomach hurt really bad
Yeah, I don't want to do that if it's gonna make my tummy hurt, but they literally like expand your consciousness. Okay. Well, hold on
Maybe I could use some consciousness expanding. What are you talking about? I think that you you need some consciousness expanding
Yeah, yeah, I have hip-hop for that. I have Jedi mind tricks to do that for me
Yeah, well that that doesn't really explain your consciousness so much as change your perspective and but it
Shifts your paradigm. It's in your face. Yeah. Yeah, I guess if I listen to Jedi mind tricks on mushrooms
I'd probably that probably would kill you. Yeah, probably kill most people I
Think I I think like mushrooms can
More so than acid just like completely rewire your shit. Yeah
Yeah, like I know people who did mushrooms and like we were like well like like annoying hippie kids for like a
Year, and they did too many mushrooms, and they became like young Republicans. Yeah, yeah, yeah
I don't know like he's in the military now. He used to be like such a like like yeah
I think we're old enough now
You can't do a lot of psychedelics because it would be it would be too it would be too weird if you became a different person
Like people who do a ton of psychedelics when they're 17 and then they turn into a monster
or whatever, that's fine because they weren't a person yet.
Exactly.
When you're mid-20s, 25, that's like a brain fluid for us.
You can do it like once every year or so, maybe.
Maybe.
It needs to be at some kind of fucking retreat.
Yeah.
Where you'd really disrespect.
Oh, that would be the worst.
What?
Becoming like a different person at like 25.
Dude, it's great.
told me this like this story about this guy who he knew some guy like some guys
like uncle or something like like accidentally dropped like an entire
because it was like it was like acid in like Sprite or something and basically
the the fucking good time thing just like happened to him where he like yeah
he just like drank the whole thing without realizing like the dosage and
like just like literally was a completely different person yeah like
Yeah, pretty crazy and saying I become like a genius
Somehow like I drink too much. I think I think I'm probably measurably stupider
Post like doing a bunch of drugs in like high school. Yeah. Yeah, I think I was probably probably would have ended up being a smarter person
Yeah, yeah, I don't think I would have no no I
Think I would
Definitely I think I think I definitely also dumbed myself down by smoking way too much weed
I think like like and even after quitting weed
I'll still sometimes like sit around and just like have thoughts like be like damn like it's crazy that like there's a soda called dr.
pepper
Yeah, like that's it yeah, I was just destined to be like this yeah
Perhaps yeah, I think it's fate. Yeah, it's working out for you. Yeah, I'm doing your but nice fine
It's made my butt smell so good apparently.
I'm not going to over, it doesn't smell so good.
I don't want to take a bite.
I do.
I think it smells good for a butt.
Okay.
I'll give you that.
Your butt smells good for a butt.
Next week I'm checking cam.
Don't prepare.
Bye.