Hey everyone. Hey. Did you guys see those two crazy black guys getting a fight at the
Oscars the other night? That was crazy. That was gangsta AF. Yeah. Alright guys,
well welcome. Operation Frogtastic Voyage. Let's give it up. Yeah. Yeah. Big night.
Big night. You guys are about to watch a comedy show, okay?
But it's not your typical comedy show.
It's kind of weird.
You guys are gonna have to use your imagination.
I'll give you an example.
Using the power of imagination, this is no longer Union Hall.
This is an operating theater and you guys are no longer just losers in the audience.
Your medical students and I am no longer a guy with a penis problem. I'm a nurse
Pretty pretty crazy pretty cool. Yeah. Yeah pretty sexy
Yeah, so we're gonna get started in a bit but I just want to explain some rules
We're about to watch a procedure. Okay, and that procedure is going to be completely dependent on your
actions okay we're gonna be using a little thing called crowd work okay
I'll show you an example you sir where are you from oh my god I'm gonna come
there you go yeah so I'm gonna be holding a can one of you guys pass me
the thing. I'm gonna be I'm gonna be holding this fucking thing and it's
gonna be completely dependent on what you guys say so I'll demonstrate.
Okay, clap if you believe in Santa Claus.
(audience applauding)
I think we're getting presents this December.
(audience laughing)
Cool, does that make sense?
Did everybody get that?
- Yeah. - Yeah, it's a vibe.
Alright, and I guess just a couple other general housekeeping rules.
No talking during the show.
If any of you talk, this guy right here will be ejected from the theater.
Just this guy, no one else.
And this guy tomorrow is going to prison for the rest of his life.
For a totally non-violent crime. Wink.
okay? So this should be, he should have the most fun ever tonight, right? So don't
talk and get him ejected. Yeah, no, no, no ugly people, no secrets, no getting too
scared. We should have like, we, if you're Italian you were, you should have
been stopped at the door. So if you're Italian just let us know so we can take
care of you. But I think that's about it. So yeah, strap in. Get ready because this
is Frocktastic Voyage.
Amphibians. Small, wet, smelly, annoying, racist, rude to service workers. Or at least that's
what some say. I happened to find the creatures utterly delightful, full of vim and vigor,
strangely resilient. For example, the North American treehorn frog can withstand temperatures
of up to 127 degrees Celsius for nearly seven seconds, according to studies conducted by
by Jimmy O'Toole, researcher at Miller Elementary.
But today isn't about the ordinary frogs we encounter, the ones we eat, dissect, kiss,
and use.
Today is about a very special frog.
Today is about Sullivan the Frog.
Sullivan to many is just a weird little frog man, but he's gone on many adventures, the
face of a successful comedy institution that actually pays its employees, star of a bizarre
radio play and video game release date to be determined, but he is also a loathsome,
weak, simple-minded buffoon.
Always too kind for the world he's in.
And today, for a buffoon like Sullivan, nothing will go right.
Not without your help.
(laughter)
(applause)
- It's so hard, I've never been a director before,
it's hard to get into these seats.
- You're fucked.
- I'm gonna fall backwards,
the bat came off of my chair immediately.
- Nurse!
- I'm gonna break my neck.
We're gonna have to have a second operation tonight.
nurse that is my let me please let me I'm sorry it's okay the arm is falling off
- oh wait guys I have a whole thing I got to read you gotta let me please just this
one then pull it up patches pulling up pulling it up mm-hmm
hey everyone hi exterior all of Brooklyn ah Brooklyn home of New York City the
The most beautiful city in all of Brooklyn City.
Everyone's hair looks normal.
Nobody eats more than 700 calories a day.
Coffee, latte, avocado, latte.
I'm gonna skip through this.
Freaking hips, okay.
Nevermind there's all those poor people around.
Does anybody here in this audience in particular
know where the poor people are going?
Don't worry about it, yeah, okay.
So well, one such resident of this super awesome city
of Brooklyn, New York City is Sullivan the Frog.
He loves Brooklyn.
He loves to ride his bike in Brooklyn.
And he always wears a helmet.
He loves hanging out in Prospect Park, right?
And just watching all the people go by, he thinks,
wow, this is his voice, so you'll get used to this.
Wow, what an amazing array of people who live in Brooklyn.
Hi, Mr. Barbarino, hi, Mrs. Rabinowitz.
They never say hi back,
But I think they like that I say hi.
I think I...
Sullivan loves his 100 by 100 foot studio apartment.
He loves his landlord, Dmitry,
who makes him pay on the eighth of every month
for some reason.
And always in cash, which he hands to him directly.
Sullivan loves his little paper lanterns.
He loves his rock salt lamp.
He loves to eat authentic Brooklyn cuisine
like cold Popeyes.
He loves to watch Brooklyn TV shows like Broad City.
Glad I got this box set.
Ha ha ha, ha ha ha.
These girls are crazy.
(audience laughing)
- One day, I've never had hair this long.
One day, however, Sullivan woke up, 6 a.m. as usual,
so he can scroll through his phone
and sort of play around with the free weights he has,
when tragedy struck.
- Oh no, oh my God, I'm getting really sick.
- And he collapsed on the floor.
Is this turned around?
No, ooh, cool.
Lucky for him, Dimitri came into his apartment to steal his television
and then when he thought, "I can't have a dead tenant,"
so he stole his TV and called 911.
My name is Dr. Wizard.
I'm an accident in Party City.
I'm also a professional doctor.
And today we're going to be operating on Sullivan the Frog.
Oh nurse!
Yes, it's me, Nurse Conrad Murray.
Well this frog is fucked.
If we look at his day more closely, we can see that in the park he swallowed some kind
of fly, and then it seems he must have contracted a depressive disorder from a DVD box set.
You should all know if you spend more than $10 on any DVD of any kind, you're going to
contract depression.
As far as the STD, this frog hasn't had any sexual activity in at least 400 years, although
it says on his ID he's only 33.
But based on the distance between his eyes, he likely pulls his pants all the way down
when he's at the urinal.
It presses his penis against the cold, wet porcelain.
We're gonna have to take him into the operating room immediately.
Yes, doctor. Right away, doctor.
Thank you, Nurse Conrad Murray.
Absolutely. Time to go listen to Michael Jackson.
Okay.
I'm not responsible for that bit.
And so they wheel good old Sullivan into the operating room.
And they get all the lights up.
They're trying to figure out what to do.
And they address you.
You are the med students who are here to help Sullivan.
We're gonna rely on your input at certain moments throughout the show.
Um, and so, get ready for that. That's what the applause-o-meter is for.
You'll start to get the feel of it as we go, don't worry.
And who is in, Sullivan? Who are these three fuckers? Huh?
My name is Toteria, and an hour ago I was laid back in a piss pool,
sipping on leftover stinky sperms from the urinal of a TGI frog daze.
Then, all of a sudden, I got sucked up by what looked like either a giant green clit or an
outie belly button, I'm not really sure.
Usually, I love being an STD.
I get to see the world and turn people's crotches into a bunch of crunch.
And boy, do they smell.
The weenies I work on make frog farts smell like toad tits.
Simple and plain, I love what I do.
So I never work a day in my life.
But this Sullivan guy is different.
The point of being a disease is to be spread, but I've seen his shitty wide body from the inside,
and there's no way he's ever gonna shoot me into a wife who loves him.
*laughter*
So basically, I'm gonna kill him.
Or at least try to.
Because he has a better chance of being fucked as a cold dead body sitting deep in the dirt.
Maybe an earthworm will wander near his rancid private parts,
mistaking them for an old box of Chinese food or a fossilized poop.
*laughter*
Or maybe a long buried rock will develop sentience and sexual desire along with arms and legs
and put Sullivan's lifeless penis into his mouth.
That is infinitely more possible than Sullivan the Frog ever touching the gangrenous genital--
his gangrenous genitals to another living thing.
Sorry, Sullivan, but yeah.
It's not inaccurate.
And who else is here in Sullivan?
Yup, I'm a fly.
I love poop, I love rotting meat, and I love movies about flies.
I come from a very impressive lineage of flies.
My family is known for achieving great things, and for being flies.
My great-great-great-great-great-great-great-great-great-great-great-great-great-great-great-great-grandfather Fly
abandoned his wife and children and moved to Mike Pence's head, where he became a famous TV star.
He was killed shortly after, but the whole country knew his name.
Fly.
My grandfather was also a deadbeat. He faked his death and widowed his busted
fly wife and moved to Italy where he built one of the seven wonders of the
fly world, the Leaning Tower of Poop. Flies from all over swarm to admire its glory
and eat little pieces of it. When I was two days old my dad told me and my
10,000 siblings that he was stepping out to get a molecule of potato salad but he
never came back. I should have guessed he was planning something by the way he was
rubbing his hands together. He ended up publishing a best-selling autobiography
about his annoying family. The men of my family taught me an important lesson. If
you want to achieve something great, you have to leave your family behind. And
that's just what I'm going to do. Leave home and become a famous superstar. I'm
either going to be a singer or a dancer, but I haven't decided yet. There's only
one problem. I don't have a family to leave in abject misery. The more children
that you abandon, the more famous you will be.
So, I set out to lay as many eggs as possible.
Inside this frog seems like as good a place to start as any.
I'm going to lay tens of thousands of slimy eggs
inside this stupid ass frog's organs,
or my name isn't Fly.
- That's right.
And there's one other disease in here.
- Yeah.
I'm seasonal affective disorder.
(laughter)
Yep.
Oh boy.
(laughter)
Yep, oh please boo me.
I love it.
The only thing that makes me happy is making people sad.
Yeah, people use me as an excuse to buy weighted blankets
and pad thai on Uber Eats and that just pisses me off.
My life is basically shit because I'm pissed the fuck off all the time.
And I make myself sick with a bunch of food and it just makes my shit worse.
Oh boy.
I'm such a piece of fucking crap.
Yep, I'm basically a shit sandwich made of shit.
And poop.
And the bread is seasoned with farts.
And instead of mayonnaise, it's jizz.
Yep, it's a sandwich made out of poop and jizz.
And that's my life.
Oh yeah, and the cum shot is from a fat bulldog.
The cum shot is from a fat bulldog named Craig.
Yeah, the bulldog is named Craig.
And he has a jizz problem too.
He has too much jizz that smells too.
And yeah, that's the mayonnaise on my shit sandwich of a life.
Oh yeah and guess what?
I have a cousin who just got diagnosed with cancer.
Yep, my cousin is- has cancer in his brain.
Sorry if that pisses you off, I guess.
Yeah, guess what his name is.
It's Caleb.
Caleb Affective Disorder.
I want Sullivan to stay home forever and eat chips until he eats his self to death.
Anyway, that's my shitty fucking life.
(audience laughing)
So, your job as the audience is to save Sullivan
while these three try to kill him.
We're gonna be traveling throughout his entire body,
starting with his mouth,
and then we're gonna go to his stomach,
we're gonna go a few other places, we'll get there.
There are gonna be certain moments
where I'm gonna yell for the nurse,
I'm gonna do something like, "Oh, nurse!"
- Yep. - Okay.
And he's gonna come out,
I'm gonna offer a couple of options.
you're gonna yell for which option you like.
He tested that audience thing earlier,
so I know that you guys got it.
And when that happens, there's gonna be some effects
to the enemies that these guys are fighting,
'cause it is Dungeons and Dragons.
They're gonna get buffed, maybe they'll get debuffed.
Don't worry about knowing what that is.
It means the enemies will get better,
the players will get worse.
With the goal of you guys killing them,
and each time they die,
before they finish killing the boss inside of each organ
is another point for you.
If you guys get three points of the five,
there's five organs total ever.
If you guys get three points, you guys win.
I have nothing for you.
It just feels good probably though.
And Sullivan lives and I've got a few different endings
for him, which is fun for me.
If you don't win and these guys win, Sullivan dies.
Sullivan's a sweetheart.
He doesn't deserve death.
deserves life wrong okay well you know there's juries out I guess I'm a jury's
out shut up can we just start got it okay you guys got it thank you let's get this
show on the road hmm so all right we're in the mouth okay you guys got that so
it's Sullivan's mouth it's in big you're in Sullivan's mouth you're all in
Sullivan's mouth I thought I was contracted through the penis you went up
to his mouth. That's how I have this written. Or maybe he used his mouth on the journal.
That's how he flushes it. He's got a frog tongue, he can just stick his tongue under
the handle. He was like, "Where are you?" and used his tongue and flushed it down and
then he got totoria on the mouth. Thank you. You're nestled in the crease of his tongue
actually right now. On either side of you are pink, sorry, sorry about that, slimy walls,
dotted with taste buds,
with these like microvilli that gently tickle the air,
right in front of you, thank you.
A bit ways away, you see saliva pooling up
in the crevices between his gums and the tip of his tongue.
Behind you is a long, slick, hollow shoot
that is Sullivan's esophagus,
the end of which is his stomach,
where he could start doing some real damage.
So, you guys are in the mouth, what do you guys wanna do?
- Yeah, I'm already like just farting out
clutches of eggs down his throat.
- Okay.
I'm using a giant straw to suck all his saliva up because I think it's jizz.
Okay the doctor's just like watching this happen like trying to trace what's going
on. They hear it. They hear the sucking noise. He's taking the what's that called
the stethoscope? Yeah. I studied a lot for this. He's putting it directly on
Sullivan's mouth. It sounds like like ground beef like rolling down a hill.
This sounds like ground beef rolling down a hill. He's taking notes on this and all
the other surgeons are all the other surgeons in the room are watching on.
Of course. Yeah you guys are doing that you guys see on the corner by Sullivan
some of Sullivan's teeth you see a piece of a popcorn kernel and it's like it
It starts to yell at you guys.
What's going on?
I've been here 50 years.
I'm never going away.
Who are you newcomers?
- Whoa, chill.
- Okay, sorry.
- Chill, dude, chill.
- Oh, does it sound like that?
It wasn't the, no.
- Have you ever seen the movie Hard Candy?
- No.
I mean, no.
Have you seen the movie Hard Candy?
I heard it's a bummer.
[laughter]
Okay, cool.
I get your deal now.
Um, yeah.
You guys want to go to Sullivan's stomach, you gotta go down the esophagus.
Oh, really?
Not everybody knows that!
Like you would fucking know, you're in his tooth!
Well, I like it here.
No you don't, how'd you--
You really like it here?
Well...
Roll persuasion on him.
What'd you get?
- I got a three.
(laughing)
- He's not gonna tell you what he actually feels about it.
He's like, "Yeah, I love it here!
"I actually really like being inside his tooth.
"I love bone marrow around me."
- I'm straight up chewing on him.
(laughing)
I'm gonna eat this fucker.
- Okay, roll your tackle attack on him.
It's 1D10.
- Just roll that?
- Oh, just the--
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's the one.
- That's seven. - The seven.
Okay, yeah, you're just gonna do damage to him.
Oh fuck you're eating me
For you
I should have known that was gonna happen
Corn I would like to also my phone needlessly attack the popcorn. Okay. Yeah, that's fine. It's not that important
I'm gonna I mean was that the information that we go down his throat to get
But if you go too far you'll come out the butt that's the next thing he's gonna say right you should go he's dying
He's dying do I even have to attack him or you don't have to roll an attack. He's roll damage
Okay, we just drawn corner. Yeah, he's almost dead. I'll just tell you he has 10 HP
Yeah, hit it - and then but you have to add your strength, right?
You're the dungeon master
Okay, so five yeah, he's dead in the dirt. Yeah, how did you kill him? How did you kill him?
I just I mean I just Totoria eat things I try to fuck every single
So I fuck I like being this guy fuck him to death. Okay, is that we?
Thing to death yeah, and I'm evil, but he is dead that way exactly that way
Yeah, yeah after
I'm a fly. I'm just I'm clapping really slow
(laughing)
- Well done guys.
Well done, he had stuff to tell us,
but I guess we're just gonna eat him.
- All right, can we see his uvula?
- Solvents?
- Yeah.
- Very easily, yeah.
- Okay, I'm gonna use acid spit.
(laughing)
- We're still in the mouth, he's gonna throw us up.
- No, we'll dodge it.
- That's fine.
(laughing)
- Okay, you can try.
- We're gonna have to hold and dodge it, no.
- You are gonna have to hold and dodge.
I'm making a mental note that I'm gonna do that later.
Okay, if you find your way back to the mouth.
Okay, so what do you guys want to do?
You guys can just go down the esophagus.
I mean, that was, this was meant to be like a hub area kind of thing.
So...
A hub? There's only one place to go, right?
Yeah, but you'd come back. It doesn't matter. He's dead.
Just go down the esophagus.
Alright.
Sullivan's dead?
No.
We win!
Yeah!
Okay, I will run into his mouth.
- All right, let's do it.
- You're in it, okay.
So yeah, you guys go down the esophagus.
You're the only one who can fly, right?
- Yeah, no, I can fly.
(laughing)
- How?
I'll give you 10 seconds to explain to me how you can fly.
- Wings.
(laughing)
I can see it, you can use the rest of my time
You can't fly. I can fly. But wait, Patrick, how can you fly? Wings. It's the
worst day of my life. Okay. Also, I can't fly. My wings are too wet. He can fly, but
not in here. Right. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. So you can fly outside? Outside, yeah.
Okay, you need to really fly inside. Yeah. Yeah. Okay, so you're gonna take some fall damage and they won't is that yeah
Yeah, I'll take you know what I'll take that so okay
You guys slide down as a salvo you guys don't you slide down as a soft. Okay? I think I have the least HP
Yes, you do. He's cheating. Oh, this is
Happens awesome. Oh wow what does it say I need you guys all to applaud whenever he does that?
Every time here, so as loud as you can be six damage. That's half my
Yeah, okay my wings oh my god, I'm gracefully it's the one thing I like I look like Michael Wow
Mike Mike like John Angel
From the movie with John Travolta. I knew it. I knew it. I knew it immediately
Michael 1995
He's like he's like yeah, he's like an angel who smokes cigarettes and my mom hates it
He needs to get better as an angel he does I look like the bee from Bee Movie
Yeah, we know fly so as you yeah you guys land down the esophagus you splash
It's a sort of a caged off area of the stomach
There's a little bit of acid sort of trickling around you
and what looks like to be in front of you a loading dock of some kind you see a
a cell come out, in this case a parietal cell,
and it looks at you all.
- Excuse me?
- A what?
- A parietal cell.
- Bless you.
- What's that?
- It's a kind of a digestive cell.
- A cell.
- I knew what that was.
- It's a cell, right, yeah.
- Yeah, is that okay?
- You got it.
- I have not done, I did.
- Cell.
(laughing)
- Can I copy that later?
- I'll take a picture.
- Looks at you all and it says,
okay we got three,
you guys on food.
Well one of you is kind of food.
Hold on, let me get my manager.
I guess I'm kind of food.
And he kind of walks back and he walks back towards the dock.
Are you talking about me?
You guys are inside of this like sort of like little like caged off area.
And every... I start banging on the cage like a madman.
You guys take four damage of stomach acid.
All of us? Not well, you can you can't fly.
So really just you, right?
What's up?
So you guys don't don't worry about it.
All right, and I'm at 2 HP.
So I like this already.
So yeah, and as you guys look out you can see the vast town of
you're really you're going to take away all my fly jokes.
I have a thousand fly jokes.
You took away your own fly jokes.
You took all my way.
I let you take them away.
I have so many fly jokes written down.
So yeah, and you guys, you're in the stomach there
where it's a port town called Stomachville.
- Did you say pork town?
- A pork town called Stomachville,
where there are the four gland families that rule it.
The mucous family, the parietal family,
the chief family, the endocrine family.
And they're always vying for power,
warring over territories, crying a lot more
than I personally think a man should.
But they all have one thing in common,
which is they all defer to Don Gumbino
of the Gumbino crime family,
who's a stick of gum, piece of gum
that's been in Sullivan's stomach for,
I thought it was pretty good.
- I like that, it's a good one.
(laughing)
- That's 'cause he eats gum, he swallows every piece.
That makes sense.
- Yeah, the doctor can't even chew, just down the hatch.
- He's better than littering.
- He looks like he, it's a mint pill.
- Oh God, he swallows every piece of gum he's ever had.
I can tell with my gum meter.
He's able to tell.
Yeah.
One word.
Thank you, man.
I'm trying my best, which is not good enough.
And they all defer to Don Gambino of the Gambino crime family.
All these different families.
Right now, you guys are stuck in sort of this docking bay while they're waiting to assess
what kind of foodstuffs you are.
I'm going to tell you now, for your sake in particular, they are going to take some time
to do that.
So if you want to try to get out, I would try to help him get out before he dies, at the
very least.
I'm just gonna sit here and wait.
Guys, we gotta kill Sullivan, we're getting out of here.
Grab my penis.
Grab it.
All six hands, right on your penis.
I don't know, I'm more of a...
I don't know what I look like.
I don't fly you out, I just sit...
Nice, yeah.
I'm pulling you into the cage with me.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
All right, I fly you out.
So, well, hold on.
There's, I gotta--
- We are, we're out, yeah.
- No, no. - Yeah, we're out.
- We decided we're out.
- Roll a-- - We're at the heart now.
(laughing)
- The heart is coming.
Roll a strength check, just a straight strength check.
So I think for you-- - You should do it
with a pencil. - I love when he's,
I love when he says that and I pretend I know
what I'm supposed to do.
- You're doing this for so long.
What I did for like two years. - Doing the die.
- This one? - The one you always,
people paid money for this.
- Yep.
(laughing)
- Oh, oh.
- Oh, let's try it again.
- Boo him.
- No.
- It's a 15 down there.
- This is good, this is a good sort of--
- I'll take that.
- 15.
- 15, okay, yeah.
I mean, you can pretty easily carry him out.
You're pretty strong.
And so yeah, you're able to carry him out.
Are you gonna just vibe in the cage?
- I guess I'll go.
- Yeah, you don't have to.
- I didn't wanna go, but I guess I will.
(laughing)
- Can I say that by being carried out,
my wings have dried off from the rush of air
and I can fly again.
- You've taken enough damage, I'll let you do that.
I'm a nice guy.
- You guys don't have wings anymore though.
That's done.
- I was gonna say my wings, they shrunk.
- Your wings are done.
- I took mine off.
- Please.
- Okay, the wings are gone.
Whatever, the wings are gone, man.
It's fine.
- Okay, cool.
Yeah, so you guys are in this town.
You guys kinda got out.
I didn't know that two of you would be able to fly, so.
So you guys got out and you kinda can start
overhear conversations from members of the different members of the family
talking about what they're going to do about Gambino, he's gotten too powerful,
all these different things you know the this the town has like all these
different little shops with their own like kind of like they're kind of their
own storefronts for each of the members of the family so they seem to be looking
to overthrow Gambino so there's kind of a way there because he's clearly the boss
of this area but the manor the manor sits way in the back of the stomach by
by the pyloric sphincter.
- Woo!
- Oh hell no.
- Well done.
- You didn't have to clap.
- It's fine, but I need that more than you know.
- And what does the pyloric sphincter do?
- It's where the stuff goes out.
- Yeah.
- And so, which is where Gambino is.
He's sitting at the very end,
kind of holding himself back
from ever falling into the small intestine.
So getting there though,
there are gonna be people who are gonna be suspicious of you.
You are pretty obviously diseases.
I will say.
Sneaking.
He's a fly.
He could fly over to it.
Yeah, there's probably a bunch of
flies in his stomach.
He's like just the only alive one.
You're the only one that's alive.
Yeah, that's true.
I could also disguise myself as a
fly.
I'm just a concept.
Physically, what are what are you?
Yeah, give us a visual description
of yourself.
Peter Griffin.
I look exactly like Peter Griffin.
You do look exactly like him.
- You sound like Droopy Dog.
- White shirt, green pants.
- I think that's good.
- Yeah, looks like Peter Griffin.
- Yeah, that works.
- So yeah, I mean, there's a few ways that you can,
I mean, there's a few ways you can go.
Again, there's storefronts you can visit.
There's, obviously, you can try to sneak towards the manor.
- I go to FYE.
- There is an FYE, I decided now.
Okay.
And that is where, I guess I'll swap them for that.
I think that is funny.
That's where the parietal tomb will be.
- Is that too regional of a, do they have FYE here?
- I don't know what the fuck that means.
- You don't know FYE, dude?
- You don't know FYE's?
- It's only us.
- Bruh, bruh.
- Don't, you know I hate getting bruhed.
- Okay, I go to Spencer's Gifts then, how about that?
- For your entertainment.
- Everyone knows what Spencer's Gifts is.
- Yeah. - Yeah, all right.
- Yeah, you see a member of the family that looks so cool.
- I feel like FYE's not regional.
- It is.
- I think it is regional. - It's regional?
- It's regional, yeah.
- You guys are just dumb, you guys just don't know it.
(laughing)
- You guys thought it was called Fi.
- So yeah, do you guys wanna go to one of the store?
You can go to the Spencer's Gifts.
- I go to Spencer's Gifts.
- Oh my God, I'm gonna have a good time at Spencer's Gifts.
- I run straight to the back.
- Yeah.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, take it easy buddy, where you going?
- I don't even know anymore.
- Okay, are you doing all right?
Is there anything I can do for you?
- I'm laying so many eggs in here.
I'm filling it to the ceiling.
Okay, can you control your friend at least if you're gonna be sad?
I walk past everybody into the back and like wave at you like, "Hey Geoff, how you doing? How are the kids?"
"Oh, they're doing alright."
"Wait a minute, I don't know who that is."
They slowly realize.
When you go to the back you do see like,
suits that belong to the members of the Parietal Gland crime family.
So you could, those would be your disguises.
I'm about to look sexy as hell.
So the problem is that I think I'm a giant ball of cells.
How would I suit?
Aren't we all?
They're all.
That was some Adam Savage ass shit.
He just said that's real shit.
In this crazy world we call life.
That's real shit.
There's nothing I can say, bro.
That's true.
That's facts.
OK, so we'll ignore.
We'll put on the suits.
Yeah, I put the suit on.
They're all form fitting.
So do you put the suits on or are you just.
I just put on the jacket.
Like a loose tie.
Yeah.
Mmm
Yeah, I'm still I want to save money
Okay, cool, I'm
Actually, this is something where you guys ran to the back and that guy is sort of like
Would watch you guys put on the suits it would try to figure out what's going on there. Well. I'm already in the suit
So I'll just be like yeah, I'm actually one of the crime guys now me too
Yep, so we're three crime guys, and you're just not gonna want to mess with us anymore roll deception, okay?
We play fast and loose here folks do we all roll deception or just him just him just him
19 no oh
Don't clap for him
Maybe do never happens. I always get zeros you do it's live. It's the energy. Oh my god alright
Yeah, that guy's just like oh you guys seem pretty tough now, but I think now that I think about it
Especially this one look at him. Yeah, I mean he doesn't seem as tough, but yeah, I'm gonna kill you I
Actually believe him
Okay, yeah, I guess I guess go through go nice nice to see you guys in you know salute. You know what?
Yeah
That's how you sound
Alright, yeah, you get away with it. Okay, so now they're disguised. They're dressed up as the
as the parietal cells so you guys can start to make your way to Gambino's
Manor. As you're doing so, the doctor is starting to trace the traces of the
infection. Trace the traces. And he says, "Oh nurse Conrad Murray!"
I'm here, I'm here!
[Cheering]
Sorry, this hospital is crazy.
They just let you go into any room and do whatever you want.
whatever you want.
(laughter)
- That's, okay.
Well, there's some gastrointestinal activity.
It's hard to-- - Oh shit!
- Yeah, that's right.
It's hard to tell if it's idiopathic or not.
- Of course, idiopathic.
- Mm-hmm.
I think we can either provide an H2 blocker,
though that might be overlong,
or we can start the antacid in case the blockers are overkill.
- The blockers are overkill.
- That's right.
No, I wrote that down too, don't worry.
- I just saw it in your notes.
- Okay.
So, to the audience, you can use the antacid,
and if you use that, it's sort of a milder,
you know, milder option.
Hi.
(audience laughing)
We didn't work this out that well.
Just put it in front of me.
- Yeah, just go in.
- Just put it in front. - Stand right in front, yeah.
- You don't need to see our ugly bugs.
- If you use that, there's a good chance
that something good will happen,
but there's not a great chance that
something great will happen.
If you use the H2 blocker, I'm gonna roll,
and something really good or good but kind of bad happens.
So, the antacid.
Am I saying that right?
Well, people don't want that.
- Whoa.
- The H2 blocker?
Oh my God.
So it was the antacid, right?
They picked the antacid.
That's what I heard, yeah.
Up to you, nurse.
They picked the antacid.
Okay, the antacid it was.
Okay.
He's impartial.
He's the one with the device.
I don't know what he's doing.
He's the impartial judge.
We tried to tell him that it's when they cheer loud, but he doesn't get it, so it's fine.
Okay, cool.
The antacid it is.
All right.
So enemies will have resistance to non-physical damage going forward.
So that means your assets spit, they're gonna have resistance against some of your moves.
They'll have resistance against...
I don't know about your moves.
I have to double check your sheet, but I think you have one or two moves where that will
be a problem.
No.
But it's not that big a deal.
So yeah.
So now you guys know to cheer for the opposite, I guess.
So now, you wanna approach the manor or what?
Yeah.
I'm approaching.
You're approaching?
Okay.
Yep.
I'm guessing we have shoulder pads on our suits and stuff, right?
So we're like, walking like...
I'm like flying, but I'm hovering like, just a few inches off the ground,
so I look like I'm the fly equivalent of 6'6".
I'm just like straight Charlie Brown, like I don't...
And I'm flying two of my wings, so we're going up to the thing...
Yeah, we're going up, we're walking up to the thing.
Everyone has wings, they're all fucking flying.
You get to the manor, and...
Gumbino walks out and he is as advertised a big ball of gum and he looks over you all he says who
The fuck are you three?
What are you doing in my stomach?
Well Sullivan stomach, but you know, it's my this is in your stomach. I'm your
I'm your son
I'm his son and this is I'm fly
I'm gonna be honest I'm not really gonna let that work on tackle initiative
- Let's do it.
- Okay.
(laughter)
- Let's go.
Rolling initiative means we start the combo.
- I got a 15.
- Yo, natural 20.
- Oh my God.
- Oh!
- That's insane.
What are the odds of that?
- One at 20.
- Oh my God.
(laughter)
- I got a 17.
- All right, let's see how--
- Oh great.
I'm gonna last again.
(laughter)
- Gambino also got a natural 20.
What's your dex?
- Oh, yeah.
- 1000. - One.
- It's one, okay.
- No.
- No, you're reading that wrong.
- That's 12.
- That's 12, okay.
You are faster than him, actually.
He's slow as fuck. - Damn right I am.
- So you're gonna go first.
What'd you get?
- I got a 17.
- Oh, wow, okay.
Everyone got really high rolls.
Okay, you're up.
- Okay, I'd like to use my ability, seduce.
(laughing)
- I didn't think you'd use it in this context.
- Which I don't know what, well, I said I was his son.
I don't know what it is.
(laughing)
Oh, that makes no sense to use,
but I already said I'll use it.
- Okay.
- I'm gonna use it.
So, okay, there's a DC of 13.
You're gonna roll, I'm gonna roll against that.
You're gonna sexually approach this man.
Yeah.
What do you do and say?
- Like I said, I'm your son pretty much, so.
I'm gonna suck your penis in one second.
Let's go.
(laughter)
- I'm wearing a wizard outfit.
Okay.
- What do I roll?
- You don't roll shit.
- That's right, I just get to suck it, let's go.
- Check what his wisdom is.
What did you, oh your DC's 13?
Fuck, it worked.
(laughter)
This sucks.
Okay, all right.
(laughter)
- Okay, forgive me father.
- I didn't know what this did.
- I have sinned.
(laughter)
- You read seduce and you're like,
I have no clue what this could possibly do.
- I thought it was just like a name
for like a punch or something.
I didn't know, okay, I struck his dick, whatever.
Yeah, let's get it.
- Oh yeah, maybe it's like seduce, like Hadouken.
- Well I'm not really, I would like to say,
I'm not really his son, he's gum.
- Yeah.
- He's a ball of gum.
- You're basically gum.
I'm nothing like gum, I think I'm gonorrhea.
So he's turned on, we gotta move from the stomach
at some point, so he's turned on,
and he says, good God, okay,
I hit him in the back of the head.
- He's distracted, he's distracted.
- So he is right now like, oh, all right,
wanna be one of my gumas then, huh?
- Nope, I wanna be your son.
- This is extremely confusing.
I mean, he can't attack you.
He can attack the other people.
It is gonna be his turn.
I'm gonna give him a disadvantage
on trying to attack you guys though
'cause he's so turned on by his child.
- You're welcome.
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
- Wouldn't be this show
if we didn't do something like that.
Okay, that is pretty good.
Yeah, he's going after you, Fly.
- What the fuck?
Does he know I have two HP?
You didn't tell him.
- I didn't tell him. - I have two HP.
- Somebody tell him.
- Who's told?
- Oh, you take, 'cause you like misery.
You like sadness, anyway.
- All right, give it to me, how much damage am I taking?
- You're out.
- Yeah, I'm dead, okay.
- You're dead, your first character is dead.
(cheering)
- What attack is he using on me?
'Cause I'm gonna describe it to you.
- So he has hardened pieces of gum on him,
and he has sort of like a stringy bit,
he attaches to them, and he whomps on you.
- So it hits me, and I just like,
you know like the scene in Scanners when the head explodes?
like my whole bodies like that which is eggs discover your everything
just all right everywhere and you can see the babies inside and they're crying
uh...
i think it is
your fault
that you remember when i was born
no my sexy son no
europe
i pull out my gun
well i forgot i gave you a gun
yeah you have a guy but you only had people with it we decided you pistol
with people
the area can run up to him and try to hit him
i put it in my mouth
really
and that's what you want
uh...
you want me to kill myself
no i
you want me to fucking kill myself right now
i'll fucking do it
i don't know i'll fucking do it right now i swear to god
i don't know i don't
that was a little bit your father will know what your fault
i'll put the new it
this could be returned i want to know
it's up to you why i know he's gonna say first
he's gonna say if i can do it i don't like you guys
boy
the
really
yet though i don't give a fuck
Oh my god!
Ugh, I take it out of my mouth and I point it at him and I just fire.
Okay, you can hit him with the gun.
We didn't give you a ranged attack with the gun for this reason.
You didn't bring any bullets?
There's no bullets in the gun?
No.
Yeah.
You forgot your bullets.
You forgot, you left them at home.
Oh my god.
I don't buy them.
So roll a d20.
I'm secretly too scared.
Roll a d20.
It's supposed to end in 40 minutes.
I got a 17.
Okay, yeah, that hits.
twenty
was and forty but it was seventeen okay yeah that it's a
okay role d ten for damage
which was ten sides
uh... is that a nine years it yes and i have a nine god damn okay cool alright
yet
so we did you just like weapon i think you know that good at him because i i
think that's how you shoot
uh...
well
the other way to shoot
the
Alright, yeah, you got him. Okay, yeah, so we're back to the top of the order.
So you're out. He's not gonna attack you right now, so you can do what you want.
I'm doing him a favor. I'll use my, um...
My itchy stick.
You're gonna use your itchy stick? Yeah.
Yeah, go up to him. Go whack him with it.
What do you mean up to him? His penis is in my mouth.
I didn't say that was happening.
I thought it was. I thought it was this whole time.
Okay, I guess that's happening.
You get advantage, just do it. Just roll the dice.
It's how it's done. - This sucks, just roll it.
- Okay, so I-- - He's so quick.
- What do I roll, this? - Just suck a guy's dick.
- It's the same one every time.
- 20. (laughing)
What is going on tonight?
19, 20, 20, that's all I've rolled.
- All right. - And then one other one
I forgot. - So.
You're gonna roll damage for that,
so you're gonna roll your itchy stick, one D8 twice.
- Yeah. - Just a D8, no.
- Yeah. - Just a D8.
You got it right in the first one, yeah.
That's a six.
Wow.
And that's another six.
God damn.
And you get to roll again for doubles like Monopoly.
No.
(laughing)
All right, he's not looking good.
Okay.
I was like.
You're right, his son is sucking his dick
and there's a stick up his ass.
He's not looking very good.
He has disadvantage on his next attack
because he did the itchy stick,
so he's scratching his body all over.
Okay.
He's gonna try to attack you,
'cause he still can't attack you
'cause the dick's soaking. Fucking do it.
So good, okay.
Your joke's better.
It's just you and me.
We had to kill him.
I don't care.
I'm running out of things to put in him.
So what?
Basically this is what happens in my life.
All the time.
God damn it.
Oh, what does it say?
What does it say?
(audience cheering)
Well he got it.
He got it, but it fell also.
My hat, that's fine.
No, your dice.
Oh.
Why did you assume something else fell?
All right, he swings at you and he misses.
He must be in a euphoric state.
He's gonna try to swing at you one more time.
What's your AC?
- My AC is 12.
- Oh, that does hit you.
- Oh, I actually like that.
(laughing)
- Okay, he does eight damage to you.
- Oh, shit.
- Yeah, uh-oh.
- I gotta do math on paper.
- You have built the most unplayable
Dungeons and Dragons character ever.
(laughing)
- What's 24 minus eight?
- The card is up though, too.
- 16, Pat, it's 16.
- 16.
(laughing)
- Let's see, okay.
- 16. - You got it, dude.
All right, you're up, dude.
- Me?
- No.
- Oh.
- Did I say dude?
- You did say dude.
- All right, it's usually you.
(laughing)
- You're up. - I guess I...
You only gave me-- - Just kill him.
Just kill him.
- You only gave me a gun.
(laughing)
- You have some other abilities.
- Okay, hold on, let me check them.
- The gun is probably your best ability in this case.
- Do I?
- You can use that-- - You only gave me a gun.
(laughing)
I have nothing else on here but gun.
- I gave you three other abilities.
That makes me sad.
- Okay.
- That makes me really sad,
and that makes me really, really sad.
And that second ability is your damage dealing.
- You see a force ghost of the fly saying,
"Use the gun."
- Okay.
So I throw the,
I have to go find the gun.
'Cause I threw it.
- Okay, this is interesting because it's stuck to him.
- Okay.
- He is gum.
I have another thing he does,
he'll probably kill him before he does it.
but it is stuck to him, so you can try to run up to him,
grab it, I'll make you do a strength check,
and I'll also make you do, you'll do a dex contest first
and then a strength test.
- Okay, then I'll do that.
- Okay, so roll a d20, and we're gonna just add your dex.
- It's a two.
- That's not gonna be good enough.
He's able to sort of dodge out of the way
with the gun inside of him.
- I'm running out of moves here.
- That's your action.
- Yeah, I-- - That's that.
- He only gave me a gun.
- You're up.
(laughing)
Usually hitting him breaks the charm,
but I guess I decided not to do it,
so he's still not attacking you, so you can go again.
You can hit him again.
Not that you couldn't anyway.
Don't be jealous about this.
- I guess I'll use the itchy stick again.
- Yeah, go for it.
- Yeah, okay.
- Can I have another gun?
(laughing)
- Four.
- That does not help.
- This guy's gonna kill us, man.
- Yeah, he's probably gonna kill you.
- Oh my God.
- Pat.
He attacks you again.
that's gonna hit you no it's not you can't say that anymore all right it
does another 10 damage to you you're up again
combat's the best part of D&D I'm up again yeah you're up again I guess uh you
can summon your counselor Martin to help you yeah I'm gonna do that right now
okay yeah so you summon Martin your counselor he'll talk you through your
feelings offer guidance insight he's Martin's invisible to everyone but you
Um, if an enemy tries to enter within 15 feet of you during your conversation with Martin,
they'll start crying and take 1d8 damage.
Okay.
So he is within 15 feet of you, so Martin's gonna show up, he says,
"Hey, Sad, how's it going?"
"Bleugh."
"That's how I cry. Bleugh."
"I know, I know, you cry that way."
"Basically I'm a piece of shit and I only brought one gun to this."
Well, Martin, we talked about you starting to write things down a little bit more often.
Mmm, what? You think pen and paper's gonna kill this guy? Mmm?
No, so you can remember things.
And so anyway, this goes on, and then he takes a d8 damage, he starts crying, he's like,
"It's so sad! This guy! He just can't get his fucking shit together!"
Shit, you do 8 damage to him. Okay!
I'd say one more hit, he's dead at this point. Good God. Okay.
Is it his turn or mine?
You're up.
[Gasp]
I would like to...
You... what?
I'd like to bite his penis.
(laughter)
It's not a move I have here, but...
But it does make a little bit of sense.
It makes a lot of sense. I've been doing other attacks
with his dick in my mouth. I guess it's...
I guess it's...
An unarmed strike with advantage.
Thank you. Just say it. So roll two d20s.
Come on. That's a six.
You're telling me that this guy's been
and all these other six and what and you're saying one bite to the penis
will not kill him
I'm not saying I'm saying it well they should kill him instantly
no even thought of even me thinking that I should do it we should kill him no he's
made of gum
what I'm chewing his penis then you're doing his penis
it does 1d for damage roll 1d for I love it's making you do you love that
- Two.
- This doesn't kill him.
- God damn it dude.
- Oh my penis!
(laughing)
- But, but, that does hurt.
- It does hurt him and he is also breaking though
out of his stupor.
That was what broke him out of his charm.
- Ah, okay.
- So now he's mad I'm sucking his dick.
- You're up.
- Okay.
(laughing)
- Yeah, he's mad.
- So, did, okay, the gun is still in him?
- Yes.
- And he's still sucking his thing?
- I think so.
- I'm chewing it now though.
- Can you get the gun for me?
- No.
yeah but you're yeah I do that it's your turn now
okay can I tell him to get the gun for me I mean yeah but that doesn't just you do
something we I literally have to go just go home to do an unarmed strike I I take
off my white gloves and I roll attack roll okay it's d20 yes 11 plus your
strength which I think is a minus yeah I'm gonna say we're running out of time
guys okay so he kills him I think you lost this one oh running out of time you
guys won fuck man the doctor is trying to save the stomach and he realizes the
stomachs kind of a lost cause but he does think that there could be a potential
replacement that could save Sullivan. So we have... NURSE! Sorry I should have said
that before I... Thanks sorry no it's mostly my fault. We have two choices for
a replacement stomach. We have the hungry hamster and then we have the Jewish
woman's stomach. Hungry hamster! A tri-state area Jewish woman's stomach!
(cheering)
- I really don't know what to write.
Let me have a go.
- Okay.
- Oh yeah, you got a couple.
I was gonna put it on.
- Yeah, that's right.
(laughing)
- All right, Sullivan feels a sort of stirring in him.
Thousands of years of history leading to this.
(laughing)
Why do I feel so guilty?
Like I got a shit at the worst times
And that's what's happening and speaking of which no
All right, you guys are gonna travel to the lungs now. Well. We're gonna be reborn in the lungs
You're reborn as a lungs as your new characters. Yes, okay, your new characters. Oh, I'm good. We're all getting reborn yes, okay
You already died fool. Yeah, well. I mean, but you guys didn't so I'm considering you dead. We faded out. Yeah
Yup, I'm a caterpillar
You will not believe how many legs I have or how many eggs I lay or how beautiful my adult butterfly form will be
Yep, I'm a child, but I lay eggs. I'm going to have about a thousand children before I grow up like a Mormon
You know, I love Mormon jokes, dude
What's up? My name is hop a titus see I'm what happens when a frog gets a tiny piece of poop in his mouth
But Sullivan's different. He's a little bit different. I won't get into it, but our hero gorged on a Thanksgiving size helping of doo-doo
Anyway, I'm gonna kill him. Okay
I'm chronic fatigue, and I'm so tired all of a sudden oh
Dear all this bullshit in my life made me so tired
Oh does anyone have an Adderall for me? Does anybody have an Adderall? Does
anybody have Adderall? So I can stay up and be a piece of shit? Oh geez. Okay. I'm
gonna kill Sullivan with sleep. So we're in the lungs. Yes. We are on top of the
The Bronchi Mountains.
That's right.
The Bronchi are, they bring the air to the lungs.
Right.
There's a couple temples on there where the alveolus.
Listen, Patches, this sounds really cool, but I'm going to stop because you actually
gave me an ability.
Oh no, fuck.
It's called Burrow Level 2.
And let me just read this out to you guys.
Once per live show, the fly can burrow so deep into Sullivan that they can free travel to
any organ they wish in his body.
So I think that we're going to skip the boring lung shit and I would like to go to his wiener.
Immediately.
Now.
That's fine.
If you do that though, you sacrifice the win here.
I don't give a fuck.
I want to see his wiener.
His lung succumbs to asbestos.
I had a whole thing where there were two different kinds of monk clans and they had like sort
of a-
Yeah, I definitely want to do the wiener.
Crystals.
Okay.
I love that the crystals for asbestos, there's like a tiger eye crystal.
I don't want to hear it, you may as well double gun for 30 minutes.
Yep, yep, that's true.
Oh nice!
Sorry, the cadence of this is very weird, yeah.
There's a guy, there's a patient with like melanoma in there.
He looks crazy.
(laughter)
Yeah, he'll be fine.
Okay, lungs time.
Alright, they won they won they saved his lungs for running out of time so we have two choices
Used bagpipes
Or gills which our artist Joey I love him very much
He said I don't know how I'm gonna do gills so I think two fish kissing would be kind of dope so
That sounds about like that sounds like Joey yeah, so
Used bagpipes, that's what I thought the kills
Your call
Okay, all right wow you guys did a really good job with this thanks nurse
Okay
So hot oh
God doctor immediately realizes that he only has gills available and no spells despite being a wizard
- It's a family name.
- Yeah, it is.
Mother's side.
And he's picked up and dunked into a fish tank,
Sullivan that is.
And Sullivan is sort of woken up with a start for a second
and then they use the,
the anesthesiologist uses a hammer,
knocks him out, he's knocked out again.
So, now we're in the penis.
I guess we're going to the penis.
So yeah, you probably would have been traveling--
- Billions of eggs.
- Right, through the kidney,
down the ureters into the bladder.
It's very dark where you are.
You're waiting in urine.
There's a prevailing smell and slight,
there's no world here.
It's just a penis.
- Just a real penis?
- It's just a real penis.
- Okay, take a bite.
- Yep.
- It hurts Sullivan.
- I'd like to join him in that.
- What sound does he make when he bites him?
(meows)
- He meows?
- No, he's like (meows)
- He meows.
- No, he doesn't meow.
- It sounds like a passionate kind of noise.
- Wait, he likes it?
- No, he doesn't.
- It sounds very gentle.
- We'll roll to see if he likes it.
- A wiener bite.
- More than 10, he likes it.
Shit, I got a 10.
Less, oh, so then he doesn't like it, huh?
(laughing)
- I had to think about it, but I got what I wanted.
- All right, fine, I keep biting his penis then, whatever.
- Okay, yeah.
Yeah, this one is literally was meant to be like,
you guys just kinda win this one.
- Yo! - Yeah!
- This is gonna work.
- That's right!
- Yeah, I wrote all this text.
- It's just useless now.
(laughing)
- Bitch. - We don't need the nurse
for this one, we can just sort of rip this off, I think.
There's his penis.
(laughing)
- Is it disgusting?
- Oh, show the world. - You guys not see his penis?
Oh yeah.
He's very embarrassed.
- Why'd you give me this?
- Okay, that's fine, yeah.
- Cover that thing up.
- I know I need to. - It's been staring at me.
(laughing)
So yeah, you guys are now going to ride the Millard-Fillmore Tunnel.
So a lot of people don't know this actually.
You guys move out of the way for a second.
Oh, okay.
Just a little second.
Okay.
What?
Can you slide show?
Okay, so a lot of people don't know this about the Millard-Fillmore Tunnel.
So there he is, right, Millard-Fillmore Highway.
So Miller-Fillmore Highway was discovered in 1924.
His last name's Highway?
Yes.
Researchers at Tapioca University.
Research team led by Dr. P. Waters Simpson.
It was the Roaring Twenties, right?
So they were actually trying to make a chemical that could destroy jazz.
Jazz was invented by a precursor to the INR, themselves a precursor to the CIA.
But things got out of hand, black people started doing it, so the CIA got nervous.
Anyway, they discovered the tunnel instead.
Here is actually him when he was younger, and here's him now.
Isn't that amazing?
And so you can see there that rainbow sort of tunnel there, that's the tunnel.
Okay, we get a little bit closer we can see the rainbow connection there.
Here's the oldest corpse, Ootsie, I believe Jack you helped me correct me on that earlier.
And so there's actually, you can see here in Tootin' Common he's got the tunnel there,
there's the mummy from Fortnite.
The David not in the front but on the back, the Vitruvian man on the back.
Some celebrities now have the tunnel, they've been sporting it around.
Some of them get them removed, Timmy.
Okay, Betty White, RIP, Board Ape has one, Kevin Hart doesn't, Seth Rogen, there it is.
Okay, a few of these.
[Laughter]
We have the Neversoft.
This is cool, this is all the Neversoft intros.
You guys ever play the Tony Hawk games?
(laughter)
Oh, we don't have to watch, I'm sorry, okay.
All right, yeah, so I just wanted to,
so you guys ride that tunnel.
Come on, get back, get back.
- Oh, okay, yeah, yeah, sure.
- So you guys ride that tunnel up to Sullivan's brain.
We're gonna just fucking skip the heart.
We don't have time.
So Sullivan's brain is composed of his id, his ego, and his super ego.
You're going to have to go past each one to fight the final boss.
Okay?
It's going to be easy.
Has anything happened to the heart?
It was a game show.
It was kind of fun.
You shouldn't have said that.
I'm sorry everyone.
It wasn't a game show, he's lying.
It sucked.
It was a lame show.
Thank you.
- That was fire, Pat.
- Uh-huh.
- Holy shit.
- No applause for that?
All right, I guess you guys want me to die.
- That's good, you're in character still.
- Yeah, that's a character.
(laughing)
- All right.
- It's a character choice.
So, Sullivan's id is just,
Sullivan as a little kid,
a little propeller hat and a lollipop.
He's just enjoying everything.
He's just so happy.
- Everybody's being really nice.
I love that everybody's nice.
- Eggs on his face.
*laughter*
*inhales*
He's like, "Oh! Oh no!"
"That's not how you're gonna get-" "More, more, more."
"That's not how you're gonna get-" *laughter*
"That's not how you're gonna get past this at all!"
"One billion!"
He's like a little kid. "Sullivan, yeah."
"Can I sit this flight out?" *laughter*
*laughter*
You don't have to interact with him in any way you don't want to.
Okay.
I just never- *laughter*
*laughter*
he just says oh wow three new friends Santa is not real what tooth fairy is
not real wait what what wait Pat leprechaun not real Pat so do that what
are you talking about Easter Bunny Pat I swear to you that's right
As Moses Jones is not real that I knew he just wanted you to say something nice to
him can you guys do that you're perfect to lay eggs on Sullivan's ego he's
looking at a giant terminal filled with all gizmos and widgets and buttons and
all these different things and he's looking over it and he doesn't know what
to do this Sullivan's perpetual state of being like I don't know there's a lot of
stuff going on why did somebody put me in charge of all this and he's running
around back and forth trying to figure out what to do and he looks to you three
and he says can you guys help me please there is there a can I can I roll
perception real quick yeah go for it what are you trying to what are you in
particular you trying to notice well I can't notice shit I got a six okay well
- Well, whatever you're trying to notice, you can press--
- I was looking for like a big red button.
- You don't notice any big red buttons.
- Okay. - No.
What do you guys wanna do?
There's a few options you can start to go down here.
- Or a big switch.
- Okay, I'm gonna look for a big switch.
- Okay.
- Okay, let's see here.
All right, that's a two.
- Okay, yeah.
- So is there a switch?
- No.
- Okay.
- No, the buttons look even more confusing
than they already did.
- I'm gonna go for a lever.
I'm gonna go for a lever.
I'm gonna see-- - Is that where it's
gonna run down the--
Maybe there's a lever somewhere in the room.
I don't think that's the issue.
I got a two, so...
I'm gonna roll for a racing wheel.
I wanna see if there's a steering wheel.
I'm gonna roll for an outlet, maybe, that has a power strip plugged in.
Can you guys keep rolling?
I'm gonna see if there's a solo cup with a string attached to it.
Yeah, can you roll that too?
I'm gonna see if I can get some help. Fourteen!
That's pretty good. I'm gonna roll also, though.
I got a twelve.
So...
I just wanted to roll I started
Okay
Perception check you can kind of tell that part of what Sullivan needs is just some confidence
Okay, some way you guys can like hey
You should try looking for a lever or a wheel or a button or a switch roll persuasion
That's it
Nine
It's a nine. Oh, I don't know those all sound really complicated to find plus four, baby
It's pretty good, but I don't know still maybe the DC is a little higher in the brain. You're perfect to lay eggs on
Yeah, my it told me that earlier let me roll for it you can roll for that
What are you trying to persuade him that he's good? Yeah? Oh, that's at 18 Wow yeah, I get that makes him feel pretty good
That's kind of nice none of this matters anyway. We're all gonna fucking die. I wish I had eggs so I could lay them on you
well
Just is there a way to
Do you as any of you guys know how to work?
Work this terminal at all. I'm pressing random buttons
Yes, oh all of your role role deception
Sullivan sort of looks to you
Juicing hard tonight. Totaria or hop hop hop a Titus a hop a Titus. I bet I is he goes down
He goes see you said you seem to really know what you're doing. What do you think?
What do you think I should do when you're just pulling all the shit, and I think you should help me pull all this
He starts helping you along with it
and you can start to see that the gears are turning and things are just click and clack and start to work and
You see it opens up a door and he says wow. Thank you guys
It's the first time I've ever felt like I could do anything.
I mean, I still needed help and stuff.
I spit in his mouth.
Alright, okay.
That's about it.
Okay.
We already won.
Just shut up.
Okay, yeah, that's fair.
No, I understand.
I do the worm out.
You guys go out and you end up with Sullivan's super ego.
He believes in the good of all people.
He believes that kindness and naivete are good things.
He wants to give the world light and graciousness.
sees float he's floating
he says uh... there's no challenges here
one eight a hundred miles per hour
roll the tack roll
just straight at your decks
uh... fourteen
yeah roll a d6
for damage and add your decks
uh... six yeah
he's just floating around
(laughing)
- From behind, Sullivan's super ego rages his soul.
It's massive, it's Kaiju-sized motherfucker.
I need you all to roll initiative.
This is your last fight. - Nope.
- I got a 19.
- Ooh, I got a 13.
- I got a 10.
- Sullivan's soul--
- Oh wait, no, I got a 14.
- Sullivan's soul sucks.
Okay, so we got a six.
- Okay, who got a 19?
- Me.
- You up?
- All right.
- If you don't use the gun, I'm gonna kick you off stage.
- You have other moves.
- Yeah, I have other moves.
- You should not be reading at all.
You should be saying the word gun out loud.
(laughing)
- Well, okay, okay.
- Close your eyes.
- Can negate the, okay, okay, that makes me really,
really sad. - Patrick, close your eyes.
It's the best for your reaction.
You're really, really sad.
- Close your, literally close your eyes right now.
- Okay, I pull out the gun and I throw it.
- Yeah.
- I wind up, I wind up like fucking--
- It's crazy, this was a melee attack.
- Huh?
- Nothing, just keep going.
- How big is the gun?
- It's regular sized.
- Okay, then I swing it.
- Yeah, like six or seven feet long.
- Yeah, I swing it like a bat.
- You do?
- I guess.
- You swing it at Sullivan's soul,
it's this big black inky thing,
it's like (growls)
and roll an attack roll.
- So nine.
Okay, yeah, that does not hit Sullivan's soul.
It sort of just phases through it in a weird, queer way.
You're up.
Don't do that.
I say queer like that, I don't know why I do.
I don't know what books I read.
He's a wizard.
Yeah, thank you.
(laughing)
Interesting choice.
Good God.
All right, you're up.
I'm gonna use my love tendrils.
Oh, okay.
So this move, this move's pretty intense.
So, out of your body spews your nastiness, for real.
And these tendrils will just attack anything within range
and do a huge amount of damage.
You're susceptible, obviously, if Sullivan Soul dodges it.
So, he's going to have to roll a Dexterity saving throw,
which your DC for that is, I gave you 15 for that,
that was stupid.
Okay, I should've just actually calculated it
and would've been lower.
(mumbling)
(laughing)
- Okay, he is able to dodge it initially.
But your tendrils are flying out of you.
He's gonna have to try to, you know,
not get hit by it next time too.
You are up.
- Okay. - Fly.
- Can I like try to-- - He's a caterpillar now.
- Caterpillar, I'm so sorry dude.
- I'm basically a fly.
I'm a butterfly now.
- I transform while you guys all hang around.
- Whoa! - And I am sexy.
- Yeah!
- That's right dude!
- Describe the pattern on your wings.
red. Okay, I'm going to it. Can I can I try to just like corrupt his soul with
evil thoughts? Oh my God, that was my plan and you guys told me to use the
gun. That's true. Yeah, so I do it for that. Yeah, I mean, let's figure out how
that would work. Okay, I do acid spit. All right, six. Okay, that's not gonna
- Yeah.
- Just phases right through him.
- It's butterfly acid, so it's not very good.
- It's worse than fly acid.
- Yeah.
- I mean, Sullivan's soul tries to like,
do a massive swipe at you all,
and you all were able to dodge it out of the way.
So we're gonna go back to the top of the order.
- We're gonna beat you.
- Back to the top of the order.
- We're gonna get the prize at the end.
- That's right.
- Alright, so it's his soul.
Maybe I try this one more time.
(laughing)
- Santa's not real.
Roll persuasion. Actually sorry roll deception. 18. Oh shit. Yep my mom told me
when I was one. Maybe your mom is wrong. I grew up 18 so I don't believe in
anything fun. Oh no. Oh okay. Maybe. Maybe.
Santa's not real. Please stop. Please stop saying that.
Peter Pan's not real.
Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde, not real. Robin Williams, not real.
Okay. Peter Cetera, not real. You're gonna have advantage on attacks against him. I'm
I'm gonna let that happen. That's pretty fun.
Okay, then I do I still have an attack roll or?
No, that was your action.
Oh shit, okay.
So I can only use my love tendrils.
Unless you want to stop using them.
But you can keep using them.
They're pretty strong.
I'm just kind of wiggling them a little bit.
At first I'm like, I like tried to hit him and I had to play it off like,
"Yeah, but that would have sucked really if I hit you, huh? That would have sucked big, yeah."
Okay, I mean he was not able to dodge it this time. Roll 2d6.
Yes.
You know where they are.
That's the normal one.
Okay.
(laughing)
- He said D6 instead of Monopoly dice.
- Four.
- Okay, all right, yeah, you do four damage to him.
That's not bad.
Okay, you're up.
- Thank you.
Me?
- I hope so.
- Okay, I'm just gonna do the acid again
'cause it's gonna work one of these times for sure.
- Yeah, it's gonna work almost definitely.
That's how D&D combat works.
- Yeah, let's see here.
Oh, oh, okay, that's a six again, I think.
- You just whiffed.
- The second time, yeah.
- All right, he's gonna try it.
- The acid is hitting other parts of Sullivan's brain
and they're just like turning off.
- Yeah.
lights that is going out. The doctor's like trying to figure out what's going on.
There's like sparks like when you pour soda on a computer. You know when you do that?
Is he dancing? What's happening here? Been there. Yeah. He's gonna try to attack you
guys. That does hit all of you guys. Oh. It's not gonna be. Wait, wait, yeah, but we're
at full health, right? Because we respawned. Yeah. Did you not think about that? Yes. When
you wrote this? I did think about that, actually. I thought a lot of things. I thought about
my family
yeah i'll tell me what you think i loved ones yeah
the guys take uh... we you guys take fourteen dam all right i'm dead
yeah
what
solomon's old ron she i'm a i got one h p dot it
mcdonald my wings fly off
and i'm back to a caterpillar and my wings fly off to
the uh... as sucks
i still have mine
the good
okay
you're up uh...
rights i swing the gun again
i'll say this if you can try to convince them one more time okay that everything
is horrible
i can give it to you
you gotta really do it this time it's all on you
you got this dude
because you're not going to win this place
otherwise don't show probably
it'll be unlikely of the second time just think of one thing passes what you
I don't think people say a thing just anything close your eyes. Don't think about Peter Griffin
He's thinking about Peter Griffin, I'm thinking too hard don't think too hard too hard about Peter Griffin no stop
Don't do that one thing oh Jesus Christ everything stressing me out so much
Is your bunnies not actually real
All right roll deception again
That was a five
Fucking choked it wasn't even a good bit
Bullshit I fucking okay you're up
So I got my tingles out yeah, oh yeah I
Got my having to use a man
I'm gonna use him again. Okay. He's gonna try to dodge again
Does he have like ears in him face?
It's like a giant like sort of shade version of Sullivan's what I'm okay thinking, but didn't describe
Okay, yeah black Sullivan. Yeah, well yeah, okay
17 that is a dodge
He does it yeah, he died again. I play it off
I like I like shoot the tendril out it misses and I bring it back like kind of comb my hair back
Pretty cool, I have the tendrils in the first place so yeah, yeah
What do you do what I'm dead
All right, he's gonna he's gonna try to attack you Pat he misses he's really mad at you though for trying
You can keep trying to convince him. No, I'm gonna let I like this. I like this a little parachute I gave you
I think it's good and let me just go we're two two with the audience right now, right?
Cuz we got the wiener. I feel like we get the heart by default, right? So we
Yeah, it's - - so it's - - it's game point yeah, yeah, cuz like we we totally got
This is your last chance if you take out a loan you got paid back
Yeah, all of us in real life
That's an 11 plus. Oh wait. Yeah. Yeah, wait. What do I add to that?
Deception oh oh true
Let's say come on. I'd say that's a 13
Adding a 2 to an 11
No
He evaporates
Fuck you
One what huh okay, all right, so there's not like you don't have a secret thing at the end where they win oh
Okay, okay
We need them to pick the heart in the brain
Okay
For the heart
Let's see we have here a the Grinch
And a time bomb that's a tough one
Wonder what the audience will choose
ranch
People people like the Grinch these days. I don't know the kids these days time bomb
We hate that we don't like that actually and we want to change it to the other one
I'm one of the audience members, and I hate the grill
My name is Brian, and I hate that nurse the brain
Nah you wrong for that jack-in-the-box
Or a magic 8-ball that only says outlook not good and reply hazy those are your options
Jack in the box
You should listen to him
Magic 8-ball
The pro to you. More like a magic one ball. What up? That's what's up. Jack in the box
or magic eight ball? Jack in the box. He's the worst nurse ever. How many patients have
you killed? You're like one of those, you're the one of the nurses who makes the dancing
videos while the guy dies a fucking mono. I think I saw a true crime documentary on Netflix
about you. Alright I've got the ending here based on your choices. So. You can still,
you can go, you can do whatever you want bro. Just put the applause meter down I guess.
Alright so the gills ending. Bring it with you I guess. Just go. Leave the venue. I'll
you guys tomorrow Sullivan immediately dies into the nearest body of water so
he can continue breathing and then what was the stomach it was IBS thank you oh
this one's fun okay yeah he starts shitting up a storm
you have to check the notes for that what does he do with IBS what's the joke
here the angle propelling him far too wide across the sea until he reaches
London where being the best-looking person in England he is immediately a
celebrity Sullivan the handsome sea frog goes on to have an illustrious career as
a personality and then would you pick for the heart Grinch okay but the hatred
instilled in his heart means he wants more not just an acting career he needs
to do singing he needs to be a director he is bad at both of these things he has a
Hasselhoff style downfall with no end in sight finally he gets a call it's Elton
John who always seems to be there when a celebrity is on the brink of killing
themselves in case you haven't noticed okay and what is next what else do we
got here got Jack in the box and we got talk about his penis oh yeah that doesn't
affect any of the endings. Elton John, Sullivan, I love you. I love you. You're
my Tony dancer. You wrote a script, but you need to take a dance break and dance
back to your roots. That's confusing.
Elton John says, no, Sullivan says to that, he starts humming the only thing he
can say now with his new brain.
(mimics the tune of the song)
(laughter)
Oh, did you guys pick the 8-ball? No, you didn't. Good.
Elton John says, "I like that
Sullivan." That's a
hit. And it is a hit.
His 'Pop Go the Weasel' tune spreads
throughout the nation of England and he's back
on top. The hatred in his heart melts
away. This is the best ending!
You got the best ending! (cheering)
And then he dies!
And then he dies eventually!
Later in his life.
That's way later in his life.
DM me if you want all the other endings.
Thank you guys so much.
I mean, I'm good.
Are you guys good?
I have like five minutes
I want to do.
You want to try it out? You've been working on it a bit, right?
These smartphones are actually making us bummer.
Alright, bye guys.
Bye everybody.
(audience cheers)
[APPLAUSE]