Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
(dramatic music)
♪ I still see your armor in my room ♪
That's what it is.
♪ Can't get back the emeralds I gave you ♪
Wait, I'm gonna play that one that I just sent you guys.
Wait, can I play that one into the mic?
Is that okay?
Do we do gifts up top?
No, we're doing theme song.
Shut up!
We're doing our new theme song that we found.
Yeah, just chill for a second.
I mean to tell you to shut up.
This is Lucid Dreams Minecraft parody by Fleep.
77 views.
3 years ago.
This is going to blow your mind.
This is real shit.
Rap along if you know the words.
This kid also overdosed on Percocet.
He did.
It's just because he took one.
He was too small.
He's too young.
Here we go.
Get ready.
He took one, 60-ish.
He took a Perc5.
Your creepers in my room can't take back the diamonds I give you.
It says that I am enchanted, but I break it and I cannot build it.
So I must replace it all.
Easier said than mine, that you were my diamond.
The same two black blocks and emeralds instead of my head.
You've got another diamond, but my blocks are enchanted.
I am the better Minecraft crafter and won't let you loot me.
This is so serious though.
Yeah, damn.
Straight up.
He's putting his whole heart into this.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
You do me a huge favor.
What?
I forgot to do this when I got here.
Can you?
Shit, hold up.
Is he taking out my gift?
No.
What are you doing?
You wish I was taking it out.
What did I forget?
You wish.
What did you forget?
I forgot to...
You want me to plug your headphones in?
Yeah.
I'm gonna plug the diamond, listen to my blocks in my head
You find a doll, and I'm gonna rock you like a rock star
Yeah, yeah, the chords you have a chord like you're not like tied to your chair. Yeah, I know I forgot to do a
Somebody to do like a like a real like ether like a real homophobic
This song in a Minecraft. Yeah
Yeah, I'm sure it's happened. Yeah, there's no way it has it through your soul like ender
You know like that yeah
You're a flamer. Yeah, you're a gamer damn. I've heard that one in a long time
Yeah, you're about to hear it for me for the next couple weeks. You just reminded me
Yeah, yeah, hell yeah. We're playing right back cuz you even get in trouble for saying flamer. I feel like now I feel like
Probably I mean
Going to like a gay bar like standing at the door John flamer
Like as soon as everyone I think they wouldn't get mad like I've got no
No, no gay guy would get mad if you called them a flamer
Let's test it out. Okay. Let's go to the hood. I call people
Calling people Flamer in the hood.
Viral video.
God awesome.
It's just a bunch of guys saying thank you.
Thank you very much.
I am a Flamer.
I appreciate it.
What are you doing?
What?
Siri is talking to you.
God damn.
I leaned out of my way.
No, come on, pull it up.
No, come on, let's talk to Siri.
Let's talk to Siri.
Okay.
Hey Siri, call Caleb.
Calling Red Caleb home.
I'm getting a phone call.
Who could that be?
Why are you whispering?
Hello?
Hey.
Can you put yours on speaker so I can hear you?
It's going to do an infinite loop and everybody's going to get mad.
Damn it.
It's going to sound awful.
I'm not going to do an infinite loop.
I'm not going to do an infinite loop with you.
Why not?
Because it's going to, I hate that sound.
I would love to be stuck with you in an infinite loop.
You would hate that.
If you and me got stuck in a Palm Springs situation, you'd hate that.
We're going to go to Palm Springs?
You haven't seen that movie?
I'd like to go to Palm Springs with you.
Great, now an alarm is going off.
What the hell is happening in this house today?
This is a rough start.
You made me plug in headphones.
You know what?
I can redeem this.
How?
How ever will you redeem it?
Close your eyes.
I've got to turn this fucking alarm off.
the gift alarm.
Ok, well he's over there Cameron, close your eyes.
No, wait until he gets back.
I want to see him get my gift.
I want him to see me get my gift.
Ok, I'll put his on his chair so then he comes back and he sees it.
No, just wait.
Just wait.
We'll have a conversation just the two of us.
Alright.
I saw this when I was shopping for a humidifier recently.
I saw this review that I remembered last night and I couldn't fall asleep because I kept
laughing out loud.
I was trying to fall asleep about it where somebody was like, "I bought this for my son's
bedroom and when we plugged it in it emitted the most foul odor I've ever
smelled in my life. So we threw it away but we couldn't get rid of
the smell and now my son won't sleep in his bedroom anymore. And I was lying there
trying to fall asleep but I just kept going like...
There's a thing about the evil humidifier. It ruined a whole room.
When my youngest brother was like young and he's like a lot younger than me
He had a room and we had a dog, a really young dog.
Brody was really young at the time.
And his room smelled terrible for like a month and a half.
It smelled like complete shit.
And my little brother was maybe like three or four.
And we were like, "What the fuck is this smell?
It smells terrible."
And then one day, he like, came up, he like, called me into his room, and he's like, "Hey
Caleb, look what I just found under my truck."
And it was just like a humongous pile of dog shit that had been sitting there for like
six weeks.
And he was just sleeping in a shit room.
Dude!
And that's why he's like that.
The miasma would fuckin'-
That's absolutely why he's like that now.
Yeah.
No, you guys never went to my parents' old place.
If it was under a toy truck, he should have been moving that truck around and
playing with it.
Yeah, he should have been playing with the truck.
There was already something wrong with him if he wasn't playing with the truck.
Yeah, you're right.
He should have been with the trucks.
No, you guys never went to the place in Manchester.
If it was under a Barbie, he would have found it.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
Got his ass.
Yeah.
I hope he's listening.
I lived in that really old, that fucking, like my sister's house, my sister and my parents,
where they lived in that place in Ware.
And uh...
Ware?
where where where where in New Hampshire where in New Hampshire this yeah no where
in New Hampshire where wait no you lived in nowhere where underwear
god damn let's go we planned that before how did you guys know I was gonna walk
into that I mean under where I'm fuck wait wait what I'm gonna wear in her
wear? I barely... They caught me in her wear. I was wearing ladies clothes.
Ladies clothes? Mm-hmm. I do feel like I... Oh, but there was a mouse that died.
A mouse died in the ceiling and the smell, it was in my room. Yeah.
And the smell in there, we didn't know what it was for weeks until, and that's
how I learned what a dead mouse smells like. What does it smell like? It's like,
like a decaying flesh. I'd like to see Patrick do like an 8th grade spelling bee. I would
kill it dude. Unless the words were room or warrior. And then you do R-U-M and W-O-Y-E-R.
Dude I got room. Room is fine dude. That's normal. Rum? Rum? I don't say rum. You do.
No I don't. You say rum. Yeah we both say rum. Rum. And then you say warrior. Warrior I don't
know. I'm dropping an R in there. That one's weird. I don't know about that one. There's
two R's and you're replacing them with a Y. Warrior. But I'll defend rum. That's an okay
thing to say. I don't know where warrior came from. Rum is a proud New England tradition.
Warrior. Rum? My grandmother, she would say roof. I don't say roof though. Yeah I don't
either. I say roof. I sometimes say roof.
Yeah, because your grandma, you know why? Because she was a dog. Nope. Dog asshole bitch. No.
Yep. No. Dog. Wrong. Yeah. Wrong. Frog. Fum. Did you guys know that rabies has like a 100%
kill rate? Isn't that cool? What? In people? Yeah. Isn't it crazy how like if you get rabies
you're like afraid of water? And you just die, you 100% die. But like, like, it's not
like, like, is it like if you see water you run away or can it be like if somebody tells
you about water you get scared too. I think if you're to the point where you're afraid
of water. Imagine a glass of water and you start you get really scared. I don't think
it makes I don't think you would like I don't think you can understand English if you're
to the point in rabies where you're afraid of water. I think I would I would. I think
you. If I get the shot. If you saw a picture of water would you be afraid of it? Maybe.
Yeah that's possible. I could probably survive rabies. Well apparently there's been six people
who have ever survived rabies.
- What? - There's only seven.
- Yeah. - When I'm there.
- Six people ever. - I'm through with rabies.
- Damn. - Isn't that cool?
- That can't be true. - It's true, look it up.
Six people ever and they were all just like,
they think that they have just some like genetic,
like predisposition to like-- - They're half dog.
- Yeah. - I do.
- They had some kind of doggy DNA in them.
- I-- - You think you have dog DNA?
- I think I have-- - You do have dog DNA.
Oh my God, you have dog DNA.
You have dog. - I sleep on the floor.
- Yeah, you do have dog DNA. - I eat a lot of beef jerky.
You have that extra toe like halfway up your leg.
Yeah.
Damn.
That makes so much sense.
And a tail.
Your tail, yeah.
Yeah.
That doesn't explain your tail.
I mean the tail is...
Yeah.
You like everybody.
Mm-hmm.
You mostly have your tongue out.
Yeah.
I don't have my tongue out a lot.
I think I'm one of the... I'm not like a pug.
You would definitely be one of these fucked up, smushy...
Nah, I'd be like a golden doodle.
You'd be like what?
I'd be like a golden doodle.
No, you'd be a shit, dirt, cheap, fucking dog.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, what the hell?
That's so mean.
I don't know.
I don't think you'd be a golden doodle.
Yes I would.
No, you wouldn't.
Nothing about you strikes me as golden, personally.
Yeah, that's one of the golden doodles.
Golden retriever poodle mix.
You might be like a pink doodle.
A chocolate doodle?
No, just like a pink, rosy cheeks.
I think I'm a chocolate doodle.
I don't think you're a doodle.
I think I might be a doodle.
You do not have, no part of you is doodly.
You're not hypoallergenic.
- No, I am.
- No.
- No, I have a lot of allergies.
- You are full of dander.
- No.
- Yeah.
You're completely, and you have brain worms.
- No, I got heart worms.
- No, heart worms.
- That's my problem.
- Yeah.
- I do take a lot of heart worm medication just to be safe.
- Smart.
- Yeah.
- What is that, Zantac?
No, Zantac's for heartburn.
I take a lot of heartburn medication too.
- You think you have heartburn 'cause it's warm.
My heart burns for worms.
How do you, how does a dog get heart worms?
They just get it in there.
They just get it in food.
Yeah.
Who, does their food go to their heart?
And they eat, dogs eat anything off the ground.
Which, another thing I do.
Yeah.
It does, it's starting to make more and more sense.
Yeah, when I was at a...
I almost picked up a Twix off the ground the other day.
I was really drunk one time and ate a slice of pizza off the floor.
One time I was in the Dallas airport.
At Suffolk University.
And there was a half empty bag of trail mix on the ground I ate it.
Yeah.
in the wrapper on the ground?
- You see I saw Twix on the ground the other day
in the wrapper, it's completely sealed.
- Yeah, if it's completely sealed--
- I was with Joe though.
- I'll pick it up.
- And I wasn't gonna, if it was--
- I'll do that in front of Joe, I don't give a shit.
- If there was nobody with me I would've eaten it.
But I was like, I'm not gonna eat,
I'm not gonna just like,
it was in the middle of,
I was in a conversation with him.
And I'm not gonna, in the middle--
- Yeah, I would've straight up stopped him.
- In the middle of talking to him,
I'm not gonna bend over and eat a,
something from the floor.
it is i don't like it don't know if you're outside or outside you know where
like what what what where where was arrested
is that it was on the sidewalk on the sidewalk to the group thrown candy from
the floats in the privacy at the thing to be different or if it was in grass
in grass i feel it's almost
in grass above could get in it
affiliates of those who are on the side will not be done
you are definitely not in new york
in i kinda was like there's got to have so later i was like
as they met with slater cuz i'd
can you tell me a look at what if you saw it works
on top of a closed trash can
it's not so i don't know
on top of the video covered in cheese
i'd probably i would probably more inclined to eat
a twigs on a trash can
then it would so is in spaghetti i'm trying to find your like your line
and letting that weeks in the toilet
if that's a fully sealed police you get no water than that
is there
a turd in the toilet. No, it's just the Twix. Oh yeah, I'll eat that. But there's pee on
the rim of the bowl. So you don't know if somebody went in there and just was really
hydrated. But is there somebody who pees out, he like passed it like a kidney stone? Did
somebody push this? Would you eat a Twix that came from a man's penis? Okay, yeah. If it's
wrapped. Okay, what if the Twix is in the toilet and you know 100% that someone did
pee on it, but it's sealed in the wrapper? Then it doesn't matter. It's floating in pee
in the toilet you have to reach into the pee to get the Twix.
No candy is worth it for me to touch pee.
What if it's a really big Twix?
But if somebody, hmm, if somebody gets...
If you had a glove and the Twix was floating in pee.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, absolutely.
Are you kidding me?
Would you take it out and you wash it in the sink?
You'd wash it in the sink, okay.
Yeah.
I'd probably put soap on it.
Hold on.
What if it was a Baby Ruth instead?
Baby Ruth is better than a Twix.
What about an Almond Joy?
Okay, what about an Almond Joy?
Do you like Almond Joy?
eat one out of the wrapper stuck in a piece of shit. What's it what can do you
not like? Mounds. I like I kind of... Can you think of a candy that's like a map?
That'd be funny if you were like really into a mid candy. A mid candy? Maybe a payday.
One that you don't love. I love everything. You know what I've been thinking about it I love payday too.
I have a bag I've been eating candy every day since Christmas. Yeah. I've been eating like 10 pieces of candy.
What about a circus peanut? Oh I like. I like circus peanuts. I haven't had a circus peanut.
You never had a circus peanut?
No.
Is that like a Boston baked bean thing?
Oh, Boston baked beans, Jesus Christ, I gotta get some of those.
What about you, like candy corn?
Are you a candy corn fan?
Love candy corn.
I love candy corn too.
Would you eat candy corn out of the toilet?
If there was no water in the toilet, and the candy corn, and the candy corn, would you
scoop the candy corn that's not touching the edge of the toilet, off out of the middle,
and eat that?
Wait, describe this better.
It's a toilet, and it's complete, the bowl has no, nothing in it.
- When you flush more candy corn comes out.
- No, listen, the bowl is completely filled with candy corn.
- I'm listening.
- So there's a lot of candy corn
that's touching the bowl, right?
- Oh, yeah.
- But in the middle there's candy corn that's not.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- You would eat the one in the middle.
- Yeah, I'd probably eat every--
- How much, how far would you go?
How many layers of candy corn away from the bowl
would you eat to?
- Okay, so I would get a Ziploc gallon bag
and I would fill it up as much as I--
- Oh, you'd pick it up like dog shit?
- Yeah.
- Like you'd invert the bag and then grab it out?
And I'd pick up like probably, I'd probably go two, I'd probably, here I'll show you.
Here's what.
I'd probably put it like it was one big glove and then I would, I would kind of scoop around
it like this, create like a little ball and then I would pull it up like this and then
I would zip it.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And you would do that without a second thought.
You do that immediately.
If you walked into the bathroom and you saw candy corn, you just, you do that.
It's candy.
But even if you needed to go to the bathroom.
Well of course I have to get rid of the candy corn before I go to the bathroom.
Would you?
And then I have something to eat while I sit down.
Okay, would you, if you had to go to the bathroom really bad.
Okay, okay, wait, no, okay, here's a new scenario.
She eats brownie from a hungry pan on the toilet.
Yes.
I'm also very pro eating and drinking on while you do that shit.
Did I ever tell you, did I ever tell you to sit down on the toilet a lot of times?
Here's a new scenario.
You have to go to the bathroom so bad.
You have to pee so, so bad.
Okay, and you're not very hungry.
You're pretty full.
Well, but I'm not, but I'm, I'm food full, right?
I'm not candy full.
Okay, you're pretty candy full.
You walk in, okay, no, listen to my scenario, Patrick.
You are trying to ruin this anti-scenario.
I'm adding to it.
No, you're not.
You are taking away from it.
Now listen, you walk into the bathroom, you're about, your bladder is about to explode.
Droplets are shooting out of your pee hole like particles of light.
That's how fast they're going.
You open up the toilet lid and you're about to pee.
It's completely filled with candy corn.
There's no water.
You have a Ziploc bag in your pocket.
Are you scooping out candy corn to eat first or are you just going to pee right into it?
Which is more important to you?
Honestly, I would rather piss...
And you just took the pill that makes you hungry.
I would rather piss my pants...
Even if you're candy full.
...than waste that much candy.
Because, okay, so I can't...
So it's a whole toilet full of candy corn?
Yeah.
lifetime supply of candy corn at your apartment? A lifetime supply? Well yeah, but it's in my toilet.
And it's that, it's that. No, this is a different, you're at a restaurant. Oh. And it's that like
brown candy corn too. Okay, well let me ask you. You know the candy corn that has the brown on the
bottom? Yeah. Do I have? And you don't know if it's the candy corn with the brown on the bottom
or the normal candy corn that's just been in the toilet. Answer me this. It got brown from the
Exactly. That's what I'm saying you don't know.
Answer me this Riddle Master.
If I'm at a restaurant and I have a lifetime supply at home, do I have any candy corn with me?
Yeah, is candy corn on the menu at the restaurant?
Yes, it is.
Okay, did I order the candy corn?
Yes.
Well, then it makes you think.
But you finished it already.
Then probably...
You have no more left.
Then probably not because it's possible that somebody else at the restaurant ordered the candy corn and candy corn doesn't digest.
It shits it all out.
Okay, you made the right choice, because can I tell you the secret detail?
What's the secret detail?
Before you walked into the bathroom, a really, really fat guy walked out.
[Laughter]
Huh.
Wait, or maybe a really skinny guy who was really fat when he walked in.
Yeah.
I was like, it's like the ghost in the sauna in Halloween Town.
Yeah. Okay. Alright.
Yeah, so I would not eat that candy, I don't think.
He ordered a lot of candy corn at the restaurant.
I swear.
Yeah. Yeah, I bet you would.
I bet you would.
But I'm so pro candy.
I've been running, you know when you get a bag of candy for Christmas or something?
Here I'll show you guys.
Oh hell.
Dude, I'm getting some candy shipped to me from my dad's house.
Whoa.
You're getting candy chips?
I'm getting a candy shipment.
You know they had, they used to make.
This is my candy bag.
Damn.
Oh dude, oh holy shit.
It's gotten really bad.
Can I give you a dollar for that marshmallow reindeer?
You want the reindeer, not the Santa?
You like the strawberry?
Wait, is that the, it's the marshmallow one, right?
Yeah.
Shit, dude, actually I might take the strawberry one.
This is the strawberry one.
Actually, can I give you a quarter for it?
You can have both of them.
Whoa.
For free.
Holy shit.
You know why?
Because this is the worst candy in the world.
I still like it.
Those are terrible.
I don't care.
So do you eat those out of a toilet?
Yes, of course.
Wait, okay, you said you like all candies.
This is the one that you don't?
I still love it.
I would, like, do anything for that.
But it's not my favorite.
So this is my point.
So this is...
Okay, I got you guys your presents.
It's too...
So this used to be chock full of just every...
Chock full.
Every...
A lot of chocolate, okay?
It had...
Chock full.
It had a ton of Reese's trees, Christmas trees.
Oh, those are good.
White and milk chocolate.
Those are good as fuck.
Right?
Oh, dude.
So now I'm down at the bottom, so I got some Mexican shit in here.
I got some fucking shit that...
Oh, dude, yeah, there's a Konos in there.
Yeah, dude, I got candy canes.
I got Lifesavers.
I got fucking a piece of peppermint bark, but I still eat probably four pieces of this per
day.
I've not slowed down at all because candy is candy.
Is that gum's lifesavers?
Or is that, um, gummy lifesavers or hard candy lifesavers?
Hard candy.
I got a candy box coming in the mail and I can't wait.
I'm going to make my own candy bag.
I love candy.
And I forget every year from February to October.
I forget how much I love candy.
And then I get some candy for free.
It's important to forget that you like candy.
Because otherwise my candy budget is very low right now.
I'd be blowing it.
The realization, I had this, when I went back home last weekend, I had like the realization
like oh yeah, no, finding out that I could just buy candy and beer for dinner fucking
ruined me for a year.
You guys saw me, sometimes I'd eat just like a bag of like Sour Patch Kids and like a Modelo.
A Modelo?
a modelo a modeling six-pack yeah yeah and bottling bottling plant of an entire
modelo bottling yeah I forget I just eat candy for dinner yeah candy and some of
the best dinners of my life have been to Reese's cups and a PBR oh yeah
that gentleman's dinder that is a great dinder gentlemen's dinder gentlemen's
dinder for two to your four reseason to PBRs strong choice fancy but yeah I
really like high-class restaurant it's like yeah it's still worms well that we
go
lime seasoning maybe a candy popcorn oh my dude popping the candy corn in the
microwave at Alamo Draft House
biting into it is like really loud like it did like it's like every time you
bite into it it's just like it sounds like it sounds like when you're like
biting into a handful of popcorn.
Going to Alamo Draft House.
So everybody's watching the movie and it's just going like...
Ordering a 64 ounce
cup filled with
pop rocks at Alamo Draft House.
And you're eating the popcorn elote like
Looney Tunes, so you're like...
They just kick you out for anything there, right?
Yeah. Alamo Draft House.
I only went there one time. Did you get kicked out?
No. I feel like you got it.
They kicked me out at the end of the freaking movie.
I wasn't even done with the credits! I thought there was gonna be more credits!
Yeah, I wanted to see second credits.
Who made the credits? Where's the credits for the credits?
I thought there was a post-credits scene in Licorice Pizza.
There should have been one. Every movie should have a post-credits scene.
Yep, Bradley Cooper shows his penis. That's a post-credits scene.
It should be, no, it should be Iron Man should be in all of them.
Oh, so Iron Man shows Bradley Cooper's penis.
Iron Man should show up and recruit whoever's in the movie.
Yeah.
Right? So like at the end of, like, at the end of, uh, Hereditary.
Bradley Iron Man should show up and recruit the girl's head.
Yeah, it's just like a shot of Iron Man's glove picking up the head.
Yeah.
I think it should.
And he's like talking to the head.
He's like, "Do you want to join the Avengers?"
Yeah.
That's what he says.
Yeah, that could be good.
Because he died too.
Well, I think it should be, instead of Iron Man, I think it should be Thanos shows up and kills the main character.
Or like one of the secondary characters.
And then the main character of the movie is like, "I'll get you one day, Thanos."
Mm-hmm.
Thanos and then it's like
Thanos one day I'll get you
It's like the Paw Patrol will return in Marvel's Marvel
We already did this
We did?
We are when when Caleb was away and we did karaoke we talked for like 20 minutes about
Oh every superhero getting cancer
About a giant Marvel crossover with every movie ever where they all have cancer
Yeah
So we
Well it'd be so sad though
Yeah well you'll have to go back and listen to it if you want to hear how actually funny and as hell it is
(laughing)
- Yeah, don't tell me that's funny.
- I won't spoil anything about it.
But it's pretty weird.
- Okay, so candy has gotten me in a serious present move.
- Yep. - Move.
- All right. - Mood.
- All right.
- Mood. - Yours is already out.
- My move is so happily today.
- So Cameron, close your eyes.
- Oh, this is it? - And then I give,
and then I give, no wait.
- Oh, that is for me.
- Yeah, this is Caleb's gift.
- Am I holding on my hand right?
- So I'm not, so Cameron,
you actually are not getting yours yet.
- Okay, you close your eyes now.
- Okay.
- What, me?
keep yours close what you're doing both at once now one at a time okay then
never mind okay open open okay so I this looks I haven't unfolded it yeah looks
like it looks like a dishwreck looks like it looks like some kind of towel
thanks I've been eating a towel so what you know you can't see it you should
wipe yourself on it so there's a really really big shirt not the first big shirt
Patrick got me. Let's see what does this have on it. Let me see it. What is it? I think
it's Bill Cosby. That's, it's a giant airbrush of red fox that I found. I think that is a
3XL tall T. That is sick dude. That's tight. Yeah. Damn that's clean. That's swag as hell.
Thank you Patrick. Wow that's beautiful. Okay Cameron you close your eyes. Okay I'm gonna
close my eyes. This is a completion. This is a good gift. Okay, I'm going to open my eyes.
Whoa! No way dude. It's going to go great with your slippers and your shirt. The only problem
is I don't know if that will fit you. Where did you get a kimono? I don't know if it's
a kimono. It's a Chinese shirt. A Chinese jacket. Let's see. Well on here it says 35%,
percent sixty five percent one hundred percent it's probably that hundred
percent Chinese exactly all right let me try this so if you guys it's a 4xl and
I do not Cameron has a bunch of Chinese crap yeah so this is gonna be kind of a
perfect I mean we have to go to the casino right now you look so good holy
this might be better if I take off my sweatshirt yeah hold up oh my god that
is
You're saying he's a 4XL woman?
No.
What the hell?
He has a beautiful frail body.
Like a model.
Okay, here's the reveal.
Here's the reveal.
Wow.
Oh my god.
Okay.
Check it out in the mirror.
This mirror?
Wow.
Dude, you're damn good.
It's going to look sick as hell at the casino.
Holy dude.
This is going to be so...
Now I just need pants.
- Yeah.
- You mean, if anyone has a--
- Oh shit, I forgot about the pants.
- If anyone has a lead on Chinese pants.
- Yeah, do they make those?
Do those exist?
- I don't think they wear pants.
- You gotta get some kind of green satin pants.
- I also need to get Chinese shoes that aren't slippers
so I can wear them.
- True, yeah.
You said that you got me two gifts.
- No, I kept one of them.
- What was the other one?
- It was a XXL Freshman 2017 Snapback
sponsored by Magnum Condoms.
- And you gave me this shit?
And you kept that one for yourself?
- Yes.
I
I know you're fucking...
I told you.
I just downloaded...
I told you I knocked it out of the park first try.
This is good.
This is really good.
I just downloaded Duolingo today.
So, probably going to try and learn Chinese soon.
Damn.
The Chinese century is happening.
I'm really excited to be Chinese.
It's going to be a tough road ahead of you.
It's going to be hard.
Yeah.
But I'm going to persevere through my struggle.
A lot of people aren't going to like a lot of the things I do in my path to become Chinese.
You're going to hit a wall.
A great wall.
of all you're gonna have to push past that yes to finally be like an invader
like a Mongolian and like a Mongol horde member fine I'll become Mongolian no you
guys can spar well then we'll have to spar but sparring is a friendly thing
yeah that's true that's true you'll probably you'll end up pillaging me and
doing other things that come with pillaging - I wouldn't I don't even I
wouldn't want to pillage you I respect you too much to ever pillage that's
really nice of you to say. And then Pat can be Marco Polo.
Marco. Marco. Marco Polo. Don't you say just say Polo.
No, you'd be the guy. Marco. Marco Polo.
Yeah, you'll be Marco Polo. You guys don't know how to play this at all.
I'll go over there and I'll say it. He invented seeing fireworks for the first
time. Really? Wow.
In that game... Is that what he does? I literally, I only know the game.
He went to... In the game, if it was realistic, in the game, when you catch somebody, you
would rape them. That's what he was. Is that what he did? Yeah, he was a bad guy. He was
a bad guy? No, he wrote about how beautiful China was. No. No, no, no. I thought he just
liked swimming. Nope. He was a... I thought he was just like a really good swimmer. He
was a super duper raper. Yeah. Can't have shit nowadays, huh? Serious Michael Jordan.
Michael Jordan.
Of, oh yeah.
Like he had crazy, well more like Wilt Chamberlain I guess.
He had some crazy numbers.
Yeah.
He was putting them.
That's rough.
Yeah.
Wow.
I actually don't know if that's true.
Yeah, I don't know if that's true either.
Marco Polo was kind of just a guy like.
He went to China and he wrote about like.
Well, who was that guy?
The one they just fucking canceled the holiday.
Patrick Dorn.
Bill Gates.
No.
Bill Gates?
No, what?
What did you Franklin did like to get his you like to get his fanny tickled? Yeah?
Nah, you got a
His fanny tickled by a fancy French woman. Yeah. Yeah, the French woman would take a big feather giant feather
Set a feather big too big to belong to any real bird and white - no white bird is that it's like a die
It's like they bleached a peacock feather
Yeah, it's like they bleached the the long feather that runs down the spine of a condor
Yeah, and they put it they would just they would go up and down that thing make it brown
Mm-hmm, you know, they didn't have to early paperbacks. Yeah, they turned and I mean the feather it would get so wet
It would turn to a line. Yeah, I got all that all that. Yeah
We got you know
Tough to party would just get and then they would like a like that and call it macaroni like the tail of a cat
It would look like yeah. Yeah, it looked really bad. Yeah. Yeah, and that's where they go the other direction
It'll look like a pine cone.
And then one day he...
That's why the song is called Yankee Doodle.
One day he pulled the thing...
Because it's got a lot of doodle on it.
He pulled it out of his ass and he got struck by lightning.
Yeah.
Well, he only pulled it out of his ass because he had his keys on it.
Well, he couldn't find them.
Yeah.
Well, his keys were in his ass in the feather.
There was a feather and keys in his ass.
But he was looking for his Game Boy, which was also in there.
And a kite.
A kite was in there too.
Yeah.
Did he...
What is the importance of that story?
I never understood.
electricity he didn't event did he did event he didn't event electricity
discovered that if you fly a kite with a key it will be crazy it will be crazy
what happens when I do this hypothesis even did the scientific method yeah
silliest glasses in the world it will look crazy when I wear these I think
I think he was more of a novelty inventor.
Yeah.
He literally was.
He invented chattering teeth.
A lot of people know that.
He invented the Groucho Marshmallow.
I mean, literally down the side of that is the chattering teeth and the original teeth
were slave teeth.
He did invent a fake poop too.
He did almanacs too.
Which is like, he's just like Peggy Hill, like writing that newspaper thing, you know,
where she writes words of wisdom.
Like he's just sitting there writing, like a penny saved is a penny earned.
He just sat there and would just make stuff up like that.
He was basically Dr. Demento back then.
He was a bit of a fried gossip.
Mm-hmm.
He was busted as fuck too.
Yeah, he was mad ugly too.
Oh yeah.
Thomas Jefferson.
Jefferson was getting it in real quick.
Oh yeah.
Fine as hell.
Yeah, he had it on lock.
Yeah.
Right?
Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah.
Definitely.
Over there in, what's his house called?
Jefferson Manor?
No.
Vernon, Mount Vernon.
No, that's, that's, wait, maybe it is Mount Vernon.
Jefferson Street. No, no, he had a French name. Al Vernon was Washington's. Oh, Lafayette.
No, that was his friend. Was it? You know what I'm talking about. I know you're talking about
it. It's in Virginia. Is Ponce de Lafayette, is that a person? I don't fucking know, man.
Marquis de Ponce de Leon. Got a couple of Hamilton listeners among us, huh? No, a couple
of paid very good attention in fifth grade. I think we had a project. I bet you did. We
We had a project in third grade.
Yeah, yesterday.
Oh!
[SCREAMING]
We're back.
We had a project in--
I crashed off my candy, but I'm back, baby.
We had a project in third grade.
Pedophile.
[LAUGHTER]
Where we had to make these things.
They're called bottle guys.
And someone made Marquis de Lafayette.
So we had to make bottle guys, and then someone
and someone told me about bottleguy.com.
- What's bottleguy.com?
- Pull up bottleguy.
- Is that like one man, one jar type thing?
- Yeah, it's like a guy in a field,
it's just a JPEG of a guy in a field,
whole 40 ounce of beer in his asshole.
- Oh, maybe we've talked about this,
but I can watch any shock video like that
unless the sound is on.
- Yeah, it's just a JPEG, it's one of the funniest things.
- I can watch any--
- 'Cause it used to load super slow.
I can watch any video of a guy getting exploded with a piece of dynamite.
Yeah, like the horse versus the train.
Yeah, donkey versus...
Donkey hit to train, train hit to donkey.
Train hit to donkey, yeah.
Train hit donkey, Pat.
But the donkey's fine, by the way.
The donkey lived. He's perfectly fine.
He's just...
That's why it's fine to watch that video.
Yeah, it is fine.
He's pleased.
like you I because I follow like there's a bunch of random shit on Facebook like
it's a bunch of random pages and there was some video of a dog getting like
like like flying into the air cuz like like it's basically just died instantly
like it like a thing like some big like I don't even know what it was like like
it hit like it was almost like a like when those videos are people like sit on
an airbag and then the airbag goes off yeah it's not like that and the dog like
goes flying and then the like description the video is like do not
take this down the dog is completely okay.
It's a good hack.
Clearly, yeah.
And I know when I watched it I was like, oh maybe the dog's okay.
Yeah.
Maybe they're right.
It's good to do, yeah, like with the collateral murder video just being like, oh all these
people actually, they were fine.
They were fine, yeah.
They were fine.
They just had to.
You know what, you know the video just makes it look weird.
We were dropping fireworks.
We were dropping fireworks and presents.
They're running around in circles like when people are having so much fun that they run
around in a circle.
Yeah, it's yes, they're fine. They're okay. They're listening to La Cucaracha down there. Yeah, we thought it was Mexico. We're bringing pinatas to them
Yeah, that is everybody's favorite song in Mexico. Yeah, I've confirmed this with a lot of people
Dude, imagine if you could walk anywhere and hear your favorite song just from traffic wouldn't that be amazing just from people hawking their horn
Yeah
It's it's like if in the American equivalent so La Cucaracha is the Mexican one of those in Tampa happy birthday
Absolutely. I mean imagine you walk down the street and everybody is honking at each other
but just so that they can hear the national anthem again. You know, because that's what
the La Cucaracha is as well. The national anthem of Mexico. And everything else that's down
there.
I thought it was live in La Vida Loca.
Huh?
No, that's the national anthem of Shrek.
Oh, yeah, Far Far Away.
Far Far Away, that's the national anthem.
I don't know, because when they pull up, they play Funky Town.
No, but when they have the big party at the end when they all sing together.
They sing Livin' La Vida Loca.
And Puss in Boots and Shrek and the Donkey and Pinocchio.
Wait, what's the song that Donkey sings with the dragon?
Is that...
That's uh, in which, in Swamp Idol?
Swamp Idol?
You remember from the DVD?
Oh, Swamp Idol, yeah.
It might have been Swamp Idol.
What do they sing in Swamp Idol?
I forget what they sing together in Swamp Idol.
How did you remember? How did you pull Swamp Idol?
Swamp Idol sounds like a Dark Souls item.
Yeah.
Swamp Idol, they got Simon Cowell in it.
No way.
They do.
Yeah.
And if you pick someone who isn't a main character to win.
You remember when they pulled people off the stage with the big hook?
Did they say fuck in Shrek?
They do.
I kinda have...
I wanna fuck this donkey!
They don't say?
You ain't gonna fuck me, Shrek!
I'm gonna fuck your ass!
Yes!
It's gonna happen!
And I've got a turtle head poking out!
And I ate a baby!
Cause they are the same voice!
Shrek and Fat Master are the same voice!
Yeah, they are!
Remember, he does curse a little much for me in that movie.
He says yeah, he's got a he can swear. He's an ogre. He said I had to save me ass
Nah, remember that I was a double entendre
This makes it even more. It's twice as foul. Yeah. Yeah, I
Wish Fiona never turned into an episode in donkey voice. No, I'm not gonna do the donkey
I did I hit my maximum until I put on this red fox shirt. Then you got to see me turn to it
told me
I'm gonna turn to the old me. I just heard like Shrek again and make you do that. No, I'm not gonna do donkey voice
No, you'll see the holes
It sounded perfect the first time the the cracks will start to appear if I try to say anything else
Same I'm making waffles, please. I'll make you waffle. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, but I love to do that I love to do that Eddie Murphy
Now make waffles
I don't really like waffles that much.
I like waffles but I don't want...
You're... oh man.
Pancakes are good.
Pancakes...
I like pancakes.
Compared to waffles.
Earlier I said I'd eat candy corn out of the toilet and I just said that I'm a pancake
man and he said "Ugh."
I don't like pancakes.
You're weird.
What?
You don't like breakfast in general so you're thinking it really doesn't matter.
You have to recuse yourself from any conversation that has anything to do with delicious breakfast
because you have a mental disability that keeps you from...
I'm starting to turn around on breakfast.
No you're not.
Shut up.
Name one breakfast food you like.
Uh, smothered, covered, chopped, and uh, peppered.
Waffle house.
It's not breakfast food.
Yeah it is.
No it's not.
Waffle house is all food.
Biscuits and gravy.
Biscuits and gravy is I guess breakfast, but you're, these are like, these are things.
Chicken and waffles.
But coming around on breakfast he means we ate at Waffle House one time in Tampa.
No, because then we went to that other, into that deli, or the diner, with patches.
But you don't like eating at breakfast.
It's still too early in the day.
See you were trying to be like, "Oh I actually like breakfast right now."
I do like breakfast now.
And you literally can't even keep up the charade for one minute.
No, I like breakfast.
But you don't like eggs.
You like breakfast but you don't like eating breakfast.
I like a fried egg.
I like breakfast for dinner.
This is, I don't even know.
You're a bitch.
You're not even an American.
I'm sorry, that's too far.
Breakfast for dinner does rock though.
You're an idiot.
Piece of shit.
You get breakfast for dinner is really good.
Breakfast for dinner is really good.
That's like one of the best.
of the best like treats you can have. You're like, "Oh, I'm gonna have breakfast for dinner."
I don't have any food. I already took an egg.
The J. Kenji fried egg thing. I've been doing that.
What does that mean?
He puts it in the-
He likes watching breakfast making videos.
The basting it with the oil?
It's been helping.
It's been helping him.
He has to watch videos in order to like the meal.
What does he do with the egg?
It's like, he basically bastes it like a steak with the oil.
Yeah, okay.
And then it gets super crispy.
his thing is not no it's like the oldest trick in the book that's how i learned it from him
god bless jkenji lopez alt the five the five named man that's what he would be in a circus yeah
see a man with too many names of five say almost any word it could be one of his names
I don't know, Alt.
The pentaman!
Who would be named Alt?
Bingo!
That's, but what part of the name?
I've never seen one of his videos, I always assumed Alt is not part of his name.
That's his name.
That's part of his name?
Yeah.
It's his last name.
He took, okay, so his name was Jay Kinji and then his first name starts with a J, one of
his parents' last name is Kinji, the other parent's last name is Alt, it's like a German
Okay. And then when he married his wife, he also took her last name of Lopez.
But he put it in the middle. And he put it, I mean, he's making a sandwich. This guy's a
fucking professional chef. So he made, he has three last names. His name, what if he had just been
J-Alt? That's cool. That would have been cool. That's a cool, that's an ADM.
He's already a band. It's the opposite.
Whoa, that's the Alt-Alt-J. Yeah.
Wow. And then if he, and then they would,
I would write alt comma J.
Instead of a period.
Yeah.
I think I'm gonna become a food YouTuber.
Yeah?
I think it might be my future.
It's just like you!
You with the one cast iron you have in there.
Actually no, you have way more pans than me.
I shouldn't talk, but like the cast iron that's always on the stove.
I gotta walk, you don't even know that.
Fuck, really?
Yeah.
I make everything in my walk.
Damn.
I'm straight.
This is what happens when you live.
You wanna talk like you Chinese.
Peep my walk.
Can we see it?
Go get your walk out.
walk out. I'm gonna take it out. It's in the, guess what I just used it this morning so it's
in the fucking, it's in the dishes pile. So go wash it and show it to us. I'm not gonna
wash my walk. Show me your walk. Get your soap on it. Then go get it out and show it.
Show me your walk. No. You're not gonna wash it. I'll show it to you guys afterwards. That's
the problem with living with three other guys though is I, I, I found a fucking apple core
the other day and we own one knife. What? We own, we own one knife. Okay, explain how
these two things are related? No, just like you know. You found an apple core. An apple
corer. Oh okay, and now I thought you said you found an apple core and you own one knife. No,
we own one knife. I just bought my own pan. Nice. And do you guys do the thing where you're like
that's my cup, that's my pan? I only do that with the one cup and it's the. So you do that though?
I do that with two actually two cups. I have my Guinness cup that my mom got me and the Yoda cup
my brother. So nobody fuck with the Guinness Cup? Yes. Or the Yoda Cup? Yes.
Jana got mad at me the other day because I used her water bottle. Yeah? Yep.
Beat my ass. Beat my shit in. But yeah we have we have I just got my own pan. When
the fuck like when the fuck are we ever gonna eat I've never seen somebody eat an
apple in the house. Who cores an apple? Yeah, coring an apple is stupid. Why the fuck do
we have an apple corer? Make an apple pie? We just got a pizza cutter too because I was
at the hardware store and I saw one and I was like, "Pfft, shit." You don't need a pizza
cutter though. Nobody needs a pizza cutter. No, you need a pizza cutter. How often do
you eat pizza? No, that's a fake lot. How often are you making pizza? A lot. What? Frozen
pizza. Oh, okay. Isn't frozen pizza usually already cut? No. Even if it isn't, you don't
need a pizza cutter. Yeah. You do. Just fold it like a big taco. No, you don't need it.
- Or you can cut it with a knife, yeah.
- I hate doing that.
- So you got a pizza cutter?
- Yeah, I got a pizza cutter.
So I have a pizza cutter, a knife,
a bunch of old spatulas, an apple corer.
- Did you get, you probably, you might wanna get--
- And one cookie sheet.
- You might wanna get sippy cup lids for all your cups too.
- That'd be pretty smart.
- Yeah, 'cause I know you don't really need it,
but if you don't like drinking from the cup,
it might be better to just sip.
Plus, if I drop the cup, it won't spill.
- Yeah, well it'll break, 'cause it's a glass cup.
- When I was a kid, I had these cups--
- Well, hold on.
(laughing)
- When I was a kid, I had--
- None of the cups in my house are glass.
- I had cups, and I want these now as an adult,
like adult size, I had cups that had straws built into 'em.
- Oh yeah.
- You ever have those?
- I remember those, yeah.
I had a bowl with straws built,
it was a straw built into it.
- That's messed up.
- What?
- You're a Dr. Seuss character.
- You are a Dr. Seuss character.
- My mom bought it.
My mom bought it.
You kinda- wait, I wanna see your hair again.
Nice haircut.
Mm-hmm.
It's a bit who-ish if you ask me, but-
It doesn't look who-ish.
It's kinda got a who-ish curl.
Yeah, they'd fuckin' do that.
You're a who-ish ass snitch.
That barber, that barber went to town on me. I thought he was gonna fuck me.
What does that mean?
Dude, he was massagin' my head and shit.
Really?
Uh-huh.
What's his- where does he work?
Soho.
You went to Soho to get a haircut?
I went to the place Neil goes to, yeah.
What?
Wait, isn't that a place that they have like scientists that work there?
Yeah, it's like a place where they can like risk like it's like a place that has like hair restoration
Whoa, did they try to sell it to you? You're there really?
Yeah, I put that fucking I put that
Haircut on my credit card. I don't want to fuck it. I'm paying for that next month. I don't care smart. Yeah
Yeah, I bet it's pretty expensive. Oh, yeah, it's like 65 bucks 65 bucks for a look at me
Okay, yeah, I mean it's clear that you had a comb in your head
Yeah, I do most of what most of this is the face that you're doing yeah, you're just making a face
Yeah, but I feel really good - you feel good
Well, so that's worth 65 bucks in my book - he massaged the fuck out of my head. Yeah, you're put
That's what you're paying for. Oh, they did the hot towel thing on my face. Whoa
Really? Yeah. Oh
I've never had that before. I really fucking did they bring did they do your beard?
No, but duty did like the hot foam on my neck straight razor. Yep. Oh my god. I would be so
No, I had a little spa day basically that's so sick that's why I'm so relaxed to that be worth the price actually
Oh, yeah, totally. I would go get if I was rich. I'd get my head straight razored every single day
Yeah, give my entire dude you should just go in there and just like grow your hair out for like a week go in there
Demand they shave your head. Yeah, they'll do it. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, but like I cut my hair was bald
I'm sure he all dude he probably gets another better barber to like and then that guy probably has a better barber
Yeah, and they do it in a train. Oh my god
You wish that you were so wait
If my barber ran a train on me with a bunch of other barbers
I wouldn't care. We've all had the fantasy. If they have to, but they'd have to go in a
circle and then the one, the last really good barber will be cutting a bad, or the bad barber
would have to cut the best barber. No, the last barber is one of those guys who has like
the world record for the longest hair and beard and his hair is like, goes, walks, it's
like behind, it's like a bunch of people carry it like it's the train of the bride at a Mexican
it
- It's like a crazy, like, dude, there's just--
- I'm not aware of this at all.
- If you go to Nashua, New Hampshire, Main Street,
there are four different barber shops
owned by the same beard pomade hair guys.
- Yeah, and they're all called--
- That's what they, all the barber shops are like that.
- White barber shops are--
- And they're called like Gentleman's Affect.
- They're called, everything's called like--
- Everything's called like Sandalwood.
- Yeah.
- White barber shops are like veteran owned
and they have Wounded Warrior Project shit everywhere,
but they only know one haircut,
and you go in there,
and you ask them to do something specific,
and then they're just like,
yeah, you know, I basically just,
I did what made sense,
'cause what you said made no sense.
- Or they just say, okay, I did it,
and then it's you look in the mirror,
and it's something. - And then you have
like a fuckin' high and tight.
- And somehow your hair is like,
even though it's like so greasy,
you can see your reflection in your own head.
That shit's cool, man.
Damn.
They use a pomade that says, like, "Do not put near open flames."
You know why those popped up?
Macklemore.
Shia LaBeouf in the newest Indiana Jones movie.
Yeah?
Yep.
I was thinking it was Macklemore, but I guess Macklemore probably sounds like Shia LaBeouf.
I don't know who Macklemore is.
Macklemore.
I don't know who that is.
(singing)
Do you remember that song?
What, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what,
Well, I was thinking of the other one.
What's the other one?
The gay one.
It would make sense that you know that one.
Yeah.
That song actually was Mad Beautiful.
I only know the straight one.
Thrift shop.
The one about being...
That song was Mad Beautiful and it brought me to tears, but okay.
The one about being so straight.
Patrick really loves listening to a song about a third grader who thinks he's gay.
[laughter]
Yep.
Do you have your piano?
We're back again.
My keyboard?
I learned that in high school.
You learned...
I learned how to play Same Love because I thought it was funny.
Thought it was really funny.
Yeah, we were like, "Guys, look! Guys, listen!"
I think it was more, you learn it like,
you learn it like how a hunter learns how to use a bird call.
Yeah.
Going into like, going into like, that fucking evil place we went to with the piano
and just like playing Same Love over and over again.
Evil place we went to with a piano?
The Russian place.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Remember we walked in, there's a dude.
Oh yeah, okay.
It was playing that Joe Jackson song and the dude was just freestyling on the piano but
it was so clear he had no idea how to play the piano.
Yeah, that's pretty cool.
Yeah, going in there only playing Same Love to attract gay men.
I'm trying to relearn how to play the piano.
Yeah.
It's pretty tough.
It's difficult.
I have really small hands.
I never could make my hands do different things, my two hands.
Really?
That was my issue when I tried to play the piano.
Yeah, but you're stupid.
Yeah, I know. I can't play. Actually, I can play a little bit of piano, but...
No, other hand.
Oh my god, we're comparing hand sizes.
Look, he's got big hands.
He does have really big hands.
Yeah.
That means you got a big long cock.
No.
Oh, you have small hands.
Yeah.
Oh, I didn't know that.
Wow, your hands are tiny.
You guys didn't know that? I have really small hands for my size.
Jesus.
You got a little tiny baby cock, huh?
This big.
(laughing)
- My shit's small as hell.
- Yup.
- My hands, my feet are very big.
My thing, it's like a caterpillar.
- Really?
Does it move on its own like a caterpillar?
- No, it's in a cocoon.
- Oh, yeah.
You need to put it in a sapoon.
- A sap, are you trying to say a saporo?
- I'm saying some poon like Adam Sandler.
- I put it in a saporo can.
- Oh, you gotta put it in a sapoon.
- I put in a Sapporo can of shit, bulletproof.
- I had a Sapporo last night.
- I saw you drinking it.
- Dude, have you ever tried to like,
you ever sit there and just try to squeeze the can?
- No dude, I know my limits.
I'm gonna strain my fucking ligaments in my hand.
- Yeah, I know, you break all your fingers.
- You know what, that is a prank can though.
Because the can is so, it's so much metal
on the bottom of the can that it convinces you
whenever you pick it up that there's one sip left.
And then you go to sip it, it's just a fucking metal.
I mean, I'm sorry.
- Even the fucking six packs, Sapporo.
- Really? - Sapporo.
- They have metal on the bottom of the six pack?
- No, like the--
- Something about you makes me think
you might like Sapporo.
- Yeah, what is it?
- Sapporo. - No idea.
- Is that how you say it?
What is the proper pronunciation of Sapporo?
- How are we gonna kit you out?
What's this loadout gonna look like?
- Sephiroth beard. - What else do we need?
- Well, okay, so I got the tiger shirt that I'll--
- Yeah, that's the jacket.
- Yeah, this is the jacket.
I need some kind, I need really loose-fitting pants,
like really satin. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Some kind of shoe. I don't know. Maybe, maybe
something like... There's no way this alarm's going off again. Maybe like a curly elf shoe
could be good as a shoe. And then I need to figure out some hat, some kind of hat that
I'm allowed to wear. Because that's a tough one. That might be the hardest part. Yeah,
New York Knicks hat, yeah that might work.
Yeah.
The hat that short round, why'd you bring your mic away from your face to ask what hat short
round wore?
Yeah what are you?
You just got exposed.
I'm DJ Vlad.
I wanted to, I wanted the joke to work.
He doesn't know what kind of hat short round wore but he knows exactly what kind of pants
he was wearing in that movie.
It was a Brooklyn Dodgers hat.
Brooklyn Dodgers, Ebbets hat, you could probably pick that up.
were bricked up in your Dodge watching that movie yep when short rounds there
yeah you went that one's crazy the Temple of Doom because it's just it's just
Indiana Jones just got a bunch of Chinese you get a short round with
himself you filled up a thimble of coom when you yeah yeah
playing with my bone oh my god you guys don't stop I'm gonna read this key foods
receipt okay dox me what I ordered boxing you right now what I get GT rock and
kombucha hibiscus yeah I like kombucha so what GT Ross energy tea yeah I got two
kombuchas go so damn thirsty and I need to kill yeah that's only well hold on
two versus it's not even a deal at all did you get two of the same one no it
says it costs $11 I wanted two different flavors from two different brands
problem no GT is the brand wait this makes no sense why did you have to pay
11th do you got you got scammed I got scammed you got scammed at the key foods
dude oh no wait I didn't see the medley of tomatoes I was only paying attention
to kombucha teas and not the medley of tomatoes it'd be funny if there's a
boy I didn't want you to get scammed at the key foods it just says three
tomatoes it's kind of a medley of tomatoes that I got I got two heads of
cauliflower and he wouldn't fucking show me they're not for you to look at that's
true what's on the menu cauliflower
that
air fryer. Yeah, pretty good. I'm trying to think. Oh, you guys have air fryers? Air fried
tofu. It's taking the tofu game to another level. Oh, dude, I can imagine. It's really
good. It's straight up, it feels like you're eating chicken. Yeah. It's great. Do you do
the freezer thing? What freezer thing? I don't think so. So you take the tofu, you drain
the water out, put it in the freezer, thaw it out, drain it again, cover it in flour.
That sounds nice but I'm really lazy.
Yeah, I mean it's a process but the texture that it gets is like similar to like chicken
McNuggets.
I mean we just, we just, we just drain it and press it and then like.
I feel like I can get too much damn water in this tofu.
Some corn starch?
Can never get it out.
I can never get that.
I can always get corn starch on it.
I can never get that tofu water out.
You gotta just press it for a while.
You gotta buy the pre-pressed shit and then press it again.
Yeah.
I don't know what the hell you're even saying.
The pre-pressed tofu comes in a plastic bag.
What are you saying right now?
Pre-pressed tofu?
is are you in speaking English?
well it's I don't know pre what was it?
pre-pressed what is that what? pre-pressed
pressed before I'm gonna depress you
I'm gonna give you depression you already do
that's right you're mean to me on that's right stupid
bitch
I'm sorry that was rude of me
my mom was gonna have a talking to with you guys
She would never pull up on me.
Yeah, she, oh.
Fine, tell her, "Yo, if you're listening, Pat's mom,
I'll send you the addy right now. All I'm gonna need is your phone number."
[laughs]
"Come on, just send me your phone number.
I'll get it from Patrick if I don't get it from you."
It's that simple. Add me on Facebook.
Mm-hmm. She would love to add you on Facebook.
She would send you all the videos that she's trying to send to me.
She'd send me all the videos, you say.
Yeah, like videos that are like--
All the videos.
all the videos.
Shit mom says.
Shit my mom says.
You guys befriending my mom on Facebook and then immediately she's just sending you like
America's Got Talent crazy.
Speaking of Facebook.
I have a new Facebook discovery for you guys.
I found a new Facebook page that where the guy who does like energy healing like over
Zoom and I found his like Instagram page where he has like videos of his energy healing sessions
and there's one video also to you guys
but it's just it says in really big letters
energy laser
and it's just a video of a guy like lying down on his stomach
and it's just a video of a guy standing over like his legs
and the energy healer
just points his finger at the legs and stands there for like ten seconds
and then it zooms in on the legs and the legs just like go like this
like they just like twitch a little bit and the video ends
like that's the whole video
and it's called an energy laser. What was that one? It's really cool. When we were at, oh, oh, it was that
class reunion. Oh, yeah. I keep finding groups that I forgot I
joined. I'm in some like, dude, you're like high school class of
I don't remember what year it was. Like it was like fucking
joining Facebook. Oh, yeah. What was that one Facebook? Ascension
fifth dimension? No, what was the science? I fucking love
science. Oh, that was
what was it? Oh, he was arguing with me that dogs didn't have
dreams or dogs had dreams or something. Did you say high
high school class of one thousand nine hundred and two. Apparently I'm in this
group and now it shows up on my timeline on Facebook all the time and it just it's
only post of people like. Unfortunately, another classmate has died
as literally the only post of that fucking comment. You showed me where
it's like that guy like saying like my condolences and then the lady is like,
oh Ron, my high school. Yeah,
that's so awesome. It's a really good. What you I'm going to I did. I haven't
yet but I will soon. I thought you did. No I will soon. I have to think I'm gonna post like
anybody here would happen to and make up a name but I have to think of a good name.
What's it alright let's think of it now. Yeah well you guys I'll post it right now if you guys help me
think of a name. This will be the finale. Wait okay how old are these people? Class of 1992.
That's probably my mom's age. Okay so we could. Yeah I think so. What about what if we did like
like
test. No, we need to make up a detail about him. He was he was always wilding
out in camp. Why? Wilding out? Wilding out? Wilding out? He was the shortest kid in class.
Quite the firecracker. He was quite the fire. Okay. Shortest kid in class though.
Blonde hair, quite the firecracker. Been trying to keep in touch. Yeah, been trying to reconnect.
Yeah. Blonde hair, quite the firecracker and then an M-dash trying to reconnect.
it
I can't do it.
Just do it.
You know like the screens that you can get?
Like the backgrounds?
Yeah.
How about this one?
These flowers.
Ooh.
Scroll through them.
Let's see.
Okay, wait.
Here's a bunch of options.
Okay.
Maybe the hearts?
Oh, the fire?
Oh, yeah, dude.
Fire.
Firecracker.
Okay, I'll post it right now.
All right, I'll keep you guys updated.
Yeah, we gotta know.
I just posted it.
I'm excited to know.
Yeah.
All right.
What happened with Johnny Test?
Yeah, yeah, all right. Bye
Bye everybody.