You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[laughter]
Okay, alright. That was perfect.
Who coughed?
Wasn't me, dude.
It was our very special guest, Leo.
Oh.
I didn't know he was in the call.
Yeah, you did.
Welcome back Leo, what's up? What's going on?
I'm good, I'm feeling good. I think my audio equipment is busted and I only just found out now.
So I don't know what I'm going to do. I think I'm going to be kicked out onto the street.
Yeah, get off the episode now.
Get the fuck out!
I'm sorry guys.
Get out.
Unless you cry and turn your video on.
Yeah, I will turn my video on.
Turn your video on and cry and maybe like squint like, whoa!
Yeah.
Holy shit.
You guys can't see this, but he's in outer space.
That's right.
Yeah.
Just, I was saving that for when the podcast started.
I really wanted to blow your minds.
It worked.
Yeah.
I thought that maybe you were so, I thought this is, this was crazy.
I thought you were so poor that you couldn't even afford a webcam.
Now I realize you're so rich that you're in space right now.
Well, I can't afford, I couldn't afford an astronaut suit, but they did just put me up
Which is nice of them. Yeah, I mean look at his shirt. He's so rich
That's true. I am wearing a
prisoner of war shirt right now
Heard they're making a sequel to boy in the striped pajamas
They're doing a crossover with the boy in the striped pajamas at ET
This looks like Richard Branson going as a boy in the straight pajamas.
Just in space, shirt halfway buttoned, ready to have sex.
You look good man.
Thanks man.
It's been a long time.
I think actually there's a scrapped episode of your show that I was on because the audio.
Yeah.
What did you do?
Patrick said something really nasty.
Oh, I said a few pretty bad things about Inuits and um
The end of the cp, but no no, no, no, no, no. Yeah together in the same sentence
About both those things and found a way of intertwining them. It was really impressive
It was about it was about a half an hour of the podcast. They had to scrap it
but
Yeah, well it was it was a really re-recording
It was a really impressive poem that he that he told
Yeah, he did a soliloquy. It was really great.
I've been getting into poetry.
No, you haven't.
No, you have not.
That's on the list of like 5,000 things you could tell me that you were starting to gain
interest in and I would just not believe you.
What's, say, with some other things? What are some other things?
Like vitamins? Like if you told me I'm taking vitamins every day.
I have been I have
What are you doing over there? Yeah, what is he what do you think he's gonna pull?
If you can't find them, you're clearly not into them because you're supposed to take them every day. I
Put them on the the thing at the foot of my bed my little like you're supposed to put them in your mouth
I kicked him off of my thing while I was asleep because I didn't take him today.
Were you sitting in your bed eating vitamins like chips?
Why were they in your bed?
On the foot of my bed!
Okay, let's see these vitamins.
Okay, yeah, show me, go ahead.
Okay, well, I can only find one.
It's my E3 supplements.
Okay, let's see here.
I don't see those.
E3, that's not real.
That's not a real vitamin.
Vitamin 3?
It's for, it supports immune health!
No.
for bone immunity?
Bone immunity?
You're immune from bones.
It's a division three.
Bone health.
Bone immunity.
There's an asterisk.
What does the asterisk go to?
The asterisk, um, let me actually see what that means.
It actually harms your bones.
This is actually candy.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's like candy cigarettes.
These statements have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration.
All right, then, I don't count.
I don't count.
administration. All right then I don't count it because I go by the FDA on everything.
Are you kidding me? Those are vitamins to me. It says vitamin you know what I'm
gonna take three right now. Did you get those from like Info Wars or something? I got
these from Walgreens which is the same thing. Is that AlphaBrand? I'm gonna get
into that I think. I've been thinking about getting into nootropics because I am so
stupid that the only thing that could cure me is a pill. Yeah I would
like to get into those. My brother my younger brother had a thing that was
called like libido strength or something like that.
They always tie in.
Like testosterone like pills and I started taking them.
It's always like brain booster plus ball sack expander.
So you never get, you can never just get like it's good for your brain.
It always has to have something to do with your male penis.
It's true.
But I don't, I don't really, it's not that I don't need a bigger dick.
I definitely do, but I don't really want one.
I'm like content with how my shit looks.
Yeah?
Really?
That's how your shit looks?
That's good.
I saw a video the other day of a guy whose dick looked like if Bowser had a dick.
And I was like, that was the first time in a while where I was like, I wish I had that
guy's dick.
It had a turtle shell.
Well it was just like so, it looked like it was not green but it did look, it was like
all veins.
Oh, okay.
And like insanely hard.
It looked like a rhino's horn with a vein in it.
Alright, maybe if I saw that too I'd have the same reaction.
You'd be less content, yeah.
Yeah, but I think, you know, you can't really...
I do want one.
Wait, where did you see it?
Yeah, I saw it in a pornography video.
What do you mean?
Okay, that's cool.
But I didn't know if it was in person or something.
I saw it, did I not say a video?
Oh, through the lens, through the viewfinder you saw it.
Yeah, I was filming a pornography video.
And I saw this guy's dinosaur penis. Okay. I said that's pretty good man. Yeah, look more like a weapon
Then a play show you weren't just watching new grounds animated pool. I'm watching like a Mario theme. I'm not sure
I'm really not sure. Yeah, I have a hard time in Bowser. Yes, Ernie between
Yeah, my parents my parents caught me when I was a kid
Firstly my mom came in the room once and said can you stop googling naked celebrities on the family desktop but secondly,
they found in my search history animated frankenstein porn that i was watching on youtube.
That is the most british thing i've ever heard.
So here's what happened, it was an american production, they weren't talking in english accents, it was an american production.
Easily you probably you you probably have much more to do with it. But anyway, here's what happens in it
Or what I remember is it's uh, it's halloween themed first of all
A woman a nice sexual woman is uh opening her door and giving treats to people
And frankenstein it's actually frankenstein, but she thinks that he's
A trickle treater. So she's like, oh, would you want some candy and then he?
Sort of flips her around and uh has his way with her
Oh, Frankenstein flips a woman around and has his way with her.
Yes. So I mean, that's I mean, he's evil.
Yeah, we knew that she likes it.
She likes, OK, well, the way that you just presented it did not sound
like it was, you know, kind of sounded like Frank, one of Frank
and his many crimes. Yeah, kind of.
She's kind of oblivious in it, if I remember correctly.
This wasn't I mean, this was a long time ago.
And also so she's still while she's getting fucked she still thinks like this is a little kid in green makeup
Presumably I know
Heroes in this story
I'm I searched Frankenstein porn. Okay. I found a video here on X videos called
Frankenstein's monster fucks like crazy
Whoa, well at least you know at least at least they're making the distinction that it is the monster and not the doctor
Yeah, that's true. It is true. Not too many people do that brand-new dashing Frankenstein does his first scene
dashing Frankenstein
Is that like Frankenstein like shows up like is it more of a behind-the-scenes thing? I
Don't know. I haven't watched I'm still super
Ever did the fuck to the monster. I mean, yeah
Okay, you have to right. Yeah, how would you not?
I mean, does doctor does the Frankenstein's monster have like an asshole and a dick?
Like why would he go through the yeah, give him an ass you just make him plain down there
Do you think like I feel like I would if I was him it would like yeah
It's also a lot of a bitch would be right away on women's doors and flipping them over and shit. Yeah
Cuz why does he build?
Frankenstein it was to like reach something high on a shelf or something like I don't know
I thought he was building Frankenstein to like just prove that he could.
No, he's he's the one of the villagers actually came to his house the day
before he made Frankenstein and said you could never make a green guy.
Yeah, you'd right.
Yeah, blue guy maybe.
Red guy for sure.
You could never make a green guy.
The villager with knocked on the door.
Villager knocked on the door. His blue guy answered.
And then got Dr. Frankenstein.
And said
He said, "I mean, I see that blue guy.
That, you know, anybody could do that shit.
But how about a green guy?
You know what?
There's lightning in there too.
I bet you can't add lightning somehow."
Fucking dare you.
You try to make a green guy with lightning, then come back to me.
You'll never make a guy with a flat head.
It wouldn't happen.
Yeah, why is his head flat?
That's just the head that they found at the graveyard.
Yeah, why does that guy's head look like that?
I bet you can't do anything with the two bolts I have in my back pocket.
Yeah, I bet you can't make a green guy with, hold on, let's see, toothpick, ball of lint,
yeah, and this shit.
And bolt of lightning.
Yeah, I dare you.
Yeah.
And what is the moral of Frankenstein?
It's like.
Is don't play God, that's the moral.
Don't play God.
Yeah.
Don't play.
Well, it's don't play God and then like.
The monster is actually nice is also one of the morals.
That's a nice moral.
It's a good moral, yeah. It's very helpful in real life.
Yeah, because any time that I've run into a monster before I've been attacked by them,
I thought, well maybe they might, they could be nice.
They could just be nice, yeah. I could be misinterpreting this whole situation.
I think it's good for if you run into Brett Garrett, it tells you how you should act.
Yeah.
True.
If they do like a new reboot of Frankenstein, I bet that'd be the best guy.
I bet Mary Shelley would feel so stupid about her moral of the monster actually being nice
if she watched Alien.
She'd be like, "Oh, I guess monsters are actually evil."
Yeah, she would sit there watching all these horror movies and be like, "Oh, well, maybe
they're going to be nice to the-" Ah, fuck.
Yeah, she's like, "Oh, I got it so wrong all along."
Jason, I mean this guy Jason, he's got to be nice at the end.
No, he's fucking easy.
Maybe my moral is actually wrong all along.
Yeah, it's not a very good.
I don't think I don't think that is a moral that anyone should
live by.
Usually when you see a monster, they call them monsters for a
reason.
Yeah.
Why?
Because of how monstrous they are.
Because that's what they're called.
Yeah, you wouldn't call it something else.
No, I do.
You know what?
Sometimes I call like moon.
Yeah, moon, you know, you think it's a
Jamaican thing? Monsey?
It might be a Jamaican thing, yeah.
Oh. See, but you should, I mean like, they, it would be called a, like a, it'd be called a "nicester" if it was a good thing.
Yeah, a goodster.
A goodster.
A youngster if it's a young one.
Yep.
But the, not a monster, it doesn't make any fucking sense.
What about like a fucking friendster?
A fucking Friendster?
What?
The fucking is in there because I was trying to think.
I could see you ordering more vitamins on your computer screen and then being like, "I have to say something right now."
Faggin' Friendster.
What about a Rockstar?
Oh yeah.
Oh!
That is maybe the opposite of a monster.
And you know a lot of Rockstars end up being monsters.
stars. I was going to say the opposite. There's no rock stars
that are monsters. But then I remembered Kiss, which are all
there's a demon in that band. They are. Yeah, they're scary.
And like David Bowie, didn't he like fuck like 10 year olds all
the time or no, no, they were 14.
Yeah, he's not a monster. Wait a second. And David Bowie had a
lightning bolt on his face. Oh my god. He was in space. Oh my
God, wait a second, Leo.
Wait a second.
He was the Goblin King in that labyrinth.
Oh, yeah, a goblin is a monster.
He was bisexual.
Oh my God.
We have him dead to rights fucking call the police right
now.
Yeah, we have to exhume him and put his bones in jail.
I'm going to dump David Bowie's bones.
it's not Linda Art.
David Bowie's your- David Bowie, your bones are going to jail.
That should be what happens if you find out that someone committed a crime and they're
already dead, they should dig up their bones and put them in a jail graveyard.
There should also be no trial, just the accusation should be enough because like, who cares if
someone's bones are in jail, I don't give a fuck.
You know?
Yeah.
Just as soon as somebody's accused of doing something evil if they're dead, just put those
damn bones in jail.
I don't want to see those bones.
Put those bones in jail!
the
Complete brick wall and she worked for Adolf Hitler. Yeah. Yeah
Well, cuz it's problem with a lot of bodyguards is they got to jump in front of a bullet
But like for a lot of bodyguards, right?
They jump the bullet goes right to their right or left or like, you know between their arm and their torso still hits the fucking guy
This bitch was I mean she was always in front of him
There was basically no angle that you could take on Adolf Hitler without using a cylinder without hitting my grandma mom
Her CV looked so narrow in her hand, he just instantly hired her.
Yeah, exactly.
She was very flat from one angle though.
Yeah, that was a really bad angle to bodyguard from.
But there was one part where it was like, you're not getting through her.
Yeah, absolutely.
I'm surprised there weren't more people trying to kill Hitler.
You know that there's that movie, that Tom Cruise movie.
Oh, Valkyrie.
Where like some guy like they put a briefcase kind of near Hitler. It was under his desk, right?
It was a desk bomb. It was it was a they had a conference table basically
yeah, and he like yeah, he blew up all the wrong guys and
Happened like a million more times, right? Yeah, why didn't anybody ever think like, oh, let's just lose a
Guys like all the Jewish people
Yeah, well it was it was like it was like Thanksgiving dinner
It was like Hitler and then a bunch of Jews and that's where he tried to do it didn't work out
It is yeah you'd day I feel like most people don't get tried to be killed that often
Yeah, I mean no one's tried to kill Caleb yet, and I think you know
Has anybody tried to kill any of you guys one guy a lot of people are after him
That's one guy at a convenience store went like this to me is that why I be trying to be killed
He's just did that to me. He did not do not he just looked at me and did that nothing. I
Was that way?
That was like a few years ago. It was okay
I remember one time you telling me you thought it would be funny to look at people and just do that
Came from like a real story.
I mean it's not really a story, he just did it.
By the way, the thing I'm doing is drawing my finger across my throat.
Yeah, as if you were.
Like that universal gesture for "I'm going to kill you."
Yeah.
But no, I didn't do anything. He didn't say anything to me either.
He just did that.
I was like, "Okay."
And I bought the lighter I was buying and left.
One time me and Neil were, the guy threatened to kill us.
And he was like, but not like some homeless guy, he's like walking down the street.
"I'm gonna kill you. I'm gonna fucking kill you, but not here. Two blocks down from here."
And he was like, "Meet me there so I can fucking kill you."
And we were like, "Yeah, man. We're headed that way too.
But here. So we don't walk together. We'll go, we'll take a left at this block,
and then we'll like wrap back around and meet you there."
He was like, "Alright, cool. I'ma meet you there with all my friends and we're gonna fucking kill you."
And then we just like went to like a bar instead.
That's lucky.
I mean, yeah.
A lucky break that he fell for that.
I would have gone.
I mean, he's pretty stupid.
Because like, why? I mean, I should have gone because there's no way that I just like get to that blog.
He's like, OK, middle of downtown Boston, timed it for me and my friends to kill you right here.
But yeah, I should have gone and two blocks away would have been like
it would have been the the corner of
like the CVS on like the corner of Chinatown in Boston.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. So by the like the Duncan.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Leo knows.
He knows all about this shit. I saw a guy.
Oh wait, you've actually been to-
Yeah, I've been to Boston, and I did go to a CVS in Boston.
Oh shit.
Which CVS? Oh, you know what? It was my fucking joke.
It was that CVS actually, I think.
Really? Oh, there you go.
Yeah, because we did, we went to a cafe near there, so I bet it was that CVS.
Yeah, I was the guy threatening Caleb.
Oh, fuck.
I waited for years, like Fry's dog in that Futurama episode.
It was just as sad.
That's why you are in the future right now in space.
The rest of us are in now.
Uh huh.
I do miss Boston style homeless people.
Yeah.
New York style is just, everybody's just tired.
Yeah, it's true.
They're sick.
Yeah, not many inventors in New York.
No.
You don't get, there's no Sebulba.
There's no like, nobody has like,
nobody has like a,
looks kind of normal and then like one day
one day they pull up their leg and they have just like one.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Black leg.
I think disease on their leg.
Yeah, it's cool.
Remember that guy?
I mean, it's a perfect like just I remember all those guys.
They were my best friends.
Yeah, some of them.
I gave fosters home for imaginary friends.
Is I gave a lot of those guys cigarettes many times.
I gave some points to a lot of something that'll kill them.
Great.
Yeah, I would give them hundred dollar bills.
They didn't even you would not give them hundred dollar bills.
I'm getting one time I had to I told the guy with the with the evil leg
I told him I would buy him coffee and I came like I was like I have to go clock in to work
But I'll come back and buy you a coffee dude, and I came back and he was gone. It's like really man you
Couldn't wait what a jerk. Yeah
Some things can't wait man, yeah, he killed himself because he was like my best friend is
He was like I don't like coffee
And I got to get out of this somehow
Yeah
Now the like this yeah, it's just so you know, it's all just guys on beds here. It's not yeah, it's fun. It's not funny
Something funny like yeah, well like that's a post like mattresses
Mattresses is why else does a guy that's the point all over the city
Make us all laugh really hard
Just guys are like beautiful king-sized beds
One of them one of I've talked to this before but one of the guys with the bed a block away from me
There's like a little like underpass and he died, but his bed has been there for like six months.
Nobody is like touching the bed out of reverence for him.
He seems like a pretty good guy and people in the neighborhood would just like come and like talk to him and just sit in his bed with
just talk to him.
It's pretty awesome.
And like read him stories like fairy tales.
And he's fucking this is all like Polish and like Eastern European people here.
And they just have the craziest street culture.
They will just sit, you'll see two old ladies bump into each other and they're ready to actually fight each other.
And then one of them will say a name and they realize they have the same granddaughter or something.
And they'll just become best friends.
Skid Row should just be one long bed with homeless people.
Oh yeah, I agree.
Like the Family and Jolly and the Chocolate Factory.
Yeah.
But Twice is damn lazy.
That's right. Yeah, what would you guys do if you were the mayor of Los Angeles?
How would you deal with the skid row problem?
If I were mayor of Los Angeles, first thing I would do, give myself a star on the Walk of Fame.
That is a good call for a first thing.
Yeah. Yeah.
First thing I would do is I would find a star and I'd spit on it.
It would say, Mayor Patrick.
But you're not famous.
It wouldn't just say the mayor.
What would the icon say?
They have a movie thing or a record based on what the person did on the star?
What symbol would yours have?
You should retroactively cast yourself in Vicky Cristina Barcelona
so that you have the acting credit and then put the star on the Walk of Fame.
Yeah, that's clever.
That's a good idea.
Cut yourself into Javier Bardem's parts in that movie.
That's what I do.
Just find like a guy with a mustache in the background of like an episode of Shameless
and then just put that on the star.
That was me.
Okay, do you guys want to hear my solution to Skid Row problem?
Yeah.
Can I ask a question?
What's the name?
Well, first change the name.
Skid Row.
That's a good idea.
It's called Skid Row.
It's kind of a broken windows thing, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
First thing I'm doing now, and just bear with me here.
First thing I'm doing, the Oscars, they happen weekly.
Yes. Okay. Okay. Second thing I'm doing no celebrities are allowed to come to the Oscars.
Okay. Third thing I'm doing only homeless people at the Oscars. They can live in the Dolby
Theater. They each get a chair and they're the whole audience. Okay. So here's a question
homeless host or Jimmy Kimmel. Kim both. I mean both preferably at the same time. Jimmy
Kimmel how about homeless writers but Jimmy Kimmel has to read what they wrote.
I would like Jimmy Kimmel to be the host but I would also like him to be homeless.
Exactly. He sees his house. Yeah exactly.
My solution would be have you guys ever played Fallout 3?
Yeah. You know that thing Megaton? You know that city?
Oh come on man. What?
I already know where this is going. What do you mean? I don't know. I have no idea where this is
You know how you save the town?
[Laughter]
Yeah, I do that!
Yeah.
You guys know the Death Star?
[Laughter]
Yeah.
You must be amazing to be the mayor of such a star-studded city.
Have you guys ever seen Infinity War?
[Laughter]
You guys ever seen Saving Private Ryan?
I basically want to do that to Skid Row.
skid row. Yeah, there's a guy in skid row named Private Ryan. I have to save him. I have to
save him real bad. You know what might be a good idea is give some like humongous tax
credit to any film that is like filmed in skid row. So then you have all of these like
actors who are doing they're playing like homeless people and they're trying to they'll
do like the method thing so they spend like a month before they start shooting just living
at Skid Row and then they all get like HIV from like dirty needles and then all the actors
die.
Right.
What do you guys think of that?
I don't know about that play.
Yeah.
It doesn't seem like it solves a lot.
Well, the actors die.
We kill all the actors.
Seems like a roundabout way to do that.
You could do that.
Yeah, but then like you don't get in trouble.
You just kill all that.
You know, all the actors are dead.
Now that you're saying we're not gonna get in trouble. Yeah
That changes everything all the actors are dead cuz they they all died there
Okay, I mean you have a better solution
No, I I think I think your solution here is pretty good
If you could be the mayor of one city in the world, what would it Boston?
You don't want to be the mayor boss. No, I don't know too hard many hard decisions
I don't want the city to be mad at me.
Atlantis, yeah?
Yeah, I was thinking Atlantis as well.
But Atlantis, like, just by becoming mayor,
first of all, how are you going to run when you can't even, like, breathe underwater?
That's going to be fucking tough, right?
Well, I can't.
Okay, let's just change it and stuff.
And Leo, I'm guessing you can too, if you want to.
I can breathe in space.
So, I don't think that translates.
I just generally can breathe anywhere, I think.
All right, so what would you guys do in Atlantis?
If you guys became mayor of Atlantis,
are you trying to like, would you,
the big infrastructure thing would be like--
- I'd move Skid Row to Atlantis.
I'd establish a sort of twin cities thing.
- Just drown 5,000 homeless people?
- No, we're just saying, look,
don't worry about the specifics.
Don't worry about how it's gonna work.
We take a giant plane and fly it into the ocean
and it's full of Skid Row homeless people.
And it comes down to Atlantis and then the plane lets him out.
And then it's all good.
Yep. We'll see what happens. It's an experimental policy.
I mean, did you guys ever...
You can't do it. You gotta do this shit before you find out it's a bad idea.
Yeah, exactly. It's called experimenting.
Thank you.
The mayor in my hometown, he just lived in a normal house,
which I always thought he would live in a palace or something.
But he just lived in a normal house and he would mow his lawn and sometimes I would ride
my bike by his lawn and he would scream at me if I touched his grass.
He's a pretty cool guy.
And in my brain, I know this is not his name, but I think his name was Bill de Blasio.
I'm not kidding.
Like anytime I think of the mayor of Wilmington, North Carolina, I'm like, "It's Bill de Blasio."
I don't think it was Bill de Blasio.
I think that's probably not his name.
Maybe his name, maybe one of his policies was building the Blasio in Wilmington.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
It's Bill Sappho.
Oh.
Which is, you know, pretty close, right?
Yeah, it's pretty similar.
Someone was running for mayor in my roommate's town called Nigel Diaper.
And that's real.
Wow. That is real?
Nigel Diaper? Diaper spelled like diaper?
D-I-A-P-E-R.
Wow.
I can't even imagine.
I don't know if I feel stupid for asking.
Does he wear a diaper
all the time?
I don't know. It would be nice though with a giant
pin in it.
Like baby new year.
That would be a good look I think.
For the mayor.
I'd vote for him.
Definitely vote for somebody named Nigel Diaper.
Nigel Diaper is a
Is it you said he was a mayor?
He was running for running for running. Yeah. Absolutely. I mean, yeah, no, it doesn't merit mayor does not matter
Like I'm not doing my research for voting for mayor if I look at the ballot and I see a guy named Nigel diaper
Absolutely. Yeah funniest name is the only thing that you go for when you get into that position
Yeah, that is why I voted for Jill Stein because I thought she was related to Frankenstein
Well, yeah, that's the thing is like mayor like what can a mayor really do besides like like I mean the worst
Thing he could do is like run with his big scissors
I feel like like there's not like a serious like thing that he can make happen in the town
Yeah, or if he's like is like snipping stuff. That's not the ribbon, you know, that would yeah
That would could be problematic if he's maybe going around the city
I guess it makes sense that people think that like the president is controlled by like an
Illuminati style council because that is the way that every town in America is governed.
There's one guy who pretends he's in charge and then there's a bunch of 18 public school
teachers and guys who own Chick-fil-A's who vote on what actually happens in town.
Nobody knows who they are.
In your hometown, did they record all those meetings and play them on the public access
channel?
No.
in Londonderry. Yeah, so you just like, channel like 21, like every night was like some school
board meeting. And it's just like, some kids fucking parents. And like, a guy who owns all of
the Tedeschi's in our town. Do you remember that video of that lady who, it's like a news story,
like a local news story. It's like, this brave woman. Oh, yeah. Attacked the would-be mass shooter
at this public, uh, this like, uh, city council meeting.
And she, it's like this whole buildup where they interview her and they're like,
where'd you get the, have the bravery to do it?
And then they show the clip of her and she like,
tries to tackle the guy and he just like throws her off to the ground.
Immediately.
The noise she makes is just like,
and then it's like, aren't you? Did you screaming? Yeah.
It's like a 15 minute video.
The first five minutes are setting this lady up as a hero.
She immediately just like fucking falls over and the guy the the shooter feels so bad for her that he just lets her leave
Yeah
She comes back and tries it again
And the same thing happens
and then it ends with like the guy like like
He like, uh missed like of all his shots point blank on everybody and then that guy shot him in the head
Oh, my pretty it's a pretty amazing story. Yeah, I never heard of this. Yeah
somehow it should have been national news
where was that
i don't know
uh... arkansas
i don't fully using it should have been national news made me think that it was
on inside it
so that i know i i think is i think like joshua to to me or something okay yeah
and i didn't like see it on my news
channel okay
jimmy and jimmy
No, it's Joe Mama.
Oh my god.
Oh yeah, you might want to stay in space after that one because if you come back down to
earth people are going to be pointing and laughing at you like Ralph.
Oh my god.
Yeah, that's right.
You got fucking kaboomed.
So how have you been Leo?
I've been alright.
It's been a little sunny here.
My parents are on holiday.
It's your half birthday.
That's just not true.
My half birthday is September 24th.
Is that true?
No, I can't.
I don't know how to do that math.
You don't know?
I don't know what my half birthday is.
I'm guessing that's like kind of like, let's see.
Did you make up the number?
It would be October.
It would be somewhere in October.
No, nevermind.
it would be did you guys ever like do the math and figure out when you were conceived?
um no i just have a video no
i have a commemorative plaque
no i mean i was born i was born 13 months after my older brother
so i don't want to what does that mean or that means we're irish twins
But what is 13 months? That's what my mom used to say growing up, was that my brother and I were Irish twins.
13 months isn't how long it takes to have a baby though.
Well that's how long I was in there.
[Laughter]
No, I guess my parents probably had sex somewhere in...
Well, the thing, you look up Irish twins on Google,
you look up Irish twins and it says that it's 12 months, so I missed the Irish twins by a month.
and two days
Unlucky I never even know my mom's a liar. So my mom's a fucking liar
Yeah, what else is no is there a top result when I Google Irish twins? What are Irish twins and is the term offensive?
Yeah, let me Google Irish twins real quick. I think
I looked it up. It was all pictures of babies. Why are you saying Baba voom?
Because maybe maybe it's tailored to my interest more this term was originally used as a derogatory
Stereotype of Irish Catholic culture and therefore is inherently offensive don't care
It's I'm Irish. I don't give a shit
Nope, it's offensive. No Irish are in the world of people you can say anything about no matter what and also the Irish are the
Polish of the
UK world Oh
Can you be mean to the Polish in Europe?
Polish kind of occupy like Mexican status in the UK and that they're immigrants and I
Like yeah, I like to keep the podcast moving by giving a serious answer to the things you
But yeah like the whole like say something funny about the
Really was like the 80s like it was all like because there's that style council song
Is this how you're gonna relate to me as a human being?
Yes. Yeah.
Okay.
I'm gonna tell you about British stuff I know about.
I ate a jammy Dodger yesterday.
Yeah.
Think of that.
Well, there's that Style Council song, the stand-up comedian's instructions, where it's
like, "Tell Irish jokes."
And so I just assume that like, yeah, like the way that like the people in the US have
Polish jokes, like the UK has like Irish jokes.
Is that right, Leo?
I haven't heard.
I haven't heard, I think my grandpa told me an Irish joke.
He also had a truncheon and started calling the neighbor's kid by my name.
So I don't know what like is a good example.
[Laughter]
He kept it, yeah, he kept a truncheon by his bed.
We don't really have like an analog for the Irish here though.
Because like we don't have, there's not like a group of people in the U.S.
that we are like actively like have been at war with on and off kind of.
What are you talking about? Canada?
Well, but that's a different country, you know?
Because Ireland is all the UK and it is all Great Britain.
I guess Hawaii.
You guys know Hawaiian jokes? Those are so funny.
Telling Hawaiian jokes at a party.
Everyone's like, "What are you talking about?"
It's like, "Dude, what the f--?" Everyone just gets mad at you.
Everyone's confused, too. The jokes are just like...
I guess for a little bit.
Yeah, he saw a flower and said, "What's that, a necklace?"
And it's like, "It doesn't...
[laughter]
...doesn't work."
It's just all that.
He saw a coconut, said, "What's that, a damn bra?"
He saw some leaves and said, "That's a dress to me."
These damn Hawaiians, Jesus Christ.
I guess for a little bit, it was dumb blonde jokes.
Oh, dumb blondes are the Irish of America.
That's a really good point.
Yeah, we've been at war with them for years and years and years.
I mean everyone was mad at dumb blondes after that fucking weird guy in the 40s wanted everyone
to be blonde.
Yup.
Yeah.
That's right.
Weirdo.
He was weird.
He was seriously strange.
Absolute freak.
So what did you do to be shot into space Leo?
It must have been really, really bad.
No, it was really good.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I have terminal cancer and this was my wish.
So you were in the hospital for a while?
Yeah.
I was in the hospital for a while.
Yeah, to be sent up to meet E.T.
My uncle knew a guy called E.T.
He didn't know a guy called E.T.
He knew a guy whose nickname at college was E.T. and it's because he had three testicles
and it was E.T. the extra testicle.
Oh, that's actually pretty funny.
That's good, yeah.
demented grandfather who like you have two demented grandfathers yeah well
one of them is dead. The first guy I mentioned is in the ground you can accuse him of
anything and send him to bone jail. The other guy still alive wakes his wife up at
3 a.m. every morning to ask her what a computer is. He claims before he developed
anything he he claims to have known a guy with five testicles. Five? And actually
My other grandpa, going back to the other grandpa, the dead guy, he knew a guy with two dicks.
I don't believe any of your crap. It doesn't matter where you don't know. There's guys with
two dicks. And my grandma, who is alive, defends his honor and says, no, he did. He knew a man
with two penises. The the bi phallic dude. Yeah, that guy was that was a fraud. He's got fucking
I seen the photos got two cops on his car. No, no, that guy was a fraud. Like, there's like,
a fraud? How is he a fraud? He was exposed. But what was he doing that was making it a
fraud? Like it's all photoshop. It was photoshopped? Yeah he was photoshopping two dicks on his
photos. I do think that there are biphallic people and maybe your grandfather did know
a biphallic person. Yeah I mean you're participating in biphallic erasure right now. I don't care.
He said his name, he called him Double Ogan.
It's Diefallia.
Diefallia, got it.
Let me see some photos.
Oh my god!
I saw the same!
Oh no!
See the one that's on the Wikipedia page?
That the one that you just saw?
No, I'm gonna look at this one too though.
You gotta look at that one.
Oh god, what the fuck dude!
None of these!
The Wikipedia page is crazy!
Okay, now there's no, I agree, there's no way that guy was telling the truth.
All these other people have like diarrhea and like big red lumps where there was...
Yeah, this guy has, yeah, he has like an anglerfish lore.
Yeah, there's a guy on like Reddit who had like the Photoshop pictures of like his two
dicks and then he just...
You know who has...
He used that to promote his erotica that he would write.
You know which famous person has um, diphalia?
Who?
The Coen brothers.
Wow.
I never knew that.
(laughing)
- Wow.
- I never knew that.
- I didn't know that either.
- Yeah, I think,
I don't know that I would love that, having two dicks.
- Yeah.
- Cry Fowl-ia.
- It'll be all right.
- Well, that's the thing, that's the thing.
The photos that he would use is like,
it was like two dicks side by side.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Right.
is yeah and I mean you know I I believed it at first but now like looking at it
like real yeah it's uh you know first of all they were too big they were pretty
imagine having diphalia and then like somebody's like we need to take a
picture of this for Wikipedia like you know I have a choice like we don't have
a photo of it yeah I'm gonna believe that this is a real condition unless
But like cuz it so this guy if it was real he would have these fucking huge dicks in his pants all the time
Yeah, no one sees one they go. That's cool
But then they notice the other
Mm-hmm. They're gonna bring it up to you, right? Yeah, cuz like nobody knows that die fallia exists. So they're gonna be like, did you?
What is there like a your dick and then like a poop in your pants that you have right next to it?
Like why do you have yet? No things are you photoshopping this real life in front of me? Yeah
And then I think you have an answer because I'm not going to walk around telling people
like, yeah, I got two cocks.
I have two cocks.
I'm a two cock man.
Yeah.
Call me Mr. Two cocks.
He goes, he goes by the double dick dude.
Well, now if I had a name like that, instead of Mr. Two cocks, then maybe I would tell
people I think double dick dude is one of the lamest names you could pick.
Right.
If you had two dicks.
Yeah.
Triple D. And you know, it's like I'm getting like, I'm looking at all these pictures of
this guy with his two penises. I'm just getting mad. I'm getting
mad because it's like he lied to me. Let me see these. Yeah,
let's take a look. You know what I've been. I've been right
pissed off in a while. Let me double check this. Yeah. Okay.
Yeah. Yeah. This is absurd. I mean this is absurd. You would
need to double check two penises. I don't think so.
Here's what he says frequently asked questions. Both are 100%
Functional number two. I did not absorb a twin
You know, you know what the other thing too is it's it's photoshopped, right?
So it's like that but then he also photoshops his asshole to be like completely like destroyed like go see
And it's like
Like dude, you've already like like it looks like the sarlacc pit like it's like you got like fucking like destroyed asshole
that's like, you know, like hand big, like, like, like he's
getting like, fucking punched in his asshole. And two dicks. It's
like, it's disgusting.
I have something fun here. He wrote a book.
Yeah, the double dick dudes memoir.
Double header, my life with two penises. And I'm on the Amazon
page. And here's the top review of it. One star gross from Jill.
This book was a little too raunchy for my taste and downright disgusting and sickening.
I mean, a two liter in someone's ass?
Right.
It's messed up that he like, and he does, and he does like insertions into his penis and stuff.
Like it's like, here's a review of three stars. He's for real. There has been a torrent of online
chatter dismissing this as a hoax, but I don't see any reason to doubt what he said.
Nah, that's him.
The many photos available on Google Image are pretty convincing IMO, as is the consistency
of his writings.
Well-formed double penises have been described in the medical literature, but usually one
was cut off.
Like other reviewers, I liked best the autobiographical material in the early part of the book.
I could have done without the accounts of his sexual exploits and the FAQs that pad
out the rest of the book.
I think I might have to order this book.
Yeah, let's do like a reading.
it's not like even if it's fake it's not an uninteresting fictional tale. Right
look at look at this one that I just sent. Okay what is this here? It's a photo?
Mm-hmm. This is I'm guessing he wrote this on a whiteboard or a piece of paper
Always remember you are special no matter what they say
Yeah, that's beautiful
There's a twist you guys are expecting to see his ruined holers two penises
When you post it does is that yeah, and then someone responded you're so inspiring and with two dicks it makes you cool and expiring
Very cool
Yeah
I'm just mad that he's a liar
Yeah, me too. This is like it's like when you realize supersize me is all just like, you know, kind of nonsense
Yeah, yeah, exactly like that
That's the biggest disappointment about the guy who made supersize
I agree. I don't keep up with the news much
But I think it's just that he ate he ate only burgers the whole time when he knows damn well
there's salads on that.
McDonald's.
It's still so funny.
He's of Apple.
He tried to do it again with with Chick-fil-a.
Oh, yeah.
No, but nobody's even heard of the fact that he made.
I did watch.
I did watch that movie though.
You did.
Yeah.
How was it?
It's horrible.
It's fucking horrible.
So he that what's the the premise of that is he's trying to outdo Chick-fil-a.
The premise is at first.
He's like he's like he doesn't like just eat chicken every day for a month like the same.
Yeah.
is like, oh, like chicken and like health food at like at restaurants
is like not actually healthy.
And then he makes his own restaurant that like uses that same premise
of like a fake health food, like Panera bread kind of thing.
OK, who the fuck who the fuck is going to Panera like, oh, I'm healthy.
Me, dude, a bread bowl.
People got to be healthier than eating the plastic bowl.
They give me.
Yeah, that's true.
You got me there.
There's a review of, I'm just looking at reviews now,
there's a review of Super Size Me Too Holy Chicken
that starts with, with greetings again from the darkness.
(laughing)
The chicken conspiracy you never knew existed.
- Someone told me, someone, it was Patches,
just told me that it's $10,000
to start a Chick-fil-A franchise.
- Oh, what the fuck are we doing with this thing?
- Dude, that's exactly, I was like--
- It would be so easy.
We open up the Chick-fil-A in Boston.
That's going to be the easiest money that anybody...
Because I've never driven by a Chick-fil-A that didn't have like,
like 13 year olds, like overworked, like breathing onto iPads,
trying to take all the fucking orders that are lying around the block.
Oh, it'd be really easy, especially around here where there isn't one.
People would go nuts for it.
It's true.
Oh, and then we could get like people to like protest it on the first day it opens.
Yes, dude.
Like we could get... Oh, fuck, dude.
Do we have to become like super Christian?
Can you do that? We will.
Can you do it anyway?
Just do it in like and I'm because I'm ready.
Just build a house.
Use it as a house.
I'm ready.
I just want to make a house.
Just do that. Yeah.
But apparently they like they get almost all the money,
which is the kind of the back end of that, you know, like it's $10,000.
But they get all the money actually.
And you just you just you get all the chicken.
But you get all the glory of a chick-fil-a.
It's true. Yeah.
Open get one in the in the middle of the Mojave Desert.
Yeah. It's air conditioned.
You live there. It's nice.
Don't worry about free food and water.
Yeah. You know, and then when they ask her, like, we want our
we want our 90% of the profits, you say, OK, yeah, here's a dollar.
You fucking idiot.
Yeah. Yeah. Thanks for all the free chicken.
Thanks for the free chicken in the building.
And guess what?
It only cost me $10,000 and I have to live in the desert now.
So look who has chicken on their face.
Yeah, you could do it.
You could if you if for example, if somebody if you really want
someone's house, but they won't move you can open one in their
house true.
This in their living room.
They can't do anything about it because you paid the money.
So Chick-fil-a is this kind of eerie thing where they have like
they've like captured what is nice about like old Southern
ladies and they have like brainwashed and trained all their
employees to act like that.
So you'll have like a 17 year old who will be like,
what can I get you today, darling?
And it's like, what the fuck?
It's fucking weird, man.
Like you're just, there's like, you're acting like an old lady.
They're all sitting on rocking chairs.
Yeah.
They knit in between customers.
It's not a good environment.
And if you don't say my pleasure, when someone says thank you, they actually fire
you.
Really?
Yeah.
I know someone who was fired because they I think like five times their manager heard them not say it is
It's so funny that like we're just saying my pleasure
Really weird. You pleasured me. Thank you. Thank you for my pleasure. You just
Here's your food. It's like you get pulled aside cuz you keep saying shit like that. It's like that
Yeah, yeah. Hey, thanks for the chicken. That was mighty pleasurable for me friend. Oh, you pleasured me
You pleasured me hard.
Hey, come on.
Like, you're technically saying it, but you're creeping them out.
Yeah, just getting right up in your manager's face.
"What?
Fucking do something.
Fucking do something."
Yeah, it is funny how off-putting it is.
I was in Atlanta recently, how off-putting it is to me as a guy from Boston to walk around
and people go like, "Hi there."
And I'm just like, "What are you doing?
Look at me, leave me alone.
Even even in like,
like, like my I'll go visit my parents
and like if any of their like neighbors like wave at me, I get so mad.
Because I'm like, what the fuck are you doing?
Like, don't like neighbors are different, though, in the south.
It really is.
So this is random people.
You walk by an old man.
How are you doing?
You walk by an old man on the street who's just looking directly
into the sun and smiling.
And you walk by and we'll be like, beautiful day out.
Yeah, get the fuck out of my face.
Exactly. Yeah. Yeah. Like, what are you doing? Yeah. Like, I, we, there was like a, a guy,
like a security guard who was standing outside a bank or something. And he was like,
like, Hey guys, like, how are you doing? I was like, I'm not going into the bank. Don't talk to
me. I, I would say Boston is the least personable city in that way. New York, there's a lot more
people who would just talk to you on the street. That's my, that's what I always explain is as the,
the
lot of really mean stuff to you.
Yeah, they'll kill you, dude.
It's awesome.
I love the city.
Do it's the best.
Where do you live?
Now?
What city?
I live in East Anglia, a city called Norwich, small to midsize.
You know, we got some where you live in Norwich.
There's a puppet theater.
I was a theater.
I was just about to ask you what to do.
And I'm just going to ask if there was a puppet theater.
I'm telling you, you live in the Alan Partridge city.
I do, I live in the Alan Partridge thing.
Ask a British guy what there is to do.
Is there any nightlife in your city?
Yeah, there's a puppet theatre.
Yeah man, come over.
Yeah. You guys should do a tour.
Do you ever go see the statue of him there?
I wasn't aware of that.
Oh yeah, there's an Alan Partridge statue in Norwich.
Where is it? Tell me right now.
Uhhhh, let me see.
He's about to find out that it's not real.
not real and then it's a joke there is a there's a statue of Alan Partridge in
Norwich okay cuz I'm get ready countdown in your head to find out that it doesn't
exist no I'm looking at a fucking statue right now oh wait the statue I'm looking
on the onion.com right now no no no no it's on it's on BBC but it says the
The statue of Alan will be outside of the Forum in Norwich until Sunday.
So...
So it was a traveling...
What Sunday?
Sunday like...
Sunday...
The week of September 24th, 2020.
There you go.
Okay.
Excellent.
So they got a kid...
That's even better than it was Sundays.
I thought they just kept it up!
That it was real but they took it down to prove Patrick wrong.
*laughter*
yeah
I mean, you know, the troubles are still happening
*laughter*
I can't believe my countdown worked
It did
We didn't quite get to
Yeah, I'll go check that statue out, thanks
You'll have to find what kind of
Indiana Jones giant werewolf
Was it an ice sculpture maybe?
No, no, it was a bronze statue
It was a bronze statue
The statue will be on display until Sunday when it melts
*laughter*
Oh fuck.
Man, I- I- I'd straight up just believe that that would stay there.
*laughter*
Like, I like heard about it and I was like, "Oh, that's gonna be there forever!"
Is Steve Coogan from, uh...
No, but at- no, Alan Partridge takes place there.
Oh, okay.
Or, yeah, he like moves there. I forget the fucking story.
The joke is that it's not a very sort of showbiz city.
It's very small and there's not much to do.
So it's funny that he's like a local celebrity there.
I decided just like Leo.
Yeah. Yeah. Do you get high five?
I'm trying to put it on the map, man.
I hope people come visit, huh?
We should come visit Norwich.
I would love to.
I've never left this country and I don't have much interest in the UK.
I destroy it.
Oh, come on. Don't do that.
Yeah, no. Yeah, I'd probably I would actually love to visit Norwich
like the rest of the UK you gotta blow it up with a bomb. Yeah.
Yeah. And then we like go to like actually fly out and then like Kostjam
just plays this episode. Yeah. Yeah I would love to come to Norwich.
Norwich. Norwich. Norwich. Norwich. Norwich.
Oh, hey, welcome to Norwich, I'm Leo.
How are you?
Oh, I've got a pot of jelly eels going.
It would be funny if like, like kind of like shallow Hal style,
like Leo thought that he was like this like, this like nice young British guy,
like talked like he, like he does talk, but we all saw him as like Hagrid.
[Laughter]
I'd enjoy it.
Yeah.
Yeah, I've just got like a force field of like people getting out of my way in the street
and I'm like, "Oh, that's unusual."
Yeah.
Stink.
You stink and you're a huge ogre, man.
I feel like you must see at least one Hagrid a day.
There has to be real life Hagrid's in that part of the country, right?
There's a couple of Hagrid's.
Yeah?
Yeah, yeah.
Everyone knows Hagrid's.
People being coaxed.
Yeah.
Do you guys...
A couple of haggers, a couple of dobbies.
Like Chavs are your rednecks, right?
Uh, kinda.
I thought they were like Jersey Shore style.
Yeah, Jersey, yeah. They're like the guidos of like the UK.
Rednecks, I don't know, rednecks is like rural.
I don't know what our equivalent of that is.
I guess you guys just don't have a word for your rednecks, huh?
I guess. Maybe we just don't have that type of guy.
the
rednecks would be like serfs or like yeah like peasants that have like they wear like burlap
sacks and have like bowl cuts.
Bowl cuts?
Yeah.
Oh my.
Men who wallow in mud outside the castle.
Yeah.
Yeah that's alright.
They're called they're called the moatmen and that's their they live in the queen's
moat and the queen of whatever town.
No they're happy they know that place.
Yeah.
Oh yeah what what's it is the queen?
I really didn't want this episode just to turn it on like you're like the foreign
kid in school like like like years and it's still like so what is a banger and
and
I'm gonna do banger and mash.
I'm gonna do a banger and mash.
It's not something you order, it's something you do.
Yeah.
Would you like to banger and mash with me?
[Laughter]
C.
Yes.
I would.
Yeah.
When I come to America and I don't, if I'm not visiting any of the major cities, which
one do I go to?
What's the one I should?
What do you consider the major cities?
Oh, you know.
Morocco.
Albuquerque.
[Laughter]
I will say, Bakersfield, California.
be on your list.
Yeah, yeah, 'cause it's just
and not not because it's the best city.
It's probably the third best,
but because it's just something you'll never get in the UK.
It is.
You ever see like a like an English experience.
Yeah, like, you know what?
You know, he's got to go to like like if not Bakersfield.
You have a go on.
Sorry.
It looks like the cover of like Dune.
If you like photoshopped a bunch of like oil derricks all over
it. It's a perfect fucking place.
I think the perfect tour for Leo is like flies all the way like UK to like the Manchester
airport in New Hampshire.
We had this conversation last, one of the last premium episode Pat when you weren't
here we listed all the shitty cities.
All the best cities.
Oh really?
Yeah all the best cities sorry Manchester, Bakersfield, Gary, Indiana.
Yeah see I was going to say somewhere in like fucking Indiana.
Yeah definitely Gary.
I mean, you you went you lived in like Seattle for a little bit
and like in now, Indiana is not close.
I have been to Springfield, Massachusetts.
That was a oh yeah, that's another bad one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that was bad.
Check out definitely Lowell.
If you come back to mass.
Oh, yeah, I know.
Lowell rocks.
I love the great part about Massachusetts is like literally
every part of Massachusetts except Boston can be included in that list.
Yeah, no, I said, dude, not not the not the damn beach.
Not those beautiful beach towns.
Oh, I love it.
I mean, back to it, back to the beaches of Massachusetts.
So gorgeous.
The clouds, the cold.
You are thinking of the beaches in Boston.
Yeah, they're all there.
Have you never heard of?
You've never been.
You've never been to like.
I had a sport.
It's not right.
Dennis Cock, dude.
Have you ever been to Manchester by the sea?
Yeah, it's bad.
No, it's a beautiful town.
Oh, you come to come to.
How about this?
Try pleasure island, North Carolina, an island so gorgeous they decided to call it pleasure.
Okay, do you understand how beautiful something has to be to be like this?
This is like the pleasure island. I think they would call it beauty island if it was beautiful.
Well, they wouldn't call it fucking island by the sea. Okay, that means it sucks.
What about by the sea? It's not Manchester by the sea is really nice and joyous. That's
That's why they said so many upbeat movies.
Yeah.
You ever been to you ever been to Provincetown?
I have been to Provincetown.
You talked about Provincetown before.
Talked about it probably three times in the past couple months.
I didn't spend much time at the beach when I was at Provincetown.
You gotta go to the clubs.
That's right.
I was eating a fucking $18 hamburger.
When was the last time any of you were at a nightclub?
I've never been to a nightclub.
Actually, I've been to one nightclub.
Unless you count like a concert, I've never been in a nightclub.
I've never went clubbing before.
That's not...
Wow.
I think I accidentally went to one last night.
Accidentally?
Last night?
I, um, you know that dude, Rob, CatholicDad420, shout out Rob.
He was like at this place that's like down the street and I went because it was like
pretty close to my house and then like I got in there and it was like, like playing like,
some there's like a DJ there and there's like a bunch of smoke in there and I was just like
in that scene from triple x like yeah like I was like opening scene from blade I thought it was
just a bar so I was just like oh like whatever like I'll just go to like this place and then
like got there and I was immediately like oh this is not the vibe that I thought this was I thought
this is going to be like a quiet bar whoa yeah you saw fog and you thought it was going to be
be a quiet bar. I didn't see the fog till I like I turned like this like there's
like a long hallway. This must be a tranquil, quaint bar with fog and rolling in. It had a long hallway! It had a long hallway and then you take like a right and then it's like the foggiest, darkest room and I was like oh nah I'm gonna
I'm gonna drink like two beers I'm go home. That was probably pretty smart. Yeah.
Those two beers probably cost you like $30 right?
It was...
Even in nightclub.
$12.
Ooh.
That's not...
That's still not great.
I know and they were Modellos too.
Oh god.
Oh no.
Um, alright Leo.
What is your podcast called?
Uh, it's called I Am Killing You but no one listening to this should check it out.
You should check it out.
It's really good.
I uh...
Don't worry about it.
I enjoy it.
Check out...
He talks to his grandmother.
Oh yeah.
I showed my mom that and she thought it was great. Oh, that's cool. It's a wonderful. It's a good podcast
It's nice. It's fun to listen to you enjoy a good idea would be interviewing your demented grandfather. That would be
We should get all three of us to have an episode with your grandma, yeah
You're not in that you just give us your grandma's phone number
I'll push her into a room with three of you and lock the door for
I didn't say shit about locking the door. What the hell man? Oh my god. I'd like to say you did offer
Thank you Leo for coming on
Love you
Bye.