You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[Laughter]
He's got to turn the shredding off.
You never had that before, Caleb.
That drink is new. You never had that before.
It's an-- I drink this same espresso every single episode.
I wear this hat every day.
You never had that before.
You never had that before. That's new.
- I always have this big dookie chain on.
- You never had that before?
- No, that's all new.
- That's new.
- Never had it before.
- Never had that before.
- I've always had this tattoo.
- You guys, I wrote a song for you.
- Really?
(guitar playing)
- Whoa.
- That's a new song, you never wrote that before.
- That's a new song, I never wrote it.
I wanna sign you to a deal.
Really?
Yeah.
I wanna sign you to a deal.
The deal is, the deal is you never ever play that song again as long as you fucking live.
Why?
And I will kill you, okay?
What?
I will fight this is the worst shit I've ever heard.
You don't like my music?
It's terrible.
There is nothing, there will never be anything iconic about that song.
Yeah, I'd like to sign you to a deal, Patrick.
The deal of matrimony.
and I graciously accept that's right do you guys realize that this is starting to
really hurt my feeling that's an old marriage that happened before mm-hmm we
had that that before oh no you guys are so in love that you're speaking at the
same time mm-hmm whatever explain this stupid fucking bit no what bit yeah the
had that before the Cameron pulled out his inhaler and I said that's new you've
never had that before. It's not much of an explanation. Yeah, I mean, great it's ruined.
We have to chop off the first two minutes of this episode now because Patrick spoiled the
joke. We can edit it out. Today's episode is the carnival episode. Patrick's on a ferris
wheel right now. We're gonna do themes now. Yeah. Yeah, so this week we sent Patrick to
the carnival and he got stuck to a candy apple and now there's a kid dragging him around by
stick of the candy apple to every ride yeah they thought Patrick was it was a
giant stuffed unicorn and they they hung him up by his collar on a they thought
I was a prize yeah caramel yeah caramel and they put I've never heard somebody
combined to never heard so shut the fuck up dude somebody combined the chief
associations like that I'm gonna carry it again have you say it again caramel
that's weird that's like combining caramel and fucking caramel yeah I don't
yeah I don't know that I've ever heard anyone say it like that before it's fine yeah I
think Caleb's got his brain all weird which one do you say Patrick except for
me I say caramel I say caramel really yeah this is perfect cuz I'm in the
middle yeah yeah but you you've met with that's never been that's never happened
yeah that's a new pronunciation no you didn't have it before said that nobody
- No, they didn't have that before.
- What are you drinking?
- He's drinking brown juice.
- I'm drinking brown juice.
It'll make me feel good.
When brown juice hit me, I feel no pain.
- I drank a coffee before this.
- Oh, that's really cool, dude.
Wow, yeah.
- No, that is for me.
- That is big news.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Caleb, shut up.
- Yeah, oh yeah, I'll shut up, yeah.
- This is my second coffee I've had in the week.
And that's the first two coffees of all time.
That's a good thing for him.
Don't ask any questions that might change his mind.
- I'm just gonna tip it.
What made you switch to coffee instead of Monster Energy?
- Master Energy.
I think I read something about kidney stones.
- Oh, dude, yeah, you're getting fucked, man.
I hope you know that.
You are riddled with all sorts of cancer.
You have kidney stones outside of your kidneys.
- Yeah.
- You have lung stones.
- What people don't tell you about Monster Energy
is that it gives you energy, but it also gives the cancerous cells energy that are growing
inside of you.
It also gives you faster.
It makes them work faster.
Yeah.
They were designed for somebody to drink once in their life.
Everybody was supposed to buy one and then keep it as an emergency.
It's called monster energy because it makes the cells inside you take your body over like
Mr. Hyde.
That's true.
And it turns you to a monster.
It does turn you to Mr. Hyde.
White Ultra turned me to a monster.
I'm the White Ultra beast.
The white Ultra Boost.
I'm the white Ultra Boost.
Yeah.
You're an Ultra Boost.
You're a Yeezy Ultra Boost.
I'm a shoe.
Yeah.
I'm actually just a shoe.
I've just been joking this whole time.
I've just been joking.
I've just been a shoe this whole time, man.
It was not a good move.
What have you guys been doing?
What's going on in the...
I think I'm going to grow my beard out.
In the cam-a-verse and the Patrick sphere.
That's pretty good.
Right?
I just, I think I'm going to grow my beard out.
Okay, one at a time.
All right.
Patrick, go first.
I just, I've been relearning guitar.
Wow.
And I'm going to, yeah, I'm going to grow my beard out and I'm going to get, I'm going
to start drinking coffee now.
I'm making big moves.
Wow, dude.
All right, for me, basically, I've been relearning guitar and I'm going to grow my beard out
and I'm going to be drinking coffee.
No, no, you're not.
And I'm also, you know, also at the carnival.
I'm also, I'm not at the carnival.
- Camera can't say that.
Camera can't say that.
- That's true, I can't say I'm at the carnival.
I've been doing nothing.
I've just been sitting at home and then working.
That's pretty much it.
- Yeah, I've been working at the carnival
as the bearded lady.
- Yeah, you have been the bearded lady, yeah.
- See, the trick is about the bearded lady
is they just get a guy that looks like me.
- Do you think, I mean just the lipstick.
- If you got a binder and you wore it only on your stomach,
you could be the bearded lady.
- Yeah.
- That's true. - That's true.
- You just, yeah.
- You just gotta give yourself an hourglass,
an hourglass figure. - Just do a dress.
You feel like you could be a bearded lady.
- Just a beautiful hourglass figure.
- The thing is, most Eastern European women grow beards
after the age of like 15.
So it's not that crazy to have a bearded lady.
- Yeah, Cameron started growing one when he was six.
- Yeah, 'cause I'm high T. - Oh my God!
- 'Cause I'm high T. - Woo!
Let's fucking go!
- 'Cause yeah, 'cause I'm high T.
- Yeah, high tolerance.
- Yeah, 'cause I'm high tea.
- High tea, high tits.
- High tolerance for having--
- 'Cause you got high tits.
- 'Cause I'm high tea, yeah, 'cause I'm high tea.
- High tolerance for having a pussy.
- That's right.
- No, I'm low, I don't--
- 'Cause you're a girl.
- You're low, now you say you're low tea?
You got that right.
- No, yeah, you have a low tolerance for jerks
making fun of your small penis.
- That's right.
- So which is it?
- Which is it?
You're a girl.
- Whichever one you wanna be.
- Whichever one makes you a girl, man.
- Neither of them, man.
they anything does literally low T he's a guy if he's high T's a girl and that's
how it works sus mm-hmm no no you guys are wrong
yeah cam you're so yeah I'm so wrong yeah I'm so wrong hey Cameron you're a
girl fuck dude something my bad man I'm totally wrong I'm way oh I'm so wrong
about that. Oh my god I'm so wrong. You guys are wrong about that. Oh man I'm telling a fib.
Oh I'm totally telling a fib. You guys looked into a mirror and saw yourself. I'm being naughty right now.
Yeah oh yeah I'm totally lying. You guys would love to be naughty with me because I'm a guy
but it just won't happen. No I don't want to be naughty to you. You look at a guy and you go oh my
god I would do anything to do naughty play in that guy's little briefs. No I look at a guy and I say
I would do anything to be normal with that guy. I look at a guy I say I'd do anything to play naughty
dog games with him. That's right. I want to play last of us 2 with him. I want to play
uncharted dude. I want to be. You'll be playing bum farted with guys dude. No, no, no I don't
do that. Bum farted that doesn't, am I, tell me how that game works Cameron. You put your
- Put your mouth on his butt, and he farts.
- And the bum farted.
- Who wins?
- You.
- The game has to have a winner.
- 'Cause you get sucked down.
- That is a loss for me.
That is a huge loss.
- A big helping of farts.
- It's not a helping, dude.
- A huge loss of cum from your balls, dude.
- It's a serving.
- 'Cause it makes you blast off.
- Farts, there's a serving size of farts.
- What is it?
How many calories are in a fart?
- Probably the same amount as any food that you eat.
(laughing)
That's where the calories go.
You get all the nutrients and the calories come out of fart.
Say you eat like a whole bag of beef jerky, look at the bag of the bag and then the first
fart that you have after you're done eating that, that's how many calories is in that
fart.
The way the body works is it converts the numbers on the bag into the sound of a fart.
It changes a number into a sound.
It's the Hertz, yeah.
It's the calories, it's the Hertz at which your fart comes out.
Do you think people should, like people who are trying to gain weight and they like eat like a
like spoonfuls of olive oil, you think instead they should just sit in front of a friend's ass
and just huff? Yeah. Yeah. Wrestlers? Yeah, wrestlers. I was mostly thinking about wrestlers.
Yeah. Do you know what that is? I think we've talked about that. Checking the oil? Yeah,
checking the oil is an illegal wrestling move where if you're pinned down you stick your finger
in the other wrestler's ass. When you say illegal, what- It's illegal because it's assault. The police will come.
The police will, they will shoot you if you stick your finger into another wrestler's ass. Yeah, they have, they have one-
What if it's a girl wrestler? It's still assault. No, that's fine.
They have one cop that, it's the same cop, he's at every wrestling match and he's just there to make sure that nobody does
checking the oil. He's there because his son is one of the wrestlers. Yeah. He's there
because his son died 20 years ago checking the oil. Uh huh. And he was like sure it never
happened again. His son was the one sticking his finger in another guy's ass. Yeah. And
the ass was so poisoned. He immediately died. He got stuck and he died. It burned his finger
off. He starved to death. It melted his finger like acid. Mm hmm. Yeah. And it spread up
his whole body. His son lost his finger. Yeah. He turned into poop. He turned into poop and
got sucked into the butt. If you climb into your man's ass, are you legally poop?
Yep. That's exactly it. Yeah, if you climb into an ass, you're poop.
somebody somebody asking somebody as Steve Harvey that and he just leaves
no cuz that now I'm wouldn't if you if you enter and then leave your poop but
if you enter and you stay in your you become another person like master of
disguise your pistachio disguise you're becoming another person okay now do the
voice that he does when he's changing into a certain type of person. All right
let's go one two three. If you become if you are a criminal and you're fleeing maybe a
murder charge or a robbery charge and you climb into another man's ass. That's
the plot of child's play. And then he shits you out. That's what happens he
climbs into the doll's ass. You climb into a man's ass and he shits you out. Can you
then argue that you cannot be prosecuted because you were legally a piece of poop.
Yeah, you got to put me in the toilet, officer. Your honor, my client, look at him.
He is a piece of poop. Clear as day. Open and shut case.
The jury's murmuring. The jury stands up in the middle of the case and goes,
we've already made our decision guilty of being a piece of the bathroom you are
this man to the world's biggest toilet
that's right yeah yeah I sentence you - you're still a piece of poop yeah just
just to stay a piece of poop forever on your driver's license it said instead of
like hair like hair bread says hey like instead of hair it says corn yeah sex
poop yes sex poop yeah I remember this kid John when I was my older brother's
friend and he was a piece of he was a real guy he was a real crap he's a real
piece of crap no he was he pulled me aside one day and he was like check out
I took this out, just got my learner's permit,
and I was like nine or 10.
And I was like, "Oh, that's cool."
And he's like, "Yeah, get this."
I asked him under sex to put, "Yes, please."
- Holy crap.
- Dude, I lost my shit, dude.
I started crying.
- He started having sex with him.
I just immediately started crying.
I wasn't laughing.
- I was so scared.
It was scary.
have sex with you. I thought he was about to have sex with me dude. He said yes please.
Yeah imagine saying that to your friend's 10 year old brother. Yeah he was like 15.
Yeah yeah. Hey kid. Sex yes please. Well yeah because in my head when I was 15 I was just
who I am. I was just an adult. Yeah. But there's no I had to have been way younger. Yeah no you
I feel like when you were an adult when you were 15 you were one of those kids who like tried to be an
adult too early like you were one of those kids that was like...
You definitely, because you said that your homepage used to be the...
What was it? The Fed? The National Debt Clock.
Yeah. Yeah, dude. I used to go on... I one time
thought that I had a heart attack when I saw that it went over like 18 trillion.
I like opened it up one day and I was like my heart started beating so fast
that I thought I was gonna have a heart attack.
Yep. You had high blood pressure from the age of like 14.
from the national debt
Yeah
Yeah, you definitely tried to just have conversations with your friends parents
Yeah, I always tried to I tried to call them by their first names. Hey, Michelle. Did you did you read that piece? Yeah
You're right, yeah
I remember talking to my friend's mom about tea for a long time one time.
Yeah. Yeah, I mean I did the same thing but only because...
But my friends had moms. I mean they were all supermodel hot bitches.
Michelle, did you catch that newest edition of Nintendo Power?
[laughter]
Dave, good to see ya. Tell me, did you see the new episode of Spongebob?
You'll never guess what that guy Plankton got up to. He tries to get the secret formula.
Yeah, hey, why don't you come over sometime? We can crack open a few cold
ones. We can crap. We can crap together. I got a tandem toilet. How about this?
Tandem toilet. Does it have two holes or is it one hole and it's really wide?
It's one wide toilet that has two different basins. More of a Code Red or a
Game Fuel kind of thing, huh? Dave? You know what? What's the date on this Game
fuel. What year was this game fueled?
Beautiful. 2006 game fuel.
Notes of battery acid just delectable. Really nice.
Really, really nice. And this is a... This is a 97
crystal Pepsi. Check it out.
It's rare. It's really rare. Yeah, down in my cellar I have a
few bottles of the original surge. Oh that?
Oh, that's nothing. I just... glow in the dark casio.
Megan got it for me.
(laughing)
Really thoughtful of her actually.
You know I already had one but.
Sorry, is this too much to ask?
Do you have purple ketchup?
(laughing)
I'll take green but I prefer purple.
- How are things at the office?
How's the missus?
Yeah, no I've been pretty busy myself.
I've been making big piles of mud
and putting them in the oven.
My mom's been getting very angry at me.
You know how it is with women.
Yeah, it's true. It's basically Stewie.
We were a person.
We just engineered Stewie Griffin.
Yeah, I did the same thing as Caleb, but only because I understood their fucking...
You said classic rock.
Yeah, but only because I actually understood all of them perfectly.
I actually understood them.
I could speak like a 40 year old man.
I just loved the milfy dog walkers that made up my friend's moms.
Yeah.
Yeah. Oh, so ugly.
I just talked to my friend's dad.
That's cool man.
You just did?
I just did right now.
Recently?
Is he at the carnival?
Yeah, he's in here with me.
He's in the...
In here?
What's the party right now?
Hey, shut the fuck up!
Yeah, he's...
Nice.
Why did you tell him to shut up?
I thought he was your friend.
He's saying the n-word.
Oh my god.
Come on dude.
At the carnival?
What kind of friend is that?
You're friends with this guy?
Look I...
as I get off this Ferris wheel we're not friends anymore. I tell you what when that
thing goes back down uh-uh. But you you were hanging out with him when he was saying it before.
Wait, you were on the Ferris wheel with a man? Yes. What are you guys gonna do when you hit the top? Propose.
You're gonna propose to your friend's dad? Mm-hmm. Is he married? His name is Jerry. Is he married?
Jerry Doran? He will be. Soon to be?
Mr. Doran to be? Yep. Wow.
Yeah. What's he look like? His wife, Terry, is not gonna like it.
No. Do you think he'll like it? When guys get married and one of them takes the other name, they should have to add
"Junior".
Just so you know.
I think that's why they originally made gay marriage illegal.
yeah i would do it anyway i think it is
the end of the year you guys have a
you guys have a name which names
when they do hyphens is it
the mix the names you know i just do
you know legal
just you know what we're talking about
the x bullshit yeah when you do yeah
when you're gay and you get married you
have to change your last name to x
yeah yeah yeah you change your last name
i am gay i am gay married
there might be of the thing that middle
name has to be gay. Yeah, Will Found, there's like a, if you go on Facebook and you search
the name, first name, I love men, last name, all day, there's like 50 accounts called that
because it's just one guy who keeps forgetting his password and making new accounts. I love
men all day. Yeah. Isn't that the best name of all time? Yeah, I know, I keep forgetting
my password. I love men all day. That was, I may have said this before, but I used to
play RuneScape with like this guy whose username was I love men's cock and he was
like 13 and then we found out that he died and we had a RuneScape funeral for
I love men's cock. Wow. That's sick. Yeah. So when you say that I was mature for my age
it's because I went through a lot. His ache he was broken he meant I love mensa
cock. Which you know isn't gay because they're geniuses. He was a sapiosexual. Yeah.
homosexual. Bit of a smarty, smarty pants. I'll fuck anyone's brain. Yeah, I'll fuck any brain.
I'll fuck any brain I see. Yeah. That's right. You. Would you fuck a brain? Yeah, why not?
I, we've talked about this, dude. I don't think we have. I don't know. No, we've talked about this.
I would fuck anything like 80 degrees and, and gooey. It doesn't matter. I don't care. You'd
You'd have to heat up the brain.
I feel like the brain would be cold.
The brains are hot, dude.
Why would you think- That's where all your heat comes from.
Patrick's brain is cold.
You touch the top of Patrick's head, it's ice cold.
Patrick's brain is frozen.
Once that shit thaws out, I'm gonna be in Mensa.
Super genius.
Yeah.
Once that shit thaws out, I'm fucking golden, dude.
I'm solving all sorts of theorems and shit.
Yeah?
What's a theorem?
I'm creating my own theorem.
What is your new theorem?
It's the type of liquid.
it you have a theorem that's a type of liquid yeah like a formula yes I know
it's I just have a lisp okay what's the liquid it's my semen it's disgusting
dude I think you have meant to confuse with nambla as I know it has no man in
the name but it's you know yeah and it's a lot of overlap membership overlap yeah
- Yeah, it's one of those things where you can pay
half price for both of them, if you're in both.
- Yeah, it's like if you're going to a museum,
you can get a half price for a bus tour, too.
- Yeah, it's like when you go to Six Flags
and you get the water park for an extra $20.
Nambla's the water park, it's only that much.
- Can I interest you in Nambla today, sir?
- You know what, yeah, just throw it on there.
- Hey guys, if I got a Nambla membership,
would you come hang out with me there?
I'm already the worst guy you can be in Mensa, so I might as well also join Nambla.
Hmm. Yeah.
Put me down for the Nation of Islam too. Let's just, let's run the gamut.
I got a weird new line on my face.
Yeah? Oh, that's the gay line.
Yeah. Yeah.
Oh yeah, they just announced that at the-
They just announced that at E3.
On Nintendo Direct. 'Cause I've been- 'cause I've been laughing too much.
Did it make you gay? With my friends.
Nah, that sounds pretty gay to me.
If you ever have laughed at what another man said, you disgust me.
I'm not laughing.
You're fucking...
No, the only thing that you can do...
Whenever you guys say something and I laugh, I'm just thinking of something else.
Yeah.
I'm thinking of how much I...
I'm thinking of the funniest boobs.
Yeah.
I'm looking at a Farside cartoon.
Well, a man drew those, you know.
I have it taped on my...
We have no proof of that.
Gary Larson has never...
There's no photos of him.
no recorded interviews of him. So you were searching for photos of a man?
Well cuz I wanted to check to make sure I wasn't laughing at something a man said.
And also if we're getting specific these are cows and chickens that I'm laughing
at. Sometimes bugs. Male. Sometimes an alien. Male chickens, male bugs. That is not for us to
decide. A cow and a chicken are... A cow and a chicken could never be brothers.
They could never have it.
They could never be brothers.
That's a really good point.
Yeah.
Well, they could.
Try it again.
There could never be a demon that's trying to fuck them.
I think there could be.
I think there really could be.
I don't know.
Yeah, I think so.
Yeah?
I don't know.
I don't know about that.
You would think about something trying to fuck a cow and chicken.
Yeah.
You would think about a demon.
And let me tell you, the something is a male.
I would think about it so I could stop it.
You would try and get in up close and personal.
You'd stop and it could happen to you.
It sucks when you're trying to think about something so you can stop it and you accidentally
manifest it.
It's such a bummer, dude.
That's why, yeah, I'm downloading child porn on my computer so I can get inside the head
of somebody who would download child porn on their computer.
That was Pete Townshend's defense.
Oh yeah, I forgot.
That's literally, yeah, he was like, well, I'm making a documentary.
I'm making a documentary.
I'm making a documentary about this.
You can't take my computer.
about a little boys way
well i'm trying to download it also nobody else can have it
but i'm gonna tell loaded i'm gonna delete it
you are poor old it down where you are on my honor printed out and right bad on it
because i think i was gonna
yeah i was gonna put a good giant circle gyrates are cool with a lot of people
who don't know who does
in photoshop and i had to have the photos to do it right now
yeah try that there is a
there was like this British like TV presenter I think his name is Richard
Mabley and he's like they're talking about like cybersecurity and like the
dark web and shit and he's like why don't we put a virus on all of the child
pornography websites so that as soon as somebody accesses it it deletes it right
away. That's ingenious. That's really genius. It's the best idea I've ever heard.
Yeah, Snapchat for child porn. That's a great idea. They wouldn't do it because it makes too much
sense. Exactly. The government is pro-child porn. It's funny that like probably most child porn sites are just run by the FBI.
Yeah. So there's like a whole section of the FBI where their entire thing is just
like uploading kiddie porn and curating it. Yeah, like what yeah like guys who sit there
and are like, "Which ones are they gonna download?" You know they take pride in their work too.
Yeah. They sit there and they're like, "I did such an amazing job with this
triptych putting these three photos together yeah oh my god
they're listening to this they are listening to this yeah because of you
and they're and they're happy because somebody finally recognized their hard
work yeah they're fishing for compliments yeah they're just waiting
yeah they turn the comments on all those websites it's just waiting for somebody
And there's another even more secret division of the FBI
whose entire job is to boost the morale of that office
by going and commenting nice things.
So nobody actually downloads Child Board.
It's just the FBI downloading it and then uploading it
over and over and over again.
And we're paying.
And that's why the national debt is now at $26 trillion.
- It costs a thousand dollars every time.
If China gives us a call a couple, today,
if they give us a call today and we go,
"Hello, is this China?"
And they go, "Yeah!"
Or they say whatever,
and then they ask for their money back.
(laughing)
And then they ask for their money back.
- What did they say?
On the phone?
- We're just not gonna get it.
Probably something like, "Hello, this is China."
(laughing)
"This is China and we would love to have that money back."
- It doesn't sound like the same thing you just said.
- Wow.
What?
"Hey, this is China."
- Was that Waluigi?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Waluigi's Chinese, people don't realize that.
- "Hello, this is a China."
(laughing)
- Yeah, so Waluigi calls,
he's the ambassador to China's money,
and he calls us, and he's like, "We need the money back."
"Why, we need the money back."
I don't know what Waluigi sounds like,
he doesn't talk much.
- Yeah, he sounds like that.
- We, all of a sudden, we're having to sell
every TV in America, every tank in America,
We have to shut down the FBI child pornography program.
The whole thing just fucking falls apart.
- Yeah.
- Without the child pornography program,
the way that it cycles around, it's spinning.
That's the turbine that powers the internet.
So if that goes down, there's no more websites.
- That's true.
- All the websites go away.
- That's a really good point.
- It's like a hamster wheel.
- You don't get "we fucked" anymore?
- Exactly.
- "We fucked" done for.
The bastion of American free speech.
- Yeah.
- Right?
- And you know what? - The last place.
And you know what? The National Debt Clock, you can't look at it anymore.
Nope. Yeah, because China's Great Giant Firewall is going to fucking block the National Debt
Clock.
That's so true. The Great Firewall of China. Has anyone thought of this yet? Has anyone
thought, "Hey, Mark Zuckerberg, I have an idea for something you could use to totally
bash the Chinese against how they hate your website." You could call them the Great Firewall
of China.
You could call Bebo that.
You could call them a lot of stuff, but you can definitely call them Great Firewall too.
- Let's hold off on that other stuff
you've been calling them, Mark Zuckerberg.
- Yeah, Mark, cool it on the other,
cool it on those other choice words.
Let's just stick with, it's the Great Firewall.
- Look, I know you have like a word document
and you keep thinking of new ones
and you keep putting them in, but.
- Mm-hmm, but no.
- No, we're not gonna say any of those.
- We're not gonna say that.
- No.
- We're saying Great Firewall of China.
- The Great Firewall of China, or you could say,
you know, something else, but.
- Yeah, but we're not gonna say that.
- Well, Patrick is.
No.
No, go ahead.
I saw you had something.
You raised your hand.
Okay.
I did raise my hand.
What were you going to say?
Listen here, Jack.
But I'm raising my hand because I'm having so much fun on the Ferris wheel.
I'm raising both hands.
Yeah, you at the top of the Ferris wheel.
I'm having fun.
Keep your fucking hands in.
You put class in the circus?
Fuck you.
What?
That's it.
I was doing like you're raising your hands.
Somebody's calling.
A teacher's calling.
Okay, the teacher at the teacher who rides the roller coaster and calls on everyone when they go down the hill
Hey you there in the front who's having fun? Yeah
Try to ruin the
Teacher ruins everything
Everything. Oh my basically Adam Conover is a teacher. Yeah, Adam bend over more like it
Yeah, see that asshole man. Let me see over
Adam yeah more like a cum rover cuz he sniffs out come and
I mean yeah, and he does a red rover. We're just playing a game with him now. Yep. Yep. Yep red rover red rover Adam
Con over yeah more like
More like up and Adam sleepover cuz he's always freaking sleeping over his clock time his alarm go
Okay, it's always first to wake up at the sleepover and he makes the best omelet. Oh my god Adam ruins China
Adam that would be Adam ruins everything but pretty messed up episode. Yeah, Adam ruins China
But it's not him even talking he goes
He just ruins it yeah
Everybody yeah, sorry. Yeah
China is ruined for me now. That's right
China hood ruined
Okay, yeah, all right, I like that I'm liking this now. Mm-hmm. Yeah
I'm starting to get sleepy now. I had a yeah, no coffee does not keep me awake as much as
many megabytes of caffeine
Yeah
Multiple cups of coffee. I had an acai bowl, which is just a very smoothie. Yeah, that's just a that's just a
- Have you ever seen, have you ever seen the,
when I worked at Life Alive,
they had like, I had to pour the bowls
and it comes out and that shit looks like poop.
It really does.
- I mean, it really do's.
- It really do's look like poop.
When you put it in a little ice cream maker or whatever.
- I don't really like them.
- It comes out, it's all thick and brown.
- It's just an expensive smoothie
where they put peanut butter on top.
Fuck you, man.
- Oh yeah, dude, $10.
That was the price of the smoothie.
- I just had one, the one I just got.
- Great, great.
- 10.95, talking to my woman. - I also, I can't believe
that they make me pronounce that word, acai.
- Acai. - That makes me wanna die
to have to say that.
- But then, it like, it's more, it's annoying.
- Let me call it a...
- An acai bowl.
- A drippy bucket.
Let me call it something like that.
- Something American.
- I'd hear that every day from like European tourists.
- Hey, can I have a acai bowl?
- Can I have a acai bowl?
- Acai bowl?
you want to get a please have a guy bowl yeah you want to guys balls yeah I can't
understand your accent all right here you go do you have do you have a bone a
cable hello I am from Germany hello I am from Jim Henson's house yeah oh that was
the worst the day that the Muppets came in oh it's so annoying dude there's
There's complete divas dude. Yeah, no cuz each of them has like a different relationship with one of the co-workers
Yeah, and Kermit this kid this guy loves nose beers. You know, yeah
Oh, yeah fucking Kermit loves that shit. Did you have a nose you think you think it's gonzo? No gonzo's on?
Gonzo
Yeah, the only drugs are the are the barbiturates or the or the whatever they're called to keep him sane
Barbiturates? That's what killed Marilyn Monroe. Yeah it's what they gave women to shut up in the 50s.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah. I don't want a gumball. Shut up bitch. I'm thinking of Benzo's.
I'm thinking of Benzo's. Benzo's for Gonzo's. No Benzo is the guy who had beef with Eminem.
Yeah yeah and then Enzo is his cousin. No that's Benzino. Enzo is his cousin who was in Assassin's Creed.
Yeah, yeah, and and Crenzo is an evil chef that I made up in my mind
He's an evil character. I just let's hear about him. Let's do that for you. Yeah
He sounds like that okay, what is what is he from Italy?
No, he's from Manhattan the most evil chef I can think of is Mario Batali for me. It's Anthony Bourdain
He's evil for me
It would have to be Hannibal Lecter
Yeah, okay. Yep animal Burris. Yeah
Burrits, yeah landlord style. Yeah. Have you heard what he what he flicks onto his bread for his sandwiches?
Have you heard about the flavor? Have you heard about the flavor? Have you heard about his roommate with those lizards? That guy's evil
Mm-hmm. That's right. Yeah
And also he said that thing about Bill Cod. He's a reason Bill Cosby's in jail. Yeah
Also, I heard that he's that he's some kind of Lord
Mm-hmm.
Of a land.
He might be the lord.
I heard he's the lord.
Yeah, the only landlord I respect is Jesus Christ.
That's right.
He's the lord over this land.
Jesus would be landlords.
Well, maybe not.
Do you think, Jesus probably didn't know America existed.
Yeah.
No, he knew.
That's the truth.
He knew.
His whole world was Israel.
Yeah, man, Jesus didn't know America existed.
There you go.
Take it down.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, that's right.
Jesus, oh, you think God blesses America?
God didn't even know that America existed.
That's right, God blesses America-ka-ka, right?
That's right.
Uh-huh.
America-ka-ka?
That's right.
How about, huh?
Yeah.
And, yeah, One Nation under God?
More like I don't think so.
And we gotta do something.
My mic arm just fell off.
You could do like, you could do like, "Dodd blesses America," like the Department of Defense.
That's true.
That might get people going in the streets.
Yeah, let's think let's get some let's get some fucking Banksy style. Let's get some Banksy style. Okay, it's
We're doing we're becoming activists now. Okay, so Homer Simpson basically a dollar bill
Homer Simpson is is sitting on his couch eating a donut
Okay
What if?
Drawing that what if most and how about is hand is filling a beer mug with money. What about officer?
Simpson was arresting
Disney Mouse.
Alright, so here's, so, to, so Mickey Mouse, right, he's just got his whole, like, you can
see he's got, holding one glove, and he's got his fist up Homer Simpson's ass, and he's
using him like a puppet.
Okay.
And that is Banksy protesting the merger of Fox and Disney.
Wow.
What about Monkey Mouse sitting on a cloud, and he's getting fucked?
We should do, we should do like, I feel like we should do political politics.
cartoons he's labeled America and the person fucking him is labeled Hillary
what about a ninja what about a ninja his shirt says China and he's throwing a
Star of David shuriken at the National Debt Clock all right that's that I could
see that as a Ben Garrison cartoon. That's a pretty good Ben Garrison one.
What about a guy and he's named America, that's his name, it's Amerigo Vespucci and he's taking
a shit and he's crying while he's shooting and the shit says the Democrats.
Yeah.
Okay, what about, what about, what about it's an animated gif and it's AOC rolling around
inside of a stinky wet diaper and the diaper is labeled America and AOC is labeled Alexandria
Osocio-sor-sorkin.
socio source
sorkin
what if about
it's a real picture of an alligator
and it just says Barack Obama
laughing
what about it's alien vs predator
and it says Joe Biden vs Joe Biden
Joe Biden vs this
yeah vs this alien
vs xenomorph
what if it's Barack Obama and
Joe Biden they're kissing and it says
in love with predator mm-hmm alien whoever whoever wins we are America uh-huh
what if it's like what okay so picture this woman with blue hair right picture
that cannot picture that woman over blue hair and it and it's Bulma from Dragon
Ball Z and she and she's and she is 27 and she's 27 years old now and she and
it's her having sex with me.
Okay, my boner just came up and it closed my mouth, which was a gape.
It pushed my jaw up and closed my mouth.
What about...
Beerus from Dragon Ball Z
and he's voting.
Okay, okay, okay, hold on, hold on.
Voting? We need to get more voting in this.
Yeah, voting. And he's voting and he says, and it says,
"You'd have to..."
Let's do something to make people on your age vote.
Okay this is the vote.
Okay an XKCD.
No let me finish.
Beerus is voting and it says if you're not, if you're, if you're Beerus you better vote.
That's right.
What about an XKCD and it's that little fucking stick guy.
Yeah.
Fucking dumbass and it says V, he's doing an equation.
Then it says V plus O plus T plus E. Yeah okay.
Equals.
And it says it equals, it equals Linux.
Alright so you know all the kids, all children, all the people our age are obsessed with Sherlock
Holmes.
You think we're children?
Yep, we're children.
You think so?
How old are you Pat?
Are you 22 years old?
No.
You're 23.
I have the mind of a child.
Patrick is 2 and 3.
Yep, 2 and 3.
So people our age, well because people who want us to vote are calling us kids.
So they're like, "Oh, we gotta get these kids to vote."
So the kids nowadays are obsessed with Sherlock Holmes.
So it's Sherlock Holmes and he's searching for democracy.
And he finds a clue.
And that clue is to vote.
Yeah, and instead of Watson, it's Wopson.
And he's got a huge pussy.
What about a stone-toss comic?
pussy this big. And it's a stone toss comic. It's a line of people that are being forced to vote
for Joe Biden at gunpoint and then there's this little smug muppet looking guy who looks at the
camera and says, "I'd say this is more like a bullet box than a ballot box." Oh that's pretty
good actually. And then in the bottom right it says stone toss. That's pretty good. And yeah,
we could get people to vote that way. What about a Ben Garrison cartoon and it's like 9/11,
Right? Yeah. And it's 9/11. It says, "My dad survived 9/11." Yeah, he fell off the guard tower.
Okay. He survived. Yeah. I mean, technically, we all survived 9/11. I didn't. I didn't. I died.
You didn't? Yeah, my brain didn't, though. I'm different. Yeah. You know who didn't survive 9/11?
Lady Liberty. Two-- oh, yeah. Okay. What about a cartoon and it's a clown jumping out of one of
of the towers into a tiny little pool okay what if that cloud says Congress on
it yes what if it's super Mario and the towers and the towers say voting because
Congress and the pool the pool pool is that gay shit and it's a picture of Lisa
Simpson on the yeah and she's playing jack what about what about a cartoon and
it's like yeah it's been Garrison cartoon and it's Lisa Simpson playing it the
saxophone and then it's like Lindy West or somebody saying like this is cultural
appropriation Lisa yeah yeah yeah and then a real-life picture of Ben Garrison
with his hands up saying what the hell is going on in my great nation what about a
you know of a poo and there's a speech bubble and he says I'm voting for Donald
Trump what about a picture a picture of a poo and then it says equals and then a
a piece of poop and that's the Ben Garrison cartoon.
It's like a poo equals a poo.
- Yeah.
- You know, I think that might get the base riled up.
Which side are we on?
- I think we're in the middle.
- We're just making cartoons.
You don't have to have a side to make a cartoon.
- Listen buddy, I don't give a fuck
about all this politics shit.
I love cartoons.
- I love cartoons.
I love any political cartoon.
- Listen, I love anything dude.
Fucking Garfield, Dilbert, it's all good to me.
i'll give a fuck
okay what about a garfield cartoon where he's in in the first panel
he's sitting with
on john's lap
okay then this next panel john sees liz
third panel garfield is stuck to the ceiling and he says
i can't believe this
yeah okay monday monday yeah
yet seems like somebody
just saw a sexy woman
Yeah.
Wow.
That's what he says.
Does Garfield, does he get horny for human women?
He gets horny for Arlene.
Yeah.
Fuck, dude.
Arlene's a human.
Arlene is just a really fucked up looking human.
Yeah, she's just, uh, she's just Greek.
Just barely.
Speaking of, dude, I need to shave.
I'm wearing this hat because I haven't shaved my head in a couple days and I'm starting
to look like I sell falafel.
Yeah?
Yeah, it's getting bad.
You thought I was Greek for a little bit.
I remember you telling me that.
You just have dark features and you look evil.
That's true.
Yeah.
You look like I need to stop you from doing something wrong.
I look like my economy's bad.
Yeah.
I mean, you do look poor.
So I just assumed you were Greek.
What do I look like?
Don't tell him I'm Greek.
I was always playing a bouzouki too.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's true.
You look like if you inverted the colors on Violet Beauregard, that's your head.
From Charlie Chocolate Factory, the one who blows up like a big blueberry, you're a red
one of that.
That's so crazy that that created like a whole fetish.
Like, seeing that woman inflate.
There's like inflations you can do.
No, not me!
Not me!
- I don't like the fucking story, big guy.
- No.
- I feel like there was definitely,
I feel like there were,
I feel like cartoons probably started that.
I feel like there were a bunch of cartoons
where like the wily coyote gets blown up
and then blown up into a balloon
and then the roadrunner licks his feet
and like starts, you know, licking on it.
- That's cartoons, once they start becoming human.
- Once they actually blew that girl up.
- Yeah.
- Then it was a game changer for.
- They did that for real on set.
They had like, they had a bunch of.
- They had a bunch of girls just in case they fucked up.
- They kept exploding, yeah.
- Yeah.
It was the first girl to not explode.
Yeah, they had to figure out the PSI rating of a girl.
They filmed that scene first and they were just like,
we're gonna take five actresses for this audition
and just whichever one doesn't blow up,
we'll use them for the rest of the movie.
This is before like the Triangle Fire,
there was no real labor laws in America.
What's the Triangle Fire?
The Triangle Shirtwaist Factory Fire.
Nevermind, man.
I know about that one.
I thought you were talking about John Landis' helicopter.
I thought that would be--
that's the helicopter incident in 1982.
yeah.
did you guys hear about the...
is there footage of it?
is there any other footage?
there's definitely footage of it.
i think they used the actual footage in the movie.
let me look that up.
did you guys hear about the polish triangle fire?
we're back!
yeah!
what happened at the polish triangle fire?
a polish guy was trying to boil water for his freaking pasta.
and he set the water on fire.
Is a Polish guy filling up his car with water at a gas station?
Man, the Polish Triangle is definitely the scariest thing we've ever thought of.
That is horrifying dude.
Yeah.
I forgot about the Polish Triangle.
Also, it's a real place.
So they say.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's a real place. Yeah. Yeah. So they say
Yeah, they want you to think it's real. Yeah, don't go visit. Yeah, baby flights to the Polish Triangle are so cheap
They've reduced they've reduced costs on the plane by putting a
Glass at the bottom and you can see the other Polish planes that flew over the Polish Triangle an evil
Gypsy travel agent sold me tickets to the Polish Triangle
(laughing)
- It's also so funny that it's in Boston,
where I feel like I never met a Polish person.
- Yeah.
- Well, they're all in the triangle.
- We have no camera.
- It's the Polish triangle,
'cause they don't know how to get out of there.
They can't figure it out, yeah.
- Yeah, Marty Walsh put up a force field
around the Polish triangle to keep them in.
- Yeah, well, all you have to do is just--
- We're keeping us out and them in.
- All you have to do is just draw a line on the ground
a Polish person can't cross it.
With salt.
Yeah.
It's running water. As long as they can't cross it,
we're running water.
Oh, God. Polish people.
What are we gonna do with them?
What?
Alright, let's brainstorm. What are we gonna do
with Polish people?
Daycare.
Yeah.
Oh, that
killed Vic Morrow. What? The helicopter crash. Well it's not, we understood that part
although you did just say plane but besides that who's Vic Morrow? Vic
Morrow was the guy from... I feel like Pat just says Nancy. I'm gonna know exactly who this is for
sure. He's from Bonanza. And he's like oh he did set design on Babe 2 Pig in the
city Patrick watched Bonanza every day after school growing up I did he was on
two episodes of Bonanza he was on two episodes is that is that is big name no
why did you why did you say Oh Vic Morrow died like what I heard that name before
I just have to figure out who he is and then you watched Bonanza watched the
Western from 1959?
That's what I'm saying dude!
I watched Bonanza sometimes.
Patrick would absolutely watch Bonanza everyday after school.
What channel did Bonanza come on?
It was on TV Land.
Oh, you were a TV Land freak.
Sometimes. It was the channel
right after Comedy Central.
So I would go.
Comedy Central was 55, Cartoon Network 57,
Spike TV 58.
Pretty much that was my...
Oh wait, no that was the...
I mean that I think yeah 51 was Comedy Central and then 52 was TV Land.
That's so interesting.
It's different wherever you live.
And then 50 yeah oh yeah that's true.
Fucking come on man.
I had Time Warner Cable it doesn't even exist anymore.
Yeah Time Warner is now Spectrum.
Oh really?
I think Cartoon Network was 117 on my TV.
Whoa once you get into the hundreds I think you're rich.
It's fucked up yeah.
Yeah once I went to a kid's house and they were like yeah go to 125.
I'm like, okay, get me a Capri Sun, Richie Rich.
- What do we have, we had Verizon.
Verizon, whatever. - You know what,
I'm realizing I've only heard of Vic Morrow
because of this incident.
- Fucking.
(laughing)
- Oh, did you guys hear?
Stephen Paddock just shot up a hotel.
You know, Stephen Paddock.
- Oh my god, Muhammad Atta died in 9/11.
Where do I know him from?
- Oh my god, that was Muhammad Atta.
- Where do I know that name from?
- Where do I know him?
He was in something.
He definitely was.
- Oh yeah, he was at my house before.
(laughing)
- Oh, I taught him how to fly a plane.
That's who it was in Florida.
- Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, I know that guy.
- That's what it was.
Okay, now I remember.
(laughing)
God fucking damn it, bro.
That is the funniest thing of all time.
Pat, you are one goofy goober, brother.
- I'm telling you, once my brain thaws out.
- Yeah.
- You're gonna be, what are you gonna do?
- You gotta drink a little more hot coffee.
That's the thing, he's been drinking,
for his energy, he's been drinking cold stuff.
- Yeah.
- But now he's gotta drink hot coffee, hot energy.
- Okay, all right.
What's your next hot drink?
- My next hot drink, ooh.
- Don't say ooh.
- Ooh.
- Don't enjoy this.
- Ooh-la-nti.
Okay. Yeah, oolong something. I bet you will enjoy that.
You say oolong pee man.
Yeah, you want an oolong pee man.
Yeah.
Yeah, for me personally, I go, "Ew, oolong pee man? Ew, no thank you."
I go, "Ooooh."
And you go, "Ooooh."
"Ooooh."
That's what Patrick does.
That is a damn fine scooby-doo, mister.
It's the only impression I can do.
do
Elvis Presley go. Johnny Bravo just the same voice. Johnny Javo. Baby. Baby there we go.
impression yeah Vic Morrow he's like he sounds like this I love helicopters I
have so I finally I get to ride in a helicopter for the first time ever I've
got another I've got another impression ready Randy Rhodes yeah who's that
rainbow road Mario rainbow road Randy rainbow let's go can't do don't hold
back don't hold back don't hold back give him what for yep come on do it do it
Randy rainbow Gandhi Wow okay saying Gandhi was a dog huh okay yeah I don't
- I don't think I can support that one.
- No, I don't think...
- No, I'm saying Gandhi liked snacks.
- I don't think I'm gonna let you submit
my SNL packet with me this year.
- No.
- No, you got too much heat on you
for that calling Gandhi a dog thing.
- It's too much.
- I'm gonna have to wait a few, wait a couple.
- Yeah.
- Trying to think based on, talk for a second,
just say like five words.
- Five words.
- Give me an impression of the computer.
- I'm trying to think of what, in my head,
what voice do you almost have that we could tweak one thing
and get you to an impression?
- Yeah, Brad Pitt, probably, and George Clooney.
- Try Gilbert Gottfried.
- It fucking stinks in here!
Oh, Christ!
- Okay, see Gilbert Gottfried is perfectly,
perfectly like, he has like the,
he has like probably when Gilbert Gottfried
isn't doing his fake voice, he sounds exactly like that.
- Yeah, yeah.
So that's like, so we need to find your Gilbert Godfrey.
- Yeah.
- You know?
- Yeah, a guy who sounds like me.
- Which one are you just one degree away from?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, it's probably a woman.
- It's probably CK.
- It's probably, it's probably Scooby-Doo.
- Probably Susan CK.
- It's probably Scooby-Doo.
- Susan BK.
- Susie BK.
- Susan Burger King.
- Mm-hmm, yeah.
- She was the first woman who said,
I've had it up to here with McDonald's.
- She was the first woman who ever ate Burger King
they changed her name against her will yeah I'll take a whopper take a uh uh whopper junior is
what they have now they got fucking whopper juniors got a fucking diarrhea shit whopper
and I ate it it's okay this whopper's a cunt this whopper is a whopper stupid bitch cunt
I hate my lousy I gotta I gotta figure out my I used to have a louis ck impression
No you didn't. I did. You did when you were playing Louis C.K. on multiple phone calls.
Yeah. You did have a great impression then. You fooled a lot of women.
No. Yeah. You did that all. You did all that. No. You did that. That wasn't me. Just admit it.
Dude it would be your biggest crime. I'm a Patrick Hotep. I believe that Patrick did all of Louis C.K.'s
crimes and took credit for them. That was not me. He just did a pitch perfect. I probably could maybe
get Griffin McElroy in trouble for something you know if I get like a cheesy flip phone
and then make some phone calls. 3, 2, 1.
Yeah what could I get what could I conceivably get him in trouble for?
Who could I call? Yeah I'm thinking I'm gonna kill all the polish.
Uh yeah so basically I hate the polish people uh
hate the polarinos. That's that's acceptable.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
That's acceptable, but only in like a three mile radius in Chicago.
True.
Yeah.
But what could believably, because like with Louis, what he did, it was like, yeah, I guess
that makes sense with his character.
What could Griffin McElroy, what evil could he do?
Being rich.
Being a freaking bourgeoisie.
Yeah, I'm thinking I'm a landlord.
A boudoirsie.
Yeah, I love owning a bunch of condominiums in Malibu.
Yeah.
I use my podcast money to buy a bunch of condos in low-income neighborhoods.
Yeah I'm thinking of gentrifying.
That sounds really high rent.
Yeah, so basically I'm a gentrifier.
There we go.
Yeah basically I have no problems with gentrifying.
Yeah, he thinks gentrification is good for the community.
Hey Griffin, here I gotta change my voice enough so that people know that it's two different
guys.
Hey Griffin, what do you think about the national debt?
I love it.
I wish it was higher.
Hey Griffin. You're going to jail okay. I'm Joe Swanson. Hey Griffin. Hey Peter Griffin McElroy.
Peter meet Griffin. Lois, hey Lois. Hey Brian. Hey what's up Pupperino Brian. Oh look at my gay little baby. I love my gay
little baby oh he's oh he's British maybe he's kind of like a British kind of baby
and I have a black guy neighbor Griffin yeah that's horrible yeah yeah yeah
that's gonna get him in trouble uh-huh he's gonna get in trouble for all of
Peter Griffin's crimes that's true fight the chicken pretty soon
I'm actually probably gonna fight the chicken pretty soon now, like any day now, probably fight this chicken.
Hey, Peter Griffin McElroy, it's me, your brother, Justin.
Hey, what's up, Justin?
I like- it's good that you have bad legs.
They call me "Oops."
It's actually- it makes you stronger.
I'm Scooby-Doo!
Hey!
What's up, Scooby? There's my dog, Scooby.
I can't even do a normal Scooby-Doo voice, just the laugh.
That's the only part of the approach that I can do.
After the laugh you sound like fucking Lead Belly.
You just sound like an old blues guy.
I like it though.
Yeah?
Yeah, I like it.
Yeah, you like me?
I do like you.
Maybe I'm giving up on Patrick and I'm just gonna marry and fucking kill you.
Can't do that Cameron and I are already married.
Marry, fuck, kill, us three. What are we doing?
Marry, fuck, kill, us.
Marry, marry.
That's up for the fans to decide.
Yeah, somebody definitely has asked that question.
I know everybody is marrying me because I'm a sweetheart.
No, people will marry me because I'm going to keep them safe when stuff goes poorly.
Fine, I know they all fuck me.
People are going to say "befriend me."
They're going to create a new option to say "friend."
There is no option.
"Fuck, marry, befriend."
"Fuck, marry, kill, and the friend."
You can use the friend as a secret option.
Everybody fucks and marries me.
Nobody wants to kill me.
People just ignore Patrick.
Nobody cares about him.
that's fine people just i'd rather i'd rather have that people say people say they say marry
fuck kill the podcast about list boys and then someone says isn't there just two guys on that
isn't it just caleb and cameron that's not what people say isn't it just caleb and patrick
no people say absolutely what happens this is just caleb and then two girls how do we marry
and fuck two girls. How do you marry a girl? I don't know. Kill I understand. If it was
marry kill kill. That computes but yeah that makes perfect sense.
But fuck a girl. What? Somebody's like hey you're gonna fuck that girl and the guy
just goes where where would I do that what where this is what yeah an armpit
what are you talking about dude we fucker thighs nasty dude nah nah you
can't do that no you can't no you can't you can't do that can't just fuck some
girl no you can't fucking armpit I'm telling you right now you can't
Absolutely no.
No armpits.
Look I've tried.
And there's one rule.
No armpits.
I've tried.
And failed.
Could you fuck a kangaroo pouch?
And more importantly, would you?
No, dude, it's bones in there.
Nah, dude, it's bones in there.
Nah, man, it's bones.
It's bones.
It's so fast.
Listen, bro, it's bones in there.
Patrick has tried.
No, I saw, I saw a kangaroo.
No, no, no, I've seen inside a kangaroo pouch.
I've seen inside one.
It's bones.
It's all bones.
I did.
I did and it freaked me the fuck out.
It's all bones.
It's bones. It's all bones.
I did. I did and it freaked me the fuck out.
It's all bones.
It's completely bones.
It freaked me out. It freaked me the fuck out.
It's a fucking bone pocket. Fuck that.
I'm... No, I... It's... It ruins every cool thing.
No, no. It ruins every sexual fantasy about a kangaroo I've ever had.
Yeah. The bones are just somebody else tried to fuck the kangaroo first and they died in there.
That's true. It's like a penis fly trap.
Yeah. It's like seeing a cow skull in the desert.
I'm telling you it's effed up in there.
Real shit.
Listen I've been in a kangaroo pouch and I ain't lying.
You can see the organs.
Look up a fucking picture of it.
Ok.
I'll look this up right now.
Inside of kangaroo pouch.
It's disgusting.
You can see the bone.
You can see all their bones.
Oh wow.
Whoa.
I told you.
That's fucking swag dude.
That's awesome.
I would fuck that.
It looks like a vagina.
I mean it is, right?
What is it?
No, that's not the pouch, dude.
There's legs coming out of that, dude.
That's the vagina.
Yeah, well, I mean that's...
They birth out of the pouch?
Yeah, the pouch is just a...
I think they do.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm pretty sure the pouch just falls out.
I think it just rolls out.
I think it just falls out.
No, the pouch is not the hoo-ha.
Can you imagine being a baby and you sit inside your mom like that?
Okay, wait.
I'm going to send you guys one that I think you're really going to like.
I think you guys will like this one.
Yeah?
I'm serious.
Tell me what this one looks like.
Okay.
Tell me that's not some fire ash.
That looks like Caleb's pussy.
No.
Dude, that's fucking gross.
What's gross about that?
You think women's bodies are gross?
For people at home, it looks like somebody cut open
a kangaroo and stuffed an Arby's beef and cheddar
Yeah.
into its stomach.
Ugh.
And it's looking pretty good to me.
I think I might have to invest.
I'm looking at the URL of this image you sent and it says gothic in it.
Yeah.
There's a word gothic in the URL.
Real gothic shit.
Oh my god.
That's disgusting.
That is disgusting.
That's good dude.
Kangaroo pussy.
Stop looking at it dude.
What are you doing with your hands?
Nothing.
Why is your camera shaking around?
Oh my god.
What are you doing dude?
You better be trying to open a can of tuna, otherwise I'm off the podcast.
Oh my, that's so gross.
We can't do this twice in a row.
Now that's a perfect way to end it.
Yeah.
Yeah, Patrick's fucked a kangaroo.
Bye everyone.
No.
I'm not Australian, I don't want to have sex with a kangaroo.
I'm stopping recording.
Okay.
Patrick fucked a kangaroo.