Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
- Premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Yeah.
- Wait, so when people listen to a podcast,
do they hold their phone up to their ears like this?
- Yeah.
- Really?
- Yeah, like this.
- Like they put it up like they're talking on the phone?
- They do it exactly like this.
- Right guys?
- Like they're talking on the phone, right?
- Yeah, they do it like that.
- Like this.
like that like this but they did it we're pointing at the same thing no they do it
vastly thusly sometimes yeah yeah how about as pictured they do it as
pictured do they do do we do the podcast as a picture sometimes we could do that
I guess yeah I just release a picture instead of an episode one week well yeah
I think that if we do it's like a big enough picture with enough stuff going on
It would take an hour to look at.
Yeah.
Then they'd be like, well that's the same.
Yeah, that is. You can't argue with that.
Plus, you don't have to wear headphones.
So, you know what we would need to do?
What?
We need to do, we'd need to make an eye spy.
Because that's the only thing that you're going to get an hour's worth of entertainment out.
Or a really hard magic eye.
Where you have to stare at it for an hour before the 3D comes out.
Yeah.
Alright, well those are already very hard for me.
Or a picture of like a bunch of words.
True.
Oh, we could just do a picture of a podcast. Okay, but some people are speed readers
Go around
Lives catering to the speed readers. Exactly. You're a speed reader. Fuck you speed readers are fucking dog shit, dude
Uh-huh. I know you didn't I know you didn't hear Harry Potter's voice in your head
You don't even know what he sounds like you don't know that there's emotional tenor behind his words. Oh
See speed reader sounds like speed reader. That's what it sounds like no, that's you know, what do you mean?
That's what he sounds like. No, he doesn't yes. He does. He's more child. How did he sound? Okay?
No, that's Ron Mary Porter, that's Ron Ron says that Ron's are this
That's wrong. That's Hagrid
What that was Hagrid? Yeah, hey
Marnie Granger that is when I'm here to take the test
She's so I'm here to do my own work and take a test. Yeah get her
Fucking door of doing homework. Oh my god. Are you watching this? Are you seeing what he's doing? I love to I love to
wash my arms
Bitch, and follow the rules bitch. Oh
You Hermione green. I have a bedtime
Bet she does actually and it's 830 and do you follow it? I follow my
What do you think about chores or mining I love chores what
Yeah, which all of them all of them all of them. What about playing? Oh, yeah. Oh my god
I hate playing and I love doing chores
Potter Hermione's is a villain
Yes, really. Uh-huh Wow
I love getting people in trouble.
Oh my god.
I love tattletaling.
No.
You better take that one back.
I'm a turtle, I'm a snail, and I'm a tattletale.
You're a turtle and a snail?
You know the rhyme?
You like rhymes too?
I love poetry.
That was it.
Because it's homework.
That's...
Mmm.
For poetry class.
Oh, come on.
Do they have that at Hogwarts?
I have it at Hogwarts and they got spells.
So the thing about these Hogwarts kids, they go to...
And they got a little goblin who's Jewish.
They go to school to like fucking...
The goblins control the banks.
Alright, Hermione, you're edging towards something bad.
I've got some things to say about Israel.
"Oh, I'd love to cast a spell over there and fix all the problems."
And that problem is...
Careful now.
We need to cut Hermione's mic off.
So in Harry Potter, these kids are going to school for doing this, right?
Yeah, as pictures.
That was the motion you were doing.
They're doing Wanda waving.
Thusly.
So, can they read?
Yeah.
They didn't go to reading school.
No, they definitely...
There's no English classes at fucking Hogwarts.
No. Can they even do long division? I think they do a spell that makes them learn how to read.
That is pretty funny, that last "Kerminey."
Well, like, yeah, like, imagining, like, like, like wise old Dumbledore, and he walks into McDonald's, and he's like, "I'll have, uh..."
"That one."
Yeah, he can't read that thing. Just a pointing.
Yeah. "I'll have the, uh, uh, bun."
"I'll have the one that's this many dollars."
"I'll have the this many meal."
I'll have whatever I can get for this many dollars.
But they can't be all that smart.
No, that's, yeah, they're definitely, they're probably very stupid.
I mean, really, like, illiterate, these, these, uh, what are they called?
Wizards.
These wizards.
The hater said I would never recover from my head injury, but here I am.
I'm smarter than I ever was before.
Fully recovered.
My head is in it.
Ask me a trivia question.
Congratulations.
I think I might have to apologize for the Hermione bit.
Go ahead.
Ask me a trivia question.
This week.
What?
Ask me a trivia question.
In 2003, what movie was cheaper by the dozen?
Cheaper.
Correct.
In 2006, there was something cheaper by the dozen...
Two.
Yes!
More trivia, I need it.
Okay, in 2006, there was something that was cheaper by the dozen two.
What was it?
Cheaper by the dozen two.
It's Steve Martin.
Wrong.
A movie.
You get a dozen movies for $10 at Walmart.
I said there was something called Cheaper by the Dozen 2.
What was it?
It was movie.
It was really obvious.
It was the easiest one yet.
In 2006, Eugene Levy and Steve Martin starred in what movie that was Cheaper by the Dozen
2?
Let me think about this.
Eugene Levy, Steve Martin starred in what movie that was Cheaper by the Dozen 2?
I'm going to say Cheaper by the Dozen 2.
What year did Cheaper by the Dozen 2 come out three years after its prequel Cheaper by the
Dozen 1 in 2003?
Prequel?
I'm going to say 2006.
Correct.
Your Honor.
In 2003, Hilary Duff-
My Socks.
Wait, was she in that movie?
How many was it Cheaper by in 2006?
Two.
I think it was cheaper by... I think... Okay, so the movie's called Cheaper by the Dozen.
I think it's technically cheaper by 13 in that one. I think they have another kid.
Well, they're called the Baker's Family and it's the... the joke is that it's the Baker's
Dozen.
I didn't get that.
You didn't?
No, that one flew right over my head.
Oh.
Yeah.
But it's cheaper to have 13 of them.
What was the name of the Baker's Family in the Dozen movies?
Cheaper by the...
In the Dozen franchise?
In the Dozen franchise, who was the star alongside Eugene Levy and himself, Steve Martin?
Steve Martin.
Correct.
When are they going to do a third Cheever by the Dozy?
Oh, I don't know.
2009, based on the pattern.
Nowadays it'd probably be a whole family of girls with a lesbian mom.
I don't want to see that.
these girls make all these kids. Hey with that many girls in one house it's gonna be called
more expensive by the dozen. Yes sir. Jewelry, makeup, nail, nail makeup. Yeah. Whatever they
put on their nails. And you know that bathroom line is long. Uh huh. They have a line for
the bathroom in their own house. Guess how long it is. A dozen long. And you think that's
the water bill is not cheaper. Let me tell you what also with a dozen girls statistically
every month one of them gets their period. You don't think they'd sync up?
Well it's cheaper to sync up. So they all at one month you're never safe.
So who's the star? Of cheaper by the dozen women?
Cheaper by the dozen three. More expensive by the dozen the girl one?
expensive by the dozen the star would probably be probably they got to bring
back bonnie we want who do we want is what girls we want to see kiss Scarlett
Johansson and Halle Berry I was gonna say steve uh Marta
steve a Marta she's she's too hot right now they she would never say yes to a
a comedy. Eunice Levy. No, I want to see some smushing. You wouldn't want to see
Steve Amarta and Eunice Levy? I want to walk in and just be mad at Arthur and their lips smushing.
Is there a reason you want this to be part of the, you could just have a movie like that. I don't
understand why it needs to be the third entry in a family franchise. What do you
You need 13 children to be in the house?
No, they're all grown adults.
Oh, okay.
Uh-huh.
Okay.
You know where this is going.
And they fuck each other, even though they're sisters.
So it's Steve Martin and Gianna Michaels.
No.
No Gianna Michaels.
She's not invited.
Also, it is a weight loss competition with all the girls.
And they're singing too.
It could be called lighter by the dozen.
vote on the surgeries they get with your phone. It's a live, it's a game show. It's like the
Bachelor. It's also a sequel to Cheaper by the Dozen. They should do a game show or a
reality show like that called The Beautiful One where you get 10 really ugly girls and
then you get to vote with your phone on what happens to them. Why is it called The Beautiful
One? Because at the end they become beautiful because of all the surgery. Didn't they make
Was that a show?
Did they?
Oh, I'm thinking of Extreme Makeover.
Yeah, well that kind of is Extreme Makeover.
Yeah.
But also...
But Extreme Makeover Royale.
It would be a Royale.
Yeah.
Because they're in the woods too.
And they have to do all the surgery with like chipmunk bones and shit.
Yeah.
They don't get real surgery stuff.
A lot of them are going to die of sepsis.
This is the sad truth of the matter.
Well, at least, you know, you do the surgery with chipmunk bones.
You get pouches in your mouth.
You can store food for winter.
That is a really good point.
Yeah.
Do you guys ever wish you had a colostomy bag?
Because I'm not going to shit in it all the time, so it would be fun to have a little
pocket.
I mean, if I had a colostomy bag and I was waiting in line at Domino's or something,
or Popeyes or something that was taking too long, I'd just whip it out and shit on the
floor.
Okay.
Or if, you know, I could probably use it to stop an attack.
Why on the floor?
What?
Well the lines long I want everyone to leave the restaurant.
Oh that's true.
So you wouldn't use the bag though?
No I would lift up my shirt, take the, poke the tube out and just start like spraying it
on the people in front of me.
Oh I see.
Yeah.
That's nasty.
That's not right.
I gotta try that flounder sandwich.
I haven't tried it yet.
Knowing me I'd have to walk around with like a fucking 40 gallon trash bag attached to me
if I had a colostomy bag.
There's no.
I don't think I would fill that coin purse up pretty far you really only that you know
You think that there's poop inside of you all day, right? There's literally always poop inside of you. Yeah, but like
It's only enough for like one
One toilet full that's not true
You the poop it takes like it takes like sometimes 48 hours to like digest something fully from eating to pooping
I was going to say it sometimes takes you 48 hours to poop.
I mean it can, but you always have 48 hours of poop in you.
Really?
Yeah.
Is that what that movie is about?
Which one?
Cheaper by the Dozen?
147 hours?
No, Cheaper by the... we already established.
That's about two hot momos.
What about Cheaper by the Dozen 127?
It's a family of climbers that get trapped.
Oh.
It's a crossover.
I think there's a lot of...
Movie 127.
Number seven.
Yeah.
I feel like we could do a bunch of crossovers with like number movies.
That'd be big.
Yeah.
Number 23 by the dozen.
Number 23 by the dozen would be really good.
Yeah.
It would be scary.
Because that's, you know, two dozen.
And then eventually, once we do like a bunch of cheaper by the, a bunch of the dozen saga,
then there can be like kind of like the infinity war and it's called like cheaper by the dozen
generations and it's like all the families in the same house.
every single family from every movie. It's called Dozen Annihilation. Dozens of Dozens.
Yeah. What? That could be one of them. Or it's like called like Dozens of Cheap Things.
It could be called like Dozens with a Z. Like the Z is really big. If I made that movie,
Cheap Brother Dozen, I would have called it my white ass family.
They're white as hell in that movie.
I call that crazy ass family and you know they white.
And you know they white.
Remember they have that ginger kid?
Yeah, they had two.
Who's not white enough?
Yeah, Steve Martin.
No, they had one ginger kid.
They had two.
They had twins.
FedEx.
It's called FedEx.
They did have a ginger girl, you're right.
They had the ginger twins.
But they picked on FedEx because he was more obsessed with toads than his family.
You know?
And apparently that's a crime in the Baker family.
He was the one...
Was he the skater one?
No! He was the one who's a fucking nerd!
He looked like Jonathan Lipnicki!
Do I need to look up a...
a Dozens roster?
Cheaper by the Dozen wiki.
I don't think that's gonna exist.
It's gonna exist.
You think so?
There's somebody who is probably very
earnestly obsessed with those movies
in a very weird way.
Yeah, here it is.
Cheaper by the Dozen wiki.
Cheaper by the Dozen...
Cheapbythedozen.fandom.com
Couldn't even put the "er" in there?
Let's see what the pages are. This wiki is a joke.
Well it's okay, so it's just got pages for all the different family members.
Pages for the movies. Do they have any news on a sequel?
Yeah, there's actually a cheaper by the dozen 2 which came out in 2005.
Whoa!
Believe it or not.
2005.
So I was wrong about every single trivia question.
Cool.
Well that was because of your concussion.
Yeah.
I didn't know, I wasn't going to be like.
So all of them were trick questions and the answer was it actually came out in 2005.
I'm talking about the DVD release.
Oh, okay.
It's a movie that came out in September, I believe.
There's a lot of pages on this.
Really? Is Hilary Duff in this movie?
I have a vague recollection of Hilary Duff being in this movie.
There is a Hilary Duff page on this wiki, let's see.
Okay.
Hilary Erhard Duff is an American actress, singer, songwriter, designer, producer, and author.
Well, who would have guessed?
Not me.
air last night at the bar when Hillary Duff showed up?
Yeah, when Hillary Duff, no, when that homeless lady was like, "Whoa."
Oh yeah.
Were you there for that?
Yeah.
That was so fucking funny.
She walked in and stared at all of us at the table.
Okay, what happened was the homeless lady walked over to a group of people who were
smoking and then one lady, me, was like, me and Eamon were out there and we just saw this
lady be like, "Can I have some money?"
She did sound like Droopy Dog.
Yeah.
And then it was crazy how much she sounded like female Droopy Dog.
Insanely droopy.
this one girl was like, "Get the fuck out of here, you fucking bitch! You fucking stupid
bitch! Fuck you!" She was trying to fight her, and me and Eamon just couldn't stop laughing
because it was just like a homeless person asking for money.
Immediately, just a lady is like...
So then she walks into the bar.
She walks into the bar, yeah. She looks at me, like me, Patches, Cam, everyone who was
sitting there, and she's repeating herself, "You got any change? You got any change?"
And then the bartender was like get the fuck out of here.
Emily, she's like get the fuck out of here Emily.
And then three other people on the other side of the bar went Emily get the fuck out of here.
I mean it was the funniest thing I've ever seen.
Like an entire bar yelling at a homeless woman.
It's a world where like you don't even pretend to ignore homeless people you just actively
like.
I thought I slipped into a different reality.
I think one of them told Amon...
The girl outside who was screaming, who also was like celebrating after she left, she was
like, "Yeah, go on and fucking walk away from me, Emily, you stupid bitch!"
Called her a cunt, swear to God, it was fucking hilarious.
And then I was like, "Hey, that was cool that you yelled at that hobo."
And she was like, "Oh yeah, she like steals people's phones."
Yeah.
So, it all had a happy ending.
Nice.
It was said, Amon said that he heard she calls people the N-word.
Yeah, I heard she has two eyes.
Yeah.
I heard that she has a lot of mental problems.
I heard she has a tail.
And is disenfranchised by society.
Yeah.
I heard she used to be addicted to drugs, but she can't afford them now.
Hmm.
Yeah.
I found a very exciting page here on the cheaper, but less than wicked.
I heard that she owns a Quiznos.
Wow.
I just heard that.
I just got news from EmilyNews.com.
Oh, you're getting a report?
I'm getting a report.
What's your report say?
It says she sucked my dick.
Whoa!
Yep.
Hold on.
I got laid.
Is that?
Here, I'm getting a report.
She touched my balls too.
Whoa!
Sources are saying she touched.
That's true.
Who's your source?
Where's the report coming from?
It's coming from my earpiece right now.
Your earpiece?
Is your earpiece linked up to emilynews.com?
It is a red alert.
It's actually, people are...
Okay, my source is saying I've had sex with all the girls in the world.
Whoa.
Even your mom?
Sources are saying no, not my mom.
are saying well my source says that you had sex with your own mom well yeah my
sources are every every so is your mom not a girl and your grandma - sorry and
all of your aunts sources are saying that and your cousin
sources are saying that second cousins who were feeling all your great
grandmothers guys the feeds really scrambled right now I can't get a clear I
think there's kind of too many saying this saying different things looked up
girl named Kayla Bina sources are saying that one's true I fucked Kayla Bina yeah
who's also bald. The sources are saying she has beautiful long hair. She has beautiful
long hair down there. Oh wow this is coming in right now. This is coming in right now.
And by down there I mean the legs. Okay all right this is coming in right now. This is
a little bit of a clarification on the story. So apparently it's it's it's all
I only had sex with your moms. No. According to my sources. You had sex with every woman in the
world including your grandpa. No apparently it was a bit of a editor is
making a note for me. That it was correct. That it was wrong actually.
That it was correct. Oh I just got a million dollars also. I just got a report that that
story has received six Pinocchios. It's more than more Pinocchios. It seems like the story...
There's a five Pinocchios scale. Oh wow this is interesting. It seems like there's actually...
so there's actually a character called Reverse Pinocchio whose nose goes inside
when he tells the truth and I'm getting sources that are saying that the story
actually got five reverse Pinocchios. Five reverse Pinocchios on PinocchioNews.com.
So I'm getting some Pinocchio news. Apparently Pinocchio is in the belly of a whale.
No! Last seen. I thought he got out.
Seems like he's there again. Is he real yet?
Let's see. Sources are saying that he's not real yet, but he is currently in the belly
of a whale. Well this is crazy news, because earlier I
I heard that Pinocchio was turned into a braying jackass.
No.
Yeah.
Wait, I'm getting a report.
Oh wow, he's more than braying, he's ornery, they say.
Whoa.
Yeah.
But he said that, but I heard that the curse was actually reversed, but his two friends
I'm getting that too.
His two friends who taught him swearing were turned into braying jackasses.
Yeah, yeah, I'm getting the exact same.
I actually, I received a report too that that scared me a lot when that happened.
I'm receiving a report that actually I'm being, I'm actually being scared even just thinking
about it because of how many bad memories I have.
I am, I am receiving a report though that I'm rather intrigued and wish to return to
the scene as an adult to see whether it still scares me.
I'm getting a report here and I mean this could be a typo but it just says uh, hee haw,
hee haw.
I will say you're kind of revealing your sources here.
Heehaw.
Can we just, you know what, split the screen.
Can we just get one of these braying jackasses on the phone?
Okay.
Alright.
I'm here with a braying jackass.
Jackass, how are you today?
Heehaw.
Very interesting.
Now what do you have to say about reports that Pinocchio is in the belly of a whale?
Haw.
Heehaw.
And it seems like that's all the time we have.
I'm splitting the screen again over your interview.
This is ridiculous.
This guy clearly has nothing to say.
Listen, can we just be civil, guys?
He calls himself a journalist.
He's literally a brain jackass.
Hold on now, hold on now.
Getting reports that the whale has sneezed.
Huh, I'm getting reports there's something in the sky.
Oh, I'm getting reports that it's getting closer.
And there it is. That's Pinocchio.
He actually landed safely.
safely. Everybody at the office is cheering. We're all doing great now. And
that's all for us. I'm Caleb Beena Pitts. Have a wonderful night.
We should just move into news. I think we'd be some good newsmen.
It'd be the most amazing. We could do crazy stuff. I have some news for you.
Oh yeah, we still haven't read this cheaper news. Cheaper news coming in.
I'm getting a report. I'm receiving a report from from the dozen actually
Oh
apparently chandelier. I'm hearing that the chandelier was a prominent
lightning fixture that first appeared in cheaper by the dozen. It was located in
the Baker family's new mansion in a Chicago suburb and was infamous because
it crashed several times to the floor as a result of various mishaps. Wow wow wow
and that's some hard-hitting journalism.
- Well, this just in.
- Oh.
- This just in, we're hearing from Tom Baker here.
I have some information about Tom Baker.
- Tom Baker?
- Thomas Tom Baker, born October 27th, 1953,
is the father of 12 children and husband to Kate Baker.
Tom grew up in a large family.
And now I'm seeing, I have an,
there's an info box popping up on the screen.
A wiki-style info box. - I see it, yeah.
- Yeah, you can see here, it says, "Status alive."
it says well i think that is always good romances kate baker wife love his life
and it says that there's also the final category as you can see here on your
screen is in fact loyalty uh... he has to loyalties which are to the baker family
and the profession of being a football coach currently
wow
wow while i'm also i think you know just
before you know before you have to cut the commercial at one more tidbit about
tom here
tom baker is also the insulin waiter from jim henson's the muppet movie when
Kermit the Frog and Miss Piggy went out for dinner. In that scene from the Muppet movie,
Tom Baker had a sip of the wine and spit and then said, "Excellent choice," in a beautiful
voice that sounds like Bing Crosby's voice.
Wow. And on a lighter note...
What? Are they connecting?
On a bit of a lighter note, we have in the studio with us a very sad mouse. Mouse, how are you today?
And that's just horrible to hear. Back to you, Cameron.
I don't have anything else. Cut to commercial. Now.
Are you tired of sucking? Do you want to be better? Try out my drink.
Hi, I'm Todd Bosley, inventor of that drink. And I put a bunch of pills in a blender and with fruit.
And this could actually make your life better and make you much stronger.
And it put acai berries in it?
I'm allergic to acai berries. Oh no, my throat's closing up.
That's the announcer of the commercial and I should have told him that before.
Hi, I'm Dr. Monster. Have you been- have you received side effects as a- as an effect of
the drink that was on the last commercial just now? You may even be entitled to
nothing. It's still part of the last commercial. Fuck you.
I can't believe Dr. Monster bought ad space in my ad.
And we're back and we're receiving reports that celebrity doctor, Dr. Monster is actually going to jail for being too weird.
Yeah, this is actually a very interesting development because many people thought that he was too cool to go to jail.
Yeah.
But it seems like the courts have finally changed their mind.
This just in, actually, this is actually just continuing on their story. My bad. I thought it was breaking news, but it wasn't.
You're our worst newsman.
I'm new to the job. Dr. Monster was deemed too cool to go to jail after giving
Michael Jackson all those prescriptions that killed him. People were very
excited once Dr. Monster killed Michael Jackson and he also went on to kill many
other people with prescription drugs including Prince. I'm getting reports
that Dr. Monster hmm yeah like I thought he's behind Mac Miller and Little Peep as
well. Yep, I've actually just received a second report confirming that and adding
Epton Yelchin to the list. Yep, I'm getting reports of that as well. Oh, I'm
seeing pictures of him attacking Juice WRLD. Oh wow. Yeah, so it seems like
federal investigators were able to put this together by all the the the giant
claw marks on each and every one of these deceased bodies. Matching the claws
of one doctor monster that's a great that's great well breaking this just in
Nora is 22 years old as honey blonde hair with sunny highlights she has a
boyfriend named Hank who her younger siblings do not like Wow I'm getting
this in right now I'm Wow so apparently according to my sources I'm imagining
Nora in a bikini hmm my wow my source here is saying that in cheaper by the
dozen too. Nora is pregnant and is played by Piper Perabo. I'm getting reports that
her being pregnant is only making me more attracted to her. So that's an
interesting unexpected development on my end. I'm getting reports here my sources
are saying that Caleb is imagining pregnant, what was her, Nora bobbing up and
down in a swimming pool on her pregnant belly. I'm hearing that too. I'm also
I'm also getting reports that my boner got so big it's in my mouth now.
And it's out.
There's a...
Well I'm very glad to hear that. That could have been a dangerous situation.
We're going to ask the audience
what they think of this and
I have a message here from user Caleb
and it says that
Oh, oh man, I'm imagining feeding Nora a Jimmy John's sub while she's bobbing up and down in the pool on her pregnant belly.
I'm seeing another comment here that actually from the audience, it's from a user cpits, and it says,
"I wish that I could bob for Nora like an apple on Halloween day."
I'm seeing reports that I made both of those comments.
Very impressive work, boys.
There's one more here from Cpits8baller.
"Oooowee, I wish I could hit her pregnant belly with a pool cue and watch her spin around
on a pool table hitting the 8 ball into the corner pocket just like Super Monkey Ball pool."
And here's actually a follow-up comment to that, a reply by the same user right under it that also says
"I would love to hit her belly like a gong"
And there's an added thing to that thread that says "I don't even care if there's a baby in it"
No pat
I'm seeing reports that I'm developing a sexual fetish for pregnant women who actually don't have a baby in there
That's what it says on the teleprompter
So if you or a loved one knows of any pregnant women who quote unquote
don't have a baby in there, please call the toll-free number on your screen.
There's a... It's my number. It's 911.
Doing a cursory glance through CPIT's 8BALA's page...
Oh, I'm seeing reports that you should not do that.
It appears that he hasn't unlinked his Amazon account to his account,
and he has just purchased a fake pregnant belly.
Wow, I'm actually getting reports that upon purchasing the fake pregnant belly, I'm getting so horny that even my balls are hard.
Wow, I've actually seen a report just now that he's made another purchase right after the pregnant belly, and it seems to be a full-length mirror. How strange.
Wow, he's-- oh, this is interesting. So apparently, I'm researching cloning and whether or not I could go to Indonesia and have it done for $600.
And there's one more Amazon purchase here and uh...
Seems to be a $20,000 ultrasound machine
and 600 ounces of ultrasound gel.
Ah, okay, this is making more and more sense as we piece this together.
It appears that I think that ultrasound gel tastes like candy.
Yeah, there's another post here by Cpitz8bala that says
"Ooo-ee-oo, I wish Haribo would turn this ultrasound jelly into candy."
I'm seeing actually another purchase here.
It's actually a video rental online for Star Wars Episode II, Attack of the Clones,
and I am seeing a cancelled plane ticket to Indonesia as well.
Oh, okay. Alright.
Well, this is actually taking a turn for the worse, this story, I would say.
Apparently, I just imagined a pregnant woman pooping and got a little movement down there.
It seems like this could be big trouble.
And doing another cursory glance through C-Pit's 8-Ballers thing, his posts.
Oh, it appears that I got another movement when Patrick said that he was looking at my thing.
Another cursory glance through C-Pit's 8-Ballers account says here,
"Damn, what if a pregnant lady could poop out the baby then put it back?"
That's foul. That is, that is uh, that's horrible. You know what?
Insanely disgusting person. And to me for the sports. Welcome to the sports segment.
I, today is basketball, NBA debut. Okay, so basically. Don't let this guy look at a basketball.
Basically the basketballs are so beautiful when they have a child in them and they are attached to a blonde woman
and there's a ch- and a ch- and the beautiful milk is coming out of them.
And there's basically every ball is beautiful and big and the- and I- and I'm-
um, back to the news.
This just in, Caleb has been fired from the news.
This just in, guys I'm calling you from a cellular telephone.
Apparently I've been fired for trying to finger myself at the desk.
Caleb has been trying to Caleb has been fired from the news and in an unexpected turn of events
He has been hired at the beach ball store
Guys I'm live from the beach ball store. I've been duct-taping all the beach balls to myself him in I don't know why
Our connection is like this is like in the Batman movie when they had the Joker on TV
Hmm. I'm getting reports that the Batman movie is actually very good. We actually got that report. Are we talking about?
I'm getting a report that the best one is Dark Knight. I also got that report.
We can't say that yet. Oh wow, I'm getting a report. Wow.
I can't say that yet, there's a new one coming out soon. Wow, I mean this is a truly big story.
Apparently, Dr. Monster also had something to do with Heath Ledger's death.
Really? Oh yep, and Elliot Smith. And Elliot Smith. Yep. Well I guess that makes
sense there was a lot of people forget there was a giant claw found in Elliot
Smith's chest. Many people thought that he stabbed himself with the claw mm-hmm
and I always thought that made no sense. No, he doesn't have claws. Yeah. Exactly
how could he have done it? Yeah. Wasn't him. I do think his wife did that though. Yeah. Do you
think that? I don't know too much. I don't know anything about it. I know that he got
stabbed in the heart. He either got murdered or just was like the
coolest shit ever where you just like a samurai just stab yourself. Yeah. What do you guys
think about Kurt and Courtney? They were so beautiful together. They were. Courtney Love
is the one from Man on the Moon? Yes. That's an ugly woman. I don't think so. Oh yeah. Have
you ever heard Hole? The band? Have I seen her Hole? Come on. Hey come on now. I don't
think urkha bank killed himself i think he did why he's famous he was bored that's
not a good enough reason government did it because his music was getting too
good yeah yeah they saw that acoustic set and they're like yeah no white boy can
play this soulfully damn he did lake of fire yeah damn damn I recently was
covering meat puppets what the yeah I that pissed me off when people think
that that's a Nirvana song oh yeah makes me so mad dude that's such a good song
- "Lake of Fire"?
- Yeah.
- I thought it was a Nirvana song.
- Yeah, you're a piece of shit.
- Jesus, Jesus don't want me.
- Sorry, I like cool music and not stupid music.
- Me Puppets way cooler than Nirvana.
- Me Puppets is so sick.
- I don't know what that is.
- You ever heard that song?
- I don't like rock.
Oh fuck.
'Cause they have a song called,
I always forget the name of it,
but they have a song called "The Whistling Song".
- Mm-hmm.
- And then there's the other one.
- Oh, I've heard that one, it goes like.
(whistling)
- I love it when Me Puppets, they put like three songs
on the same album that have the same name.
- Yeah.
- That's such a sick thing to do.
- I think that's a bad thing to do.
- It's awesome.
- Well, how's that a good thing to do?
- It's funny.
- What if we named three episodes in a row the same thing?
- Yeah, what if we named the episode "Boo"?
- Hmm.
How about "Beautiful Pregnant Woman"?
Pregnant Caleb.
Caleb got pregnant.
Caleb got himself pregnant.
You can maybe make your own thing and call it that.
I'm not, I don't, I'm not unattracted to pregnant women.
I guess, I mean, that's probably good for you.
Why for me?
If, you know, you ever get your wife pregnant.
I can get my wife pregnant, you're right.
Oh my god, that's huge.
I think it's Maiden's Milk by the Meat Puppets, it's the whistling song.
I thought you said it was called the whistling song.
No, there's another song called the whistling song but that made its milk is the one where they whistle where it's uh
Yeah, there's a lot of whistling in it
That's got to be one of the most boring things i've ever heard
What oh
I just got breaking news. Uh
Pinocchio has been turned into a real boy. Oh my god last wow
I'm getting this exact same news from my sources.
I actually am getting a similar story that apparently Jonathan David Bennett, who played
Bud McNulty in 2005's Cheaper by the Dozen 2, was also the host of the Food Network series
Halloween Wars.
Are you also getting this news from Geppetto?
Yep.
Wow.
He's a bit of a Dozen head.
I've heard Geppetto is a huge fan of Cheaper by the Dozen.
As well as Halloween Wars.
I'm getting reports, and this is interesting, that Halloween Wars is actually very scary.
And it's happening soon, on the 31st.
Okay, I'm getting reports, I'm still in the beach ball store by the way, I'm getting reports
that I'm very scared of Halloween Wars.
It seems as if it's a war where whoever wins, we lose.
I am getting a report from Geppetto that each episode does have two rounds which consist
of the small scare and the spine chiller.
Wow, I'm getting reports from Japano who is the Japanese Geppetto and...
Yeah I will not be saying that on air.
Japanese Japetto dude. Oh man. He makes like a, he makes a little pup, what are those called?
Those little puppets? You know those little Japanese puppets? Oh, Bunraku. Mannequin. Bunraku?
Bunraku. Those things are cool as fuck. They're so scary. They're really cool, yeah. You've
never seen Bunraku? No. It's basically like a, an evil kind of, Bakugan is actually what
I'm thinking of. Yeah, the ancient Japanese art of Bakugan. Check this out. What's thisly?
the Halloween Wars logo.
Halloween Wars, the screams do come true.
Fuck that's scary.
What do they do in Halloween Wars?
It's two cupcakes.
Oh, oh.
Two cupcakes.
That's the one where they make scary cakes?
Yeah, it's just Cake Wars, but for Halloween.
That actually, I did watch it one time and it was more scary than I thought.
They did some scary cakes.
Cake Wars is such a funny show because they have that one, they have one judge who's like
an old Israeli guy who's just like incredibly catty and mean to everybody.
Oh yeah, that guy is crazy.
He's like a chef.
He's so funny.
Is that one?
I think it's Zohan. Yeah. Yeah, his name is Ron Ben Israel. No way. Yeah, that's true.
He's Ben Israel. This whole time. He's Ben Israel.
Yeah, he but he's just he's always like the taste is disgusting
Plus it's scary. Yeah, but it's way too scary.
Well, yeah, they didn't have him on Halloween Wars. I'm sure. Because he's too scared. Yeah. Yeah. Well, he's scared of everyday life
That's why that's why he's rude to everybody. He's afraid of being unwanted
He's a friend. That's why and that's why he lashes out on people's cakes. Why is there not a scary?
I've been thinking about this for a while. There should be a horror movie where the villain stop right there. I'm already too scared
Start right there. Okay, there should be backup
There should be a horror movie where the villain is actually somebody's maybe depression or anxiety that could whoa
What do you think about that?
It would be a little too scary because it's kind of too relatable in real world terms.
Like maybe like a movie about where the villain, where the monster is OCD?
Yeah, so maybe like it's Chucky, right?
Right.
And Chucky kills like a million people and then at the end somebody like, somebody is
like smiles for the first time ever and Chucky kind of disappears.
Right.
Would that be good?
That could be really good.
Maybe a Kaiju movie where the real Godzilla was my depression.
Or maybe a Kaiju movie where he gets in trouble for not cleaning up his toys.
I'll call my agent for pinching his baby sister.
Oh, I'm getting reports here, Kaiju has been grounded for pinching his baby sister twice.
I actually did, I did receive a breaking report right now and this is something that, you
You know I'm a little, I'm loath to say on air but, Mommy Duck, angry on Tom.
Oh the humanity.
And apparently, Ducker was part of the situation as well.
And there are reports, I mean there are millions of reports coming in, I'm looking through
social media here seeing people say that Ducker saw Goober.
Apparently Ducker saw Goober and then Goober went around.
Wow, wow.
I'm getting...
Wow, this is just coming in right now.
Bear with us.
I'm getting reports that Goober was here.
Apparently Ducker went to the restaurant, ordered food, ate, paid, left, and went.
And was Ducker at the restaurant?
I'm getting reports that that in fact has been ascertained to be the case.
He was last seen leaving the restaurant.
Oh wow, apparently he's now on the road.
Ducker's on the road.
Ducker is on the road.
Now let's just pray for us and everyone there at home that he doesn't run into Goober again.
And we're seeing Goober driving a white 1994 Ford Bronco.
Wow.
Down the highway.
I'm getting a report that the nation of North Korea has launched a ballistic missile at
the United States.
Breaking news!
Goober just saw Ducker again.
This is the most important story in centuries.
We have someone live on the ground with Ducker and Goober.
Let's cut to you, Dave.
Hey there, Caleb.
Yeah, I'm here with Ducker and Goober.
Well that's great, Dave.
So what are, what are, what are, what's up with these two guys?
Well it appears they actually saw each other earlier today.
Well that's very...
That's very nice.
I'm getting reports here that uh...
Why don't you set up yourself as two different people if you're just gonna...
Oh, I'm getting reports that there's actually a pregnant woman right next to me.
Hey Caleb! It's me and I'm pregnant! And there's no baby in there.
I'm getting reports that that is officially awesome.
Now, I'm getting reports that Caleb was so horny that he saw a beach ball and he thought it was a woman.
I'm getting the same reports actually.
This beach ball next to me...
Well, let's just say it's in no shape to be returned.
So if anybody would like a free beach ball, you're more than welcome.
And that's the news, ladies and gentlemen.
I'm getting reports in...
Jerry with the brain.
Jerry was with the brain. He was with the brain. Somebody should have stopped him.
True. But you know Tom was busy.
Mommy Duck angry at Tom. Those Tom and Jerry pages
have been... What? Those Tom and Jerry pages. What are you talking about?
Where they talk about like laughing Tom. I have no idea what you're talking about.
So Mommy Duck was... We're talking about something different. Yeah well
anyway I mean we didn't talk that much about Mommy Duck angry at Tom. Sure. We were just talking about that for a little while.
Yeah, yeah, that's fine. I mean
What you know, yeah, well, I'm Tommy Duck
Happy on true on bun buck buck. Yeah buck mom. Yeah, there's one of the schizophrenic episodes
I've ever done Jesus. I feel crazy right now. I'm not recovered from my injury. No, definitely not. I need a bandage
For again, you already got one on your head. I just want a big mummy bandage around my head
Yeah, you want to wrap you would that be offensive if I was a toilet paper mummy for Christmas or Halloween for Christmas?
Yes, it would be offensive
Yeah, I have the top review of Halloween Wars here on IMDB do you know I do it's a one-star review one out of
What are they saying the subject line is ruined it?
The one holiday show I looked forward to has now been ruined where are the pumpkin carvers
Sorry, not watching this season.
The Pumpkin Carvers.
They got rid of the Pumpkin Carvers on Halloween Awards.
No, say it ain't so, dude.
Oh, Jesus.
Here's a 5 out of 10 review.
The host is awful, over the top, loud, and annoying.
Do they think toddlers watch this?
Replace the fast-paced nonsense with more adult content and I'd really like this show.
That still gets 5 stars?
I guess.
Congratulations, you killed your own show.
your own show you took away the pumpkin carving your place everyone's so mad
there's Carla already did that and did it better I've watched ten seasons some
more than once but I'm done with you until you bring back carving you also cut
the price in half while making more advertising dollar and your host sucks
damn people really are mad about Halloween Wars yeah maybe I'll get into
baking cake pull that up I just need it I need a new hobby with my hand you
You should get into making beef jerky.
Dude, no way.
Why did you say it like that?
Because I'm not going to have my fucking house smell like beef jerky all the fucking time.
You could make like teriyaki jerky or like...
I know that I can make teriyaki...
I know I can pepper the jerky.
I don't know how you would make Korean barbecue jerky.
That doesn't make any sense.
Gochujang or something.
It's probably the same deal as teriyaki jerky.
I am not gonna live in a world where I walk into my house every single day and I get scared by a piece of beef.
Get scared? You don't have to get scared by it. It's gonna be in a smoker in your living room.
I'm gonna forget that it's there!
No, you just put it in a dehydrator.
I don't have a dehydrator, you idiot!
Oh my, I'm telling you, just get one or something. Or maybe put it in the oven for like...
How about this? What if I make a beef jerky cake? Doesn't that make way more sense? Make a piece of cake?
So like a savory cake?
No, it just looks like beef jerky.
Oh, so it's like one of those damn things that you cut into and then snap, it's cake.
I think I'm going to start doing that.
Yeah.
It'll be fun.
I really defied that.
I try to do that just horrible at it.
It's like, "Is this a tissue box or a cake?"
It's just like a pile of bread.
It looks like a gray blob.
You'll never guess.
You cut into it and it's just the most beautiful marbled cake.
Just sending pictures of my butthole to celebrities and when they ask, "Why did you send me a picture
of your butthole?"
I'm like, "It's actually cake."
It's cake.
negative you'd like to cut into it's just cake unless you find it unless you
think that it's a very clean butthole in that case it's my butthole but if you
don't if you see poop it's cake remember when Trisha Paytas posted like a picture
of her butthole and there's like a bunch of toilet paper on it no I remember that
do you yeah does she do naked stuff she did I don't think she does anymore but I
know she's good for her she get into Christianity or something she got into
Judaism. Wow that's like kind of Christian, that's like diet Christianity. She either married her,
I'm not too familiar, I see you know, I see. Seems like you're pretty familiar if you've
seen the woman's asshole. I'm familiar enough, I know that that was one of the big thing because
she, there was a, I've seen clips of Frenemies, I know. What's Frenemies? It's her show with Ethan
Klein, H3H3. Wow. Yeah. That guy's a genius. That guy's the smartest guy of all time. That guy
actually he he there are there are some pretty good clips from that show i will
say really that there are some pretty funny
conversations that dude's a master of putting himself in situations where he
looks smart because he has it's like him opposite the
stupidest person yeah trisha in the world yeah but there is a
there's a pretty funny video of trisha paytas like in her car and it was like
raiding my jew lunch it's her like eating different like israeli foods well
don't be a tease what you give it i don't remember
I just remember the uh well I saw the interview where Ethan Klein is like
you're not supposed to say that she's like well actually I can my husband said I could
I think she belongs in a zoo
well yeah does yeah well now that she's converted to Judaism
no no what I think she belongs in a cage
Jew he's no it's you
Jew
Zoo she belongs in a zoo
no there's a Jew inside of her and it's her husband
No, she should be in a thing.
She should be in a...
She should be in a thing.
What's a word that isn't camp?
A fucking enclosure.
Enclosure.
She should be in a zoo enclosure.
Fucking piece of shit.
What?
See, I literally...
I almost said encampment.
I was like, that's a bad look.
She should be in an enclosure with a bunch of gorillas.
You know what?
That honestly...
Will she like...
like like those uh fucking gorilla like puppets you know like the what's the
word I'm looking for and metamorphic the massive fucking AI gorillas hey I
gorillas oh oh the ones that like the ones from Fallout 4 what you know the
synthetic gorillas no from Fallout 4 I never played you never went into the
Institute huh I've never played Fallout 4 I never played Fallout 4 either it's
fine yeah it is a track they should sell more video games in Boston there's so
many Boston movies they make it so you can walk from fucking Concord all the way to Fenway
yeah Boston is like this big in the game yeah there's also you say there's a lot of
Boston movies there's not enough Boston movies there's more Boston movies than
most other cities yeah but there's not enough Boston movies every you're right
every movie should be set in Boston pretty much with with Donnie Wahlberg no
I've heard of the neighborhood where he lives the tagline of Southie is the most
dangerous neighborhood in the world. The Southie Project? Yeah. Yeah I think that
they should do like, I knew all more Boston romantic comedies. Oh like Fever
Pitch? Fever Pitch was a perfect movie. So good. Jimmy Fallon and Drew
Barrymore. Why Jimmy Fallon stopped doing all the movies man? He was crushing. He
was on TV. He was way better at acting than he is at doing that job. Yeah
Yeah, because he has multiple takes and it's not live so you can't see him just go like
"eh, eh"
Like a baby.
Don't you dare talk about Jimmy Fallon.
"Eh"
He does that on purpose on TV though.
That's not-
Yeah, I can't imagine laughing on purpose.
Goddamn, fuck that guy.
Yeah, aw, that piece of shit.
His laugh is so fake.
Oh, man.
[laughter]
What, it was funny?
That was pretty funny.
That was pretty good. What about Jimmy Fallon? That was a good laugh.
I sabotage every one of my own bits by laughing.
What? No, go ahead, Pat.
Hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee
hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee
What is that noise, dude?
Dude, dude!
I must just have, one of my burners must be unlit and just pumping gas into this room right now.
Yeah.
That's how it feels most of the time we're here.
This is the, this is the, you know, we had our sleepy summer episodes.
It is getting darker in here.
This is our falling asleep fall.
It's true, it's darker earlier.
Yeah, that is true.
Oh, that's why it's getting darker in here.
We're going from sleepy summer to weary winter is the problem.
the problem we're in falling asleep fall and then it's wow I need to sleep winter
and then it's so tired spring sleep spring yeah sleepy sprint no that's
sleepy summer some spring into my bed summer slumber some slumberish spring
and sleepy slumberish spring because I'm slumberish oh I'm feeling so slumberish
tonight why is it called the fall let's be crazy tired Christmas is coming up
Oh, you know I'm gonna be tired cuz I'm gonna be
Head on the pillow Halloween is that doesn't work
Trip to fan Thanksgiving, that's it
Yeah
The sleepiest day of the year Thanksgiving, okay, we'd be Thanksgiving sleepy Thanksgiving. I like that better enjoying my dream
Easter
Bedtime Black Friday. Oh, yeah
Yeah
Really tired Rosh Hashanah bitch, I'm sleeping Bastille Day
Erm I'm gonna go to bed on Earth Day. Yeah, are you honk shoe Hanukkah?
Are in bed Arbor Day
Like we are in bed is Arbor Day. Did they did they honestly make a holiday for a tree? Oh, no
Oh, I know that ain't right. I mean they got out of your laptop charger. That's Janice laptop chair. Oh
Can we just have one romantic night soon, yeah, can we just us three have a romantic night?
We have to do that if you guys showed up - all right, honestly, if you have had on a date a few months ago
go by accident. Oh yeah. I still remember we went to that Vibes restaurant. Oh you
went to Cream. Yeah we went on a date. So can I give one of you a date?
It's been a while since date night. Yeah we've been we've we've done it before we've we
both have. I've never been on a date with you. I don't think you two have. You may have
been on a date? We've definitely gone to places. Where? Where did we go on a date?
Probably went to a bar. That's not a date. Probably went to a bar. Me and
Caleb will probably... Me and Caleb had more... Me and Caleb had some breakfast dates.
Yeah, which are casual though. It doesn't mean much.
Yeah, casual dates. Yeah.
Might as well need a fancy date.
Yeah, we used to be breakfast buddies.
Mhmm. Breakfast bruddies.
We used to be the breakfast bruhs.
We used to be breakfast bruhs.
I used to look at my breakfast and say, "Bruh, breakfast."
That's the problem with Cam. He's not a night owl at all.
What do you mean?
He's not any kind of owl. The man's a fucking human.
You stay up till like 5am.
It's not that I'm not a night owl.
I go to bed at like 2.
You're like an early morning owl.
You, you don't, you can't, in relation to you,
yeah, I go to bed pretty early,
but I don't think that counts for much.
You don't stay out too much late, right?
Not really.
You're usually the one that goes home first, I think.
I don't think that's necessarily true.
I think I usually go home when other people do.
I used to be.
It used to be that.
Well yeah, because I lived an hour away.
That's true.
I'm staying out past like midnight now.
I fucking hate it, dude.
I like it.
I fucking, I hate it.
I fucking hate it.
I fucking hate it!
I love spending like $600 to get home.
Yeah.
Guess how much my Uber home was last night?
How much?
Eight bucks.
Really?
Guess how much my, uh, how, Zero, I walked.
Me too.
Nothing.
I walked.
I'm sorry, but I like to be manly.
That's probably pretty much treated like a king.
Like a mile away, though.
What?
From where, that bar to my house?
Yeah, after I took the Uber, I was like, "That's stupid."
Yeah, I don't know why I took that.
I was like, "Oh, that's so cheap."
I was like, "Yeah."
Yeah.
It took exactly how long it would take to just walk.
A very short walk.
Yeah.
And the guy robbed me.
Really?
He took every last possession I had.
Wow.
Yeah.
And then he came upstairs.
Came up here?
And he made me open the door so he could watch TV.
That makes sense because we've been sitting on the floor this whole time.
Yeah, so he stole every single thing in my apartment.
That makes so much sense.
Remember there used to be a wall here?
Yeah, I thought, I thought, you know, your, I thought your wife was doing another one of
those projects.
So basically he walked into my house, and then he went into Sims Bird's Eye View, and
he just sold everything, including all the walls.
So now I'm just in an empty apartment with no walls.
But he kept the toilet though.
Well he thought that was fucking funny.
Yeah, he kept the toilet but he also installed.
He thought it was funny, he was like, yeah, a guy who only owns a toilet, yeah that's
fucking funny.
I'm also, I mean I'm going into my UI right now, I am seeing that that toilet is, it's
It's not worth any money at all because of what you've done to it over the years.
Yeah, I've disgusted it.
Is that illegal to do disgustings in your own toilet?
No, but it depreciates the value so it makes sense that he wouldn't steal it.
I think that it should appreciate the value.
I'm just taking a logical standpoint to the situation.
I just think it's weird that he downloaded the Hollywood pack and put six cameras around
the toilet.
That was a bit weird of him.
Yeah, to buy the DLC just to do that.
the DLC and it's like it's not even like like it's like 360 view all all cam
quarters not even not the expensive ones to know because he doesn't want you to
resell them it's all 360 view of just like the toilet well that's okay cuz
then I can tape my shits like I'm doing stand-up so I can improve every single
time yeah and then I'll send them to venues yes and yeah I just wanted to
borrow bad bars and be like could you think I could do you think I can share
What do you think of this?
Here's a tape.
I'll have my manager be in touch.
I'd love to get five minutes in your bathroom tonight.
Oh no, sorry.
Listen, I watched your tape.
Pretty good for a beginner, but we have some heavy hitters at this bathroom who will do
30 minutes to an hour in our bathroom.
So we like to set a standard.
Maybe you work the door a couple nights.
Maybe you open the bathroom door for some people.
Maybe you're on wipe duty.
nights you know you gotta earn your keep here. I mean look at some of these posters on the
wall here we got Dom DeLuise you know that guy was taking insane shits. Mega shitter.
Lizzo now that's a dookie. She's playing the flute. She put some dookies in that toilet.
Yeah. Yeah. Shallow Hal. Shallow Hal is here. The character. He was here he signed it. He
signed his thing cause he shit in our bathroom. We don't sell any food or drinks we are just
a bathroom restaurant. I have had that idea before just in the city just like
they should make a store that you can go to. You pay like that's actually
actually, oh that's such a good idea, like a really nice bathroom. Yeah. Like in
St. like like bidet. Uh-huh. Well actually there's different packages you can
purchase. Yeah. One dollar you basically get a porta potty. Ten dollars. It's just like a
tap on the door. Like it's not like a. Also you can pay to just be in there as
long as you want. Yeah, it doesn't matter what you do in there. It's like the massage chairs
at the mall and it's on a boat in the water so it's international water so you can do
anything that you want in there. You can go in there, into that bathroom, as soon as that
door is locked. You can sit on the toilet reverse. I don't care what you do. You can
sit on it like a teacher having a heart to heart, right? But you're on the wall. Did
you ever do that as a kid? Poop, do a reverse shit? Yeah. No. Do that in reverse so you
to eat a hungry man dinner off the top of the toilet bowl.
The toilet bowl?
In the tank?
What were you doing?
Were you sitting on the floor and eating it off the bowl?
Eat a hungry man off the top of the toilet tank?
It's actually not a bad idea.
Well that makes sense.
Why is that tank there?
That's farm to table.
That's just, you know.
Maybe we've been fucking using toilets all wrong.
the guy who invented the toilet invented it and he was like this is great people
sit and they'll have a little place to work while they shit and then he immediately died and
then someone could tell no one knew and then backwards Dan walked in and sat on
the toilet and everyone was like oh that guy looks like he knows what he's
doing yeah well I know it's backwards Dan he does everything backwards yeah he
walked up to the toilet backwards. Backwards Dan. You can shit fast, fast as you can.
It's like he walked up there backwards, he was speaking in reverse.
Nobody could tell he was backwards, Dan.
They thought he was a genius German scientist.
They thought he was a normal guy named Nad.
Yeah.
Alright.
Is that it?
We're done.
That's it? Alright, well, uh...
I mean, unless you guys want to say something else.
Uh, I'm barely...
Boogers.
I've been eating boogers. Fucking a booger.
Eating too many boogers.