You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
Oh, I'm in so much pain.
Ow.
Patrick hurt himself.
Yeah, I did.
Hurt myself.
What? Did you- Is this why you called me the other day?
No.
Oh.
No, I called you yesterday because
I got to the skate park.
Like, I was skating for a good, like,
hour or so and then it just started pouring and I was like hiding under like
like it's this like community center next to um this like skate park and I was just hiding under
their like alcove thing and I was like getting wet no I didn't want to get my board wet I didn't want
to get my board or my bearings wet it could ruin it. You're afraid it'll warp into a Dr. Seuss board?
Yeah I'll have like a big like curvy like the nose will be like looped around like a jester shoe.
You could be like the goofy skater.
Yeah.
I could be the...
That's uh...
There's this guy Simon Woodstock in the 90s.
He used to do shit like that.
Of course, his last name was Woodstock.
Mm-hmm.
I mean, come on.
Yeah.
He would like uh...
Put like...
Trucks on like a big surfboard.
Like skate... skate parks.
Could do something like that.
Well, I mean, I'm out of commission now.
'Cause I fucking...
I didn't warm up today.
And I dinged my knee pretty hard.
You slipped on a banana peel and hit your knee on the ceiling.
Yeah.
[Laughs]
He got so much...
is the most air he's ever gotten is eight inches.
He hit his knee on the ceiling.
(laughing)
Maybe you're like the greatest banana slipper of all time.
Maybe you should transition from skating
to riding a banana around.
- I could.
- You know, just you on one leg,
going whoa!
All across town.
- Yeah, up the corner of the pipe.
- Holding onto the back of a truck.
- Yeah.
- Whoa!
- Oh God!
Somebody stop this thing!
I feel like you'd be better at that than skating.
Oh I already am.
I can, I like, the good, the thing I'm good at is making it look like I can land things.
And then be like, "Oh, today's just not my day."
Yeah.
That's basically, that's basically my whole thing is like I'll land something once or twice
and then like try to do something that's clearly out of my skill set and then people will be
be like damn dude you got that and I'm like I hope I do that's exactly how I am
with like pool I have like a nice you and I know how to like how to look like I'm
good at pool and then I'll just miss shots but oh sorry I'm getting over a
cold right now right oh yeah I'm usually hit every shot if skating was about
excuses I'd be amazing I'd be the top pro it is about excuse it is a jail dude
yeah yeah where you should be by the way I don't condone any form of skateboarding
I watched skating dancing I think should be illegal I watched Lords of Docktown
today oh yeah yeah yeah just again yeah what does it time do you think you've
seen that movie not a lot I don't know yeah I saw it like a bunch when I like
maybe like I've probably seen Lords of Docktown five times nice those are the
guys who invented who invented sitting in a pool and hurting yourself yeah they
sound awesome it is funny that it's weird like framing it like like the movie
frames it like Tony Alva was this like huge star which he like was in like the
skateboarding world but it's like he's riding in like limousines and shit it's
like it's making them like it's I don't know it's kind of gassing them up too
much yeah I think all skateboarders should be
taken down a peg yeah I think we're a truck I think we should be gassing all
skateboarders yep what the that's right up up yeah into the Sun yeah I agree we
should be experimenting on you guys like lab rats don't take it dude you guys
cannot yes you're talking about it's like the man and I'm no I am NOT the
man I'm going against no I'm the opposite of the man fighting the man no I am NOT
no you are not he likes being Amanda you are the man dude thank you thank you
yeah the woman he like he likes the system I feel like this one time I was
talking to to Neal's parents and they were like super Catholic and I said
something about wanting to fuck Mary from Jesus's mom and that's exactly how
they reacted is like when it's um when I talk shit about skateboarding yeah same
reaction is them and I was like yeah Mary probably had a wet-ass fucking butthole
and pussy. You didn't say that. You didn't say that. I did say I want to fuck Mary.
Why? Why would you? That is like the worst thing you could say. It's funny to mess with your friends parents dude.
What do you think I why do you think I'm fucking a mess on your mom every time I
see her. Caleb was like look I'm gonna go I'm gonna go mess with Neil's parents
then he goes over and he goes, "Excuse me, Mrs. Neal, can I have another Ritz Cracker,
please?"
And then he comes back and he goes, "Yo, dude!"
"Dude, I didn't need one!"
"I didn't need one!"
Yeah, he did not even do anything like that when my mom was here.
You hid from her.
I hid on her.
No, you hid from my mom.
Nah, dude.
Yeah, you thought so.
You stayed in the other room.
Remember when I walked her out to the car?
You didn't.
Remember how it took four and a half hours to walk her out to the car?
Remember how long that was?
You hid from my mom.
You stayed in the living room.
I didn't hide from your mom, dude.
Yeah, you did.
I didn't hide from your- I would never hide from your mom, dude.
I'd run towards the light.
You hid from my mom.
As soon as my mom and dad were in the living room, you were like, "Me and Julio are nowhere
to go."
I had to leave.
I had an appointment.
Oh, you had an appointment.
Yeah, with Manhattan.
Yeah, you had an appointment, sure.
I did.
With the Statue of Liberty?
Yeah dude, I had to make my time.
You saw my mom and my dad in the same room and you ran away.
No.
Why would I run away from your beautiful mom and your ugly dad?
Don't say- no, uh uh uh.
Your weak, ugly, short dad.
I'll stomp him to the ground like a Goomba, bro.
My dad is like way taller than you.
My dad can beat the shit out of you.
My dad's-
Dude, your dad's 80 years old.
I would break his fucking femur bone.
For 55, my dad's ripped as fuck.
455 he's 55 years old yeah I'm gonna beat the shit out of your dad no you're not
yeah your dad's a fucking your dad's Bowser and I'm Mario right now he's gonna
hear this dude my dad's gonna listen to this episode he's gonna beat the fuck out
of you pull up whatever your name is I don't even know his name is nothing to
me fucking dirt Eric Eric fuck you Eric like you could be saying that to my
brother you got to say Eric senior fuck you Eric senior well he's not okay I
I've talked about this before I think but he's not Eric Sr. because he
doesn't have the same exact name as my brother. There's about to be one Eric in town.
Okay is it only junior and senior if it's the same middle name too? I think so.
I don't think that's true. Well yeah but... Because my dad is a junior I don't
think that he his dad has the same middle name. But my dad says like well
he's not Eric Jr. when he talks about my brother. I mean that's
just him protecting your brother like you can't go to school as someone named
Eric jr. it's true like that's the end that's it yeah you know oh and my mom
claims that I'm not named after her her name's Patrick her name's Patricia
we had no idea weird coincidence right I guess it is mostly the exact same so we
have one kid Eric and one name Patrick yeah she's like she swears up and down
I'm not fucking named after her but when people called me a girl when people
called me a girl in middle school and people called me a girl now they're like
okay Patricia it's my mom's name it's my fucking mom's name you're gonna cry
about it girl I'm crying right now yeah my dad named all of us by just like he
did he did like he just like opened the Bible to a random page and picked the
first name every time that he knew that we were he was gonna have a kid he also
did the same thing with our dog with a with a Spanish to English dictionary we
named him amigo that's pretty good yeah that's funny go far is Hebrew for dog
right yeah yeah oh my god dad what did you do you wanted a dog not a medicine
yeah I guess so he got it eventually until amigo ran away mm-hmm
died probably got hit by a firework there's fire remember there being
fireworks that day and I as a kid I was like dude he got shot with a fire a
bunch of fireworks going up in the air and then you saw just a dog my cousin is
also named Patrick too. Damn. And he's the same age as me. I mean there's only so many
names you can choose. Twelve. Being Irish is the thing. Yeah. Yeah that is true. You
don't get a lot of options. My cousin Patrick is born like July 9th or something like that.
Yeah. And I'm July 23rd. So I guess like my uncle and my mom weren't talking or something.
And they just said you know. Your mom copied your uncle. How the fuck. Both got a Patrick.
It was the same year too?
Yeah, two fucking Pat- same year, same month.
Damn.
Two Patricks.
What the fuck is that shit?
That's the funniest Irish shit of all time.
My name was almost Edmund.
I mean Irish people are named with a magic 8 ball.
What are you fucking-
True, yeah.
Patrick, Colin.
Yeah.
They don't even have enough for like a roulette wheel.
Like there's only enough names for a magic 8 ball.
Yeah.
A die.
These are the two-
Seamus.
My brother was almost named Seamus.
if he was born this is a cooler name than yeah whatever his name is Eric if he was
born he's born the day before st. Patrick's Day so if he was born on st.
Patrick's Day name would have been named Seamus that would have sucked dude yeah
growing up in Boston named Seamus born on st. Patrick's Day I mean first of all
you have to be the mayor if we yeah if we stayed in summer well no he would
have moved to Boston yeah he would have had no question he would have stayed
there they would have whole I would have deported him they would have become a
mask Austin the mayor of fucking well there's no mayor in London there's only
four mayors in New Hampshire yeah yeah good for them only four mayors it's
useless job dude man doesn't do shit well for sure the mayor in my hometown
his name I almost said his name is build a Blasio but I don't think it is it's
Bill something guys a fucking bill nobody knows what he does and he's just
been the mayor for like 50 years all you do as the mayor is you just have to wear
the sash that says mayor that's pretty much it
ceremonies but other than there should at least have to have like a physical
fitness test they need to be like they need to be like extremely ripped yeah
you know our hot that's the governor no the governor has to be ripped
California's at the president no I don't like that that precedent I don't think
all governors need to be hot governor I think the mayor should have to be very
ugly yeah oh the mayor could be like a like a troll like a hunchback type yeah
yeah that's good too you only like lives in a tower yeah it's Punxsutawney Phil
the mayor he should be if if mayors acted like the hunchback of Notre Dame like if
they had to live in a tower and their job was they like rang bells and stuff
that'd be pretty cool maybe that was the mayor's job back in the 1700s and we
just don't talk about it it's just lost in translation yeah maybe there's just
just
the world I got some big checks to write right now. Dude we're gonna have a fair
tomorrow yeah that's right oh what oh oh oh you like the mayor now? The first
cool mayor looked at his giant pair of scissors and was like what if I
what if I use this to cut ribbons for new buildings instead of chasing children
down the stairs of my tower. What if I opened a laundromat with this?
yeah that'd be so sick that'd be some swag ass mayor shit do people actually like
me can I get a giant top hat and a tuxedo that I wear every day for some reason to
my mayor job yeah all these motherfuckers are wearing two glasses
check this out only got one lens yeah check it out one lens only need it for
one eye that's right I've 20 20 zero vision dude the sash is just it's it's
actually it's very tight it's a corrective it's corrective for the
hunchback yeah it's like a last day like a back binder uh-huh yeah yeah you're
taking that hunch out yeah that's true that's completely true yeah you can
fact-check that dude yep fucking call the infographics show they'll get let's
get Snopes on here come on Snopes I know you listen come on Snopes I know you're
in the room with us come on professor Snope
Professor Snope. Come on Snope. The inventor is Snope. Yeah. Come fuck with us.
Mm-hmm. Yeah. We should hire a live fact-checker. That is a good idea. Yeah.
We could get a like a hire like a like a really good live fact-checker like one
of these guys they hire for like the CNN debates. We should hire Pinocchio.
And then just have him sit in the in the call. Yeah. And just interrupt anytime he has
something to say. We have Pinocchio on the call right but he's muted the whole. Let's get Nate Silver dude.
Pinocchio's muted the whole call so anytime that like he's just repeating
everything we're saying so anytime he says something. Oh that's smart! That's very clever.
Until he knocks his webcam off. Uh-huh yeah well he just doesn't face the
webcam that's yeah he has to sit sideways. He sits sideways and then and then we'll uh and
then we unmute him when we have to ask him what the the fact is that we got
wrong right he what he doesn't know the I guess he knows because of his nose
grow yeah it's like a thing see Pinocchio could if he just said
different things out loud he could figure out so many formulas and
scientific rooms you know if you're for cancer is yeah and then just start
vinegar no it's not that yeah be careful someone's gonna call
Paul Paul no audio I was gonna cut that yeah no I I strongly said think that
nobody is gonna cut me saying that yeah no it's always doing right I have a cold
I got a really bad cold yeah yeah yeah I wish my lips would get bigger every time
my lide. Why? Just have big lips. Just be kind of funny. That's fair enough. You know, I
could talk like that. Yeah. I'd be like, how does lips get so big? Oh my god, it's got to
be thousands of dollars in plastic surgery. If you think about it, the word
lie is an allergy. So. What? When your lips puff up from allergies. Where is lie an
an allergy allergies plural there's a lot of word lies in there
around who else yeah okay all right yeah you're right that's a good point there's
also gaze so is that have it you have something for that no I don't have
anything all is in there that's all you don't have to move stuff around for that
one yep legs legs legs yeah gag which is kind of the opposite of gay yep when you
think about you know the more you think about the more you realize there's a lot
of words and the word allergies yeah pretty interesting you're really
bringing a lot to the table today I got it I you know I'd like to I like to get
my car I want to give you I want to give you the the ribbon of intriguing fact of
the day. Wow. You can pin that to your shirt. Oh my god. Hold your shirt away from your skin
when you're pinning it. Cameron the Mayor. No. No I'm an award. Oh Cameron the Mayor.
No, no I don't want to be mayor. Oh that's what all the mayors say. That's part of the
deal you have to be self effacing. Oh me I can't be no damn mayor. Oh I'm no hunchback.
What's that these giant scissors my hands fit perfectly in these? Oh it must be some
sort of coincidence Jesus Christ yeah imagine how big a mayor's hands must be
to kill this fucking system. That's so true. We gotta be strong. Do you think he gets back, do you think when he signs a bill into law he's a giant pen?
It's a two handed pen. I need you to, ah fuck, big checks, I'm all about big checks, big scissors and big asses.
That's how you make sure that nobody else can sign a bill it has to be the mayor.
true that's a good one.
Well, Diane, fuck, I need you to go to the aquarium gift shop and get me like six big
pens.
I, this one's out of fucking ink.
I'm all out of big pens.
Yeah, I should just get a big fountain pen.
I don't know.
I just prefer a ballpoint.
Oh, fuck, hand me the big stapler.
Hand me giant whiteout.
I fucked this one up.
Give me the giant whiteout.
It's just a bucket of paint.
Yeah.
tragedy struck last night as the mayor accidentally decapitated himself while
trying to sharpen his giant pencil with his giant scissors.
[Laughter]
Dude, that was always the worst, like...
That was always the worst when that happened.
No, just like sharp, when you like, you're doing your homework as a kid and you just...
Did you guys like own electric pencil sharpeners in your house?
No. Yeah, because my mom was a teacher.
Oh, right, yeah. I was actually from the ghetto.
Yeah? Yeah.
I didn't know they had electricity there.
I was actually from the ghetto.
Yeah.
I didn't have electricity, didn't have water.
We'd always have those like those fucking shitty like
scholastic book fair. The small ones?
Yeah, we'd have those but then like you know
you fucking like those break or you lose them
and I would have to like sharpen my pencils
with like a kitchen knife or something.
Dude, you were pissed off
about having to use a kitchen knife?
What kind of fucking kid were you?
It's the coolest shit ever to get to take a knife and sharpen a pencil.
That's literally the coolest thing. It's cooler to use an electric sharpener. I only had it's cooler to use an electric sharpener
I like the electric sharpener much better. You know those flat pencils that people use for like construction jobs. Yeah, yeah
That's the only pencil I had growing up cuz my dad was like we don't need to buy pencils for school
You just use the ones from work
And I had a pocket knife that I sharpened all my pencils with if this is explaining anything about me. Yeah, yeah
I always sharpen my shit with a knife
And then I put the knife in my gold teeth and I'd look at the teacher, say, "You want to give me a F now, Holmes?"
[laughs]
It was not good. It was a very offensive child.
Yeah.
I used to, I just hated teachers so much, dude.
Me too.
I was on a mission to destroy the teacher.
Oh, man.
Mentally and physically.
Did I, when I was in fifth grade, I just never did homework. I almost got held back in the
fifth grade because like I just didn't want to do homework but there was this thing called
homework club.
It sounds awesome.
And my fifth grade teacher like kept me in the homework club.
I couldn't go to recess at the end of the day because I was constantly in homework club
and I learned that her last name was like German and I came home one day and I was like
she's a fucking Nazi.
Dude, there was a teacher in my school whose last name was, she was Italian, her last name
was Be a Nazi.
Oh my god!
No, I have a good funny teacher name.
It was the lady at the front desk, her last name was Dabona, so they would go in the intercom
and say, "Paging Miss Dabona."
That's a good last name, though.
Really good.
There was a-
And you know they'd said miss instead of misses every single time.
Oh yeah.
Miss Dabona!
Miss Dabona.
Oh, drats, another one gone.
We had a teacher in my elementary school named Mrs. Pringle.
Why do people with the stupidest names become teachers and nurses?
That was fucking... the fucking... when I worked at the liquor store, the guy who...
there was the guy who was named Swastikar, and then we would always get the order from Swastikar,
and then also a guy named Jimmy Pringle, and we would get them on the same day,
be like okay you have to prepare an order for swastika and also one for jimmy pringle
damn dude yeah that's the thing before pringles were chips it was definitely just like a name
you had just a silly word like yeah name people had i wonder what um jimmy wonder where pringle
comes from the can it's too easy for me it's just too easy yeah well it's actually it's from it's
from it's from like colonial times where the every town had a Pringler
mm-hmm yeah he would hear people would bring him their chips and they would
bring him they would bring him yeah like flavor sludge and he would it's a
minute of various shapes I think it's a Scottish name because I found a a
clothe a clothing brand called Pringle of Scotland could be that would make sense
Robert Pringle established Pringle of Scotland in 1815.
Wow.
You guys have relatively normal last names. I was cursed with a stupid last name.
I have a teacher style last name.
Yeah, Clan Pringle is a lowland clan from the Scottish borders.
Pringle clan.
Dude, imagine you fucking, you're like, "Alright, I'm finally gonna figure out my Scottish heritage.
out of sheritage like I'm gonna find my clan I'm gonna go to like the highlands
I'm gonna visit their castle or whatever and you find out it's called clan
Pringle yeah and it's in a tube. I'm gonna buy all like I'm gonna buy the family crest I'm so excited.
The family crest it's like it's like some like it's like a shield with just a Pringles guy in the middle.
I'm a descendant of Lord Hostess of the of the Hostess clan of Britain.
My great-great-grandfather Tobias Tastycake did not come to this country for me to be a
fucking slacker.
Oh man.
I don't even know where my family is from, really.
I got some notification today from Ancestry.com that they found my grandpa or something.
Oh yeah?
And yeah, and the first thing I did was text my grandpa to see if he had like died or something
so there's finally a record of him.
But I just don't know.
Pass them.
I gotta do Ancestry or something, because I don't know either really.
Yeah, I gotta figure that out.
Dude, we can read it all on the podcast.
I did Ancestry.
I remember, yeah.
I don't want to give him my spit, dude.
I don't want him to clone my ass.
Well, no, I did 23 and me, but I also did Ancestry for, like, Lineage.
Nice, dude.
It sounds like you're brainwashed.
Yeah.
What's that like?
It's pretty good.
I found out that I'm a descendant of John of Great Battles.
Yeah.
Doesn't sound like it.
the FBI is gonna put your spit on the next bullet that kills a president dude.
That's right. Okay, sounds pretty sick. Being framed for the murder of the president just being like yeah I mean
it's good sure I guess I did it I don't really remember. Yeah I don't feel any
remorse. Yeah I don't see any reason why I wouldn't do that. It's kinda cool actually. Yeah you know I guess I guess if I did have that
bullet in my mouth then I must have done it. Yeah I don't know I mean why would I have a
bullet in my mouth I wasn't gonna shoot somebody with it doesn't really make a
lot of sense yeah I guess that's right this is the last time I've spit my
bullet shells out at the ballgame
have you guys why is it that every 18th sunflower tastes like a fucking asshole
you're in the Sun oh yeah the fucking sunflower seeds they're like the ones
that what's that wallop from camp how many of these can I take - there's the
ones that have like too much salt on them and then they like taste chalky
right why is it the same with pistachios why do you know why does every fucking
one pistachio in every bag tastes like fucking Shrek what is that about it's
probably like maybe Shrek could be Shrek get involved no it's one of the most
fucked up realities of life dude they should make a they should make an
article about that I mean they what they should do they should have to open the
shells of the pistachios check if they're okay and then seal them back so
you still get to like I've been saying this for a long time every single bite
of every food that ends up on my plate should be taste tested should be quality
checked yeah yeah yeah somebody sitting in a in a factory should have to chew it
up spit it out and then see what's good yep I don't know they get shelled
pistachios in a bag true they do they just sit in their mouth
it's a guy in his back molar and he goes and it just like shoots it out that's
pretty check to see if it tastes like Shrek mm-hmm yeah you guys fuck with
pistachio y'all rocking with pistachio ice cream when it's done when it's done
- If you put it on like shitily, it's delicious
'cause it just tastes like the color green.
- Yeah.
- Otherwise it's like a vegetable ice cream.
- I don't want that shit.
- It's a weird flavor. - I like it.
- I like it too. - I like pistachio ice cream.
- I think pistachio flavor, I mean,
the thing about it, it's one of those flavors
that I don't think really tastes all that much
like the actual thing, but scientists have somehow
created a chemical that just is its own flavor.
Like they created like a, you know,
it's the same thing with like watermelon.
- You know what I think it is?
I think it's I think some pistachio ice cream has like almond extract in it and I think
it's a combination of the almond extract and the pistachio flavor.
Yeah I think it's also that you never eat you can it's literally impossible to eat pistachios
fast enough to get a concentrated flavor from them because you have to shell them.
Yeah they just taste like salt.
Right yeah yeah most nuts do nuts are pretty overrated.
But you gotta love how those shells taste.
Oh god damn when you're crunching those shells.
I make sure I lick the outside of the shell before I open it every time.
The best thing is just throwing them all over your floor and stepping on them.
Do you guys ever wish you could eat an acorn?
Yes, dude.
Are you kidding?
When I was a kid I used to eat anything that fell off a tree in my backyard.
I would crack it open and I would eat it.
I've eaten like the inside of a pine cone.
Why do they taste so bad?
They look like they should taste amazing.
Yeah, how stupid are these squirrels?
Squirrels?
How fucking stupid are these squirrels?
It's a double R, you pronounce it like that.
These squirrels are absolutely foolish.
Anytime I see a squirrel put a bunch of acorns in a tree and be like, "Oh yeah, these are
all mine.
I'm taking these for the winter."
A squirrel?
Every time I see a squale put a bunch of acorns in a tree.
A squarrel.
It's called a squarrel.
It's what it's called.
Squirrel. That's what it's called. Okay, I didn't want to say it the normal way I say
it because I knew you guys would say it funnily.
What's the normal way you say it? Squirrel.
That's how I say it. I thought that was like a southern way to say it.
No, squirrel. Squirrel.
Squirrel pronounced like girl. Yeah, you don't pronounce the E enough anyway.
It doesn't matter. Squirrel.
now say okay now say pen pen I don't even remember which way is it right pen that's
how I say it pen you guys are mad at me now because of where I'm from this is
racism and it's not racism Monday I'm the rootinest tootinest guy on a podcast
I'm not root I'm a little rootin but I'm not tooting
I'm the tootinest tootinest guy. I'm not the double tooter dude. Shut the fuck up. You don't know
anything about what it's like to be in the-- neither of you have ever been to the south.
I've been to the south. No you haven't. I've been to Florida. Yeah you've been to south of the border
the Mexican restaurant you ate some nacho cheese. Fuck you. Sounds good. It does sound good. Sounds
like a better time. It's not a better time. The south is great. People, you can have a gun.
yeah i'd rather not go to the bible to the bible belt thank you very much no
thanks i'm gonna spank you with my bible belt keep talking about my hometown
my home country yeah we should do a civil war on this boston new england versus the south yeah
and i'm taking you down yeah i got two you're not i got okay we get the midwest also you know
New England and the west coast
Fine we get everything we get the entire world. That's not the cell. I get all the pussy States like California and India
Against you and India South you said all the rest of the world
India say that Cameron it is like snowflakes
Every everywhere, but the South what we get everywhere, but the South
Yeah, you're gonna lose. That's like seven billion people
Yeah, but he's got India now. No no you guys have India
Oh, that's why we have the entire world. I heard it wrong
Do you even know what a civil war is dude?
Yeah, it's a war between two sides. Yeah, Captain America and Iron Man. Okay. All right, I
Get to be Iron Man rich
Okay
I get rich on man. Oh nice. I'll crush him like an bug. Well, he'll get big - that's weird
I will crush him like a dinosaur. He shouldn't be allowed to get big. He should be a different guy.
They should yeah they call his name is Ant-Man but then they also call him Giant-Man too.
Like he has multiple names because they couldn't because they couldn't just call him like
Grow and Shrink-Man. Yeah if he's so big they should call him Elephant-Man.
That's what I think. So you're gonna just pick the biggest thing. That's why um at least DC had
had the right idea where they made their Ant-Man like...
The atom, right?
Yeah, the atom.
Because an atom could be anything.
And the thing is, that guy too, he could just be a normal sized guy named Adam.
So the name is really, it's multi-purpose.
But his name is Dr. Choi.
It's insanely, I would say he is the most fucked up superhero that they've come up with.
Who, Adam?
The Ant-Man.
Yeah.
The idea that he can like jump into your shit and rearrange your molecules.
That's true. That's fucked up dude. Yeah. He turned you into slush. Personally I think it's Captain America because of imperialism.
Nice dude.
Fuck. Yeah, you're not coming back from that one. Damn. You just lost all your political capital. Oh my god dude.
Okay, I also I think Red Skull is fucked up because of obvious reasons. Because you don't like Nazis being portrayed as evil?
No.
No, I mean the Todd Nishikot's
one the one where he's like where he's Jordan Peterson yeah he's like he like
likes Jordan Peterson or whatever yeah that's a brave as a brash move yeah I'm
further than brave that was brash I'm gonna start if I had that job I would I
would just make the Nazi character just anybody I didn't like dude yeah yeah
yeah just make like I mean that's yeah it's basically I'd make a I'd make a
Patrick one no definitely be a Patrick Nazi Patrick's goal hey what you could
rename him Patrick skull his power is that he can headbutt people cuz his head
is too thick yeah yeah Gabby Gifford she'd be catching the smoke for me who's
that that lady that that senator who got shot in the face and it's not nothing
personal but I just don't like her vibe really. She gives off bad vibes. She showed up to your
party dude she'd be like complaining about everything she'd be going to the
bathroom multiple times. What's wrong with going to the bathroom multiple times?
If you're at a party and you go to the bathroom you get one bathroom visit. No you
don't. If you're at my house for a bit of a get-together you get a single
bathroom visit. I'm gonna hand out tickets you get a hall pass and that's it.
If I was a comic book writer, every time a celebrity died in real life, I would write
the celebrity death into the comic and have everybody celebrate it because they were evil
in the comic.
That'd be a good way to balance out, like, you know, people are feeling really sad, they
could maybe read the comic and, you know, he could have been a super villain who destroyed
half the planet.
It could have been a lot worse, we'll say that.
Maybe if he had lived, he would have lived out.
Anton Yelchin could have done some horrible things.
you know.
Yep.
Yeah, dude.
He could have tied up a dame behind that jeep.
I mean, he could have destroyed the entire planet of Galactroid if he was still alive,
so I'm glad that he got crushed.
Why anti-Yelchin?
I don't get it.
I was just trying to think of the most inoffensive celebrity.
Just a guy who just, I mean...
Just total dog shit.
You can't say he didn't deserve it, I guess, because he did just like...
He created a rude gold person.
What do you mean he didn't deserve it?
- Yeah, he's like, "What are you fucking talking about?"
- Dude, anybody smart enough to fly on the Starship Enterprise
should know not to be crushed by a truck.
- I mean, also just like--
- It wasn't a truck, it was a Jeep.
- Okay, that's the same thing.
- You're so stupid you can't put your car in park?
- Yeah, I thought it was.
- I mean, I don't know the details,
but here's what I'm thinking happened.
He put a brick on the gas pedal,
swung that thing in reverse, and said,
"Watch this, I'm practicing a magic trick
"for the first time."
didn't work out. Oh look at me I'm so famous and cool but I don't even know to put a tiny
little door on my gate so if my car rolls down and crushes me against it I can open the little
door and crawl through and escape without being crushed. That's my impression of Anton Yelchin.
He should have had Scotty beam him up. Exactly. In a moment before. He probably thought that.
He just like looked at the jeep and was like "Yeah you think you're about to fucking kill
me with my own hey Scotty yeah he's standing there with the fingers over
like the Star Trek thing beam me up you know I gotta say he did a good job in
green room but he's down in a red place right now poor Anton dude man yeah he's
so good in green room he had a great injury humor though he would love this
conversation yeah you'd actually think he's probably smiling about yeah yep
probably as a some sort of demon gargoyle flings a pitchfork he gets a
single glimpse at the world above says well a clip of audio for any down and he
has a small smile on his face the first smile he's had in the millions of years
he's been trapped in there as far as he is concerned and he says you know what
you know what he says you know what I'm still still putting smiles on the
American people's faces even from way down here in Christian hell Wow so fuck
no no no it's fine dude it doesn't matter defend I'm taking it I'm taking
Anton's side you're gonna help down there with them Jesus that'd be really funny
I'm open to legal action oh I don't I'm not open to that please we're gonna be
screening all of Anton Yelchin's movies live on twitch we're gonna be doing
mystery science over the over the movies most of it's gonna be about you know him
be anytime he dodges a bullet in green room I'll be like oh well could have
been in hell there but he postponed it a little bit kick that can down the road
no I'm Pat I'm sorry that's your friend I'm really I'm gonna cry he's not my
friend I don't know him all right well do you have any friends that died we could
talk about this instead okay all right sorry
thankfully not Patrick well except for my friend Patrick Prince Philip oh he's in
heaven he's living it up yeah now he's in heaven God he's gonna have a lot of
those indigenous people that he put out of their misery immediately go to heaven
he's up there with them they're all partying first. Did you guys see that video when he's talking to
Malala and he's like he's like you know the funny thing is most kids don't want
to go to school. Talking to Malala just going blah blah bleh blah bleh blah you understand that?
He was evil. He just said shit like that to everyone. If you look it up, there's so many funny things.
He said to these, like he went to Australia and like the first thing he said to like a group of Aboriginals was like,
"Uh, you guys don't still throw spears, right?"
He's just like, he's like the worst guy ever.
Yeah, dude. Yeah, that's a guy that like, he should have been dead a long time ago.
ago yeah and British people like oh he was such a such a brave he's such an
example for the people yeah no it's like you know no he's actually he's actually
kind of rude he was an example of how to stay alive forever found a web page
here's a I know it's a premium but this is a list of Prince Philip's funniest
gaffes that made us cry with laughter and sometimes wince if you guys hear any
Yeah, yeah, let me know
He told the president of Nigeria while he was dressed in traditional robes on a visit in 2003 you look like you're ready for bed
It must be nighttime down here Jesus Christ
What a fucking insane per dude his just brain was just riding just going to visit like Native Americans that he sees the
the he's like oh you guys camping out here I love your did this is great I'm a
marshmallow they have the stuff with they have the thing with the aboriginal
men here and then there's a bunch of them where he's just he just says
something goofy like the Queen hates my guts or something and then number nine
is just tender times and it's a picture of him holding his kids and it says he
is well known for making gasps but Prince Philip has also also often been
pictured sharing tender moments with this family what website is this on it's on
the sun. Oh, well, fucking course, yeah. Oh, of course the sun is gonna give him great treatment.
I hate the bloody sun. They're a bunch of, bunch of buggers. They're a bunch of nonces.
Nonces and buggers to me. To schoolboy George Barlow in 2003 who had written a letter to
the Queen, Prince Philip reportedly said, "Ah, you're the one who wrote the letter, so you
can write then, ha ha." Wow. Damn. I mean, this guy's a real scallywag. He told, he told
13 year old boy you're too fat to be an astronaut you won't even fit in the
spaceship lad I'm sorry there's not enough thrusters on earth to send you
past the atmosphere damn maybe he was kind of cool this walking around London
you're fat you're gay I'm going home I'm going back to my castle you know that he
had like he just kept petitioning for them to put like a like alligator
infested swamp around the castle yeah Buckingham Palace dude he if he could he
would have like I mean he would have been it he would have still had like
trebuchets in the castle yeah shoot so much shit at poor people I mean if I was
in the royal family I would dress up in Knights armor every single day oh for
sure I'd be at like for sure yeah I'd be visiting the White House just like
clank clank clank clank no helmet yeah no helmet you have like amazing hair
plugs are you know you constantly no I get a king Arthur hair I'd get a Knights
plume in installed in the top of my head oh okay yeah so yeah so you have like a
big like feather yeah big red feather yeah out of my head uh-huh
yes hello president no yeah and there would be there'd be pictures of me like
walking out of the gym trying to be like incognito paparazzi pictures and I'm
trying to not look like myself but I saw the giant red feathers coming out of the
top of my head yeah you're in like a t-shirt and gym shorts but like under the
gym shorts it's like chain mail leggings yeah exactly mm-hmm dude I would be such
a good royal family member oh man me too no oh they would know actually no you
try to say go three of us together would would make a rule it would be really
great I mean it's not like we couldn't just start one true yeah wait let's be
the royal family goodbye yeah we can buy so we could there's there's a place where
you can buy a plot of land to become a lord I did see there's a there's a an 18
bedroom house in North Carolina, a palace that I think is eight million dollars.
I don't think that's a palace, I think that's called a plantation.
No, no, it's a palace.
It's a palatial plantation.
It's a cotton palace.
There's tons of shit everywhere, it's sick.
No, but it was like eight million dollars or something and like the monthly payment,
the zestiment on Zillow was like eight thousand bucks a month or something.
I was like dude that's like get my fucking 17 closest friends split $8,000 a month
live in a palace with a golf course on the property. Yeah but it's yeah
interestingly enough though 17 of your friends have to live in a small low
house that's a little bit off of the big main house. It's mostly a big wooden it's like a
like a chicken coop more than anything that they'd be living in but I get that
whole palace for myself dude I'm gonna be in there making cooking videos for you
Do you think you could live with like a fucking a ghost haunting you all the time in that place?
There's no ghosts there. Why would there be a why would there be a ghost there?
Do you hey Pat do you know anybody who's ever been killed by a ghost? Yes, who?
Luigi
Yell cheese
He was not killed by a ghost. There's a ghost in the driver's seat. Well, okay, you know what? Yeah, he was ghostwriting
You know a good point. Yeah
Yeah, dude, this is it he was in South Houston ghostwriting the whip he's swanging and banging dude you bang too hard
I don't like telling those jokes about him. I like him. You did like him because he was your boyfriend
Maybe yep, and you were at the scene. Maybe maybe I'll start a rumor
No one to deny it dude. Yeah, I'm sure nobody in his life could deny that. Mm-hmm. Yeah
What do you think that Jeep is?
What do you think I could buy that Jeep is it's in the same place that they bring the the ark at the end of Raiders
of the Lost Ark
That jeeps it like some like some some impound lot the owners like yeah, you know if you want to buy this
We'll get it all, you know cleaned up for him. I don't clean it up leave
Leave all that all the crap on the back. I that's mostly why I'm interested
That's messed up. Yeah, you know, it's not no it's not
It's a pay tribute to him dude. Yeah, I'm paying tribute right now
That's like one of my things I pay tribute to people. Yeah. Yeah pay tribute to somebody else right now
All right, I'm gonna need a printed out photo of Scarlett Johansson, oh come on come on
what exactly not that kind of tribute why that's gross I get that girls think it's
a little nice no what I mean I've been asked him but I it sound off in the
comments girls come on ever if I ever got girls could put I don't know poop on a
picture me or something I'd be kind of through here okay you're no you're
You're opening up a Pandora's box right now that you're not going to be able to close.
That's fine.
You're doing, that's going to be the fucking Hellraiser puzzle.
You're going to get poop smear pictures of yourself all the time.
Alright, that's what I'm asking for.
Put some poop on a photo of me, send it to me, and I'll tape my reaction.
You're disgusting.
Just to prove.
You're grossing me out.
That it's actually a little bit of a compliment.
Who cares dude?
It's just, it's not really him, it's just a picture.
Or boogers I guess.
How is that a compliment?
that's in your body if you want to put it on a photo of me I'll go oh thank you
that's very kind you you you gave a part of yourself for me you're like Jesus
Christ that's disgusting all right I'm not disgusting it's normal it's gross
mmm something gross dude yes it is nope if you don't like my foot all right well
would you consider it gross to lick your friend all over the face probably not
yes and yet it's gross to wipe poop on a photo of your friend what are you not
getting you what you probably you know that Donald Trump toilet paper yeah
it's like the highest compliment you can give that's it's a bestseller at Barnes
and Noble you know they only have like can argue a hundred sheets right yeah
I'm sure it's like half-ply - yeah oh it's like terrible toilet you try to
wipe your ass with that just gets sucked into your butthole if Pat thinks it
cum tributes are gross and offensive I have a John Lovett's cameo order I gotta
cancel.
Wow I came on his face! I came on his photo! Wow! The highest honor! I love it!
Do you get it? It's my last name. That'll be $800. Check please.
John Lovitz you simple son of a... You disgusting little man. Isn't he like an insanely right-wing now?
Uh yeah, I mean he went down the same path as like Schneider and stuff.
Dressed like a, looks like a weeble. Oh, that's your move. He's a little, he's a tiny man,
John Lovitz. John Lovitz, really? I don't, I don't know a single thing about him. He's small.
That's how he snuck into our hearts and minds, dude.
He is 5'10".
Yep, he's tiny to me.
Whoa, dude.
Yeah, that's right.
5'9" and a half, talking up at John Lovitz.
Oh, nope.
It's going to be talking down.
You're right, because you're big, dude.
Yeah, that's right.
I'll whoop him.
You're going to whoop him?
You're going to shoot to whoop him, dude.
Yeah, that's right.
That's right.
Hit him with the shoot to whoop.
Ooh, John Lovitz, you're not ready.
I'm just looking at pictures of John Lovitz right now.
How did that guy become like, what did he do on SNL?
- How did he become the most famous guy of all time?
- Oh, how is he like, every woman is upset.
Oh wait, I just remembered his feud with Andy Dick.
- I'm not familiar.
- You don't know about the John Lovitz, Andy Dick feud?
- No, is it like, who could stay in the closet the longest?
No, John Lovitz blamed Andy Dick for the murder of Phil Hartman.
Oh yeah, I do remember that actually.
Yeah, yeah.
He claimed that Andy Dick had given Phil Hartman's wife cocaine or something and made her go crazy.
And I guess Andy Dick, it was like a feud forever because they were both on news radio.
And then in like 2004 or something like that, or 2005, Andy Dick walked up to Jon Lovitz
at the Laugh Factory and was like, "I'm putting the Phil Hartman curse on you!"
Oh, that rules.
You know, I can't make a ruling until Rogan kind of gives his take on that.
I've kind of got to wait for the big dog to send it down the ladder.
And then I'll let you know who I think did it.
Could have been Jon Lovitz, you know?
Yeah, could have been Patton Oswalt.
Yep, I guess you're right.
Could have been.
Could have been Anton, dude.
True.
Okay, so I'm on his Wikipedia.
"Politically, Lovitz is a Democrat.
However, he was an outspoken critic of Obama, called him a fucking asshole, and accused
him of hypocrisy."
I wonder why.
Yeah.
If he's a Democrat, you know, I wonder what was different with him.
Yeah, strange.
Yeah, I don't know.
We'll have to look more into that.
We'll have to get our fact checker on that one.
Yeah.
Yeah, John Lovitz is one of those guys who like got famous on TV and then started doing
stand up and just sucked but just could sell out anywhere because it's like, "Oh yeah,
that's that fucking, that's that freak from television.
Let's go see him."
Mm-hmm.
That's always such a funny move.
Why would you go from being an actor to being a stand up, that's such a clear downgrade.
Yeah.
I mean like Steve-O did that in like, I mean that's a whole other thing I think.
I mean, Stevo's just like storytelling stand-up.
If you already have a good job,
why would you like fuck it up
and make it like the worst job in the world?
If you have a good job being addicted to whippets
and like stapling your balls to your thigh for money,
why would you do stand-up?
He was fucking on top of the world.
Yeah, oh my God.
There's no videos of his like lowest point doing jackass.
Definitely not.
I just don't get it, man.
That's great, good for Stevo though.
Have you seen those home movies of him where he's just fucked out of his mind?
Oh yeah.
And he's like, he recorded himself where he was on too many whippets and he thought he
was having a conversation with somebody and then halfway through, in the video he's all
fucked up and he goes, "I thought someone was here."
Damn dude, on whippets dude?
Yeah.
I've been there on Redditor.
Dude, he got addicted to whippets.
know how fucking hard that is? Yeah, that's nuts. It's fucking easy now dude I go to the
smoke shop they have giant whipped cream cans that are called Whippets and
but then it just says like whipped cream dispenser and it has like a mouth on the
logo. Well okay in like 2006 2007 this is probably way harder. Probably yeah you'd
have to go into the grocery store to empty out some whipped cream cans. Yeah.
Yeah just sitting there. I'm taste testing seeing which flavor of whipped
cream is my favorite. I actually have a lot of pumpkin pies coming up. So you're kind
of being rude by trying to stop me. Oh look who ruined Thanksgiving.
Look who fucking ruined Thanksgiving. Yeah you guys. Yeah I know it's January but
yep it's called planning ahead okay. It's called prepping. Listen if I leave all the whip
cream in the fucking can it's gonna go bad. I take it out and I
freeze it okay and I wait for Thanksgiving. I have it, I hold it in my mouth, I have six
Tupperware containers right next to me. I'm spitting a whipped cream into the
Tupperware then I throw it in the freezer. Can somebody drive me home? I've tested too
much whipped cream and I need somebody to be my DD. Yeah, Whippets is not good dude
that's not I never done with any any
inhalants I is not not my thing really
mm-hmm yeah it's it's fun but it's the
most insane thing to get addicted to I
think yeah yeah the last like fucking
like 30 seconds and it's just it's the
same as it's just it's not even that you
get like an interesting high you just go
like whoa it's the same entertainment
level and procedure as inhaling a helium
balloon yeah and being like exactly like
yeah that i would rather do helium it's like getting addicted to pong in 2021 instead of
like league of legends yeah it's just it's nothing yeah it feels like an early it's like
it's like a pong if every time you pressed a button in pong half of your brain disappeared
yeah exactly yeah yeah it gives you the same i would guess like it's probably the same
as like a runner's high as far as like how much you like it i mean i don't think that
It's just like standing up too fast but like multiplied by two.
That's all it is.
When I was in high school I was like, "I am going to try and get a runner's high because
I bet that shit is so fire."
And then I just got skinny.
It never got it a single time.
Every single time I ran I was like, "This fucking sucks.
I want to die."
Oh, I am a wimp.
Cameron, you're lying.
You've never had a runner's high.
I have.
I used to run in high school.
It's not a thing.
It's not real.
It is real, dude.
It's fun to run.
Yeah.
You guys wouldn't understand because you're short.
My oxygen's thinner up here.
You get high when you breathe faster.
Yep.
You get high when you're high.
That's why they call it high.
So what I need to do is invest in some stilts.
What you need to do is leave me alone.
All right.
You know what?
That's fair.
I guess that's fair.
Yeah.
Dude, my knee is so fucked.
Yeah, are you gonna go to the hospital?
No, I just have to
wait for this to go away. I think it's just I bruised
like something.
Time is time's oldest doctor.
Yeah. Dude, I'm
getting, it's so crazy how old I'm
getting. It sucks. I'm the oldest one
so you have to complain to my face.
I know, but I'm like
- Ah, fuck, I'm getting so--
- I'm 24, dude, Kobe year.
- I'm still young and happy.
- Second Kobe year, my first one was eight, I guess.
But now, second Kobe year, dude.
Who knows how much time I got left.
- My Kobe year's coming up.
Dude, when I turn 24, it's all downhill.
- Yeah?
- I think.
- I think you're about halfway down the hill, I would say.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- What do you mean?
- I mean, I think--
- I mean, Patrick, I'll admit--
- You peak at, everybody peaks at 18.
- It may be downhill after 24,
but you know, you could hit a pebble
and get some real air, like, you know,
like fall off the board and go flying.
- I thought you were a skateboarder, man.
Think about it like you're skateboarding.
Why'd you come down here?
- Dude, there could be a ramp at the bottom of the hill.
- Yeah, that shoots you up into the stratosphere.
- I saw your computer freeze.
- See, that's another downhill moment.
- You said hit a pebble and you just went,
you could've just hit a pebble.
(laughing)
- Yep, it's all downhill, nevermind.
It doesn't get picked up on my end at all,
but it sounded really funny.
- Yeah, my computer does that sometimes.
- Yeah.
- So it's pretty funny.
- Yeah, I don't know what it is.
It's like, for some reason my computer will just like stall.
- It's the government trying to access your files.
- It's true.
- Nerd alert. - That's what it is.
- I'm gonna close my ears while you guys
talk about computers.
- Okay.
Well now that Caleb's ears are closed.
- Yeah, we can finally talk about cool stuff.
- Yep, spider.
- Yeah.
(screams)
(laughs)
- I knew he was listening.
Sorry, I can't help it. I was worried that you guys might talk about spiders.
I don't like bugs, dude. Yeah, I was talking about the spider right behind you! No! Are you serious?
You're kidding. Yeah. Okay, now hit him in the back of the head. Oh, sorry. Oh, turn back around.
I don't like spiders. A lot of times I'll have dreams that there's a spider on my face.
Yeah? Yeah, and then I'll wake up and I'll be slapping myself in the face.
like a stooge. When I was living with my parents I woke up to like a spider
hanging in front of me. I mean just get it over with and put it in your mouth at that point.
Dude I woke up like I woke up and the spider was right there I just woke up and
just swung at it. You just fucking speed bagging a spider. It was like it wasn't even ah fuck I was like so scared it was like a brown
recluse that I like just I just went ah! I just punched it. Nice. And then it just I
I think it just ended up in my bed because I punched it and I had to like I just squirmed
at a bed.
It sucked.
I do not fuck with spiders at all dude.
I don't know.
My uncle, my ghost hunting uncle had a tarantula when I was growing up and he was just...
I used to be scared of tarantulas.
I'm so sorry.
You just like bring it around the house.
But he was like, I can't let it go because it'll like just like hide somewhere in the
house.
Yeah, that's what I...
That's my biggest fear.
afraid of tarantulas like when I was in like elementary school and then they like
did that thing where they bring animals to like the after-school program yeah
and they brought like a tarantula and they were showing it and they're like
yeah well like just so you know like everybody knows tarantulas if they try
to climb they can like climb walls or something but if they try to climb glass
they'll just slip and die and they don't know the difference and I was like okay
these I'm not scared anymore I just close the window you had to have the
realization that a bug is stupid yeah okay what tarantula looks devilishly
intelligent oh you're sure yeah it's a very it's why I like third grader or
something a tarantula looks like something that will follow you home it's
got a bunch of eyes you know how many glasses you can put on those eyes
exactly how I knew it was just a killing machine though mm-hmm
that's true exactly yeah I I just I don't I don't anything that I don't like
things that move too fast that's my problem but yeah stop me where you going
You don't have a damn appointment.
That scared me just a little bit, honestly.
That one didn't scare me as much,
'cause I saw you do it,
the Patrick one really scared me.
Didn't know he was capable of that.
- How about this, did this scare you?
- Waving your hand like that,
yeah, I just feel very welcome.
Pat is--
- I'm waving goodbye.
- Pat, stop making your wrist,
this is not coming across well for you.
Why are you hitting your chest?
Stop hitting your chest.
- I'm not hitting my chest, that's not what I'm doing.
- All right, well, we'll let the evidence--
- Oh God, I wish I could hit Patrick's chest.
Yeah dude, just one punch square to the chest.
One of the best things ever.
I wanna hit his chest from the inside.
(laughing)
What?
Get all the way up there.
Ew.
I wanna hit your fucking ribs dude, when I'm in you.
Hey Patrick.
Oh, come on.
Patrick, if we were in the club
and I was dancing up on you
and my tail hit you in the face,
what would you do?
(laughing)
Would you put it in your mouth?
Would you let me apologize or would you scream at me?
Probably scream.
I would love to have a tail dude,
- New erogenous zone.
- Yeah. - Right?
You're fucking sitting on the bus.
- I had a dream. - And you're like,
nobody knows.
- I was laughing so much about like, yeah,
just bullies like pulling your tail out of your pants
and being like, just pulling on it.
- Oh, come on, my damn tail.
- Oh, my life is seriously over.
- I had a dream last night that I actually like,
we were recording something or we were on a call.
You know when you have like those dreams
where it's like clear that like
you're just recounting your day?
- Yeah. - I think we were talking
about it last night where like,
oh yeah, maybe you should dress up
like Nightcrawler or something.
And I had a dream that I actually did it.
- Nice.
- I was just walking around my life normally,
like I was dressed up like Nightcrawler.
- Would you, did you go into an antique shop
and just hit all the china?
- Try to teleport, yeah.
(laughing)
- Hit everything with your tail, dude?
That would be the bad thing about a tail.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, it's like what if you accidentally
knock over knock over grandma's favorite cup just walking up to someone on the
street and behind them and favorite urn tapping them on the shoulder and then
just yelling BAMF and trying to teleport away it's getting your shit rocked all
right I have to go look at an apartment yeah I love you bye okay all right guess
I guess nobody loves me back bye I love Caleb not