You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[Laughter]
[Explosion]
Finally, everybody has a no job.
Yeah, finally we're all on board.
Finally, it's a triple stack, triple threat event.
It's kind of a situation scenario.
You got a job?
Oh, you got a job at the poop in your mouth store?
Yeah, you did.
You got a job at the crapping in the suck store.
No, you got it Cameron went to the doctor the other day and they
Form that they have they have hoops where his where his lips should be. Mm-hmm
You eat crap and you suck a fuck one and you smell like a shit
Yeah, you know you put a square crap into your mouth like an n64 cartridge you I'm gonna do it's like a locket square
I'm gonna jump inside you like a painting in Mario 64, and I'm gonna mess around with your insides while I'm in there
I'm gonna collect your star. I'm gonna collect your stars
Yeah, and I'm gonna get the power-ups in there, and then I'm gonna jump out. I'm gonna 100% you pal
What no you won't you?
You will never explore every part of my I'm gonna throw your Bowser boss in the lava pal
You're not gonna have a barrel. There's no I'm gonna go in there, and I'm gonna beat up your King boo
Hey, you got a little bit. Hey, do you have a little Bowser in you? Do you want one?
That's right, you have a Bowser jr. And you
Then you're going to jail
Yeah, that's right. You're going to for jail. He's a child
True. No, he's not. He's just short. Yeah, he's just called jr. I
Juniors are not all children.
Juniors can, like, you can be an 80 year old junior.
The Sopranos.
Look at his size, he's a child.
Look at your size, pal.
I look like Bowser sized.
I look like Wario.
No.
No, Bowser, you would be,
compared to Bowser, you would be a junior.
Yeah.
You look like, you're like a Wario.
You're a Wario-lit.
You're like a baby Wario.
They do have baby Wario.
Yeah, they just have baby Wario.
Yeah, it's you.
They have baby Wario now in Dr. Mario for iOS.
Interesting how you know so much about baby wario. Maybe I know about them. You have the most knowledge of Nintendo. I respect Nintendo know about them
So this guy really what do you mean by them? What do you mean by them? Yeah?
How many parentheses are around that them? Oh come on Patrick?
Patrick loses his job and immediately
He's like I have three parentheses on this and fuck you pet who even said them. I didn't hear it. You did when I
I don't play gaslighting Cameron. You just keep saying them. You also asked some weird question about if there was
parentheses under them Cameron. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And you lost your job. Also you're fat and you're bald.
I lost my job before any of you guys so I've gone through the most suffering so
you guys should stop making fun of me. No that's not true I quit my job in December.
That's not losing your job you quit it. I lost it. You quit it because you
couldn't help you couldn't help customers because you were too busy
you playing skateboarding games in your head and they can't even come up to the
cash register and you just be like ollie sorry I have to rotate the joystick
yeah you know you'd be like I'm moving the analog stick forward okay I'm
pressing the the left excuse me excuse me ma'am I have not done the 900 yet you
cannot ask me about the salads sorry can you repeat that order again I was doing
a Christ dare in my head.
Oh God.
Oh my God.
I'm so sorry.
Sorry, I'm grinding like the longest thing ever right now.
Just wait a second.
Yeah, I have to do.
Sweet potatoes.
Yeah, I got it.
Sorry, I'm actually doing a nose grind.
So, can you suck my dick?
Hold on.
Lady, lady.
Hey, can you suck my dick?
Lady, just shut up.
I'm on the not a spin mission in fucking Tony Hawk's Project 8.
I can't talk to you.
The way he comes up in your head.
You're like, "Hey, can you suck my stupid dick, you fucking bitch?"
I'm like, "I'm not a dick.
I'm a dick."
The lady comes up to the register and you go, "Hey, can you suck my dick?"
Who was that?
Did you hear that?
"Hey lady, suck my dick.
Come behind the counter and suck my dick."
What is that weird noise?
Nobody tell my manager about that noise.
He's afraid of ghosts.
My manager hates ghosts so much.
If anybody in this restaurant hears a weird voice, it's probably a ghost.
Don't tell my manager.
He'll get too scared.
"Hey, if anyone wants to suck this guy's dick, it'd be pretty awesome!"
*laughter*
"It'd actually be really cool if somebody wanted to put a hamburger in their mouth and then put his penis in between the buns!"
"I don't know, just an idea!"
"Hey, we're selling hot dogs today and by hot dogs I mean my penis!"
Who the hell said that?
"Who's a crabby?"
Woah! Who's this ghost?
Guys, I'm really scared right now.
Again, my manager is a shivering old lady.
Oh, my manager...
My manager is the lady from Ghostbusters.
of okay so you want to you want to tell you my guy
telling customers about you want to talk to my manager
alright fine let me call my manager hey it's okay that he's doing weird voices
and saying it's a ghost
see he said it's okay we shouldn't we should have never come to Jeff Dunham's
Taco Bell
(laughter)
oh my guy
That was good. That's pretty funny to talk with your friends. It's funny
Talking with your friends and just in doing a funny voice we do me and uh, do you guys?
Oh, yeah Cameron you have a job now. What's up? Oh, yeah
What's your manager's name and what is the address? Yeah, I can cancel culture you
My manager's we're gonna cancel culture you is Patrick Doran. Whatever happened is answer culture
Oh, you know next time next when the next episode right before you move. We're gonna drop your address pal
- My old one?
- Oh yeah.
- Okay.
- Nice.
- Wait, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
hold on, you have to--
- Poop lane.
- You can do that if you want,
but you have to wait a while,
'cause I'm moving out slowly.
- 'Cause you're leaving Dom there.
- My lease is, yeah, yeah.
My lease is up in August,
so don't do it 'til the end of August.
- Whatever, man.
- Whatever, dude.
- Me and--
- Everybody knows you live at 15,
1, 2, 3, Pennsylvania Avenue.
Fuck.
Me and Pat and Will and Simon were playing Val last night and we were all fucking around
with voice mod and it completely just destroyed my brain because Patrick kept doing this thing
high-pitched voice mod setting and they go
Leprechaun laughing
Voice chat and I literally like since last night just all day today
I keep like remembering that and just laughing out loud alone, whatever I'm doing
Like I said, it's fun doing a very funny voice with your friends thinking about that laugh
Voice mod is I bought voice mod last night so I could do it. Damn you dropped the $5.99 on no
- Oh no, I got a year subscription, I dropped 12.
- Oh my, wait, it's a subscription service?
- Yeah.
- Dude.
- So that's like a dollar a month.
- He kept making us lose games
'cause he was playing a clip of Reggae Happy Birthday.
(laughing)
And nobody could hear any of the footsteps or anything.
- I just destroyed the whole game.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
- You're not pro like me.
me and i'm not gonna came down to games to me games to me is about uh... into the
air
it's about making a sound that's how it's a patrick likes to pass by i_d_ i'd be a
perfect streamer
yammy and pattergan is jargon stream co-op
one-year moves co-op what
ronald reagan evil
wall
yeah are you sure you guys won't be your pants and be so scared fight of that
they were a little
i will be scared
you are scared and i see in your eyes
I'm not scared of video games.
You need to listen pal.
You know I'm not scared.
Hey Pat, there's a video game behind you.
Ah, that's right.
That's a little tee up and a home run.
You guys think I'm going to be scared by Resident Evil 2, but you know what scares me more is
Resident Evil 45.
You're scared of listening.
Oh yeah, that's good.
I like that.
scared of listening to like music before bed. Do you get scared listening to music before
bed turn on a little swans and then bug out in your bed? No swans doesn't make me bug
out swans calms me down. Cameron gets scared of uh. I get scared of happy birthday reggae.
Cameron gets scared of happy birthday reggae yeah. Dude it's the funniest like. It's such
a funny song they have like a accountant so every time you just hear start like drumsticks
together and just be like oh no the worst round of the game I figured out how to I
figured out how to import sounds into voice mod last night so I oh well before
I did that I remembered you remembered pants on the ground from American Idol
oh yeah of course yeah so I typed it so we were playing we were playing around
and then I we're playing around were we were we ahead I don't remember I think
we're very slightly ahead I think we're up by like eight it was like seven five
or something no it wasn't even that bad it wasn't he was really close we could
have like they could have won but I typed in pants on the ground
Team surrender
Figured out how to import mp3s, so I made them wait I made Cameron Simon and will wait for like
15 minutes probably for me to download and then edit it in Premiere. So it's just the song
Then export it and then import it into voice mod and then I had it
I had it like keyed up on a button, but the to stop the button you have to press like
Three other buttons. So every time that I would try to stop it, I would end up like playing it again
So it's just be like pants on the ground pants on the pants on the ground
Like a DJ yeah
And we played with this kid. Yeah, I should be a DJ. That would be a good career
I'm that kid we played with oh, yeah, there's a kid who's one you eats his grandma's ass
Yeah
So when we started the round I had I had pants on the ground playing and then I hit the voice thing and then I just
Said sorry my TV's on
Sorry, I'm watching a lot. I'm watching American Idol. Yeah
I'm watching the new episode of American Idol. Yeah, my DVR messed up and I only got about five seconds of this episode
So it's just gonna be on in the background of my voice chat for the whole game. Yeah, sorry. I can't I can't shut this up
Were you guys ever big America? Did you guys ever follow any reality show?
I did follow American Idol when I was in third grade
I know I've never followed one, but I've watched some I guess I never watched one like while I was on I
I remember my parents were so- they hated Clay Aiken, dude.
Oh dude, I loved Clay Aiken.
When I was six, I loved Clay Aiken.
Nah, they were pro-Rubin.
My parents were too.
They were so anti-Clay.
My parents were too and when Clay Aiken lost, I said, "What the heck?"
And my dad was like, "Nah, he was better."
And I said, "Shut up!"
And I got in a lot of trouble.
A lot of trouble for- Oh my god, you told your dad to shut up?
I told my dad to shut up.
I think I tried to punch him.
You tried to punch your dad?
I tried to punch my dad when I was six because Clay Aiken won.
Or Clay Aiken lost.
Damn, if I was him I would have just been like, "Oh, okay, I have a gay son."
Yeah.
My gay son gets mad.
He gets so mad about Clay Aiken losing, he attacks me.
Yeah, I guess I watched like American Idol and then I watched...
But who's the real winner?
When's the last time you heard of Ruben?
Clay Aker is he alive?
Oh Ruben's dead isn't he?
Yeah I think he died.
Dude I don't know what's going on
but I feel like everyone's dying lately.
It says here
What did he die from?
Did he die from being a humongous fat guy?
It says
um
Fuck where'd that just go?
Where'd what just go?
I've never seen this much white in your eyes.
I mean you were locked on.
It says that, okay it says here that Ruben is an American grilled sandwich composed of
- that's why my eyes were locked on because I was looking at his sandwich.
No Ruben Stutter is still alive.
He is?
Yeah.
Oh my dad must have confused him with Big Black.
*laughter*
I think my dad
I told him about American Idol and he was like "Yeah, Ruben died"
Your dad's fuckin' racist brain was just like "Oh, Big Black is dead, that must mean Ruben stuttered"
*laughter*
He must have died
at the same exact time
I don't know, actually a better version of that is that my dad thinks that's the same exact guy
He knows both of them. So your dad's like, so your dad finds out that Big Black
died and he's like what what do you mean Luther Vandross has been dead for years?
Yeah just him thinking that the guy from American Idol and the guy from Rob
Dyrdek's Fantasy Factory are the same dude. After American Idol you know the music career
didn't really work out he had to give it a job at a factory he's like he hears big
black died and he's like what do you mean the nutty professor is a fictional
character yeah yeah yeah yeah big black is dead which is sad I love to watch all
those old clips from Robin big where like every once in a while they just cut
to like them in the strip club yeah out of nowhere and it's just them groping
women for eight minutes in a 30-minute MTV show. It's good. Yeah, it's a great show.
It's the fantasy. What's that one he had like the the alter ego person Bobby Light.
His cousin drama. His cousin no his cousin drama produced. His cousin drama
is his alter ego. Yeah. No one, Rob Dyrdek's just like a schizophrenic and
And just everyone on that show is digitally placed in there.
The fact that that dude Drama is like a very successful owner of a brand is just insane,
dude.
Oh yeah, he's the young and reckless guy.
Yeah, dude.
I mean, he is like the supreme Marfan Syndrome cousin, and he just sits there drooling in
the Fantasy Factory, walking around looking for a TV to watch.
Rob Dyrdek like found helped him found fucking young and reckless which is like
a huge like PacSun brand yeah dude it's like one of the biggest PacSun brands I
think that I think the first one was rogue status if you remember that one no
I should go to rogue status was the one they had the shirt and it was the shirt
it was the all-over print but it was guns and then it was a rogue status dude
that shirt that shirt was fucking tight that way I had a truck fit shirt as a
kid nice yeah I got into because I was I was
so in a little way and that I was like I have to support him. I have to support
little Wayne. After Katrina, I had to go by TruckFit. I tried to, I tricked the
TruckFit social media manager in high school into thinking I did a
no-comply over the Carlsbad gap on Twitter. There's a, I can find it
somewhere, but there's like a very poor Photoshop of me doing a no-comply over
the Carlsbad gap and I said yo I just did this shit sponsor me and they said hold
on hit our DMS let me find let me find the exact thing it said cuz uh there
there was someone else in the replies it was just like yo this is obviously
photoshopped don't listen to him. Nah dude he did it yeah he landed it yeah I fucking landed that
shit dude you're a liar. No those pixels around the border cuz I'm going so fast
That's a blur line.
No, no.
Yeah, I'm actually bending reality.
Yeah, I look like a ghost because like...
That white outline around me and the skateboard, that's me breaking the sound barrier.
This was shot on VX.
This was shot on a VX1000, that's why.
Yeah, I shot this on a Motorola Crazer.
And so it kind of fucked up the picture a little.
I drew this with a crayon, so it's kind of bad quality.
It's a draw...
Yes, it's not a real photo. It's a drawing of something I actually did though.
Oh, you know what it is? Look, for example, here's another one from the time I was on the sun,
and the sun had a big smiley face. It's a picture of me doing a methadare over El Toro.
That's what it is. Nothing you just said makes any sense to me.
Yeah. Patrick just rolled two dice that had random words on all the sides.
That's kind of embarrassing. I had my in high school.
I was doing a bikini slide on Mr. Monkey.
I was doing a Subway sandwich on Crap Mountain.
No.
You were.
You actually did do that.
That one didn't have to be photoshopped.
But my username was cuteboy69.
So Young Money Worldwide,
there's a tweet from Young Money Worldwide that says
It says, "Cuteboy69, A, send me pics or videos, where are you from?"
[laughter]
"Cuteboy69, send me pics... from Young Money."
That's so... dude, Birdman was definitely behind the account.
He was behind it.
He was ready to pounce.
His baby was about to pounce on you.
I was gonna say like how embarrassing that username is but like because it's in that
fucking message I don't care anymore.
Cuteboy69.
Where are you from as the tag is so good dude.
Jesus Christ dude.
I just typed in cuteboy69 in the first pictures of penis.
It's cute underscore boy underscore 69. That's your old account. That was the it's the same account that I have now
Cute boy 69 I just see a roblox profile
It's this you oh this you
Yeah, this you know when someone says you to me. Yeah, you looking square as hell brother
Actually, they know yeah, if you look it up, it's just gay porno
Who would have thought?
Whoa
What yeah, nobody can find my Twitter at its its its butthole penis in my asshole
It's because when you search it, it's all this it's gay porno. That's my Twitter
The gay guy. Yeah, the gay guy. Have you guys seen roblox recently? They made all the middle the road
Have you guys seen it recently? Yeah, what are you? Dr. Disrespect? Am I right? Yeah
Yeah, I'm basically dr. Disrespect
No, they should have done went right when the miss doctor just mr. Disrespect
He had his medical license
Happen he's mr. Disrespect. No, we should have right when that happened
We should have done episode where we ended it like that or we put on a robot roblox
We could just do it this time and lie. Oh, yeah, we're gonna do that at the end of this episode guys
Yeah, we're just gonna do that weird thing. Yeah, keep keep looking out for it
Yeah, what does he say at the end of the episode?
It's crazy that in like 24 hours it devolved into this.
At the end of the video, it's him just going, "Fuck!" and then running away.
But like people, there's so much conjecture of people being like, "Oh my god, this is something like serious."
Like he like knows something and they're after him or some shit.
And it's just like, he's just like probably going to Facebook.
What?
Like he's probably just switching platforms.
Yeah, no, it was like...
And Twitch got tipped off to it.
Yeah, that's like the current and he got like the text. Yeah. Yeah, is that like he's been maybe thinking of switching to
the Facebook like gaming platform or YouTube and
Twitch just like got wind of it. They sent cops to his house. And yeah
His house. Yeah, that is the funniest shit of all time. Was it his house got shot with a BB gun?
No, it was a gun. Oh, it was a gun somebody. Yeah, somebody shot through his window
In the middle of him fucking playing a game and he's like what the fuck is that and then he's like you fuckers
My children are here
It's awesome. Did damn. Yeah, I'm sick. Yeah. Hey, man, you live by disrespect you die by disrespect
Yeah, you better be ready to get disrespected pal. Yeah, the ultimate disrespect to shoot a drive-by shooting that kills your toddler. I
Mean that's you know
Doesn't get more disrespectful than that. Exactly.
Exactly. Yeah, man. You're a doctor. You should be used to it. Hmm. Exactly. Yeah, you have a you see how many years of school
Did you do at the university?
I mean, I would have thought you was school
Did they not did you not have a class where they'd practice this where you practice?
I mean your gun shot through your window. Honestly, that's what college should be
College should not just be like watching movies and yeah
These movies should be like well we went to a very specific
College I see that I bet no, but I've been to two colleges and I think three I've been to three
I know more about
No, cuz you went to two fake colleges. I went to community colleges, which are more more fucking. Oh, I'm saying
I'm saying even Emerson college
Absolutely undeniably so but I mean like it's basically the same shit at like a state school
We're just everything is like reading a book and being like
Isn't this cool?
Like that. Yeah, exactly
But it should be you should there should you they should shoot bullets at your feet like Yosemite Sam and make you and they should
psychological
Experiences that huh? Yeah strengthen you and harden your resolve teach you how to use a Vitamix
I just don't think it should be reading your professor should should go what the blazes every 20 minutes and start shooting at your foot
and your professors should
Be able to have sex with you with no
Consequences. Yeah, I mean if you want to have a consenting adult relationship
alright
R.I.P. Mary-Kate Letourneau
I'm just saying man. You should be able to you should be able to get you should be able to eat your professor's pussy
That's my boy the movie should be taught in all
Columns boy also should be taught in all colleges
Today did they eat the teacher's pussy and grandma's boy - no
It's just it's just a hilarious kind of comedy type film
You know what's crazy is like there
They'll they'll show you like those like movies like the black trommel that fight the tin drum the German movie from 19
Yeah, quiet. Just shut up
Just shut the fuck up right now.
Just don't you dare say another fucking word after you say "debunchimal".
Shut the fuck up.
No, "deblechtrummel".
Shut up.
What about our German fans?
We don't have any.
Yeah, we do.
Hey, you probably do.
The name of that movie is this noise you make when you see a freaking woman, man.
You go "deblechtrummel".
No, but in that movie, that movie's about like a guy, a kid who decides he doesn't want to
grow bigger than three, or older than he is at three years old.
Like he wants to like mature mentally but not grow any older at three.
And there's a scene of just like, he's like an 11 year old boy, the actor's an 11 year
old boy, but they had him like simulate eating pussy.
And they'll like, and that's like high art, but then that's my boy.
They have, they have like a, they put it in VR. They make you watch.
Yeah, it had green lines all over it like the Matrix.
That, that is no different from That's My Boy with Adam Sandler is what I'm trying to get at.
That's what I'm trying to say.
I think you're right. You should be able to watch Dirty Grandpa in class.
You, I don't give a shit about the Criterion Collection.
They should do it, you should be able to do a Marxist reading of Dirty Grandpa for a project.
I need a Marxist reading, I need a Marxist- oh they're fighting back there.
I need a Marxist reading of-
Oh they're fighting back there.
Yeah but you can actually see them now.
Arrrr they're fighting.
Arrrr they're fighting back there.
Last time I played Sea of Thieves, worst game of fucking all time dude.
Yeah?
Yeah, the only funny thing to do in that game, which to me is the criteria for a game being
good, yeah is you just fuck it up.
I would be amazing at that game.
You honestly would, because you can just blow up your own ship.
Yeah, dude.
That's...
And just make everyone mad.
It's so fun.
Yeah.
That's the only good part of it.
Anyway, today I installed a light fixture.
Nice.
And I've had like a headache ever since.
Like it ruined my day.
Nice.
Damn.
I've had a headache all day too.
We all have.
I understand why like electricians are all like...
Most paid of all time.
paid and also like total like huge like homophobes and racists because I was
doing it and I was like I just I was like I want that's the explanation for racism
and homophobia all the problems in the world they just have a headache them
headaches and they just they're kind of irritable you know look I'm sorry for
tooth at my 2003 comedy special in the intro I did do I did do blackface it was
because I had a headache. I had a headache. I had a real... it was almost a migraine. I
could be honest. Almost. I'm sorry. I'd like to apologize first off to the Laugh
Factory audience for my headache induced behavior. You know sometimes I mean I
actually suffer from migraines. I said some pretty nasty things. Well let's not even say I did. Let's say the
headache said some pretty nasty things. My headache said some pretty nasty things to some
Afro-Americans.
Kramer saying that on Letterman.
Yeah.
But I do. I feel like
complete shit ever since then.
I was like, I want to break up.
I want to...
I was honestly sitting there and I was like,
"That's an awfully hot coffee pot.
What if I break it on the head of
Donald Trump?"
I thought that for a minute.
I was like, "Oh, that's how Eminem does it.
angry all the time because he's an electrician. And then he accidentally
electrocutes himself, which when he electrocutes himself, that's why his hair
becomes yellow and he turns slim shady. How many times did you electrocute
yourself? Over a thousand times and now I have a power. Yeah, which power? Electricity.
X-ray vision. Hey, you're looking great today by the way. Have you been working
out? No. He's looking at your penos. He's looking at my penos? Has your penos your balls
and even your butthole been working out?
Cameron's been working out his penis.
You've been working out your butthole.
With dark experiences.
I have been.
He's putting his penis through a dark trial.
Actually my penis is going through
an extremely tough time right now.
Yeah, it's going through a rough patch.
Yeah, your penis is a rough patch.
That's all it is.
It's like a piece of sandpaper sitting on your
mom's pubis.
You have crystals instead of penis.
pal. Whoa! Nice. I'm gonna use my power on you. Yeah, just try it. Dude, I did. I'm gonna reflect
it back like a mirror made of glass. I have two mirrors. I have 7,000 mirrors. I live
in a hall of mirrors. Yeah, you do. Cameron has shadow powers, so you might want to watch
out. I have shadow powers. You might want to watch out, because I can basically control
an orb full of darkness that could come out and fly at you. Hey, do you guys want to see
me run across the world and back. No. Yeah, do you want to see me do it again? No, I didn't
want to see it the first time. Do you want to see me do it again and again? No. I'm still
doing it. There you go. Oh, there's another one. Stop, dude. Oh, yesterday. It's distracting
me. It's too fast. Yeah, you're distracting all of us. A guy who does that trick to his
friend and he's like, "Want to see me do it again?" And then he's like, "Ahh! Ahh!" And
just suddenly a nail in the bottom of his foot. Or you want to see me run around the world
and then just suddenly there's a red splatter on the wall just to the side of him.
He ran two feet too far. Yeah.
You couldn't stop in time. Say it Patrick.
Sorry. No go ahead say it.
I was just going to say I left my laundry in the laundry. I left my laundry in the washing
machine for like 36 hours. So it smells good? Yeah it smells really good. It means it's really
clean. Yeah dude. I don't understand that. Why does water make it smell bad if you leave
it in there? I don't know. Can we get a scientist to explain this? Okay here, let me try to explain
this to the best of my ability. Okay break down the molecule science. Alright so what
lives in water? Uh your mom. Pee, no pee. No. A poop. No, water lives in pee. What lives
in water? Frog? Yes. So now you can understand why it might smell like that. Oh, there's
a big frog that makes it stinky. Oh, alright, now I'm understanding. And what does a frog
eat? A fly, okay? And when do flies fly around something? All the time. When it smells bad.
Oh, true. I learned that from Rishi Tripes.
If you think about it, so that's why water does what it does.
Because flies smell it?
Flies smell crap.
Flies can fly around crap, which is the water a frog lives in the water
than the frog and the fly and the clothes.
When a frog eats a crap...
You better watch out.
When a frog eats...
You better not cry.
Did you guys know that frogs' tongues don't shoot out?
Yeah.
Pretty crazy.
It just looks like that.
that
don't leap. Did you guys know that elephants don't-
Did you know that if you kiss a frog it won't turn into a prince?
Yeah, you've tried. Yeah, you figured that out then.
Hey, oh, Patrick, Patrick, I know you went and tried that, but actually have you tried
fucking and sucking off the frog instead? Yeah, I hear that works.
Because I think that might work. No.
Go try it out, dude. I just burped. And it hurt.
I burped and it hurt. I burped and it hurt.
God, did you see that fucking, that picture of the guy-
I've seen every photo.
The one where it's like, "Diss for all my hippies and young rastas on the TL, dread that shit
up man."
Yeah, I did see that.
What is it?
It's just some like white kid with dreads.
It's you.
It is, it's Patrick.
No, dude, it looks, Caleb, Caleb, this is an alternate future of you.
Oh my god, dude.
I, I, growing up, so I went to, I went on a, a cruise.
If you got really into wearing pumas.
When my parents got divorced, I went on a cruise and uh.
The nice older man.
To the Bahamas with my daddy.
And when I got there I was like, "I'm gonna move here when I get older."
And then I just had this entire life planned out in my head and I was like, "I'm gonna
get big ass dreadlocks, I'm gonna put them up in a bun, I'm gonna wear like a cool drug
rug like Jamaican flag hoodie everywhere I go, and I'm gonna work playing steel drums
on the street and it's basically gonna be paradise.
And then I started losing my hair and I gave up.
But until then, that was what I was working for.
You should grow out the hair.
You should have dreadlocks made out of two strands of hair.
Dreadlocks just with the long hairline.
Whatever grows out of your hair.
Oh, like a tonsure?
Yeah, a tonsure.
Like not a tonsure, but also dreads?
Just dreads.
Dreads all around.
Dreads?
Yeah, but like a bowl in the middle.
Let me see if that exists.
Dude you could call yourself the higher friar.
Oh my god.
You gotta do it now.
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah.
You have like a monk's robe but it's a drug rug just brown all the way down.
There's a picture.
I can't even laugh at that.
There's a picture of a little kid.
Like the first google image result is a taunter with dreads.
That's so sick dude.
I'm gonna.
Damn.
I'm gonna get that.
I wish I looked like that.
Damn.
You will.
It looks sick.
Uh oh.
This is a picture of a guy with a tonsture and then he's got a swastika drawn on his head.
Oh, come on, dude.
This guy is a freaking Nazi guy?
Come on, dude.
Wipe that off.
Wipe that off your head.
Shampoo.
Use head and shoulders.
You know what?
That kind of reminds me of Adolf Hitler.
Yeah.
There's something about this.
There's something about this funky S on this bathroom stall that reminds me of the Adolf
Hitler guy from movies.
Y'all this crazy multiplication sign is giving me some unsafe vibes.
Something about this, it's just reminding me so much of Adolf Hitler from Inglourious
Bastards.
Whatever happened to that guy?
This crap is reminding me of the villain from Call of Duty 5.
I swear.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's pretty much Hitler.
Yeah, pretty much.
Yeah, Patrick's pretty much Hitler.
Yeah, I would agree with that.
Not Hitler.
I would agree with that.
are I'm looking at you right now and if you did go Hitler stash which you could
if I did no I would love to do that you would look just like him there's a
patch right here let's do let's do our own Jojo rabbit and Patrick true Hitler
goofy oh yeah I'm gonna play Hitler Hitler it's me Hitler it's me me
Hitler yeah you're not really gonna like what I have to say about the Jewish
people but I'm kind of a crazy I'm kind of a crazy silly kind of Hitler character
like a silly Hitler yeah and I'm kind of like not normal but it's kind of fun
this movie's kind of gonna make you laugh but also kind of it makes you cry
a little bit kind of makes you think it's a new it's a new type of comedy I
love I love when I get in at all I love when I get we all have stupid voices and
I'm just thinking about Hitler yeah I'm just right I'm just like finally a movie
that makes me think about Hitler.
You know?
- That movie was not good. - It's a movie
that's making me reflect.
Like really just investigate,
how do I really feel about Hitler?
- Hey, here's my new movie.
- Hey, you know what?
He is kind of funny in this,
so maybe I was wrong all along.
- If that's really what he sounded and looked like,
you know, he doesn't seem like that bad of a guy.
- Yeah.
- Hi, it's me, it's me, Taka Watiti,
and this is my new movie,
Eagle versus Shark versus the Axis Powers.
(laughing)
- Yeah, he should just keep doing that.
where he just plays a silly version of a bad guy.
- Yeah.
- I'm Dylan Roof.
Nice to meet you.
(laughing)
- Yeah, it's me Dylan Roof and I got a funny haircut.
- Taika Waititi is absolutely flipping
the Dylan Roof character on his head.
(laughing)
- Oh, he doesn't do it.
- Just Taika Waititi with a blonde bowl cut.
(laughing)
- Going to chitch.
I'm going into this church real quick.
- Yeah.
Talk about Christchitch.
- My hometown.
- Yeah, basically we made that movie.
- Yeah, we made Jojo Rabbit.
We wrote it.
- Yeah, how about Jojo's Bizarre Rabbit?
- Hitler.
- Jojo's, how about Hitler Rabbit?
How about that?
And it's a big rabbit with that is Hitler.
Okay. Hitler da bunny.
Hitler, yeah. There we go. Hitler da bunny.
Yeah. That's not bad.
What if instead of the Easter bunny it was Hitler?
And we got a chocolate Hitler for Easter.
Wouldn't that suck, dude?
That'd be awful, dude.
Just sitting at the bus stop getting pissed off at that thought.
That would suck so bad. Hey, come here. Hey you, what's your name?
Have you thought about this? What if instead of the Easter Bunny, we actually we had a Hitler instead? What the hell is that?
dude
I would
I would melt I would I would leave that my god chocolate Hitler in the Sun
I would let it melt and I would let it melt serious and you know, there would be people who would like it
You know there'll be people who would enjoy it.
Some sick fucking piece of crap
who thinks it's awesome.
Some piece of shit.
Some jerk would want us to celebrate it every year.
Yeah, just, uh, okay, if everybody could just go around the class and say their name, their age,
and one fun fact about themselves.
Uh, yes, my name's Caleb, I'm 23 years old,
and I just would hate it if we had Hitler instead of the Easter Bunny, I'd be so mad.
Yeah, and then when after everyone else gives their fun facts, and they're just like yeah
I I actually lived in France for five years and then at the end you're like wow interesting how nobody else said anything about
Truth in it and Hitler was instead the Easter Bunny instead of the Easter Bunny that a lot of the people in this class
Yeah might actually be okay with yeah seems like this get over here in the fucking mirror. Let's get over here
France for five years, okay
(laughter)
- Are we gonna talk about this in the class at all?
Are we gonna talk about it?
Hitler was the Easter Bunny in this class at all?
- This is, this is--
- I've done a lot of reading on the subject.
- This could be computer science, I'm just saying.
It could be--
- This class is about, this class is about gender.
This is about gender.
- This is math concepts. - Hitler was a boy?
- Okay, well, Hitler rounded up people regardless of gender.
And if you changed him--
- Yeah, which I honestly respect.
inclusive but honestly if like he was the Easter Bunny though like seriously we
should talk about it yeah okay okay if we can't talk about him as the Easter
Bunny can we at least admit that it wouldn't be all that awesome if he was a
tooth fairy can we at least admit that much because I here's one thing do you
want Hitler's freaking nasty little grubby hands under your pillow at night
and think about it where where where are those where are those coins coming from
Exactly. Whose coins are those? What kind of people's coins are those? I don't know, it's just a good question to ask.
Yeah, it's just something to think about.
It's something to think about. What about instead of your birthday every day you had to celebrate Hitler instead?
Wouldn't that be total crap on a stick? Wouldn't that be so shitty?
Oh my god. It would friggin suck.
You know guys, your silence is speaking volumes right now.
Everyone in this class who's just looking at me with really wide-eyed and red-faced and
not saying anything.
And I see, hey, Mr. Professor, I see you picking up your cell phone and trying to call someone
right now, alright?
Your silence is speaking volumes right now.
I hope that you are calling the Anne Frank Museum to make a donation right now.
I'll say this, I'm just gonna say this about it.
If we're gonna take down all these statues of Robert E. Lee and Colonel Mustard, we have
to take down the Hitler statue that's in my house.
I'm just saying.
If we're gonna do all this, then I'm gonna need three or four volunteers, completely unpaid,
to help take down this 20-foot Hitler statue in my front lawn.
You guys need to get rid of all my dad's stuff.
Seriously.
I'm serious.
Yeah, seriously.
If we're gonna be taking down all these statues, can we at least fucking...
Can I get rid of my dad's crap?
Can we get rid of all my dad's weird crap that he has?
All my dad's weird Hitler crap that he has.
Yeah.
Man, we've been talking about Hitler for so long.
Dude, I mean, it's the best.
It's just, it's so funny that like, I do think about a lot like how every, every like
Post online from like 2009 to 2012 was like oh yeah Hitler was epic
Like every pose like every like
Every fortune pose is like yeah, just like man hitler
It's like a Hitler pun. It's like so sick dude like I'm trying to start a revival yeah Hitler
No
Dude, do not let the voodoo magicians here. Well, honestly look look what happened. Look what happened when we let
Hitler just become a punchline
That's right. He's yeah, he's back. Yeah, he's back and he's bigger than ever back now. He's back orange
He's back and he's black. He's back. He's got a robot arm this time in an eyepatch. Yeah
He's made out of or any speak Spanish. Uh-huh because of his time in Argentina
Hitler being like I am a white Latino
That's literally that's literally a character in a Rob Zombie movie there's the he has a midget who speaks Spanish who dresses as Hitler and
kills people
Yeah, it's you yeah, no it's not but nice try
Dude, I mean, I mean honestly though like there. There's a whole like the honestly though Hitler was straight wack
Like we got it. We got to make sure we put that at the end here like we you know that motherfucker was busted
I'll say get out of here fucker fucker. Just hit the spring out of here. Yeah, yeah, yeah, damn my fucker hit the spring
Hitler hit the spring and he jumped up
Yes, Hitler's tick tocks are very funny, but we're not following anymore. Mm-hmm. I'm unfollowing Hitler today
Or cancel him.
Yeah.
Cancel Hitler.
Yeah, nowadays Hitler would probably be cancelled if you think about it.
Yeah.
I mean, it's so crazy just like there are people who just get mad at jokes about Hitler
now just because of like...
Yeah, people...
I think that...
I feel like jokes about Hitler are...
Nobody cares anymore.
I don't know because there are some like kind of like woke, scoldy people who are like,
like oh like the making jokes about Hitler legitimizes him or something or
like or like you know like the Hitler he already got legitimized yeah I would say
honestly too legit to quit you'll say what you will about Hitler man he was
too legit to quit no but I seriously don't like him yeah I don't I don't like
Hitler let me I see that listen I think he's a fucking knucklehead
Let me, let me, all right, clean take right now.
Clean take, all right.
Podcast about list, podcast about list,
hates the only podcast in the world that hates Hitler.
No other podcast is saying this.
No other podcast has said this.
I know everyone else is afraid to say it.
Hey, chopper, we'll be waiting.
Yeah, yeah.
If you choose to--
Felix, I know you're listening to this, Felix.
I know you're listening, you can condemn Hitler.
Yeah.
Then, yeah, just--
Well, I mean--
Yeah, we'll be waiting for you.
be waiting for your Easter episode, okay? We're waiting on your Hitler condemnation and your
Biden endorsement. That's the two things we're waiting on. And we want them at the same time.
Same breath. If you do them at the same time, you're just going to be copying us because
we're also right now... Because we're also endorsing Adolf Hitler. Fuck Joe Biden. No,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
president. That's right. Yeah, we, uh, well, you know, we hate Hitler, but just as much
as we hate Hitler, we hate copycats too. I think maybe the funniest t-shirt that you
can wear is just a white t-shirt in Helvetica that says "I hate Adolf Hitler." Or like
it just says Hitler and has like the "no" sign. Just a red circle with a strikethrough.
Because you know people would get mad at that.
Yeah, which is that's what would be funny about it.
Like what is, what are you mad at?
Oh you're mad at me not liking Hitler?
Is that it?
Yeah.
Oh okay, you want me to wear my other shirt?
Is that it?
Let me, I have two drawers.
One, one all I hate Adolf Hitler, one all I love Adolf Hitler.
The other drawer is just an SS uniform.
It's a dress code.
Yeah, you do have that due to your Nazi ways.
Okay, let me flip this shirt inside out.
It's just a photo of Hitler with no X over it.
With a thumbs up emoji.
A face-apped smiling Hitler with a thumbs up emoji.
We gotta stop talking so much about Hitler.
I don't want...
Yeah, I don't want to give his name power.
I hear if you say someone's name a hundred times it brings them back to life from the
dead.
more than once I mean you have to say his name three times to bring him up but
then to get a say in your times again it's just like beetlejuice where you
have to say it three times for him or bloody Mary I was so terrified of
bloody Mary until yesterday yeah you told us about your bloody Mary
fear I'm afraid of the drink bloody Mary yeah I'm kind of dude I would never I've
never had one of those I don't think I ever will yeah it looks like tomato juice
No, I do it you know me you know how bad my fucking heartburn is like I don't wanna like
There do you guys have foods that like you don't like but you want to like so you eat anyway? Yeah? Yeah?
I'm like that is I don't like
That's most of my fucking diet basically like like
tomato juice in like a like a
What's it called a michelada? Oh?
Yeah
A Michelin tire?
A Michelin tire, the kind of tire...
No, it's like a beer with like tomato juice and like spices in it.
But because I just think it's cool, I'm like, "Yeah, I'll have one of those."
And then I drink it and I'm like, "This is the worst thing I've ever had."
Yeah, dude, it's fucking beer and tomato juice.
A Bloody Mary tastes like fucking shit.
You know in Canada they call them Caesars?
You know in Germany they called them Adolf Hitler's?
is the one thing we will change. We will change most things. We removed all the flags, we removed
all the statues. We have changed our theme song. We have changed. Yeah I love how Germans talk.
We have changed our theme song, we have changed everything else.
And then they had to change it. Now it's uh...
We have changed all the names of the highways.
We have changed everything. We now have a synthesizer
that plays our national anthem every two minutes.
But we will not change the fact that the Bloody Mary is called a Hitler.
Yeah, no, he does suck though.
Yeah. He sucks a penis, dude.
And we're not being... we're not joking when we say Hitler sucks.
are not you and Caleb and I are not joking about it when we say that me and
Cameron hate Hitler yeah I do too and Patrick I said a lot of jokes I want to
put that out there right after that you're a very funny guy
you're a goofball you're like emo Phillips dude you just everything you
say just makes me roll yeah and I just want to I just want to I just want to
put out there after Patrick said that that Patrick has a twin brother that
always tells the truth you said you said emo Phillips and that and then I was just
I in my head I was imagining no emo like all right emo Phillips literally Dylan
roof that is him a hundred percent oh I'm thinking they're not gonna replace
Have you seen him in UHF? Emo Phillips? Oh dude I've seen UHF like a hundred times. I think I've seen that movie more than any other movie.
Speaking of just like anti-semitism. Is there anti-semitism in UHF? No there was
anti-semitism in my uncle. I know I mean I know he was. Is Weird Al Jewish?
sure did yeah yeah his name is I thought he was a I thought he's a fake Jew no I
just want to just well I well he's a Christian now I don't know much yeah
just well just once it's still a little bit I just want to say Zemo Phillips
like the Nazi scientist Zemo from the Marvel Comics that's my parents that's
Cameron's pun of the day nice he's not Jewish he's lying that's a parody dude
He was doing his parody, his famous parody.
Um, what was I gonna- oh, so my uncle, like, he was obviously, like, doing it to get a rise out of me.
He was doing it to get a rise out of you?
He walked up to- while I was watching UHF and pointed at the screen at Weird Al and went,
"J-O-O" and then left the room.
I think about that every time I watch UHF now, so he did some fucking psychological warfare on me.
Yeah, dude, he wrecked your mind.
He wrecked my-- my uncle wrecked my mind.
No, he's not Jewish, dude.
He's not.
That makes that, like, a little bit funnier.
Yeah, dude, he's not Jewish at all.
He's fucking-- he just has an accordion.
He's just like-- he's just, like, kind of weird.
Yeah, he's kind of--
It's funny that he made that song, he did that song Pretty Fly for a Rabbi.
Wait, so Weird Al has not, never been Jewish?
No, he's not Jewish.
That's crazy.
He's never.
I just did a deep dive.
I thought he was Jewish the whole time.
No, dude, he wasn't Jewish.
That Pretty Fly for a Rabbi thing is way funnier now.
That he's just some guy who's like, "Yeah, I'll just do a whole song making fun of Jewish people."
Why not?
That's like if his parody of Bad by Michael Jackson.
He's never, never been Jewish.
Instead of fat, he made a song called Black.
It was like, "Yeah, I'm black. I'm black."
Are you-- wait.
He's not Jewish, dude. He's never been Jewish.
He's not Jewish. He's just got like a-- does he have like a Polish last name?
Seems like it.
His name is Weird Al. Is Weird a Polish name?
Yankovic.
Yeah, Weird is a Polish-- no, he plays pocas.
so I thought he was Polish. I don't know. I think he's just like a- His whole thing is polka, so.
He's really honestly kind of handsome. If he didn't have- Oh, Weird Al's hot! If he didn't have girl
hair. Weird Al was hot in UHF. People have been talking about this on Twitter, online.
Huh. He's Yugoslav. Oh. And he's not- He's Italian and English. You hear-
You hear pretty fly for a rabbi and you just think like he's just like
yeah I just looked it up and it was that it's fucked up because he was the first
Jewish guy I ever knew about. Yeah no really really I grew up like there were
no like I didn't know of any Jewish kids in my town until I was like 12.
There's the the proof that he's not Jewish is there was a Q&A where someone asked are you
Jewish or Polish and he said no. Is that? That's what it is. Both of the assumptions I had, that was me.
That was me. I did like a, I did a looper thing or um. Yeah, you did a looper thing called pooper.
Oh this is and this the proof for I that's on the talk page, the talk wikipedia page for Weird Al.
They're arguing over whether he's Jewish. That was the proof that someone posted.
dude
here i am so wait listen to the you know i got a really really i was a little
bit of a this is about this is on the cockpit this is under that this is the
talk paid for weirdo yankovic under the heading jewish ok
okay in serbia we think he is serbian on the father's side because he is from
former yugoslavia and yankovic original spelling of yankovic is common second
name here
i know about him only because of his origin i'm not his fan
uh...
i hate his work i find his work completely tasteless uh... i don't
understand it why not just play the original song however I do respect him
as a former Yugoslav that's so funny to be I get yeah that it like just be a
sir who just goes on Wikipedia talk pages and just for everyone who you think is
Serbian and just talks about them I remember I was obsessed as a kid with
the religious affiliation, religious and political affiliations of the people
whose music I listen to. Because I don't give a shit. I was just raised like
very conservative Christian. It's because you loved Screwdriver. I remember finding out like
Lil Wayne was a Christian I was like okay swag that's awesome and then I found out
that T-Pain was a Muslim and it ruined my world dude. Like I couldn't
sleep like I was like he's going to hell this is like my favorite guy is going to
hell they really fucked me up man T-Pain I need to save pain T-Pain I need you to
accept Jesus Christ as your Lord and Savior please that's him when he talks
it's a pretty good auto-tune I'm pretty much gifted yeah yeah I'm blessed yeah
I'm blessed yeah damn I'm blessed damn I'm blessed cuz I'm blessed damn I'm
thinking i'm blessed i just found a heading on on uh... weird al's talk page
called hitler song
well it says
hi everyone i just heard a song named hitler it is said that ramstein made the
song but i'm not sure about that i don't know if you heard it before but it's
like the ramstein song son
i don't know what who is the one that made the song but i just made a small
analyze and i'm thinking it was weird al yankovic i'd like to know if this is
true or not because the song is nice and it rocks anyone knows who made that song
And the response is, "This isn't a forum.
Anyway, if it isn't on the list of songs
by Weird Al Yankovic, then it's not Yankovic."
- Do you remember on Weird Al,
did you guys go on Weird Al's website when you were nine?
- No.
- He had a whole page.
- When I was nine, no.
- Well, the year I was nine.
- I don't think I had really any internet access
besides like eBaum's World and ShoopDaWhoop.com
until like four years ago.
- Weird Al used to have a section on his website
where he would tell you the original artist
of the Limewire song that was attributed to him.
- Oh yeah.
- So it would be like Bert and Ernie smoking weed
and he'd be like, I don't know who sings this,
but it's not me.
(laughing)
- Yeah, I basically growing up,
I thought every parody song was weird.
- Right.
- 'Cause I remember, do you remember there was this,
there was this old Flash animation.
I was trying to find it yesterday actually,
where it's just like somebody singing the ABC song.
And then at the end it's like,
Next time, or, now I know my ABCs,
next time won't you suck my dick, you stupid bitch?
And as a kid I was like,
that's Weird Al's like raunchy song.
- Yeah, Weird Al said a swear this time.
Oh, Elmo's Got a Gun, that's not Weird Al.
- It's not Weird Al?
- No.
- No way.
- No, I think, I don't know what it's from,
but I found that out, I forget the artist's name.
- It says a song by Weird Al Yankovic.
- It's not.
- Elmo's Got a Gun. - Oh no, it's a parody song
by Tommy and Rumble.
- Yeah. - Tommy and Rumble.
- It was a radio show, it was a radio show,
like a AM shock jock thing, or FM, but--
- Everybody, all of the like lyric pages say it's--
- Yeah. - Yeah, it's not.
- It's fucked up. - That's so weird.
- Yeah.
Weird Al would never do AAVE in a song, I don't think.
(laughing)
Like at the end of Elmo's Got a Gun, where he's like,
you want me to walk around Sesame Street
bullet without a bulletproof vest. Patrick on the other hand more than willing. The
second Patrick gets fired he just fires off a thousand of them in one episode. Yeah he
talks about Hitler for an hour he fucking he can't stop dude. What's wrong with you
dude you're kind of like the Hitler of this podcast. I'm not like that yeah
because I'm a tyrant. Yeah he said yes. He said yes. He said yes. No I'm not like Hitler.
And you were smiling.
I am not like Hitler.
Let me make this clear.
Uh oh, let me be clear.
Let me be clear.
I think you're talking into a mirror and it's reversing all the knots on your words.
Just want to put that out there.
I am ton Hitler.
That's true.
You're one ton Hitler.
That is correct.
You are one ton Hitler.
No, I'm not.
Yo, yeah, this is my boy Squeezy.
This is Brizzy and this is One Ton Hitler.
And we're kinda like the best fucking janitors at the school, so you might wanna respect us.
Yo One Ton, which One Ton?
One Ton Hitler, come over here.
Oh I found, I found the songs, not by Weird Al.
One Ton Hitler has to be like a Wu-Tang demo.
Shaolin Hitler.
Yeah, you don't want to know what the 36 chambers were.
Yeah.
I just got that.
Yeah, because you're Hitler and Hitler wasn't very smart.
No.
You're the total.
I'm not Hitler.
I'm looking at the songs not by Weird Al.
What's that?
It's the Weird Al.
It's a list of every song that's not by Weird Al.
It was Weird Al's website and it says "Not by Al" and it says these songs are not by Weird Al.
And it says uh...
One of them is just called "Bomb Iraq".
Yeah.
I'm the only gay Eskimo.
This song is by a group called "Corky and the Juice Pigs".
Make my boobies one more size.
My fart will go on and on.
My girlfriend died.
Yeah that one's by Jim Carrey.
Livin' La Vida Yoda.
One version of this song is sung by individuals named Gavin and Todd Downing.
One version of this song is by an individual named Jimmy Fallon.
SpongeBob SquarePants theme song.
Star Wars, oh Star Wars Gangster Rap, that's a fuckin'.
Oh, which Backstreet Boy is gay?
Yeah, I forgot about that song.
one was great that was a great Newgrounds one he wasn't really as as raunchy as I
maybe thought he was growing up yeah yeah weird Al never cursed yeah like who let
the cows out like I you know I thought that was him I'm too sexy Elmer Fudd
version I ran I ran over the Taco Bell dog this song is by an individual named
Adam Sandler imagine imagine imagine getting fucking Adam Sandler in Weird Al
mixed up I like I like big butts this song is by an individual named Sir Mix-a-lot
what he says in that song is so ridiculous it has to be a parody the
The devil went down to Jamaica?
Dance with the devil.
This song is by an individual named Immortal Technique.
Combo number five.
This song is by a group named Asian Pride.
Just imagine what combo number five sounds like and just imagine attributing that to Weird
Al.
That rocks.
Ball star.
That's your song.
Baby got jack, baby got no back.
So I've been, me and my wife
have been reading a lot of David Icke lately.
We just got this
book in the mail. Nice.
Yeah, she got the book,
not me. She's pointing a blade
at me right now, making, telling
me that, that she, that
she, I, she, I can't remember
remember how the video goes.
He's like, "David Icke, a lot of interesting ideas, folks.
Champions Club, we're going to get through this.
Weird Al is not Jewish.
David Icke told me that.
Stuff's weird right now, if I'm being honest."
"We're going to get through this.
We're going to get through this."
"Fuck!"
"Alright, bye guys."
"I like to eat poop."
Yeah, that was what he said right after "fuck."
He said, "I like to eat poop."