Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
- Premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
(laughing)
- Ooh.
Ooh, that smell.
Remember that Leonard Scanner song?
♪ The smell again from around you ♪
- Such a sick song, dude.
- What song?
♪ Ooh, that smell ♪
♪ Can't you smell that smell ♪
- I don't know that song.
♪ Smell the shit and bad things ♪
- In the 70s, like, you didn't have to
like all the songs you just come up with like one sentence.
Yeah, they didn't know like about lyrics really back then.
It didn't have to be about anything at all.
Yeah, that's why Blue Orester Colt wrote "Guts" a lot.
Lyrics had just been invented. It was basically like Beethoven and then Skinner and the Beatles
and the Beatles tried to make it all about doing drugs and Skinner were just like,
"Y'all smell that? Wait, start playing guitar. Ooh, that smell." It's one of the best songs ever.
Yeah.
Yeah. He also made that song about a homeless guy.
What's it called?
Sweet Home Alabama. Curtis Lowe? No. Sweet Home Alabama. Sweet Home Alabama is not about a
homeless guy, it's about a state. Nah. Who did Free Bird? Did they do Free Bird? Yeah, Free Bird.
I saw them live in like 2011. Really? One of the sickest concerts ever. Yeah, half of them are
dead. Yeah, they're all dead. Also, they did this, like, they interrupted one of their
songs themselves to pull out a giant Confederate flag and be like, "We're sorry
if this offends any y'all we really like we're not into they said we're not into
slavery or nothing he's like you're like this is just we just think this is but
just about the coolest flag there is everybody we went before I was losing my
mind it's so funny to see a band like that what like like that late like I
remember my my neighbor who is like a year younger than me it was like bragging
to me in like like twenty like
nineteen that he saw the dead
Kennedy's.
Yeah, it gives a shit about the
dead. It's a funny like seeing
the dead.
You can have like twenty nineteen.
Yeah, like what the fuck is that
specifically funny because
Leonard Skinner only they were
only all alive for like four
years and then they all died in a
plane crash and then like it was
and I don't think there's a
single original member now.
It's like everybody's brother
now. Yeah, yeah. Isn't it? And they're just fucking, they suck. But it was awesome. It
doesn't even say, it's like seeing AC/DC now. Yeah. It's like the worst, like, yeah.
It's like going to see like Mozart now. Yeah, exactly. It's like this guy, it's like, that's
not even the real one, you fucking idiot. Going to see, you're seeing 50 people. Half
the guys from Mozart are dead. That's my problem. All right. So you go to see Mozart or Beethoven
now, right? Now it is 50 people, takes 50 people to do the job of one guy. Yeah. Back
in their heyday it's just Mozart. Now you got to get there's a little
there's like a 15 year old Japanese kid with like a violin and shit.
He used to do all, he was a one man band. Beethoven used to do that shit when he was deaf too.
Yeah he was deaf and blind. He was deaf and blind and he was stupid too actually.
He was medically stupid. He was one of the stupidest people of all time.
He ate too many like paint chips. You know what people don't know about him?
he had no arms or legs.
- Yeah.
- And he ate the paint chips.
- He couldn't play an instrument either.
- Yeah, yeah.
- He would bite the paint chips and then like,
as soon as like the,
they would come off the wall,
it would start making sounds.
- And the thing about that is the most beautiful thing
I've ever heard.
- Back then they didn't even have paint,
so he was just eating wood.
- Yeah.
- And he had no arms and legs, so he--
- Well he had no arms and legs,
but a lot of people don't realize is that,
he came up with MC Escher, right?
That was like his favorite rapper and shit.
- Yeah.
basically designed you know his funny staircases that go forever? He designed one of those
and he had piano keys. So the way that it would happen is he would just push him down
that and he would just fall and hit all the correct notes.
It was like the most beautiful thing ever. And nowadays fucking Skrillex
hits his space bar on his laptop and he writes the whole song for him.
Skrillex sits up there. A hundred guys who work for him who writes
the songs. Sits up there and presses a staples button. That's his whole job now.
That's a band.
- Oh my God, yeah.
And don't get me started on his hair.
It's like, why don't you get some
on the other side of your head too?
- Yeah, also, why don't you,
while you're at it, why don't you grow some huge boobs
and a giant beautiful ass to be a little bit of a girl?
- Yeah, exactly.
How about you try picking up a guitar once in your life?
- He's a good Skrillex.
If you're gonna do this, just put a bikini on.
You gotta stop spending those turntables
and breakdancing, Skrillex.
- Yeah, it's disrespectful to the audience.
- It's disrespectful to the vinyl.
- Put your pants up, Skrillex.
That's not what I was drawn with.
Oh, I am.
Skrillex, pull your pants up.
Damn it.
Unless you're showing me a beautiful surgery that you got to look like a...
You can lead a horse to water.
You can lead Caleb into a racist pit.
How's that racist?
He's white.
Fucking idiot.
It's not even racist.
Yeah, it is.
Do you know what Skrillex looks like?
Yeah.
He's a white guy.
What does he look like to you?
He's Colombian.
Is that Colombian?
Yeah, he is.
No, he's not.
Yes, he is.
Skrillex?
Uh-huh.
It's not even a Colombian.
You're not rolling the Ls.
It's Skree-X.
Yeah, is it screex? Yeah. Yeah. Oh my bad. I'm sorry. Yeah, that's my bad. All right. Keep your pants down
Pull your pants down far
Yeah, why your pants so high you're cool you're cold on me and pull them down
Show me that diaper. Yeah, show me your diaper scroll my god. I want to see Skrillex's diaper so bad
Yeah, I'm full of his damn music. What's up? That's right. Come on, dude, dude
And you know and you know, he stole that song cinema from the Beatles. Yeah, he did. They wrote that shit
Yeah, he literally they wrote that shit in India. Mm-hmm, and he stole it
Yeah, it was originally supposed to be the song that the popcorn comes out and dances to before the movies
That's what the Beatles wrote yeah, and then Skrillex is like I'm gonna steal this real quick and
now the funny part is the Skrillex added the singing part the Beatles wrote all
the other stuff mm-hmm yeah it's the one that says you are my cinema I could
watch you forever and then it goes this guy I don't think he realizes this he
keeps he plays a normal song for like 30 minutes or 30 seconds right it's like oh
this is a normal song then it's like he like yeah he must be not a leptin he
like falls asleep on the I know hey sir like we're supposed to be we're so
supposed to be impressed that you're dropping your instruments? Yeah. Pick the
damn bass back up. Exactly. What is this dude?
Goddamn dude. Incompetent. Making all these loony toin noises, snoozes, and loses. All these loony toin noises.
Right? It's like crash bang. It's like come on dude. It's like what is this?
What is this? What is this? It's like hey man who do you think you are Adam West?
Like come on. Cool with the sound effects. What do you think you are? What's his name?
Michael Winslow? Yeah. You doing the beeps and the bloops right? You do a playing normal
song then you get Michael Winslow to come in and go...
That's right yeah who the hell do you think you are Mario? You know it's not a video game.
Exactly right. It's not a sound effect when you jump dude. Yeah stop jumping on stage too.
And pull their pants down. And put your headphones on normal. Why do you only need
one, what you got one ear? You got one hair and you got one ear? What the hell?
Let me guess. One side of your hair? Is that why you grow your hair down on that
other side to hide your no ear? Is that what you're doing? Mm-hmm.
Screex?
You fucker.
Yeah. Hey, while we're at it, use a smaller computer. You got a giant machine up there.
Yeah, exactly.
You know how many children built that in the third world?
Do you know how many people got shot in the back of the head to harvest those silicon chips to make that giant machine with a hundred knobs?
You don't need all those knobs. A guitar has, what, four or five strings? That's all you need.
Plus, this fucker's playing 30 seconds of a song and then starts blending a smoothie and a Vitamix for the rest of the fucking duration of the song.
duration of the concert.
- That's right. - I wanna hear that.
- You know how hard it is to find those
silicon chips in the mine?
They're fully formed in there.
- Yeah, yeah.
- We're just finding the RTXs down there.
- That's why it's so hard.
People are getting fucking shot in the back of the,
they're finding full RTXs in those mines.
- I wish they did like how Jordans were in the 90s
where kids are getting killed on the street.
They should start doing that for graphics cards.
- They should start doing that for them?
- For graphics cards, yeah.
I'm sure people in the '30s and '90s.
I'm sure that's happening, actually.
You think so?
Yeah, I think that's actually happening.
It's happening, but it's not like that.
It's just like you just get swatted.
True, yeah.
Your house gets swatted by someone at the FBI
who wanted one.
That would be pretty smart to swat someone,
and then you go to like fucking Halloween and more,
or whatever, pick up a swat outfit,
and you just walk in with them.
'Cause they all got their faces covered.
They're not gonna notice you, right?
You're gonna blend in with all the stock guys.
I'm McDonald's. That's my...
We need to check all his food for anthrax.
And he started eating everything out of the guy's fridge and shit.
-Pretty smart. -Then you take his RTX out of his computer.
What if his N64's a bomb? We have to test it.
Yeah, we have to test this by playing Clayfighter.
Yeah.
-It's pretty smart. -That is smart.
Look, take that Clay... Look, he has a copy of...
-He has the rare copy of Clayfighter. -Clayfighter is a smart game to be a bomb
because nobody's coming over to your house and going,
"Yo, let's play Clayfighter."
Yeah, what's a clay fighter 63 and a third the director's cut he has that in the box
We have to open that one up. I've never got that we have to open up in front of him
So we just to make sure that was a 64 game
Yeah, that was bad in 64 was like I feel like the last thing what it's called. I don't play for you
It's clay for clay fighter or fuck. I might be thinking there's one with the with the dots, too
Do you know the ones where it's like if they all look they're all made of like a game where you play glove?
Yeah, over yeah, it's coolest game ever a glover before
- That was so cool.
- You guys ever played West 64?
- Dude, what was the name of,
do you know the name of the dots fighting game?
The one where they're like all just dots floating around?
Somebody will know, somebody will message it to us.
- Oh, that was Dots Fighter.
- It might have been Dots Fighter.
But that's so funny 'cause they were like,
oh, let's see, Street Fighter's super successful,
like Mortal Kombat's super successful,
like let's make a version of these games
where instead of having any characters,
we'll just put a bunch of dots on the screen.
(laughing)
- It's smart, dude.
That was like, that was the era where you could just make any game, because like nobody knew what was a good game then.
Oh yeah, dude, there's this one...
I had no clue.
There's one game for like Atari Jaguar, I never played it but I remember it from an AVGN review,
where like, it's like a dinosaur or some shit and he's fighting like a Scottish guy,
who one of his attacks is he lifts up his kilt and a fireball comes out of his dick.
Daaaaaaamn.
That's sick.
That is sick.
yeah they need to bring shit like that back but there's a thing like they have
shit like that still
but it's like
not good
for usually not a good game
so i guess it's never really left
it's also free on steam i mean like you can't get one of those games
on like the xbox what's the newest one xbox 360
one thousand yeah you can't get it on the xbox 360 no no no playstation 3
it's called balls with a z
no look at these characters this is what the characters look like in this
fighting game. It looked like... That was on Super Nintendo? Yeah. Oh, so that must have
been just to show like... Fighting at its ballsiest. Is it? Yeah, it's like a 3D
Super Nintendo game. Look at these. But they had like Street Fighter and shit on
the Super Nintendo. Like it's not like they couldn't make like characters.
They're already 3D. That was just to show off that Super Nintendo could be
graphically impressive at all. It could make a ball. But then it still looks like shit because they're made out of
balls. Yeah. They're just different colored balls. It's impossible to tell
what's going on in any screenshot too because they don't have any like
recognizable anatomy like they're trying to give them arms and legs but it's like
what is this yeah you can't even tell is that one guy or two guys i think it's
two guys that's two guys fucking i think it's two guys fucking will you watch
your mouth he said it too i've uh you get the bar of soap you try to
wash my mouth out bitch i think i might have to try it here
are the characters boomer okay okay balls a clown from the
Circus he air his air jumps and the tricks up his sleeves make him the most humorous fighter
How is he a clown? He's a ball. There's a bunch of balls, but they are bruiser a bodybuilder who gets quite a workout
Okay, crusher and enraged rhinoceros and enraged rhinoceros
He's made out of balls divine a ballerina dancer who twirls around gracefully
What she's the only she's the only female fighter and will sometimes give a spanking we look her up. She will give us divine balls
Divine balls divine balls divine balls
Let's see what comes up here. Oh, she's beautiful
Holy
Shit, she's fine. I was I was worried that the search would show up divine from John Waters. Yeah
Yeah, I was thinking let's see. You gotta throw that Z in there. Yeah, that's the key
Well, let's change it to the rock is a character in here to
Cronk from from yep new man from the dawn of civilization exactly what was from new group
Yeah, well, and then you know there's a bunch here, but Yoko a monkey who often breaks wind
He enjoys ganging up on you and slapping you silly. They put a farting monkey in the game
How's that a little and he's made out of balls?
LSD simulator
64 I meant to you meant to yeah like I was that was like on your to-do list
Yeah, that was like I knew people who would like do let's plays of it. Oh, yeah, little school scary game. Yeah, I love scary
There's to me. There's literally nothing scarier than a haunted video game. Yeah, somebody could like there could be a
Doesn't PS one somebody could drive a car into my home
I'd be less phase and if I played a video game and you live you live on the third floor
It was an easy skirt it no dude. I don't give a fuck someone's fucking actually I'd be more impressed
to somebody yeah like what the Dukes of Hazzard pop out yeah yeah right
you'd be mad at first cuz you know your shits broken but then you're like man
also yeah guys fucking cool yeah I live on the third floor yeah penthouse suite
sorry not gonna apologize for it yeah okay what are you mad what are you doing
not mad I sorry you're trying to sleep a little bit you seen rat race with mr.
being no that motherfucker be falling asleep in that movie yeah I just did
yeah I just said I was I was sleeping I went on a I'm telling you guys about
this I bought a monster at Walgreens yeah oh yeah we got carded which card
for your debit card for my ID what they hearted me and what else make sure you
weren't 10 would I don't know she was like you old to be drinking did you
- Do you think maybe it was a tall boy?
- I think that's what it was,
and then I think maybe, I looked at her and I went,
like, no I don't, I don't need to be carded for this.
She was like, no, I think it might be something
about the vitamins in it, 'cause you have to get carded
for vitamins on the shelf now.
- What? - What?
- I was like, what the, what are you talking about?
And then I looked at it to make sure
that monster didn't come out,
'cause it was a monster juice.
- Okay. - Yeah.
- It was the Papillon flavor with the butterflies on the can.
It's a beautiful can.
And I don't know, she just like carded me
'cause of the, she said, "Yeah, I think it's 'cause
"of the L-carotene or whatever the fuck it was called."
- L-carnitine?
- Yeah.
- They're carding kids for L-carnitine now?
- That's what she said. - What's L-carnitine?
- It says it on the can. - Nothing.
It's just one of those things that they put on a thing
that is like, just--
- She was like, "Yeah, I think it's 'cause of that,
"but I need to card you for this."
And I was like--
- So the computer was telling her to card you?
- I think so, yeah.
- What the fuck, which store was this?
- The one--
- The Walgreens?
- Yeah, the Walgreens.
- What in God's holy name is happening to this city?
- Yeah, that's not okay.
- First they ban the 64 ounce soda.
- Yeah.
- Which is like, come on bro.
- I mean, that's all right.
I don't care too much.
- 64 ounces of soda?
- 64 ounces, like I could do 40 ounces of soda,
but 64 ounces, I think I'm getting old,
that'll just give me a tummy ache.
- It's called an all day pop.
- Nah, not for me.
- It's an ADP.
It's not for me.
Yeah, dude, walk, get a Diet Coke.
Yeah, but then the ice melts and then it's just like watered down.
Don't.
Who's getting ice in their soda?
Me.
It comes out cold.
It comes out cold, but it doesn't stay cold.
Drink it fast.
Drink it too, yeah.
Yeah.
I'm not going to sit there drinking a soda all day.
What the fuck?
It's called an all-day pop.
It's just a name, you idiot.
It's no, no, no, no, no.
It's just the name of the...
It's just the name of the cup size.
Fuck you.
No, you can't change it now.
It's a name.
You're not making any sense.
You said you're not going to drink it all day.
You know those beers, the all day IPA?
What do you start drinking at 6 in the morning and finish them at midnight?
No.
It's the same thing with an ADP.
What's an all day IPA?
It's like a low alcohol IPA.
There's almost no alcohol in an ADP.
I mean, you can put some in there.
Shit, here's the move.
- That's why you got carded.
- Here's the move for the ADP.
I mean, well, it's gone now in New York.
So, hold on.
- Here's what would be the move.
You fill it up halfway, go to the liquor store next door,
put like a thing of one of those smaller bottles
of vodka or Jameson in it, then you got all day partay.
- Okay.
- Ah, different ADP.
I will say, if you're filling it up halfway,
you're gonna put 32 ounces of vodka in it?
- Okay, three quarters of the way.
Three quarters of the way.
- 16 ounces of vodka in it?
- Yes.
It's an all day partay.
- That's true.
- It's gotta last you all day.
- I cannot argue with that.
- That's a very good point.
- 16 shots of vodka during the day.
- Yep.
- Sounds pretty good actually.
- Yeah, you're not gonna be drinking it all day though.
- Over the course of the day.
- Yeah, go to work and be like,
- Listen baby, I'm a fucking sanitation man.
I gotta get through this day somehow.
- Man, I gotta drink just 'cause I hate the smell of my job.
- I bet going to work-- - Just my normal big soda
for the day. - I mean those guys,
they're stupid if they don't just get drunk all day, right?
- Who, who? - Sanitation guys?
- Well I guess the guy in the back of the truck
can get drunk.
- Yeah, well he's like literally on a rock.
He's on the stinkiest roller coaster they have.
- Exactly, yeah, you get drunk on that thing,
it becomes a roller coaster.
- You know that people in New York,
people die like all the time as garbage men because there's like
two garbage men that you can be you can work for the city and
have like normal hours where you collecting garbage at like 6
in the morning and it's pretty normal or you can work for one
of these like these like evil private garbage companies that
like tell these guys are like you have to pick up trash at
like 4,000 houses in one hour and they're like why go go go
go go go and they just fucking all of them die Jesus. Yeah,
That's so cool.
That's sick.
Being a garbage man does sound like...
High stakes.
Like, yeah.
It's the most respectable job.
Well, here...
What?
I smell like shit all day.
My dad used to be a garbage man.
He told me...
This is something that really excited me about the occupation is that when they collect...
Like if people leave furniture, like couches or stuff, when they pick it up, they go through
all the cushions and get all the change.
And then they get to saw the couch up into pieces and throw it into the truck.
That is so cool.
- That's awesome.
- That is actually so sick.
- Just imagine finding like 20 bucks
that someone forgot to take the cushion off.
Like that would be the coolest thing ever.
- A friend of mine, he was a garbage man for one day
and he like went, it's so stupid,
he like got in his car, drove to the dump,
got out and just smelled it and vomited.
(laughing)
And he just left.
- Damn.
I think--
- So funny.
- My uncle Kevin, when he was a garbage man,
He was like living with us at the time.
And I think he was for like two weeks
and then quit but didn't tell my mom that he quit.
But then was just pretending to go to work as a garbage man
and would just sit at the beach all day.
And then come home, he would pack himself a lunch
and then sit at the beach all day.
- And then before he came home though,
he'd have to roll around in trash
to make sure it was full.
- Yeah, he jumps in the dumpsters
covered in vomit, banana peels.
Oh, another hard day.
- I puked again today.
"Oh, it's the fucking worst! I can't, this is the fucking worst job! Oh, it sucks, I wanna quit!"
I feel like...
"I wanna quit so bad! Oh my god, it's the fucking worst!"
He doesn't think it through and he covers himself in trash before he goes to the beach.
The pigeons are just like shitting on him.
That's how I used to get copies of Thrasher, though.
He has beach trash on him, though.
Like a beach ball underneath his shirt.
Yeah, he's part of a-- He's wrapped in a volleyball net.
Oh, there's garbage all over him.
He's got seaweed all over him.
The fucking guy's like drenched too much.
He looks like a shipwreck.
He's got like--
He's wearing like flippers too.
Oh, I had to pick up so many treasure chests today.
Oh, fuck. Oh, it was the fucking worst.
Another fucking whale washed up on the beach.
God damn it. I had to pick up that thing, throw it in the truck.
Did they call did they call like the garbage?
Super team when a whale comes because a whale is garbage dude
They get they get scientists to come and make sure that it doesn't blow up
Oh, yeah, cuz they blow up cuz they have like gas inside
Yeah, so if you're not careful
They can just explode so they have people in like who like dress up in like crazy suits and come and like cut them open
They have a bomb squad. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, holy. I would love to see a whale explode. You can see a video
I'm gonna pull that up. Yeah, there is a video of it
Yeah, it's pretty cuz I saw it and it was in Reno 9-1-1 Miami
And I thought that the joke was that somebody put an explosive in it. No, they do that. They just do it man
Oh, no, no, no, wait. No, they they do put an explosive in it, right? I have to rewatch my man. I'm in Miami
That's a good movie. Let's see which video here. We're gonna watch. How big is the explosion warning?
This video contains footage like a new year's may your mom disturbing really? Yeah
Some viewers not me until maybe I see it and I'm actually I'm actually really exploding sperm whale carcass caught on camera in the Faroe Islands
Oh
Dude, that is so cool
What the fuck that crazy?
Play that ever
Go look this up
Is it no it's not gonna no it doesn't do it again
He's well
I wanted to see if they like play it back in slow motion these types of videos will always play it a second
He hit that white thing and it did it. Yeah, that was so fucking cool. It's sick dude. Look at that. What the fuck?
He was just runs away. Yeah, god damn that looks like it looks like cherry soda
Man
Man, that's like a cherry soda
And get this it's because it's like the it's methane gas that blows up. So it's like a hard to the whale. Yeah
You can't a whale party. I didn't
Explodes.
Whoa.
Holy shit.
You know how you think that smells.
Yeah, that smells.
Ooh, that smells.
Maybe it's about this.
God damn, dude.
Did we crack the case?
That's so fucked.
How the fuck?
How the fuck can you not believe in God after seeing that?
Look at this.
Hold on.
After one of the miracles of nature.
Oh my God.
Exploding whale 1970.
Oh man.
I hope it takes this guy's fucking head off.
Yeah, dude, his fucking toupee.
Paul Lindner.
Linman I hope his fucking toupee flies
Marilyn Monroe walks by
It off oh what's gonna happen? Oh, what's gonna happen? How long is this hold up? I think I gotta fast-forward. Yeah, we
Think they blow this one
70s were like the most humane thing was to just throw a
- And any time a deer was stuck in a well,
they would just blow it up.
Wait, this is gonna be so cool.
- Six, five, four, three, two, one.
- Holy shit. - Yeah, they just
straight up blew it up. - Oh my God.
- That's not even like the methane thing.
- They just red misted that well.
- Yeah, that thing is huge.
Dude. - Dude, I know.
You guys, you know that--
- Do you think they thought
that it was going to explode? - Imagine not getting
the memo and being out surfing.
And you get like a, yeah.
also like definitely somebody got like a whale tooth to the fucking eye.
For sure.
It's all over somebody's teeth.
Aren't their teeth like tiny?
My cousin, the cousin, I don't know.
My cousin, the one you guys met.
Not sperm whales, sperm whales are toothed whales.
When he was like 16 or 17 he went to, they were exploding like an old mall in Bakersfield
and Bakersfield obviously like they don't, they're just like stupid about everything
so they were like, hey like anyone in the town who wants to come like watch the explosion,
"Yeah, come on, there's blowing up a building."
And they're like, "Just make sure you stand like a hundred feet away."
So they giant, I mean it's Baker's, that's all there is to do is like watch
something explode. They go, everyone in the town is basically like fucking
circled around this building a hundred feet away. They blow up the building and
right next to my cousin a giant piece of shrapnel cuts a guy's legs off.
- Oh my God. - Holy flies.
- It just instantly, legs just gone, dude.
So cool. - Holy shit, dude.
- And now that guy's like the richest guy in Bakersfield.
- Yeah, that's like how you get rich there.
You either start corn or you get your legs blown off.
- You invent a new type of corn that has a fatter kernel
or you get really hurt. - What are you talking about?
- Fatter kernel.
(laughing)
- Corn from Bakersfield, the band.
Oh, it's also a big farm in town.
You guys, I spent a lot more time in Vegas.
So there's a big corn industry there.
Yeah, that's where the people are from.
Yeah, they are all from there.
I didn't think about that.
Fatter Colonel.
That you need a fatter Colonel.
Monsanto's.
(laughing)
Fatter Colonel.
You said that so much.
Yeah, you were like, oh yeah.
You really are a fatter Colonel.
I'm not really into rock and roll.
I'm more of an agriculturalist.
God damn it, dude.
I'm sorry. You guys are all on your hippity hop rock thing.
I'm just a simple man. Just give me a bigger circle.
I've been thinking of the most famous thing out of Bakersfield is corn.
Yeah, the fucking food. It's and almonds.
Corn and almonds. It's like all there is. No, you know, it's funny.
Your cousin did the same exact thing when we met up at Carmello's. Really? Yeah.
I think I made a joke about Cor and he was like, "Oh yeah, you know, it's a big farming town."
I was like, "Man, no, my bad."
We're simple people. I come from a simple family.
Yeah.
We don't even... all those masks.
You got to get your cousin back out here. That dude's good hands.
He's the man.
I've had a really rough 48 hours.
Yeah? In what way?
They're cooking me, man. They're still going.
Oh, they are.
Oh, yeah.
They're still going?
You talked about it at the show last night.
I muted it like...
pretty quickly so they're just demolishing me yeah it's great
you know that as a good peanut head as pecker would be a sick but i saw it all
that's m_f_ grow one hair please
one hair please i saw a couple i saw a couple of women i can you up i saw a
couple men a lot of men hyping you up
so i'm not saying i would crack his head open like an egg on my bussy
uh... no one said that he said you just invented that you made that up as you
You fucking that's disgusting that you would say that about your friend. Do you I'm trying to make you feel good about this
I I already feel good cuz it's like
What was that?
That's what he said we had to let a drug addict in
Guy fucking so high loses keys fucking scumbag anyway
Yeah, there were a lot of there were a lot of gay men who were very interested in in that photo of you
you.
Tracy Mattel, if I could kill one person in the world, with like a button inside of a
briefcase, nobody has ruined my life more than that fucking guy.
Fucking stupid ass, bald piece of shit.
Maybe what you gotta start doing is like doing like...
You tell me every day that I should do drag.
You should do male drag, right?
- Male, well you'd have to, you could put on a male wig.
- Yeah.
- And some male clothes.
- Maybe like a suit.
- A suit, exactly.
See, you're getting excited about it.
- We get Caleb a comb over wig.
- Yeah.
- Oh yeah, and I do drag shows where I'm just like
talking on a Bluetooth headset the whole time.
- Right, yeah.
- Just making business calls.
- Who would you be talking to?
- Probably my wife or something.
- Yeah.
- Or my mistress.
- Oh my god.
- That would be good, yeah.
drag show. You're just dressing up like another guy that you know.
Yeah, yeah. Like a guy with hair and a suit. Yeah. And I'm like, "Ahh, we're gonna need a report."
Saying that. And everybody at the dinner, people are eating their shit. I'm in Provincetown.
And finally, do we do a drag show that the boyfriends go to? Every girl in the world takes their
fucking, their boyfriend to some drag show where they have to like fucking just sit there and get
like I mean these guys are not made fun of yeah they get you know my being awesome
if they sniff out they sniff out guys that look like Caleb in the crowd yeah
and then they're like wait oh my god Trixie
I can't go to a drag show wearing board shorts you give me a hooked yep it's
horrible you have to show up in a poncho we need a drag show that's a safe space
for men yeah where you can go and they don't there's no mimosas it's all right
Yeah, I mean I've tried to solve this problem before you show up wearing a sheet like a ghost so they can't make fun of
Your clothes that's out. They call you ghost boy. They don't shut up the entire time so annoying. Yeah, it's like
See me. I'm a ghost. Yeah
They're the they're the meanest people in the world. Yeah, also you're supposed to you're supposed to be a girl right now
You're not supposed to be like
funny
(laughing)
- I'm sorry, that was just a--
- That was just a layup.
- That was out of line.
- Yeah, just a layup, yeah.
- Yeah, save that for the male drag show.
- Yeah, yeah, and the male drag show, I would crush.
(laughing)
Oh, dude, this show, I mean, yeah, it'd be like,
and they do the celebrity thing, too.
Joe Rogan.
- Oh my God, yeah.
- Joe Rogan Drag.
- It's all guys.
- Joe Rogan Drag Show.
Guys dressing up like other guys that they like.
Yeah, like they're their guy heroes.
And when they walk out they'll go, "Hell yeah."
"Hell yeah."
"Oh, fuck yeah."
"Oh, fuck yeah, brother."
"Fuck yeah."
"Heard that?"
No laughing at the show.
"It's not funny."
Yeah, it's all supportive.
It's all being supportive and supporting and uplifting men.
It's MGTOW.
Yeah.
It's the MGTOW Grab Drag Show.
show some guy comes out dressed up like Jordan Peterson or something like no
girls allow yeah and it was nothing people throw lobsters at the stage like
get this they don't say work they say relax yeah relax bro set a work bit
chill chill dog chill brother come on brother yeah instead of instead of wig
it's minoxidil. That's finasteride for sure. Yeah, yeah. That's some Rogaine.
Propecia. Yeah, some Propecia for real. Yeah, dude, that'd be... and like probably,
probably, probably, and this is, you know, probably the least gay place of all time.
Yeah. Right? So this wouldn't take place, well they have to take place.
Is everybody dressing up like their favorite hot guy? Yeah. So cool. Yeah, that
That would be, yeah.
Nothing gay?
Nothing gay.
Just the most normal crap ever.
Just support.
Yeah.
Just support and like...
Video games?
Yep.
Yeah.
Video games.
This could take place at a barcade.
Could take place at a barcade.
Could be at a barcade.
Yeah.
Yeah, could be at an axe throwing bar.
Yep.
Could be in a farmhouse.
We should do a... you know what we should do?
We should host a lock-in.
Remember the lock-ins?
No.
What's that?
Oh yeah, yeah.
They would have them in Rye Airfield.
They would do like church and shit.
- Yeah, it would get like a bunch of like,
like all the kids would, they'd lock 'em in a room.
- Yeah, you lock 'em in a room overnight.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- So like, and everybody's like--
- Wait, what is this?
I don't know what this is.
- Like church youth groups and shit.
It'd be like a lock-in, where it'd be like,
you just stay the night on the floor in the church.
- Okay, so is it like when you like go like stay
at like a museum overnight or something?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- For like Boy Scouts, yeah.
- Yeah, it's so cool, dude.
- Yeah, I never did anything like that.
- I never got to go to the lock-ins in Rye.
We need to do the male drag lock-in.
Yeah.
We could have more adult male sleepovers.
I agree.
Yeah.
Everyone makes fun of me.
It's an upliftment.
Jan always makes fun of me because if somebody is going to stay at our – I can't get
this out of my head for some reason.
Somebody is going to stay over at our house.
The other night John was going to sleep over because the couch he couldn't get in touch
with the person he was staying with.
I was like I think Johnson come over have a spin the night I don't know man I
don't know why I can't. She's probably made fun of me for that a hundred times and I still like just
instinctively I'm like yeah is it cool to be like has a spin the night? Has a spin the night?
I've never heard that before in my life. Has anybody ever said that? Is that
like what your mom would say? I guess like something like I would say when I was
like little kid. Oh yeah. Oh you would say it. Yeah. No there's some shit that I used to I think I've
outgrown a lot of it but there's some shit I was saying until I was like
probably the age of 20 that I said mommy daddy goo goo ga ga. Yeah. I'd say I would
I'd be at a bar and they'd be like hi what can I get you? I'd be like one Bubba.
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
him by one hand and I waddle around with him. Yeah. Yeah. He's basically my best friend.
Don't touch his wet leg. Don't touch my frog's wet leg. I make it wet at night, okay? Alright,
it's what I do with him. It's a playing thing I do. Yeah, it's literally playing, okay?
How long did you guys pee the bed? I was not a bed wetter ever. Really? Lucky you. I would
- I was such an awesome, horny kid that I would like have a wet dream though almost
every night. You did not have a wet dream. Swear to God. As a seven year old. I'm not a seven year old.
Yeah. How old were you? I was like fucking 18. You said... Weird. What? I don't want to... No, I was
probably 11. Okay. I was just every single night just waking up. I had a different kind of wet
dream every night until I was 11. Yeah? Yeah. I peed the bed till I was 11 years old because I was
such a deep sleeper. I was an extremely deep sleeper. Doesn't that mean you're like a serial killer?
It's like a serial killer thing.
Is it?
Yeah.
Nah.
Yes.
And it's also, you know what I mean?
It's so funny that that's like one of the signs.
Yeah.
It's like you were such a stupid pussy growing up that you wet your bed all the time.
If you poop your pants more than three times.
Yeah.
It's like, right.
Sorry.
I think you're a serial killer.
And they tell parents to watch out for that too.
And it seems like that criteria is arbitrary and it doesn't make any sense.
I think that it makes perfect sense and it has a 100% hit rate as far as the accuracy
of that. It's a good barometer.
It's just a deep sleeper.
Yeah.
I'm still...
You're dreaming of murdering women every night?
No.
No?
But you guys ever drool in your sleep as a grown man?
Oh yeah.
I did this morning.
Drool in my sleep horribly.
I woke up...
Dude, I did it on the plane to Seattle. I woke up on the seat. Thankfully it was the flight
home where I like...
Yeah.
in your sleep is normal you don't like grow out of that. Were you drooling on
the person next to you? No, so the flight... So you're a big fat guy?
Drooling on his shoulder? Oh, Grant. The flight there...
Oh, I never talked about the fucking the flight to Seattle. Where you just sat on
the plane? I was stuck on the plane for four hours. I forgot about that. I was stuck on the runway for four hours.
and they pretended you were in the air the entire time yeah yeah like oh oh no
here comes a turbulence oh yeah they were shaking my seat yeah I did I fell asleep
as it was like about to like take off and then woke up to the pilot saying
like folks we still have not left the ground there was a problem with the
bathroom the toilets are clogged you were not supposed to use the toilets
before we get in the air and like somebody's toilet was clogged that we
couldn't fly because the toilets were clogged.
Whoa.
On the plane. So they had to take, took like four hours for them to unclog it.
And then they like, dude, I want to be the guy that did that.
They let us all off the plane one by one. If you needed to use the bathroom.
Yeah.
And like, because of COVID, like they were like, we can only let you out one by one stupid
fucking arbitrary rule. A guy came back with a hamburger. I came back with a burger and I was
I was like, that's the guy that clogged the toilet.
- But can you imagine the power that you would feel
if you were responsible for that?
- Grounding a plane?
- Yeah.
- That's an act of terrorism.
- I feel like it's hard to clog an airplane toilet too.
- Clogging an airplane toilet,
then the whole flight just being like,
man, I hate the guy that clogged the toilet.
No, aw!
- What does he push out?
Like perfect circular heavy poops
that are just the exact size of the tubes in the toilet?
too strong at pooping and he's strong enough that a plane can't take it with
this guy actually eat a bathtub stopper two days ago and he just got it out oh
that is a very like he must be so he must have such good gut health assuming
that it was a guy like on your flight and not like something to happen before
the flight it's very funny to like get like board the plane and immediately like
take a giant clog the toilet like getting the also yeah not like going into
the bathroom in the airport or anything.
Thinking about it, like this guy probably cost JetBlue like $400,000.
Yeah, like so many flights.
Delaying a flight that long?
That's crazy.
Four hours.
And then it was a six hour flight.
Like a gate, nobody can use that gate.
Yeah.
They have to move all the places around, everything gets, they're probably still dealing with
that.
Yeah.
Because this guy's shit.
We had to wait, we had to wait 20 more minutes because the other flight had to take off that
was supposed to be at our gate.
So we had to wait another 20 minutes as soon as we landed in Seattle, but like the fucking
toilets were clogged before we were leaving.
You got fucking owned, man.
Yeah, I got owned by some guy with powerful shits.
Yeah.
He must have been dropping a bazooka in that thing, dude.
'Cause you can't suck out the vacuum shit.
One of the worst things ever, though, is clogging a toilet.
Clogging a toilet...
It happens to the best of us.
I've never done it.
You've never clogged a toilet?
I've never clogged a toilet.
You clogged a toilet and then someone's going in after.
Someone going in immediately after you is the worst.
Yeah.
I mean if you clog it and you have enough time to run a getaway, no skin off my back.
I don't care.
If I clog a toilet at a cafe because I'm like, "Oh, I accidentally ate too much McDonald's,"
and I just need to go into...
Well, you can accidentally eat too much of anything.
You accidentally ate too much McDonald's?
You know, sometimes you get...
I will say I've never been in that situation.
I don't know that I have either.
I feel like I've intentionally eaten too much McDonald's.
I don't know that I've ever done it by accident.
Well, you know, you think like you can pace yourself and you realize like,
"Oh, this is not today. This is not a good day."
So you just ate too much McDonald's? You ordered too much?
You order like a large instead of a medium?
You can't... A large is too much for you?
Sometimes now, yeah.
A large of what?
Dude, I swear I got IBS or something.
Large water?
Large.
I got IBS?
Yeah.
Everybody has fucking IBS now.
I think I still do.
It's so annoying, dude.
Yeah, it's not true.
Now every girl in the world has IBS now.
Maybe, here's my thought, maybe it's the makeup.
- Maybe.
You might be onto something there.
- Maybe it's the makeup.
- Maybe.
- Could be giving you IBS.
- Is bitches shitting?
- That's right.
Is they shitting?
- Are they lying about this?
- I will say.
- I think they're all lying about IBS.
- Me getting owned online and everybody hates me
and they want me dead and they want me to be an egg
that they crack.
probably would be a little bit different if I was the most beautiful woman in the
world. That's a good point. Right? Yeah, you would have been stalked and killed. No, I
think they would have been nice to me if I was... Think about it. Instead of being an
ugly piece of shit with no hair, if I was the most beautiful woman in the entire
world so if you were Trixie Mattel not Trixie Mattel well yeah of course you're
not the most beautiful woman in the world is Trixie Mattel I'm not a drag
queen I could be and it'd be fine and you guys would I'd be so supportive of
that if I showed up every day one foot taller yeah and just fucking big
platform yeah it's dressed like a lunch lady mm-hmm making you guys be your
character a lunch lady lunch lady like a farting lunch lady probably I'd have a
big like I wear a pretty good yeah we're like a good what there's gotta be a good
name for a bottom half a sumo suit right friend yeah smeller smeller yeah only
good only karaoke I'd only lip-sync ooh that smell by Leonard Skinner be really
funny yeah this is actually such a good mod loaf yeah yeah something like
something about mystery like a food mysterious meat is actually such a good
area meets good that's really there's one there's one that's staring us
straight in the face but we can't think of it there was a one there was do you
remember the when we were at Maria that one time we like met up with Jana and
there was a oh yeah what was that bet one drag queens and it was so good
here's a good it was something it was like it was like Thelonious fart yeah
had fart in the name Friday pizza day oh her name is Friday pizza Friday pizza
day what was free to eat today yeah yeah that's pretty good actually it's pretty
good it was something the last name was fart yeah it was something fart if you
know the name of a drag queen with fart in it you have to tell us it because
that's the best name. That was the best name we've ever heard. It was really like
I thought about it for a long time. I should have written it down. It was so funny.
Yeah. Oh it was so good. It just took me off guard. Yeah. You know it's just yeah.
It's pretty good. We couldn't even stay to watch with the name stuck. The name
was stuck with us for at least an hour after. I was whispering it under my
breath like a spell. Yeah. We just don't remember it. No and I just don't know anymore.
I have a really bad memory. Last night I had a dream that I was like, "Okay, I'm bald.
What do I do about my head?" And I so I got I went to go get a giant tattoo on my
head. Of hair? Of hair. Yes. And then the guy was like, "That'll be $15,000, not $20."
Yeah. And I said, "Can I be on a payment plan?"
- He's pretty good.
- What kind of hair?
- Jet black.
- Jet black, but like what style?
- I mean, just helmet.
- Yeah, like mow.
- Yeah, mowed up.
- Yeah, pretty good.
- No, it's just like exactly just following
a hairline I never even had.
- Yeah.
- You know, the steps, I had the steps up.
- Uh-huh.
- Yeah.
- That's pretty cool.
- I had the steps on.
- I wish I could, I wish I could like
get a lineup or something.
- I'll line you up.
- No, dude, my hairline's at full M now.
I can't do that.
- Let me see. - What?
- Yeah.
- Oh yeah, you got the M.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I'm rocking the M.
- Yep.
Yeah, I don't know how much time I have left with my hair.
- You can, you're one of those guys, you could be--
- You could pull it off forever.
- You could pull off the balding forever.
- Yeah, it looks good.
- I mean, that's what my grandpa does.
- Yeah, no, it's fine.
- You could literally just keep that exact hair
until you're like 70, it'll be fine.
- Yeah. - It'll look good.
I mean, I'll just, I mean, I wear a hat most of the time.
Plus you have facial hair, so it's fine.
You know, as long as it adds up to one full head of hair on your face.
Dude, it's just like, I'm straight up getting hairier everywhere else,
and I'm losing so much hair on my head.
You're high T, dude.
Yeah.
God, it sucks being this high T.
Well, I think like, like, like crazy, like, like,
Albert Einstein balding hair is like the coolest hairstyle a guy can have.
Yeah, I wish I had that. I wish I just had the thing that just went back.
Yeah, that's cool. Just I like yeah, just hair that's just like
Super thin like halloween mask hair very yeah. I love that. Yeah, it looks like a back to the future doc mask. Exactly
Yeah, yeah, that is a good hair. It's great. Yeah. Yeah, that's what i'm. I think that's what i'm gonna have
He's got a good hair. I'm saying it's gonna look sick as hell
Yeah
I mean, it'd be nice to get plugs. You look like the skating professor you would get plugs
I'd get plugs just to like push it. You know that you have to take medicine every day
- Yeah, but I would push the--
- You know you have to do something every day.
- Horrible.
- You have to remember to do something.
- He would just fall back out.
- I would push, just to push the hairline up
a little bit more.
- You know what, the recovery is like a year.
- Yeah? - Yeah.
You have a fucked up head for a year.
You have to walk around like a lady with cancer
with a scarf on your head.
'Cause you can't even wear a hat 'cause it'll damage it.
- I think I'm just gonna go gracefully then.
But I would, I mean theoretically,
would get plugs just to push it up like an inch.
- Until they literally, that'd be funny,
and then you keep balding and there's just this weird gap.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Do you know what the plugs were?
- Yeah, yeah.
- I think, until they make a literal chia pet hair thing,
I'm not doing it.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I love being bald.
- I miss it.
I can't be bald because of you.
- My head gets so cold.
You can't have two bald guys.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
I was the smartest thing I ever did was shave my head. I know before so you can't
do you know I would have dude I would have been able to fucking pull it off
yeah I mean I think my head's too round cam can shave my head what's why can he
shave his head cuz I'm not afraid you're wrong you've also I'm not a coward he's
doing it to alpha dog me that's right which I accept yeah alpha alpha Z
- Zeta.
- Yeah, okay.
- Zero.
- Sugma.
- So yeah, you're a Sugma dog.
- Alpha, alpha, like just...
- You're a wiener dog.
- Piece of shit.
- Wiener dog, dude.
- Farta.
- I've been looking at pets online.
I've been going on Pet Finder.
- Really?
- I'm thinking of...
- Not me, I'm too alpha for that.
- Yeah.
- I probably, if I saw a pet...
- I was thinking about getting a little wiener dog.
- Yeah, I pretty much get every pet I can
'cause I just like to like dominate them
and be their pack.
like a dominating dog. I would probably get pack leader.
So you wouldn't understand.
You would get 50 of them and just get them behind me and walk in a triangle.
I mean, I understand you're kind of like more submissive.
You're more like submissive towards your pets.
Cameron had sex with dogs.
Excuse me?
What?
Yeah, you probably like bow down to your pet.
Yeah, no, I mean, you're the...
Cameron had sex with dogs.
So does a pet like find you food and then bring it to you because it has to take care of you?
Cameron said he had sex with dogs.
Patrick, Patrick kneels down on the ground.
To dominate.
And he acts like he's wagging his tail because he wants his cat to fuck his ass.
Because he's...
I don't have a cat.
That's how far away from an alpha dog you are.
You've been looking at ones and you've been saying...
No, I've been looking at dogs this time.
Is this cat hypoallergenic?
Yeah.
Will he fuck me in the butt?
May I see a picture of the dog's rocket before I purchase?
Please?
Here's what you do.
Is it aggressive sexually?
Does it hump?
Here's what you would do with your dog.
No, I could never get a dog.
You would sit your dog down...
Especially in the city, I feel like that's tough.
like this and make sure it got a boner by showing it dog food or something and then
you would like you know those those jump jump rockets or you jump on the thing
you would you would jump on its balls and make it away to shoot into your own but
you're the one who brought it up I didn't bring this up yes you did you're
alpha dogging him right now I like this I like this this is for you know this
video cuz I said that I would shave my head and then it turned into I have sex
with dogs he said it clip it and fucking ship it is going in the theme song that
it's going in the intro and CNN the theme song it's going to the intro and the
outro and once in the middle of every episode that's right we're doing ad
breaks now for Patrick's and I'm not gonna say it I'm not gonna say what he
does I'm not come out that's activity yeah Patrick's hobbies Patrick's
behavior yeah this sucks you do dogs cock and his asshole oh oh my god I just say
that that's yeah I saw a dog that's like a pudding cup I don't know what I did to
deserve this to be my career you know you're squeezing the butthole around to
try to like squeeze the rest of it out and beat up every day he's sucking around
it by my good friends look at this beta shit yeah talk hey speak up kid getting
Dude, he, I was just at his apartment, I saw you had a new coffee table book, the K-9 Sutra.
He's been playing with it.
New positions.
I can't even participate in it.
I can't even participate in the fucking bit.
Did I tell you to talk?
God, this sucks.
No, no, no, we're done with this.
We're done with this bit.
That was, that was too, that was too good.
You can't keep going from there.
That was pretty good.
I like that.
You can't, it's, yeah.
God damn it, dude.
I couldn't even participate in that.
It sucks.
I'm anticipating that. It sucks.
Alright, yeah.
Alright, fine. We'll move on.
No, no, no. You can do it with me.
Oh, yeah, guys. I have sex with the most beautiful girls in the world.
Me too.
What?
You're supposed to make fun of me for that.
Oh, wait. You have sex with a girl? That's gay.
Oh, come on, man. Seriously?
Yeah, what do you have? Patrick has the canine sutra.
[Laughter]
We're nearing the end here, but I did want to bring up
We're recording this on National Podcast Day today.
Yeah.
It won't come out on National Podcast Day.
No, it'll come out today.
I just wanted to say that.
I feel like we should maybe get some money.
I think we should get some money.
Or maybe, if somebody wants to text me a question about podcasting in the next eight minutes,
I'll answer it.
Okay.
And now we wait.
So what's going on?
Do we have anything coming up?
Oh wait, no it's not over.
Fuck.
Are you guys going to see the Sopranos movie?
When's that coming out?
I haven't seen the Sopranos yet.
Oh really?
Tomorrow.
Oh, you know what?
I'll watch it.
I don't want to go see it in theaters.
Yeah.
Look, I mean, if you're not afraid.
My hair's really bad.
Yeah, should I see it without having watched the show?
Yeah.
Whoa, hold up.
Yeah, that'd be great.
What?
Hold up.
Speaking of National Podcasting Day.
Yeah, what's up?
Just got something kind of big.
What is it?
Kind of big news.
Sprint.
Important information about your Sprint Complete Program.
Get details.
Okay.
Whoa.
Wow.
Sprint just upgraded me.
I just got an email.
Or something.
Now, let me see what's in my inbox.
Oh, this one's from Capital One.
Whoa.
Oh, here's...
Important information about your account.
That's cool.
I actually have a lot of...
Closing your cards in 30 days.
I have a notification right here.
Low power mode turned off, battery sufficiently charged.
Whoa!
Damn!
Holy shit.
That's pretty amazing.
We're doing...
We're doing good.
These brands are being so nice to us for National Podcasting Day.
They said that I have 60 days until it goes to collections.
Whoa!
My package was delivered.
Is that true?
Actually, you know what?
My package was delivered.
I got a t-shirt and it was either stolen
or my mailman is so bad.
- Do you guys get packages stolen a lot?
- I don't know if it's, 'cause you know what?
I fuckin', I got this t-shirt.
I bought Matt's t-shirt that he did,
the super mega Chinatown Market one,
bought that, support my boy.
And I bought that and then it said it was delivered
and then I was like, oh fuck, it's not here,
it definitely got stolen.
And then I messaged Market and then I got a new one.
I got a new shirt, different shirt.
And then two days ago, that one shows up.
Now I have two shirts from them.
- One of them for free or did you buy?
- Well, one of them I got for free
because it was supposed to be like a refund thing.
- So you scammed them?
- I didn't mean to. - You scammed Matt?
- No, my fucking mailman. - You're admitting
you're scamming Matt on-- - My mailman delivers
my mail whenever he feels like it.
- Yeah.
I mean, I feel like you, that,
I wouldn't try and get a refund immediately.
- That's not from my friend.
I ordered it in August, and then it was shipped.
- When did it say, when did it say it was,
what I'm saying, if it said it was delivered,
I would wait like a week before I did anything.
- Why?
- Because that happens all the time.
- Yeah.
- The delivery thing's like shitty.
Sometimes it'll like show up later that day.
- I've never had a package stolen.
- Really?
I don't know, I don't think,
I think we had one package stolen in Boston.
- Yeah.
- Or it wasn't even stolen, I think the guy just like,
the delivery driver like said he the delivery driver just left it at like a random house or
something. It said it was delivered 24 days ago and it showed up so it was 22 days. So obviously
that's like... The point is you still scammed Matt. I didn't scam Matt. You scammed him. No. You did.
And I have to I'm going to message them again and tell them I'm sorry. You should and tell them
neither of them showed up. I think I need another one. You should send two this time just in case
another one gets lost. Yeah. Also I think I ordered I think I ordered a couch from you guys and it
and it never showed up too.
- I ordered a flashlight from you guys.
- I ordered a laptop from you guys too.
I ordered a bunch of crap.
- I think I ordered your personal laptop.
- Yeah, yeah.
- It didn't show up.
- And it never showed up.
Can I see what's on your laptop?
Can I see it please?
- But I mean, this other shirt,
I'm pissed off that it's not delivered.
It was a good shirt.
So now, either I have to wait a month.
- I thought you got them both.
- Yeah, just wait a month.
- No, a new shirt.
- You gotta, you gotta.
- Oh, that one didn't come yet?
Yeah, then that one will come,
'cause the first one came.
- Yeah, but I don't even know at this point.
It could be a different-- - Why not?
It came.
- The other one did.
- Yeah, so why wouldn't the other one too?
- Pat's talking about his dogs right now.
- No, no, no, no.
- One came, the other one, not so much.
- He's still working on it.
- Okay, you know what?
You know what? - He's working on it
right now in front of us. - I'm gonna get a dog now
just so I can have it attack my mailman.
It's natural enemy.
- Dogs love mailman.
Are you stupid? - No, they don't.
- They hate mailman. - They love mailman.
- No, what are you talking about?
- I'm gonna get an army of dogs.
- I'm gonna have an army of dogs attack my mailman.
- They don't follow them, they attack them.
- They follow them behind them.
- I'm gonna get the most aggressive.
I'm gonna go on Pet Finder.
- Have you ever read The Far Side?
- No, oh, the tome?
- Have you ever, do you know,
have you ever seen a cartoon TV show?
- You're right, The Far Side actually
does have a lot of knowledge.
- It does, dude.
That's literally, it's about how the world works.
- You know what, I thought about A Far Side cartoon
the other day, 'cause I was on a safari, right?
I was on a safari.
I was looking around and I was like, "Where's Bob?
We're missing this guy Bob."
Right?
Look around, outline of him in a snake.
Damn.
He got swallowed by a snake.
Yeah, speaking of, my mailman didn't even deliver my fucking cow tools.
It's annoying, dude.
I was hanging out, I was saying, as far as I did, I was hanging out with some giant bugs.
Yeah.
They're huge.
And I was like, "Well, they're probably, what are they going to do?
They're bugs probably going to eat sugar water or something."
Yeah, yeah.
human shit they're raising it they're swaddling a larvae yeah yeah this is some
far side shit right now I saw the gram check yeah I saw this like big this fat
guy mm-hmm and his he just he had he he had his eyes were aligned it's just a
line yeah right it's like what is yeah I saw a guy there was a guy on the street
speaking of far side guy in the street he said it's 1995 really yeah Wow I was
like no it's not what's not making it's not 1995 no have you see if you guys read
the far side one where he the Jane Goodall does an intro for it I think so
I guess like they're best friends is that the prehistory of the far side I
think I have that book on there yeah yeah yeah Jane Goodall does it intro for
the does it the first I thought that guy was bananas Gary Larson he was but
apparently she took him to the monkey place yeah took him to the monkey place
I showed him all the monkeys.
- You know he got a--
- Well, where else is he gonna get inspiration?
- Well, that's when he entered his monkey era.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, you know all the artists have eras.
- They named a louse after him.
Like some scientists were like a big fan of his,
and they're like, "Hey man, we're gonna name
"a discovery after you."
And it was like a fucked up ugly bug.
(laughing)
- That's awesome, dude.
I hope we get there, Wanda.
- Yeah.
- I would love--
- What animal would you--
- A frog.
- Yeah, it's gotta be a frog.
- A new species of frog.
got to be a frog. I mean, to be honest, of course I would take any animal.
I don't want it to be called like... It's got to be an animal though. I don't need, I don't
need, I don't want a fucking plant. Okay, if you're a plant scientist, I'll start discovering plants.
Unless it's like a Venus flytrap.
Well, these are two different directions, I think, that we're going in.
Yeah, well, I don't want to be a plant named after a man.
Like a new type of corn.
They discovered a penis guy trap.
Bigger than Patrick.
Yeah, fat kernels.
Fat kernels.
Probably be called the Caleb.
Yeah, because they're juicy and succulent.
Easy to grow too.
We would all get named after the corn?
No, why would you guys get named after the corn?
Maybe we could each get one of the kernels.
I don't know, maybe you guys could get like a stupid band named after you or something.
No.
But the corn itself would be named after Awesome Caleb.
It'd be called the Awesome Caleb Corn.
It wouldn't be called that.
I just came up with that.
That's pretty good.
I think if we had a corn named after us, what color would the corn be?
Probably yellow. Most corn's yellow.
Yeah, but if it's like a new corn.
Or the leaves are green, if that's what you mean.
The patch of corn would probably be real red and thin.
my corn
uh... cornwood
uh...
and i don't know how you put it out of that fucking house no no no no urge
out of the house but the great but i think the second episode in a row where
we talked about corn
we are corn on the broader you know what i do you gotta go to a shrimp a big
cajun shrimp oil
i'll say it did get some corn and seafood boils sucks shit really horrible
I've actually never been to one.
They're fucking dog shit, dude.
Yeah?
You know what it is, it's probably because you're eating the newspaper.
I'm trying to get smarter, man.
Yeah?
Yeah.
You see those far side cartoons in the newspaper, you go at them.
Y'all still read the funnies?
No.
No?
I don't get the newspaper.
It's Foxtrot, right?
That's that like the little kid one.
Foxtrot, yeah.
It's funny like...
It's like written by like a very conservative man.
The far side...
Which one of my family circus?
I think it might be the...
they're all written by conservative yeah that's you have to be conservative
yeah yeah Gary Larson is the only like this far side is the only like
non-political one he doesn't even do that anymore
yeah yeah so sad end of an era mm-hmm far so it's a bit all the other ones are
like like what if there's a right-wing aunt
yeah and he comes out yeah it's all they all want to make it about like like
teenagers be crazy nowadays yeah like all these heathcliff ones
The Heathcliff ones are crazy.
I love Heathcliff.
Well, the new, the recent Heathcliff.
What's Heathcliff's thing?
He's like Garfield's brother?
He's like Garfield, but like he had a traumatic brain injury.
It's like it makes no sense.
All the jokes are about like it'll be like Heathcliff walking around wearing a helmet
that says meat on it and then the person is like, "I guess he likes meat."
And that's like the comic.
But there's like a whole bunch.
That's pretty funny.
They're great, dude.
It's like power up.
I love those.
Power Up.
Shout out to Power Up Comics.
We love Power Up Comics.
So funny.
It's like the only good webcomic in so long.
I mean it's been around forever but yeah.
Classics.
That I heard of.
That one's a classic.
The best one, I mean the best one is when they're like, "Hey Shadow, what do you think
of gay marriage?"
And he says, "In my opinion, all marriage is gay marriage."
That's the best shit.
So good.
Go follow Power Up Comics.
That's our plug for the...
Oh wait.
But you also do have to follow Power Up Comics.
I do.
That's our plug for the--
Oh, wait.
But you also do have a plug, don't you?
Yeah.
Boston, Caleb's performing.
Caleb's doing his one-man show in Boston.
Yeah, Laugh Boston.
Brandon Wardell is opening for my one-man show at Laugh Boston.
I'm going to probably--
I'm going to come out completely naked at the end,
just to make you laugh.
And I'll probably do some body paint.
So come check that out.
Sounds good.
We're going to paint--
Cover myself in silver like 10 men.
We're going to paint the top of Caleb's head.
Yeah.
And we get to pick what's on the top.
Also, I'm bringing it. I'm bringing it up and Halloween's coming up.
So check that out, too. Yeah. Check out Halloween. Check out.
Oh, I'm going to be at McDonald's.
Oh, yeah, I'm probably going to get a taco after this.
Yeah, I'm probably I'll be hanging out later.
I'm going to be at the Hollywood Burger King in Bushwick.
OK, we should go there right now.
I already went there today. Fucking press stop. OK.