You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[laughter]
Hit that record button.
E.
Caleb was just talking about how his whole thing on Twitter is pretending to be black.
No, I was saying- We were talking about Patrick.
Patrick, honestly, was literally saying that one of those guys who's a white guy pretending to be black is one of his favorite Twitter users.
I didn't say he was one of my favorites.
He said "Deebo is pretty funny."
What do you think is funny about him?
Is it the way he talks?
There is the old, like his Brailed account.
I don't know what that is.
The Brailed parody that he has.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Shut up.
Alright, keep talking.
Keep talking.
What?
We should say we're starting a marathon.
A marathon Monday.
A marathon bombing. Yeah. It's a Tuesday. This is the Boston Marathon today. This is the Boston
Marathon. Marathon got canceled, but we're rescheduling it to today. Yeah. But because I am...
Did the marathon get canceled? I don't think it got canceled yet. It got postponed.
It got postponed. Because of COVID. Yeah. So we're recording a bunch of episodes in a day.
Every episode that you hear for at least a couple weeks will just be from this day.
and uh st patrick's day is it st patrick's day oh my god what are we doing here we have to go out
we got to go to the to the uh let's go make our own parade to the horn i'm gonna go to the names
of irish pubs you gotta go to erin go brah what dad yeah that's gaelic for something i don't know
let's go to the wee child we gotta go to pogue yeah we gotta go to pogue mahones
What's that?
That means...
Oh, I know exactly what that means.
That means kiss my ass.
Yeah.
Are you both Irish?
Uh, I don't know.
No, Cameron's a Polish fuck.
Oh yeah, you're a Polack.
I'm really... I think... I am Polish, but that's...
*burp*
No, I'm a lot of Irish.
You have a...
I just don't know.
You have a Polish vibe.
Yeah.
*laughter*
Yeah, you give me... you give me Polish vibes.
You have a Polish vibe because you look like an NPC from The Witcher.
*laughter*
Yeah.
Yeah, you look like you're like rendered too far away in oblivion where like the details haven't shown up yet
That's what Polish people look like. Yeah. Yeah, and you know people do look like oblivion characters. Yeah, let's be honest. Mm-hmm. We should
Bernie Sanders
Like it Bernie's a Polish Bernie. You're a great guy, but you look like a fucking oblivion character
Hello. A wizard has taken my gold. Yes. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Good morrow. Joe Biden is. Joe Biden is an oblivious. Bernie looks like one.
Joe Biden's brain is an oblivious NPC. Just walking around aimlessly on stage
going, can you help me? Can you? Yes. Yes. Yes. The dragon. I need to find
my father my father where is he have you seen my father my father is dead have you
seen my father my father is dead thank you for your help kind stranger one
septum for you I dropped my phone under the couch that's good that's good for
you under the couch and it's a sung by a potato shut no it's some of your phone
no yeah no no it's on to your phone by a potato chip that's been there for a
really now that's cute yeah and your potato chip and then your potato chip is
named Sebastian yeah and then your phone grows legs and I fuck your phone mm-hmm
okay my phone has a beautiful voice voice that was stolen by a drag queen
yeah which is what that movie is all about hey when a drag queen steals my
voice mm-hmm that's what that movie is about that movie is about the drag queen
takes my breath away. The moral of the Little Mermaid is be normal and do not do any gay
shit. Don't be divine. Yeah. Drag queens will kill you. It's the moral. By taking your breath
away. By taking your voice. Taking your voice. And then trying to marry Prince Eric. Yeah.
What a terrible prince name. Yeah. Eric. It's my brother's name. This was his birthday yesterday.
I don't care. Happy birthday. Actually you don't have premiums so you're never going to
hear that. Yeah we had to cancel my younger brother's birthday. Yeah we were
gonna go to Foxwoods. We were going to Vegas. Vegas? Yeah, Fallout
new style. So we were gonna do the same thing for our brother's birthdays. Yeah
which are only two weeks apart or a week apart. But you weren't gonna go to
Vegas. I wasn't gonna go to Vegas. No but you were gonna go to a casino.
Your brother's 21st? Yeah. Yeah that's what you gotta do. You gotta take him
somewhere. You gotta put him in a pool and make him pee in it. Yeah my mom just
had him at the restaurant she works at last night she just kept giving him free
drinks your mom had him at a restaurant last night last night and he turns one
he'll he's in dog years double dog years double double double dog it'd be triple
dog years no wait cuz if it was that's what I yeah when I was trying to get
laid as a baby how old are you I'd say I'm dumb 18 and double dog years
Yeah.
And then she always fell for it.
So you'd be two or two and a half.
Two and three quarters.
I was too young to do the math.
Yeah.
I probably was off by a little bit.
I'm actually a thousand years old.
I'm actually a vampire.
He was actually 19.
Yeah.
I was actually 19.
In dog years, I'm 18.
Dogs, yeah.
Dogs are always 18.
You subtract one year.
Because if a dog was the size of a person, they'd probably have health problems.
If a dog turned 18, you could finally have sex with it.
But they never will.
That's the thing about them.
That's why you can't.
That was like one of my first stand-up jokes I did.
It was like the reason you can't fuck a dog is because they don't live to 18.
Not very funny.
Kind of like...
Well, yeah, because then you start to picture what that dog would look like and it's just
got like a milky white eye.
Yeah, it has like, you know, it has like eye boogers that are like dripping off of its
face.
Yeah.
And it's got like a...
You know when dog...
Just a broken leg.
that old homeless guys beards get where it starts it grows out so much that it's discolored at the end
it's like they've been dipping it in with the homeless guy in front of 7-eleven it's because
he keeps drinking dr pepper and like accidentally dipping it in the big gulp but with a dog they
have no excuse yeah you ever google it's because they're rolling around in their shit ugliest dog
ever you ever google i feel like i've googled that so many times oh yeah when i was in when i was in
first grade. Yeah. No, I don't know what it is. And you get that brown dog with the white
eyes. Yeah, that's what I'm thinking of. That's what it would look like. What's that kind of
dog called? It's called like a zyko. It's called a Zion dog. Zion? Yeah. With an X? No, with
a Z. With an X. What the heck? Find it. Oh, check out this one. Oh yeah. Damn. Wait, I
I gotta find the specific one.
This one.
Yeah.
I have seen that.
This is what a dog would look like.
I saw that shit on E-Bombs World.
Yeah, man.
E-Bombs World used to rock.
You know there were certain games that had boobs in it?
Frank's Adventure.
On E-Bombs World?
Yeah.
No, I didn't know that.
Frank's Adventure and then the volleyball game if you put a hack in.
If you play, there's one game, I don't know if I, I think I just found it because I was
trying to download the Sims on my parents computer but I looked up it was called
the Sims day and night I think I played it on ebombs world. You make them go woohoo? No. Oh.
But there it was very strange though because there was a thing where you go to
a club and then you can like take a girl home with you and then it just shows you
like a picture of a real naked woman and it seemed it looked like it was
revenge porn honestly and I said I that I played that when I was nine and I didn't
understand but now that I'm thinking about it that's fucked up thanks for
clarifying mm-hmm yeah you're not so much porn the the Sims day and night gets
four stars for me because four out of a possible five got one star for revenge
porn. You piece of shit. I used to, uh, E-Bombs World was like where I lost my virginity.
That was like the only website I went on for so long. Yeah. Yeah. I would do, I would do
remember Virtual Buddy. What is it? Why was it as a kid I was just obsessed with hurting
dynamite. Yeah. So many games. Yeah. Games where I just was like, this is the bloodiest
game ever and yeah I would google crap most gory game yeah Madness Combat no
never play that one no that was very gory like it was like it was a Rayman style
the figures and then they like no you can shoot their hands off yeah that's
remember happy wheels yeah happy wheels yeah those are the later I played it I
never played happy wheels it's I played happy wheels and like was that like a
middle school or high school I can't remember. That's high school for me. Yeah.
It's all a blur dude. Dude life's a blur and then you die. Mm-hmm. I remember when
YouTube first started man. Yeah? Yeah. I remember when they invented the
internet. It wasn't Google Video. There was a Google, there was Google Video. That
wasn't YouTube though. Yeah that wasn't YouTube but I remember going on Google
Video and seeing sparkling. I remember YouTube. I remember you, no I remember
going on Google video and seeing sparkling wiggles you remember that
video no oh oh where the girl says FNN words yeah you said that like you
don't you're not allowed to say fuck yeah we did we took out a we did a thing
on Patrick he's not allowed to swear anymore yeah we did a thing we did a
hex on him yeah we did it we placed a curse around his neck that would be a
funny premium thing if we hit 400 on Patreon we're not allowed to swear.
Now that would be funny.
We have to not swear for an episode.
Can you imagine, oh you mother trucker.
Can you imagine the last people would get to that?
Oh sugar.
This list is sugaring crazy.
Yeah but then we would make it our goal to get to 500 so we could say F and shit again.
Now that would be funny.
The laughs never stop here at Podcasts by Lips.
Oh man, I'm gonna kick your a, dude.
Yeah, ass ass.
I'm gonna suck your crap.
I'm gonna suck your crocker.
Instead of dick.
Yeah.
Yeah, suck your crocker.
I'm gonna slip up in there.
Yeah, I'm gonna gut you like a fish.
I'm gonna get your gunch.
I'm gonna float on top of you like a ghost.
Whoa.
Put a sheet on me and scare your kids.
we do graphically talk about fucking each other all the time I'm gonna I'm gonna
flow I'm gonna flow through you like a river I'm gonna come to your room at
night and I'm gonna waterfall onto you I'm gonna go inside you and explode I'm
gonna put on I'm gonna put on a big white sheet and scare your kids I'm gonna
turn into a spider yeah Patrick is you're in the Ku Klux Klan you racist
yeah that's why I scare your kids. Patrick went clean from the KKK I think. I have a video.
He went clean? Yeah. He dropped him. He burned his head. Yeah. Oh that's nice dude. We were
partying to celebrate. Nice. That's why we got together today. That's why we burned a big T.
We burned a giant T in celebration of Patrick leaving the KKK. Yeah because I just wanted
to say that it's thank you for it stands for I totally not in the KKK anymore
yeah if we get to $1,000 we're gonna take a video of Patrick in the KKK hood yeah
we are and that's a little best to wear a dress so what do you have to wear dress
I have to put I touch dress are you gonna wear a beautiful one or not that I
my own yeah probably a beautiful probably a gown. I was thinking a
wedding dress. I was thinking a wedding dress would be funny. I was thinking
something elegant, something yeah, something elegant, something something
with a say qua to yeah.
So I was I honestly was saying I might go full Jessica rabbit yeah yeah yeah. I
have a I have a wig. I have a girl wig. Should I just go for get makeup to oh
I should cut my penis off. There you go. Yeah and I should have him form it into a shitty
vagina. Just yesterday, just throwing up just all day yesterday, I just destroyed my esophagus.
I can't believe that I'm with you right now. I had food poisoning. You were gonna give
us this plague. You have thing poisoning. No. You have thingy poisoning. Cause you've
been poisoned by that thing that's been on the news. The thing has gone into you. You
don't throw up from it. Oh you throw up from it. You don't throw up from it. You throw
- You do though, obviously.
- Dude, I, yesterday--
- I'm definitely gonna leave here
and instantly disintegrate into dust.
- That was the worst day of my life.
I think that was the worst day of my life history.
- Worst day of your life?
Just having food poisoning?
- Dude, it sucks.
- Food poisoning sucks, I will say.
- I don't get sick often.
- Oh yeah.
- But when I do get sick, I'm like, it's--
- Okay, most interesting man in the world.
(laughing)
- I don't get sick, but when I do,
it's 'cause I was drinking Dos Equis.
- Yeah.
But when I do get sick, it beats the shit out of me.
I was already having problems with my heartburn shit and my acid reflux.
Yeah, my mind.
Yeah, your mind has been really low.
But I threw up just straight orange bile.
And then like, anytime I drank water yesterday, I literally missed, I was sleeping here, I
got up and then like that I've puked all over there but it was just straight I
just threw up straight water it was all clear it doesn't surprise me that you
don't get sick much because you are so full of like chemicals and just like
random like shit preservative yeah I feel like you have like you have like a
halo like over shield yeah you have enough like aspartame in your blood that
any yeah any bacteria that gets in there just instantly like you got past the
point with aspartame where it's possible for you to get cancer with it because
cancer cells will be eaten alive by aspartame. Is there aspartame in this?
Yeah dude. No. Yeah, you didn't know monster energy ultra? No, I thought it didn't have
aspartame that's why I drink it. I mean there's no there's definitely, if there's
not aspartame, there's something else. There's probably something in here that's worse but it's not aspartame.
aspartame. This is my first time. It's chloroform. Whatever it is. Yeah, it's, it's, yeah Patrick
you have like formaldehyde in your veins. Yeah, you have like, you probably have, of
any of us, you have the most calcified pineal gland. If you tried to, if you tried to donate
blood it would just kill all the doctors in the room. That's not true, I've donated
blood a few times. Really, but you're gay. Yeah, they wouldn't let you. You don't gotta
tell them. Don't ask, don't tell. That's the policy with blood and the military. Don't
ass don't tell mm-hmm yeah this is my first time I've just been having like
mate like sometimes one cup of coffee in the during the day and I'm halfway
through this and I want to jump out the window right yeah I'm waiting to drink
my red bull crazy until I need it cuz I know we're doing you guys just aren't
used to it maybe we should just go wild completely wild on these because Jesus
Christ, P.I.D. is gonna kill us. He's coughing. I can't believe we're sitting here. This is
such a bad idea. It's insane. For me this is like my only source of income now though.
Yeah. That's why I would have stayed home. But we gotta put it out. Well, you know Mitt
Romney just proposed that one time. Mitt Romney just proposed to you dude? Are you gonna say
yes? Oh my god, you should say yes. I'm gonna have a traditional Mormon wedding. Yeah, what
does that entail? You sucking his dick on stage? No, me wearing my pajamas under my
Tuxedo huh me wearing my pajamas under my tuxedo. They should wait you should if you're Mormon. You should have to wear them over your clothes
Imagine now we're a big pair of plaid
No, they're not plaid. They're they're all white. Oh, well, you got to wear them with the butt flap on them
And you should wear a little badge to say you're Mormon you wherever you go
You should have to have a barcode on the inside of your wrist. Yeah, it's it's
A special
house you should get unlimited wives if you're more than good I agree even the
girls and that's hot to think about yeah all the wives can be wives and the girls
put their squishies together no there are they not so like but if you're if
you're if you can't be gay you're a big boss is number one bitch and you have
Big Boss from Metal Gear. If he's Mormon.
Liquid Wife.
Revolver Wife a lot.
That's just a rose emoji display name. Revolver Wife.
Who just tweets it. Revolver Wife guy.
Revolver Wife tweets it anders lee and says "Come to my city!"
Yeah.
It's like Boise.
God damn dude.
Man, he's gonna be stoked that his name was said on a podcast.
What was I saying?
No, but can Mormons, can the wives...
No.
Why?
Because they're anti... aren't they anti-gay?
But if you're all sucking on the same dick, can he only have sex with one of them at a
time?
Can he only fuck one at a time?
Yeah.
I think so.
What?
Yeah.
Dude.
Alright.
I'm not converting anymore.
Anything to make more Mormons.
man all you gotta do is go to Brigham and Young University. It's just Brigham Young.
Whatever. Not Brigham and Young. Fucking idiot. Brigham Young. You gotta go to Brigham Young.
You gotta meet one... Cuz at Brigham Young they bring 'em young if you know what I'm talking about.
Yeah. Damn dude you should write for The Daily Show. Thank you dude. Oh my god. I'm thinking of
becoming a Hard Times contributor. You should. Trevor Cameron. Trevor Cameron. The Daily Show
with Trevor Cameron. We should we should we should pitch stuff to the Hard Times. I heard they're
changing the name of Corona virus to a virus because you say oh when you get it
they're turning it to go fee fee 2045 2045 they're changing when it comes back
eventually yeah just having making no sense on weekend update Blade Runner 2049
came out this week more like yeah and all the people go buck wild my mom sends
be a clip of it the next day. That's just her filming the TV with her phone. I heard nowadays
they're calling Mitch McConnell Donald Trump. Rich McConnell? Yeah. Because he's so rich
with lies. He's rich with sin. Yeah. Isn't that a little... Your body is completely rich
with sin. And then... Oh yeah that was a Jordan sketch, it's a funny one. I heard about that
before I went to Emerson and then... How? I don't remember. I think I was... I don't
I don't think it got popular online.
No, someone told me at a party that I was at at Suffolk.
Oh, yeah.
And then I was like, "Oh, that's pretty funny."
I don't even remember what the onus of the sketch was.
It's just a...
The onus?
Not the onus, the...
What the hell is an onus?
An onus is like a burden.
But, yeah, it's just...
I'm here to call out Caleb producing, pretending to use big words.
That is the wrong one.
Colin Jost is in a time loop and he can't...
I heard that was actually the bifurcation of the sketch. I believe actually the dichotomy of the yeah
I don't know what either does mean. That was the dichotomy of the sketches hegemony. Yeah. Yeah, that's total that the sketches oligarchy
Was kind of about what if Colin Jost was it was kind of a Dadaist look at yeah
What was the point of the sketch? Oh, it's a Colin Jost is stuck in a time loop. He can't
because he
He's stuck in a time loop because he tells jokes so bad that
I don't remember. Nice. That was probably the worst 30 seconds in the history of this podcast.
He can't figure out how to tell jokes. All he knows how to do is say jokes in a - all he knows
how to do is say things in different tones of voice. Oh, okay. Now I remember it. Yeah, yeah.
I don't think I was at Emerson yet, but I think somebody showed that to me. Yeah.
That's - and I had to - I think that was one where Jordan just started with a funny name for a sketch
and then worked backwards. Yeah. Yeah, because Infinite Jost is pretty good.
Yeah. It's about as good of a... I didn't know that was CCC until the other day,
and then I was like, oh, it's crazy that that's the first thing I knew about, and then I got into it.
And you got in, and now you... And now I'm out of it.
And now you're out of it again. Yeah, man, you guys are...
Well, you will graduate. You'll never go to college again. And Patrick will die very soon.
I probably will fail the online semester. I can't do online classes, dude.
Yeah.
I'm already, I'm fucked, I think.
People who don't know that all the, all classes are cancelled and online.
Yeah, for people who don't know that.
I mean, there's actually a virus going around.
If anyone gets their news from us,
the only people who listen to this are the German Big Brother cats.
In most other states, they aren't doing that yet.
I think it's pretty big news, though.
Yeah, but...
The school I go to is, uh, the campus is closed for the rest of the semester.
- You're such a fucking retard.
- What?
- Anyway.
- Who is?
- You.
- Why?
- 'Cause you're gonna fail your classes.
- Yeah, I probably will.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, it pretty much just puts my life off track.
- Won't get a job.
- Now you're not gonna become the CEO anymore.
- Yeah.
- I mean, I'm kinda screwed.
- I'm gonna be the CEO of this podcast, dude.
- Yeah, you're a head honcho.
- I am.
- You do wear the headphones.
- Yeah, I wear the, I own the fucking equipment.
If you guys ever are too mean to me,
the podcast is over.
- Well, that's true.
I'm putting my foot down right now.
You just cut all the cords.
Yeah, one sip of Red Bull and that's my ultimatum.
Alright.
You look so handsome today.
Oh, thank you.
That's another week on the podcast.
I love the high heels that you're wearing and your leggings are really cute.
Okay, that's it.
I'm unplugging your microphone.
Cameron, those...
I didn't think you could pull off fishnets, but...
Yeah, also your humongous girl tits look so good, man.
look juicy I want to scrub them I'm gonna scrub I want to put you in the dishwasher
your natural triple D's triple D's I don't think those exist yeah well
they're so stupid they can if you imagine they've you have you have Z's
that's how big they are I don't understand is I enormous yeah yeah all
All of the different, they all stand for, the D stands for, it's damn, damn!
That's what double D stands for.
That's one of the first pictures I saw on E-Bomb's World.
Really?
Yeah, the boob chart.
Wait, is that a thing?
Let's look it up.
I want to see what it looks like.
Look up the boob chart.
The boob chart.
Look up boob chart double damn.
Mario Kart double damn.
Dang Pinterest. Oh that's what it is double dang. Okay here we go. Pat read
this. This is our list. This is our... we're not supremiums. We're not supposed
to do the list. Bra size is A) almost boobs B) barely boobs C) can't complain D)
dang double D) double dang E) enormous F) fake G) get a reduction H) help I
fallen I can't get. I can't get. That's what it says. It doesn't even say up. Let's look
it more like this on Pinterest. Can you look up boobs on Pinterest?
These ones? That's too hard to read. How about this? What do boys even find attractive about
boobs? They are literally a ball of fat on a girl's chest. Like if you can love me for
the fat on my chest, why can't you love me for the fat on my stomach, you piece of shit?
This is one of Caleb's posts on Pinterest. No, no. I actually had a Pinterest for a while.
You had a Pinterest? Yeah, I would put together, this was back when I was gardening and I would
put together photos of gardening. I have an old Pinterest if you guys want to try and find
it. Let's go. I don't know what kind of stuff did you pin. I think it's just like art. I
had one fan on Pinterest who would always DM me. I think it's like art and then like cyberpunk
drawings. It's just like gay shit like that. It's aesthetic. Check, read this one. Caleb.
It's got a call from Full Sail University again.
Nice, dude.
You should've, next time they call, pick up.
Talk to them on the phone.
I requested information in 2014 and I, in 2016 when they kept calling me when I was in community
college, I told them to take me off their list.
Now in 2020, apparently they're just going back through and they keep fucking calling
me.
So I gotta pick up one of these times and say I told you motherfuckers to take me out here.
No, pick up and we'll talk to them if they call during the pod.
You stupid four-four-
Can you call them back?
No, I'm not calling them back.
Do what I do with Capital One and just answer and talk like a baby.
Yeah?
Yeah.
[unintelligible]
Sir, your account is six months past due.
And then I just hang up.
[unintelligible]
Yeah.
Caleb, read this one.
I talk... no.
Go ahead, read it.
We each read one.
You have to read this one.
I'll just say, this whole thing is in quotes.
It's not.
It's right there.
It's in quotes.
As I read it, as it passes through my mouth, it's in quotes.
Okay, go ahead, read it.
I talk about wanting a boyfriend, but I don't even know what I'd do with one.
Like what do you do?
Just kiss him and then leave him alone in a corner?
How often does he eat?
And that's a quote from Caleb. No,
yeah, we're putting that up as a clip with the episode. No. Yeah.
Shit. Oh my God, dude. This monster energy is making me dude on my brain.
So I feel like for like a week and a half now I've been just every night
getting really fucked up and then smoking a lot of weed out of this
Android charger weed cart. Yeah, that thing's awesome. It's I mean, it's made me like noticeably
stupider. Yeah. In the past. That's why I stopped smoking weed. It really it does. If
I if I smoke more than like once a week, I can feel like I like I just fuck up like I
can't say words. I forget stuff. And I'm worse at at games. I'm way worse at games. You know,
My reaction time is slow.
After I lost that pen before...
Also I think the pen is a part of it, because that's not like good...
Yeah, dude, I'm still so mad I lost that. I feel so bad.
In New York?
No, I lost it on the way to New York.
Oh, you're right, yeah.
Because my fucking stupid denim jacket had a hole in the pocket.
Your denim jacket's cool.
Yeah, it's a cool jacket, but that fucking pocket design is stupid as shit.
Oh yeah, I should have brought my pen.
Damn, I would have given it to you, but I don't have it with me.
Damn.
We should do an episode where we all smoke weed.
I'm afraid of smoking.
We've done that before. I mean, I've done it.
I've never done that.
I've gotten way too high before.
I don't think I've recorded high on this. I would not be useful.
I'd suck so bad.
There's so many episodes where I've just fucked up just the momentum of the show.
Because you were high?
Yeah. Because I got high.
Oh, nice. Yeah, I don't know. If I smoke, I can't do anything but just watch a funny viddy
and then freak out.
If I smoked weed right now I would be like, "Oh my God, there's something wrong with my
lungs.
I have the disease.
I'm killing my family right now."
See, I stopped freaking out because this past week I've just been overloading myself with
it.
And yeah, it only makes me stupid now.
I don't even like it.
It's just like if my brain is running too fast, I'm like, "I'll smoke this.
I'll watch a video where a guy eats the oldest can of beans and then I'll fucking fall asleep."
You saw me in New York, I did have...
You went bugged.
Yeah, well I was already drunk, I was fine, but like...
So I was on the...
I had the allergic reaction of the Prilosec, did I tell you about that?
No.
I had all the rash and shit.
So that was making my heart rate go up, and then I smoked weed, and then that made me
have like a full blown panic attack in New York.
Nice.
And then I was just sitting in the crowd.
I looked like a fucking ghost.
I looked in the bathroom, I looked like a ghost.
You did not look like a ghost, you looked like Patrick.
I was wearing your sheet. Oh, yeah. I
Was sitting on that couch I thank God they had a couch at the pit pit is such a stupid
Venue the way that they have that they have a couch in the front
It's it's a terrible venue for stand-up comedy and then there's like I don't know if you guys saw there's on the right side of the
Stage there's like eight other chairs. Yeah. Yeah, that was so weird people if somebody sat there
they just have to walk like right next to whoever's on stage. Yeah. It's just a stupid place. But I,
yeah, thank God they had that couch there otherwise I'd just sit in a chair.
Yeah, we haven't done an episode since we went to New York. Yeah. Has it been that long? Yeah.
It's true. Cheese Louise, man. Cheese me. Cheese me right in. We can talk about New York.
I mean, it's already gone from my mind. I don't even remember. Well, we had the vlog,
but I mean, it was mostly just clips of us walking. Yeah, people saw the vlog. Yeah. Yeah,
we went to a vice land office. I'm glad I didn't. I think we should do quarantine vlogs. I think we
we should uh I'm glad I didn't record anything while I was freaking out cuz it
would have just been me like looking at like oh my god yeah Patrick Patrick was
Patrick was a huge baby yeah yeah I was me and me and cam we swagged out we
wouldn't stay with our shout out to patches yeah he will patches is the man
We were so much it was like 2 in the morning. We were Brooklyn and we were like we need it
We need to stay somewhere. Yeah, and everything fell through everyone was supposed to stay with fell asleep. Yeah, it's fucked up
I say was Zoe. Yeah a very cool bathroom. I
You're like a guy who likes mention yeah, you've mentioned that bathroom like 20 days
They had like seashells and mermaids and shit on the wall. I don't want to think about that one
Up on the wall pretty sure look it should look like I was in the ocean
It should look like the bathroom you would I'm a dummy you liked feeling like you're in the ocean cuz you like to poop in the
Ocean when you go to the one of the hardest time
So what her lash goes into the ocean and tries to poop in the ocean, but he's wearing his swim trunk
So it just gets caught in the netting and he comes back out and he's like looking smug like nobody
So nobody knows that I just sat in the ocean, but it's so what one of the so what one of the fucking funniest things?
I've ever experienced with me and my younger brother. We were swimming and we were like 14 and 12 maybe and
I was just like, "Yeah, that was your heights."
Yeah, we were 14 and 12 feet tall, bitch.
We were like...
That's too tall.
You look like an idiot.
No, you look like an idiot right now.
You have no shoes on.
You look like a hobbit.
It's my house.
Can you put some shoes on?
You look like a hobbit that they choose.
It's my house.
Can you put some damn shoes on?
No.
You look like the fat hobbit.
The fat hobbit.
Like, yeah, like the fat Jewish.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's you.
Yeah, that's because it's just the word fat in my race.
Yeah, yeah, but me and my brother we were in the ocean. We're swimming and I was
like fuck I have to shit so bad and he was like yeah man me too and then I just
saw his eyes go like like crazy for a minute and yeah and I was like ha ha ha
he's pretending to shit in the ocean and I was like nice and he was like yeah
Yeah, pretty funny and then between the two of us a piece of shit floating.
I was like screaming laughing and just running out of the ocean as fast as I
could because I was like the entire thing is broken. Yeah, he pooped in the ocean.
You guys ever wonder as a kid like if lightning struck the ocean it would kill
all the fish? How does that not happen? I don't really know why. I mean I know I can't go that
far. But like I always got, I was always like what if lightning strikes like near me? Yeah,
what if it strikes like 10 miles away? I wonder how far it can go. It goes one inch.
Oh well that's fine. Yeah. You're probably good then. Yeah. I was pretty scared of getting struck
by lightning growing up because there's a lot of thunderstorms and like hurricanes in North Carolina.
you know ball lightning that shit's crazy yeah the stuff that comes out of dr
strange's hands it's like balls of like electricity they don't know what causes
it but they just like float like a long they just move for it and they can like
go through doors and shit what's like super rare have you not heard of this
no it's but people thought it was ghosts ball lightning yeah i knew a guy that
got struck by lightning okay tell that story while i find this there's this kid
i played baseball with hey no i was pretty good friends with his name bruce
And his dad got struck by-- or no, his dad saw a guy get struck by lightning. That's the--
Yeah.
Whoa.
His dad saw a guy on a golf course get struck by lightning.
Did that guy die?
I think so.
I always loved-- I always kind of wanted to get struck by lightning because you get a really cool scar.
Yeah.
You know? Like an unmistakable scar.
So if you had rubber boots, you know.
What do you mean? Is that what you get the scar from?
Saves you.
It save-- saves you?
I don't think it saves you if you have rubber boots.
No, no, if it depends on where the lightning strikes you.
If the lightning strikes your boots, you're shit safe.
Yeah, I guess.
But I think, wouldn't that kill you because the current can't like move
down into the ground if you are wearing rubber boots?
No.
I thought that was like how people don't die from lightning,
is if they're like touching something that the electricity can move through.
Well, wouldn't the rubber be a ground also?
I don't know.
I don't know how electricity works.
No, I think rubber, you can't be grounded through rubber.
Ball lightning is uh...
Oh, you're gonna be grounded.
I think leather soles is how you don't die from lightning.
Oh, you're getting grounded today.
I'm gonna ground you buddy.
Honestly, when we're talking about shoes, I wish you would have any kind of shoe on, Patrick.
Why?
Because you have the worst, most disgusting feet.
Your feet look like the nasty patty from Spongebob.
They don't look like the nasty patty.
They look so much like that. You have green pustules.
I don't have green pustule.
Where do you do it?
Where?
Everywhere.
That's your noise.
Yeah, when somebody...
That's Yoshi's noise, that is not my noise.
You're Yoshi, dude.
Did one of you shit your pants?
No.
Not me.
Something smells like a... you ever have a sweet diarrhea?
I think one of the cats might have farted in their sleep.
Because if you're the only person that's smelling it and they're right there...
Because I'm wearing your cat's like a face mask.
Yeah.
With their ass.
Yeah, no, no, no.
I'm not wearing your cat's face mask.
I'm wearing your cat's face mask.
because if you're the only person that's smelling it and they're right there
because I'm wearing your cats like a fat like a face mask mm-hmm yeah with their
no Yoda in Yoda one of my farts dude. Yoda farts.
Ball lightning. Yeah so it can vary from pea size to septic. It can vary from pea size
there's like one video I think they can vary from pea size it can vary from pea
size to it can vary from pea size to several meters pad you want to you want
to weigh in on that several meters in diameter said be and it can like fly
around and it's like very rare some people say it explodes and some people
say it passes through stuff and some people say it like burns through stuff
Sounds to me like a lie.
Yeah, it sounds made up, like Cameron made this up and wrote this whole Wikipedia bitch.
I did while you guys were talking.
Yeah, you did.
You're a really fast typer.
Let's see, they don't know what causes it.
A globular bolt.
Let's see if this Snopes video is real.
This one's false.
Alright, I don't know how to find the real video because the top video is from the Path
of Exile wiki.
They don't know what causes it, but it is a known phenomenon.
Yeah.
they've been doing studies on it, it said on Wikipedia.
Nice.
They have proposed a number of hypotheses.
Yeah, it says an optical spectrum of what appears to have been a ball lightning
event was published in January 2014 and included a video at a high frame rate.
Let's see if we can find this video.
Damn, they got that shit at 144 FPS.
What came first?
Whoa, they got a mouse lightning, look at that thing.
What?
I don't know how to find the video.
Just look up ball of lightning.
I'm done with you Patrick.
Look up coolest kinds of lightning.
Coolest guy shooting lightning out of his finger.
That would be Superman.
Superman doesn't have lightning abilities.
My Superman does.
My Superman?
Yep.
Wait, your husband?
He's my Superman.
He's my rock.
I bet he is man.
Are you excited for just the next fucking 15 years of Pete Buttigieg and his husband?
Fucking on stage.
Can you see that picture of him where he didn't floss?
Yeah dude.
I've never seen, I mean I have some pretty big gaps in my-
Yeah I'm not one to talk.
I have some pretty big gaps in my teeth.
Just funny to take, like if I take a picture and you can see I didn't floss I won't post
it, I'll delete it.
I check.
I've got some pretty big gaps, I don't need to floss, but I've never seen that shit build
up.
Yeah, it was a really gross scene.
He had like British peasant teeth.
- Oh yeah, I do.
(laughing)
- You have rice teeth, dude.
- Yeah, I did.
- Yeah.
- Dude, my fucking, I got some--
- You're such a fucked up little freak.
- Little goblin, dude.
- You're just hard to look at, man.
You have those fucking crazy teeth,
those horrible feet.
- My teeth are gonna, once I get--
- You bleed green 'cause you drink so much monster energy.
- Once I get the pod money and I get my veneers.
- Mm, yeah, when we finally, when we hit like--
- 350.
- When we hit 350, what are we doing
with the what does everybody do with their cut like a heist movie? Probably
like food. I'm gonna get I'm gonna get like I'm gonna get hair plugs that are
like it's like afro hair. Just like mixed in. Yeah on top of your current hair. Just a few like parts that are really puffy.
Yeah just see I just want to see what it'll look like. I'm gonna get a snake eye on my
forehead yeah well real like it's all yeah well an actual one school I've been
looking at on the snake fangs on my fingers from this account called you a
freak and a snake tongue I'm you know where from this Instagram account called
the Istanbul hairline and it's just like some Turkish hair transplant doctor and
he posts like pictures of like the follicular like transplants don't pour
Red Bull but he posts videos of like the follicle transplants and dude it just
looks like they took a bunch of rice. Oh dude it looks fucked up.
Yeah that was I think the first time I've ever like thrown up from
looking at something. Yeah when I was like 13 that someone posted a picture of
like a hair transplant on 4chan and then I saw it and I went into
the bathroom and just threw up. So the first like six months your hair looks
your head just looks like fucked up. Yeah. Yeah. It looks like Tobias Fienke. It
looks like Tobias Fienke. No, it looks worse than that. Honestly, that
was like a palatable TV version. Yeah. Because every single one of them scabs
up. Yeah. And it gets all white. Yeah. And it looks like maggots in your head.
Yeah. That's pretty sick. Yeah. And then, but then all of them fall off. Yeah. I used to,
I used to save that to my phone. Your hairs fall off? Yeah. And then you look like Steve Carell. I saved
that to my little flip up phone and I used to send it to people when I was mad at them.
That's like I have a video of a picture on my phone of like an open penis surgery.
That sucks dude.
If somebody like air drops me a gay picture or something on the train I just immediately
air drop it back with that picture and it's really funny because they just instantly like
turn off air drop.
It's really funny.
can look at that photo and not have like an involuntary reaction so you know
exactly yeah exactly like ah somewhere on the train someone goes like ah or just
like gets closer to their phone and then really far away yeah there I can't really
write to somebody at the all troop show yeah I kept air I think it was someone
in Durban I just kept air dropping them a photo while the show was going on what
photo. I just remember they were I realized they were in front of me
because I looked down and I just saw him just going like... The screenshot I always
send is it's funny to me but it's less shocking is just the it's the screenshot
in the middle of the chimp rapes frog video where the chimp is on the ground
it's like the third stage of the video and he's jacking off with the frog yeah yeah
That's a good one to use. Or the pig with poop on his balls.
Yeah. That's a goldie.
It's so funny.
I have loved that photo for like 10 years.
Do you remember the Wolverine towel gif?
Wolverine towel gif? No.
Look up Wolverine towel gif.
Is it gross?
No, it's not gross, but it's really funny.
All right.
I used to send it to people in high school. I got into a fight with someone in high school
online and then I just sent it to them. I just kept sending it to them.
You got into a flame war?
Yeah.
I made fun of some kid for hitting his girlfriend.
Which one is it?
It's an animated GIF.
Okay, well which one is it?
What does it look like?
There it is.
This?
Oh yeah, I know this I think.
I have not seen this.
It's probably that one.
This?
Yeah.
But there's a towel that's supposed to fall off.
Yeah, he drops the towel.
Yeah, I know.
I know what you're...
I've seen this before.
They don't have the right version of it.
Hey wait what about the one next to it? This doesn't say animated GIF you
fucking stupid idiot. Press the GIF button. This doesn't look it says GIF next to the ones
that are animated. Press the GIF button up top. What GIF button? Where? They got a GIF button.
Where? It's under. Don't touch my computer. It's under tools. Don't touch my computer.
There you go. Alright now find it then. It's not here. You guys are so stupid and I'm a
a genius. Oh is that Bill Hanger? Bill Hanger. Bill Hanger? Oh my god he called us losers.
Bill Hanger is Charlie Sheem. That's a crazy guy. Charlie Sheem? Dude they shut down SNL.
Yeah. Charlie Sheen gave them all a charity. I think it's really fucked up. Me too. Because
now how am I going to get my news? Yeah dude. I get all my news skewered. It feels like
the news is pre-skewered. Feels like news is pre-roasted. And it feels like comedy is the
news now but it feels like the new kind of way for me don't move away move back
yeah you're like holding holding is right now to not like pigpin at all you are
dude you have a you have a give a cloud of vaporized guys come just surrounding
you yeah I'll have a funk just little sperms yeah just flying buzzing around
around. Yeah, disgusting little alien sperms. That's pretty good. Yeah, they have fat wings.
Little tiny things with huge fat wings. You know like how an undead dragon looks? Yeah.
It's like that but a sperm. Is that a ninja red bull? I don't know, I just picked out a
red bull. Caleb told me it was a normal one. It is normal. Yeah, no, that's a ninja edition.
It's ninja edition. Don't touch my red bull. I love touching it. We're going to call him
Cameron Blevins now. That'd be cool I'm into it. No it's not a ninja version it's it's a
USA basketball. Oh RIP. What do you mean RIP? Basketball's over. NBA is cancelled.
Because of Gobert. Well sort of. It's actually because of two Emerson kids. Yeah.
Yeah because they the Jazz practiced at the Emerson gym yeah with like four days
before with two kids who tested positive and yeah so. There were two kids at
- Was Emerson the test positive?
- Yeah, we were on the basketball team.
- What the fuck, of course the fucking basketball team
would have it too. - My alma mater
is responsible for,
one of the only things that if I'm stuck in my house
all day I like doing, it's just gone.
- Emerson kind of ruins everything.
- Yeah, it ruins everything it touches.
- The entire entertainment industry is just Emerson grads
and then some people from UCLA.
- Yeah, well that's more like the film industry,
like the TV. - It's NYU.
Yeah, like all the entry level jobs in entertainment
is just populated by NYU, UC, and Emerson grads
who all just fucking suck at their jobs.
- Yeah, it's just like Emerson people,
like half of all TV writers are probably Emerson grads
and that's why you get shows like fucking
Crazy Ex-Girlfriend and shit.
- Yeah.
- I don't know, I heard that show's pretty good,
but it's all a musical.
- No, it's not good. - Yeah.
I've heard it's good from Emerson people so it's like yeah so it's not fucking
yeah no man I mean every TV show it's like oh we're gonna we're actually
rebooting all in the family but they're queer now I think we need the only step
we took to make it woke we need another way races but he's trained yeah that's
the only step we took and it's the same show they just say he's trans at the
beginning there's a message just so you know yeah he's trans but he's not out he
comes out on like a red curtains red curtains open at the beginning of the
show he's passing just so you know Archie Bunker is passing yeah he but he
is trans yeah and then they just play an old clip yeah yeah but they're just like
just remember that Archie is trans now yeah and he says black people shouldn't
be on TV and you're like well this is genius
the Jeffersons yeah let's think about it yeah yeah hey Archie let's sit down for a while
is it Rob Reiner? It could be dysphoric right now. Rob Reiner played the son on the original show?
No it was um it was it was you no yeah it was you no just Rob Reiner had that thing did you
see yesterday Rob Reiner was like Bernie Sanders is an advocate not a president Joe Biden is a
president it's like you fat white bitch that's disappointing yeah no because Spinal Tap is my
favorite movie yeah so that's I more I like his dad more than I like him oh yeah
Carl Reiner's better I just think it's funny that he's alive
who Carl Reiner yeah he's like 98 years old yeah he should not be alive
we're gonna say this and then tomorrow he's gonna fall yeah you're right it's
our fault Mel Brooks and him they like eat dinner every night together and
watch a movie that's cute dude it's gay it's cute
yes cute as hell well yeah cuz like you're there like they're definitely gay
for each other but they're not using their penises on anything yeah yeah
they're too old to even have sex with each other but they're not gay enough to
admit that they love each other yeah yeah it's cuz they made blazing saddles
you're right mm-hmm all right now I'm thinking now he's thinking about two old
men fucking now he's now you got me thinking. Didn't somebody say that they that a
Richard Pryor. They fucked Carl Reicher. I know they fucked Richard Pryor. Oh yeah. Marlon Brando.
Marlon Brando and Richard Pryor fucked. That's so crazy. That's so awesome dude.
God that would have been such a funny turn if Richard Pryor had like
lived past the 90s and then just like in 2006 been like I'm gay. Yeah.
Richard Pryor like that story came out and he was still alive and he was just like
denying it yeah yeah man he's a man dude yeah Richard Pryor was awesome he smoked
so much crack he smoked crack because that's what winners did he smoked crack
and set himself on fire that's badass yeah dude that's like that's ghost
writer shit yeah that's a rage against the machine right there yeah yeah didn't
he try it didn't he shoot his wife's car with a revolver no that was me no you
shot Richard Pryor's wife yeah dude he had a crazy is he was braised in like a
a brothel his mom was braised in a braised in a braised cook yeah he was braised
broth yeah no he was he he was raised his mom was a whore and he was raised in a
whorehouse and I heard that and a lot of like a lot of people were like oh god
what a terrible childhood and I was kind of like that's awesome fucking sick dude
you can't get laid whenever you want by your mom's friends and you get halo 3
come on dude that's easy I'll take that over my shitty life anytime yeah they
should be like like a blank check esque movie where it's just about a kid growing
up yeah yeah it's just like by the way that happens in the movie yeah but I
mean a movie that's just about that yeah just about that one scene there's no
scene there's it's it's that scene right but it's the extended uncut edition how
How long, how many years until people re-watch Big and they're like, "He fucks a-"
I think it's gonna- Some open mic comedians done that.
Really?
For sure.
I mean, I think- No, but like until- I'm saying until there's
a Vulture article.
I think the past- The next few weeks we're gonna see a bunch
of shit canceled and people sit down and actually watch a bunch of stuff.
Yeah.
I think a bunch of people are gonna freak- 'Cause everyone's gonna go crazy in their house
and everybody's also gonna be watching like every movie.
Right.
And then we're gonna see a bunch of people going crazy over random movies that came out
like years ago.
Yes.
they'll be like he fucks a human woman he uses a piano that's too big and he
literally POC is Zoltar has a piano is way too big okay this is just sitting
unrealistic expectations for pianos plus he has kimonos virus and he's out in
public and I know the movie is called big but pick one big thing for the movie
you can't have a big piano and a big guy it makes no sense oh yeah cuz Tom Hanks
says go imagine like people try to cancel him while he's in because a big while
he's yeah trying to survive from Corona yeah and now he's trying he's struggling
to survive right now yeah no they're not not just shoveling money into his butt
and that's how you hear it he's in Australia raping children yeah he's
literally anybody who feels bad for any fucking celebrities right now have the
fire yeah Tom Hanks and Rita Wilson or Rita whatever her name is they're
they're walking around kidnapping aboriginal children with a giant
butterfly net, yeah, and taking them back to the Ritz Carlton. They have a
room that's just a blender, dude.
It looks they have this they're like yeah, let's go ride the carousel and
they all get on these little horses. It's America around, but then just the
blades come down yeah and then they drink and then they yeah they go. They
do a slip and slide after yeah, they draw a giant pentagram out of yeah out
of baby. Yeah, I'm doing Chet Chet Hanks is in there, just going Booyah
Booyaka, booyaka, booyaka, we trap the African children.
Chet, they're aboriginals.
(laughter)
Yeah, he thinks he's one of them.
Oh no, dad, what you doing to me brothers?
(laughter)
Yeah, dude.
Damn, Chet Hanks is so awesome.
He's so, I love that he did that fucking video shirtless, dude.
Yeah, so funny.
Oh my god.
And he's got the, you were saying like those fucking, those QAnon people think he's a pedophile.
Well yeah, he has the Illuminati pyramid on his chest, tatted.
That's a common stupid guy thing.
Of course, yeah.
And on his back though, he has spirals that everyone is saying is the Nambla sign.
That's so funny.
That's just a common stupid guy tattoo.
How many stupid guys like that do you think get labeled pedophiles by the QAnon people?
I highly recommend everybody, when you're stuck inside in quarantine, get into QAnon.
Oh yeah, no, go on to make a Twitter. I'm serious. So make a Twitter all this is
what I did make a Twitter all and then like find like just search cute like
hashtag. This is Cameron map.
Yeah,
and just follow every account that's it suggests you to and just like scroll
the timeline for an hour. It's the most entertaining because they're going
insane right now. They're flipping the fuck out. Like this is the best time
to look at their shit. I would say it's so fun. I like 7% believe in QAnon.
Yeah, no, there's definitely stuff that brings up this like...
There's really weird, like, synchronizations between, like, what that guy posts and what actually happens.
You can't, I mean, the whole Pizzagate thing, I did get drunk one time and say this at Muya's to us,
to the people after the "You're Gonna Love Yourself" shoot. I was like, "Yeah, some of Pizzagate is real."
Pizzagate's absolutely real.
Yeah, that one's real. That one for sure is real.
The only example I could think of up top was just like, just look at every old Shirley Temple movie.
yeah just like yeah so insane yeah yeah what if we had a baby dress up like a
whore yeah exactly that was the whole thing it was just weird old men being
it was like the biggest movie we're gonna make her a star yeah yeah what do
you think what do you think what well you think the animal crackers in the soup
represent why do you think people like animal crossing bats in the soup that's
That's what this has all been about, Shirley Temple and the Corona virus.
Oh, I'm yeah.
And yeah.
I'm yeah.
This is Dennis Miller.
I'm feeling like Shirley Temple at the Crystal Ball right now.
Dennis Miller having a stroke in the middle of his show, but people still think he's just
doing one of his jokes.
I'm a doctor.
That's kind of like Joni Lestatji and the Gizmordini.
or a server.
(laughing)
- Just like,
- Server!
(laughing)
- He comes up to me like,
- Yeah, a three headed dog.
- Dennis, you're the fucking man, dude.
- Woo!
- Hillary Clinton.
- Hillary Clinton, yeah.
- Don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't.
- It's like that video where they
- His power's off.
- Microwaved the Tickle Me Elmo.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- He's just on fire.
- God, dude.
- His face is melting.
- I'm gonna go back to,
so much as microwave shit at home when I was a kid because I remember growing up
the microwave was just another TV. Do you remember, is it a good idea to microwave this?
Yeah dude, that shit was awesome. Do you remember the one where they
microwaved the airbag? No. And it opened up inside the microwave and the microwave
just disappeared because it just blew, it just like flew off camera so fast that
it literally just like vanished. Do you remember when they microwaved the microwave? No.
No. That was a good one. I think there was one where they microwaved dynamite like outside.
Yeah, I love that show dude. That was a YouTube show. Is it still up on YouTube?
I hope so. Yeah, Jory Caron. Spend some time looking into that.
Shout out Jory Caron. Is it a good idea to microwave this?
Yeah, I think that's what it's called. I mean you'll probably find it. It was huge back in the day.
I've been back on FPS Russia. Yeah.
Now is the time. Now is FPS Russia's fucking time. He's out of jail.
yeah Jerry make a look - who dat that's the fastest shooter in the world yeah
yeah yeah I also I've been getting into this guy I think his name is Chris
Zelenoff do you know this is his name is Chris rock yeah Chris rock yeah he's
gonna get into this bit where he says the difference between it's Patrick's
favorite bit he keeps stealing it at open mics yeah but there's a like when I
I steal it I think his name is Chris Zelenoff but it's this guy who he is
like an amateur boxer but he's like this skinny little like he's like a Chet
Hanks type oh yeah and he has because he's a pedophile bought a fake like
world champion belt and he wears it around and says like I'm the world
champion of like this one league in boxing like nobody's really heard of and
he makes all these videos where he'll go to boxing gyms and he'll be like hey do
you want to like have a friendly spar with somebody and they'll be like yeah
sure we'll just have like a friendly little like spar we can teach each other
some moves and then they'll start and Chris will just like try to kill them
like he'll just like he'll try to knock them out on camera and then so it's
always just somebody like tapping gloves and then just getting punched in the
face immediately but then like he did this with with fuck what's the what's the
name of the boxer Floyd Mayweather's dad who's like this famous boxer he like met
him at some gym and he was like yeah let's let's do let's have a little
friendly spar like see if you still got it old man and he's like yeah sure haha
and they like start and then he tries to do that and there's like 80 people in
this gym who just jump on him and start beating the shit oh my god rocks - I
highly recommend watching videos there's a documentary about him Chris yeah I
I think it's Chris Zelenoff. It's something Zelenoff. Yeah, yeah. I just been
watching old interviews with Slipknot from 1999. Do they do funny Cookie
Monster voices? Yeah. No. Or do they just talk in their normal voice? They just talk in their normal, but
it's like muffled behind the mask. My favorite guy is Clown because he just is
like... It's just so funny. One guy is Clown. My favorite guy is Clown. His name is Sean. They call him Sean Clown.
It's so funny, they all have like names and then there's just Jim Roof. That's like if we called you
Cameron girl yeah but he he's just like so fucking stupid he's like an art kid
so he just like it says shit like the sound of sickness the sound of slipknot
is a dark sickness that we like to spread throughout the mind and it's like
say shit like that it's so he's so funny dude I love him didn't it's so stupid
there's like one there's one interview where someone there where they ask him
somebody asks them like what uh what do you think is the future of the human race
and then one of them's like why what are you at why are you asking us this what
and then clown takes a microphone just like we're all gonna live on Mars in
Rob Zombie our Rob Zombie went to like Parsons right something like that yeah
Rob Zombie went to like fashion school yeah I mean everybody like that is just
an art kid yeah that's true all that like that's I mean there's gonna be like
class just designing a wallet chain over just different wallet. Yeah, you
supposed to make a shirt. He's like no, you won't lose your wallet. He's just
drawing dirt and he's like what if I put this all over my face and hair? What if I
make this? What if I put dirt on a shirt? Yeah and then that's the start of his
music career. He makes a song called dirt on a shirt. Well that's an hour. Let's just stop
here and then just continue in the normal episode. Okay, all right, let's do it. All right, bye
guys. Thank you. See you. See you. Or this will come out. I don't know. We'll figure
it out. Probably release this like tomorrow or something. Yeah, we're gonna release both
tomorrow. I don't know. Yeah, we might as well. Yeah, okay, we'll figure it out. Whatever.
Premium and a regular. That's the corona shit. Bye.