Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
- Premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Okay.
- Oh!
- No.
- Yeah, Patrick's stomach hurts.
- Yep.
- Oh!
- Me and Patrick showed up to Cameron's house
and he immediately started shitting
and I started to--
- I didn't shit.
- I went, I walked out.
- What do you mean you didn't shit?
I fucking heard you.
- I farted.
- I know.
- That's how that came out.
I heard water. That was me drinking? No. You can't pretend you didn't shit, you liar.
I was hitting a bomb. You shit. No, I did not shit. You're a fucking liar. I heard it.
Yeah, that was a fart. No. No. When it becomes that wet, it's not a fart.
You're a fucking illegal. Good point. Good point. Yeah. Yeah. It was a fart I had to wipe after,
so that is a shit. What the fuck? That's a shit, dude. What are you talking about?
Any solid mass that comes out eats shit, man.
How would you say you didn't shit?
Stuff came out of your butt and you had to wipe it off
and you were sitting on the toilet and you're trying to say you didn't shit?
No, but you don't understand, it was solid fart.
It wasn't shit. It was solid fart.
It was solid fart. A fart can be kind of solid.
A frozen fart.
That was one of the...
I'm trying to not get chips every time I go to the bodega.
And I got dried apricots.
And I ate a whole thing of dried apricots
and then looked up later
that dried apricots can give you diarrhea
or they can be used to induce diarrhea.
So what did you search for that?
Do you usually search whatever food you eat and then diarrhea after a few hours later?
That's your...
Well if I'm experiencing diarrhea that bad...
Yeah, that's smart. I'm down with that.
I would google it before I ate it.
Well I don't think about that.
If you're eating apricots, you're not thinking...
The last thing you're thinking is these are used to induce diarrhea medically.
That's prunes. Prunes you think that immediately.
I guess prunes it I guess a prune is just a purple apricot. Yeah, it kind of is. Yeah
So you did kind of fuck yourself? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I mean you heard that that was like an eight-second fart
That was like the grossest. I had I put one in the hallway. I
Dusted his fucking next-door neighbor guys are so disgusting. Caleb was like literally
We can't ever go we can't was like we can't ever record a Cameron's apartment ever again
And then today's like can we please record your apartment? I need a fart really bad
I had to come over here, I had to lay down such a long bro.
We had a stink conspiracy.
Cameron, every time I have to record at my house, Cameron says I have to use your
bathroom and then he torches it.
That's not true.
You torch it.
You torch my bathroom.
I've been in there after you.
And you know what, my house sucks so bad because my house, the bathroom is the
gateway to the entire home.
You have to walk by the bathroom.
Yeah, well in this apartment, it's the gateway to the bedroom, which is where my
girlfriend sits and we're recording so it's actually worse. That is worse. That's way
worse. Yeah. Yeah. I guess, alright. Feel free to torch my bathroom whenever. Yeah, I'm just
glad we don't go to my place because it wouldn't have any effect. Yeah. It wouldn't change.
Well, my place now, I'm moving soon. I have definitely shit. And on the 28th I will reveal
my old address. I have shit at your house and left the toilet cleaner than it was
when I started shitting. Well I have shit with enough velocity that it's scraped
away. Whenever you go in and you have like diarrhea. We haven't been in my house in a while.
If you go into Pat's bathroom, not true, you go into Pat's bathroom and you have diarrhea, it will be normal and nice because that bathroom is used to having two guys have diarrhea in there at a time.
your toilet. Have you ever seen like when some really old house somebody will
take the paint off and there's like 18 layers? That is the brown like piss and shit.
I put the blue thing in there. And there's layers of blue stuck between
because you probably... I put three of those blue the scrubbing bubbles things in it. Put three?
Yeah. It was that bad? You still have to scrub though. No I do now. You do? Uh-huh. You're
really scrubbing your shit? I took an Adderall and I bought a bunch of
a toilet. You had to take an Adderall to scrub your toilet. No, I had to take an Adderall
to well I mean yeah I'm not gonna do that shit sober. Not cleaning my toilet sober bro. Adderall
is like super sober. Yeah. Adderall is is like the limitless pill and you start to do things
that you were supposed to do but forgot to. Like not get a boner and not come. Like yeah
or create 100,000 custom Magic the Gathering cards in an hour. Yeah. Those are all the
things that you had to do yeah yeah that's I found my old my old files of
custom magic the gathering cards and I like open it like a show on a nearly
when I was taking Adderall in high school and I would just like have to like
have to do homework and just take an Adderall and I like I literally open up
a file and was like 900 car like that was like one file like that was like oh
wow I don't even have the energy to read the I had an amphetamine induced budget
that I made and it was literally like it was like four days of me getting receipts
and and putting them into a Google Doc yeah and it was like the most useless
information. That's what I would do I would take I would take Adderall and I'd be
like I'm gonna type out a list of every album of music I've ever listened to
yeah it's like okay. I've done that too I've like re-edited like old Skave
videos. Yeah it doesn't make you do anything you actually have to.
- Well, I, if I use it--
- I'm still searching for my favorite drug, I think.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, I'm still looking.
All the drugs are pretty bad.
- Hi, Mom.
(laughing)
I'm not gonna say mine.
- It's poop.
It's crack.
- It's crap and pee.
- She wishes, dude.
- Yeah, she wishes I wasn't addicted to that.
- You're addicted to taking--
(laughing)
- Wow, man.
- Pat's mom, he's addicted to Plan B.
He takes it every day.
That's why he has a stomachache right now.
He wakes up every day, takes a Plan B.
- Takes a Plan B.
- And he gives himself a really bad stomachache
so he can go fart prank all of his friends.
- I wish I didn't, like, now that,
like I have to start doing more pranks on my mom
through the show, like that.
- 'Cause that was your first one.
- It was going to be, and then I felt too bad about it.
- So now you-- - But like, like, like,
- Did you really say-- - Hinting,
hinting at like a Coke addiction or something.
- It sounds like you're being way worse,
like you're doing a way worse job
covering up your drug addiction right now yeah yeah you're like adding more
pranks about drugs yeah I should think of more pranks like telling my mom that I'm
addicted to drugs on the podcast mm-hmm you're not addicted to drugs right not
but if you were if you were a drug yeah you like to do so much if you're gonna
play a prank about drugs gonna play a prank about drugs what would you say or
do well.
Opie and Anthony clips.
Yes.
That's my drug man.
Funny.
Funny videos.
Pre woke mob PC.
My addiction is funny videos.
I texted you guys about this.
I saw a homeless guy.
He had two signs and one sign said fear no woke mob, fear only God.
And then the other sign said cancel monsters, look like fools in the city.
That's right.
Cancel monsters.
- What is he talking about there?
- Cancel monsters.
- He seems like a good guy.
- Yeah.
- I think if you talk to him about
who he thinks is the monsters,
you get, probably start to believe him a little bit.
- Yeah.
- I'd like to get him on the podcast.
- Oh yeah.
- See what he has to say.
- I will have any patriot on this podcast.
- Me too.
- Absolutely.
- If you're a patriot and you're ready to defend.
- If you're the, yeah, you're the kind of guy
who has an X of tape over his mouth.
- Yeah.
- We're gonna rip the tape off first.
censored not not a not a tape over your mouth not talking about hate and tape
face you have to not a no no way and not no one tape face with it a little D next
to his name no thank you no one no one involved in the no hate campaign from
2000 we want people in hate because they're all exactly we want the hate
campaign yeah okay we want these globo homo that's right types yeah yeah we
We want if your if your mouth was stitched shut by an evil doll maker.
Mm-hmm.
We want to hear you.
If you submitted a stand-up comedy poster to Netflix and they started putting all these
all this caution tape on it right on your stand-up comedy special.
I want you.
Straight jackets.
That's right.
I need you on the podcast.
If you've ever been in a straight jacket in a promotional photo.
That's right.
You feel free to speak your mind.
If they put you in handcuffs on your on your stand-up album to keep you from hitting your
wife get on this show right this instant.
If you're from Long Island, get over here. If you're a stand-up comic from Long Island,
we need you on here. If you're playing at clubs called Chuckle's Laugh Hut,
we need to get DePaulo. DePaulo's not from Long Island, he's from Boston.
Nick DePaulo's from Boston? Well, now I trust him even more.
Isn't that crazy? Doesn't he seem like such a Long Island guy? He's from fucking Boston.
Because I don't recognize Boston Italians.
Well he's an Italian, Long Island is Italian Boston.
Yeah that's true. I think there's a kinship between those two.
What kind of kinship could that be?
White.
Yeah I think it might be some kind of white plus awesome factor that they have. Those two.
White plus awesome equals Boston and Long Island.
That's a really good comedy special name.
White plus Boston equals awesome.
Yeah.
Awesome.
Awesome plus Boston equals white.
Boston minus white equals Long Island.
Boston minus white equals trouble.
That's right.
That's the Nick DiPaolo new special name.
Boston minus white equals trouble.
He did a special a couple of years ago.
years ago yeah I remember that like the whole special I watch the entire thing dude
he's he's like just redder than ground beef he's on yeah going back and forth
just like and trans people yeah mm-hmm it's just the whole special is just him
like I think it's very pro cop - can one of you move oh I feel like I'm being
interrogated I don't want to be interrogated no you guys plan this what
if we told you that we have all the evidence we need to put you in a way for
a long time.
Cam's, ooh, I just, hold up.
What?
No socks on Cameron.
O-M-F-G.
Okay.
I'm gonna need, yep, I'm gonna need.
Vision zoom.
Activate masturbation sequence.
Voice like that.
Oh my god, he's putting it right in my face.
What do you think?
He has a tattoo on his, what the hell?
You got a tattoo?
Yeah, he's got a little stick and poke on the bottom of his face.
I'm gonna need, yep, I'm gonna need.
Vision zoom.
Activate masturbation sequence.
Oh my god, he's putting it right in my face.
What do you think?
He has a tattoo on his, what the hell?
You got a tattoo?
hell he's got a little stick and poke on the bottom of his foot it's like a X
kind of hmm what does that mean what is that supposed to mean hmm kind of a
funny symbol that's where I got tickled oh yeah it's like an X marks the spot
you got a little tickle spot yeah - - like Z's kind of making an actually yeah
I was so the tattoo artist was sleepy oh so he started drawing Z's yeah and
exactly yeah interesting X is supposed to symbolize I'm not tired anymore no I
told you it's a tickle spot. So okay. So it's like two Z's but then there's also two...
There's a circle around the Z. What is the double S? Does that mean
something like super sweet? Super sleepy. Super sleepy. So a tired tattoo artist. He's really tired.
That's the end of his shift. And that eagle is... He works a shift at McDonald's. Okay gotcha.
He tattooed you there. Yeah. That eagle is, I mean, that's obvious it's for America. No
it's you don't you count eagles when you go to sleep? You ever done that? No I don't
I don't count eagles.
You can't.
Why not?
They fly too fast.
It's too fast.
Okay, well this guy does.
I count turtles.
Yeah, he could only get to one before he fell asleep.
And it is interesting.
What is the, there's also just kind of a, just a normal smiley face too.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, what the hell is that?
Yeah, it's a smiley face.
That's pretty embarrassing for you.
Yeah, that's kind of fruity.
I kind of wish you guys didn't say that one.
You're a bit fruity for that one.
I don't.
Yeah.
Can we edit?
I know somebody has a palm tattoo. Even just talking about that, look at how sweaty my
hand got. Do you see that?
Your hand was not. He's covering his tracks.
He mentioned it to cover up how sweaty his hand got.
Look at how sweaty my arm. I'm scared. I'm scared of getting a palm tattoo.
Guys do you ever think about Dracula? Whoa, look how sweaty I got just now. That's why
I'm so sweaty.
You know what, I'd be scared of a stigmata. Hold on.
stuff really freaks me out when like somebody hurts their hand it makes my
hand sweat. You see my you don't feel it? So you think that you think that
it's not there anymore. Our King of Kings is freaky. Yeah. Well that's what it comes
from is that I'm so touched by the Word of God. I don't think so. I think you
think he's freaky. I don't think he's freaky. I think you want you want to put him on a
Goosebumps cover because you think he's so scary. No. Nope. Not at all. That would be a
fire-ass cross that would be pretty tight Jesus Jesus bumps yeah well okay so it's
like a family of God they ever do they should do just like a Christian like
goose bumps they should really Christian SNL yeah and then why not do could
actually videos no that's not Christian SNL you never watch that shit was
muffling if it's not SNL how come that motherfucking squash dress up like Elvis
that was some Andy Kaufman shit that was on the next level no dude it was crazy
VeggieTales is not Christian SNL. Then name what is okay it's the it's the
Christian Simpsons obviously there's no Christian Simpsons VeggieTales VeggieTales
was SNL did they did sketches about God they didn't do just sketches yeah they
didn't do just okay okay hold on VeggieTales is Christian family guy how
about that that doesn't know that it wasn't cutaway there's whole episodes
As soon as you go with it, you lose the argument. Okay? Yeah, that's my rule with you. So I'm
done talking to you.
Here's my pitch for the first Christian Goosebumps book. My babysitter was a sinner.
And it has like sex.
That's good.
That's a little much.
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, I don't know why you jumped to like immediately like an old babysitter
having sex with a young kid.
No, no, having sex with her boyfriend.
I mean, you can do whatever you want with your book series.
boys. How about the monster under my bed chose to be gay? What do you think
about that? Yeah, it could be stuff like that or like the the the goblins chose
to be gay. A werewolf chose to be gay. Yeah, I saw the gay werewolf. I saw the
gay werewolf. He chose it by the way. The gay werewolf did not give up anything
for Lent. The werewolf. Yeah, what about gay beasts from Mars? Oh, that's good.
yeah I some gay beasts from New York City yeah oh that's really good that's the
werewolf from San Francisco uh-huh the werewolf of San Francisco and it's like
bad a werewolf who is you know yeah he wears a harness yeah I'm like the balls
at his dick around at some kind of parade what's the deal San Francisco you
get your balls out well there's that I forget what what the fair is called but
there is like they close up in a sin common I think it's this guy's nuts fair
there's something Street Fair and if they close off a block and they put like
guards around it and it's just a bunch of like naked people yeah like people in
like pissed tubs and yeah yeah there's all the it's the the the penicillin
sphere yeah and then every year that they do that there's always somebody
post like my kid saw a guy's cock and balls out why'd you take the kid to the
Yeah, you can smell that fucking street from a mile away.
Why are you getting anywhere near that with your child?
I would love to go through there with a leaf blower.
I think that would be funny.
You'd like to go through there with one of those fucking
things a dentist gives you that sticks your mouth open
like this.
(laughing)
Just kind of catch shit and be unable to close your mouth.
That's what you want to do.
The latex one, when they're putting a crown on.
The one that goes like this.
You know, it just keeps everything in your mouth
perfectly exposed.
Yeah, I'd be using the--
I'd be going in there with a vacuum instead.
I'd be going in there with the dentist moisture sucker and I'd have a vacuum bag on my back like a Ghostbuster and I'd be sucking up anything I see.
Catching pee?
Some fat old guy in like a metal tub, covered in, he's like, "Piss on me, five dollars."
You go up there, steal all of his pee and he gets mad at you.
I'm building a homunculus from all of your DNA.
This is gonna be the biggest person in the world.
I'm making gay Frankenstein.
Uh-huh. All this pee is gonna synthesize together to create the world's tallest person.
I want to make a homunculus pretty bad. Yeah. You guys remember that video?
Uh-huh. The guy who injects semen in an egg? Yeah. Yeah. It's pretty cool.
That's more like homo-culus, because he's putting his damn semen in a male egg.
How do you know it's a male egg? You can tell it. Male eggs are brown. Girl eggs are white.
Is that true? Yeah. I had chickens when I lived in New Hampshire.
So I'm paying extra to eat a male egg and kind of--
Well, yeah, because it's got more testosterone.
And I--
That's why the egg is brown.
Absorb his essence, right?
Uh-huh.
Okay.
That makes sense to me.
That's why eating eggs is good.
That's why eggs are the best food you can eat.
I do eat a lot of eggs.
Yeah.
I know your stanky ass didn't have no chickens.
Yeah, I did.
No, you didn't.
Yeah, we did.
They kept getting eaten by a fox.
You just kept fucking feeding this fox.
Sounds like you had a fox.
Yeah.
More or less out of fog. Yeah, you were getting you fed him chickens. Yeah, cuz yeah that barn
Remember now remember that bar. No, you never I forgot I forgot you went to New Hampshire
But you got down for the farm. No the barn the barn it was a barn farm
Okay, darn the darn the dark the yarn the farm was next door and they had maple syrup tubes all through her backyard
You're just making up a Willy Wonka fucking fuck factory in New Hampshire was starring a chicken and Tim
where is in where New Hampshire you're shutting up right now is what you're
doing it was where in New Hampshire I'd give the address out but it's still the
address on my ID it was what does that mean what does that have to do with
anything I forgot to change my ID no matter gonna hack your ID card well I
I don't want them to look at my ID.
- What does that mean?
- My picture, I look so young in my picture.
- What do you mean, how would they find your picture?
- They're gonna find me in a database
and they're gonna see how young I look.
- There's a database of every ID.
- Why would they be able to search your old address
but not your full name?
- They're gonna find my ID.
(laughing)
- You have like the stupidest idea of privacy
of anybody I've ever met.
- No I don't.
- You absolutely do.
crazy oh god damn you yeah what was I thinking I was thinking of really really
good thought yeah yes probably you'll us we're talking about I want to talk about
a little July eggs for guys oh that's black eggs black eggs guys love black
black shit. It's true. Yeah, like a sleek egg. Yeah, yeah, we did like a sly.
What? Sly egg like a cool egg. Cool black egg for guys. Okay, coolest blackest egg
on the market. We just sell black. You can't what? You can't sell black egg?
You can't say the egg in the way you're saying it. It's a cool black egg. You
can't say it like that. Why would it be cooler to have a black egg instead of a
white egg. It's true. See, it's true. There's a certain way you're saying it
though you can't say it. We're making a super fly egg.
He's saying like a super fly egg. That's what he's saying. What is wrong with you guys?
Like a dope-ish shit egg. Yeah, see Pat gets it. It's a cooler egg. You're the only one
not on board. It's cooler than a white egg. Yeah. It's just always been cooler.
yeah right right it's a black egg we just black I think like an Easter do we die
black or do we add like like you know how like Batman's like car has like
spoilers we put a spoiler on the egg can't fake you can't fake the black egg
no black eggs got to be born with it okay yeah yeah I put a spoiler we got it
we got to do some kind of reverse engineering on chickens so they're
popping out there are black chickens they will actually send you guys a
- There's a picture of the black egg.
This is a real, I just, there's a picture of the--
- Oh, so you got all fucking,
your britches got up in a bunch
'cause we are talking about cool-ass daddy-o black eggs.
And then all of a sudden,
you're the inventor of the black egg?
- I'm not the inventor.
I found it on Facebook or something.
I sent you guys the black egg.
Do you remember?
I sent it, it was like,
this black chicken laid the blackest egg ever.
- Yep, I remember that, actually.
- Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
Let me see if I can find it.
- Okay, so yeah, it's fine to sell black eggs then.
And we're gonna make a million bucks.
- Yep.
We're gonna find that chicken.
- We have to find, here it is.
- There's a blue chicken.
- The black chicken.
- Oh my God, those are black eggs.
- It's the black chicken that lays black eggs.
And it was posted on a Facebook group called Earth Unreal.
- That is unreal.
- I'll send this picture to you guys
so everyone can see, we'll post it.
- I hung out with chickens last weekend.
Do not like them.
- They suck, dude.
- I thought I liked chickens 'cause of a video
- With a chicken?
- Are you like, shit, dog?
- No, they fucking chase you around, dude.
- Dude, it thinks, the roosters are fucking nasty to me.
- Roosters are, ugh.
- They're crazy nasty.
- They try to get up, I was on--
- No, we had a rooster for a little bit
and then that got picked off.
- Yeah, I was on a farm in Western Mass last year
and there was like, you could go pet the animals and stuff
and there was a bunch of little kids there
and the chickens are just chasing all the kids.
- Shit.
- It's like, little, yeah, the chicken,
they're like the same size as the kids and they put the parent yeah the parents
are like they put their arms up like that they start running after you yeah
they do they chase when they reach out their hands and they go yeah yeah but
the other love to chase kids and nobody does anything about it that's well
Colonel Sanders that's true that's true he's he saw what was happening yeah I
chasing the children around I would love to like Norm Macdonald what remember
Norm Macdonald was Colonel Sanders for a year?
Yeah, I was doing Norm Macdonald.
That was pretty funny.
That's what he sounded like, Norm Macdonald.
It was just so funny to have every other Colonel Sanders be like, "Well, I'm with the chicken
is the..." and then just one guy's like, "Ah, chicken.
Ah, fucking.
Yeah, it's good.
Can't see.
Ah, it's fucking herbs and spices."
I do want to be...
My goal, honestly, in life is to be a fast food mascot at some point.
Yeah, they're only, hey, all fast food mascots nowadays, they're making them all girls, so
good luck.
He's already the mascot of Big Boy.
has hair he had chemo you just make it I'm not big boy went through team I'm not
big and fat he can make a really good Wendy actually yeah like a wig I would
be a really good you'll be really good Wendy I really I feel like the goal is
good you'd be like a good grimace how am I grimace straight-up grimace grimace
what about me is very real spider legs at all airless no grimace was covered in
hair no he's not blobby you blob he's not purple blob your gumdrop used to be a
spider you know that he's a spider grimace I used to be a spider in the
70s 1973 grimace was a spider I was a spider how long three - probably a little
bit I want to crack him open yeah see what kind of these are these guys is an
egg I think he is a purple egg yeah no guy he's not he's a monster he's not a
a monster. Don't be ridiculous. He is not a monster. He's Ronald's friend. He's a
monster and he's not a friend. He's evil. I feel like the best. He was evil and then
he had a turn. People like that. You don't know shit about McDonald's grubber. Monsters like Grimace never go good. I feel like the
best, the best role is obviously. They never go good. The best role is obviously Ronald. Yeah.
Yeah. But I'm not sure. No the best role is that new little Happy Meal guy. They
replaced Ronald. You are on a crusade about this guy. I hate him. He does suck. He's
sucks. What if we got a new Taco Bell mascot? My nephew is being indoctrinated into liking
this. Oh, a new Taco Bell mascot could be really good actually. Yeah. A Chihuahua? Not a Chihuahua.
No, a new one. Maybe like a... So a new dog. Maybe like a banker. A bull mastiff that eats
Taco Bell. I could play Pitbull. Yeah. In a TV movie. Yeah, say Dale. That I could play
very well. That's actually the ultimate Taco Bell mascot. We used to have a
chihuahua, now we have... A Cuban guy. Yeah. The ultimate Taco Bell mascot. A clearly Cuban man. I don't know if he's
clearly Cuban. If I look exactly like him, I don't think he can be
clearly Cuban. Well, you don't look... you look exactly like him by choice. What do
you mean? You think that he doesn't choose to shave his head? No, he has no... he
lasers that shit off he's got money. He's a reptilian. It's still a choice though. Yeah he's got
reptilian dollars. He's a reptilian heir. Yeah. I wouldn't be surprised if Pibble
claimed in a song that he's a bazillionaire. That's so cool that
chameleonaires name is actually because he like they said he looked like a
chameleon. Yeah he's just like ugly and then he made it into a whole thing.
It's so cool.
You know he's like a lyrical spiritual miracle guy.
Yeah.
And the Ride and Dirty is like his only song that's like good and every other song is like
it's like he makes, it's like a song about him being like a medieval knight.
What was that?
It's just an ugly woman laughing.
Yeah.
Dude there was the other day.
It's like a witch.
(laughing)
- Don't fist bump me, that's scary.
I don't want a witch near my apartment.
- Why?
- The other day, I think it was going to your place,
but, oh, it was definitely your place.
You know how there's like the stairs you gotta walk down
to like get off the train?
- Oh, I thought you were talking about at my house.
- No, you know how your house has like stairs?
- Yeah.
- And like cabinets and like a sink?
But like there's the stairs you gotta walk down
the train station, there's like these like
Three like people just like sitting on the steps eating like slices of pizza and everyone was just like
Because there was like it was so congested because it was like probably five o'clock people were coming home from work
and these kids are like standing like
Turning to everybody in just like just go around
and like for
It took me like probably like two minutes to get off the stairs because these fucking people would just like we're just sitting there eating pizza
and then like anytime somebody told them to move,
they called them gay.
- That's cool.
- It was sick. - That's pretty sick.
- Yeah.
- I miss being a bad boy kid.
I was never that cool.
- Oh, dude, being a little piece of shit?
- I would just like,
I only felt good about shitting on an adult
when it was like six versus one.
So like even if you tried to fight me--
- Getting kicked out by a security guard somewhere.
- Like we can still overpower you.
Security guard doesn't have anything on him.
- Yeah.
But if it's like an older woman who works in an office
and is telling you to stop skating
inside of the office. That's what we used to do. You flip her off. Yeah. I didn't see a
sign that says no skateboarding. I'd flip her off the roof. That's what we did.
That's right. Do a tabletop. Yeah. Fucking kill her. You're not supposed to be on my roof. That's right.
It's her fucking bloody battered body at the bottom of the barrel and I'm a
stupid big bald bitch. Bulbous ass. Yeah with a butt. I sure as hell had a big ass.
Did you guys hear that two monkeys killed 200 dogs by flipping them off of tall buildings
and towers?
I literally did hear that.
I told you, I already heard that.
Yeah.
There's a monkey attack on dogs in a village.
Basically dogs killed a monkey baby and the monkeys took revenge by throwing 200 dogs
off of towers in a village.
Swear to God.
It wasn't any of our dogs, right?
Yeah.
Well, it was here.
It was, they were throwing them off of the Empire State Building.
No.
Yeah.
Thank you problem in New York is getting there was something that some some like
fucking truck full of monkeys that the doesn't Philly though but they could
New York City there's so many towers here I were a monkey and I were in a war
against dogs I would move to New York it is funny that if you're a monkey if a
monkey lived in New York City it would just be spider-man yeah all the dogs
dogs here are the perfect size to be thrown off a tower. All the dogs in
Manhattan are bred with some kind of poodle. They're all different. Yeah,
exactly breeds. So like I was a monkey soldier if like you know like instead of
like imagine no more rats in New York City is all monkeys. Yeah, so it's like
shit. I'm the anti dog monkey death squads. Yeah, yeah, I'm patrolling. I
- Fuck every monkey in the world.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
There was a--
- I fuckin' hate, I used to love, I hate monkeys now.
- Yeah.
- I got way more into like alligators.
- Looking up videos of like--
- Fuck monkeys, man.
- Like I saw a video of a spider monkey in a house
and saw that it like tipped over
like somebody's like medicine cabinet.
- I especially hate the little ones.
- Yeah, I really--
- The little ones love mischief, man.
- I like monkeys still.
- They fuckin' steal people's hats
and they waddle away in their fuckin'
stupid little diaper. I told you about that neighbor I have with a monkey.
No I've definitely I've talked about that before.
Yeah the diapered monkey. Speak on it. There was a diapered monkey that lived
next to me and the monkey had to gamble for its food on a slot machine. You did
you yeah see I knew about this and Pat was the one who didn't. He asked Caleb to
tell it and then he took out his phone. You dropped me a photo. Yeah I was opening
the photo. 15 minutes ago. Well I got a notification for it now. You're just a
liar now. Yeah. I can show you the photo. You belong to the monkeys. I know what the
photo is. I airdropped it to you. Okay. Do you guys think that if you went into the
jungle and met a bunch like a huge village of... A talking monkey? A community? No, not even
talking monkeys. Do you think that if you were if you fell out of a plane right
and you were you were broken and you were cold and you were naked and
a group of kind or not even kind of monkeys if a group of monkeys found you
Would they recognize you as as they would eat you you think they'd eat you they eat other monkeys
I think I think some people might be chosen by monkeys to be
You see the hair on my body. They'd be like you could pass as a
Monkey, yeah, if you're strong if you're strong and you throw one of them against a tree or something
They'll have to establish dominance. Yeah. Yeah, but like they will they'll just eat you otherwise, but not I'm not talking chimps. I'm like, yeah
Little monkeys won't eat you.
It will.
No they don't, they eat fucking fruits.
A spider monkey will bite you.
I know, damn apple.
They're omnivores, dude.
They eat like little bugs and stuff.
They're eumnovores, they ain't mean-ivores.
Okay, they're gonna eat your fucking lame ass.
They're eating you for sure, dude.
Nah, I don't eat enough sugar to be sweet.
No.
I'm sour.
You would honestly...
They literally think your head is an apple
and they would try and eat it.
They would eat Patrick's body
and like their hearts would explode from caffeine.
It's like feeding a seagull Alka-Seltzer.
You know those videos of when like somebody like in like India or something
they like put down a box full of food and all the monkeys like swarm it?
That's what it would be on Patrick's body.
Could you imagine pulling off one single hair?
Things are switched like we have like India's monkey problem.
And what problem do they have?
I mean like monkeys are pests there.
Yeah.
Yeah dude.
Of course I would hope they're pests if they're throwing dogs off of towers.
Yeah, that's more like villains. Yeah, that's true. That's like monsters. We don't even know we don't have villains like
Those are pet a rat has never thrown an animal
Taking the trash out at night and you just see like like ten raccoons and like a thing imagine that but it's just monkeys
Yeah, yeah, I think about so scary. Yeah, they're too smart is the thing. Yeah, and they have human bodies
Yeah, what am I supposed to do? There's this one like I think I was
I was leaving that bar that we were hanging out at and every it was like
cold out so all the the rats were hiding in the trash bags and then every step I
took near a trash bag fucking ten rats would jump out yeah dude I was oh those
are cool that was monkeys I like the rats that would suck to have like a monkey
that's like in your apartment yeah monkey living in your wall you'd like
leave a window open one day or like you come on there's a monkey yeah it's
fucking you all your all your all your waffle crisp.
It's the last time you ever eat.
Monkey.
Yeah, they're also there's more like if you have a rat in your
wall, it'll eat like your drywall or something, but a monkey
smart enough that it knows what is good that what you like and
it will eat that stuff.
Yeah, like a rat won't like eat your like favorite snack, but
a monkey will be lying to your favorite snack.
Yeah, because it's also its favorite snack.
A monkey is going to put like waffle crisp you bought in bulk
on Amazon.
The monkey exactly.
It's going to put monkey dress.
- A monkey dresses up like you,
goes to the door, takes the package,
and then you come home and all of your
waffle crisp is eaten by this monkey in a suit.
- We designed the stuff that we like to look cool,
and monkeys have the same brains as us,
so they also think the same stuff is cool.
- It's true.
- So they're gonna come in,
they're gonna just steal your PlayStation controllers
and run away.
- They literally will.
- It's like their brain looks at it,
and like this is a fun thing.
- The monkey touches my Switch,
deletes my save game.
- I'm gonna walk in,
- A monkey's gonna have my Oculus Quest
on playing Hitman 3 in virtual reality.
- Exactly, a rat comes into my house,
it's gonna try and steal my trash,
you stupid fucking idiot, I don't care about that.
I'm gonna get rid of that.
- Hey, newsflash, I hate the trash.
(laughing)
I hate trash, eat all you want, you fucking idiot.
- You can have that, check this out, it's a banana peel.
- Monkey's gonna take the trash can.
- That's when we have a problem.
- Hey, I actually seriously need that monkey.
- I know it's shiny monkey.
- Yeah, monkey, stop taking--
automatic trash can you can't take that my money's gonna take all your like like
your coin jar that you use for laundry you can't use that monkey the monkeys a
hundred percent taking your Funko pops - oh they're gone this is first thing
this is gone yeah this is the this is the audio that plays in like a like a
cutscene to like a planet of the Apes reboot where it's like guys listen to
who plays it and monkeys yeah the money's like before like the takeover
just everyone like monkeys are so stupid we realize that our intercom is on monkeys
are so bullshit yeah that would be no good I've never been all that I've never
been I've never touched a monkey I would like to touch a monkey never done it I
wouldn't touch you ever seen those videos of the monkeys being amazed by
the guy's hair yeah it's pretty cool yeah I'm afraid I've been afraid to I've
been afraid of like not touch a monkey but it been afraid to eat around monkeys
since I saw us Moses Jones as a kid because I like oh yeah he tries to take
your yeah yeah the monkey yeah he tries to take his hard-boiled egg and it gets
all into the dirt yeah you never know what's on the dirt yeah you get AIDS is
it is it supposed to be now it's a it's Moses Jones is about a oh I didn't even
think about that it kind of is yep well I know Forrest Gump is about a he shares
his egg for a month it's not about AIDS it's about not eating food off he takes
a monkey's egg that is him yes he's like well no the monkey takes his egg well I
mean we don't know what happens think about the monkey yeah they share an egg
together yeah they share a beautiful they cohabitate yeah Bill Murray fucks a
chimp yeah yeah osmosis Jones is a scary looking
Eric punishes have you seen what he looks like when he smiles as Moses Jones
cool is the scariest smile of any like good guy animated character it's so
sick I've rewatched osmosis Jones recently such a good movie man the
animation it's so scary when he slices the guys in half they turn to go do when
he has his his hot finger and he's like cutting through stuff. The hot finger is
like one of the ultimate villains. That is the coolest. So first of all this is what
Osmosis Jones looks like when he smiles. That's just his normal smile. He looks
like he does that when he's like hey guys nice to see you and he does that
smile. He looks evil as hell. It's good. Is Osmosis Jones about AIDS? When I
rewatched Osmosis Jones like a year ago, maybe less, and I was watching it with Anna
and I was like yeah the bad guy get the bag guy so cool his name is strep finger
believed in my head that his name was something I made up in my head as a kid
when I watched it no wait like they're gonna call him strep think like he
showed up and they didn't call him stripping or like they'll call him that
later his name's supposed to be racks strip is that movie about the anthrax
scares what does his name's tracks it's like tracks a mundar what are you
fucking talking about Thrax and virus yeah yeah it is made out of spores it's a
poison poison virus doesn't have spores I did not get a good grade in my plagues
class you thought they you thought it's about a monkey that puts anthrax on in
the mail and then gives it to Bill Murray somebody at NBC when they did the anthrax
scares was like we're gonna make this movie yeah but it's gonna be a monkey in
an egg now. What came first? You honestly asked the question. What came first, the
monkey or the egg? It's a good question. But yeah, I was so mad that it
wasn't named Strip Finger. I felt like that's like a way better name. It's a
cool name. I googled it and it's just nothing. If I caught Strip Finger, I'd be
"ooh". You better catch this Strip Finger. That's right. Right up in your fucking...
Hmm?
Right up in your--
And do kids in a sandbox?
Is that what we're gonna do?
Doing it in your dookie shoot.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
I was thinking of the front hole.
Nope.
That's nasty.
Sounded by a finger.
You're gonna hear the sound of this finger going up your doo-doo surprise.
Yeah.
Finger in the dinger.
Well, there, I mean, I would not do it today.
Today is especially good for me because of all the dookie in your butt that I wanna fucking
feel around.
I was gonna save it up.
No.
out my window. I don't want one, I don't want a giant. Because we were in LA like
two weeks ago I'm still thinking of like remembering the you tell me the story
about the lady getting a cup of diarrhea thrown at her. Oh yeah, that's a great
story. That is the most evil man. I probably told that to eight people while we were in LA.
Yeah, they were like hey you lived here for a minute why'd you move and I was
like there's a lot of things but one thing is a lady got hot diarrhea and
then somebody told me I told him that story and they were like I actually saw
that on the news and it wasn't hot diarrhea in a cup, it was hot diarrhea in a bucket.
Yeah, it was a bucket.
Okay.
Yeah, it always was a bucket. I think when we originally talked about it.
That's the rarest kind of story of like telephone where it actually gets less,
there's less diarrhea.
Yeah, no, I remember it being a bucket.
It was actually way more diarrhea than I even thought.
Yeah.
We want to soften the blow.
Because the bucket, so it's already...
If I was that lady, I'd tell everybody it was a cup, not a bucket.
It's already premeditated, but if I was 40% crazier, I could imagine myself finishing
a large sweet tea from McDonald's and then saying I'm gonna diarrhea in this
yeah but to go and get a bucket yeah and diarrhea in the bucket and then put it
on a woman's head also you have to walk around with the bucket of diarrhea like
Kevin from The Office we just look I mean just pretend as your business goddess
it's got to stay hot so you got it exactly you're holding it with you're
holding it with pot holders, you're walking around with the bucket of diarrhea.
Just whistling, skipping your loo.
Keep the lid on so it doesn't...
I think maybe he was going to a diarrhea pot look and had an accident.
He might have been going to a diarrhea cook-off. That's a really good point.
And then he spilled it.
Eddie's million dollar diarrhea cook-off.
Do you think it was hot because it was fresh or do you think he heated it up?
Well it's not because of the damn LA sun and climate change.
I think it was night time probably.
it up, well it's got to be nighttime because you're smelling the
diarrhea and looking around saying which direction is that coming from. If it's
daytime you're identifying the threat immediately. If it's nighttime it's
a little bit harder. Yeah exactly. So I think yeah no this guy this guy really
planned it out and I think he had to have heated up the diarrhea because if
there's enough diarrhea to fill up a bucket. Yeah exactly. It can't be that fresh.
But it might have been like you know when you're sometimes you're in a bath the
bath gets a little cold you add just a little bit of really hot water so maybe
Maybe the diarrhea got cold and he spurted out an especially hot one.
Yeah.
Just to like kind of temper the entire thing a little bit.
That's a good.
Does that make some sense?
That makes a lot of sense to me.
Thank you.
Yeah.
You're welcome.
But yeah, I think that is one of the coolest things I've ever had.
Yeah.
He could also have had, it could have been like, you know, a tin bucket, like a classic
bucket and he has a set up kind of like a witch and he kind of has a cauldron type set
up with a fire and a big stick and he's stirring it.
bucket that goes on two burners that like that Cajun chef guy uses? Stale Cracker?
I only know about witches. Oh yeah. You ever seen that guy, Stale Cracker? No I've seen a witch.
He's great. I only know like porn stuff. Stale Cracker is a guy that's like he makes like the
big-ass like gumbo pots and stuff. Oh he pours orange juice and shit into it? Yeah. Why'd he be
pouring that orange juice? Oh I don't think it's that guy. Stale Cracker is the guy that's like
"We're gonna put on a cracker, dude."
He sounds Cajun.
He's got like a big, yeah, he's making gumbo.
Oh, really? He sounds seriously Cajun.
I was watching a video of him earlier where he's like, "Today I'm gonna learn you how to make deer lollipops."
Deer lollipops.
Deer? Deer meat lollipops.
- That's hot. - Okay, popsicles or lollipops?
- Dear meat popsicles. - 'Cause a lollipop is not cold.
- Yeah, that's frozen beef jerky.
- That's just, oh, dear lollipop is just meat on a stick.
- Yeah, it's just the rib bone.
- And so is a popsicle, it's just cold meat on a stick.
- It's the rib bone cooked with a little bit--
- A dear lollipop is so much more gross
than a dear popsicle. - Yeah, it's just hot.
- Yeah, 'cause a lollipop is hot.
It's a good point. - What if they gave you
a bunch of-- - What is the Cajun two-step?
- What if they gave you just meat at the bank
instead of lollipops for the price of that?
- Yeah, the meat bank?
- No, not the meat bank.
- No, like as a treat.
- Oh, like you get a Slim Jim instead of a--
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Like instead of a--
- I feel like I would much rather,
I would start going to the bank
and I would start getting money.
- Yeah, I would deposit and withdraw like--
- Yeah, why don't we just go to the bank every day
and withdraw and deposit and just get a free lollipop.
- Just get free lollipops and then start a lollipop business.
and then start selling the lollipops.
- It's always, you're always gonna make a profit.
- Plus it's dumb dumb mystery flavor.
What the hell kind of flavor is that?
- We're working, yeah.
I mean, with the money I make from my lollipop business,
I'm gonna be funding a research study.
- Yeah, I got a couple scientists.
- Huge research team into the flavor of the mystery flavor.
- Well, the thing is, well, here's the secret
about the mystery flavor.
- What is it?
- It's different every time.
- It's always strawberry.
- What does that mean?
- That would be, they could just do,
they could, it would take a while for people to catch on
if they're just like, just did only strawberry
and just put the mystery,
you can't tell what it tastes like
without the wrapper color.
- I wonder how they get the,
oh, do you know that,
I wonder how they get a wrapper that doesn't say a flavor.
(laughing)
Where do they find those?
- How do you get those question mark wrappers?
- And how do they get the question mark onto the wrapper?
- That's a really good point.
- You know if you save the-- - Pencil or crayon or--
- If you save the wrappers,
if you, it used to be you could send them in
and get like a t-shirt.
- I'd like to save the wrappers
from these pressed fentanyl Xanax pills.
- Yeah, I'm not saving any of them.
- I'd like to save every last one of them.
- Maybe if instead of doing Xanax,
we replace it with lollipops.
- A little peep would be alive, man.
He'd still be, he'd be singing his little
fucking heart out every day.
- Yeah, I mean if he knew the wonders of Mr. Dum-Dum.
- I would love to have him taxidermied
and set up like right in that corner right there.
That'd be awesome.
And he's doing a bear pose and be like, "Oh, he almost got me."
"He almost got me.
Luckily, I popped a Fiddle pillow in his mouth with a dart gun."
Thank God, dude.
Just him, you're just like dressing him up.
You're using him to play in your outfit for the day.
He's my coat hook.
He has his own map.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
That'd be so hard.
That'd be sick, dude.
Well, not Lil Peep.
Are you kidding?
That's Lil Peep.
Well, I mean, just like a taxidermied thing that holds your clothes.
I want to have little people is going to be like you know that they would they put
outside of pizza places the little pizza guy statue he's gonna be that for my for
my bedroom check out this place is that little peeps dead thing out holding out
a plastic plate of spaghetti he has a long twirly mustache yeah you know
that's mostly a north end thing you see that mostly there's a north end in
Boston has the same yeah yeah in chef yeah yeah that dude every restaurant
with the big black mustache.
I think if I make a lot of money, I'm gonna buy the corpses of every rapper and I'm gonna
make a merry-go-round with them where you ride on them.
Oh that'd be cool.
Yeah.
Like House of Wax.
Yeah, like House of Wax, except you ride on them like horsies.
Yeah, that'd be really fucking cool.
And I could make really rich, fucked up guys pay money to do that.
I think that might be illegal.
Do you ever see the pirate that they put in restaurants?
No.
There's a, okay maybe it was just in my hometown, but there was a pirate that they had, it's
like a big like pirate statue.
There's two or three different restaurants all had the same pirate.
None of these restaurants were pirate themed.
I think it was one of the-
I think you've seen a ghost.
There was this diner my mom used to work at that had a pirate in the lobby.
Have you ever seen this-
And then there was a different pizza place that had the pirate.
This red and white stick statue they have in front of all these barber shops in my hometown.
I've seen that.
Also, they have a different red and white stick when Santa comes.
Yeah, that's true.
It's kind of interesting.
I hear it's the same one, but it's a seasonal.
Were you mad as a kid when you found out that that barber pole didn't taste like candy?
Yeah.
Yeah, I think so.
I was really mad.
Yeah, I got really, really mad.
I killed the barber.
When I lived in Boston, near Coolidge Corner, there was some apartment building that had
a fake like a butler statue in the lobby and it was like I don't know if it was
like a Halloween decoration that just left out or not because it like was like
it like held out a bowl, but it didn't look like like Halloween. It was just
like a butler that held out a bowl with something for swing, but it would
literally it would startle me every time I walked by because it's just like a
like it was like like the guy you're talking about holding out a boy. I would
all I would always be walking by at night and like everything would be dark
except that like the lobby would have all the lights on it would just be like a
got like a hunched over butler guy looking at me. That's a seriously bad gig. Yeah.
Yeah, just you know. I want one bad. Oh, I want a butler to torture. You want to torture the
butler? You want a butt butler. Oh, so paying somebody to serve your turds. You
want a, you want to, you want a Hutler. Hutler. Above Hutler.
Yeah, you want that guy. Yeah. Yeah, I want it so I can throw him off my balcony.
No, you want to get Adolf Hitler to be your butler.
Off my penthouse balcony when I'm rich as fuck.
No, you wouldn't be.
I buy Hitler's bones when I'm rich as fuck and I keep them skeletonized in a glass case.
But not the real Hitler's bones.
I buy all of Hitler's real bones.
if I had a million dollars I'd buy Hitler's bones.
It's the first verse of that song.
If I had a million dollars, I'd buy Hitler's bones.
It's just all about buying Hitler's shit.
If I had a million dollars, I'd buy Hitler cyanide tooth. If I had a
million dollars, I would buy you blondies ball.
These ball
I would get I would buy Hitler's bones and I would keep them all in separate
room, so they could never reassemble and become an evil skeleton. As far as
dry Hitler
you're clink clink clink.
- Yeah.
- Oh great, I got to go go-cart racing for some reason.
- I have to ground pound him again.
- Yeah.
- Take another few years to reform.
- Taylor was in front of me, bro.
He's catching a blue shell to the back of the head.
- Oh, dude.
- Absolutely.
- You think Taylor's in first place?
- If he is.
- No, but if he would, I'd kill him with my blue shell.
- You see.
- And I might do some mushrooms and get even speedier than him, so.
- I finally found that video.
- Guess who's the racist Nazi now, Mr. Nazi you?
I finally found that video of the guy where he's like cooking the fruitcake in the microwave
and he's like "I used to look up to Hitler!"
What?
Oh you didn't see that?
No.
Oh it's so good.
He's making like a 75,000 calorie fruitcake in his microwave.
You've been sitting around googling fruity Hitler videos?
I looked up Hitler microwave until I found it.
You're being a bit suspicious to me.
You're being sus. You have imposter vibes. I do. I'm sussy as hell. You're acting like
Renuder. Nah, don't you dare. You are being a complete Renuder.
I learned a little German, let's see, it's being Kali Muscle.
Yeah, that's good.
It's Kali Muscle?
That's pretty good, huh?
Oh, I know Kali Muscle.
I looked up to, I ain't gonna lie to you, bro, this is how I got, I was too, I looked up to
Hitler, man.
I know a lot of y'all might say that's weird, but you know, me being a leader and a killer,
like, you know, we admire other leaders and killers.
You know what I mean?
I'm
Are you driving a Mercedes Benz?
Are you got guns?
40 cows, SK, all that?
You admire Hitler, man?
I'm just saying.
I'm just saying, bro.
Whoa.
That is sick, dude.
To be like a on my grind Instagram business post guy and be like, "Listen, say what you
want about Hitler."
He was a leader and he was a killer.
He said that he invented Uzi's.
Those are Israeli guns.
He invented the Uzi, he invented Mercedes-Benz.
He invented the Uzi?
Yeah, Uzi was the one that was wrong, the only one.
Yeah, he invented all the others.
Everything else though.
Everything else Hitler invented.
Yeah, he says he praises him because he invented steroids.
[Laughter]
He said it, methamphetamine dude.
If you like meth, you have to give your Hitler fam.
I mean, you go to Huntington Beach, that's not a problem.
There's a lot of meth heads who love Hitler.
I mean y'all have been talking about you know Adderall. Seriously like you guys
are kind of my proxy. Y'all are like y'all have done a lot for Hitler's image.
Crap. This episode has. No you guys have. No I haven't. Hey I I've done a lot for Hitler's image. I
printed out and put it up at the shooting range and shot my damn gun at
it a thousand times. It is funny to be to be have like a six-year-old kid and take
him to the doctor and the doctor's like well he's a little energetic so I'm
I'm gonna give him the same drugs that Hitler loved to do all the time.
(laughter)
It's basically an Omega Mac, exactly like Hitler.
That's why I can't think.
Because you're stupid as Hitler was.
Yeah. He was dumb as hell.
Yep. He was choogy.
Yeah, he was kind of normie.
Hitler was choogy as hell.
If you saw Hitler in Dime Square being a choogy normie, what would you do, honestly?
I'd probably say fuck vibes.
Yeah, I'd say the vibes are off here.
Yeah, yeah, I'd say you have zero swag stay out of my imagine. Okay, you get out you
walk out of the bathroom at Klando. Uh-huh. Look who's sitting in the corner.
Adolf Hitler. Yeah, I'd probably I'd probably post on my I probably post on my
Klando. I probably I'd probably post on my Instagram close friend stories some
people really walking around Klando like the Hitler and then I probably delete it
after five minutes. And then say sorry about that last post. Yeah. That last
story was the vibes were the vibes were f'd in that one.
That was a little chewy of me. What if you yeah but what if you get out of the
bathroom you find out he's in the corner you're like ah great Hitler's here then
you find out while you were in the bathroom he put his debit card down he
said for the next hour all drinks are on me. That's fine I'm taking his money
away from him. Yeah it's it's yeah Adolf Hitler? I'm bleeding him dry. Yeah that's
good yeah. I'll have 17 Long Island iced teas. Wait it's not like you're buying
It's not like you're buying-
Four Long Island Iced Teas, me with my arm around it.
You know what man, you're like a pretty funny and a bust of Mercedes Benz is the fastest
car I've ever-
Yeah.
I'm putting my debit card down.
Anything you want.
Rest of the night is on me.
Okay?
You know where we can get some-
Yeah.
Cause you know he would have the connect.
Oh yeah.
seriously. Hitler would have that, he'd get you a blow up from the flow up. You guys
would be walking around like the messed up versions of Cheech and Chong, just having
all the fun in the world. And you'd be singing, you'd be singing that Mexican
American songs but it'd have a different perspective. It'd have a way worse
perspective. Argentinian American songs.
be crushing it. Argentinian Germans are named Helen and Olga and they have a son-in-law
named Jose. Be awesome dude. Yeah. That Argentinian German song is gonna be great.
It's gonna be huge for you. It's gonna be fire. Oh God. Argentinian America or fuck.
Who's the new, who would you guys say is like the newest Hitler?
Joe Biden.
Hillary damn Clinton.
Joe Biden I said first.
So you guys saying it's a tie between Joe, I would like to say.
I don't think it's a tie, I think it's just Joe Biden.
Okay can I submit maybe Dr. Fakie himself?
Oh definitely.
Dr. Fakie?
Dr. Fakie's more like a Mongola.
True.
A Mongolas?
A Mongola.
I'd like to Mangle him.
He's like a Mongolas, he's such a sell.
Yup.
That's true.
- Yeah, that's a fact.
- And that's a t-shirt we're making.
- Or maybe LeBron, LeChina.
- LeChina. - He could be seen
as a Hitler figure. - True, LeChina shames.
- Who do you guys honestly think
might end up being the Antichrist?
I've been feeling like the Antichrist
has come up for many years. - Oh yeah, no, it's like,
what, say like six years, seven years?
- Seven year tribulation. - Yeah, seven year
tribulation. - So first of all,
we already have the microchip in our,
it says the left arm is where the microchip is gonna go,
the mark of the beast.
- Mark of the beast. - I got it.
you know so according to a screenshot on my phone.
So like I...
Something pointy.
Yeah, something pointy is going to put a mark of the beast in your body.
So now I think...
We can't say what.
Something pointy and sharp.
And vaccine-ish.
Yeah, rhymes with Maxine.
Yeah.
My favorite drug.
And you're addicted to vaccines.
Sorry mom.
Yeah, but I think you get, I think it's one year, within one year of the mark of the beast
the Antichrist shows up and then seven years of tribulation yeah I think are we
in the tribulations now it could be like I don't think so cuz I nobody's been
raptured yet true you gotta get rapture people get raptured all the good people
get rapture so I'll probably we'll be recording you know when the rapture
happened and nobody got taken yep damn not gonna happen though because of how
good and Christian I think one day we're gonna be we're gonna be recording an
episode right we're gonna be laughing about somebody got raptured what was your
name? The one we've got Dookie on her head? No, never mind. Who are you talking about?
I forgot her name. Who's? Is there a woman who famously flew up into the sky
angelically? Who are you talking about? Who? Who's her? The lady that... What?
Gabby Petito? She got raptured? No, maybe. That guy's innocent. Yeah, that could be true.
you got raptured. Yeah, I guess you're right. But you guys are gonna be recording with me
one day and we're gonna be talking about something and you guys are gonna say
something really kind of off color. I think the queen of England might have got raptured. Oh my gosh!
That might be true. Yeah, she was the only person who was as pure of spirit. If I got
seriously left behind, I'm gonna be fucking mad. Yeah. But I yeah you guys are
gonna be recording one day and you're just gonna my mics gonna drop you're
gonna see all my clothes cuz you go into heaven naked. Yeah, and then in your
pants of thong yep it's not gonna be I I won't care I'm gonna be in the kingdom
of heaven you guys have to suffer for seven years of war fall to the ground
there's like a loud like client like what is that like oh it's like a chastity
it would be funny when you got raptured because you don't need your dick and
ball just leave them behind yeah oh yeah when you get to heaven you're playing
down there I don't want it I don't want to have disgusting sex up there that's
right my grandma's line is silk mm-hmm also you just become like a blanket or
some shit you're not even a human anymore yeah you know once you get to heaven you
become an angel and clear that I mean biblical angels don't look like people
you know what I look like I'm like to Rubik's Cube yeah you become like two
rings intertwined with an eyeball or like you know what form or like a
yeah like a person with wings and a halo would probably be you I would become
honestly like the the cherub one because it would be funny to prank people I
would choose to look exactly like God that's not an option no you just asked
me to pick my form you're in God's image right now
that's like a new Lucifer thing that's literally what Lucifer wanted to do and that's why he fell
that's literally why he fell from the kingdom of heaven. He looks like
bizarro Jesus with that damn hair look at that look at that boy yep mm-hmm so
you think it's wrong to want to be just like God. He's trying. Oh my God, you're
trying to become the Antichrist right now aren't you? He's been trying all
along. Are you fucking kidding me? This is what you're choosing to do? Is become the
Antichrist? No. His voice has gotten a lot deeper since we met him. That is actually
true. Mm-hmm. And you walk it, look you're even, you're shoeless like Christ.
You want me to bathe your feet? Yes. This is actually getting weird.
yeah this is actually I'm starting to look at his hair uh-huh his is charming
smile that could absolutely sway millions towards the followers he have
billions he does have 12 I have 12 followers so that means I'm Jesus right
so you're saying oh my god he's named you haven't named a single so either
thing yeah so you could you could be the Jewish Messiah yeah I don't think you
are they don't even they don't have one right yeah they say one's coming right I
I don't, I don't, I literally, I met like my first Jewish person when I was 12.
Okay.
But you...
That's, it's been a long time since then.
You have plenty of time to learn something about Judaism.
I haven't met another one.
I haven't met another one yet.
That's not a good excuse.
I moved here in the hopes that I would meet one, but no.
Pretty hard to find around here.
Yeah, it's not easy.
No.
It's way, I mean, New Hampshire, I was lucky to have one.
But if you become the Antichrist, I will be pretty pissed.
So I need you to...
I need you to...
I need you to drop your...
- Hey, if you guys-- - Your global microphone.
- If you guys help me--
- Why would I help you? - Be Jesus.
- Why would I help, you won't be,
you can never become Jesus. - You guys don't wanna be
my Jesus apostles?
- Wait, what, you're gonna have two apostles?
- Well, let's just start. - Or two at a time.
- I thought you said I already had 12.
- He has 12 followers. - You have 12 followers.
- You have 12 followers.
- Oh, okay. - Yeah.
- My mistake. - Yeah.
The apostles are way different.
- Yeah, completely different. - 'Cause we have to,
we have to write a psalm.
- Oh, you do. - Really?
- You do. - No, I mean, I guess.
So do I have to though? You just said you did.
Okay, what is your... Well, I mean, getting our own book of deals,
that's going to be nice. That's a really good point. This actually
might be pretty cool, but what are your tenets that you want to base your new world order
on? I didn't see tenet.
What are your rules that you want to base the world on? But you only get seven years
of rule, by the way, until you have to be punished by God forever.
That's fine. I mean, that's... Okay, so what are we doing in the seven years?
Chill. Chilling is not very Antichrist of you.
about Barca I'm not the Antichrist hmm go to Barcade that could be pretty good
that's very sinful yeah that's but that's kind of like all the sins rolled
into one mm-hmm could we indulge in wealth to my indulgence will be big
dairy dairy no can I eat can I eat a meat that was boiled in his mother's
milk finally sure I've been waiting on that one I've been really waiting on
that one yeah what's the you can't eat what why did the fillet of human flesh
human flesh that's why the fillet of fish yeah I was invented for some Christian
reason or some presbyterian reason or something it was a McDonald's Catholics
on yeah you can't ever don't they don't eat they don't eat red meat okay yeah so
we're eating right we're eating red meat on Sunday I think it might be back on
yeah with my best bud we gonna eat a McDouble with the anti-christian partners
the Antichrist and I think we're about to have the most fun summer of 2016 I
used to go to a human school where everyone was the same but now I got
transferred to a antichrist school because and Cameron is his name
Seju is my last name Jesus backwards I hope I don't know it's a sausage
it's oh my god what sausage sausage who do we know actually the real antichrist
would be named sausage so you can't eat red meat on Sunday yeah somebody's
Sausage is a red meat.
What is non-binary roommate named Sausage?
He's going to be the Antichrist.
We're fucked dude.
Okay.
Subscribe to the Patreon.
We're in the Patreon.
This is the Patreon.
Subscribe again.
Bye.