Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
- Premium content!
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- You spappy-are with the butterflies on it.
- Do you guys, are you guys into home remedies at all?
Do you have a home remedy for me?
- Yeah, I can definitely carry you.
- I think I have a pinched nerve.
- You can punch your shit out.
- That's not done fucking.
- Just un-pinch the nerve.
- That's not gonna work, I don't have a--
- Just slap you.
Slapping is actually one of classic home remedy.
You guys are doing an opposite cure where you hurt me even more.
What do you think of this?
Chiropractic is about killing somebody before they hurt their back anymore.
Chiropracting, that's the act of chiropractic.
It does feel like it.
Just try this, try taking a big bunch of needles and sticking them wherever.
And this is supposed to help us?
Medicine nowadays is so crazy.
Have you seen, there's a video somebody sent the other day.
a guy who has a robot that puts needles into his ball sack.
And that's supposed to be medicine nowadays?
What the hell is this healthcare shit?
Exactly.
Wait, what is the point of it?
I mean, I heard just the other day.
Because he just likes pain in his nuts.
I heard just the other day there's this doctor named Ken Jiang and he tells jokes.
What the hell?
Hey, doctor, you're not supposed to be funny.
Be serious for once.
Also, imagine this.
He's been your general, your GP for years, right, Ken Jiang?
You take a day, it's your only day off the entire month, right?
You're a trucker.
You're going to the movies.
It's 2007.
- Yeah.
- You walk into the movies, you're just enjoying
just a complete romp, and then you see your doctor's penis.
- Oh my God.
- I don't wanna see that, dude.
- I don't wanna see that at all.
- Yeah, you're supposed to see mine.
- Exactly. - Exactly.
- Well, I actually heard Dr. Ken Jeong,
he's like rich and famous now,
so he doesn't have to see that many patients,
but I heard they fly him in just to do the prostate exams.
- That's true.
- He's really, really good at it.
- Really good at them.
- Well, I mean, he says it's fulfilling.
- You want the best, you know.
I mean, I would trust that.
I think he's the best at prostates.
- If they flew in a doctor just to do my prostate exam,
I would be like-- - I would trust him.
- They're airlifting you with a helicopter
out of your town to New York City,
good to see your side-eye.
- Imagine finding out that they had to bring
a special doctor.
- Doctor, his prostate, it's too big!
- You walk in, it's that big.
It's that Indian guy with elephantiasis hands.
Have you seen that dude?
He has nothing else that is huge on him except he has like three feet across his hands.
Baseball gloves.
They're huge dude.
And all the videos, I don't know what they're saying.
You got to get that guy in the Mets.
You'd be the best catcher ever.
I don't know, if you would have elephantiasis and it would make you really good at a sport,
Would you cure it?
Are you allowed to play?
I'm sure that the antibiotics you have to take or whatever the fuck would be considered PEDs.
Maybe.
But this guy honestly would be a world class volleyball player.
You guys think...
Well you have to...
Here's a question.
You think that Percocet is a PED?
No.
In sports?
Percocet?
Yeah.
I don't think so.
killers? Probably not. You wouldn't consider them a PED? No. But what if you
are in the BME Pain Olympics? Then yes, probably. Yeah, that's a good point.
You know what I was thinking about? Yeah? Is it legal in tennis to just have a really big
racket? Yeah. I'm serious, like can you just have like a really... because there's different sizes.
Well that's what I was about to say, I was thinking about this
regulation, this elephantitis guy who has a giant catcher's mitt for a hand.
You know, maybe I feel like in the future we could see somebody with like a
Resident Evil style golf club arm and maybe they have greater control over
where they're sending the ball. They're getting holes in one back to back to back.
I think biotechnology and technotronics are gonna be change sports.
And techno-optics are gonna, sports is gonna be different in a couple years.
Definitely, yeah, like biological, mechanical, like just kind of like...
Mechanologically?
Yeah, mechanologically and probably like voodoo tronics as well and kind of magic.
Magico, techno, biologic.
Dude, imagine if they added magic to baseball.
Yeah.
Imagine too.
Syncopatronics are going to be like really weird.
I heard that they're putting crafting into soccer too.
Whoa.
Yeah, the players can craft better cleats on the field if they gather enough materials.
Now there's glowing materials too.
You have to have leather and metal, raw metal.
Well, yeah.
And also you have to have an ore and then of course there's a smelting station at work.
Yeah.
Bad news for some of the teams.
Apparently one of the crafting ingredients
is a British guy's pinky bone.
So you can only craft it when you're playing
against one of the UK teams.
Yeah, and you're not gonna wanna be a British guy.
No, biting off pinkies left and right.
Oh my God.
So far.
Yeah, they're gonna be saying, "You man," like, "Oh man."
Yeah, that's right.
Brazilian referees.
They'll say, "You man," as if they're saying, "Oh man."
There's a potion you use a Brazilian referee's head
to make it, yeah.
It's very intricate.
That's what they...
There was a referee who was beheaded?
Yes sir.
It's funny to me, like as an...
I've read that Wikipedia page more than...
That's funny to you?
No, as an American, just how serious like soccer is taken.
Well okay, get this though.
Because that's just a sport you play as a little kid here.
That story was like this whole thing where it's like, oh my god, they got so mad at the
referee that they cut his head off.
But what actually happened is that the referee stabbed one of the players and killed him.
And then the entire crowd was like, what the fuck?
take that guy's head off of him. Yeah, that's cool. And they actually
pulled all like his limbs off of him. Oh my god, that's so cool.
So what happened was the referee and the player got in a fight and then the ref
pulled out a knife and stabbed him. Yeah. And then the player left, the game
continued, everyone's booing the ref and then news hits the stadium that the guy died in the
hospital and just immediately that guy's head was just off. That's like, yeah,
imagine like yeah being in that crowd and being like okay like I guess we're doing
this. Yeah, you're looking side to side. Yeah. Well, is this? Yeah. Oh, we're
taking his head off right now. We're pulling his clothes off, right? That's
what we're doing. If he dies, we're taking your head. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. He's
like, he's never gonna die, right? We don't have to take the guy's head off.
It'll be fine. Yeah. The opposing team people are like, well, the guy died. I
would love to take this ref's head off. I would love to have that experience
under my belt, be a part of a crowd of 100 people tearing Amanda Shreds,
because they're never sending me to jail. At the referee at Chuck E. Cheese,
the guy who stops you from doing back flips off all the slides.
Yeah.
Let's say they decide to send us to jail, right?
Like what?
Did you kill someone that's a life sentence?
Sure, we'll all do one year.
That's right.
That's a hundred of us.
True.
Yeah, there's no way that any of those people got prosecuted, right?
Yeah.
Well, yeah.
It was like 2003.
No one's filming it.
There's no cops at a Brazilian soccer game.
Yeah.
And if they are, they're not being--
They're on the team.
They're trying to enjoy a chili dog, right?
Yeah.
They're not doing a fucking watch the--
Or what are they--
I meant--
Is it Brazil?
Skinny pigs?
Skinny pigs, somewhere in South America.
Brazil eats tons of fucked up shit.
I think it's not fucked up.
They eat some fucked up shit.
I've looked at a guinea pig one time and been like, it's basically a pig.
Exactly.
Brazilians eat like sponges.
They just inhale large pieces of air and then just keep all the dust and that fills them up.
Brazilian food is mad good though.
What's Brazilian food?
uh... what's that one p_p_ khana
p_i_ c_h_
you think you have proper rana and i'll let you know you are the promise for
you
uh... mixed up with a in a very brasil in the amazon
you will be you know if you run a
uh... yeah
well based on what i would
i think it was a little bit of brazil and movies they usually
uh... birdseed
yet yet i've seen this movie rio
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
And sometimes they bounce off a woman's huge ass.
Yeah.
That's not really food though.
And they go flying.
I saw this Brazilian movie where they eat a full English.
What?
I saw this Brazilian movie where they eat a full English breakfast.
What are you talking about?
And there's a menu and his mom gets her face pulled back.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't really either.
I'm talking about the movie Brazil.
Oh, okay.
That movie scared the shit out of me when I was a kid.
That's my dad's favorite movie.
He showed it to me.
It's the Nostalgia Critic's favorite movie.
Is that true?
That's how I found out about it in middle school.
That's a good movie.
You know, I just downloaded Letterboxd again.
Yeah.
I was like, I'm trying to watch more movies.
Dude, I hate how people talk about movies, bro.
It's the worst.
It's fucking disgusting.
It's so fucking stupid, dude.
Oh my God.
Everybody.
They're talking about like American Pie and shit and about how it's like, this is the beginning
the like new American like people it's like dude just yeah American Pie Review
just Stifler's mom five stars dude it's some huge ones in there yeah that's it
entire review liquid 82 be in this yeah damn yeah like I looked up I looked up
the CKY movies on Letterboxd and did like lowest star just to like yeah see
what people were saying yeah it's just like great yeah dude that that is some of
the funniest shit I've ever seen. I found one German guy who got so mad at CKY2K. I wish
I remember what he said, but he was just like, "This is so immature!" basically. It's CKY.
I'm done with movies again. I was into movies for a week. On Pluto TV, I found they have
a Johnny Carson channel. He just plays Johnny Carson all the time, and it's so fucking good,
dude.
Yeah.
Pluto TV has great stuff.
He is so fucking racist and hates women so much.
Carson. It is hilarious dude. Yeah. I watched one today where they had a lady who was
Amelia Earhart's friend on there and she was like, she's like, "Amelia Earhart is a
real, was a real woman you know, she wasn't, she wasn't like these, these
women's lib people today." This is in like the 80s. Yeah. And Johnny Carson says, "You
know what I say about the women's lib movement? If it barks like a dog and
looks like a dog by golly it's probably a dog. I was like dude fuck yes dude.
He's just calling women dogs on like the biggest show in the world.
Yeah. Just like women are all dogs. Women are crap and I love to put my
cigarettes out on them. And Amelia Earhart was a bitch. It was cool Susan
Sarandon was on one. Oh yeah. He just was he was like. He better not have said
anything disgusting to her. Beautiful woman, beautiful woman coming on that
stage tonight, beautiful, beautiful, gorgeous, absolutely dropped it, just
couldn't stop talking about how hot she was. Yeah. It's so cool. That's awesome.
Then I don't have to kill him. I'd be sick if Jimmy Fallon just started doing that.
Oh shit. Yeah, well they're also, the best part about those old Carsons is no one
laughs. Yeah. You know and he goes all out. He came out, he did this thing called
Carmack which was it is he pretends to be an Indian yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah classic the antlers on his head so good and it's a whole notebook under his head
people are people are people don't give a fuck dude yeah yeah he's getting
nothing he's out there putting it he does this every night he still does and
they're just not doing giving him anything well Ed McMahon gives him the
(guttural sounds)
- He was, Ed McMahon was reanimated.
- Really?
- Yeah, like that's how they got him to be the co-host.
- Wow.
- Yeah, he was one of the first Frankensteins.
- Oh, that's huge.
- Does he have the bolts?
- Yeah, well he had the bolts, but he had them--
- They're in a different place.
- Well he's a Carson's monster.
Is he Ed McMahon's monster, or is he Ed McMahon's?
- No, he's Ed McMahon.
That was the name of the gravestone.
he's Carson's monster though. Yeah he's Carson's monster but his name is Ed
McMahon. I'm sorry I looked oh you have steam open I forgot that your username
is rubbing me one. Threw me off mid-sentence. I just gave out Cam's steam
name to everyone. Add him on steam. A few freaks have already tried to add me on
steam and this is an open letter stop I'm not gonna say yes you guys are
freaks you're weird don't do that to me. I'll add you and then I'll forget. You
You already have. I think I've added a few people and then if they ever request me to
play with them I delete them.
What you think I want? You think I'm going to open a line where you can see what I'm
doing and ask me to play games with you? Are you psycho? No chance. Not happening. No way.
I love the fans.
You can come to my house.
Ed McMahon. Yeah, he's a Frankenstein. Let's get back to this.
Dude, it's awesome, dude. I mean, Johnny, I never have watched much Carson. He's the
fuck, he's a beast.
I liked-
Oh, he did this one joke where he's like, "The governor of-" Fuck, what is it? You
hold your nose, Carson, right? There we go. No, he's like, "The governor of California
came into Los Angeles today and met with community leaders from the black community, and he said
that they taught him more than he taught them like how to say police.
Jesus. This used to be every night on TV. Yeah yeah.
And now they got Spongebob on TV. That's right. Apparently they got this
comedian nowadays named Ken Jeong and he's a doctor. That's right. What the hell
is this? If you're a comedian you're supposed to be funny not a doctor. He probably goes up there and talks about being a doctor.
How about you do a transplant on your fucking little ass cock, you idiot.
That's right.
If you're such a doctor, do a colonoscopy on me and show me what's inside me.
Yeah.
Come on.
X-ray me.
Feel me.
Rub me.
Come on, doctor, rub me.
Do you think he demanded his trailer?
Paging doctor rubbing me.
Oh, this again.
Oh, God.
Do you think Ken Jeong has in his trailer like an X-ray machine and a CAT scan and stuff?
Yeah.
He sees patients while he's on the set?
He fixed Ed Helms tooth on the set of Hangover 2.
Really?
Yeah, because he's a dentist too.
I forgot that's not what the name of doctors for teeth are.
They're still doctors.
Dentists are not doctors.
Yeah, they are.
What are you talking about?
Okay, is a nurse a doctor?
Fuck no, dentists go to medical school.
No, doesn't count.
Dentists go to clown school.
They don't go to clown school.
They go to a medical school that specializes in dentistry.
They go to dentist school.
Yeah, wrong.
Dentist school.
No, dentist school is for a dental assistant.
They're fucking nothing.
- Thank you. - They're not doctors.
- Dentists are lowest of the low.
- Dentists are not, like, straight up not doctors.
- Wait, wait, look, do this.
Okay, that makes sense.
- Yeah. - Yeah, you literally have,
like, your teeth look like a crossword.
(laughing)
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Well, dentists can eat my butt.
- They can suck my dick, dude, they're nothing.
- Well, that's what they do. - What happens
when I go to sleep at the dentist's office?
- I've fallen asleep in the dentist's chair before.
- Yeah. - Me too, actually.
They make you wait a long ass time.
I fell asleep in the orthodontist chair.
I never had braces.
I like when they x-ray your face and make you wear that bulletproof vest.
Yeah, it's awesome.
And they do.
You were not given the free heart x-ray.
They put in like the, you know, they ever put in the plastic.
Oh, dude, that thing sucks so bad.
I hate that thing.
I love it.
You take some funny ass photos of that though.
It's cool as hell.
Take some funny ass photos.
That's right.
It's crazy that I never.
That was the crush on Snapchat.
I need one of those.
When I was fucking 14.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
You're still crushing on Snapchat, right?
I wish I had one of those dentist chair buttons where you can fill a cup of water, like just
on my office chair, where you can, you know, it has the little faucet, you can just fill
up a little cup of water.
We've talked about getting a sucker before for...
Absolutely.
When we get an office, we have to get a sucker.
A sucker and a water shooter.
Yeah, a water shooter outer.
I do have a water pick.
That's different.
Yeah.
I guess it's the same.
A spouter.
That's what we need.
We need a spouter.
And a pusher buttoner.
A sucker and a blower, though.
Yeah.
We need a blower.
lucid or downers and a papers putter on her. Yeah, I want to get a watch. We might
need a looker at the timer. True. That's a good point. Yeah, probably. We'll probably need like a
food heater upper. Yeah, definitely. Yeah. A snacker holder. Yeah. What's that thing?
Some looker at her beautiful women. A colder snacker holder. Mm-hmm. Oh, and a water boiler.
But you mean a waterer boiler? Yeah. Yeah. Waterer boiler. And a fooder boiler.
Steak in a bag boiler. Yes. Yep. Definitely.
Steaker in a bagger boiler. Yep.
Patrick boiler. Potatoer masher.
Okay, so we need two chairs and then a torture machine for Patrick.
Yeah. Yeah.
A big cauldron?
No, a big spike that you sit on and just put a rock on your head and it just kind of slowly
kills you. I'm inventing a new torture device called the boiling chair.
yeah and it's a chair inside a pot of water i feel like i would be and you
have to wear a scuba outfit well i wouldn't know that the water was boiling
i wouldn't leap out exactly i would be so good at making torture
devices for the medieval ages yeah i would have fucking crushed it dude
how about this how about a uh just a just a loading screen yeah never yeah
you have to listen to justin bieber's music for
probably an hour on end a wi-fi network that has no pat like they
they won't tell you the password.
Yeah, you can't get the password.
Oh, Wi-Fi network from a plane.
Yep.
Yeah.
But it's only a...
Fly-Fi?
Yeah.
Oh, how about this?
It's one of the...
It's Harry Potter, best book ever, right?
All the pages are blank.
But it only turns one page every two hours.
And there's no last page, so you never know the ending.
You never know what happens to Voldemort.
Yeah.
How about this?
Voldemort shocks you with a magic dark spell.
Well, that's the other thing.
If you had witches and wizardry, like, why are you involving them in everything that you're
doing yeah like almost no there's no like okay like the Trojan horse right
Trojan horse if I yeah there's witches and wizards just or God I mean you know
why not oh well here's what I want to know why not the Trojan dragon that
would have been way cooler way cool I would a horse I'm sending a horse back
yeah dragon come on in you go next to my mantle yeah yeah is it gladiator the
movie with the no no it's Troy right the Trojan horse in the movie Troy Brad
pits in a plays achilles around i was
in troy i assume it would be a use of
roy i did you know i saw that movie when
i was like seven when i thought when i
saw the people get out of the trojan
horse and just killing all the civilians
i got really sad how they get in there
are they getting that horse they wouldn't
they weren't in there before i know door
in this horse i got insanely upset yeah
walking in walking into the movie like
like just at the scene where they're
like wheeling the horse into the city
you're like oh cool they see people
so cool.
And that's a cool. Oh, it's a movie about this horse. Yeah,
horse is awesome. I think I'm interested to see where you go.
I think I came inside from playing some my parents watching it with my sister
and then saw the guys come out of the horse and kill like a bunch of
civilians.
Patrick saw Troy and he came inside. He said yeah, he did do I got so
that a horse dude once they saw his guys coming out of a horse after he
came inside.
Once they killed Achilles, I got so hyped.
Did you guys see that video I sent you yesterday?
Oh yeah.
Why is she like, it's funny that it's like half
like she's supposed to be hot
and she's baiting that for like views
on Instagram.
And then also she's fucking jerking off a giant horse.
Yeah, she's playing like the music is so funny.
She's putting like that thermos that has like a
blanket on it.
It looks like a horse flashlight.
I mean it looks like a fucking picture of crystal light and she's just like making the horse fuck it.
Yeah.
loving it's like jerking around I'd probably do the same thing I would did
she was hot but it's funny that they're trying to like yeah it's just a very
interesting cross-section it's clearly that she wants people to think that it's
hot that she's jacking a horse well it's I yeah I'm there's some kind of scary
undercurrent of animal sex on Instagram as I follow a bunch of animal pages like
that are called like beautiful Africa and stuff and it's every once in a while
that is post a picture of animals fucking and oh yeah like it was like a lion yeah
lions fucking each other and then the caption will be like the beautiful king
and queen of the jungle like your love below and the comments are like wow he
really fucking her like that this is a lot of it is like this this is me this
same page post them like like ever like it's mostly normal animal pictures and
also it post the same picture of giraffes fucking like every week with the
captioned Tower of Love. That's kind of beautiful. It's kind of sick. They just
posted it again like a day ago. Yeah, here it is. The Tower of Love 11 hours ago.
Damn, that sounds like a Kramer Sutra move. Yeah, it's when you're
both giraffes. Yeah, that's what the move is. Let's see some of those comments.
Here's another one. One of the dominant Barbara male. Oh my god. There's lions
going at it. The big lion is bigger than the small one. Yeah, read the comments on that one.
I'll read the comments. It's like all like dudes being like, this is me and my girl.
And like this is, oh man. Perfect timing with a bunch of...
Here's a comment from Nina, I won't read the whole name, but from Nina.
Moi avec mes enfants, which is French for me with my children.
(Laughter)
That's advanced.
Here's a comment from Eileen. She has toothache and if he doesn't get off her
back she will give him testicular ache. It's so fucked up. That lady, there's no way
that she like speaks English, right? That's probably why she didn't
understand. What do you think? It's not English. You can see that
the lions are fucking. It's a picture. But it kind of looks like he's like hugging
her or something. I think, no, you're, what are you talking about? Okay, you choose to
believe a French woman is fucking her children? Yes, it's France. Alright, yeah. What's her
name? That doesn't make any sense. Nina. Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina?
Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina?
Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina? Nina?
name
the
or
got it got france's ass
i'm on the prime minister
on the comments for the tower of love now yeah here's a comment uh...
vamos we have any french listeners i just want to say fuck you
here's a comment
vamos vamos a reproducer a
and i go go reproduce
great shot a lot of work
i wonder how many cm
she jumped for joy lol oh centimeters okay
you know big is dick is yeah batting at the highest level
you know when you're fucking a lion that's when you know you've made it
this is a giraffe here's one from cheese man
she's saying get in my belly
do you have do uh... do giraffes do they pack in that long and thinny
well no you never see it look at the picture
no you see a rare
look close
all that i got that along in skinny thing on the uh... was like photos i like that
he had been in the same time i get your ass look like they have like a fucking
piece of p_v_c_ pipe to their car comes out of yeah
bigger big red uh... there was your own cut penis does
mind yeah
i guess cut boys was up
that's right
cut gang
there's another one
also scrolling looking for lines that it's like a big like it's like a big p_v_c_
pipe and then like this like a Twizzler comes out. Twizzlers pulling comes out.
Yeah it looks like a like a hypodermic needle. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But the the skin
around it very big. Big yeah. And the penis itself little it's it's like
honestly it's like a little red sharpie. Really? Mm-hmm. Little ass red penis. Yeah.
Wow. Well it's red because I colored it. With a sharpie. Yeah. Do you ever do that
thing where you're sitting in the bathtub or something you get a little
bit of a boner and you're like oh this is kind of funny and then you like flex
and your head of your penis blows up like a mushroom. Blows up? You guys ever
notice this? Next time you have a boner, just like send all your like like flex a
kegel send all your blood into your penis. Okay. The tip of your penis. Oh like. No it
doesn't do that it literally grows like this that's cool it's so cool no I
looked it up dude I watched 15,000 videos about it yeah mm-hmm it's pretty cool so
now I do it sometimes in the bath dude I wish I had a tub honestly I just have
that shower that I don't take I took a bath when we were in Atlantic City
because I had it there was like the first time I had a bathtub yeah like months I
think I got home at like or we I got back to my like hotel room at like 5 in the
morning and just like so I'm like fuck it I'm gonna sleep in the jail and then I
almost did I almost fell asleep in that tub drown yeah no that would have been
really so funny single night in Atlantic City is to wrap the city that's not even
it like like not even Vegas yeah that would be the most Atlantic City way to
go I think the low-key did have like a hangover type night let me put my crocs
into sport mode oh yeah dude hold on actually yeah you're so stupid
sorry I don't even know which now your car wasn't jock mode I'm in numb in
thinker leisure modes mode this is what I'm usually put like this or lazy look
yeah lazy Sunday mode yeah you know wake up in the late afternoon call Parnell
Just see what he's doing that kind of shit. Mm-hmm. Yo, Sam Berg. What's cracking? That's right
This is my this is my I've been wearing these everywhere man. Yeah, they're
Crocs are good. People are getting jealous dude, dude. I keep wearing fucking like weird looks from Dominican guys
They think that it's embarrassing. I think really yeah, I just stop wearing these fucking
I guess I wearing high-top shoes because every time I go to your apartment I gotta take my shoes off to go in
That's what's gonna take me like five minutes to get in a red bull
- I'm in sport mode if I really need to zoom.
- That's why I miss the summer.
I miss wearing my Tevas, dude.
My body's too cold all the time.
Anyone else have this?
- I get overheated really easily.
- I get too cold and then I'll go out
in a bunch of layers, then I'll go skate in the winter.
Right now, I went skating earlier and now I'm sweaty.
So now I just have a shit ton of layers on
and I'm sweating through 'em.
It's fucked up. It's fucked up what global warming is doing to my life.
I think it's you-will warming when you are skating. I think it's skatal warming.
I don't think that's true.
Yeah, I think it is.
I think it's true.
Because I'm heating up.
You guys need to get some cool shoes.
I do need some Crocs.
Some Crocs.
My Tevas are the same material as Crocs.
But these are great because like I said, they're embarrassing. People look at you different.
Dominican guys make the, you know when Dominican dudes walk around and they like, kinda like,
kinda trying to be cool and they make like a, like they smell something bad face, you
know?
Yeah.
Like that, you know?
That's what they do when they look at my crocs, it's really, it makes me feel like.
Maybe you smell bad.
No, no, it's like, you know when someone smells like a diaper, like a body, like a piece of
shit.
You know when someone waves their hand in front of their face?
Yeah.
And they go, "Oh, that's the smelly, that's the smelly guy who comes into the bodega!"
Well, smelly's like brolic, like it's like, that's cool.
they call you smelly.
- That's mad smelly.
- Yo he mad smelly dog.
Like they're like saying I'm cool.
- Yo he got the diaper.
- Yo pussy got the diaper on him bro.
No, no dude.
- No bro, walk around Coney Island looking bruh.
- Coney Island you brought the diaper on him?
No dog, no.
- We got the New Years baby in here.
Look at him and his crocs.
He look goofy as hell.
- Goofy's also cool.
- He smell like shit.
Shit means good.
me you wear a diaper without telling me you wear a diaper okay oh I didn't say
smell me you were a diaper damn yeah but I walk around Coney Island with those
guys all the time yeah yeah big diaper means like swag to them yeah he's like
with the diaper yeah he's got a mad like like saggy chunky diaper I'm trying to
assimilate you know I'm saying dog oh and I'm trying to assimilate to my
neighborhood so I'm trying to I'm trying to match the kind of style and energy
You're trying to ass immolate with your hot hot poop that you're filling your
thighs with. I'm not trying to ass immolate. Yes you is. But the guys really respect it.
I walk around. Yeah. When they say I don't respect you that means I respect you.
Yeah well that's like you know when someone talks about a
song they're like that song goes stupid. Yeah. That's like when they say
like get the fuck out of here. That means get out. That means stay here. Yeah that
- That means follow me around.
- Yeah, follow me around and smell me up, you know?
- Follow me around, make me smell.
- I just love this New York slang
that I'm learning every day.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah, like I hate you!
I hate you so much! - That means it's cool.
That means it's cool.
And then you know what?
- It means I love you.
- And I walk in and I take all the stuffing
out of the diaper I put on my head like,
hair, go get a fid.
(laughing)
Why your hair green, dog?
- Green?
- Yeah, green.
about dying my hair green like the Joker. What do you guys think about that? A friend of
mine, big ass Dominican dude just dyed his hair pink. Really? Yeah. And he's, I mean
he looks so stupid bro. Yeah? Yeah I just have been. I think I'd look good with green
hair. I think colored hair looks, if you're over 18 you can't have that. No. Well that's
what this guy's like. I'm including any color except brown. My friend is, he's like 30 dude.
Yeah. He's got pink hair bro. How are you gonna pass that off? Yeah. I think what I should do is
dye his whole body pink and then he can be the pink guy. I'm gonna grow a pink man. That would be cool.
Yeah. I'm gonna grow hair out, dye it green and then bleach my beard and then dye that purple.
Oh wait, I didn't even notice you. You lost the chops. Oh yeah, I fixed them up. You made one
day. They got chopped. Yeah. You don't even have the... You told me that this side was so
so
about that. Yeah true. Look forward to that. But he basically, the point is he caved
immediately to peer pressure and he lost the chops and he has no...
Well I have sideburns again. See that's nothing. That isn't. Yeah. I still think
they look goofy. You look stupid. You should grow some mutton chops. Yeah. That
would look cool. That would look cool. You should do that on Wednesday. Okay. I'll get
He's fooling them. Oh my god. He's a genius dude. I gotta get I gotta do something
Yeah, my facial hair. I it's like you put my hand man those sideburns are more like fried burns come on
You gotta be kidding me don't ever fucking say my shit's fried. Don't you fucking dare?
It's actually a bro look yeah, it's actually bad bro. Yeah, it's actually quite bro
I'm fine. I'm running it looks particularly bro like
Wow.
Tell me you're from Bristol without actually telling me
that you're from Bristol.
Let me get a chopped cheese. You know the vibes, bacon, egg and cheese.
I'll go.
You turned into a Muppet there.
Let me get a chopped cheese.
Fuck you man. That's not Bullock.
Let me get a bacon, egg and cheese.
Tell me you're from Harlem without telling me you're from Harlem.
I'll go first.
uh...
we've got a little bit of a
the
can you from hogsmeade without telling you that i have a good
i'll have a ginger beer
uh...
let me get to a chocolate frogs
figure
you know that's good
man those chocolate frogs today they were so good back in the day
i don't let him jump those chocolate frogs are gross as far as you are
- You all remember when we took the Hogwarts Express?
- Yes, sir.
- To Hogwarts.
- Dude, Universal Orlando, they have a real train there.
- I'm there right now.
- Oh yeah, aren't you going there?
- When this comes out, that boy's--
- I'm there, if you're hearing this--
- He's in movie magic, man.
- Do you have both parks?
- I don't know, Anna knows all the details.
- You have so much parks.
- I don't know shit about--
- Dude, you gotta tell me about
how the progress on Nintendo World.
- There's a Nintendo World there?
- They've been building one since like 2018.
I'm
- Yo, you gotta get on, you gotta,
you gotta go on Race Through New York.
You gotta see if that's still open.
- What's that?
- Jimmy Fallon's Race Through New York.
- Oh, that's cool.
I wanna go on the Jurassic World one.
I found out there's a King Kong ride too.
- Oh yeah, the King Kong ride sucks though.
It's like a 4D. - But it has King Kong, so.
- It's a 4D car ride. - It's a King Kong ride.
- Oh, there's the Fast and the Furious ride,
and you can take pictures with all the classic cars.
- They have Jurassic World too.
- And they got a big, I don't know if they still have it,
but they have a big-- - I'm literally only
gonna go on the ones that have monsters or dinosaurs.
I have a big wax Vin Diesel there. I got a picture with it.
That counts as a monster.
There's a monster on...
There's a monster, yeah.
...Jim Downer right there in New York.
Yeah, there's a predator.
It's a real monster, dude.
Yeah.
What else is there?
I heard the Predator got a late night show.
Dude, I wish they had a Predator ride at Universal Studios.
No.
Oh, wait.
They do. Yeah, freaking Homer Simpson.
Yeah.
You see that episode where he reached for that girl's butt?
Oh, my God.
I knew it was a Predator.
The next one was a Predator.
Yeah, you see that episode where he reached for that girl's butt. Yeah. Oh my god
I never believe the news was totally right on that. I agree. Yeah. Yeah, I only watch 16 minutes
I need to take his is Maggie. It's Maggie. It's big on that ride. She gets hit with the big rag. He gets big
She gets huge you might like that. Yeah, you would like that. No. Yeah, and then you're attracted
You get a picture with Bart Simpson there - you would like
And all the kids me I'm a Marge man, but you you're more into the kids from
Specifically the kids from the Simpsons is so fun. That's right. Oh my god. Name is P
I was trying to give you tips on where to go at Universal you're trying to give your tip to the T
Simpson e
RGRIFIN, Peter Griffin. He's not on that ride. He will be. They should put a Peter
Griffin ride in. They should. They should put a Peter Griffin versus Homer Simpson
and their families ride. Yeah, yeah. I was doing the-- Their families versus their
families. Doing the what? Doing the-- I was doing the worm at my apartment. I was
thinking, too. I thought he was going to say doing the worm. Doing the mad men
with the Peter Griffin laugh.
(humming)
Just doing that to myself for a while.
- Since I showed Neil that fucking
Peter Griffin Life is Good parody,
he watches that like once a day.
- Really? - Yeah.
- He probably just likes the song.
- He wakes up like the Lego movie
and then gets ready to that song.
- Yeah, dude he loves that song.
- That's cool.
- It's so good though, I will say.
- Yeah, never heard it.
drinking on a weekend like usual. That one? That one's fire actually. Yeah. Yeah. We got
chips and nuts. Herbert the pervert tried to grab his butt. God damn dude. It's so,
I got so drunk the other night I was just doing Peter Griffin voice while I was walking
to like another place with, I think it was with Xavier. Dude it's so funny dude. Yeah
dude. It crushes. Also you do that dude, pull that out for the parents. Oh yeah dude. I
I think the only family guy I've ever seen is that Herbert the Pervert compilation we
watched at your house.
Oh yeah, Joe put that on, dude.
So long.
Yeah.
It's very funny.
That guy, he's a goofball.
Herbert is such a pervert.
He's a total weirdo.
That old motherfucker.
Herbert is such a pervert and Chris is such a child that he wants to touch him.
And he's always going after Chris.
He's always going after Chris.
Chris is also like kind of too old for a sexual predator, right?
That's the only way they'd let it put it on TV, I bet.
Yeah.
okay you can have a pedophile character but he has to only go after forty-year-old
man yes that's what that's what the t_v_ networks are doing i hate this is
honestly disgusting yeah
like yeah
don what's the guy i had had a little
dot
don't set a little earlier on from s_n_l_ in the eighties you hated everyone
part of the on now fuck you fuck you guy
who hated everyone dot
(both singing)
That guy.
I know a guy who everyone hates, Don Trump.
Yes sir.
Boom.
Don DeLuise.
(both laughing)
Yep.
Yeah, 'cause he wanted to eat everyone.
Donald fucking something, man.
Donald Glover.
Tell you who I don't like that much, Don Imus.
Yeah.
Now this guy--
This guy called those women nappy.
That's right. It's like they're wide awake.
You know,
I learned about who Don Imus was through an episode of mind of men,
CEO, where he's defending him for saying nappy. Yeah, it's pretty cool. Yeah,
dude. I, my parents should have monitored what I did as a kid.
I should not have watched. I should not have been a mind of men.
When I was nine, I think that that's ruined me in a lot of ways. Yeah.
i was a lot of us out by their door and a home at when i was nine no no uh...
when you were not are you know my god you're not supposed to be a kid here
that's was the teach kids here to share here
i saw i saw the first episode of south park for the first time it's summer camp
and and and seventh grade
yeah and i don't know where you are
probably like to admit that it's easier summer camp now someone had a no-sum
attack on summer camp you're going to keep it on a lot of some people
there is a little and uh...
eight nano bot
late in the end of our
we jump on that one
as a record with the pilot it was a solid it was that i was at the college my dad
worked at
uh... and that we had computer time
barnum and bailey's
uh... to talk a little like i would be in the client college into sixteen
because steve-o went there yeah but it's all shut down
the last steve-o was the last graduating class of martin
if you want to be a clown you have to do some it has to be some stupid art shit yeah you have to study
into the the guy that uh sasha barron coach anyway your schools go to uh like circus whatever like
learn how to be a circus performer no i wish camp i knew a kid who did that and it's just like he
just like juggled it's like okay i wish i wish i learned that that's nothing yeah like shut up
Yeah, you can learn that a lot. I would juggle so much shit.
You're already juggling a lot, buddy. Yeah. I'm juggling my health issues. Yeah.
Manic depression. Yeah. BPD. I don't know if I got BPD. Slut disease. Yeah. Slut fucker disease.
The police calling you the grabber. Yeah, that's tough too.
Batman's looking for you. The grabber's calling you. The police.
The grabber. I heard the grabber's on the loose.
Wait, what was that? I heard the stroker
is running around. They call me the gipper because I'd be selling crack in black neighborhoods.
(laughter)
Do you now? Really?
That would be so fucking funny to
Patrick dressed up in fucking, wearing fucking Ruka or whatever in the corner of some neighborhood
in Bed-Stuy.
Pat, now that I think about it, Pat would make like, if you were like an undercover cop
or if you were like a narc or something, it would be way too obvious.
I know.
Nobody would believe that you, honestly they would be like, well there's no way he's a
cop because that would be too obvious.
Yeah, exactly.
You honestly might want to enlist in the police-atary.
Yeah.
yeah yeah I think I could I'd be the best oh man I would nab so many people for
drugs see ya anyone who says no one's ever gonna
drugs there's no way that guy could no one's ever gonna offer me drugs ever
again after this episode well you are a cop though yeah well I've been a cop but
like yeah we've all been yeah are you a cop well I used to be but actually like
just stop yeah actually that's so funny that's the whole point that's the whole
like like plot point of the departed yeah it's like he's walking or he went to
jail for like like 90 days or whatever and he's walking around trying to buy
drugs like yeah I was pretty much a cop for two seconds and then now I'm not
though yeah for no reason though I was too cool to yeah I left I left because I
wanted to do this yeah I see if your copy just look at your watch and like no
Yeah, I don't think so. No, it's past 5. Right now. No, no, no. Yeah, I'm clocked out.
You know what I really want? I do want to be a cop though just so I can get my badge and my gun taken away.
I want to be a cop just to be a cop. Well, I mean, that's for the thrill of it all.
Here's how I would fool my chief. I want to be a cop to serve and protect.
Here's what I would do if I was a cop. Here's how I fool my chief.
He says, "Pitts, turn in your gun and your badge."
badge I say oh yeah sure no problem sir walk outside guess it's in my pocket two
guns two badges yeah I took something I had two guns and two badges the whole
time oh and he had none but you didn't turn in either of them I turned in
neither of them well I turned in my gun and my my he's he really just respects
the object work so I just okay you go take my badge in my gun yeah no problem
Yeah, yeah, I turn in my badge in my gun to try some free even an even golder badge and an even bigger
That's right. Yeah, I would try to do if some if they try to take my badge my gun
I try to really confusingly kind of bend to the conversation and make it seem like it's a who's on first thing
Yeah, you know very directly asking me. Give me your badge your gun. I'm like who's badging gun
Well, yeah, I think gun. Yeah, I locked them up earlier badges and guns is yeah, I know that yeah
Yeah, I'll turn in my gun turn it into a gun that's attacking you yeah bang
And turn my badge into a ninja star
Because I'll turn in my gun turn into a gun yeah
Yeah, and then you just turn into a gun just like two floating googly eyes yeah, and then it's just a smile
We've are definitely already talked about I think about that thing all it's an image in my you know Megatron
used to turn into a gun before they made him into a plane.
Yeah, wasn't it like a Walther P33?
I don't remember what kind of gun it was.
But it's sick because everything else turned into cars
and he turns into a little gun.
It's cool dude.
Isn't he like the biggest gun of all time?
Probably, but I mean like toys wise.
Yeah. You know, it's just a gun.
True.
Didn't they used to make the
Transformers out of metal?
I don't know.
They are made out of metal.
to
Absolutely. Yeah. No, here's a question. I would be another man.
Where's the door to the transformer on the car?
Where's the door to him?
If he transforms while you're inside, do you get crushed into bits?
You see like a, like a pickup truck, like a transformer.
It's like pickup truck form and it has like truck nuts and you're like, Oh,
those are probably like his balls. That's pretty funny.
and he transforms back into a guy and there's like in the middle of his face
just like super unlucky because the like the tailpipe is like his nose so it's
cool dude yeah you're your balls at Ron no I'm not yeah no I'm not no I'm not
yeah I'm just clear no your balls are trying you got balls on your face
literally it's it's it's it's stamped on your body says your name is balls at
you know that's Decepticonian language destroyer yeah like a yeah transformer
was like a bumper sticker on his forehead that says like pussy wagon so
tight yeah my honor student went to yeah see University pussy oh my god oh my god
Hogwarts was kind of like pussy University for me what kind of we should
come up with some bumper stickers sometimes. I had a really good bumper sticker idea that
I don't want to say on the podcast because I think we should actually sell it. Okay.
I'll tell you guys after. Can you remind me? Yeah. Should I just pause it now and tell
them? Yeah. It's such a good idea. Oh my god. Yeah. Oh my god. I'm losing my mind. I'm so
glad we didn't say that on the air. Yeah. Here, I'll pause it again and we'll say it
again and will react to it again okay
haha
in time
man
really well you probably wish you heard this
yeah all you wish you heard this you will never hear this you'll never hear
the you never know
all that one day i hear this
yeah and one more reference here this year that's what's my part of or at that
is for one day he get the lady get this year that's a pretty funny one i mean
he's a poor at
he's a jokester. Probably my favorite comedian ever. You know when he says "Bajin hang like sleeve of wizard"
yeah that shit fucks me. That shit gets me every time. It really does.
Borat is so funny.
It's literally the funniest movie ever made. It's so funny.
There's never been a funnier movie. It's crazy it should be like not funny.
And it's crazy that Borat 2 was even funnier.
It shouldn't be funny anymore.
It should have been. It kills me every time.
It's so good.
It hits every time.
Because I forget certain shit.
Like the fucking, it's so stupid, but the scene where he sees the tortoise and he's like,
"Oh, what kind of dog is this?"
Yeah.
It still gets me every time.
Genuine chocolate face.
When he says "crumb," when he's talking about his wiener, oh my God.
Oh, when he's in the...
That's not what that is called, Borat, you foreigner.
You freak.
It's funny that he actually is a foreigner, Sacha Baron Cohen.
Yeah.
You know?
He's from the UK.
Which also kind of makes me like the movie less.
say that about me I can only say that about me mm-hmm you can't say from and
what is he's not about me you can't say not to me I can say not about myself and
I can do all those jokes but that's because I'm actually from here you
fucking idiot yeah my suit is not black but not what my suit is not black not
see you did a good job when he says when he says smile a bit when he says smile
- Open pussycat, smile a bit.
- Yeah.
- Yup, that's funny.
What else is funny from Borat?
(laughing)
You know, I don't like--
- I see just that thong that he wears.
- When he sings that damn song in front of the rodeo,
oh my god.
- See, and then the second one,
they had to get some like fucking blonde haired lady
to be the most beautiful girl in the world in it.
I don't care about that.
- Is that Borat's daughter?
- Borat's 16 year old daughter.
- Some girl who's like a normal age, I think.
she's the most beautiful girl I've ever seen,
all of a sudden I'm distracted trying to watch Borat say not,
but instead I'm looking at her eyebrow.
- That's Borat out there.
- They're making noise.
- They should make a movie.
- They're making Borat 3 out there right now.
- They should make Borat in New York 3.
- Yeah.
- The thing is about Borat is that
they should have never made a second one
'cause you can't walk around as Borat.
People would--
- Right, yeah.
They must have had to do so many like,
out to like, just like,
so many takes must have gotten ruined.
because if imagine you like like them walk in Borat walked up to you on the
street right now and tried to interview you about fucking you know Trump or
whatever you just say like hi bore. Oh you are bore at okay. They didn't have
that part of the in the movie. Yeah, he's in the skies. Well they also had him be
like oh he's famous because from the first but also like I but it's stupid.
It's a bad movie. I could tell Borat from the I mean it did what the no any
layer of makeup could not hide Borat for me. Yeah, you know I'm a real I'm a real
Borat Bloodhound. I inspect for Borat every day. I mean it's not just Borat too.
Caleb can sniff out any person from Kazakhstan just instantly. That's my job on the force.
That's right. As an undercover cop. I'm sniffing out Borat. Yeah. Borat's a street name for
Sacha Baron Cohen. I'm trying to find him so he doesn't confuse any of my fellow officers,
trick them into saying something racist. He does do that. He does do that. Yeah.
Yeah. Once I find him, I'm beating him with a stick. I would hate to be tricked into
saying I fucking eat farts in a Borat 3. Yeah. Yeah. So like if a Borat 3
comes out. A Borat 3, yeah he comes up to you and he's like, so you think like Donald Trump is awesome right?
And you're like, yeah I love to eat farts. So there's a, so what I'm saying is if
there's a Borat 3. Borat 3 is such a fool. We don't know if it's coming out. We don't know if it's coming out.
but if there is and there's maybe a video of me saying that I fucking love to eat farts,
then it's probably that he'd used movie magic and Final Cut Pro to make that look as a deceptive tool.
He did some kind of YouTube poop sentence mixing.
Basically, what I said was that I have a glove that I catch farts with and he edited it to say,
"I love farts." And it's just wrong, dude. I think that what he does is wrong.
True.
Absolutely.
and also John McCain was a hero. Let the boy get some pussy.
Or no. Rudy Giuliani. Rudy Giuliani. Let the boy get some pussy.
He's trying to get some pussy. He should have gotten some pussy too. Yeah.
They're going to dig up John McCain and give him the pussy he deserves. Rudy Giuliani. Why is
Borat cock blocking Rudy Giuliani? He should not. Trying to get some snitch.
He's trying to get that golden snitch. He's trying to get that snitch.
He's saying Wingardium Leviosa. He's trying to get that snape.
Mm-hmm that's ever a snake get some Elmer's glue dude. Let the boys stick it up
Come on trying to grind that horse down turn it into glue. That's right. That's right. He's trying to make some too far
Yeah, just let's try to put he's trying to put some glue on his hand. I try to peel it off
Hey, I mean Rudy Rudy Giuliani. He's trying to get that bacon egg and cheese. Mm-hmm. Let Rudy do the duty. Mm-hmm
That boy cook. Yeah, Rudy do the duty man. All right, you acting fruity
in your movie in your movie Giuliani's really harney yeah Giuliani's penis is
Ruali scrawny mm-hmm old yeah but it got Rudy got nudie in that movie showed his
girl is named Judy right he has two movies two movies and he's trying to
watch them he wants his penis to shooty mm-hmm and on you D PP we on booty on
boobies mmm just let the man basically just like the guy have sex with the kids
let that boy go he's trying to shoot goose it's like he puts his hand yeah I
know yeah I think it's just a movie magic yeah yeah there's probably movie
CGI also like this guy's fucking I think they rigged him up with squibs in that
scene make that happen either they make the white squid that if the camera gone
and like 10 seconds more yeah I've exploded yeah also Rudy Giuliani used to
just he had a rule in New York City where if you were a black guy in a hoodie
they could just put you in jail it's like you're mad that he did he's touching
his penis yeah get him on the other stuff get him on the why are you worried about
got this penis thing dude this is one of the worst guys ever just the penis thing
it's almost it's almost in the long run pretty good that he did that compared
to everything else I don't know even if he was trying to have sex that is like
pretty good if you judge it on a curve if you judge it on a curb that's pretty
good that he did that and I believe he his penis is curved yeah into your mouth
into his own mouth all around your head you know you see you see that man you
look at Rudy Giuliani you don't think he's that flexible. You call him
gooby splooging on me. Yeah. That's what you call him because that's what he's doing to you.
Well that's what I was part of my job on the force. Yeah. I gotta suck him off.
I gotta suck him down. He shoots tendrils on you. You call him rudely
shooting longly because it takes so long. You're working overtime at the force.
You call him gotta do my laundry because he's covering everything you own.
Everything in my room. And gooey ookie spider webs. Yeah. Oh my god.
He shoots big ropes from the front and back in my room.
You call him shirtless feeling spongy because that's how much he saturates your shirt.
True.
It's like a cloud in the room.
Yeah, I call him sock is very crunchy.
Why is he shooting into your sock? You take your sock off and jerk off?
It goes all the way into himself.
Well, that's how it gets on the floor. I step on it.
Yeah.
It's like a tornado or a whirlpool.
he's self-sucking I put him...
What? No, you just said you suck him.
Well I suck him but then he's like I can do it, alright?
I'd rather you watch this.
I'd rather you watch this and then he...
I put him up onto the ceiling fan in my room
and he's spinning around like a droideka
and he's self-sucking on a ceiling fan.
Like Rudy Lachezman, you devil.
You ever seen like a microscopic view of the brain
where you can see all the neurons?
Like you know when it goes inside Jimmy Neutron's brain?
That's what Pat's room looks like after...
looks like after he's done.
He's spinning around on that fan.
Yeah.
Spinning around on that fan.
He's got ropes coming from the front and the back.
Looks like a street map of Boston.
Just meandering roads that lead to nowhere.
When I explode the room and come everywhere
it's like a grid system.
It's perfect.
It's like a cube.
When Rudy does it, it's like trying to get
It's like a map of Wal-Mart.
It's like a map of Harvard Square to Porter Square.
Am I right?
Yeah, that's right.
What do you do?
I'm going to hit my head with the microphone.
That's cool.
I don't think anybody likes that.
We do need to find new ways to brain damage ourselves now that we don't have this gas
leak clutch anymore.
I'm set.
Yeah, that's what I mean.
You're hitting your head.
Yeah, I'm hitting my head.
That's good.
I was thinking I might start holding my breath for like 20 minutes before we record.
Ever tell you guys...
You're just going to be breaking world records, man, you asshole.
Okay, what should I do instead?
That's something that isn't impressive and fucking coolest thing you could do.
I mean it's not...
Oh, I'm going to win an NBA championship.
Okay, okay, hold on.
You should...
You should breathe out as much as you can.
Not in, out.
What do you mean?
Like...
I should just do that?
You do that because then, what is it, CO2 leaving the body?
You breathe...
Well, I just breathed out too much.
You breathe out so much CO2 that your room fills up with gas.
You and me should just stand next to each other and breathe each other's CO2.
Maybe we should all just, before we hit record every time, we should just spend five minutes
hyperventilating together.
It's a good idea.
Honestly, we should try that sometime.
Wouldn't that give us more oxygen?
What's that thing where you lean over?
I guess maybe Whippets.
That's what people do.
Oxygen bars and shit.
People get like oxygen machines.
Hyperventilating is not good for you though.
I think it is. No it's not. You'll get it. It calms you down. You want to faint? That's
a bad way to start an episode. I don't know. I'm trying to. I'm brainstorming here. You
guys are tearing down every fucking thing I say. Just smell. Okay, come over to my house
because I actually have a new fume. No you don't. Yeah I do. They're painting my roof
with this paint that smells so fucked up. Oh fumes. That's actually a good idea. And
all my windows have been like this my entire. I have a computer duster in my place. Yeah.
A computer duster would be good. Yeah. We could do a computer duster episode. I have
to tell you, before I forget, you were talking about holding your breath. When my little
brother was like four he found out that he found out about suffocation mm-hmm
and if he could if he lives my mom said like he couldn't play video games or
something he gets so mad to be like I'm gonna hold my breath and then would like
hold his breath until he got super rich just cuz he was like like you want to
guess what he's so bad. He just sit there like...
*makes weird noise*
That's so funny.
Sounds like a brat.
Yeah, I think you have a monster family.
If my kid did that shit I'd say, "Fuckin' do it, pussy."
You won't, she won't.
Smart.
I dare you.
How crazy your family is, you guys would probably drive the Adams family out of the neighborhood.
Come on.
That's true, my friend Adam did move in the third grade.
Adam's family didn't move next door to me because he liked me more. Yeah,
Adam's family, I could easily scare them.
I'm so funny, finding out like your elementary school friend is moving and he's just moving to be like next door to his other friend.
Like he doesn't want to be next to you anymore.
I could scare the Adam's family.
Yeah, it's easy. All you have to say is I'm normal. They don't understand it.
I've been watching a bunch of old Adam's family on Pluto TV.
I'd open their mailbox and put my big juicy ass in there, in their mailbox.
and stuff it in like putting play-doh back in the box.
You think the Adams family is afraid of sex?
Not sex, they're afraid of my ass in their mailbox, the way I've been farting.
They want to see that.
I haven't been eating meat so many times.
They are crazy sexual.
Even on the original show, they want to fuck so bad.
What?
That Gomez.
There's like multiple jokes in the episode where Gomez will say a French word and then
go like, "Wait a second, that's French."
And then look at Morticia and they both go like, "Ahh, ahh, blah, blah, blah."
and they fuck each other on screen.
- Who's Gomez?
- Gomez is the guy on Breaking Bad?
- The little mustache. - Gomez Adams.
- Gomey?
- Yeah.
- Wow.
- Gomez, Morticia.
- They got Fat Fuck, The Sun.
- Pugsley, Wednesday.
- Who's damn, they named their damn kid Wednesday.
- What the hell's that?
White people be wildin'.
They got a cousin named It.
- One of their friends, just a hand.
- Yeah, every white people name's like Vester.
- Lurch.
Come on. White people, we have the stupidest names.
[Laughter]
Fester.
What kind of name is Fester?
What the hell is that? Yeah. He laughs like this.
[Groans]
Remember when he laughed like that in the movie?
No.
The comedian doesn't know about the Adams family. He just thinks it's just white people
names.
Yeah, I know.
Yeah.
Chris Rock.
What's the hand's name?
The thing.
Thing?
Thing.
Yeah.
been saying that I don't want to see that shit who else what others is there for
Adams family plus that bitch Eddie you little vampire freak I've never seen him
there's a mom in it right Morticia hey tish tish how about you show me your
tits take your clothes on it's only your bish it's your bush and your tush yeah
and your snush and let me and you know what let me put a new hole in you call
it the this blush all right and show me that one too hey Gomez you got it why
you trying to tell we talking about fucking in front of your kids go as
nasty if you're talking about it be about it go out your Gomez yeah let me
see the whole mess come on now that's right that's right uh-huh yeah I want to
I want to see you going Adam.
Damn.
Ooh, damn son, where'd you find this?
Oh my God.
I want to see your slow mess go, man.
I want to see that thing fester.
That's right.
And I want you to have sex on Wednesday.
Ew.
Oh, come on, man.
What's wrong with you?
Just the day of the week, not on the kid.
The day of the week.
I've never seen the Addams Family.
All right.
*weird noises*