You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
I'm sorry he's so stinky and sweaty.
That's right.
Oh my god, I'm so sleazy and wheezy today.
Oh.
Oh guys, I don't want to record. I'm too slimy.
I am, dude. I'm sticking to the chair. I'm like...
You're like a fishman.
You're a mesh chair. How are you sticking to this thing?
The leather on the sides.
Wow, your beard flutters.
You hear that?
That's crazy.
Patrick's back hair is like Velcro hooks.
And it's attaching him to the mesh chair.
I went skating before I recorded.
And I sweat through my shirt and my shorts.
You were wearing all black.
Yeah, look, I didn't think anything through.
I thought it was raining today.
I thought it rained earlier.
Did the forecast call for rain?
It rained earlier, but then it was just cloudy the rest of the day, but it was hot cloudy.
I've been asleep.
Yeah, hot cloudy is the worst.
Hot cloudy sucks because it tricks you.
Yeah.
You look up.
Yeah, I got tricked into thinking, "Oh, today's a good day to go skate."
That's why I don't like sunglasses.
And then you end up all oozy and floozy all over the place.
Yeah.
Oh, god.
If I wear sunglasses, I get confused because I think it should feel brown in my body, but it just
it only looks brown.
Right.
It's the same thing as a cloudy hot day.
Yeah.
Where you look up.
my tooth hurts so bad. What else is wrong with you? A lot. Yeah? Oh my teeth are so sweaty today.
I think I chipped one of my teeth. I've been grinding my teeth a lot and I chipped one of them
in my sleep I think and then another one. I think my wisdom teeth are coming in. I think
grinding your teeth is a good sign. I think it means you care. You know what I mean? It means
you have a strong jaw. Yeah it means you have a strong jaw, you're thinking of your small business,
You're like worried about stuff, you know?
It's a good thing.
Also, I mean, grinding your teeth, it's better.
That means you're dreaming about chewing something, which is better than dreaming about licking
something.
Yeah.
You could be dreaming about candy canes.
If you wake up and you're licking your bed, you...
Yeah.
You...
Candy canes are not a thing you chew.
Yeah, 'cause you can explain grinding your teeth, even if you are getting like, in your
dream you're getting like a blowjob from a shark.
Like when you wake up, you can explain that to your wife.
You can be like, "Oh, I'm grinding my teeth 'cause I'm thinking of like, oh, the door's
unlocked.
I'm so stressed."
up if she wakes up and you were like licking one of the poles of like your
bed up and down and going on saying like you're your friend's dad's name oh my
god I just so stressed just that stress tree oh my god oh my god Barry baby I
think I think I need to start meditating or something I gotta get a TM keep
having these horrible stress I keep having these night terrors where I'm
going like oh yeah you're just like you have your phone in your mouth with the
speaker like yes in your mouth and it's playing like fucking like what's that
"Right about now, hit it!" That song, fucking, "It Takes Two"
That's playing in your mouth, you're going like "Oh!"
You're going in sync with the "Yeah! Ow!"
Yeah, in your sleep you've navigated to YouTube, found a lyric video for "It Takes Two"
and then started playing it and sliding like... DJ Rob Bass and DJ Easy Rock
rock and putting your wife's hand through your butt cheeks like a credit card.
Yeah, he eats you example. What are you doing? Why'd you eat me? I've been having horrible night terrors.
I'm an owner, I own the greatest hip-hop club in the world.
People are dancing and singing but then one night someone came in they brought
an ecstasy and people were ODing. And that's why your hand was in my butt, I was trying
to get the ecstasy out of my butt.
Yeah, but when I was rubbing my crotch against the doorknob, that was just from stress, that
didn't have anything to do with the dream.
That was pure stress.
I was sleepwalking.
It was just a release for me.
I was stressed in my dream where I was my own Shay Patrick.
I'm not a sleepwalker, but I thrash around in my sleep a lot.
You're a sleep thrasher?
I'm a sleep thrasher and a sleep talker.
- He's doing like kick flip.
- That's way cooler sounding.
- It sucks.
- At least.
- Sleep thrasher.
- I wake up and all my sheets and covers are on the floor
and my girlfriend is angry.
- Yeah, it's bad.
- What?
I think I told you guys this before, but yeah, I do.
I'll like sit up in the middle of the night
and like try and like be asleep,
but try and wake up my girlfriend
and tell her something while I'm asleep.
And one time she said that I sat up in the middle of the night
and like, like shook her and was just said,
"Lord of the Rings."
And then went back to sleep.
(laughing)
- Dude.
If I was dating I'd be, I would have my shit packed up by the time you got up.
I would be, there would be boxes all over the house.
I'm not living with Lord of the Rings, man.
Dude, I can't do it.
I must be so horrible to sleep next to, 'cause I also have sleep apnea, so you know, I'm going like
*snoring*
Yeah, I'm the worst to sleep next to, 'cause every, like, my ex-girlfriend would tell me that, like, when I would, like,
snore, it would sound like I was choking in my sleep.
Yeah.
So it's just like I'm sitting there just snoring just like
*snoring*
Dude, sleep apnea is terrible.
Yeah, it is terrible. I used to, in high school I would fall asleep on the couch and like
once I like, my mom woke me up because she thought I was dying because I was going
*snoring*
My ex would wake me up in the middle of the night just like, like, like can you not sleep on your side please?
Like, or no, no, no, if I sleep on my back, she's like, can you just, please just roll over like you, I know how to fix this, just do it.
I would get so mad because it was like somebody's trying to wake me up.
So if someone tries to wake me up, I guess this has happened before.
Alex has been like, I've been, I've fallen asleep on the couch in the living room.
And I think I was watching fucking the Suicide Squad and I like was drunk and I just really
liked it. Sitting there just like, "This movie rules!"
He told me that from his room he heard Pat go like, "Yeah! This is awesome!"
(laughter)
- In the middle of watching.
- I was pretty drunk.
- Oh yeah!
Do it again!
(laughter)
Come on!
- He's exaggerating.
- I'm pretty sure if I--
- If I remember correctly, 'cause I--
- Hold on, let me finish the snoring thing.
- You reviewed it on Letterboxd,
and you were like, "Yeah, this was okay."
- Yeah, I didn't take it or leave it.
- Yeah, it's so funny.
- He's throwing popcorn all over the place.
(laughter)
- Yeah!
- Two stars.
That's gonna be two stars for me.
I guess I guess somebody Sam you're so excited you wake up just like a
toddler running in the aisles you're just running back and forth to all of your
roommates rooms. I knock on the door. Like New Year's Eve like the poppers
like any time that like Idris Elba's like we gonna take down his stall man I'm just like
yeah wake up your your MacBook yet another style over substance but so
after I mean after I had the greatest movie experience of my life I I I fell
asleep on the couch and was like snoring so loud Alex had to work the next day
that he just like came out of his room is like can you just please go to bed
like go to your bed like don't sleep here because the couch is like right
next to his room and I was like if you wake me it takes it takes like three or
four times to get me up from a deep sleep and I guess like he would wake me up and
I look at him and go like hey what's up man and like just immediately go back to
bed and it took him like three times and he says that like the third time he was
like Patrick just go to your room I guess I got up and ran like the guy from
get out to my bedroom. You need to be, they need to do a sleep study on you. Maybe worse
than they've ever need to do a sleep study on anybody. Oh dude, I, yeah, I don't, what's,
get in here. Don't. Now. Go. I need a new phone number. He needs a phone number. Get
back to this. Oh my god, what a throwback. Yeah. Neil will be out of the room while we're
recording damn this is the this is the we're back to it boys I know buddy in
New York again now just in a different city again yeah crazy what will be our
next city what about let's try like we should move to Paris yeah we should go
to like Alaska Tehran mm-hmm what's that Iran t-h-r-a-n Tehran yeah where is that
It's in the Middle East. Yeah, what part of the Middle East in Syria?
Okay, all right. Okay, Pat
Is that true? I don't think so. I don't think that's right. I think I hold on Tehran. I'm pretty sure it's not in Syria
Yeah, where is Tehran?
See rhymes
You know what and I was gonna guess that too, but I was I thought that's too obvious
obvious. I know because both of you guys are like, both of you guys are like
fucking just glaring at me and I'm like, it can't be my first guess. They were
naming cities in the Middle East and they were like, well let's call this Tehran in
Iran. Now that's too obvious. No, we're not gonna do that. Well it actually means
the Iran. Yeah, yeah. Duh, Tehran. It's like back in like forum posts in like 2008 where it's
like Ted like yeah yeah yeah on the pun boobs dot-com slash forums you guys ever
go on forums oh my god the boobs forums in the day there was rape my shit
right my poop calm oh they said rape my shit fucking what a fucking rape my
That's what I thought you said.
And I was like, what kind of fucking kid from Toy Story shit was Caleb doing as a kid?
RapeMyShit.com?
I thought it was like eFuck or something.
No!
You thought it was eFuck but it was all people fucking shit?
I don't know what I thought it was.
And like, not just fu- what is- you have- you should be in jail.
I didn't hear you. I didn't hear you.
RateMyPoop.com
Yeah, rate-
rate my poop rates my I did go on there though it's a website you've been to
before I feel you're hearing okay all right but yeah rate my poop yeah calm I
hated that really yeah I was a power raider poop poops disgusting like my
My older brother and his friends would send each other pictures of their turds and I was
like "Yeah, I'll do it too!" and then one of them sent me a photo of their poop and I was
just like "I don't like this."
Speaking of Yik Yak being back.
Oh yeah.
Yik Yak, they brought that back after it was gone for a long time.
When that was a big thing, I was in college in North Carolina and I only used it, every
single shit that I took on campus I would rate in detail and post it on Yik Yak and I
think anybody ever saw it and then I told somebody that like years later that guy
Sonny he was like you were the shit Raider guy yeah he's like me my friends
tried to we like to find out who you were that's funny that's yeah yeah I
used it to uh like I just spam everything yeah yeah it's spam that the
lyrics trapped and then it did it didn't work on my have like a username I was
trapped fan I think was it was it always that you couldn't use it near a school
or did they add that later cuz when I tried to I live too close to a school to
use it from home and I'd like it was you like I'm not gonna like walk somewhere
to open this app like walking yeah I use yike yeah exactly so I never I never had
it that was the thing I found this spot I was at an away game because I used to
my job in high school is I would film the football games for the coach.
Not for the school, but for the coach so he could be like, "Yeah, I want to get like
play-by-play analysis of my team."
Get a really, really low angle of the
quarterback from behind.
They would put me in like a fucking booth like up top by
where like the two like the two fucking like either like VFW or like town
comp troller announcers are. So I'm like standing next to these guys and I'm just
like like do you guys want me to move you feel like God no I felt like shit I
hated that job really yeah I mean it took away like every Friday night I had to
work so videography is really boring yeah Caleb also did that yeah we in college
when we were working like like we had to like film meetings of people and it was
always like the most boring it's always like it's only just filming
PowerPoints and stuff oh yeah I like so and then you but you get to steal food
from them which is awesome.
Yeah, get free food and like you get to like miss class or whatever.
Like when I was in high school I was like, I would film like assemblies and shit too.
So I would just like, I'd be like, oh cool, like I get to miss like most of my classes
today but like I have to go to the elementary school to film like the sing-along thing that
they're doing.
Well ours was, a bunch of the stuff I had to film was people applying for jobs at the school
at Emerson.
You'd film them applying?
Yeah, so that because they give like presentations or something like and I
remember they were all the most horrible annoying people of all. I remember one
guy. It's like I need to teach somebody. They like show research they've done and
shit and one guy came up and he's like have you guys ever heard of the book
Llama Llama Red Pajama? Basically the Migos wrapped this book on a radio show
and it's crazy. He showed a video of that in his powerpoint. Damn. Dude, I remember I would just sit
there like filming like these classes or this these interviews or some shit I
just be like please for the love of God like natural disaster or mass shooting
or ceiling collapse right now and I get it on film it'd be so awesome.
I'm keeping the tape. Yeah, I would just sit there and imagine any of those three happening being like dude
that we'd get like a million hits on Worldstar if I put that up right now.
We in high school had to film like the chorus concert. Nice. Like I had to film
like the middle school chorus and there's just like one kid just going fucking
nuts yeah yeah singing and dancing every song so I just like like pan around the
crowd and just like get the kid in the shot nice it's just like I don't know
what they did with the I think they aired it on the public access channel but like
I feel like dude maybe that kid's family was like oh well my son's a star like
they'd be honestly pretty dad probably beat him up for being on TV yeah getting
some call. Making our family look like fools! Larry, you turned on CLTV recently. Your son's
on there. Look, your son's on Leo 21 acting a damn fool! I think that's CG item to be queer
on TV or something like that. I remember when, I don't want to give too many details, but
when a comedy show was being filmed that we were at and me and other person were standing
next to the camera and on the tape you could hear us talking about how bad the guy said
was.
I'm not going to give any more details of that until after we're done recording.
I've never heard that before.
Okay wait one second I'm going to pause it.
That was a great story Gavin.
Oh my god.
They're never going to hear that too.
They're never going to hear that.
God I can't imagine being so stupid that I couldn't hear that story.
Oh man.
You'll never get to hear it too.
Unless you subscribe to the Patreon.
Yeah.
Oh wait, we're on the Patreon.
If you subscribe to the $3,000 tier, I'll tell you the first letter of the person's
name.
Man.
It was Louis C.K.
Yeah.
We were sitting there roasting Louis C.K.
Did you see that thing like a couple weeks ago where it was like this performer, they
were like, "Oh, I accidentally bumped into Louis C.K. on the street and I yelled at him."
just like oh cool like you're yelled at an old man yeah you yelled at Louis CK
like I I don't know it's just like it seems very like perform like that seems
very performative to like go on your whole like tweet thread about it and
being like oh well like I'm a hero for yelling at somebody if you're like about
it don't you know yeah yeah like if you're that fucking mad about him yeah
just like rob him dude he lives in New York City he's around all the time you
could like kill him so easily also you know when you yell at somebody it makes
them stressed out and you know what the number one way to relieve stress is so
you could have caused something very bad there I was telling Caleb that is he
gets home he sits down and like he's opening a newspaper to open some fun
book I was telling you don't think I mean you don't think that like he that guy
Louis CK you don't think he likes getting yelled at by women true like
you're just giving him what he wants yeah I was telling Kayla but his like
comeback show thing he should have like brought a random person up on station
just had everybody take a picture with him.
(laughing)
So there's just a hundred pictures of them.
- He's my best friend.
- You guys shaking hands with Louis C.K.
- I've known this guy for at least four years.
(laughing)
This guy taught me everything I know.
- Through thick and thin.
(laughing)
- Yeah, that would have been funny.
- Yeah, this guy helped me back on my feet.
He booked this show for me.
(laughing)
- If I saw him on the street, I would,
you know what I would do?
- What?
- I'd probably buy him a hot meal, you know?
put a coat around him and I'd say, I'd say, you know what, kindness, kindness, kindness
kill, kindness kills. As he's eating his soup, there's cyanide in the soup. Right, yeah. Well
the soup's really hot, he burns his tongue. Yeah. Burns his tongue and immediately dies.
He realized Louis C.K. He ate soup that was too hot. Yeah. Yeah. Is it, and now that Bill
does Bill Cosby live in New York? Bill Cosby lives in a cube. He lives in a cube that they
spin around. If you're Bill Cosby right now, okay? Hello! No. That was a really good impression
too. I'm glad. It's funny that that came out like a burp. It was like involuntary. It was
like you had to do hello. It was a really accurate hello. Okay so say you're Bill Cosby
not you not you are so your bill Cosby no I give up I give up on my hypothetical
let's just let's just do
oh Bill Cosby
that's all we want to do right?
yeah Bill Cosby
oh it's me Bill Cosby
yep that's right
yeah
I'm gonna touch ya
you're Bill Cosby
they let you out of jail
I don't remember why
hello it's me Bill Cosby
you hit me on the head in jail too many times
and now I sound like this
(laughing)
- Let me out!
They trapped me in a cube!
Oh no!
They put me in the Cosby cube!
- That's America's dad that you're
having fun of right now, you realize that.
- Get me out of here!
- Okay, what's your idea of that?
Keep going, keep going.
- So we're Bill Cosby.
- So you two are, so you're the left brain
and you're the right brain.
- We're Bill One and Bill Two.
okay so you walk around in red outfits with our arms interlocked yeah doing what now?
Probably getting his fucking weird eye checked out. Yeah but like what part of America do you go to or
anywhere where you just like nobody like shoots you on the street? Yeah. Like how do you how do
do you survive like it's an RPG game it's it's fallout you come you come out of
the vault of prison where are you headed as Bill Cosby where no make it so no I
got bad news okay then what's it I think Boston might be I might go to the
fortress of solitude oh that might be a really good yeah yeah I mean if I was
like you know Bill Cosby I guess he doesn't need to ever be on the street
again is the thing yeah rich yeah if I was Bill Cosby in a dome I would get so
good at working out just get ripped yeah that's I can only do that if I'm Bill
Cosby crap I'll never be able to work out yeah yeah I'm too good of a man yeah
man I mean the hypothetical of like where Bill Cosby would go imagine your
1000 tiny Bill Cosby's. Okay. Okay. Like a nano-box situation. One inch tall each. Yeah.
So now what? That's it. Well it's gonna take you a while to imagine that. That's a lot of
little Bill Cosby's so I'll wait. That's true. I think he is, he is like the one person like
that where like I... No one wants to see Bill Cosby perform. And I also just can't. It's
not like, it's not like Louis where it's like, it's still like people would pay to go see
yeah yeah like everyone's just like oh no that's like I think it's maybe like I
remember it wasn't the amount of time until he went to jail he was still he was
doing a tour where he was like until he was like he got arrested he was like
packing out stadiums being like just saying like these women are fucking
liars like that was his old tour it's so crazy the fucking video of him leaving
the courthouse going hey yeah so nuts consummate performer dude he doesn't know
I mean this guy doesn't know he doesn't know where he is right now. He's so old
He has like a fucking agra from Dark Crystal. I
Like yeah, he's old as shit. He probably doesn't like know how to wipe his ass anymore. He's so old
Yeah, it could be yeah, or he could be a mastermind
It's true. He could I mean he was always it cause me so say yeah
That's a good point. Yeah. Yeah that that hey could have been completely calculated and played in reverse note. He says yeah, yeah, yeah
It's terrifying and as in yeah, yeah, yeah, I did that. Yep. Yeah. Mm-hmm isn't it is
chilling admittance
Yeah, it middle and missile a bill Cosby's admission admission
It may one to the bill Cosby show, but Temple University is Alma mater
I'm not going and his name backwards
Yizbok lib
Wait, I've read about the is buck lip they talk about him in his water chair
Yeah, that's really scary. It was really scary. Yeah, that's the one that when you reverse you
Bill Cosby
If you reverse that that's that black guy TV. Oh my god
He did something really wrong
It's scary.
So, I mean, crazy that it was Bill Cosby.
Yeah.
Let's stop talking about this.
Yeah, we can stop talking about this.
Jesus Christ.
I watched it.
I finally watched it.
That's a good, like, metric for when to end talking about a topic is when you get to "It's
so crazy."
Yeah.
It's like, "Oh, yeah, we're done talking about it."
I finally watched on, like, I had, like, ten people recommend me that show, White Lotus.
Oh, yeah.
In, like, a couple days.
I finally watched it.
I didn't finish it because it's not good but yeah every show like that here's
what's awesome about okay it brought back one of my favorite like kinds of
characters in any TV show which is the video game son oh yeah it has one of the
best video game sons of all like a switch with like he's in Hawaii his dad
is like hey look there's like a shark fucking like an octopus outside like
let's go watch that wouldn't that be awesome do you want to go jet skiing do
you want to like have your first drink do you wanna have sex with a prostitute
And he's like, "But dad, I have to save my game!"
It's like so good, dude.
I guess Mike White wrote that all by himself.
That makes perfect sense.
Yeah, it's clearly written by like a very stupid guy.
Yeah.
You don't think Mike White is a good writer?
He, well, he didn't-
No, I saw the show.
It's not good.
Think about what he did to Jack Black.
That's true.
He held him down, dude.
He stopped him from starting a band of children.
That's Beckley's Gung by Ned Schneebly, not Mike White.
yeah yeah it is also funny the entire time watching that show to be like like I
can't Ned like he ruined his career by being Ned Schneebly at any point like I'm
gonna take it seriously because it well I mean I've never I haven't seen him in
and it's so funny to to write a movie and then name yourself Ned Schneebly in
the movie yeah wait he wrote I'm pretty sure he did yeah really yeah I'm Ned
Schneebly you know what no I respect that more cuz it's like well okay
I'm the like, wimpy loser.
You can still make yourself the wimpy loser, but don't name yourself Ned Schneebly, because
that's what everyone's going to call you forever.
The reason that he's named Ned Schneebly is so that Jack Black can fucking like, it's
a fucking funny, he hands it off to Jack Black later.
So Jack Black becomes Schneebly to the kids.
So genius, genius move.
Fuck you guys.
That's a good movie and a good move.
It's a great movie.
I love that movie.
I think that he consigned himself to a lifetime of torment.
And also it doesn't really necessarily mean that he's a good writer because he wrote that movie
because most of the lines are delivered by either a child or Jack Black.
Have you seen the screenplay? It says, "And then Jack Black sings a rock and roll song."
Yeah.
[imitates rock and roll song]
Jack Black hums the 12-bar blues.
Yeah.
[imitates rock and roll song]
That movie rocks so much.
It is an awesome movie.
I love that movie.
more they should have a rock band that's why I got an SG they should have made
like 50 movies about Jack Black having a job yeah like yeah I should have been a
be kind rewound did you guys did I talk to you guys about have you guys seen the
movie year one about him being a cave yeah have you seen the black face that
Bill Hader doesn't that movie no it's really it is crazy nuts it is full body
pitch black with a bone through the nose gonna ask I was gonna ask if there's a
fucking crazy and I've never seen anybody talk about it. I think nose bone is like that's
like that elevates it it almost loops back around where it's like well that's
kinda. And he's named medicine man. That's so fucked. That's from like 2009 I think.
Oh yeah well I mean 2009. This is very funny. Yeah 2009 the Jim Crow era.
They got away with that.
I mean what is that? Year one of Obama.
And they have him, he does his normal like, his normal Bill Hader voice for the character.
But then it's one of those movies where they have like bloopers at the end.
And they show him doing a bunch of different takes with different voices.
And let me tell you, some of those voices, they should not have included in the blooper reel.
I do want to watch it now.
It was just like 15 minutes of him like, "Do I have to wear all the makeup?"
Yeah, this kind of looks bad.
Is this going to age well? I'm not sure.
He's only in it for like two minutes, so you know they were just like, "Oh, we want you to do a cameo."
And he was like, "Okay, fine." And then he got there and they're like, "Okay, put this on."
And he's like, "Oh, God."
"Okay, yes, fine, yes."
Yeah, yeah.
He was probably, what was that, 2009?
He was like lower SNL cast.
Let's see, camel, fallon, and me. This will be great for my career. This is gonna kill.
Yeah, it is just crazy because I've never, I like had never, I assume something that
crazy I would have seen at least one picture or mention of before.
Yeah, of some, you know, person.
Well, that's the thing, he's just built, so beloved that everyone's like,
"Oh, well, let's like, let's not talk about that."
Exactly. It's also not, it's also a bad enough movie that I don't think people are watching it
it to rediscover it.
Yeah, it's like, remember Bill Hader did Blackface in year one?
Yeah, I was like, what are you talking about?
Yeah, it does sound like a movie that you just make up for...
Yeah.
Oh yeah, Jack Black and Michael Cera are cavemen.
They're cavemen and then it's about the Bible.
Yeah.
What?
They're cavemen who live through the Bible.
It's like, there's some funny parts.
I don't think it's horrible.
It's definitely not good.
I like anything with the Bible in it.
You know?
I'm fine with...
David Cross a very funny as Cain the ten. Yeah that about the Bible it is the commandment ten commandments
It's like Michael Showalter, and I have like all the state people no I haven't seen it either
Noah oh
You mean have no mighty no yeah, yeah
You know I was fucked about that movie. They did they did Bruce almighty, which was you know classic Jim Carrey
funny
Funny-ass shit, right?
Classic Jim Crow movie.
Yeah.
Bruce Almighty.
But then they did Evan Almighty, and Evan Almighty is like, seriously, like, about God.
Yeah.
It's like, God rules, all this is real, like, this shit.
Like, in the first one, it's like, I'm God, me so horny.
And then the second one is like, I'm God and like, Christ died for your sins.
In real life, you watching the movie, you have to go repent.
It's pretty beast that they just twisted it like that.
- So there's like, I mean, from like the 80s or like the 90s,
like there was like extremely shoehorned Christianity
into a shit ton of movies.
- Yeah.
- Which is like, like you don't think about like growing up
like Catholic or Christian or whatever,
like you don't think about it, but then like,
like movies like Michael or like Bruce Almighty and shit.
- Michael is like about like--
- Oh, it's an angel fell from heaven or like the prophecy,
movie where it's like oh there's like a war going on in heaven it's like oh well
this is the only religion yeah it's the only religion where there would be a war
between like gods or angels or whatever or like an angel falling from heaven we
should make a movie bird like to counter that we should make a movie about Islam
what and I will play Muhammad I remember watching Bruce Almighty as a little kid
and getting whatever dude and getting the DVD and like and reading the back
back and it's like you know like Bruce and like Prince these Jim Carrey but like a
visit from God and the prison Morgan Freeman and I was like they made God a
girl and like a very distinct memory of that what's that movie about like
Brendan Fraser yeah yeah with the devil it's not called charmed it's basically
maybe it's like a reverse Bruce oh my yeah it's like it's supposed to be like
instead like German Faust is it supposed to be like Faust I actually I don't
remember it all I remember is like seeing that movie it's like Elizabeth
Hurley's in it and I remember like being a kid like whoa that's Vanessa it is
cool of like there's a lot of there's a lot of men in the 2000s whose biggest
fantasy was to fuck the devil yeah you know there was a does a pretty big
motif was like the devil is real but well I mean you girl imagine that the
female devil get up to oh my god she that tail ain't just for show ooh don't
worry about it I want to tail in my ass devil's tail it is it does have that
spike at the end yeah it's I mean that's going in I mean you know maybe it's
going in that's going in your butt like an arrow so I mean maybe because it's
got like the pointed tip and then it goes down you know what I mean? Would you fuck a
bitch with a tail? Hey I don't know. People are born with tails.
There are people who... How big is a tail? Like a six, seven feet? Like a reptile tail? Having a tail like a lion
style tail that's just like a tail with a little tuft on the end is like one of
the funniest things ever to me I think just the concept of having one of those. We gotta talk about what kind of tail it would be.
I mean they don't have the tusks but they have like you know like a three-inch tail
Yeah like a vestigial tail. Three inch tail. But it's not like an animal tail.
People have three inch tails. If it's a three inch tail no no way I'm gonna be...
Dude it's like it's like that you know that like that that hand hold that you get out of a car.
It's like that. What's it what's it made out of? Person. It's not like metal.
I know like cartilage or like you know. I would assume that I was like the stuff
that yeah cartilage like an ear. Well cuz it could be a bone. I don't know.
I don't think it's a bone.
Well, tails have...
The spine goes down the tail, right?
Okay, then I'm gonna...
I don't know how far it goes.
I mean, it depends on how long the tail is.
I think it does at least a little bit.
I don't really know anything about that.
It's gotta be a fucked up tail.
Like really long or really short, though.
Like the longest tail in the world.
[laughter]
Yeah, would you fuck a girl with a tail?
Well, only if it was like the longest in the world.
If it was, yeah.
If she was famous for it, yeah.
Yeah, exactly.
If it was a fucking celebrity, sure.
I think that would probably be it.
Do you guys want to hear this Facebook post about a tale that I found?
Yeah.
I am quite sad today.
I was getting off of the bus and my tail ripped off and was left on the bus.
I checked around the stop to see if it fell out the door, but it did not.
It was the tail I blessed and have worn whenever doing a ritual involving nature, the dead,
or animals.
Now I have to get another tail and do another blessing.
When did you find that?
He wrote that the other day.
I found it in a demonology Facebook group.
it's been really I've been thinking about it a lot is I'm quite sad today I was
getting off of the bus and my tail ripped I bet you getting on to the bus and just
seeing like a tail doors closing the next stop it just falls out like Peter
there was a devil on the bus picking up the tail and be like wait a second is
this blessed I fucking hope this is blessed yeah going up to the guy me like
hey man I think you have my tail no I don't turn around that's my tail
I have that I can smell that it's blessed yeah it's blessed for nature the dead
and animals yeah yeah clearly what is demonology it's like the study of demons
and summoning demons and stuff I bet you fucking idiot I didn't know if it was a
very I don't know it's yeah it's a real science yeah I didn't know yeah you know
no I thought it was like no it's where people people like post to be like is
there any demon who who if you call upon them you can get 1 trillion dollars and
then someone will respond and be like yes there is a frog demon who does that
Here's a symbol and then you like print out the symbol and do a really yeah, can we try that?
I would love a trillion dollars in the living room. Really? Yeah, if you guys want I can we don't just print a trillion dollars
That's a better idea. Yeah, it cuts out the middleman of a deal
Yeah, it's true. It's not a bad idea. Would you fuck I'm not
Would you fuck scenarios? Would you not fuck would you marry a conjoined twin?
This is actually a really great question by Caleb. Good work. I mean, because I'd
have to love both of them. Oh here's the other thing. One of them you hate and one
of them, and one of them's your wife's sister. I mean come on.
Too easy. I mean I would have to like, I would have to like, you know, wouldn't
have to be like... You tell me it would need to be a the same damn time
situation. Yeah I'd have to be in love with both of them I think because if I'm
like if I find one of them very like their personality very grating it would
be so hard are you kidding me they're there all the time. Yeah. But if the if
they're both like you know like hey you know I really love your sister. Yeah. I'm
saying it to them like in the bathroom I would like to get married to you.
Yeah okay you know so you'd do you'd be you invest in the the side cart for the
car so you all sit in the front seat uh-huh and you'd get the three person bed.
I mean if I really did love them I would yeah yeah but goddamn could you
imagine how fucking horrible it would be if like your conjoined twins like sister
is just annoying as shit yeah like she's like a fucking like she's like I want to
go to Disney. It's like, well, you know, I can't like fucking be like, okay, like,
you know, you go to Disney, you know,
or joined at like a really inconvenient place on their body. Yeah. Yeah.
It'd be pretty bad. That's what I was thinking. Like the two heads. Yeah.
The two heads or their butt. Yeah. Or their damn butt. Yeah.
But if they're like conjoined right at the hip and it's like clear that they
could have at any point got surgery to, to unconjoined, but then they didn't.
Like a stuck on you situation. Yeah.
You know what's fucked up is when twins marry other twins.
Oh, I hate that.
And then they--
Yeah.
I hate that.
I hate watching videos like that.
Dude, I like-- fucking twins--
I hate twins.
Twins like that freak me out, because then it's like--
like if you're marrying your--
like if you're a set of twins and you're
marrying another set of twins, that
means you like being a twin that much.
And that's weird.
But if it's like twins and it's like--
what feels like you're completely different. Oh yeah, imagine if like if you're like it's
like you and your brother and your sister and you're like we have to find another
three children to marry. Like another like another group of another group of
brothers and sisters that are mapped one-to-one exactly to us. Like exactly
identical twins marrying exactly identical twins? Yeah it's fucked up it
shouldn't happen. I mean what happens what happens when you're in the dark?
They should just take one of the twins away. I don't think I've
ever known an identical twin I knew I knew some identical twins and I'm trying to
think did they do you know them as an adult Mitchell and Michael that's just a
recipe for disaster name them the most opposite give one of them a girl name
who cares just like make them as opposite as you can I knew them in
fifth grade they moved the last thing I want is like two kids showing up to
school dress the same that and they have my last name they both had Mohawks
- Here's what I do.
- That's sick.
- I do, whichever one wants a mohawk, give him the mohawk.
The other kid, don't care what he wants,
shave a giant line in the middle of his head.
- Reverse mohawk.
- Everything has to be completely reversed.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I mean, if I had twins,
I would not dress them up the same at all.
Are you kidding me?
- No.
- I'm trying to goatee on one of them
as soon as they're born.
- I'm like, I know which one's which.
- I would put one up for adoption,
whichever one crawls slower.
- That's actually smart.
- Yeah.
- No, that's horrible.
- Why? - What's bad about that?
you don't have then then when they grow up they can have like a cool reunion yeah
like for them like a cool it's an excuse to have a party three I mean you've not
seen three identical strangers you know what happens that one of them kills
himself yeah because of something else it's not the twin shit and also one for
three is like also that's so funny that like back in the 70s like those dudes
were like just cuz it was like the story was so crazy and there are three
identical guys that like back then that's all you needed to do to get into like
Studio 54 it's just like holy shit these three guys look the same yeah bring them
in here they can party with David Bowie also my favorite part of that movie is
when they talk about like they talk about like like both of them like they
don't really know where they're like you know orphans and really know where they
came from and then they meet the first two brothers like meet at like a
community college or something and they meet each other and they're like whoa
This is so weird that guy looks a lot like me. Oh, that's really weird
It's so weird that this guy looks exactly like me and they hung out for like weeks
And then they were like wait we might actually be brother. Yeah, this is a guy mirroring every single move you do
Yeah, like this is
The coolest we twinning today, you know what now that I'm thinking about it. Maybe put the fucking other kid
Go for four identical. Yeah, yeah, if you have quadruplets, oh, yeah, I'm sending them to the four corn
I'm sitting to the four corners of the world. I'm also putting a different
colored stone in their pocket that represents an element. Hopefully they
come back with like a water power and then they join in the middle they
summon me back after I'm dead. Yeah. And maybe we rob banks or something.
Just to bring it back to demonology for a second I was looking up demons that
give you wealth and the demon who gives wealth, who can bestow great wealth is
is named Klonic also named Klont and this is what it says on Wikipedia about
Klonic. Klonic is first or numero uno in the ordering of the 18 spirits.
Oh numero uno. Is that where numero uno comes from? Yeah I think so. Oh wait that's Spanish.
Oops. No it's demonology. That's really all that I'd want to share it's just that
It says he's numero uno.
I thought that was Klont.
Klont is numero uno.
I really needed a...
What?
I got a shipping notification.
My shirt came here.
You got a shitting notification.
Yes I do.
I got to take a dump right now.
You got owned dude.
Don't do that.
If you do it on that chair,
it's going to go through and make it look like
Yeah, yeah, it's gonna look like silly putty. Yeah, really sweet actually you ever seen if you ever left like silly putty in your mom's car
And like gone and touched it the next day, and it's just goo
Isn't it always goo?
And you smile like I was gonna be like oh, yeah, no no you know like you'd like melted silly putty
You ever like thrown silly putty against the wall and it cracks open and there's some kind of sticky stuff inside
It's the weirdest thing have you ever if you ever left an ice cream cone outside on a hot day you leave for an
hour you come back it's like gone. It's like the weirdest it must be quantum
something. Yeah yeah yeah. Oh man this fucking tooth is killing me. I know
somebody who cut their wisdom teeth out. You should just do that. Honestly who told me about that before? Yeah he that guy
maniac but yeah. Well I mean you know if you if anyone wants to sell me opiates.
(laughing)
- It's also funny you like high as shit
putting a scalpel in your own mouth.
It's probably a good idea.
- Yeah, yeah.
- No, don't try to sell me opiates.
- No.
- Do not.
(laughing)
- Yeah, don't sell me opiates.
- Yeah, don't.
- Don't.
- I hate Oxycontin.
- Oh, don't do that to me.
- That'd be so mad.
You know people get addicted to that crap?
- Yeah, not me.
- Not me, dude.
I'm not on opiates. Yeah, I hate medicine. I hate Tylenol. I'm really scared to go to
the doctor. Don't tell me Tylenol. No, seriously. Oh, I can't take acetaminophen.
Not maximum strength Tylenol, anything but that. I'm going to the doctor next
week for the first time in like ten years. Congratulations. I'm very, very
scared you get there and they're like oh my god this patient has cancer his hair
is completely gone yeah somehow I lost my hair from radiation therapy not having
you know the doctor it's just your doctor thinks that like you have cancer
cuz your hair's cut I do hope I doesn't understand that I get a funny doctor
yeah yeah yeah I'm gonna patch Adams style doctor oh yeah well you know
laughter is the best medicine yeah you know it pisses me off when you see like a
comedy show that's called like Best Medicine it's like oh fuck you that is
you fucking that's if your comedy show is called anything other than like like
Legion of Skanks live it's a terrible name for a show yeah yeah you're picking
the best name Legion of Skanks exactly no you have to name it like like it needs
to have a disgusting name I think. Yeah. Right? Yeah. Or just something stupid. Not
like, not like, look, because Best Medicine is like 40 year old like
promoter. That could be like a UCB House Troop name. I truly don't know if I've ever seen a comedy show
with a good name. Yeah, they're never good. Like literally never in my life. Or just name it,
name it the place that it's happening. Yeah. Like if you're doing it at a bar
just call it the bar's name. Yeah. Stand up today. Yeah. You know like that's a pretty
good you know that's not bad yeah cuz no one's gonna like care about the name of
the show yeah like if you're trying to make the show the name of your show
funny there's five thousand fucking shows in New York City that are called well
here we go yeah and they take place like they're on like some kids roof yeah they
have the most famous comedians in the world there and they they sell half the
tickets yeah it's a very weird ecosystem names to pun names good names horrible
can't can't have those yeah you got a name is something good like podcast
about list yeah that's a good talk to us about the about naming stuff yeah sorry
we're fucking have a natural talent podcast about list is a great name
people won't admit it but ten years from now they're gonna be looking back and
this is they're gonna be like oh that's the way that's what sparked this and
this naming craze yeah. I mean everything naming crazy everything. I mean
everything's going to be called something about something just wait for
the twenty thirty naming crazy. Yeah, it's going to be crazy dude every tv
show tv show about yeah about tv show about the office. That'll be the
reboot
because that's like you know, that's what it was really tv show about a
band of brothers.
- Yeah, yeah, see, it's like so easy to rename stuff that.
- Yeah, yeah.
- It'll be, actually, they'll do like a Criterion
collection release where everything is TV show about,
and then, yeah, kind of the name.
- Yeah, they're gonna put TV shows
in the Criterion collection too.
That would be sick.
- And podcasts, and pictures, funny pictures.
They're gonna put that in Criterion.
- I mean, the Criterion collection,
once they put the baby, screaming baby photoshopped
with Mr. Bean's face on it,
once they put that in the Criterion.
- They're gonna be putting in fast food too.
can get a criterion Big Mac yeah they're gonna put in big balls little dick yeah
the video deserves to be preserved I mean I want to find the original because the
thing about that video is it got passed around so much that it was screen
recorded so many times yeah you can make out that there's a big balls and little
dick but maybe we need a restoration team yeah yeah we need Peter Jackson and
like a team of people to go through and there needs to be a full documentary
about them restoring the video.
- Yeah, about, yeah.
- Yeah.
- Them restoring, look at his butt.
- Let me see your butt.
- He naked.
- Oh man.
- Yeah, and Peter Jackson will just be like
sitting there with some dial just like perfectly.
- Yeah.
- We could do AI upscaling on it.
- Boost the color up.
- We should.
(laughing)
- I think, yeah, we will do that.
- Boost the balls up.
Make the balls larger.
- The balls.
- If you raise the contrast.
- We're trying to be as close as to the original material
as possible.
the contrast up you're gonna you're gonna you're gonna lose
all the shadow and a little bit not a microscopic dick a little
bit comes out in a bunch of like like film reviews are really
pissed off and they're like they it completely ruined there's
there's this weird green tone now and they totally overdid it
they CGI remastered the balls to make them bigger and bouncier
video that's like clearly made in like blender. I got gray box
the audio yeah Oh he naked big balls little dick let me see your butt and
then just like a bouncing like a buzzing like liquid simulation of the ball gonna
be I like the thing that's gonna piss me off the most about it though is once
they once fucking Universal Studios remakes it big balls little dick the
right yeah big balls little dick the ride and there's an you just go it's just
- There's a roller coaster that just goes slowly
and there's just an animatronic next to you
and it's running with his legs, his dick out.
And they're just like, over like a tinny speaker,
it's just like, "You're naked, big balls, where's death?"
- They, dude, they honestly--
- Like a 4D experience. - And then it does,
and then it does-- - That's a good idea.
- And then it does a hundred loop-de-loops at the end.
- Yeah, to get you really dizzy.
- Yeah.
- So you come off the ride, you're like, "Ugh."
- Oh, I was thinking, I was thinking like,
one of Universal's like, 4D rides,
like the fucking like, race through New York.
So it's like you see the big ball, you're trying to chase the big ball.
Oh yeah, it's like swerving through, it goes like between the balls and the dick.
Yeah. Oh, he gets hit by the biggening ray.
Oh yeah, they have to build a story around it.
Yeah, and then the big balls, little dick, so he's trying to, so it starts out,
he's trying to, he's in the lab,
and he's trying to make his dick bigger. He's a scientist.
He's trying to make his dick bigger with the ray.
- Yeah, the beginning ray.
- The beginning ray.
So it misses by, I mean, his calculations are off.
- One nanometer.
- Yeah, it was one nanometer off and it hit the balls
and that's why the balls are big.
- Yeah.
- So he gets so mad, he drips off his, I mean, you know.
- He hulks out.
- He's already naked, he's hulking out.
- Yeah.
- So then, you know, you're going through the city
and you get like a call, it's like Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson
and Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson's like calling you
he's like like oh we need your we need your help we need you and a crew to get
into New York City and I need you to chase down the big balls little dick
man you have you have those like you know those water guns where you're
trying to be great is going off the chain it's going crazy where you have to
like shoot the thing to do the race like I like it like at an amusement park
there's one of those booths yeah the water gun you have one of those and you
have to shoot it into the dick hole inflate the dick to be the same size as
the balls. So it's also like the MIB ride at Universal. I haven't been to Universal.
Okay. So you're Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson.
[Music]
So Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson, you and the other riders are a part of a team.
Yeah. Well that's and all the briefing is in the line. It's like what you see
in the line where it's a looping video and he's like listen agent we get a we his
balls are it's like a blob and balls are gonna take over the city we have to
balance it out by making his dick large as well there's also there's
velociraptor yeah and then the stormtroopers walk yeah yeah it's
exactly like that new Star Wars right taking a wrong turn when you're walking
through the new like Star Wars experience and walking into like an
unfinished room and you see them building like a big
else is so high quality and then it's like a Chuck E. Cheese animatronic with a big balls
little dick man.
You're like, "What is this?"
And they're like, "Oh, we're still working on it.
Get out of here."
"Get out!
You're not supposed to be in here!"
There's a guy with like all the, what are those called, the fucking electrodes on his
head sitting there and they're just feeding him lines with a big balls little dick as
he watches.
Star Wars Episode 10.
Let me see your butt.
that's actually not a bad idea because like I see these videos a lot and I'm
like I wish I was there I wish I could experience this oh I wish I saw the big
balls little dick there's so many yeah like I wish I would have done anything I
walk around in my life waiting for to be in one of those videos so I would do
anything to have like the 40 created in an amusement park yeah it's a really
good idea with the right so would that ride end with you getting the video look
at him big balls yeah with that would it's like Pokemon snap at the end yeah
okay yeah and then and then there's like a booth where you can buy the video of
yourself standing next to him uh-huh taking the video of him yeah I mean
there's so many good ones dude like yeah imagine they recreated the like that the
at the end of the mummy ride when like I still don't know the rides the rap
battle video of those two kids in school where the guy says you smoke fagues
remember that one no or like the mind if I while out video yeah that would be so
many ones oh you can't do this on concrete yeah yeah that'd be a great one
yeah and they could I mean and I would want them all to get their individual
right your mission it's it's Black Friday you need to get all the you need
get all your shopping done for black Friday yeah and the my you can't do this
on concrete guys like he's like the final boss yeah yeah it's not a bad arcade
game than a ride mmm no I think no it has to be a ride what other video it was
there Kato has been caught straight slipping it's your job to fire the
mustard you just have to shoot mustard
he starts chasing you and you have to take a face of action
the car moves back in the ride
he's going like with like mustard
yeah damn
there's so many videos I would rather have a 40 ride of
than fucking, what is that one, Escape from Gringotts?
- Escape from Gringotts?
- At Universal.
I keep talking about Universal, I wanna go there,
so we should do a trip.
- I would love to, dude.
- That would be, yeah.
- We gotta go to Universal Studios, Orlando.
- It's probably insanely expensive, huh?
- Yeah, probably so expensive.
I used to go with my ex all the time.
But, fucking, we gotta go there, not go in there,
we have to go to the Hot Dog Hall of Fame, that's it.
I do want to buy I all the fame we need to all the fame we need to go back to me to
take a trip back to New England ago to canopy
we can we did that is not a candidate is better that I like I really want to go
to the summer but we did and we didn't have you any we we
might have time at the end I mean September's probably the best time to go
there
yeah everyone's going back to yeah no kids middle the day go to canopy
dude and have their Halloween stuff in October all ship is fuckin spooky world
yeah
Yeah, dude, we gotta go. Spooky World?
[laughs]
Is where you wanna take me?
Spooky World.
You two scared? Do they have good rides?
No, I'm not too scared about Spooky World!
They do have good- well, if we-
See, that's why we gotta go at the end of September,
'cause it would still be hot enough that we could go on the- the...
Boston Tea Party.
Yeah.
Dude, the Yankee Cannonball.
You gotta check out the Yankee Cannonball.
It's fuckin' sick.
What that is.
It's a really old wooden roller coaster.
Oh, I love hurting my back.
Yeah.
It's sick.
Dude, Yankee Cannonball, um...
Ultimate Frisbee, I think?
The Ultimate Frisbee, yeah, that one I wrote that one so many times.
It's the worst name ever.
They have a fun log flume.
Oh, it's the whole park is New England themed.
Oh, okay.
So Ultimate Frisbee is like one of...
It's not, no, just some of them are.
Some of the older ones are New England themed.
You play Ultimate Frisbee with white people, shit.
White people play Frisbee in Harvard Yard.
I guess that's true, yeah.
Harvard Yard.
They have a skateboard ride too.
Really?
That's like a baby version of the Ultimate Frisbee.
Yeah, I like that one.
They have Da Vinci's Dream.
Da Vinci's Dream, oh, fuck.
Yeah, what else do they have?
The Caterpillar, they have.
I think I've heard of Da Vinci's Dream.
Yeah, it's like a big like, you swings and it goes like...
It was to cut open a pregnant woman.
[Laughter]
I think Da Vinci's Dream is just like a, that's just like a carnival ride.
Yeah.
Yeah, only a few of them are New England themed.
This one's huge.
Humongous, you said.
This one's way bigger than the one at the carnival.
Those are the scariest rides.
Those will give you more...
Yeah, 'cause it's teenagers operated.
Those will give you more of a thrill than any like,
thing called like x-squared maximum fuck you.
Speaking of untamed. Yeah untamed. Is that a good one?
I've written untamed. Oh dude, untamed fucking rules.
Yeah. God, we've planned a canopy trip on the show
three times now. Probably. We've never done it dude. You have to do it. You guys are promise breakers.
We have to do it. I think if we just keep saying it. Look me in the eyes and tell
me you promised me you'll take me to Canobie Lake Park. I promise that I'll take you to
Canobie Lake Park. You have to just drive us to Canobie Lake Park.
- No!
- You have to.
- You would have to drive us, that's the thing.
- When?
- Tomorrow.
- I'll go tomorrow, sure.
- Really?
- Yeah.
How much are tickets?
- No, not tomorrow.
- Not even that much.
- We have to wait 'til it cools down some.
- Yeah.
- And then we're gonna go, we'll plan a trip.
- Oh my God.
All right, we'll plan it tomorrow.
- We'll stay with Patrick's family.
- Yeah.
- Oh, maybe.
- Yeah!
- We'll stay with all of Patrick's family.
- Maybe we get like an Airbnb or something.
- I think we'll stay with Patrick's family.
- Why?
- My parents would fucking love to keep you guys.
Okay, me and Caleb stay with Patrick's family.
And I stay at a hotel.
Patrick gets an Airbnb.
Patrick has to go back to New York.
Yeah.
Me and Cam go to Canobie Lake Park.
You know what?
Now that you've mentioned my parents-
And we show up at your door-
They're gonna fucking text me about this now.
We show up at your parents' door with an urn.
Good.
You know what?
We need this to happen.
We show up at your parents' door with an urn that's labeled Patrick.
We just start crying as soon as I open the door.
The other day we were-
I forget what we were looking at it for.
were looking at we found these like these like custom urns on on on on etsy and
and there was one that was a sponge most of them were like designed like they're
like pretty well made like there's one that looked like a bowling pin but a
sponge from one is just an urn that just has a picture of sponge it was fun and
dude it's so depressed yeah but that I was a child urn yeah well but just like
imagining like looking down from heaven and seeing that like your shitty
city daughter is ordering an urn for you off of etsy but like but after we
looked at that we're laughing about it. I like I was I just started getting
ads for the like the sponge bob urn like not for urns but for specifically that
urn showed up twice like side hunting urn to it is yeah, it's like a child's
urn yeah, how pissed would you be if you were fifteen and you and then you
similarly look down on your mom buying a pink Spongebob earn for you.
The age when you're like you don't talk to you don't tell your mom what you're into
because you're a teen.
So she's like, "I don't really like Spongebob I guess."
Plus I have this Etsy gift card I guess I'll do this.
But imagine how sick it would be if she was trying to order the Spongebob earn from that
Etsy store but she misclicked and accidentally got the beer keg one.
True.
The beer keg one I was like put me in that.
Actually kill me now just so I can spend my time in that.
It's pretty cool.
There's one that just had the Bud Ice logo on it and then one that had like Natty Light.
What kind of urn would you guys want to be put in?
Me?
One that's like shaped like a pool.
Oh that's cool.
I want a clear one so nobody can mess with my stuff.
Nobody can mess with the stuff in there.
Because otherwise people are going to be like, I'm walking around and I'm holding a glass
of milk, I don't feel like finishing it.
It's going in the urn.
It's opaque, you can't see it.
My dad had my grandma's ashes in the living room for like years when I was a kid.
Like her urn was like above our TV.
And I was like, I always wondered what it was because like the urn kind of like looked like a...
Like a PlayStation?
[Laughter]
I didn't find out it was an urn until I was like seven or eight years old.
I think my dad was like pointing it out and was like, "Yeah, that's your grandma."
And I was like, "What?"
Because it was kind of shaped like an old, like the palace from Mulan.
yeah yeah so it's like oh like what is that why is that box up there it's like
oh that's your fucking grandma it's like oh cool people just get burned alive
like that's like it's pretty scary such a weird thing to learn as a kid I don't
really put into a dragon egg or used to like cut cocaine yeah I think that'd be
pretty funny right is like just hundreds of people just snorting like my brother
every salt shaker in the city yeah yeah all right or Disney World spread my
ashes there. But yeah but just on one ride. And just on one kid. You know that's a huge
problem. Get in front of a roller coaster. You know that's a huge problem. So everyone
gets off stage like they held a stick of dynamite in the tune but it's all my body. That's a
huge problem on It's a Small World for some reason. I think you can tell me this. Yeah
people will go in there and try to like throw their like family or friends ashes into It's
a small world which that's the scariest fucking ride you can do that I I've like
seen videos of it like the old ones and shit it's nuts yeah that well it's okay
we'll throw my ashes at the Tasmanian devil performer at six flags yeah yeah
yeah appear in them like a magic yeah all right yeah Pat's parents me and
Caleb are coming for you