Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
- Premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Right, start.
- Oh my word.
- Maybe we will give you that bulletproof vest.
- I think, here's the thing.
Most of my clothes are airsoft proof.
- Yeah.
- You know?
- My skin is airsoft proof.
I've been hit by a number of BBs that I've gone through.
- They hurt pretty bad.
I can't believe kids do that.
it might really hurts my brother shot me with a airsoft shotgun in the ass when i
was like
ten
and uh... and you've never been the same no
i really i really want to do it
when i was in high school there's this like group of guys that like i i kind
of hung out with but like
we were like good friends and they would go play airsoft and never invite me and i
remember being like i really really want to go
i feel like so like left out
but like i'm glad i didn't go because it would have been like one faggot and then
I would have gotten destroyed.
Like a wolf.
Yeah, exactly.
They were just like being kind
and being like we can't let you come
because if we do we're going to fucking kill you.
You know what's funny is that
Airsoft, like my brother
is like, he runs a paintball field
and I grew up playing paintball and stuff.
To paintball guys, Airsoft is the gayest
thing you can do.
That's so funny.
They hate Airsoft.
the case because I always thought airsoft was more because you it's because you're
pretending to be like in the military instead of just like like paintballs
about like it might as well be like basketball you know they think it's like
a sport but airsoft those guys like are serious they're like LARPing hard. You know what's so sick is the
the airsoft POV videos where it's like like it's like 18 year olds playing with
like 12 year olds and they're like fighting each other over like like call
Call your fucking hits!
Yeah.
Call your hits!
And the guy who makes the videos, he'll add like a hood, like it's Call of Duty.
He'll add like a chair in the middle.
It's so fucking cool.
Oh my god.
Our cable's broken.
You can't hear a single thing I'm saying?
It's just messed up here.
Just take this.
Okay.
We're doing, we're changing it out live?
Does that work?
Talk?
Hello?
Is your, no, it doesn't work at all now.
Did you turn the mic off?
No.
Oh my god.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Awesome.
Oh, I love this.
I love our podcast.
Okay, that's the worst cable.
Oh my God.
Okay, hold on.
Oh no.
I'm going to pause it.
Okay, we're back.
Sorry.
If you put your phone near the cables, it stops working.
I don't know how it works, but we've discovered this.
If the phone gets near the cable.
Have you guys heard about the new iPhone?
It has a podcast mode settings.
When you're podcasting, you put it in podcast mode and then it won't mess with the cables.
Really?
Yeah, really.
Oh my God.
I don't know.
I think mine gives the most interference.
really yeah really
that's all
oh my god
no i think mine gives the most interference
no i think mine gives the most
mine has flatburden
mine's better it gives more
my phone's more powerful so it interferes harder
wow
april spends way too much time on 9to5mac.com
i know so much about iphones
finding out what's gonna be what little little gadget is gonna be the next one
who's that guy that guy marcus
incredible things, you know, I Apple is yeah, I'm doing some really great
things. They still have that bald guy makes all everything silver Steve
Johnny Ives Johnny Ives Johnny Ives. He's the guy in the commercials.
Who's like I wanted to make a phone that was silver. You know those
that guy with it when they're showing the product shots and then
they're interviewing the bald British guy and the and he's in a
black shirt. He's like we wanted to make a job. We wanted to make
- Not Steve Jobs.
- Wait, are you telling me you've like
watched an entire presentation?
- My mom is like an acolyte for Apple.
Where like I grew up and we watched it
like it was the ball dropping on New Year's Eve.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah, yeah.
Which is weird, 'cause like we didn't own almost anything.
She had like one laptop.
And she was just--
- That must have changed your damn life.
- I think it really did, yeah.
'Cause she's so like technologically illiterate
that there was finally like a computer she could use.
It's basically a jitterbug.
It's like a, like kinda.
It's like a phone almost with five buttons on it.
- I love my Jitterbug though.
- Jitterbug rocks.
We're here with the girl god, Grace and April.
- Hey. - Hey, what's up?
Hi April. - Hi, hi Grace.
- How are y'all?
Doing good?
- Doing all right, it's been a pretty crazy,
it's been a pretty crazy little bit here.
- So you got into New York yesterday?
Or two days ago? - Two nights ago, yeah.
- But yesterday you had an event happen.
Yesterday I got absolutely decked like really hard.
Like I've been in a few bites before and I've never like,
this guy who is like a self-described,
essentially self-described feminist filmmaker
who like made this movie that just came out
with like Ezra Miller in it.
That's about these like,
it's about these women in college
like getting revenge on their rapists and stuff.
It's called like, what's it called?
like he did he made the film to study what's gonna happen when the women from
college come back to get nightmare he had a crazy dream I need to write this
down but this fucking so this fucking indie filmmaker dude at Clara's that's
like pool bar that we go to was being so like he was like he was being like a
little bitch to like begin with because he was like, we were
playing pool with him. And he kept being like, this is the
rule. That's what I was like, What do you mean? He's like,
that's bar my table, my rules. When you scratch you suck me
off. Yeah. Yeah. He was like, every ball I get in lets me say
a new slur.
My table.
My rules, but he he was just like, he was just being a little
bitch and I let him be a little bitch until we like Callie our friend Callie
was was holding her boyfriend's dog and so we're like okay so love shot and her
boyfriend was gonna take a shot and he was like no no no no no no no no no no
like just like got so upset over it and you guys put money on this game or
something we were just trying to have fun I had a lot of money on the
money that this guy was good
I left the night about a million dollars
this guy is a Brooklyn indie filmmaker with no job except directing one movie
he's a billionaire. His parents must be billionaires. My job is to direct one movie. That's my job.
100%. Just got hired to direct one movie. So what led to him using your head like a
speed bag? So I'm like the kind of person, April and I were talking about when a guy
is being an asshole at a bar, there's like the school of mind that April adopts which
is to kind of just like who cares. Yeah. Or I mean like, I mean yeah you care because
he's being an asshole. And then mine is like, I just don't want to slide. I'll go up to them
and I'll be like, "Fuck you." So basically what happened is when he didn't want the celeb
shot to happen, I was like, "You're a little bitch. Why are you acting like a little bitch?
Fucking calm down. This is pool. Let's have fun." And I roasted him a little bit and I
called him like an assistant scout leader and really angered him to a point and
then at the end of the game he walked up to like shake my hand and I didn't shake
his hand and he got really really really offended by that. Well that's the honor of the game.
of the game that's why I do want to cop to that and apologize to that and I'm
learning and I'm growing he's posting pictures of you on Instagram like this
one does not shake my hand anybody knows her name
He this this continues he like he's like just kind of like getting like progressively way way way drunker
He was walking around like I wasn't drinking, but he was like fucking yeah
You know and I go up to the bar to close out my tab
and I had just like lost the last game of pool that we were playing and he and
And it was like it was a dumb shot where like I was like
Trying I was trying to get the eight ball in and I I scratched and totally missed the eight ball
You know, it was like a really bad shot up in there when that happened. We all just laughed and stuff. Mm-hmm, but he walks up like
Two people down from me. So there's like one guy in between us and he loudly says
Well, I guess karma always gets you in the end
Actually, like what I I cared about losing that game because again like I guess it is mine
Every game of fool is like Yu-Gi-Oh level
He says that and then I look over at him and I'm like
And I was a little drunk so I was kind of being like a bitch
But I was like, what do you do for a living? Like are you happy with your life?
I'm like I'm happy with my life. I said I said I write for Rick and Morty
Yeah, I was like I was I just fucking was like I started listing off things that are good about my life
Basically, I was like, you look like you work in tech and hate your life and have a bunch
of exes that hate you for good reasons.
And he walked over and just got like in my face in my face, like was like, like spit
coming off of me just yelling at me.
I was like, dude, please just like, stop this.
then he just fucking like slam me in the head a couple of times.
Whoa, right at the bar, right?
At the bar, right in front of the bartender.
Did they kick him out or anything?
No, they, I had to like walk him out.
Like I got in between them and was like, all right, it's time to go.
It's, it's time for you to leave.
And he was like, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
And then he left and then his, his friends followed him out.
And then I think the, one of the funniest parts to me is afterwards his girlfriend was
was like came back in to close out his tab and she starts talking to me and she's and she's
like "Grace was making like all like I know he punched he punched her but Grace is making
all these assumptions like that he's like straight like he's not straight"
*laughter*
I was like oh oh yeah that's the biggest takeaway from this.
Some guys sucked him off one time
Any trans woman he wants I know
It's legal to murder
Not real people
Yeah, sounds like a fun night
Something about pool really takes it out of people. It was also at Clara's. Do you remember that one?
That crazy woman.
Yeah, that woman was so mad about everything. Something about that bar, people who play pool there are real psychos.
Yeah.
It's cool.
It's cause the wings of them, something in them.
The wings, yeah. It's too good. Too much MSG in the wings. Makes you go crazy, dude.
Biden's gotta regulate that out.
Yeah.
There's stuff in our nation's buffalo wings. I'm not just that far from that.
But you never see...
That's ruining our men.
What is it?
It's making men go crazy.
Wings are ruining masculinity.
There's not like a practical difference between like playing pool at a bar and playing like
ski ball at Dave and Buster's.
Right.
But something about, you never see...
It's the sticks.
It might be the sticks.
That's true.
That's the difference.
You're holding a weapon.
It makes men, it's like brings out a certain kind of masculinity.
Yeah, it's like you're holding a phallic weapon.
It's a spear.
It's a caveman spear.
Yeah, right.
It speaks to a very primal urge.
urge. One of the big differences is that
skee-ball, who knows what the rules of
fucking skee-ball are. I know all the fucking rules. I play league. We can talk shit about pool all we want, but skee-ball we're not fucking talking shit about.
I bet you go for those little holes in the corner. Yeah the
thousand one. Oh my God, that's the dude. Fuck you man. What you're going to sit
there and use all it's about getting tickets. No, it's not to impress your
sweetheart. If you're not going for the tiny corner a thousand holes on
skeeball, you probably you probably shoot the cue ball with your hand.
Probably, you know what I should have known that he was going to be violent
because he was shooting the cue ball by punching.
I really think that he drew your face on the cupid.
He's using a sharpie and lipstick to draw.
I don't know if you can do that.
He's like, bar rules, bar rules.
Faggot, play.
You got a ball in this game.
You can say faggot.
You think he's about to pull out a pool cube,
but then it's just a duffel bag that has Hulk hands in it.
He chalks them up.
Yeah, did he chalk his fist up before he punched you?
Yeah, he did.
He did, dramatically.
really long yeah I mean I noticed that people who are like that about pool
usually kind of suck at it yeah people who are good at pool they don't care
about like a free game they don't care about games have money on them yeah you
know yeah so he probably sucked yeah he wasn't killer I mean it which he was
like fine but like he definitely was acting like he was really good by that I
I mean like when he was about to take a shot he would he would spend like two
minutes looking at every angle and being like I think I could do no no maybe this
you know he was like beautiful minded like five minutes calculating the angles
So I do have one question. Do you guys think if I was there it would have gone
completely different? I would have stopped it pretty much? I do. I kind of think
like if like a guy had been there, like a straight guy like one of
yourselves, it possibly would have. So it's our fault?
Considering going out last night. I'm too tired. If one of you guys had been there he would have been way too horny to even see it.
Yeah, he's gay.
He would have been busy sucking my dick and he wouldn't have even thought to punch you.
What's I'm done with this?
He was like hitting on April low-key too.
Really?
He was just what a guy.
What a guy.
You know what I think actually got him like really pissed?
Like the, like I didn't remember this until now but like legit I think the last thing I said before he punched me was
was and also you're hitting on April a bunch and that's weird and he was like
I'm not hitting on April. I'm 12! That's so weird of him. And then it got in my face a bunch and I just went like this and like I grazed his hat and he fucking touched me twice.
He was just looking for an excuse. A molecule of you touching him. He was gonna he's gonna wail.
And just fucking wailed me. But I didn't even like intentionally touch him or
anything. Yeah, yeah. But you should have. Yeah, you should you should start
wearing Wolverine claws. Yeah, yeah, yeah. You should get them installed.
That's the surgery.
My mom gave it to me. So it's a little embarrassing.
Oh, wow. Yes, it's a it's a double barrel like
it's a
love mom.
on and now I want to buy a I wonder if you can you have just like a flintlock
pistol yeah really I know
what is the I feel like you could get away with when you see the well. I mean
you see those pictures well, no, because you see those pictures like that, like
like police departs. It's like office yeah off the street. It's like a
homemade gun or like an antique store gun or something. If you show up to the
store like dressed up like a colonial soldier I think they are forced to sell
you that yeah I think it's like well it wouldn't make sense it's not a story of
a George Washington I feel like you could have though a laser gun yeah
get two options you get blunderbuss or you get like the needler from Halo yeah
it's the only shit you could walk you could open carry a need you should be
able to have a musket without a license it's like you're not gonna like you got
a hundred guys you're never gonna be able to do a mass shooting with a musket I
don't know if this I think this is just a New England thing did they do this at
your school - they had a guy when I was in fourth grade they had a guy who was
like a like a colonial reenactor from like Sturbridge village or some shit and
and he came to our school in the parking lot just fired a bus.
Showed us how to load it and everything. He was like, and this is what they used to use
back in the day. And then he's like loading it and shit. And then he just shot it into the air.
They didn't do that at my school, but we went on a field trip to, uh,
so we didn't have to, like, he could have just done this at stir bridge instead of like
little parking lot like why we saw a guy doing that on the beach in North
Carolina
for sure. Yeah, you don't remember get into the he's demonstrating the
musket yeah, he shot it into the air a couple of times. I would love to get a
gun and shoot it into the air. Yeah, probably the coolest thing.
Especially if it's like a musket like if he's like yeah, you're shooting that
straight up in the you're aiming that up in the air and it's going directly
sideways. Yeah,
- I got it straight up into the air
and I killed someone 10 feet to my right.
- Do you think people ever shoot straight up in the air,
like hoping that it'll come back down and kill them,
but it'll look like a goofy accident?
(laughing)
So they're like, it won't look like a suicide,
their family will be like, oh, that's horrible.
What a dumb move, and not like, why did he do it?
(laughing)
- Yeah, we'll always remember Yosemite Sam.
Loving father and brother.
(laughing)
that big trick shot. My God,
seventy Sam's kids are probably so annoying. Oh my God, imagine a class with
you seventy Sam's kids and
annoying did and they were short to yeah yeah
being for like meeting so in a bar being friends with them for like a few
months and eventually get in the covers. I were like yeah, like my dad's
you seventy
by the way
He's like, just don't Google my dad.
- Yeah, thank you.
Thanks for being so cool.
Like, I knew you know.
- Know what you don't know.
- I know what?
I know what?
(laughing)
- I mean, come on.
- You got like a big mustache.
(laughing)
- Big red mustache.
I still don't get what you're saying.
(laughing)
- Cowboy hat, just any time, it's like,
"$50, what?"
(laughing)
Okay, yeah, that's like a fun thing you do, but please, I'm not connecting the dots here.
[Laughter]
Dude, it's so sick whenever like a fucking like lawn company, like a lawn special, a lawn
care thing has like a fucking like just bootleg like Looney Tunes logo on it.
Well that's really common here.
There's no such thing as like copyright infringement in New York.
Yeah, like being Panther if you're like doing insulation, like Yosemite Sam for lawn care
for some reason. The ice cream trucks? Are you kidding me? Oh yeah. They'll have like,
they'll have Dora, SpongeBob, Dexter, and like Captain Marvel on one. The sickest one I ever saw was like a tikka
kebab vendor in Niagara Falls that just had Lightning McQueen on it. That's so cool.
It just said "King of Tikka Kebab" and then it just...
Lightning Queen!
Lightning Queen is the king of Tikka Kebab!
There's a place in North Carolina, my hometown, that they had to change their name.
It was a vape shop called Darth Vapor.
They got owned.
Darth Vapor!
They had Darth Vader was their logo, but he had smoke.
They flew too close to the sun.
Yeah.
They should have had some sort of caricature or something.
No, they went "Picture of Darth Vader" as their logo and they got in trouble.
and now they're called smoke cangs smoke cangs my friends in Chicago will took a
picture of a vape shop that was called smoking bad with the breaking bad
I learned that there's like a it's like franchise like not franchise but there's
like multiple Zaza R Us locations.
- Zaza R Us, yeah.
- So cool.
- Like Zaza Gabor?
- No, I think Zaza means weed or something.
- Like Toys R Us, I think is the play.
- But for weed.
- What?
- I think it's probably tobacco.
- What is it, do you ever see places,
there are places that have like Rick and Morty
as their logo.
- Oh, everywhere you see that.
- There's like, there are, I feel like are weed places
that'll just have Rick and Morty like posters in there.
They won't even go as far as to put a logo or anything.
Just a poster, yeah.
This is where you gotta go.
There's a...
It's probably a sign of a good...
Noah Colvin's been taking pictures of every Rick and Morty weed thing he finds.
Yeah.
And he said he's probably up to like 500 pictures or something.
My God.
They're everywhere.
Like Rick and Morty bongs.
Yeah.
They got the fucking pickle Rick bowl.
I've seen some truly terrifying Morty bowls where it'll be like his...
mouth is the hole oh and one of them there was glass teeth
expensive weed stuff is so crazy yeah and it looked like shit are you saying it
would be a dumb idea to purchase one of those are you saying if someone had
purchase one of those it would be for my
Not telling I
Remember Joe who shares the office with us?
He like somebody gave him like a bunch of like like weed stuff for free
they like quit smoking and I gave him like all these insane like an insane bong and it's saying like bubbler and stuff and
and the bubbler that he got was like this crazy blown glass spaceship and he
handed it to me and he was like, check this out.
And I immediately just dropped it into a million pieces.
And then he was real mad at me. Yeah. And I was just laughing.
I was like, it was free. And also who cares a fucking bubbler.
It might as well be an apple.
You might my ex had this like Smurf bowl.
It's just like a piece of glass, just like shaped like a Smurf.
and then its butt was like the bowl.
- Oh.
- Yeah, so you just-- - Oh, come on.
- Look at this damn Smurf's butt.
- It's fucking disgusting.
- That's nasty.
- But like the glass, like it looked enough like a Smurf,
but it was like if an AI tried to like create a Smurf,
because like the eyes were like protruding off of its head,
and like its face just like it had no mouth or anything,
just like a big nose too,
and it's like you couldn't set it down anywhere.
- Doesn't sound like a Smurf at all.
- If you did, it would like immediately
like topple over like that.
It broke like immediately.
I love getting the toys where they got the colors wrong.
The figures where they painted the wrong color.
They like didn't paint the eyes or something.
Those are so cool.
Yeah.
I want one of those right now.
Me too.
I'll get me one.
I'd love to go to a flea market and find a flea market right now.
Is there like a good there's not flea markets.
there's one in a Dumbo I think but that's so funny there's a place called Dumbo here
it is really funny I'd never where is Dumbo? It's up there it's like it's
downtown Brooklyn it's yeah yeah yeah I would not want to live there I would maybe it's magical
It's where the circus is
I don't think I think Dumbo is like $18 ice cream and shit oh yeah yeah it's
that's really stupid. It's bad now. We first moved here two years ago. It was
the coolest neighborhood in the world. The fucking losers move to New York. Oh
yeah. Everyone wants to move to a dumb ball.
I want to flea market like like the ones where they sell the which I guess is
just the new Hampshire flea market.
Yeah, because you can are you from New Hampshire from Massachusetts. He's
where in New Hampshire? I'm from Londonderry. That's a made up place.
It's so fucked up. I think it used to be called Nutfield and then...
Do you think it used to be? Do you have a suspicion?
I have a feeling. I have a feeling.
I think Nutfield is like weird because there's places like Pinnardville.
There's Pinnardville but Pinnardville is technically Gothstown and then Nutfield is in Londonderry
I hate this damn New England tarmac. This guy just did words. He's just out here saying words.
Nutfield? Nutfield, yeah. Why'd they change it?
Oh you, you know what I'm doing. The indigenous people called it Nutfield.
Yeah, I think you're right. Yeah.
I met someone who like lives in New Hampshire and I was trying to get them to like come to New York
for the show this weekend and they were like it's six hours away and I was like what?
six hours from where?
I thought everything was like right, yeah.
To like top of the Keys?
It's probably four hours to London Airfinir.
So it's gotta be a little further than that.
Yeah.
It's probably two hours further.
I don't know where in New Hampshire exactly.
Probably two hours further.
Something tells me, yeah.
Okay smart guy.
Okay, well you didn't factor in traffic.
Five to six hours.
It's one to two hours.
(laughing)
- Yeah, but the London Dairy Flea Market's sick
'cause you can just get, it's like,
there's so many swords there.
- Dude, yeah, I go--
- It's the most amount of swords.
- So every other booth is like, it's guns and swords,
and the next one is like, is $1 DVDs.
- Yeah, the ones that come in a plastic wrap.
- Yeah, it's the best.
- I could spend like five hours in a place like that.
- I would, like, you would go every other Sunday
and just like make the rounds there,
just trying to get behind like knives and shit.
Yeah, there is a
some of the best t-shirts ever too.
In Wilmington that has like,
I mean, it's just like a great like Southern one
where you can get like every famous painting
that somebody has redone with Obama in it.
Oh my God.
You can get like the Mona Lisa with Obama.
You can get the Last Supper with Obama,
just like all this shit.
That's sick.
And then also there's this booth that is like
this like one-
Is Obama Jesus in the Last Supper?
Or is he one of the disciples?
He's Jesus, yeah.
And then I-
And he's all the disciples.
I actually, no, I think he's Jesus and then like...
Rahm Emanuel is like...
[laughter]
I think it's like, they give Obama Jesus and then like MLK is one of the disciples.
Oh my god!
Who's Judas?
Oh shit.
You.
Oh my god! I'm in the painting!
You know who Judas probably is?
Mr. Kanye West.
That's right.
they also have at this sorry to have to say it
I don't know if you guys have been following along
you go to a flea market and there's a booth and it's all paintings like that
but they're replaced with you
where did you get this? who did you get these?
it's uncanny it's not based on you
I'm actually like that at the one with all the Obama paintings
that happened one time because I thought you would think it was sweet
You bring it up all the time, you act like it was a weird move on my part.
This flea market also has this one booth that's like this older little Mexican lady and she's
selling the only things that she sells are posters and t-shirts that are in support of
El Chapo, the like drug guy.
Oh that's so sick.
So I have a shirt and it's just like, and it's just all these shirts that say like,
like don't arrest El Chapo, he's like the richest guy in the world, it's awesome that
he's rich, he has this many cars, this many shoes, it's so fucking cool.
I want a shirt that says all of that.
Yeah.
The one I have says, says the number 107 billionaire in the world, El Chapo Guzman.
Sick.
Yeah.
That is so tight.
Do you think she like, um, she, she's doing that for the love of the game, or
do you think she like got into the trade somehow?
You know what, everybody loves him in, in Mexico.
Cause he would just like walk into it.
I bet.
Yeah.
He's like, he's like the biggest, everybody loves him.
I'm wondering if he's like funding this.
he's like sending her across America and she's just selling it to like North
Carolina. It worked on me, dude. I'm pro him all the way. Apparently he like goes
into very used to like walk into restaurants and he would just buy like
like four or five times a day by everybody in the restaurant their meal
and say give everybody money. I would I would support him if he's like what a
president should be. Like a president should just be a guy who gives people money and walks around being cool.
the president should buy me a big president should buy Patrick happy meal.
I agree the best part of free markets that they don't do in other places.
They should do is if like like like if I'm looking at like a table, it's all
DVDs and I like pick like I'm going to buy this transformers DVD or whatever
and the guy will be like if you buy all my DVDs, I'll give you a good price.
Yeah,
let me buy all the food in the grocery store for cheap
any store. I go in
looking at one thing. It's be like you want everything
I at the London area flea mart specifically because it's like they have
like a big food court - like it's like a bunch of like truly like taught like
food truck vendors and then they have like a bunch of like tents and shit so
they have like a food court and then like next to that food court is like a pond
where they put like a bunch of like fish yeah but like a bunch of fish but they
have like a on a boat on a boat in the middle of it they put a mannequin in
in like a full, like full army fatigues
and he's got a fishing pole
and the boat just moves around.
- Whoa.
- That's sick.
- With a mannequin with like a fishing pole.
It's so fucking sick.
- That's awesome.
- That's cool.
- I gotta fucking, I gotta go there
when I go there this weekend.
- I gotta go there when I go there.
- I gotta go there when I go there this weekend.
- Yeah, I'm going to New Hampshire.
- What are you gonna do in New Hampshire?
- I didn't go home for Easter, so.
- What?
- Who goes home for Easter?
That's not a normal thing.
How many movies are there about like, there's someone who's already Easter.
If you really believe in his word and power, Easter is always happening in your mind.
It's Orthodox Easter. It's Greek Orthodox Easter. I'm not Greek or anything.
I see, I see, I see.
I just didn't go home last weekend and my mom wants us home for Easter every year.
Why? I don't know. She fucking grew up Catholic. I don't know.
Wait, but then it's not Easter though, anymore.
It's Greek Orthodox Easter. Wait, was that her reasoning? That's not a joke you made? She actually is having you back for Greek Orthodox Easter?
No. That's a joke I made. Okay. It's a joke? Also, I don't think that's true. Yes it is. Look up in the iPhone
calendar. It's in there. They do it later than the normal? Did you check what holiday it was this weekend so you could have an excuse to go home?
Orthodox Church also celebrates Christmas a lot later. Really? They're like, this is the actual
calendar. And at least with like Christmas stuff I think they're kind of right.
Do they, one of those Orthodox religions or like versions of Christianity have
their own Pope and he's like way less popular. Yeah I think the Eastern
Orthodox. There's several, there's the whole history of Popes is super weird.
The Eastern Orthodox Pope like is, he looks exactly like Borat.
I don't know if you mean he's wearing a swimsuit.
Yeah, I don't know exactly what this is. I can't remember, but and I don't know
if it still exists, but for a long time there was also a guy called the
antipope. Yeah, yeah, there's like the pope and the antipope, which I think
it'd be so cool to be the and decides on the antipode.
No, it's like it was like some people were like no, the pope's the pope and
something like the anti popes the pope well then you like it's easy to figure
out who's the pope because he's the one that's not called the
yeah his name is the not he loses a lot of credibility right off the bat
changer start going I would have myself yeah the real pope yeah yeah I call
myself the fancy Pope yeah I want to go visit that I can say I think I would
call myself the illustrious
something new. It sounds like poop. It does sound like poop.
There's a dude he was like a historical reenactor in like the
Boston Common. They just have that he's had like guys that
fucking walk around there like yeah, they just have that now.
And his name was Jeremiah poop. No, it's spelled like no at the
in. P-O-O-P-E.
P-O-O-P-E?
Yeah.
That's such a good name.
He's like, "Well, it's pronounced different. It's Poo-oo-oop."
You're not fooling anyone, dude.
It's not poop, it's poopy.
I know your name's Poop.
It's also the perfect name for a historical reenactor. There's like a guy who's walking
around in old colonial gear, like, "My name's Jeremiah Poop!"
Jeremiah is also such a crazy first name.
Is the only place he could become a celebrity.
I don't I never saw him one of my friends
One of my friends my friends got like
No, he's like a real guy I like my friend like talked to him one time because like I don't remember
But he was like, yeah, I talked to a guy named Jeremiah poop the other day when I was like 16
I was like, what do you mean?
Jeremiah poop fucking prove this to me and he showed me is like Facebook. That's like a name in like a like a bad college sketch
Yeah, Jeremiah poop
I feel bad saying his name cuz it's just my a poop has a picture with Conan O'Brien. Oh
because it's a real guy who I don't know but I'm sure he's like yeah the nicest
people in the world I found is his Twitter account and the last tweets are
before he retweeted an Onion article twice that said that it's just a picture
of a toilet.
No way!
I don't want anyone to look this guy up.
I feel so bad just saying his name.
He only retweets the Onion, that's all he does.
Maybe he's awesome.
Who knows?
Yeah, he's cool.
I know a lot of Boston comedians did the historical reenactment of that.
Yeah, that's so, why?
Because it's, you know, it's so weird.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
He's doing tours, basically, but you get to have a cool outfit on.
Yeah.
That's the only reason we think it's funny is because they're wearing the outfit.
Yeah, I don't think I would think this guy was funny if he wasn't.
Yeah, if he was just a normal guy named Jeremiah Poop working in an office, that wouldn't be funny at all.
Yeah, that would not be funny.
I went on a historical Salem tour one time.
And my like the the dude who's like clearly like one of those like, you know, like I moved to Salem because I'm a Wiccan
Oh cool, and
He like in the middle of his fucking
Thing like the middle of the Tories just like and by the way, I am a brony
Like his fucking tour we're like he's like, yeah, so bear with me I do have ADHD
squirrel. He's walking around in a top hat in Salem. That's what happens to those kids
man they become Salem reenactors. Oh yeah yeah he's talking about like Giles
Corey with like the more weight shit and then I think he's peppered in that ADHD
joke again. That's cool man. I would love to be I want to be one of the double
Decker tour bus guys. Yeah. I feel like if last comic scene was still around, that tour
guy would get it. He'd go really really far. He would crush it. He would take the whole
thing home. He would take home the comic statue. They would build a statue of him like they
have with the Bee Witch Lady in Salem. They would put him there. Salem has a statue of
different witch on every corner yeah dog shit city yeah I don't really like
worst worst worst town in New England
it's way too scary
I hate it for no reason
it's not the ghost or anything
I'm sorry I've tried to like understand this you hate Salem because they respect women enough
to make statues of these fallen heroes
statues of evil women.
(laughter)
- Statues of like, yeah.
- It wasn't about misogyny, there were real witches.
(laughter)
- Yeah, you don't understand,
they had scary pointy hats and robes.
- Okay, now I understand.
- Oh, it's a misogynist witch hunt.
No, they're doing magic on me.
(laughter)
- They're flying on the brooms
when they should be using them for cleaning.
I'm sorry.
- Yeah.
- The house is dirty.
I think it's actually statue in Salem is cool though Margaret the Margaret
Thatcher
I'm only gonna say this once my entire life to you so listen up Patrick
It's Salem on the water yeah
No, is it sounding weird?
It's your cord, whatever, it's fine.
Basically doesn't matter at all.
I went one time and I didn't even do any scary stuff.
Yeah, we went there to go see our friend do a stand up set.
Oh, I've been there twice then.
I used to live real close to there.
I used to live in Revere for a little bit.
Seems like it sucks.
It's literally...
Are you talking about Salem?
Yeah, it's an adult field trip.
Yeah, yeah.
oh yeah there's also a place in sale and it's like like all you know you go see
the witches and stuff
then you can get the picture in front of bunghole liquors
i did take a picture of you
it's not a it's not a i will say is pretty
i want to know that there's there's like so many
cool like actual haunted houses in new england yeah i do know what i want to
bring out a little bit of a serious issue of the go is in the amityville
house in new england
I think it's upstate New York. Is it? Yeah. I think it might be. I'm pretty sure it's upstate
New York. Lizzie Borden house is in New England. Is that the Winchester house in New England?
No, that's also in upstate New York. Really? Oh my god. Okay, they're all there then. That's
a scary place. Upstate New York haunted as hell. A lot of people think that the World Trade Center
in Manhattan. It's actually the same. It's in Albany.
Jaws. Jaws is in New England though. And he's scary as hell.
Jaws? The shark?
Yeah, the shark.
Did he haunt a house?
Yeah, he haunted the beach.
Holy shit.
Oh shit, this beach is haunted by ghost sharks.
He haunted the memories of the men who survived the fateful summer.
Oh fuck, my beach is haunted with sharks.
Oh shit. Oh god.
It would be impossible to tell if a ghost shark or a regular shark was attacking people.
That's true!
Oh shit!
So you can, like, yeah, anything that is a ghost that's not a human, how do you even
know if it's a ghost or not?
Oh my god.
We might be haunted by bugs here.
This would be like underwater, especially if people are being eaten, you know?
Like if you like find half of their body or something.
That's true!
Yeah.
Then if you get half of your body eaten, is there like half of a ghost out there?
You could tell if you find half a body and they're and there's a full ghost
who's half hungry.
They look really scared.
It's probably a ghost shark.
Ghosts by getting eaten all the way.
That's not the rule.
Like really, really scared.
If they peed themselves.
Yeah.
If you find half a body with teeth marks and they're as pale as a sheet,
that was a ghost shark.
And they kind of got like George from Seinfeld face going on.
That was probably a ghost shark.
Have you guys ever been viciously attacked by a shark?
Not yet.
No.
A couple times.
One time I got attacked by a bunch of jellyfish.
Really?
What do you mean they attacked you?
Don't they just float?
Wow!
Jellyfish attacked me!
Okay, so I was in like open water and before the keys.
They intentionally swam and they attacked me.
And I was like diving down and I was like 17 and as I was coming back up what had been
like totally clear was now just like what looked like a mile of jellyfish.
Whoa.
So like I'd only, I wasn't like scuba and so I was only down for a second,
you know? So I had to go through like, like, like, like 10 feet of jellyfish.
Oh my God.
I was okay. It actually wasn't the end of the world, but like it was, it was,
yeah, that's basically a shark when you think about it.
It's also, it's funny that that is an attack. They just,
they occupy your air.
- Exactly.
- I'm taking it over.
- Sorry, sorry, sorry.
- When you said attack, I was thinking like a
SpongeBob jellyfish came up and stuck his tentacle out at you
and stung you.
And also when you got electrocuted, you saw your bones.
- Yeah.
- You turned blue and saw your bones.
- That'd be cool, that'd be cool.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, well actually the problem is I got stung so much
that they stung my swimsuit off
and I was on a Boy Scout trip.
- Oh my God.
so all the Scoutmasters saw my minor dick and that is why they all went to jail.
A lot of people think that they're pedophiles. They weren't. They just happened to see my
penis and then immediately went to jail. So the jellyfish, mostly they attacked your Scoutmasters,
not even really you. I'm sure those Scoutmasters are in jail to this day.
There's just a guy like in a boat far away, he's like, "My jellyfish plan worked!"
evil scoutmaster
he will see he sounds evil he sounds like the evil one
well that's not necessary perception i mean he's attacking evil
describing right now is eerily similar to what's happening to transfer
there's a guy on a boat
I would say yeah, essentially, there's a man on a boat trying to make it look like trans women are pedophiles
through any means necessary and then saying "Aha!"
"I sniped the W.O. off that bathroom sign!"
"Now they're gonna get in trouble!"
"I'm Steven!"
"Don't give that to me."
Steven Universe!
Yeah, that's why I never got that show.
Like, a lot of people like that show when he does that stuff.
Yeah, it's really fucked up.
Yeah, it's not cool.
People always think, for some reason, they think like Steven Universe is a
Tenderware show, even though it's a show about an eleven year old boy trying to
get his many trades women arrested.
And he looks into the camera and announces it like jackass every time.
He's doing a prank.
Hi, I'm Steven Universe and this is Getting Grace Arrested.
Burn her now.
Oh man.
Did they even put gay people in that show or was it just because it looked gay?
They did put like I'm like okay, Steven Universe is like an interesting show because like a lot of people
Prescribe it as this like super tender queer syrupy show and it like kind of was at the beginning
But also it was made for kids, you know, but there is like there is gay shit
There's a gay like wedding and a show for kids
The weird thing about the show is the last season of it is called Steven Universe future
And it jumps like a few years into the future and it's all about like how Steven has like PTSD from saving the universe essentially now
He's going
He's like kind of a piece of shit in it
And so all these tender queer fans hated it because they were like, what do you mean?
You have a care like the main character like isn't just like a good boy
That's weird. I really like how it ended but like a lot of the big fans were like it's like the same
Like people like a lot of like these dumb queers like act like
Steven universe and shit like that is there like
Examples of like what good media is that teaches kids and teaches people how to act yeah
And then this show ended with like Steven like being a piece of shit kind of and they were not and they were like
Yeah, I'll be pretty pissed off if Spongebob started acting like
it
it's nice to his friends squidward inmates and i had a very for mister crabs
very hard to get a crappy patio he's a best-fried cook in the in all but he is
yeah but he's never recognized as privileged
it's true shit I never thought of SpongeBob like that I'm learning it is
funny that like there of all the cartoons somehow SpongeBob is the one
that has the most like five-hour YouTube videos about it oh yeah they're not
about like the politics of it at all it's just like SpongeBob is actually a
sociopath yeah yeah and then you watch you're like you're spitting right now
yeah that's true boys on one not tree Squidward with respect actually low-key
mean to him it makes no sense there's this guy my partner went to high school
with who who makes us like make spongebob edits but they're not they're
not like why Spongebob has like AIDS or whatever. That's a good one though. That was heartbreaking.
Six hour video. They're just like these weird like psychedelic edits that people really like.
And mishmashes. And we were at their friend's place, like their other high school friend's
place and they put on a video from him. And I was like oh it's so cool that he's doing
this now, you know? He was kind of a weirdo in high school and whatnot. And then two weeks
later this guy messages M's friend and is like, "Hey, I need to tell you something about
myself and I'm trying to work through it and it's been really difficult." And so Swaya
thought that, "Oh, he's coming out to me. We haven't really talked since high school,
but I guess maybe he just needs someone, you know? And that's totally cool." And she's
what's up and what he was coming out as was attracted to pregnant women.
Woah!
Oh my god!
That is awesome!
Hell yeah dude!
That's so sick!
So pleasant to meet you.
Are you supposed to come out for that?
Yes!
Mom, Dad.
You are in the closet if you are not told people about that.
Just taking your mom and dad out to like a dinner at the age of 28.
It's just something I've like always known about myself since I was like really young and I don't know.
You know, it's currently...
I like when a woman blows up like a balloon.
Your mom is like, "We know honey. We always knew."
We always knew baby.
sad that people in that community can't get married. The kid
starts bringing home exclusively pregnant.
He sends fire a photo of him with a pregnant chick. It's like,
"Yeah, I just visited this girl in Ohio."
(laughing)
- Whoa.
- So he not only was coming out,
he was that way, I don't know, pregnant.
(laughing)
- That's actually, it's cool that you can,
if you're into pregnant women and you're like a single guy,
you have like a cap on how much,
how like long you can like somebody.
Where it's like, as soon as they have the baby,
you're like, "Oh yeah, I'll just fucking."
- That's a rom-com.
- Just fine.
(laughing)
- Yes, yes, yes.
It's like we only have two more weeks.
I will find you disgusting as every other normal woman in the
world.
There's like a really tragic scene where he's giving birth and
he's like sobbing.
Yeah, he's not. Oh, God.
That's the resolution.
With a bowling ball like Indiana Jones.
The movie called the plug. This girl like because she knows that
Her BF will like leave her when she has the kid like buys like just like one of those big old timey bathtub plugs
And she just keeps getting bigger and bigger
That's how I want that I wish I could have just spent 18 years me too. Oh, man you get so much done in there
here
you know that they sell those like fake pregnant suits on amazon we should get
them
i could write that off as a business expense
i'm gonna get one of those i'm not joking i'm gonna get a fake pregnant suit
and wear it around
a big pregnancy suit just like
Oh, I'm gonna wear it to the bar and like
Don't
Don't buy one of those yourselves yourself because me and Camille might have already
My god
with the pregnancy suit. I'm gonna wear it to the bar and get tainted. I want a whiskey neep.
Can I get a gin and tonic for the little one?
We're like wearing it. I'm drinking for two tonight. Wearing like the biggest one that
makes it look like you're nine months pregnant and then pretending you get a phone call and
you're like oh my god I'm pregnant. I would try to do that prank but I would accidentally put the
suit on backwards. Yeah, I probably would have a sumo suit.
I'm pregnant.
Like what?
Why do you have a
no, I know I know you're not pregnant, but I'm not gonna serve
you because your fat is full.
Call it the bar. You're like we the abortion appointment is back
on. Okay,
swag. I have to go right now.
You're totally tanked and
Somebody on the jukebox weighs that fucking it's a
Yeah, you're running out you're running out of the bar you think it's a push door you just run
Like 10 a.m. In the morning full pregnancy suit you order your first drink when you time it just right
So just as you're about to take a sip on the screen CNN reports that the Supreme
gorgeous struck down rovers well I guess I'm doing this myself or just like going
to the bathroom and throw away and then come back down. Somebody clogged the toilet.
I must have eaten four meatballs and not digested them.
(laughing)
- Four bloody meatballs.
- Four disgusting bloody meatballs.
And put them directly in your toilet.
- Do you think for people who are like
pregnancy fetish guys, do you think like,
like how much, how big of like a watershed moment
was Octomom?
- Hmm, no, no, no.
I think pregnant women are hot, Octomom's too much.
- You think pregnant women are hot?
yeah okay pregnant women are hot all right there they look like a balloon
there's kids in there dude
heard that song pregnant pussy and something changed in him no that song is
disgusting they're mad disrespectful actually really disrespectful okay well
it's good it's good that you draw a line so I think I just had a pregnant
teacher when I was a kid and I something about that I was like cool mrs. Sullivan
And then she wasn't pregnant and I was like, I don't care about you anymore.
Whoa. Wow.
Wow. Wow.
This is a big unlock on the episode.
It's a premium.
That's true. You gotta pay a premium for this.
I'll make it the teaser.
The teaser for the episode I'll be like, yeah and I, and then I'll do like, you have to listen to hear what I'm going to say.
And it's weird because like, it wasn't until she had the baby that she even noticed you.
I was nine years old. I liked her because she listened to rock music. It was like,
that's always the first time you had a teacher where they were like, not like an old lady.
And you're like, Oh, well, it was like an assistant teacher at my school, who would like wear her son's
like nine inch nail shirts on like casual Fridays and shit. So I was like, Oh my god,
damn that's how old is her son like five
yeah that's what they're really small kids for like yeah
yeah so hot no she i i the that that lady mrs elvin i she drove me on a on a field trip one
time she drove you crazy the bus we had a really small bus for the school bus yeah i was it was
there's too many kids you couldn't fit in the bus i was yeah it was huge i was in this big as a room
but I it was me and like one other kid and she played a paralyzer by finger
eleven. I was like I think she's going to fuck us.
I am going to get laid on this on this field trip.
She's pregnant and I got her pregnant
just the truth
dude yeah that baby was probably going to be so young because it was you were
so young. I know it was half half mom half young yeah, so it ended up
Yeah, it ended up being a baby.
Nah, I could have impregnated a woman if I even wanted to at the time.
I didn't have a job.
I didn't even have fucking cum at the time.
I had nothing. I was shooting blanks.
Really?
Yeah, dude.
At nine?
At nine, yeah.
What were you-- you were doing meeting nuts at nine years old?
No way.
I was-- I was--
Creamy mayo?
I was blasted.
No. No chance.
I was cumming in the bathtub and it was just making bubbles.
it was all that was happening at the time. Yeah, I was like nine like pixie
dust when I was nine and I first learned about that and I was like, okay, I
guess I have to try that because I'm growing up and it like I think I was at
it for like an hour and then I peed and there's foam and I was like that must
be my sperm.
That must be it. That's gotta be my sperm. That must be my sperm. My sperms
must be those bubbles. Oh and then and then like I think I also breathing in
pee. I saw there's like a you know when like a hair gets in a toilet and like it
knows like that like if there's like a hair in the toilet and it has like that
reflection it kind of makes it look like a like a sperm. I saw that and I was like
that's the biggest sperm you've ever seen.
Wait, the biggest sperm you've ever seen, it's the first sperm.
And even then you're like that's too big.
That's way too big.
It's too huge.
That's crazy.
I must have the biggest sperm of all time.
It'd be so cool if sperm was big and it hurt to come out.
Yeah, if you saw it.
You got one.
Like little bugs.
You shot one nasty butt.
One nasty tadpole at your thing.
Now that's a rom-com.
Falling in love with your own sperm.
Oh my god.
It took me like a while.
I feel like all of my friends
have started coming
Before me like like we like I was masturbating but just nothing like I was not coming
Yeah, and so like by the time I think I was like 13 when that happened and once that finally happened like I was like
Just I had a gooey gooey hand as I was like a weepy
like in the computer room just like fucking which was like half of my mom's
room.
Covered in coffee in front of the computer.
It is my sweeper open on this.
All right, you guys are you guys going on tour?
We're going on tour.
Where can people find all the when in a few weeks, because this will come out in
a few weeks. How many weeks this will come out on May 7th. Oh cool. So the
First date of our tour is one day before that.
But the rest of our dates are, we're in Seattle on May 21st.
- No, no, no, no, we're in Portland on May 21st,
Seattle on May 22nd, New York on the 25th,
and then San Francisco on June 1st.
- And you can find all of those tickets
at girlcotshow.com.
- Whoa.
- Nice.
- We gotta rehearse.
- That's right, we bought the website.
Thank you all for coming on.
Thank you for having us.
Anything else you want to say about getting hit in the head?
I just want to say, can I say one last thing?
Sorry, I just want to say I accept you for your attraction to pregnant women and I hope
that it becomes legal.
I hope so.
We've been fighting the good fight for many, many years.
I just want to say the exact opposite.
You don't support me?
No.
I'll be in the middle.
It's like my version, you have skateboarding, I have jacking off to millions of pregnant
women every day.
I just want to say that I think as long as men are punching women in the head at bars,
that none of these men should be getting any women pregnant.
Dang!
Oh!
Feminism!
Yeah, sorry.
Just for my thing.
Oh!
Bye!