come back and make a bet
and receive a bite
you have a plan to change style
uh... things that i've done it he you're you're seeing you're going to be
he's literally seeing your is a total sheen
you're seeing but instead of
all that's already are all your your ass motherfucker
No, you're Carl and Shane. Do you want to see my Godzilla shirt? You are Carl. He's Shane
and Carl. He's on both. Yeah, he is. I'm Jimmy Neutron and you're the dog. What? I think
I'm the-- And you're Carl, Shane, and all the girls. What's the girl's name? Cindy Vortex.
No, the black girl. Libby. Libby. I'm Libby. Libby Wabi. Yeah. I'm a mixture of the two
Remember when they go to Egypt in that one episode and they find and they're
like that the mummies think you're Cleopatra?
Mm-hmm yeah.
That show was good.
It was awesome dude.
Yeah that's one of those shows too where you go back and you watch it and it's
like the animation has progressed so much since it came out.
This is like scary.
It's terrifying.
It's like hoodwinked.
Yeah it looks like a demo of like what anime like before animation was they
made movies of like this could be this could be this is what this is what we
could do with the computer you know those those videos where it's like a ball that
fights a square yeah yeah and they're like this is gonna be something pretty
soon it looks like a game that you have to play with a control switch yeah it's
a game that you play with a light switch is what it looks yeah mm-hmm there's
only on and off yeah but damn was it a good show the writing the characters they
had a lot of music into the candy bar and the movie there's a soda the movie
came before the show did you guys know yeah I know yeah I learned I found that
out like we're gonna I've not like recently but like years yeah like I've
been watching the show took me a long time that's open there's a lot of echo
that's really not that much well but it is because I want to put on the on-air
sign anyway that's true we do have an on-air sign now do you guys the movie
also has the greatest concept for a movie ever yeah parents always I had that
one on DVD I watched that movie so many times I saw it in theaters I saw I think
it does have a little bit of a cop-out though which is like when your parents
go away you might get a tummy ache that's fucking bullshit ultra was the
coolest thing ever dude if I had a the chicken yeah poultry
remember they're all eggs yeah mm-hmm they're green eggs where's the ham
where the ham at soos soos where's my ham yeah
soos where's my ham yeah with snitched in
cushion snitched in snitched in grincher soos where's my ham
sometimes i'm just i'm just perfect just absolutely
Steph Curry long bomb half court.
- Yup.
- And that was one of them, dude.
- Pretty tired today.
I've been not sleeping good again.
- Me too.
- Yeah.
- I don't know what it is.
- You know what you need to stop doing?
Tossing and turning.
- That's true, yeah.
- You should not.
- Another thing to avoid is waking up
in the middle of the night.
That also will keep get you tired.
- I did go to bed early last night and woke up
and then I just stayed up until I was sleepy again.
And that was at four.
when I went sleepy again.
- You need to knock yourself out with a big bone.
- I have melatonin.
I should start running into walls.
- You should get one of those--
- I should get a low pole.
- Yeah, with your bed right underneath it.
- So when I wake up I just hit the fucking--
- Well no, you run into it to go to sleep.
- Oh dude, it's so, like literally yesterday,
or two days ago, Joe walked into that fucking pole
right there that you see that that one that like curves down that makes sense
Joe it's so fun Joe cannot go on this side of the no he's of course he's a big
big freak yeah he's banished mm-hmm he's for what he did for it's for what you
did he's banned all right we'll take it let's not let's not relitigate yeah
double jeopardy if we try to try him for it again yeah yeah so he's already been
exonerated no no guilty he's found guilty we could find him guilty again yeah
they basically you guys branded dassy'd me and which ones oh that's the the
stupid one from yeah the one who wanted to watch WrestleMania mmm you cut you're
right that is kind of what we did to you yep we took advantage of your learning
disability yeah we made you a pariah yeah an unnecessary pariah can I go to
the X Games now awesome yeah okay I did it can I watch WrestleMania yeah sure
so sick yeah I had his priorities straight he just yeah he just wanted to
go home and see what the fuck didn't they use him a murdering a woman and
putting her body in a car or something what is that movie called making a
murderer that really had dude that was like the worst cultural phenomenon
because it was like the fucking this one was it with that or Tiger King which one
was worse you think Oh Tiger King obviously Tiger Kings way worse but like
that was like I didn't watch making a murderer but Tiger King was annoying but
it was like fun to make a murder was so boring it was so boring in every episode
it was like well did he do it he did it but in the next episode he doesn't but
in this one yeah does the same thing with six fucking episodes of that true
crime so cry it's all it's all annoying cereal is so fucking annoying the this
bitch Sandra Koenig she's like doing Sarah Sarah what Koenig be careful that's
her name dude someone could chop that I'm gonna chop you someone could chop
that last to make it say yeah K Sandra that'd be scary yeah it's too cool
name true crime is like what like people you know when people like complain about
about like Martin Scorsese and they're like,
oh, he only makes the same movie over and over.
Like true crime is the actual thing of that,
where it's like every true crime thing
is literally exactly the same.
- The truth is, yeah, it's like,
honey, you shouldn't have gotten murdered.
- Yeah.
- It's like--
- The truth is that crime is pretty boring.
- Yeah.
- We're almost, the only cool murder--
- That's the thing, I always,
so I would listen to like,
listen to like a few true crime things before,
or like watch them, and it's always like,
the thing about it is like,
when you watch a TV show, you're like,
I want a cool like climax and like really like I want something awesome to have
yeah and the end is always like and then they found out it was the guy they
thought it was all along he went to jail that's that's the that and then it's
like oh like this I'm always this case remained open because the cops were fat
and stupid they never knew they never figured out who it was but it's always
like I want to watch it and I wanted to be like it like it was actually his
twin brother all along and there was an alien that's why you guys seen the jinx
no I still have the only good true crime thing yeah that one it's this guy this
like five foot I keep following the Herman Miller I'm not going to it's like
it's like this five foot tall like Robert I know of Robert and he's just
he's just like moving through life murdering people and then all the cops
are like so stupid like there's a he fully got away with a murder in Texas
because he dressed up as a woman and came back and pretended to be like oh
like a woman who lived next door instead of himself yeah, and he was like and
the cops like yeah, my man, she was not the not the most beautiful lady I ever
seen, but yeah, I read this book that was like about like this guy who's like
the conspiracy theorist who believed that, like all serial killers are like
like primed by the CIA or whatever and they're like the cops are all like like
trained to like let them go and like let them do their thing and it's always
like it's always like he was able to kill like ten people before they caught
them, because they were like the cops were so devilishly clever to like to
fight to accuse people that weren't him. It's like they're all just like really
stupid, yeah, and Robert Durst is literally like he's so he's so like
bad and like self incriminating the entire time. He keeps being like well,
and then I killed I mean I didn't kill yeah like in the interview and then the
show ends with him. He leaves his hot mic on and he goes to the bathroom. He
is peeing and he just goes like I killed every last one of them yeah he's like
like every true crime thing ends like that what's the um that the that's the
only one that is like that no no the arrow the arrow Morris one or yeah yeah
the fucking uh fucking thin line of something or then blue line line yeah
the thin line is yeah yeah that one the old one is being like well what do you
think I did like yeah the same thing yeah like the good ones and with the killer
just being like yeah there's something what yeah there's something to me so
specifically cool about Robert Durst because he like they asked him to do
this interview like 15 different times over like 10 years and he just kept
doing it and coming in and just being like well if I did kill him I chopped
his legs up and put him in a trash bag yeah and then he just keep he just has
no idea when to stop because he just thought it was cool he's in a movie yeah
which I feel like is that's that's like what if you're a serial killer that's
like probably what you well you just jealous of his brother Fred yeah yeah on
mainstream success you know if you watch a movie actually is jealous of his
brother his name is not Fred though oh really yep he's jealous his brother took
over the family company what's in he comes from money right yeah like billion
trillion zillion dollars Wow no way he wasn't CIA or something this guy like
like the old true no this guy was a this guy yeah the MK ultra thing is just
because every serial killer was like abused by their parents as a kid I like
a ultra and that's what I'm K ultra is is basically like being abused like
you're a child let me kind this ultra Robert Durst mom jumped off of their
house when he was a kid and he watched it and he was like yeah that make me go
crazy. That's literally like always what it is. It's just like just chill out,
relax. Why are you being so fucking weird about your dead mom? It's so funny
that that like one of the like warning signs of like a psychopath or a serial
killer is wetting the bed. I know I feel like I feel like the actual the thing
that makes them psychopaths is that people make fun of the people say it's a
warning. So I also feel like it wouldn't it wouldn't make you a serial killer at
if nobody talked about it.
- I also, I always--
- If everyone is just cool about you
being a little kid wetting the bed,
like if everyone's like, "No, it's okay,"
but everyone's like, "Oh, look at this
"fucking little pee hound, dude."
- I always liked that one of the warning signs
is like, that they write down is like,
yeah, torturing small animals.
- Yeah, that's a warning sign for any--
- Yeah, you're like going to WebMD,
you're like, "All right, my son is torturing small animals,
"let's see what this could be."
Oh no, it's actually really bad.
- Ah, crap, you're grounded!
found it might be a psychopath yeah. Well at least he's not peeing the bed yeah
he's
wetting the bed. God he's not one of the other thing that bad guys the bed arson
and torturing small animals. Yeah, my brother I've did two three of those
things. My brother's friend used to put he's to put lizards on the end of his BB
gun and press the trigger. Yeah, you told me about that before. One of the other
funny things about like cops like failing to catch serial killers is like a lot of
they'll like they'll get they'll like go to the serial killers house or like the
place where they like bury the but like like they'll go into a guy's house who
has like just a room in his house that literally just has like 20 dead people
in it and just like you know smells yeah like 20 dead people and cops go in there
and they're like oh it smells normal to me in here so my house smells.
Can't be anything wrong in here.
Gee what's that smell? It's chili.
Been cooking chili for about-
That literally happened with like like uh
that happened with so many people like they just go into their house and
like well it's all normal here. Yeah. The door with the lock. People six doors down
are complaining about the smell. Yeah. The cops are walking in and they're like, nah just smells like the bathroom.
Yeah, it smells like my house. It smells like my wife's room. Yeah. It's my wife's room.
She has her own room. That's cool dude. I wish I had enough money to give my wife
her own room. Yeah. Kick her out dude. Give her a bunk bed. Mm-hmm. Yeah. Yeah.
So she can sleep with her with her friends on the bottom bunk. Exactly yeah.
and then but me my wife's fantasy but then I get the was cuz she's a girl she
never had a bunk bed yeah it's true girls have you ever met a girl at a bunk bed
no my sister at a same node no that doesn't count that you're bunking with
yourself you're bunking with the homework version I had a I know it's like racing
a ghost in Mario you ever have a triple bunk bed what the fuck kind of what are
you what the hell are you talking about I triple bunk bed you did not you owed you
at a space camp - where you know middle I was at the top you did not have a
- I don't deserve that. - I did.
- Oh, and my sister, yeah, my sister slept on the--
- Oh, my sister had a quadruple bunk bed.
- No, my sister-- - Oh, and my dad
had a septuple bunk bed.
- Shut up, dude. - So when I was like four,
my sister slept on the top bunk,
my older brother slept on the bottom bunk,
and then me and my younger brother
had like two beds on the side.
- This is a false memory.
- No, it's not. - This is a--
- No, it's not, 'cause my sister broke my arm.
- This is a Dianetics false memory.
- My sister broke my arm when I was--
- Triple bunk bed. - You guys had like
rotating beds on like a track,
like the doors in Monsters Inc.
- No, I had triple bunk beds.
I had triple bunk beds.
I had Yu-Gi-Oh sheets, I was on the top bunk.
My little brother was in the middle bunk.
He had Spiderman sheets and my older brother
had SpongeBob sheets. - Did you like Yu-Gi-Oh
as a kid?
- I did, I was Yami Yu-Gi for Halloween when I was six.
- Really, wait, do you have a picture?
- Nah, I don't have a picture of it, but I had--
- Can you ask your mom for a picture of that?
- There might be a picture.
My Aunt Maureen-- - I need to see that picture
if it exists. - Took a shit ton of pictures.
But when I was four, my sister, my cousin Ryan
was babysitting us and we were playing,
like we're playing some game and my sister kicked me off the top like I was
like holding on to the like the ladder that goes up and my sister kicked me off
and I fell down. How did you have ceilings high enough for three? Did you live in some kind of great hall?
They lived in a cathedral. No, the ceilings weren't, they were just tall enough.
I would wake up and hit my head on the fucking ceiling all the time. They lived in a cathedral with a giant spider-man mural on the ceiling.
I'll call my mom right now, I'll ask her about the triple bunk beds. She's just gonna lie to you
like she lied to you and you were a kid no dude I had triple bunk beds dude I
just this is impossible for my head triple bunk you have a photo no your
parents never thought to take a photo of your your triple bunk bed the only
triple bunk yeah exist there's no dude it was a wooden it was a wooden triple
bunk bed a wooden triple getting less believable by the second we would like
draw on the fucking. It was made out of magical you. And it was made out of paper too so we
could draw on it. And it had a chalkboard paint on it. And it tasted like every flavor. It
had a candy cane leg. A candy cane leg? And the third top bunk floated above the other
ones. Yeah it was actually completely magnetic. That's how they. Yeah it had triple bunk beds.
You didn't have triple bunk beds. I did. I had a pet cheetah. There wasn't enough room
in our house. My brother was actually a monkey. Yeah, I had laser shoes. Mm-hmm.
My sister had her own room and then we had a triple bunk bed that stretched
across multiple rooms. I didn't age 65. I had a Murphy bunk bed. It was just tall enough that like it
could fit in the room but like not tall enough. So when I was like sometimes I'd get up in
the morning just fucking hit my head on that. I think that explains. I think that's
why I just can't fucking think at all. That's probably why you think you have a
triple bunk bed, it's because you were on the triple bunk bed and you hit your head so many times.
Dude, I had triple bunk beds. You didn't have triple bunk beds. Yeah, I did. You might have had three sets of
bunk beds. No. I believe that before I believe that you had a three-story bunk bed.
I had a three-story bunk bed. You did not have a three-story bunk bed. Look up triple bunk beds right now.
I don't even want to know if it's real. It's a real thing. I also know that it
wasn't real whenever you were a kid. No, it's sounds like a new. Yeah, that
took that takes a while to invent. Yeah, that sounds like a SkyMall kind of
invention. Yeah, that's a shark tank thing. That sounds like a Skynet kind of invention. Yeah, exactly.
Whatever it is, it's also morally wrong. Yeah, definitely.
You calling mommy? Yep. Go crying to mommy. Hey, I had triple bunk beds as a kid, right?
Yes you did. Bullshit! Liar! You used to... You'd call it all over them, you destroyed them, and you used to bang your head off the top.
I told you! I fucking told you guys! You think you're the only one that can make a call, huh?
Amanda pushed you off, you were climbing up to the top, and Amanda kicked you in the face, and you went straight home.
Alright, let's talk on the phone.
mm-hmm all right I think she's lying she's not telling the truth I love you
I love you so I love you so let's ask let's ask chat and count emoji phone how
about that two bunk beds - how many bunk beds did Patrick have okay so I had two
triple bunk beds how many bunk beds did he not have chat and count he did not
not have three. It's not true. He did not have three. My mom just confirmed it.
How many inches long is his penis? One. That's right. That's right. Damn. And how
old am I? Nine. I'm nine years old. So guess who just won? I had triple bunk
beds. My mom just confirmed it. You think I came in today, I planned that? You think
I texted my mom earlier? I think you were sitting around, you were like, I'm
to have the best thing ever for the podcast. I'm gonna make it funny that
you called your mom and she said literally every exact thing that you
said without being prompted. It's like she brainwashed you into things like
she might be the original the original every morning when you're a kid you
would wake up and she would like swing like a watch in front of your face like
him knows to be like you have triple bunk beds. You got kicked off the top.
You destroyed the sheets. You used to bonk your head on the sheets. That's what
She said she said you destroyed the she said you come to pooped all over the
sheets.
No, she did say you destroyed the sheets. We should have. We should have probed
that. She didn't say I just said I destroyed the bed. She said you told him
sheets up. I did not. She said you tell it up. Nope. Call her again. Ask her if
you tell him up. I'm not. No say mom calling her again. My charity likes
charity likes that she got to be on the episode technically too much. Yeah. Yeah.
I don't like that you she knows she has to pay us yeah yeah mom you have to pay
us right now mm-hmm we have all our guests pay us yeah yeah yeah it's
because it's a thing about the show we're giving them exposure of course
yeah it's yeah exactly you they need to compensate us for our same it's the same
as a bringer show yeah I mean we have to deal with them basically it's like
they're paying us a babysitting guy I fucking hate it when we have a guest on
me too me too they're always like yeah no I have something to plug it in shut up
up dude I don't think I give a fuck about your stupid show that's right Gavin
Matt's fuck you Gavin coming on your plug your stand up four months ago yep
who else who else Eric Eric no that was he was a vampire oh right
Dracula no we never had ever had Eric on yeah I mean I was thinking about nothing
is what I was thinking. And Brandon and Jack. Fucking fuck you bitches. We went on their
show. No they came on our, oh wait I don't remember. I think we just had Brandon on.
Fuck you Brandon and Dracula. Fuck both of you assholes. Felix. Felix, bitch. Fuck you. Alex
and Joe, fuck my ass fucker. Fart my face. Sarah. Sarah. Fart in my face. Sarah.
I can fuck you stupid ass yeah yeah Santa Santa bitch-ass let me suck your dick
let me suck your penis Santa suck your dick by me
chat and count emoji phones my shit you Patrick's mom I love you Patrick's mom I
love you you miss you we've also had my dad on - oh yeah yeah remember that one
time. Yeah, I had your dad on. I wore him like a mask. Who else did we have on? Jesse? I
had his balls, I had his balls like down my throat. Like a xenomorph tongue. It was really
awesome. I agree with both of what you're saying. Yeah, I had your dad's nipples were
like, they were poking into my, they were so hard. I didn't even listen to the first
first part of this. I was so hard when he was stuck on my face. He's this big.
He's about the size of a hand. My dad is a face hugger for alien and he's in his
nipples were like going into my pupils, like penetrating the like the like
watery kind of skin thing and they were and it was really I was seeing inside
and I was looking at his milk.
My dad has milk.
My dad does have milk.
Checking out all the milk.
Does have milk.
would be kind of funny to see your dad milk it up. It would be funny to see
what if you were like out drinking with your dad and he got a little too drunk
and isn't
he pulls his shirt up. He's like check this out. I've been doing this lately.
No, no, we see it. We see it just like a leak. We just see like some kind of
like stain on both his nipples. What if he's wearing? I gotta go pump
ah shit. I gotta fuck. I gotta pump. He's wearing like a dress shirt. Why
are you making my dad? It's Peter Griffin and it's he does sound like
it starts filling up his breast pocket
like a little cup yeah that'd be awesome dude i would love to make a shirt that
does that i've been trying to i've been trying to breastfeed phil yeah don't
feed phil remember that episode of evil of bam good episode there's also somebody
feed phil yeah the the show about the the annoying guy who the annoying larry
David of that's so Raymond.
- It's so funny to be-- - That's so Raymond.
- Yeah, it's so funny to be the Larry David
of everybody loves Raymond.
- It's just like a completely autistic guy.
- Yeah. - Who loves food.
- Oh dude, that's awesome.
- Yeah, he's cool, dude.
- That's why all the-- - And he just like,
looks like somebody will be speaking Bosnian to him
and feeding him a bug, and he'll be like,
"Oh, really, oh, this looks great!"
And he'll take a big bite and then start crying
about how like touched he is.
- Yeah.
- That they get, let him like share his worm.
- That is funny that every episode of
Everybody Loves Raymond is about food
now that I think about it.
- And Phil.
- Debra, my lasagna!
I need you to feed me lasagna right now!
- I, I, isn't that like--
- My stomach hurts from eating too much cow chocula!
I need you to rub my belly, Debra!
- Didn't he make so much--
- He's a gainer.
- Yeah.
- Oh, he is.
Everybody loves gainers.
seats rate that'd be a better
braving them computer community
movement
who do you feel popsicle
popsicle
that i think that really fat but you get what your popsicle
the three-hour wait it's weird
he's like his mouth is no proposal
the
from all the mixed colors of all the popsicles.
He's got frostbite on his tongue.
Yeah, yeah.
Have you guys seen that video of that guy with the frostbite fingers?
And he's like doing this against an elevator door?
No.
I saw there's a...
So cool.
They're just like rocks.
I saw a guy with frostbite in his foot.
Like somebody is hitting it with a chimney spoke or chimney stick.
You know the thing?
Does it shatter?
No, it goes right through.
Damn.
Yeah, it goes right through and he starts screaming.
It's cool, dude.
or he pretends to start screaming so he doesn't he doesn't hear it at all yeah
his butler like stabs it through his foot okay this is i don't know what this is mr deans
oh yeah his butler john determine
yeah it's been since i've seen mr i can't believe we're all in new hampshire movie
We're almost 30 minutes in and nobody, we're not going to talk about the leprechaun in the room.
Wow, me?
It's St. Patrick's Day.
It's true.
Well, it's not going to be St. Patrick's Day when this comes out, so I didn't think it was important.
But it's St. Patrick's Day.
It's St. Patrick's Day.
Is he wearing green?
Can I see your shirt really quick?
What's green?
My pants.
I don't know.
Those are green.
Those are olive.
I don't know.
I got green on.
He's wearing green.
Not all green.
He's got no green.
What do you have no green on?
That's not green.
How is this not green?
Dude, the pinch...
It's not green.
Let the pinch fest begin.
The pinch fest is not...
Dude, I will literally get the pinch cops involved.
This is green.
Nope.
The pinch cops...
You don't get to...
You have put a thing of scotch tape on your shirt.
That doesn't count.
He...
Oh, dammit.
He's halfway down the office already.
He's gone.
Now we can talk about the real issues.
Yep.
That's right.
(howling)
- Dude, having two mics is honestly pretty sick.
Is this fucking up the audio at all?
- Why would it, no.
It's just gonna sound weird.
- It's gonna sound weird?
- It's not gonna, yeah. - That's fine.
(laughing)
He's wearing one green, green glove that he, that...
(laughter)
Can you move your hand in that?
Yeah, it doesn't look like you can move,
that glove is too small.
That glove is for...
It looks like a prosthetic hand.
That glove is like, Alex and Joe bought those.
They, we've already established, they have huge hands.
That is not gonna, let me see it.
No.
(laughter)
I like it now.
Can you make a fist?
Oh, dude, you can't even...
- I can try it, yeah.
- Yeah, you're faking it.
- Dude, that...
(laughing)
- It looks so funny, dude.
Yeah, but I'm wearing green now.
- That's true.
- Can we all admit that this is green?
- At least I got one pinch in.
It wasn't even a good pinch, though.
- It's true.
- And now I have a beautiful hand.
- Oh my God, dude, that looks so weird.
- It looks crazy.
- Wait, tuck it under the thing.
- You're Dr. Strangelove.
- Yeah, 'cause that looks like,
It's green enough that if you told me,
if somebody had a hand that green
and you told me, oh yeah, this is what diabetes
does to your hands when you get it.
Like your hand turns green.
- It turns your hand into a glove.
- I think it looks pretty cool.
- That green looks like enough of a shade of skin.
- Yeah, that's true.
When it's the back of the hand, it does kind of,
- The way your knuckles are in it,
it's tight enough that it looks like skin.
- Don't pick your nose with it.
- Aw, don't pick your nose with it.
- That's nasty.
- Stop.
(sniffing)
- Oh.
- People have to listen to this.
- That's so gross.
- He's gonna wipe a booger on Cameron.
- I'm just gonna put it on my pants.
- Yeah.
- It's not even your glove, you're ruining that glove
with toxic boogers.
- That's Allison Jo's glove.
- I don't care.
It's my green.
- It's making your hand look smaller somehow too.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
It's so funny.
It looks like I don't have a real hand in here.
Yeah, it's it's it looks like exactly like a prosthetic hand. Yeah, but it is real
Did you chop your hand off like you know, oh do what was that fucking um
Not er it was on TLC. It was basically a show about the ER
but it was on TLC and is like real like Ian like real surgeons and
There's this one episode I saw where a guy chopped off his own hand
What?
A guy chopped off his own hand for like some rea-- like he was going through like psychosis
or something and like brought the hand in a cooler and was just like, "I need you guys
to reattach this."
Whoa.
Yeah.
Oh.
I saw that when I was like seven.
Somebody told me recently about some--
Was it Alex talking about ER?
No, someone was telling me that they like saw a-- they saw somebody like walking down
the street and they thought that they were like like it was like a crazy guy
like dressed in like like a hospital gown and they thought that they were he was
like eating shit he was like eating something like red and brown out of his
hand and the person realized he was eating his own hand oh my god that's
crazy eating is a dude it's so nice you know I'll say it I would never do that
that yeah, that'd be fucking stupid. I know it might be good, though. You don't
know never do that. I don't know the hand is I mean the part of the body. I
would eat. I did not eat my hand in one single bite. As soon as I went behind
that curtain, I'll tell you that much imagine if you if I saw a guy walking
down the street like think about how much it must hurt to be eating your hand
that must taste really, really good for him to keep doing that
right true. Yeah, it's got to be good. Yeah, like you wouldn't be eating his
understand if it was disgusting right. His brain was probably telling him this
is prime rib baby a little bit of sweet baby prime baby raise. This is prime
rib and you're at the super bowl after party and everyone is congratulating you
for throwing a touchdown. You gotta put a little stubs on that one. Yeah, he's
gonna have a stub after. You gotta put stubs. Yeah, accidentally spilling some
like barbecue sauce in your hand and just looking at me like well.
It's already there. This is the only time it's gonna taste good.
I might as well take a big bite right now.
Do you think this is funny to do?
I think that's really funny to do.
Yeah, you're holding it like a Lego.
What?
Oh, I-- oh my god, you're right.
That is a Lego.
I have a Lego hand.
Yeah.
That's crazy.
The way you're holding it, though, it like--
I don't know.
You're doing some like Klaus Nomi movements with your body.
Who's Klaus Nomi?
He's an opera singer.
The fuck?
And he dressed up like an alien.
Does he do weird shit?
He does do weird shit.
Nah.
He had this song, "Simple Man."
pretty good song I saw that the didn't Joe go see that guy Oliver tree yeah I
I looked that dude up he just has a bowl cut all the time not just that he dresses
like yours Jankos and drives a speed dress is just like a fucking idiot yeah
he looks like the in Hitchhikers Guide fucking what's his name the who's a good
actor in Hitchhikers Guide I don't know who's a rock well Sam Rockwell when the
him Rockwell's chin comes up he's got a second face that's what that fucking guy
looks like oh this I don't like the look of this no you started dressing like
that because of vine and then just never stopped is he a Viner he was oh my well
he was a musician and then used vine to be like sir you like his biggest fan no
Oliver just remember him maybe were Oliver tree will hurt you with his talent
in this wacky video watch also at some point he was in every photo he just had
mouth wide yeah I I think all all celebrities are really cool yeah I think
if you have like if you if you're like a celebrity and you have like a costume
yeah that you like if you will put that down put that down put that down
shit where Lady Gaga dressed up in a meat dress yeah that now that was what
the hell was you guys but that was I just saw that this bitch is fucking
insane. Wait did you actually never see that before? She's wearing... no I just saw it. Wow. Yeah I just saw this. Lady Gaga she wore a
bunch of steaks and fucking hamburgers to the VMAs. She's got something crazy up
there. I think you know why I think she did it because her pussy is so
disgustingly blown out. She wanted to hide it. She had to blend it in. Mm-hmm. So people would say oh
Oh, it's just salcido turkey pork head.
(laughing)
That's what that is.
It worked.
I saw a guy dressed as a silver statue.
Yeah, at the VMAs, there's a silver astronaut.
Didn't fucking CeeLo Green dress up as a gold--
CeeLo Green dressed up like a statue.
Gnarly Davidson.
Oh, yeah.
Do you remember when there was that,
when the Samsung Galaxies were blown up
and CeeLo Green made that video
where it's like him in his studio
I'm like there's a like a Samsung Galaxy explodes. No, I got it like a
Facebook notification of like a memory of a post that I like liked or share
or something from like six years ago and as a picture of it was from CeeLo
Green's Facebook page and as a picture of him with a dog on his head and the
capture was well, my head can fit a dog.
Yeah, he's a roof here. Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's funny that yeah, he's a he's a
roof here and then he's like well, I need an evil art alter ego.
(laughter)
- Yeah, also like, imagine--
- I need to become an evil gold man.
- Imagine like, taking a drink from a guy
who looks like that.
A guy who's dressed up exactly like Bowser
and then hands you a beer.
- Drink this!
- It's like, it's like mad scientist like bubbles
and like, like--
- And he's going, "Ee-hee-hee-hee-hee-hee!"
- Yeah, dry ice, like--
- It's a flaming moe, I got it at Universal Studios!
(laughter)
- Oh, you can't get that glove off.
- I'm gonna try here.
yeah good luck
all the records for a period ago from the back
all that no it's terrible for the
they get picked up
the color what
uh... do you really do it so it is you can work with ever
this was the same way they looked wet
uh... plastic
is shining a hate no me today
yeah is in a way you know where green anymore here
all all
with the peace
He's picked up a hammer.
Just be careful.
It's hammer day.
It's not hammer day.
Hammer day is tomorrow.
This would be a horrible way to die.
A hammer?
Have your skull caved in.
You know this might be...
Two guys did it to one guy in a video.
This might be an unpopular opinion but I think that maybe, I think pretty much every way
would suck to die.
Yeah people say like oh that would be an awful way to die in general.
Yeah dying just sounds fucking shit.
I also don't think it matters how you die because then you're dead. Yeah true except maybe like
maybe like
Dying sex to death dying by getting my fingered so hard yeah that feed sex to death would still suck as you die at the end
Of it. Yeah, you know it's good is sex without death at some point to try that
At some point during the the the sex to death it's gonna start to hurt
Yeah, I don't think even if you have a heart attack while fucking it's like I don't think
Cut, you know, like you're--
But doesn't--
That's the noise you would make.
Like the tortoise.
(tortoise squeaking)
Yeah.
The cumming already hurts so bad that like it--
(laughing)
It doesn't, like you could sneak in a heart attack
and I wouldn't even--
I'd rather die than cum ever again.
I wouldn't even notice, right?
I mean, I do it a lot, but it does hurt so bad.
It hurts my entire body, dude.
Yeah, it feels like I'm getting hit with a ray
every single time I cum.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, even when people are like,
know like you know dying I'd rather just not die yeah I'd rather feel everything
leading up to the death by sex and then stay alive after I think that would be
my choice. That would be a good way to go out I think. What? Like it would be so
funny if like it's like you know those stories where it's like yeah my
grandfather was a fucking stud he died while fucking it's so sick and it's like
that you find out like they were running a train on my grandpa.
They're running a train on my grandpa. He got fisted so hard
that it ruptured. They ruptured his intestine and they touched
his stomach and that would be a good way to go. That would be
cool. Oh my God. Imagine imagine they're fisting your grandfather
and he pulls out his fist. He's holding a hot dog
whole a whole big bite. In bun. Yeah in the bun. Hot dog in bun. Ketchup perfectly kind of
squiggled down the entire dog. That's why they loved my grandpa down at the cock. He could suck a
whole hot dog bun and all all the way down to his belly. He was a shooter.
He's a dog shooter. Yeah. Yeah. Remember that video? The hot dog shooter?
Yeah. They pull out their hand and just like a just a just a torrent, just a
drench of just diet coke. It's the moment like when a samurai runs by you and you're like
oh yeah that's it. It has that like it has that like that white kind of layer that
comes out from a soda fountain when you get coke. Yeah it's like when you when you
look close enough. It's before it thinks to add the syrup. Yeah when you when you look at the
coke freestyle machine you can see like the soda and then the two syrups like
squirting on the other on each side. Yeah that's exactly. That's the thing about the
coke freestyle machine little bit of syrup not too much syrup that's why it's
perfect perfect amount of syrup every time here let's go to Qdoba right now
it's going on God's green or look at that fucking even talking about you look
at the coke freeze look at the stream at the coke freestyle machine it's two
syrups on each side what does that why
- Okay. - Look at--
- That's smart.
- I'm like recusing myself from this one.
- You gotta take a closer look
next time you look at a Coke freestyle machine.
- I get that, but what about that is impressive to you?
- Just the spirit of ingenuity.
- That they put syrup in soda?
- That they put the perfect amount,
they have a robot that puts the perfect amount of syrup.
- So you think every other thing
is fucking it up the entire time?
- Look, sometimes you get a bad fountain drink
at like a Burger King.
- Well yeah, sometimes-- - The syrup dispenser's broken.
dispensers running low on see you're running low or like the dispenser I
think I've had that happen at a coke freestyle though sorry to burst your
bubble but yeah it's happened to me yeah and I don't like to talk about it are
you kidding no I'm not you're not just saying this because we're on the air
sort of got it happened I think they should get rid of the I think they
should get rid of the soda fountains they're replacing with soda mountains so
so if you want to get soda, you gotta climb all the way up to get it,
burn some damn calories. You gotta mine the syrup.
And you gotta hit a... Oh, I struck coke!
It's like finding your Kyber crystal. Yeah, exactly.
You have to fight a rancor to get yourself...
I'm dressed up like a... This is the perfect soda for me.
I'm dressed up like a... Soda calls out to you.
I'm dressed up like a prospector and I'm walking down the street.
I'm looking in the windows of restaurants and I'm like,
"There's Coca-Cola in that restaurant!"
I run in and start hitting their soda fountain
with a picture in their car around the tracks broken
because the cave in a kill everybody in the burger king you walk into a cute
overlooking the accident is that it is a little bit like hit the wall by accident
is the whole group is going to have a lot of load-bearing like all the
readiness for a team young cuba customers are stuck in the soda mines
today
they say that a a
but but they're completely fine because there's plenty of soda and there's so
much so that's almost flooding the restaurant
and i say that i a x_-eight shanti prospector walked into the cuba
for the pickaxe and took out the one load-bearing poll
you can't afford the one look at the people
it's in the middle of the rest of the poll is a side of this
do not break the do not have a good guess it's not very good
this is the focus will be a bit israeli iran soccer team is stuck inside of a
cute little
but they're perfectly fine there's beans and soda
that's not a good as a best place to get started a good rhyme dude really it
thank you stuck in a cute over
there for a play for a good line there's beans and soda
and they're going to eat a load of
yoga
baroda baroda so they're going to load up a road as welcome back to rap news
uh...
I'm MC Crist.
(laughter)
Yeah.
I basically would love if the news was just rap
and rhyme themed. They should auto tune that news.
Facts.
They should do schmo yo ho to the news.
Yeah. They need to auto tune
news. Everything sounds better auto tuned.
Yes sir. Yep.
Damn. That'd be cool.
I do want to go to a Coke Freestyle machine
right now. I want to go to a schmo yo ho concert.
I need to go see auto tune the news live dude that'd be so sick. I need to see
schmo yo ho like do they still auto tune the news? I don't know I never figured
out. I think I feel like that got replaced by the like bad lip reading.
Oh yeah. Oh yeah. They are still doing that. I remember there was like
there was like 2020 election. Some of those were funny. Some of those were
funny AF. Some of that shit dude when they would make when they would get Tom
Brady oh yeah they would make him say hmm some of the shit they made
some of the sounds they made Donald Trump make the shit they made Mitt
Romney say the things about that show. I call him Mitt Romney. Yep that's what I just called him.
The thing about that show though is that like it's cuz I don't respect the
Mormon faith but it's funny until he like is actually disrespecting the
office of president yeah it's like he would not say I want to eat a diaper
today yeah he would not say that you know if you did it wouldn't be funny it would
be it would be you respect it yeah you know it would be like it would be like a
call for help from Donald Trump yeah not like it'd be like Johnny Cash saying I
hurt myself he says not like that you said you sit your ass down and listen
today yes to see if I still my favorite Johnny ass song
Johnny as pretty good a diaper today
And you can have my pee on my shirt
I will I will I will sit down
But will
Yep, he basically pooped and he went to he went to the ball. I heard he had to go to rehab
He would lie from the Vulcan prison and he did a bad shit my pants and Reno
Cuz I had depends on just to make just to smell them stink just
Just because it smells like fries
Shit my pants and Reno dude speaking of food that tasted smells like shit
that I just had some some Euro meat yeah that it look it tasted it tasted like
farts and it felt like I was eating a spider
chicken place
literal
rotating like meat thing it's just like spider meat
we got frostbite spider we just got frostbite spider dude it I mean it tasted
like like I loved it but it tasted like far they have they have atronachs from
Skyrim. They have a frost atronach in the slurpee machine but dude a Euro meat is
just like it's so hit or miss yeah yeah sometimes well cuz if they get the
frozen shit that comes pre-cut like the pre shaved shit yeah that's like always
is
hair. Yeah, it doesn't exist, but like a good like a like a euro from like good
food. Good food. Yeah, but like good good actually and drink to drink to drink.
Good drink is so good drink is basically life. I just have a limeade subscription.
You know what else is good good music. Yep. You guys aren't going to say
anything about the fact that I had a line. I don't want at a yearly. I paid
$15 and I went to Zoe's kitchen down the street for my dad's and I brought my
and I got a Limeade every day.
- You got a what?
- Limeade.
- What's a Limeade subscription?
- I would pay, I paid a yearly fee.
- I guess they have kids upstairs.
- To have a 99 cents Limeade.
- Can you hear that on the microphone?
- I don't think so.
- I don't know.
- Okay.
- But there is a child being beaten to death upstairs.
- Yeah.
- There were a lot of children screaming
when I was here yesterday.
- That's awesome.
I love this place.
- Pretty cool.
- Yeah.
- It's so cool how the soundproofing did not work.
- I just met a guy at the chicken place
I was getting lunch. Yeah. And he was telling me he works at the smoke shop and he was telling me that
he had to scare off a bunch of kids who were who were robbing an old lady the other day by shooting
his gun in the air. And then he was like yeah one of the kids was actually trying to take a shit in
the bush and the gun scared him so bad he started running away with shit in his ass and he fell and
he got shit all over himself. That's true I believe him. I believe him too dude. Yeah. It was cool. I
totally believe that. Yeah and he was like yeah just and then he was like he was like you come to
to the smoke shop if it's $30 I'll give it to you for 29 he does that yeah dude he
fucking I was going there to buy a jewel charger and he's like I don't have a
jewel charger and I was buying fucking idea they have the Chinese chips there
yeah I bought a bag of these like Chinese cheddar chips to bring you those
chips I'm sorry oh dude bummer that's all right I'll bring him tonight okay
but he like he's like it's $6 I'll give it to you for five I mean it's a gene if
you just price everything $1 more than a subtract a dollar yeah yeah yeah he also
he gave me seven examples of that instead of just saying I'll give you a
discount on everything he was like if it's $30 I'll give it to you for 29 if
if it's eight dollars and give it to you for seven if it's fifteen i'll give it to
you for fourteen if it's twenty one i'll give it to you for twenty but
if it's six
a hundred dollars
just for you my friend i gotta make my money so
yes that's smart
you give a you one one secret price that if you buy it you have to pay ten times
as much what that he was giving me the discount because he didn't have jewel
chargers
no he was just giving me the discount 'cause like that's how his store works
I thought I was getting special treatment because he felt bad. I think he's racist, dude. Yeah?
Yeah, he's he was he was he's black and he was telling me he was he kept telling me just
like about how he was like he I think he's giving me a discount because he loves white
people. I think I think he might be a racist. Yeah, yeah, that tracks. Yeah, because he
also mentioned the race of every single person in the story that he told me about shooting
his gun in the sky. Yeah, and if it's $15 you get a 12 cent discount. Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, he's a bad guy. Yeah, but yeah, I think I'm gonna go over there and buy a Rick and Morty
backwoods rolling paper tray. Yeah, nice. Yeah, that'll be sick. Yeah, that's good for the office.
We could put the recorder in it. Oh, that's actually a pretty good idea. Oh, that's cool.
we need now that we're cool now we've gotten the essentials we basically need
to put some swag in here yeah yeah we need to swag the place out we have too
many chairs we have way too many chairs but it's good if we ever have guests we
already said we never will yes okay we're done saying I'm saying like
guests that can come over and hang out not on the point we this is an office
there's no hanging out that happens here not even a little bit of workspace
exactly we don't play and we don't roll chairs also you brought did you bring
some fucking did you bring drugs to the office yes you brought a seat see but I
brought a CBD sparkling water you were a fucking junkie piece of shit you know my
joints hurt yeah you probably love your joints yeah
smoker you smoker yeah you're a smoker yeah smoky Wiederson yep and I'm gonna
and I'm not gonna be doing anything over here so don't look what are you doing
don't are you gonna snort that but I'm not gonna there's nothing that's gonna
to happen. He's gonna freebase it. He's basically smoking this soda right now.
What did he just say? He said it's so hard to open his mind without drugs.
He's reliant on CBD for creativity. I didn't drink any of it. You're addicted.
I would have never thought that you could handle some bullshit like that.
I can't.
How many milligrams of CBD are in there?
I drank something.
I drank a thing of...
Oh man.
He's already so high.
It's already hitting.
He's so high.
Listen pal, you might be a junkie, but I'm a punkie because I don't respect authority
and they want you to do drugs.
So I rebel by not doing it.
This is the only escape we have, man.
I hate these damn kids sitting on the corner drinking CBD soda, getting high out of their
fucking minds, giggling to each other, playing the penis game.
Oh my God, I hate that shit.
So what is...
I know so many people who are teachers now that I'm like...
It made me realize one, every teacher I had was like 20, every assistant teacher.
Yeah, they're young.
They're all like my age.
That's why they're so hot, man.
Because they were nice and young.
time in second grade. Did you fuck your teacher? I had sex with my dead teacher.
I had sex with my teacher and she was 94. I wanted to fuck my teacher so bad she was uh
I never had a teacher that I wanted to have sex with. It was all
strictly a business relationship. You had business? You made business with her?
No. You did your business in her mouth? I did my math and I turned the paper in.
Whoa. Did you ever calculate her number? No. I wouldn't want to. Cameron left to pee
and now I'm gonna go get a cup of coffee so you're gonna you and your high mind
are gonna have a moment. Hey don't go don't go a Cheech and Chong and out on
me. That's okay. I was gonna say something before I forget. Oh oh the penis game. It's
so funny like there's like so many people I know who are like assistant
teachers or like teachers now that are like my age or older or like you know
and it's so funny that like I've seen I've seen and heard them basically play
the penis game with me. It'd be impossible to not. It's like how do you
not laugh as a teacher? You have to train yourself once you become like an assistant teacher. You gotta like hate fun.
You got exactly you gotta uh-huh you gotta train yourself not to laugh at the
penis game it's like yeah it's like it's like fucking how do you not let I could
make me realize I could never sensitizing like the the like showing a
drone operator yes dude that's what that shit is they're desensitizing them like
the like the SS yeah it's true they're trying to get them to be fucking and
it's exactly like the SS it's a hundred times worse the to teacher does the to
Steve. Yeah. That was my sub.
Do you have the rotating cast of substitute teachers?
Oh, yeah.
Like, it was like, oh, like this one is.
We had this lady.
There's a lady named Mrs.
Herman who was just like, she sounded like a Roz from Monsters
Inc.
Yeah, and she was my, she would substitute Spanish sometime.
Were they just kids of the school's parents?
Yeah, that's what mine were too.
Yeah, her kids were like long gone and she was just this
old died. No, no, did you get you know what the best was was like if you had like a
long-term sub like if your teachers like if your teacher had a miscarriage or
something and I took me out for a few months and you got like you got a
long-term sub who was just like and it's never like they're just the same as like
others so like it's not like they're like more skilled or anything so it's
just literally every day yeah just only for this one I had that - oh dude we had
like that was like our only mean sub was this long-term sub and she I remember it
It was Miss Sullivan, she was pregnant, she had her baby, she was on maternity leave,
and she miscarried the baby to life, I guess, and it's a bit similar thing.
And then the lady came in and she was like,
it was like a, it was like a, like she was like, so how do you guys do things
around here? We were like, Miss Sullivan lets us have fun and watch movies all
day, and she like, she was like, well, we're gonna do things a little
differently, and dude, she put the hurt on us. Damn. She like ruined school.
- Dude, yeah, that was my math teacher in seventh grade.
- I remember thinking, maybe I'll drop out of fifth grade.
Because she's so fucked up.
- Dude, my math teacher in seventh grade,
Mr. McCarthy, went on paternity leave.
- Was he bald?
- Yeah.
- Really?
- Uh-huh.
- What did he teach?
- He taught math.
- Did he ever teach biology?
- No.
- I had a math teacher--
- Was he short?
- No, his wife was a cop and she had a kid
and then he had to go on paternity leave
because his wife was a cop.
He had Mrs. Williams, who had a very short haircut.
can't lose one cop right yeah but she had really short hair and she was like an
evil bitch yeah dude and she short haired teachers always bad I had a math
teacher in middle school whose name was mrs. cow chick and I was like that's
like that's like hardcore difficulty like okay you can't go you shouldn't might
be a middle school teacher my brother's my little brother had a teacher who's
her last name was spelled, she was Italian. Her last name was B-E-N-A-Z-I.
I feel like I said this one before too, but one of the like, one of the-
Is that crazy? How do you-
Be a Nazi.
Be a Nazi, yeah.
Mrs. Be a Nazi.
One of the like, you know how like schools just have a hundred old ladies
who work in the main office?
Yeah.
One of the old ladies was-
A bunch of grannies.
Was named Miss Dabona.
Yeah.
And they would just always call for her over the last few years, just like a
a few times a week, I would just be like,
"Mr. Bona, Mr. Bona."
- Ah, Mr. Bona.
- Mr. Bona. - Is there a Mr. Bona?
- Mr. Bona is literally that.
Like, they do it like twice a week.
- Why you little, yeah, wait a second.
- It's so funny, literally a Bart name.
- Oh, dude, you used to call--
- Damn, he got a Bart name, damn.
- That substitute teacher, Mrs. Herman,
she was like this short little fat lady,
and we called her the Hermanator,
and she didn't like that.
And she,
oh dude, she substituted Spanish.
She did like, she taught like Spanish one day
and just like the most Peggy Hill
pronunciations of everything.
And we like kept, we, oh dude, it was so fucking funny
'cause she didn't speak a lick of Spanish
and she kept being like, "Well, I don't speak Spanish,
"so I don't tenor cue, I don't know, I don't know what."
- Y'all remember our health teacher, Mr. Poop?
did have it we had a like a fat lady sub and I literally don't remember her name
she was so fat that the kids just called her mrs. fudge oh dude there's I forget
she was like a guidance counselor in my guidance counselor caught some strange
oh they wouldn't see me yeah I asked to see him and he was like no there was -
why there's one of them there's a woman named Bart who is my guidance counselor
and then another one and she was a really really like morbidly obese woman with
like a start like a sergeant hair could hear like dials haircut and her name was
mrs. Wario oh this is Mario with a w-a-u-r-i-o there were two school
psychologists at my high school for like the like like Learning Center like like
thing and their names were were miss Glotzbecker and miss Wisnitzer were they
like twins in the circus yeah they were like the characters yeah they were like
the witches in Ocarina of Time in the Spirit Temple yeah there's this one of
them did where they where they joined at the head and we had a big head one of the
small head there's this substitute teacher everyone that everyone hated at
my school and she would drive like like a moped uh-huh to school so you'd like
see the moped outside and be like what she a drunk driver I don't know but she
you see a moped outside and you're like, oh, like she's here today. And I
remember one time I was on vacation in Cape Cod with my family and like we went
to the beach and I saw the moped like parked. Oh, I was like, oh my god.
She's substituting for my opportunity.
We ran into her.
She's probably substituting for a shark.
She's in the ocean.
That's like one of those nightmares where you're like, there's like something that shouldn't be in that place.
It's just like, yeah.
That's terrifying, dude.
so scary to be alive scary substitute everything about life when you're a kid
everything is just terrifying there is literally when you're a kid life is
unfair and then when you're growing in the world when you're a grown-up you
literally get to get a very funny office yeah yeah with poop and and a young
monkey and a crazy frog yeah what else is in here lights camera this is almost
exactly what I thought I was good. I thought that I was going to work in this
office when I was a kid, but I was going to be doing like real business stuff.
I thought I was going to work in this office, but be a firefighter.
Pretty much. But this is where I imagined working.
Yeah, I was thinking I was going to be in an office like with chairs like this,
but I was going to be a Tyrannosaurus Rex.
I thought I was going to be a doctor when I was 11.
Yeah, we went over that.
When you were 11?
Recently. Yeah.
We can't rehash this.
We can't rehash it.
We had a whole big thing.
I watched a lot of Scrubs as a kid and I was like, yeah.
you're a funny doctor. Yeah, I'll be the funny doctor. I don't know what I
thought I was going to be. I it's so I literally there's like a old like
drawing that my mom saved from like kindergarten where it's like a
worksheet is his like when I grow up, I want to be dot dot dot and I drew
like a green blob and just wrote a frog.
It's embarrassing, but I'm getting there. I'm pretty close. I think as
soon as I got out of the firefighter thing, I was like I'm going to be a
stand up comedian. I wanted to be a cartoonist. I wanted I like I was
obsessed with the far side. I was like I want to be I want to be like Gary Larson
Gary Larson's a goat. He is the goat. I wish I want to meet him before he does
so badly. I need to show him my drawings. I draw a lot of cool things. This is called the smiler.
The smiley face. I do think it'd be so cool to just make like far side things
where the captions are just. You just look at smiley faces. The smiler.
- A picture of a poop store and the caption says poop store.
- Dude, we need to make a webcomic.
- We have to.
- We can host it on the new website.
- Yes.
- That's our next big thing.
- Okay.
- Yeah, like a weekly webcomic.
- A weekly, like years long webcomic.
- That is a plot.
- A control alt delete.
- All right, we'll start it.
- That's what we need to make.
- What's it called?
We'll start it today.
- We need a name right now.
- The Smiler.
- Alt F4.
- Adventures of the Smiler.
- Okay, we'll do Adventures of the Smiler.
- First issue will be out like this week, I can say.
Yeah, definitely. Are we doing one panel or multi-panel?
It varies.
Yeah.
Whoa!
Yeah, new paradigm.
I think first one, I think first one we establish who the...
Don't spoil it. Don't spoil it.
Okay, okay. I'm just saying we establish who the smiler is.
Definitely. That'll be big.
Next week.
How do you... You don't have to establish... Everyone knows from the name.
No, you got to establish it.
Rethink so.
Week after?
It's... Yeah.
Week after that, our tribute to Ukraine.
One week into the webcomic, it's like no comic this week.
yeah no comic is heartbroken and it's like the smile is a loopy here's some
places to donate yeah yeah Venmo comm slash Cameron fetter it's a good idea
dude yeah I'm really I'm gonna start the smile I've just I'm gonna start we are
I've been fucking around with the web I tried to well I won't spoil anything
that I'm trying to work on with the website but Squarespace sucks ass and and
and we need to protest against them, because they're stopping me from doing
all the awesome stuff I want to do on the website. You were going to make a you
were going to make he's going to put the scary mace game on the website. Really
yeah, then we literally can't do anything with squares. We should just put
the page. That's what I wanted. I was just going to put a bunch of like cool
math games on. Oh really you can't do it. I mean I okay. I was trying to do
something else on Squarespace. I was getting mad about not being able to do
I'll tell you after I'm gonna find a way to do it. Okay. Hmm. It used to be like you could host like a thing on fucking like
Blogs where it just doesn't give you any
Like it's you can't like yeah
You can't like it sucks
You should be able to just like every game used to have an embed code and then you could just put it on your website
And it was so easy. I bet I bet there's still something you can do that with I bet I can just get I bet there's
Like with HTML 5 I'm sure that I'll figure it out. Don't you guys work going on? Why are you making that face?
Damn, all right. Well that that's where it is
That's how it is
No speaking the website go to swag poop comm slash shows to buy tickets for the tour. They're going fast
You don't want to miss out
Philadelphia Philadelphia
Dallas
No, we're going from Philadelphia to Dallas. Come on. We're going you got Philadelphia, Washington DC, Richmond, Virginia
Atlanta, yeah, then Fort Worth. Yeah, yeah, then
Boston yeah, yeah, and we're going to Los Angeles yeah, and then we're going to
Shuba's in Chicago yep, Shuba's the Lincoln Lincoln Hall Shuba's and then we're going to hell yeah, and then we're going straight to hell immediately
if we get a
pandemonium
We'll be cool. We got into a huge car accident on the tour. We all just died. That'd be so sick
I was right that we just all died like like Lynyrd Skynyrd. We just wiped out
we're never one of us one of us survives our brothers pick up the podcast and
just start doing all of our shit version of it yeah Cameron has to get a bro oh
hmm oh look at you fine I don't want if we all die I don't want to be part of it
anymore can we at least get you a backup brother yeah I guess patches okay patches
is now your legal brother that's cool stop thinking it's cool man down with
Okay, then this the smeller is your brother yo
All right, bye everybody
Fuck seven one two
to
go.