[MUSIC]
>> Hot about list versus seeking derangements.
Let the fight begin.
[SOUND]
>> Just me playing bass the whole time.
>> Yeah.
>> So you can't, you like, you respect these guys enough to not play bass during
the episode, but every single time we start recording, just us three,
you're playing the bass.
It's different.
You're like figuring out how to do like Katie Tut on bass.
>> You're having guests.
>> I just did that.
>> You're trying to impress them, dude.
>> Now, where are your houses now, bitch?
- Yeah, I don't need them being breastfed.
- I'm farting into the mic.
I'm pissing with the door open
and like turning up the mic so everyone can hear.
- No respect.
- No respect calling your girlfriend toots.
- Did y'all hear about that school board member
that didn't realize her camera didn't pause
in her Zoom meeting?
So she put her laptop into the bathroom
and took a shit in front of the computer.
(laughing)
That rules, dude.
Have you seen the picture of it where it's just like the zoom call and it's just like the laptop like bathtub level?
Just...
Just shitting.
Is she still looking like into the camera?
I think so.
So apparently...
She thought she paused it.
This is how you get fired from your job, kids.
She was already...
People were trying to have her fired because she was a bigot.
[laughter]
So...
So they just use a big way.
How do you know this?
What is there was a news article about it?
I read a news article for Jack goes to that school.
Keeps calling me fag in the hallways.
So tired of it.
I'm so tired.
Jacques has got Jacques gets fired from his teaching job
because one of the students calls him.
Mr.
Gonsolin instead of Miss Gonsolin and he freaks out or MX
Gonsolin someone gets console.
(laughing)
- Yeah, you have to say it with a Z.
- Did y'all see that new trans--
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What did she do that was bigoted, Jacques?
- Well, I mean--
- She was like anti-gay.
- Yeah, I'm pretty sure she was against--
- No, but what did she do that was bigoted is what he asked.
- Did I?
(laughing)
- What was the wrong thing she did?
- Yeah.
- True, woke.
- Took a shit during the "It Gets Better" speech.
(laughing)
- Yeah, she kept wheeling in a TV
and just playing Love, Simon
and taking a shit at her desk.
(laughing)
- It was weird, it was a weird day at school.
- And that's fucked up, 'cause we got paid to do that.
(laughing)
- Whoops.
- Is that a pull-up bar behind you?
- No, that's a crazy--
- I'm so glad you asked.
Yes, it's a pull-up bar.
- Is that intentional?
Do you leave it there so you can be like,
oh, I'm gonna--
I only put it up when I'm on video calls.
- You don't even have to pull it.
- Yeah, I've never used it.
Couldn't do a pull up to save my life.
- I use it every time I'm there.
- Pat tries to use it every time he's here.
- I do try to use it, yeah.
- Pull up, it's just a monkey, it's a single monkey bar.
- Right, it's fun to jump, like grab onto it and jump.
- Yeah, sometimes when I'm going from the living room.
Yeah, when I'm going from the living room to the kitchen,
I do think it's like a quarter of a second faster
to do a swing on the monkey bar.
(laughing)
- Yeah, to kind of vault yourself.
Just trying to do parkour.
Yeah.
And but but I have a very slippery tile floor, so I always eat shit.
Slam my knees into the sink.
Break that precious egg head of yours.
I don't have an egg.
Jock didn't know I was bald until like 10 minutes ago, which is so crazy.
I feel like I just recorded with you and you were bald then as well.
I've always I've been bald my whole life.
Oh, you've always been bald.
It's not true.
Potato head.
I shouldn't I shouldn't be ostracized for discriminating
hidden. I didn't. I love it. You're one of the **** talk.
Take that hat off. Let's see.
You wanna call me an egghead? **** you, dude. I love you. You
guys both look good bald, you know. Yeah, I look better
bald. Yeah, like if I went bald, I would instantly age
like like 20 years. I would look like a good thing. I've
been on slowly aging 40 years plus. Wait, when did you go
ball, Chuck. Um, very recently. Look at this. This is horrible. It's still it's going on.
It's ongoing. It's on. You look like a private investigator. Yeah, the Christmas present
that keeps giving, of course, just somebody who needs to like, never be noticed. Like
that's the hair exact hair. I believe the word you're looking for is Hanukkah. Yeah.
When I'm trying to not be noticed somewhere, I have this fake pair of glasses that I wear
and then I wear a button up shirt and it's like I'm trying to get away with something.
You just hold a newspaper in front of you.
I would bet my life.
A Chinese newspaper.
Yacht newspaper.
Holds up a painting with the eyes cut out.
Just standing in the middle of a crowd.
No one's going to freaking notice me.
No one's going to notice me.
Well, it worked.
I mean, I was you would you if you didn't dress the way you do,
you would be very inconspicuous person, but you're wearing like
yellow.
Right.
Maybe skirts.
Yeah, when Jacques says that they're wearing like glasses and
a button-up shirt, it's like a Hawaiian shirt and like 2010
New Year glasses.
Under the radar right now.
Hey, I'm a spy.
Whatever.
That's your normie camouflage.
I love normie camouflage.
It's like every once in a while I'll wear something on the way home from like working at a restaurant
All black like a black t-shirt and black pants and this guy's like you like fucking women, right?
When I was a I was a bus boy when I was like 15 and I was dating another bus boy
It was really hot and we got off work one day we were both wearing like all black, you know, like busboys do and
Like a teens do we were looking for a place to like have sex
And this guy's back
Strangers backyard a
Backyard. Yeah, we were like hopping fences to get back. This is when Ben was dating by nada. Who's that?
the murderer
Joke about me, but I'm making a
I'm
the
I was always told it was the devil growing up until I was like 15, maybe.
Whoa. In Maryland?
I hate you. I'm done talking to you.
In Jock's defense, he only knows four states.
Okay.
Hey, please.
Maryland is the South.
Caleb, where'd you grow up again?
North Carolina.
Oh, that's why.
That part of Maryland, yeah.
That is why.
That's why they thought Pokemon was the devil.
That's why. That part of Maryland, yeah. That is why. That's why they thought Pokemon was the devil.
That makes sense. I know a lot of people. I mean, I knew kids whose parents like burned
Harry Potter books in front of them. And in hindsight, it's like, oh, like they were...
They were right. They were right. And they're doing it because they think like, you know,
Harry Potter. That's anti-Turf shit. But it's like... Yeah, I mean, they were doing anti-Turf
book burnings. Whatever you want about, you know, like hard right.
That's why all those kids are evangelicals now.
But like they were completely correct about several things,
one of them being like Harry Potter being the devil, right?
Second, life begins at conception and three, all gays go to hell.
I read about a lot of stuff.
Michael Moore's a pussy.
That's the four rules of a podcast.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, no, so anyways, I was blowing my busboy co-worker in this guy's backyard.
Wait, did you know the guy?
No, no, no, no, no.
Was it a barbecue situation?
No, it was empty. It was empty. This is like 11 o'clock at night. We didn't...
Strangers backyard.
Backyard, it's either barbecue, baseball, or blowjobs is the only...
I think how horny you are as like a 15-year-old, like, gay guy.
No, I was a... oh, gay guy? Nah, never mind.
I
Almost beat the shit out of us.
We were like, no, no, no, we're not trying to rob you.
It was like, we were wearing all black.
And we're like, we're not trying to break in.
We're like, we're having sex.
(laughing)
Imagine like two cat burglars in your house.
You wake up at 3 a.m. to a noise.
(laughing)
- Like the little, like the black, like,
knobby mask, shirt.
- Just like fucking shoving.
I have a ski mask on because it's sorry.
(laughing)
- Yeah, just two homos napping.
- They're snapping tomorrow.
(laughing)
- It's out.
- But yeah, that was one time,
last time I almost got beat up.
- That was the last time?
- Who hasn't gotten beat up?
- I mean like assaulted, assaulted.
- I mean, who hasn't gotten beat up,
getting caught having public sex?
I mean.
- Not me.
- These guys.
- Never ever.
- You guys need to, come on, get it, pump it up.
I had semi-public sex once and then the janitor walked in.
That was it.
(laughing)
I had, I had.
That was just at your house.
It was at my dad's.
My dad had it.
(laughing)
My dad's a janitor.
I had sex with this person once
in the laundry room behind their house.
And the next day, the neighbor went and told--
The laundry room behind their house?
I don't understand.
It was like a laundry room.
There was like a laundry room,
like a separate room outside of the house
that was just the laundry room
that they shared with the next door neighbor.
And the next door neighbor walked in on me having sex
with someone in there.
And then the next day he went and told this person's husband
that they caught us having sex.
And I found out when I was leaving on the Greyhound
and I opened my Banh Mi sandwich
and it was to my dismay and disgust.
course is a close to you fleeing on a greyhound is
the on a greyhound and I I open my sandwich and it's the wrong bond me it's
tofu instead of pork and then I go and it is a sandwich and then I get about
five or six calls and text messages being like what the fuck did you do and that
was the worst moment of your whole life no it's great I mean sandwich is still
good I mean that was I loved it I was basically living in Houston it's fine me
the
Just one by me in the parking lot. It's like a very like inavigable city.
It looks like you've made LA in The Sims and then
uploaded like a mod that makes everyone fat. Yeah, it's literally if
shock was an urban planner.
(laughing)
- The restaurant's here, grocery's here, let's go.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Yeah, everything else can be whatever.
- Just restaurant, grocery store alternating.
(laughing)
For like 60 miles.
- Just a straight line.
(laughing)
- One road alternating restaurant, grocery store.
- Let's say you get your own city
to build from the ground up.
- Yeah.
world are you doing it? This is Jacques, Dubai. Okay, we're gonna
we're gonna go God. Huh? Glasgow, Scotland. Why?
Nowhere like it there. It's my favorite place. Have you bet
your favorite place? Yeah, Scotland. Yes, I've been to
Scotland. The country is crazy. I've been to I can't believe
they would let you out and then into another country right out
of that. I can't believe it. We're gonna drop back in.
any border and then crossed it again is crazy. I'll give you a little preview of what's happened
since then. They've taken my passport away and I was unable to travel or get a new passport
for the last six, seven years. Why? What happened? So when I got arrested when I was 17 for five
felonies for industrial vandalism.
Industrial vandalism?
As you do, as you do.
Explain industrial vandalism.
Graffiti.
Oh, oh, oh, Pooey.
Don't make it sound like a fuck is like what it was.
I thought you were like a factory.
Yes.
I thought you did like a killdozer thing.
I was imagining like the beginning of the Minions movie, just like Jacques
going all around every country and like, like burning Notre Dame and like,
like doing like, like the Haiti earthquake somehow.
Twin Towers.
Taking Haiti.
So, okay, so.
Bass went too hard on that, on that DJ mix.
Her point of print was never the same.
Natural disasters for the last 10 years.
All of you.
What did you do exactly?
Mountain melons.
You spray painted something.
No, yeah, I spray painted a car dealership, a school property,
University of Louisiana property.
And I can't even remember like maybe like a stop sign,
but the technicality was that it was on the business
and University of Lafayette's campus.
So I got five felonies for industrial vandalism when they
were doing the court proceeding.
I had no clue you were a felon.
and that's so cool.
Rock.
When I was in jail for I was in jail for three and a half weeks.
What?
17 like coming off of so many hallucinogens.
I used to do hallucinogens.
Oh, yeah, I read a story.
Yeah, I used to see I and like research chemicals research
chemical but also I was addicted to you're doing.
I would drink 13 bottles a day in the high.
I'm going to tell you I'm being dead serious when I was at the height of
this.
I would go to how long was this period of you doing 13 bottles of
Awesome at least six months.
Wait, how many bottles is that total?
I'm sure I mean look, I think first jocks never going to die.
I say this let me say that I've been trying for so long.
I know I want that.
This is what the this is a good vaccine is they've just killed
that much cough syrup.
I want that sweet escape by Gwen Stefani.
So anyway, I would do like whole boxes of mucinex also in her
instead of doing, it's the equivalent.
And I would just go into a blackout.
- Has the same amount of DXM.
- Yeah, and I would just like, I would do it,
and I would like, one time I took
like a box of Mucinex at a McDonald's.
And I had two cheeseburgers beforehand.
- You just eat the whole box, with the paper included.
- You've done that, Caleb.
I've seen you do it.
- I've done that, yeah.
- Whatever, listen.
- I'm eating cardboard, it's fine.
I get the 10 chicken McNuggets, two apple pies, a large Coke,
and an ice cream.
And I eat all of that, and then I take my box of Mucinex DM,
and then I just go crazy.
And I wake up in a blackout.
And this one day in particular, it's like winter,
and I'm running around--
I love the idea of waking up in a blackout.
I'm so blacked out right now.
So during this kind of like blacking out period,
I mean, I'm riding my bike so fast.
lost
fuck is going on.
So obviously I don't trip anymore.
OK, wow.
Holy shit.
It sounds like that.
There's no way that could have ever been like awesome doing 13 bottles.
Now, have you guys done that shit before?
It's the worst.
No, I would.
I did it once and it was like I hated it.
I mean, I was probably like I had good times on acid and stuff,
but I would never even do acid again.
And when we did acid together, the only thing I hallucinated was a ceiling fan.
Like you hallucinated an entire new ceiling fan or the ceiling fan which is feeling weird.
I was laying down and I looked up and I guess there was like, I was like, can somebody shut
the fan off?
It's like the middle of lunch.
And there just was no fan.
There's no fan.
That's kind of a scary.
That's really creepy.
That's like a creepypasta.
The worst creepypasta ever.
(all laughing)
- The worst creepypasta ever.
Including at the beginning,
I took acid before this happened.
(all laughing)
- That's a Polish creepypasta right there.
- Let me just round off this story really quickly.
- Okay, let's go.
- In court, I was being charged for this
and one of my friend's dads had spoken to the judge
before my proceeding and said that I was--
Sir, this is a retarded man.
He was like, "Kill him. Please don't kill him."
He was the opposite. He said, "This man..."
"He's the smartest man of all time."
He put him in jail.
No, no, no. He was like, "This guy is a danger. Don't let him..."
This man is a fucking genius.
"He's a flight risk. He's planning on moving to California to grow weed.
He's a drug dealer."
So...
Was he wrong?
They said flight risk?
Yeah, so...
Okay, well, you absolutely were a flight risk.
Yeah, but you know, you should not.
You have to be sure to jump a greyhound risk like you.
Yeah, well, well, so possibly a boss risk.
Yeah. So the judge was like, and we're
a vote, we're taking back your passport.
Like they took my passport at that proceeding.
But anyway, you went to jail for 24 days.
What kind of fucking sentence is that?
Well, I went to jail for 24 days and then they sent me to a state
rehab next to the jail for three months.
- A state testing facility.
(laughing)
- During the day, they would bring us to group therapy
and then the other half of the day,
they would just bring us food from the jail
and they would be like, we don't know what to do.
So they'd either play a weird old VHS,
or they would put--
- A weird old VHS?
- Yes, or they would set up a karaoke machine.
And this is all people who have been sent directly
from jail to the rehab.
You join and there's literally karaoke for like Jeff sex
and Joe.
No, is this how you gained your love of music was the karaoke
and rehab?
No, but I did learn how to sing power of love by Celine Dion.
They had like four going to say Huey Lewis.
They had like more CDs.
The VHS was back to the future.
(laughing)
- And two of them were like early 2000s.
- Back to the future, we thought it was a documentary.
(laughing)
- It is a documentary.
It's about how Doc Brown's trying to get into
Marty's pants the whole fucking time.
- It's true.
- Old pussy doctor.
Well, anyway.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- He had great hair, by the way, Doc Martin.
- Oh yeah.
- Imagine if he had that straightened out, like--
- Is he still alive?
- Like, three billion.
- I think he's barely alive.
- I think he died.
I think he died like two years ago.
Christopher Lloyd's still alive.
Oh.
Yeah, he's in that new Bob Odenkirk movie. He's in the trailer.
He plays Bob Odenkirk's dad.
How is this motherfucker... He's only 82? Jesus Christ.
He's one of those guys who's looked old forever.
He was like John Huston or something.
Yeah, I don't know how old he was on Taxi, but even on Taxi he looked fucking old.
Holy shit.
He came out of the womb looking like Larry David does today.
It's all right. He literally looks like a month and then
pussy like and he looks like exactly growing, growing,
wisen than old. Well, he it was a it was a 30 year
pregnancy term. Oh, he came out at 30. Can we talk about
the great of all time? The greatest, what's the greatest
pregnancy? Um Junior, the movie Junior with Arnold
Schwarzenegger. Oh, man. Day to be done. Dream on. Where
Danny was called Mr. Mom.
No, no, no.
Mr. Mom is the one.
That's another transmate movie we haven't seen.
Sorry.
Why do you like that movie so much, Jacques?
This is relatable.
It's relatable.
Who do you think you are?
Arnold or Danny?
He's the baby.
The best scene in that whole movie
is where Arnold goes to live
among pregnant women at some kind of
like halfway house for pregnant women and he's in full like drag straight
disguise bullshit it's so funny does he fuck any of the women yeah he fucks
Helen Hunt whoa wait he has sex as a pregnant man no what does that trigger
you Patrick hmm I'm trying to figure out the logistics of it I do remember like
There was so many in like 2009.
There was so many.
Shut up.
How does that?
Wait, no, no, try it.
Yeah, go ahead.
Well, it's a pregnant women's place, so they're both pregnant.
So there's.
Arnold, I don't know, I'm
Arnold Scissorhands.
Jail for what was the question you were going to ask?
What do you know?
I was I.
So you say like two fat people can't.
That's that's the thought that I had after.
I didn't think that I thought maybe you thought that he didn't have a dick.
No, no, I knew what he does.
He's confused about the pussy thing.
How does he get how does he get pregnant in that movie?
It's somebody fuck his dickhole.
His ass.
Yeah, it's sounding.
Oh, no, no, no.
It's her keeping super.
The advancements of medical science and the super science
and the advancements of medical science in this have
super science. Super science. Okay, now I'm getting it.
Say no more. That's it. The field of study known as super science.
With a simple
force known as black girl magic.
They did black girl magic to Arnold and he became a pregnant
man? It was science. Danny DeVito is a scientist.
Why why did they pick a black woman doctor who did black girl magic to Arnold Schwarzenegger? Oh
that's that's awesome and
That's really awesome
That's so cool, yeah, I
Remember I was saying like I feel like 2009 there was like 15 books about like some
news before like
Anybody in my hometown knew what a trans person was and there was like 15 books by this guy
Who was like the pregnant man, and I feel like everybody was talking constantly about the pregnant man
It was like a work of fiction. No, it was a biography. It was like a
trans guy who got pregnant and
Just kept going on the Daily Show and being
And it was like good morning America. Yeah. Oh, yeah the Oprah. I remember the Oprah episode
He would just go on and be like, yeah be like
surprised
Yeah
That is just
Wasn't
The whole country
I bought the whole country with my Jamaican...
You've had so many bottles thrown at your head out of moving cars.
Literally!
One time I was wearing skinny jeans in downtown Lafayette
and this guy said
"Hey, your jeans are too skinny, fag"
and then I got hit in the back of the head
with a glass bottle.
Dude, I miss when skinny jeans were something that was gay.
Yeah, you know.
That was the best.
Now it's like if you're gay, it's like really hot.
If you're gay now, the biggest pants possible
is what you're looking for.
that
and
Okay, Ben, you wear all white like a professor like maybe like three times in the span of like two months and Jacques remembers me
As constantly wearing all white for you Ben dresses like a liberal
That is a little true you have a flannel this is like Sadie Doyle
Yeah
Welcome welcome to the you to the boys club Sadie or I guess what is what's his?
Grady
I welcome her. She wrote an article about me when I got about you
Was it was it a positive article? Yeah
Positive a t-sadie at the time was like this guy is
So fucking funny. No, it is
She called me like a Bernie bro
Cutting so cool
I hope you know Max, you are one of those Twitter accounts for me because
I'm a big fan of yours.
Can I miss it?
I hope you know, Max, you are one of
those Twitter accounts for me, because
everything you post is like a drill
going into a penis hole.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah. No, literally, I was trying to
scan through your Twitter page.
I was like, why do I follow this guy?
I was like, oh, it's Max.
Yeah, I have that.
Yeah, I do make that impression on
people.
But yeah, who the hell is this person?
A cock.
(laughter)
- My favorite one so far has been
just the guy getting hit in the nuts with a mallet.
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah, that one's been, I've been getting a lot of miles.
- You're the one who posted the guy
shitting out a rubber baby?
- Yep.
- Yes.
- Oh yeah, we saw it.
- That was a perfect one too.
- Who's that guy that does the Pierce Paris?
- Pierce Paris, yeah, the god.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah, literally king of Twitter.
- Honestly, he's so creative.
You said the one of the guy fucking the foreskin.
Oh, oh, yes, yes.
A guy put so much like saline in his foreskin that it's like this big.
And his the tip of his foreskin is like a hole.
And some guy fucks in it and then comes in.
That's his actual that's I think he's on.
I think he's cut.
That's his actual dickhead that's gotten that. No, no, I don't believe.
You got no answer.
Nobody's fucking his urethra.
Oh, I feel brother week right now.
(laughing)
- And honestly, I feel like Westboro Baptist Church
is like paying them to do that.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- It's a gay style.
That makes me like ashamed to be gay.
- Yeah.
- I can't even imagine how straight people
must feel about this.
If I was a straight person and I saw that,
I'd be like, yes, we need to kill them all.
- It's like the circus to me.
- The gay people?
- The gay people, yeah.
(laughing)
- We do be like that.
Like an old timey traveling circus.
Exactly like a freak show.
You put a nickel in a pot and then you get to poke someone with a bamboo stick.
This man fucks other men in their ass!
Be amazed!
And I'm like, wow, that's some funny ass shit, dude.
The crowd gets to guess how many times he's been fucked in the ass.
I don't know, one, maybe two times?
That's basically a punishment to me.
Oh, God bless your soul.
We should do I mean, that's basically what we do is rock.
But oh, yeah, I just like a less side show spectacle for you,
faggots like a circus freak appeal, but that's also so much shit on.
I mean, that's just what Tick-Tock is.
Oh yeah, no, totally.
I made like a talk is just like a modern day.
No, I made five Tick-Tock circus freak show.
Jock has a tick tock. Oh, fuck.
All I do is dance on it.
Jacques Tintouk is next level.
I haven't seen it.
Sincerely, yeah, next level.
I have videos of instructions on how to float.
Oh, like your rafts?
Yeah, down the river on an air mattress.
How to levitate.
[laughter]
Even though I just fled Montana.
Listen up, y'all. This is how you freaking levitate.
I'm trying to find out when exactly the weather is going to be good enough for me to go back
just to float.
There's a flu season.
- Yeah. - In Louisiana?
- No, in... - Oh, in Missoula, Montana.
Yeah, I'm gonna go back to Missoula for like a week
during whenever it's warm enough.
I mean, even if it's like... - Why don't you just float there?
- Hmm. - There's a river everywhere.
- His face, Jacques's face. (laughing)
- You literally considered it.
- What? - I didn't consider nothing.
That was just one of my many strokes.
- I can tell with your like,
go back to Missoula and on the flight back, I'll get groped by
the same flight attendant that did it last time. It's like a
curb your enthusiasm episode gone wrong. Yeah. I mean, that's
just your entire life honestly. Is it a a gentile curb your
curb your enthusiasm. Gone wrong. Gone very. I mean, of
course, it can't go right if it's just a gentile, you know.
I think my life is more adjacent to the golden girls or
the
I'm every and any woman.
What's that little cum dribble on your shirt there, Caleb say?
This is a Monty Python shirt.
Oh, OK. Pretty fucking cool, huh?
I couldn't read that little sploosh.
It doesn't look like cum.
Now it looks like it does.
It does now.
Now that Caleb wears that shirt, Caleb wears that shirt around in public.
I do. I think it's funny.
Yeah, he just cocks his eyebrow and goes like, it's ironic.
Hello.
Oh, do you want to say a quote about...
Good morning America, like the pregnant man.
Oh, so you have anything to say about my shirt?
Yeah, he waits until someone comes up to him,
like some nerd comes up to him and goes like,
"Oh dude, the knights who say 'knee'"
and Caleb just goes, "I don't know what that is."
That's what being cool is, dude.
Yeah.
John Cleese was the original crazy-ass white boy.
He was.
That's some real shit.
There's a crazy discourse.
I know that was that that they blew up.
He tried to return to inherit.
That's a crazy white boy.
Right.
He's tricky.
Hey, that is pretty crazy.
Damn.
If I had a fee shopping shit, if I had been that that cashier, I would have been so I
would have been so funny.
Who's the crazy?
Imagine if you had been works chat.
Can't I can't be binary.
It can't be.
No, can't be max because he's actually not white.
His defense down.
I would say I'm the original crazy ass white boy.
I think Caleb has the most calls from the government.
Me and Jacques might be like this, honestly.
Yeah.
Wow.
I feel like all non-white people would see you, Caleb, and then just see you as the little
bully in the Toy Story movie franchise.
Sid.
I get compared to Sid by, you know, most, a lot of people, mailmen and waitresses.
My mother, my daddy.
Everybody kind of thinks I'm Sid.
It's either Sid or the guy from American History X, so I think you should be.
Or just like, or like, people be like, "Where do I know you from?"
"Oh, you look like a baby I saw yesterday.
Are you that baby?"
And I just have to be like, "No, I'm a man."
- I will say, before I shave my head,
I wouldn't get carded for alcohol.
And then after I shave my head,
I get carded every single time.
And I feel like it's like, do you honestly think
that I'm like a bait?
I'm like a little kid now?
That I don't have any hair?
- Yeah, when they card me at the liquor store--
- You're like a make a wish patient.
- Yeah.
- When they card me at the liquor store--
- You gotta, this is my one wish.
(laughing)
I'm buying two Modellos, 'cause I can't afford a six pack.
- Yeah, every time I go to the liquor store
and I'm trying to buy something,
I'm like, my ID's expired or something,
and they're like,
you look like an old, fat baby that's 50 years old,
but we're gonna give you liquor.
- That's what they say. - That's so rude.
- You need to go to a new liquor store.
- You got a lot of sloppy bitches.
- Are you going to like the Dick's Resort liquor store?
- Hi, welcome to Margaritaville, what can we get you?
- You go to Margaritaville every day?
(laughing)
- Who wouldn't?
- Exactly.
- What do you do for the drinks, dude?
but is it an actual place margarita bill
yeah there's a couple of the universal city walk
of all it went to the one in new orleans but i thought i was going to kill myself
when i was there so i can actually go on the cover because of the restaurant
i mean no one wants to listen to jimmy buffett's music
do there's one in atlanta a little i might have to make it a little i want to
go
you know we can listen to the jimmy buffett i a week of just jimmy
- Wow, Jimmy only, I don't know.
- Were you preparing for something?
- You were fucking an older woman or something?
(laughing)
- I just got really into Cheeseburger in Paradise
and then that one song where he talks about,
he like tries to be serious.
You know that one?
(laughing)
No?
He talks about like a, there's a song that he wrote
that's like about-- - Oh, the one about a veteran?
- Yeah, it's like about a World War II veteran
that he like knows in Florida.
And he like sings a song about that guy's life
and the guy's whole life is like,
he uh... he fuckin like loses i in the war
his wife dies to bombs and veterans are kind of a kind of like for scum
yeah but they said it's a way more tragic it's it's a horrible life his
whole family dies in like he loses his eyes and some shit
and at the end he's just like a classic king it like a florida bar
and he's like
spree alright honestly is pretty cool life
that's what's happening
did you be both of the guys like it is honestly i'm not going to sit here in
Florida and drink with Jimmy.
You just roll with the punches.
Yeah, yeah.
Look, Jimmy's big lesson here was that all veterans are complainers and alcoholics.
It's true.
[LAUGHTER]
And anti-inferiority.
These people still matter, honestly.
Jimmy Buffett.
Yeah.
He rules, dude.
How do they put the veterans on an island away from us?
I think that's Hawaii.
Yeah.
[LAUGHTER]
That's already a place.
Like, Guantanamo.
I feel like a lot--
I guess they're not really veterans if they're there, though.
If I met if I met the guy from one by Metallica, I would tell him to grow up.
Tell me, stop complaining.
You know what he needs to do is just move to Florida.
Darkness and prisoning me.
Dude, you sound like a teenager.
Grow the fuck up. You're an adult.
Come on. I'm from hurt by Johnny Cash.
He's to go to therapy.
That baby from the Nevada.
Stop expecting your your listeners to do the emotional labor
Processing your trauma.
Hey that baby from Nirvana from the Nevermind album is the CEO
of Goldman Sachs.
Now, do you feel old yet?
If you were that baby, is that a meme?
That kid's in the I just made that up.
I just turn that into a meme shot could be funny.
Do you think that Nirvana baby if that happened if you were that
Baby, would you be pissed that your wiener was just always like
God, I'm going to be like the most famous wiener in the world.
I'm not going to be proud forever.
Yeah. In certain circles.
Yeah. In certain islands in the Caribbean.
Big fans of that one album of Nirvana.
And I never listened to it, but I love it.
I love it. No, no, no.
You don't understand.
I like the cover because of the dollar on it.
OK, yeah, I like the money.
OK, we're back on the trips now.
I
Which is like a dating app for girls.
I didn't know either, Caleb.
It's like a VIP dating app where you have to like apply to get into it,
but there's a Jewish one that you apply to get into.
But it's a total ripoff because there's only,
there's probably only like 20 people on it. Maybe only 20 gay guys.
Yeah, there's like 11 people and they're all really annoying.
Like they've all been banned from like Tinder for like calling everyone they've met.
Which gay Jews on a dating app are annoying?
Oh my god, no way.
The thing is, they're not even actually rich.
It's just like a kind of like aspirant class of like young person who...
It's just influencers?
It's the Jewish interns.
Not even. It's like people who are like,
"I'm a young budding CEO in the making."
It's like that, which is horrible when you encounter one of those people.
But then if they're gay and then also Jewish on top of that.
It's like a gay entre...
Are you saying the worst person is a gay entrepreneur?
Yeah, but yeah, no locks love is a scam.
They they charge you money.
You don't even get a part of it.
And they don't even get it.
They don't even mail you.
They don't even mail you locks.
I thought it was like I thought it was like a loot crate.
Yeah, I thought they were going to send me smoked salmon every month.
I got to fuck a guy. What the hell?
This son of a bitch making me talk to gay entrepreneurs.
Oh, I have sex with them.
Now I'm investing in his business?
I thought I was getting fucking salmon!
What the fuck is this?
But they didn't let my black friend on.
So we're gonna cancel.
Wait, do you have to confirm that you're Jewish to get on?
Send them a picture of your cock.
Yeah, just a circumcision scar picture.
I didn't.
I said, I told them I was a philanthropist.
And they were like, close enough?
Yeah.
Yeah, just like philanthropist and small business owner.
I live on the Lower East Side.
on the lower east side.
- That coat is Jewish.
- I don't know. - COVID.
- They didn't let my black friend on,
so like I said, we're going to cancel them.
It's really messed up.
He had his feelings hurt,
and now I'm gonna do like a kind of like
stand and deliver thing.
- Can you believe they let Dan Allegretto on,
but not like your black friend?
- It's like public, what is it, his attorney or whatever,
make my case with my black client.
- You're gonna protect him?
- I'm gonna protect him. - From Lost Club?
do you know i don't know why it is way to some jewish
to jewish asshole lawyers are a very interesting to the show uh... lee
you see them and like
the result is that they'll they let him on but he has to have a little mark on
his profile that's like we were forced to have a look at it
like with the with twitter puts under like trump tweets yet i think i would
like to make a point we were sued at this time you know we did not want this
this
you're doing in their bed
yet everybody's like blood in the smooth them up
boy blood smoothie blood smoothie
now i'm having a the beats me
uh... is wrong with you it's worse i think myself a very good
i love it we mean that's where the only reason it'd be to be so good to have a
it's to have a funny poop
That does scare me though.
They're good.
They scare me every time.
I mean, every time.
I've seen his drug shit split anyway,
so it's not like a big deal.
I did have years for shitting blood and throwing up blood.
I also had a shitting blood period in my life.
Never went to the doctor for it,
just completely ignored it.
Oh, oh my God, really?
(laughing)
Yeah.
I think it was the shitting blood period.
(laughing)
The shitting blood was not so bad.
Caleb's a pregnant man.
I'm not the pregnant man. I'm not gay.
I'm not a baby. I'm not Sid from Toy Story.
I didn't have a bumba clot. Nobody knows what that is, Max.
Is that some Spanish thing, you fucking loser?
Yeah, it is.
Shut up.
It's worrisome when you're spitting blood.
It's only when you're pissing blood or you're throwing up.
That's not true.
What if you're just bleeding from somewhere on your body?
Is that okay?
You can smell it before you...
You're gonna get a cut. You're human.
These bodies aren't hard.
I keep eating needles and broken glass.
We're not made of bugs.
It's kind of fucked up.
I really like the taste of them.
You both just had ulcers then, right?
I think that I had a...
What's it called when you have a thingy on your butthole?
A hemorrhoid?
I think I had a hemorrhoid.
Sometimes I would touch it and it felt so bad but a little good.
Oh my God!
I think you're going to talk about touching your hemorrhoid.
What?
That's okay.
I mean, we've covered hemorrhoids.
It's a bigger...
Hemorrhoids like a male clit.
I had to have...
Like super sensitive red spot.
You just like touch it and rub it a little bit.
That is the male G-spot.
Yeah.
You rub it a little bit like the fucking dot on an old laptop.
You have to do the come Heather motion on the hemorrhoid and then you come.
Exactly, yeah.
I was just sitting in the bathroom fucking shoving, doing the alphabet with my finger
on my asshole.
Spelling hemorrhoid.
Yeah.
And just feeling it.
And I was like, "Oh, I'm gonna have to do that."
And then I was like, "Oh, I'm gonna have to do that."
Exactly, yeah. I was just sitting in the bathroom fucking shoving, doing the alphabet with my
finger on my asshole.
Spelling hemorrhoid.
Yeah, and just feeling amazing.
Free tip to any homosexual listeners to Potrat List, do that on your bottom next time and
they'll not immediately.
First, you got to give them a hemorrhoid.
First, you got to give them hemorrhoids. Ask them to sit in the bathroom on the toilet
for like 20 minutes.
How do you even get one of them?
You get hemorrhoids from sitting too long on the toilet.
Yeah, which I used to love to do.
Oh, I did that too.
Yeah, I definitely.
Honestly, that is so gay.
I would go to the bathroom to jack off,
but for some reason I would like sit on the toilet
like I was taking a shit just in case
somebody walked into the bathroom.
So I was like 15, I didn't want to get caught.
So I'd jack off for like, you know,
eight hours straight sitting on the toilet.
They're like, no, I wasn't jacking off for eight hours.
I was shitting for eight hours.
(laughing)
It's so gay.
Normal in here.
Yeah.
I think I got hemorrhoids from going to the bathroom and going on my phone at work.
Oh dude, that's the best.
When you sit in the 30s.
You always tell a boss that you have IBS.
Because then you just get like 2 hours of an 8 hour shift.
Oh dude, it's the best feeling in the world just in the middle.
Like if you're working front of house and you're the only person there.
Just to leave and go on your phone for 30 minutes and then come back with a huge line.
I'm
but I was like, I was like, what?
He's like, my stomach.
I was like, what do you mean?
And he he was having diarrhea, but he didn't know how to say I'm having diarrhea.
Diarrhea. Isn't that a Spanish word?
Yeah. The role of the diarrhea.
Diarrhea. Diarrhea.
This is my cousin diarrhea.
But I think about that every time I have.
Every time you have a stomach
ache in your butt.
Yeah.
That's so good dude.
I mean, I feel bad for him, you know?
Yeah, I wonder like if I try
to not being able to tell your boss
you have diarrhea.
Yeah, like having to do
like charades with it.
I mean, I would never tell
an employer I had diarrhea
just because I don't want to go through the struggle of having to tell them that.
I tell my employers everything.
You've got to be honest, dude.
That's how I got no jobs.
First thing in the morning, every morning.
Do any of us have a job?
I have a job, but I only got one day left of it.
What do you do for work?
I work at a liquor store.
That is so hot.
- Incidentally, the cool one.
- Yeah.
- Give it up for Cameron.
- He always gets some like stupid beer
and brings it home.
It's pretty cool.
- Yeah, what was that?
You were drinking like a pig destroyer IPA?
- Yeah.
- That's like a grinder bio.
(laughing)
- Pig destroyer IPA.
- I've had that name before.
- Yeah, that's Jacques Grinder.
(laughing)
- Some, a funny guy that came into my work actually,
I was meant to tell you guys.
There was this guy who came in like a day or two ago,
who was this like just insanely fat old guy,
like just like insanely fat.
Like he had a cane 'cause he was so fat.
- Oh, those are the best.
- And he walked in and he was like,
I want a two liter bottle of Pepsi.
And we were like, we don't have,
and we were like, we don't have two liter bottle of Pepsi.
We have a three liter bottle of Pepsi.
He's like, no.
And then he just like walked around the store
looking for a two liter bottle of Pepsi for like five full minutes and even
though like we told him we didn't have it and then finally he bought the three
liter one and he brought it up to the register and he looked at me and he went
I'll drink two liters of this and the other leaders gonna go fucking flat
goddamn dude that is next-level fat you're being you're like so fat you've
Got it down to like a science. Yeah, that's always the best. We're so fat
You're like I know if I have more than two
I can't consume more than two liters of coke and I'm going to be fucking pissed if I have to buy another
Only for it to go flat. Yeah, it's like fat guys who always get fat guys who like always get soda with no ice
Down yeah, yeah
God damn, that's so cool
Dude, you want soda so bad.
I want a lot of warm soda is what I like.
I used to be addicted to soda.
I'd have to get at least one or two 44-ounce fountain drinks from Circle K.
And I would have to get a 44-ounce of Pepsi Max.
And it has 44 milligrams of caffeine for every 12 fluid ounces.
And I would get a 44-ounce and it was just pure aspartame.
I'm not following any of that.
There's too much math in that.
Too many numbers for the process.
That's like only fat guys would say about something fluid ounces.
When you're talking about soda, we know that it's fluid.
Because you're so used to reading the label on the back,
because it's always in your hand,
that you're like, "It's fluid ounces."
I really appreciate the really experienced fat guys like that,
like that, but like understand that, okay, like the human
stomach can only, you know, handle two liters of liquid at
any one time. But I really do have a soft spot for like the
the beginner fat. So the ones that like, oh yeah, I'll chug
eight beers and you know, in five minutes and try not to
throw up. Yeah, exactly. Chris Farley died choking from beer.
He had too many beers. Yeah. And he he popped like a balloon.
What was the uh...
They just throw up foam.
Oh dude that's the those fucking chug videos where like the fat guys drink like the
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
Those are just the guys from the family
Yeah yeah
Shout out to them
I was just watching those again the other night
They're like the funniest fucking thing
Oh my god
The one where he starts working out and just
Yes yes
to
the weirdest person to just like spot yeah he there's a like oh fuck that's
like a that eats cactus bouncing Rachel Joe is all at a Mardi Gras parade in New
Orleans in 2018 you saw Rachel 2017
I saw Rachel at Mardi Gras.
At Mardi Gras?
(laughter)
Rachel told us she went to Mardi Gras in 2018.
2017.
That is literally the last place she would be.
No, no, no, no, no, no. 2017.
She just, I mean, she just likes marches.
That's like how she got into that whole situation.
(laughter)
She goes for her sheer love of parades.
Yeah.
No, but I swear, a few of my friends pointed...
You did not.
No, a few of my friends pointed her out.
is
Okay
She's Rachel Dolezal, it's literally just like a National Geographic
Nope that's Mardi Gras
Look y'all can y'all can say whatever you want. She was there
It's cool. Oh, yeah the shoe nice comment was it's like hey shoe nice
What's the hardest challenge you had to do and he replied it said probably probably leaving my wife and kids
Please psycho
He's doing it yeah, he does a left for a while yet a hiatus shoe nice is on cameo
Wow, no way. Yeah, you can you can pay him to eat something for you. All right, I think I figured out several Christmas presents
Make him eat from him. I remember like just whole handles of vodka. He ate a cactus one time
Mm-hmm. I like when he's deodorant. Yeah, you that 15 bucks. He's so good at that
Shock 15 bucks for a shoe nice game. Look I haven't my god. That's nothing
I have enough stomach problems risking eating at the Quiznos across the street or eating at the Domino's next door to me
I mean, I think I think I can have asking for those problems.
We shock shock you live.
You live next to the first Quiznos ever.
I live to I live.
I can look directly out of my window at night and I mean, it's huge.
Well, you're famous.
When I was this is an insane thing to see on your counter.
Yeah, I know. I know.
Saltines, honey, bunch of oats and a blow towards.
I got poisoning from Quiznos and then I had.
I literally heard you say I got poop poisoning from Quiznos.
I basically got food poisoning from Quiznos and then I went and...
I've never had Quiznos. You can just tell from the branding it's trash.
I loved Quiznos when I was like 8.
It was awful. I love Subway but that was bad.
Do you guys remember those commercials they had?
Yeah, the baby.
The baby that says "I'm toasty."
is
that
the
You were so into the commercial that you went to the website?
No. No.
You didn't even go to the website, you just knew about it.
So you, yeah, you...
Let me explain. Let me explain why I fucking know this.
Okay.
'Cause the Spon... Okay, so the Spongebunkees were a website, they had a song about how they liked the moon,
and then from the fucking, like, the pop...
Because remember, like, back in, like, 2004, like, any time that there was, like, a viral video or anything,
It was like, okay, we need to give this a TV show or a commercial or something.
So from the popularity of Spongebunkees.com, they got the Quiznos commercial,
where they sing about subs instead of the moon.
That's... wow. I'm learning so much.
That's so smart of you, Patrick. You should have a Pod About List spinoff where you just cover
like the... 2000 stuff from 2004.
In ads. Y'all, when Ben said, I didn't know
those things had names. I thought he was talking about gay people or Patrick.
Why would I say that?
I don't know those things had names.
No, SpongeMonkey. Oh yeah, that's cool though.
Also a very convenient name for either Patrick or gay people.
Every time Patrick talks about food, I see our parallels.
You guys do look alike.
- Hey, hold up.
You look like brother and sister.
- Hey, what's up?
(laughing)
- Is that how Pat sounds to you?
- Jacques just looks like the FaceTimed age.
(laughing)
- When I did first cut my hair,
I think we were on FaceTime and they told me
that I did look more like Jacques.
(laughing)
- That's beautiful.
- You're kind of slowly turning into the same person.
- Once I get the vaccine, I'm gonna pop over to Maryland
and get two lobsters for $6.
I
and
You have like a little newscaster moment.
Well look, this is what their faces look like now permanently.
[Laughter]
They look like Twitter liberals now for like...
So I saw that too.
I don't think I'll have a permanent soy face.
Apparently it's not permanent.
No, it's only like two weeks.
But the funniest fucking thing I saw was under that on Twitter.
Somebody was like, "This is actually caused by a mini stroke that these people are having."
So it's causing a mini stroke and then somebody was like, no, it isn't like,
what are you talking about? And she was like, well,
I had this happen to me and the doctor said that I had a stroke.
So you just fucking had a stroke then
because I'm currently having a stroke.
There,
there was a time where I did get too fucked up on some stuff like in the last
few years and my face did stop on one side.
My face was stuck and drooped on the right side.
Whoa, and I my eye was fucked up and I was like, what the fuck and I woke up the next day and it was normal.
But I was like, I went to bed crying.
I was like, I'm going to look like this forever.
That was probably a really funny looking cry.
Yeah, on one side.
They're not even coming out as tears.
It's just like just water trickling as a solid stream.
That's like when Bradley Cooper was in the Elephant Man play.
Yeah.
And he just made a stupid face.
Yeah, he just went...
Yeah.
Wait, so cool.
He did that and then put his arm up like this.
That was...
Yeah, didn't even try to do prosthetics.
The best part of him, the prosthetics on that one.
It's the power of theater, dude.
It's the power of acting.
The best part of theater.
I didn't even know that he did that.
Like a live action Elephant Man?
Yeah, that was like in 2018.
Did he even use like prosthetics or anything?
No.
just like, it's so funny to go from doing like the hangover to doing live action.
Right? Yeah. Honestly, the funniest thing Bradley Cooper has ever done is when he committed
suicide on the Lady Gaga movie. I'm gonna tell this story and you're gonna start screaming
and interrupt me but don't you didn't even see that because I saw a star is born with
you in the movie theater and you left before you could see the climax which is Bradley Cooper
were dying because you wanted to go yell at the woman working at the counter because they
didn't bring you the donuts on time.
Bring the donuts, period!
Bring the donuts!
Dude, thank god Jacques unplugged the mic while you were talking.
I have because I know what's gonna set him off but this is exactly what happened.
You say that that's your favorite scene, you literally, you didn't even see it, bitch.
left you were gone for like 30 minutes and me and Stephen were just watching the movie being like
where is Jacques and then we left and the lady locked you out because you left to go smoke a
cigarette and then she locked the door after you left because you complained to her about not having
your donuts delivered in time for the climax of the movie. I paid for the donuts! I wanted them!
I paid for them! Yeah I mean you're right to you know you I'm guessing you ordered the donuts at
the beginning of the movie? Of course, of course I did. What movie theater has donuts? This
Alamo Draft House. You ordered them at last call. Either way, I ordered them. It's last
call, it's not no call. That's a really good point. Did you pay for the donuts? Yes, and
no one has donuts. And he complained about it and then got free tickets for other movies.
Yeah, I got free tickets for like three months. Yeah, there you go. Whoa. I would be focused
- I saw "Assassination Nation" four times in theaters.
'Cause I was like, "Damn, this movie is good."
Did y'all see that?
- I saw that movie. - What?
- That's what you did with your free movie tickets?
- I thought it was all right.
- Yeah, I also thought it was okay.
- It was like, at the time,
I thought it was just the best movie.
I was like, "Wow."
- "Assassination Nation?"
- Yes.
- You know the word "assassination," Caleb?
- Yeah, okay, I follow.
- Abra's in it as an actress.
that
part
that you know this is a good thing for it were like i was ready to get your
trigger dot why yeah i mean i mean it are enough in it
where is a list of the the trailers really super edgy
yes it is very good
alternative ready your safe space it was here's our area
the park
the park renews the city and where did it
come on
it would be funny to see her do like a...
it's about fucking time she did
yeah
yeah for her to just become like a
like a lauren southern character
would rule
like one of the...
like bill maher type that's like
oh i guess you're all triggered at my intellect
yeah
harry neff in the remake of
the gone with the wind
i know
that doesn't track
Yeah, it was Bill Maher and he is.
He is. That's why he made that comment about being a house.
Sometimes you just slips in the characters to an actor.
Well, who should be persecuted?
Yeah, who should be persecuted?
Robin Williams.
You think Robin Williams should be persecuted?
the
to
- Yeah, she was still up on a doorknob.
- I know. - Epstein style.
- Beast mode, dude.
- I could say a really sad story, but I won't.
But I basically--
- Is it about Robin Williams?
- Yeah, one of my parents' friend's child
was 11 years old and--
- My parents' friend's child.
- Was 11 years old and committed suicide
at the same time as Robin Williams
after he committed suicide because he committed suicide
and he was her hero.
- Whoa.
Oh, so that's why I have a vendetta against them.
Because I can't like coolest.
Yeah, that he should.
So anyway, the reason I got a point is because I was looking
out of touching that one.
I was looking out of my out of the the big jury.
When I'm looking I'll create a copycat.
I was looking at the quiz.
No, the next next to the quiz knows there's this ugly disgusting
stupid ugly.
But are you on your own?
Are you on 14th and Grant a 13th and Grant?
But yes, okay.
It's a mural of Robin Williams.
Oh, I remember. Wait, that's still there?
Yeah, it's done so poorly.
It says, "We're gonna miss you, Robin."
Yeah.
They have one of those in Harvard Square.
They have like a Mrs. Doubtfire mural.
Yeah, they do it after you die.
It's so much cooler.
Mrs. Doubtfire also committed suicide.
[laughter]
After I looked at the mural,
I googled
Robin Williams as
cerebral palsy actor because I thought he had to have had a movie where he played
as someone with cerebral palsy. Wait, what was the Google search? I Google searched
Robin Williams cerebral palsy actor. Just to clarify, that's the actor Robin Williams and not the professor with cerebral palsy.
I'm looking at this mural and I'm like how did Robin Williams have
cerebral palsy and I didn't know. That's like, did you think he had cerebral palsy?
I don't know. It's on the mural. If you could see the mural. It's all about the mural.
You thought he died from cancer. He was not even suicided. Like, oh, clearly he died from
cerebral palsy. No, but the picture, there's nothing wrong with people.
Jacques, what are these? Do you have those Buddhist flags up behind you?
This is not, this is my, I'm staying at a friend's apartment.
I'm living in a living room.
It looks a little too functional for you.
Yeah.
What do you mean?
Yeah, it's not messy enough to be a Jean-Claude.
I'm guessing the blowtorch is yours.
Yeah, you can see my mattress on the floor.
That's mine.
And a fruit bowl.
That's what I'm talking about.
Yeah, looks like a nice place.
I love the celebrity murals, especially in LA.
There's one that's like,
it's like,
the Armenian Genocide.
It's my favorite mural.
It reminds me of the Armenian Genocide.
There's one that is like it's like it says like lost legends and it's it says
has Nipsey Hussle, Juice WRLD, Little Peep, and Anthony Bourdain.
[Laughter]
Yeah, it's so good.
They rock.
They should add Dr. Sebi to that.
XXXTentacion and like Anthony Bourdain.
[Laughter]
I was reading some celebrity article about celebrities doing drugs.
Celebrity article about celebrities?
the
like
on
a
I think it's an alien.
And so having sex with a 14 year old or something.
Well, yeah, he was married to Asia Argento.
I think they were partners.
So I don't think they were married.
And she's I don't even know who she is.
She has a very funny name that reminds me of cheese.
Asia. She's of the of the Argento cheese.
Yeah. Dario's daughter.
She's Dario's. Wait, really?
Oh, listen, hello.
That's how she's Italian.
Of course, she's fucking a 14 year old.
Listen to this though, yeah, she got, she got,
so she was on a movie called
The Heart is Despicable Above All Things.
So sometime in the 2000s,
and it was an art house movie where she plays like
a drug addicted, horrible whore mother,
who like that, like a prostitute.
- She plays a stupid whore.
- But listen to this.
- And it's just like a mother.
- She gets custody.
- It's just a dumb, dumb whore.
- No, listen, listen.
She gets custody of her child again,
and she brings the child across the United States
and convinces him to be a child prostitute
as well as she's prostituting.
And Marilyn Manson is an actor in this movie
and fucks the child.
- When did this come out?
- It's just like a dream you had.
- No, no, this is a real Aja Argento movie.
And then apparently the young kid
that was the actor in the movie
ended up having a sexual relationship with Aja Argento
as soon as he turned 18.
Well, that's kind of, yeah.
So it's, it's dementia.
There's triple X too.
That's weird.
Yeah, no, she was, I think she should be canceled for being on in that fucking
shit of a movie, that massive fucking turd.
That's one of my favorite movies of all time.
How could you say that?
It's too, I think.
And triple X is one of the best movies of all time.
That's terrible.
Was she in the sequel?
Not in the sequel.
She gave up on it.
Oh my the sequel so much better
It's been diesel yeah, I remember that Vin Diesel was really hot in that movie when I was a kid. Oh my god
Come on wake up the band orbital is playing in the club scene at
The triple X movie. I've never seen triple X. Oh you was orbital. Okay. Okay. Never mind. That's fucking sick, dude
I think I heard some we every watch you know what we're gonna do what for triple for triple X here
what Felix just did to Avatar.
Everyone's like, Avatar's a piece of shit.
All those blue monkeys keep like fucking with their ponytails or whatever.
And now it's like, oh, my God, it's so revolutionary.
It's it's it's this Marxist thesis on like capitalism and shit or whatever.
People do cosplay of Avatar or secretly wanting to do blackface.
Try to convince.
Explain your
I think we could just leave it on that.
I don't even need to hear an explanation on that one.
I'm saying that without being cancelled.
So don't explain that.
Yeah.
[LAUGHTER]
I'm just saying--
No.
[LAUGHTER]
It just looks--
It looks--
We're going to save you from yourself here on the episode.
Yeah.
Cut it out then.
There's no--
[LAUGHTER]
No shot.
No.
No, he's scared.
You get to cut that out.
He's scared.
No.
Can I just have one?
Can I have one sentence to just clarify?
- You have one word.
- Yeah.
- Can not be here.
- What I was trying to say is that
I see a lot of white people on Tinder
in full cosplay of Avatar.
- What?
- No you don't.
- When?
- You're just lying.
- I am not lying.
- I wanna see where this goes.
- Now you're scared of people.
- Okay, I'm sorry, we interrupted you.
- No, I'm just kidding.
- I just see these people.
- I wanna see these people too.
(laughing)
- And normally they have, they even in the costume.
- I guess it's gay guys and straight women that you see.
- Yes, so I really, I have screenshots of it on my old phone.
There's three different people I found on Tinder.
- You're gonna need to produce a lot of documents
for the things you said on this.
Rachel Dolezal and a dashiki.
- That's, that's--
- I'll upload a dossier.
- It's true, I have no reason to lie.
- Okay, keep going.
- Anyway, I just see these people in there,
they have what dreads and they are posting all of this,
like woke ass nonsense,
like just like relating that they're like,
they are the ultimate cause fighting against racism,
but they have white dreads or something like, you know, the type of person.
I feel like there are only like nine people though. And where does avatar wait?
Yeah. Do you think that just like,
so anytime you see a white person dreadlocks, you're like,
You think that they're good?
Listen, we love we all love Avatar.
They had a little much.
They had Avatar cosplay in their pictures of 10.
Oh, they had normal pictures and then they would get to an Avatar cosplay picture.
And I'm like, are you kidding me?
How many?
And this seems like an isolated incident.
This is not like this at least three or four.
And also, yeah, once you get past three.
Also, I'm just going to say this, you know, there's like people who are clearly like on
the
I
Alright, well thanks for coming on.
[Laughter]
Take it off! Take it off!
No, there's no chance.
No.
As long as I don't sound cancelable, I'm good.
You won't. It's okay.
I'm just giving you shit.
Go listen to Seeking Derangements.
They're the best. Thank you so much.
We love them. Thank you guys for coming on.
And if you're not already listening to Pods About Lists,
then you don't have to.
I'm literally listening to it right now.
Bye y'all.