Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
- Premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase
a premium membership immediately.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- So what's your McPortant news?
- McPortant news.
- He said McPortant news.
- I didn't say that.
- You did say that.
- Well, if I did, it wasn't on recording,
so it doesn't matter.
- The Shamrock Shake.
- I do have huge news right off the bat.
- Yeah.
- The lady at the post office today called me Papa.
- I love it when she calls me Papa.
Papa Papa, it was weird. Was she a young was she your grandchild? No, she obeyed
me like a isn't that weird? Isn't that not what you would expect? Was she like
Papa? I will know it wasn't like that. She said, are you? She just said Papa
was she maybe one to two feet tall? No, she was taller than that. She's taller
than you know than one to two. She was taller than you. Supermodel. No, she
through a window that they used to protect the I guess did she have a
picture of her grandfather taped on the window no didn't see the maybe you
maybe it was like her grandfather maybe it was a one-way picture a one-way
picture I guess it could be I mean I guess a one-way picture could just be a
picture taped to the other side of but like maybe you could see fully through
it it's transparent on one side right now what do you say go go go my breast
smelled like arugula why I ate a bunch of arugula okay that's got to be the
most interesting story I've ever heard. I had myself a chicken Italian
sandwich. Chicken Italian. Yeah I didn't have any lunch yet. So why did she call you
Papa? I don't know. That's I mean I it was pretty she yeah I don't I don't know.
Is she your baby? No. You're sure? I'm completely certain. I think. Is that your
grandbaby? No. I think you gotta go pick that young girl up. No she wasn't
young she's saying you're letting her work a full-time job and you're her
Papa if I what okay if I was her Papa which I don't think I am I'm pretty sure
I'm like 98% sure maybe she thought maybe she thought I would make her work
as your time job you would you hand over to her a package a package and could it
be mistaken for a gala no it was not it would not have been mistaken for a gift
because it had an address on it that I think was not her address but what if it
was and she was like oh this is my papa giving me a gift. I guess maybe she lives with my
dad now and she saw my dad's address on the package. Secret love child of your father's
and he did the reverse of like you know when somebody has a... Well then wouldn't she call
me... No listen she would call you "Bru". You know when somebody has a kid too young
and then they get raised like siblings? Yeah. You know? So he did the reverse of that. He
He had a kid and he's old as fuck and he said that he's her brother and that you're both
of their dad.
Yep.
That makes complete sense.
See, and you know what?
Let me come up with that kind of brain power.
I solved the white side of the Rubik's.
There's a buzzing bug over there.
I don't want that.
It's far away.
I solved the white side of the Rubik's Cube.
Guys, look at this.
I would never be distracted by that.
Oh, it was only one side?
I thought, or did you solve the whole thing earlier?
Or it was always just this side?
No, no, I got halfway through the video so I only solved this.
Well, if you hadn't said anything just now, I would have always assumed that you just solved
solved it all because I earlier when you showed me just the white side, I
assumed you solved it all because you said look and you showed where you like
that was cool. I was like that was I was actually very impressed. I got
quickly, but now I
thing is putting one side no, not the white side and not in the way that you
have to do it because you have to go are our prime
you and you prime you prime. So that's a you didn't even know that you for
R U and then R prime U prime.
- R U prime?
Are you in your prime?
- I'm basically in my prime mentally these days.
- I think you're past your prime for doing Rubik's cubes.
I think that's a--
- I was never Chinese.
(laughing)
I was never like a Chinese 13 year old,
so I haven't hit my prime yet.
- Dude, there's a--
- I don't think you're going to be.
- Yeah, I mean, maybe one day I could be reincarnated.
I believe in that.
- There's a, in every community college I've gone to,
kid with a Rubik's cube walking around solving that shit.
- I don't think I've ever seen anybody
with the Rubik's Cube past like middle school.
- There was a kid--
- And then if I saw somebody do it in high school,
I would be like, there's something wrong with that person.
- There was a kid at Manchester Community College,
his name was Justin, he would sit there
and solve it with one hand.
He had emo bangs, he was in my English class,
John Buzzle's English class.
And then there was a different kid
at Lakes Region Community College
who would sit in the cafeteria and fucking solve that shit.
- I mean, it's fun.
I'm gonna finish the video today.
- They do speed, they do.
You can do like a speed solve though.
Yeah, no, I know.
Yeah.
It's crazy.
Yeah, it's-
Yeah, I've seen a lot of- I've seen- I've seen- the thing about a Rubik's cube though is that I guess
I'm trying to get across is I've seen 12 year olds do it in 10 seconds.
Yeah, definitely. It's pretty-
And I-
It's-
Yeah.
I wouldn't say it's easy, it's just you have to learn it.
You know?
I mean, anybody could- you could teach a chimp how to solve it.
I don't think I could-
It's kind of like if I were-
I don't think-
It's like if I-
I could-
I don't think you could get through the video.
Me?
Yeah.
I think if you gave me like six months I could do it.
Six months?
It's a ten minute video.
Yeah.
Honestly, I will give you fifty dollars if you learn how to solve a Rubik's Cube.
In six months?
Yeah.
Okay.
I'll send you fifty bucks.
I just feel like it's the...
You sent me ten for sniffing your poop pants yesterday?
The poop stain on your pants?
Yep.
If you guys didn't hear that, go listen to the regular episode from Wednesday.
I want to get that stain out of those pants so bad.
Did you think that maybe I was gonna sniff it out?
- Yeah. - Sniff it clean?
- I thought that you had a shout nose.
- Then don't.
- Or tied to go nose.
- Yeah, no I didn't.
But if you can solve a Rubik's Cube,
and you can't, six months you could even
maybe reverse engineer a thing that only you can solve,
but I just don't think that you have it in you
to watch that 10 minute video.
- I think I could.
- I think that's the big barrier.
I think you can physically and mentally solve a Rubik's Cube,
think the 10 minute video is a huge barrier.
I think I think it's not what if I don't watch this account if I don't watch the
video? Yeah. Oh okay. I thought the video was a big. It's just boring. I think you're
not gonna make it. It doesn't seem necessarily like a fun thing to solve.
Well the video is boring but then when you get it when once you start doing fun
to do. R prime U R prime U prime. You're like oh shit this is kind of fun.
There's like a this is like a crossword. Does prime mean counterclockwise? Yes. Then why
Why not just say that?
Because how many syllables?
It's faster.
Yes, there's more syllables than counterclockwise.
Yeah, but it makes more sense.
So U and R is right and up or something?
CCW.
Yeah, so it's the right.
If you're facing it, it's this axis and the up is that one.
Yeah.
So it's R U R prime U prime.
I guess I feel like solving a Rubik's Cube is kind of like doing like a hundred jump rope
jumps in a row where it's maybe it's maybe interesting but I don't that's
going to be honestly and I respect you a lot that's gonna be maybe your all-time
worst analogy yeah yeah that's really thinking of something that I don't like
an elementary school or middle school kid might do oh that's like impressive at
the time and then I've I see an adult doing it I'm like okay I didn't say
jumping jacks that jump rose said jump rope he said jump I did not say you are
you are looking you're a doofus he said jump roping jacks
he said that you are you are looking at so hard that i don't remember if you
said jump roping jacks we already had them on this being a bad analogy we didn't have
to we didn't have to make up things to make it easier you said jump roping jacks
we already had them pinned do i jump roping jacks i guess i must have said
jump roping jacks. That would be a worse analogy, baby.
That's got to exist. Yeah, that's the worst. I just mean that if I saw an adult
doing it, I'd be like, I guess that's technically kind of cool, but I don't
really care. Yeah, well, I mean, if you see a kid doing jump ropes, you're like...
As a kid, that's cool to see a kid do 100 jump ropes. I guess that might... In
my elementary school, we had a thing where we would... There was one gym class
a year where everyone would do a jump rope challenge and they would put up
the high scores on the wall. So maybe that's something in my mind.
Did you have a juggling unit in your gym? No, but I had no. There were a bunch of kids
who went to circus camp. I wish I did. What? It's crazy. Circus camp? Yeah, where they
teach you to tightrope and juggle and stuff. Yeah, we had a juggling unit and we had to
watch these videos where we would juggle my second grade teacher. Actually, no, maybe
we did. Now that I'm thinking about it. My second grade teacher, Mr. Larravie, had a
jump roping or fucking juggling unit and we had to watch this video where it's
like we wouldn't juggle balls we never did that we juggled scarves like yeah
yeah you are you're bringing back a memory I'm pretty sure I also did when I
was in when I was like 13 14 like first year high school maybe I was just like
really interested in joining the circus and I was looking into the like Barnum
at Bailey like Clown College yeah but they closed in like 2011 or something 97 is
that what it was Steve was the last graduating class I really I was like I
found out about it I was like oh my god that's so fucking sick I could learn to
like do a unicycle I don't have to do school anymore I can start when I'm 16
and then yeah it was wasn't it didn't exist anymore now and then I found out
that if you want to be a clown now you got to go to France and you got a cry
gold gold there and there's no you know you're showing up and it did none of
there's not bullshit there's a squirt we're an easy way for kids to run away
and join the circus nowadays what I think maybe you could technically run away and
join the circus right now but it's definitely it's - I would go do that I
feel like you used to have maybe back in the day you could just go just walk into
the circus and you then go away with you were ugly enough but now they're all but
now there's you know it's there's a vent brights for the circus there's uh
the circus was supposed to blow in exactly and now it's like they
they have they've permanent circuses yeah you can't run away with the circus was
supposed you're supposed to be there should be one the hell this wasn't here
yesterday there should be maybe 10 circuses that are like
they're like government programs where they they go across the country and any
kid who wants to be a clown or a freak can just go into it and that's okay and
their parents aren't allowed to look for them
Yeah, exactly. You give up.
Yeah, and it's like a legal thing.
Yeah, and then like officially it's a legal thing.
And maybe you can still...
Yeah, it's completely illegal. No, it's a legal thing.
But then...
You have to keep up, Pat. You got to clean your ears out today.
You'll cross off like the...
I do have some gunk in my ear today.
You'll cross off the like missing...
I have a lot of gunk in here.
The missing child thing, you know, they say like assumed dead or whatever,
then they'll do like assumed clown, assumed...
Yeah, exactly.
Assumed trapeze artist, assumed mime.
That's the worst thing a parent can do.
And that's based on like just looking at them.
you know somebody with skinny kid long face big ears mime yeah right news a
parent could get about their missing kid is assumed human cannonball yeah yeah
well who what do you each of our right yeah what do you guys think that we
would be in the circus lion bearded lady you would be a bearded lady you would be
an easy bearded lady because you have a pretty lips and beautiful eyelashes and
a beard yeah if we put big fake Minnie Mouse eyelashes on you and we gave you a
I guess I'm thinking maybe I might be the ringleader.
No you can't choose ringleader.
Ringleaders are- I think I might be the ringleader.
Ringleaders are not- you can't choose them.
I think I might run away to join the circus and become a ringleader.
You'd be so shit at the circus.
They would probably already have a ringleader.
No I'm gonna run away to the circus and be like I'm your new ringleader.
No you'd need to do a lot of stretching.
The way to become the ringleader is you have to kill the old ringleader.
It's very easy to kill someone at the circus.
Really?
Probably.
Yeah you just- They got all sorts of stuff there.
literally swords and stuff yeah yeah you're in a paper that's the easiest
way to kill somebody is it cloth it's paper okay it's complete printer paper
yeah yeah well are the the new circus that we're developing that steals
children to give them a better life it's all paper it's hearts
that they can't they get no Wi-Fi the whole circus tent is a is a raster bait
poster what what you remember that so what a what I don't know what I'm talking
about we're talking about kidnapping children also the same life hacker yeah
that was a goes a or not it was a gawker really website yeah life hacker life
hacker yeah there cuz I remember there was one or is like here's a kataku and
poster it's been around of printer paper and it was a thing and the process is
called rasturbation and then there's also another video where it's like how to
turn your iPod into a taser.
Life hacks used to be like, here's how to make a bomb with a water bottle.
Remember the one...
Drain on aluminum foil.
It was like how to make your guitar into a real Guitar Hero controller.
It was like, yeah, this is a pretty easy process and it involved soldering.
Once you hit the, when you were a kid, once you hit the solder or the dremel, you're like,
I don't know what that, I don't know how to buy that.
I feel, I guess it's probably well trodden ground at this point, but it's so funny that
so many life hacks are just like, you just like see it, like they'd be like, this is
the most useful thing ever, and it'd be like how to make a cup out of a milk carton, or
like just completely just, here's what to, here's how to keep a piece of trash in your
house.
We had a book when I was a kid that was like, how to build robots with everyday things, and
was like duct tape and like hangers and stuff to like build robots but then
that's just how to build the outside of it and then the inside you still had to
know how to make a fucking robot and it didn't give you any instruction on that
it was just like so first you you get a cardboard box you covered in duct tape
you apply the hangers so it looks like a head and then you just put a pro a robot
programmed robot fully in that and wheels on the bottom I had a Lego book
that was like that? Yeah I remember my friend had the Lego robot thing.
That thing was so sick. I wanted that so bad. Not the robotic stuff but like there was this
Lego thing where it's like it comes with like rubber bands it was like a Lego.
Yeah. It came with the the amount of pieces that you need for like
the first six pages of the book and then the next couple pages are like all right.
So we're assuming you have Legos at home so here like you need these pieces and I didn't have any
any of the pieces.
Dude, all these fancy Lego sets when you were a kid, don't spend a hundred bucks.
They're ending up stuck in my ear anyway, okay?
I'm going to fucking miss ninth grade.
When I was a kid, I had those.
Did you guys know about snap circuits?
They're like...
Oh, wait.
My cousin had those.
Yeah, they're like little snap buttons, like pieces that have pieces of circuits on them
and you can build little circuits and stuff.
It would be like, you can make a light turn on.
You can make...
There's one where it made this disc shoot into the air.
when you like turn the switch. That shit was so fun and I almost started a fire so many
times because it's that you just create a short, you just can just, there's a battery
piece and you just put two wires on it and it starts to smell really bad.
Yeah, I just had an easy bake oven. I was preparing for a much different life.
I had a, my mom bought me Shrinky Dinks once because I was watching, I was really watching
a lot of--
You don't know Shrinky Dinks?
Yeah.
Dude, I didn't have--
I was watching a lot of I Love the 70s and stuff.
Shrinky Dinks?
They did Shrinky Dinks at my like school after school program.
They did it one time.
Yeah.
You know what?
I need a special oven for Shrinky Dinks.
Yeah.
I try to put them in the normal oven.
I try to put them in at like a hundred degrees for like an hour and they all curled up in
a little ball.
What is a Shrinky Dink?
It's like you draw on like a plastic sheet and then you put it in a special oven and it
shrinks.
Yeah.
That's it.
It shrinks down to like this big.
It makes like a little like a charm.
You shrink it?
Yeah.
And then you can put it on a bracelet.
Do you dink it too?
No, that's just a cute word they add in to make it sound fun for kids.
It's a cute dinking?
Yeah.
It gets acutely dinked?
Dinking is when the curling.
It's a Spanish toy, so it's shrink-y dink.
Shrink and dink.
Yeah.
Okay.
Huh.
Yeah.
and they fucking curled up in the oven.
I got every one of my toys from the arcade.
Yeah.
Pretty much.
Arcade toys are bustin' bustin'.
They really are.
I used them one time.
One of my favorite ones.
It teaches you to appreciate them more because you earned them.
One of the best arcade toys I think is when it's just a rubber little dome thing.
You turn it inside out and then you just wait and then it shoots up into the air.
Like a snapper.
We called them poppers down in the dirty south.
I called them that little thing.
You know what the best one was?
Was the fleshlight that they would give you.
Yeah.
the one the rubber one filled with gel that was it teaches you about
infinity in my brain. That's a dentist toy in my brain. That's
I think those are probably the same thing that you put on your
penis. Yeah, I think I see this toy. The parachute man is a
dentist toy for the best, but the number one dentist toy to
me is the is the sticky hand, but I think that's also an
arcade toy. Yeah, I love the parachute. You're going to be
there. She managed a key hand. We used to go to the tower at
in Mount Auburn Cemetery and throw the parachute man down.
We used to go to the top of the Empire State Building and throw them all.
That's completely not true.
Yeah, I lied, guys.
You completely lied.
I just thought it would be fun to lie to you guys.
It really made me feel bad, actually.
You should feel bad.
Yeah, that wasn't very nice.
I don't think I want to lie anymore.
I would appreciate it if you didn't.
I think I'm going to stop lying.
Thank you.
Yeah, but my dad is just dead.
He died today.
He died this morning.
That's awesome.
So I need some money from both of you.
I mean I have a, I think I have one dollar in my wallet.
Do you want that?
You only have one dollar in my wallet?
I lied again.
He was in debt.
I left my wallet at home.
You lied again?
I just left my wallet at home.
I was about to give you money.
I've never done that.
You actually left your wallet at home?
Actually left my, look.
Can I pat you down?
Get up.
Get up right now.
Alright.
I'm going to start, I'm going to do a standard TSA patting, okay?
So I'm starting, sir, I've got to go.
Do a lot of rubbing so it picks up on the mic.
This is BBC News. We're interrupting our schedules for the following announcement.
Buckingham Palace has announced the death of Her Majesty Queen Elizabeth II.
A statement from the Palace said, "The Queen died peacefully at Balmoral this afternoon.
The King and the Queen Consort will remain at Balmoral this evening and will return to
London tomorrow."
way. He's tickling. If you were at the TSA and you did that, they would shoot you. That
is a ploy. They would shoot you on sight. No wallet. Give me your new hat. No, what? That's
scary. I'm going away. He touched my hat. I had to attack him. That's not how it works.
I'm going to attack you with this. Yeah, you don't have your wallet on you. Yep. I'll tell
you that much right now. Well, you do have a hammer. That's two episodes in a row where
we stood up. Yeah. I think we might be moving towards a new kind of standing up. A physical
standing kind of. A standing podcast. Do you guys want to stand for the rest of the episode?
Watch this.
What?
I brought my tap shoes.
We can't see.
You're standing in such a way.
Yeah, I mean all I can see is your upper body and it's your just.
You sound exactly like a horse.
That's like crazy.
Yeah.
You have a gallop to you.
Sounds just like the clopping of a horse.
It sounds a lot like a horse, yeah.
You know what sounds more like a horse?
I am wearing my horse shoes.
I learned from a movie, Coconuts.
Huh.
Huh, there's a sir. There's a movie that's that talks about that really yeah, it's a documentary the movie. Yeah
The documentary about coconuts. Yeah that I watched
Coconut I called the story of coconut. He's ever just gotten a coconut just split it open to eating it
No, no like a fucking like Tom Hanks. No, no, no
It's really hard to open one though, yeah, don't you have to like you like a buzzsaw?
Yeah, yeah, and you when you were like six or seven
And you started learning about like exotic fruit.
Mm-hmm.
That's what they usually, that's part of the curriculum.
Second grade.
That's when I started learning about exotic fruit.
I wanted to eat every single exotic fruit.
And I think I made my parents buy a pineapple.
Yeah.
Just not that exotic.
Yeah, I feel like, yeah.
I eat a lot of pineapple.
You know about pineapple instantly, I think.
Yeah, you know about pineapple instantly, but then like...
Because of Spongebob.
Guava, passion fruit.
Fruit salad.
I don't know, I couldn't even tell you what those look like.
Yeah, me neither, honestly.
Dragon fruit.
- The dragon fruit and star fruit,
I've been seeing in my grocery store,
and I'm really tempted to buy it,
but I'm scared that I would eat the wrong part of it
'cause I don't know.
- I eat a dragon fruit pretty easy.
- The thing about those kinds of fruits
is if they were that good,
they would be as popular as apples.
- That's true, I agree with that.
A dragon fruit has to be boring.
It probably tastes like nothing, right?
- Yeah.
- Eighth grader, it doesn't taste that great.
- Exactly, there can't be,
if it did taste good, everyone would eat it.
- It tastes, I mean, it tastes good.
- I wanna try it. - But if it tasted like--
- You know what we should do? - If it tasted like
of Fuji. You're not going to find a fruit that's like this is actually the best
fruit ever. You know what you're finding like I'm sure I guess you're like going
somewhere and getting one. We should buy a fucking durian. Yeah and smell it
together. Yeah wait what was the fruit that we were talking about buying when
we were on tour that was like it's like a... Oh what was it? A cotton candy?
A cotton candy grape? Or no a fuck what was it? It was some fucking like sugar fruit.
It was a tree that you could grow that made a candy. It made a candy a fruit that tastes exactly like candy.
exactly like candy tree or something yeah fuck what was it it was so it sounded so
delicious it was like a video of people eating it. It's not a cotton candy grape is it? No no it was
like it was it was specifically a tree it was like a melon that had a... I'm googling
candy tree it's that's not gonna work it was a fruit it was a fruit and we were
talking about buying the tree because it's so hard to find the fruit fruit
that tastes like candy but a durian I really want to try yeah yeah I thought
durians and jack were the same it was an ice I was an ice cream fruit yeah ice
cream bean yeah ice cream bean yeah ice cream bean ice cream bean and ice cream
bean I we I want to try one so there I think I found out that you can buy the
plant yeah you can buy the tree it's not a planet it's really hard to buy you can
buy them in New York you can buy the tree in New York no it's not hard to find the
beans but they're insanely expensive.
It would be so funny to just go into the backyard of this building and just plant it.
That is what we were talking about for at least a full day is buying an ice cream bean
tree and planting it in the backyard here.
That would be incredible.
And we get ice cream beans whenever we want.
The tree will go strong from water.
That's true.
Actually, good point.
Yeah.
And then the sunlight the next day will give it photosynthesis.
And then we can harvest the bean.
The ice cream bean.
like ice cream beans I just want to try it I want to try that I do it durian I
want to try I've never had a durian is very good I want to try a truffle truffle
I've had a truck an actual truffle not like the salt that you get at Trader
Joe's I want to travel really what does it taste like same as the salt it's just
like oh yeah you're on Etsy you can buy one ice cream bean for $30 let's just do
it I think this other website though has it for something is this maybe their
biggest fuck yeah yeah I think it's a good investment to buy one of them yeah
it's an and then and then split it into three we can buy I'm so we could buy a
seedling a live sea ice cream bean seedling for $13 on a one in like a
community garden and we should straight up just put it in the backyard here look
it has a pot we'll probably have to I guess probably take years man as a pot
hey you know that's exactly an investment though that's I mean like what
we don't know if one of us is gonna what if one of us dies in a couple I would
want to just it'll be so much more poignant to finally eat the bean but I
just want to eat the bean now don't you want to raise a tree together I would
honestly I think I would rather raise a child with you to three men and a baby
then I think you don't have to do anything for a tree I don't want to do
three minute I'm completely ready to be you're not ready no I would be I would
be the I would end up getting a mom there's nothing about me that doesn't
scream daddy it says ice cream bean is fast growing but like how fast is it
says fast growing but I want a time frame okay I'll do some research you
guys talk about being a father how old do you want to be when you have kids pet
15 you're gonna get to 15 and then have kids yeah now you get a plan on doing
And then are you 25?
Okay, so it only takes about three years.
Leap year.
Leap year technology.
I was born on a leap year.
Really?
So you're like...
I wasn't born in February.
Okay, but you were born in a leap year.
I was born on a leap year, yes.
Okay, so how do you get planning to get to 15 so you can finally start procreating?
Um, I guess, well, if I was born on a leap year, how old would I be now?
You know what?
Depends which leap year.
It's a bad day.
Speaking of procreation, we have decided that we are going to neuter Phil.
Oh, really?
Yeah, I took him to the park today.
He tried to...
Attempted, attempted rape.
Damn.
In the second degree.
It's crazy that dogs are...
Attempted.
To the point where I had to take him out. We went to the park to play, this guy, straight
insatiable, bro. Juniper, driving him crazy.
Who's Juniper?
That's a dog's name.
Yeah, okay, good.
Gray dog.
Thought it might be a woman's name.
Gray dog, and he has a type. Let me tell you what, these gray dogs.
Is it a great tall, like a Weimariner?
No, it's a schnupper.
A schnupper.
Yeah, at least I think.
yeah at least i think it's still a german breed well just looks like a schnupper i don't know
if it is is that a real dog breed no it just looks like you look at you're like kind of
schnupper yeah yeah um dogs should be named what they look like because a weimeriner does not look
like a weimeriner yeah i use i would call most dogs dog yeah or i'd call it like it should be
they should all be dogs with different numbers of o's in there yeah without whoever they are
like a big dog is like dog yeah i think if you put a but that works for if you put a bunch of o's but
but if you do put two only two O's it is gonna be Doug.
- No, no, 'cause you'll pronounce it.
- Dog. - It'll be Doug.
- No. - I think even three O's
could be dog, but two O's is just Doug.
- Dag.
- What is that?
That is a little bit of a linguistic quirk
that movie Snatch.
- We should get Gnome on that.
- Yeah. - Movie Snatch for--
- We should get my gnome.
(laughing)
- My linguistic gnome.
We should get my little gnome on that.
- But an ice cream bean tree
does take three years to fruit.
- Fuck that, man.
(laughing)
That's fucking like,
You know when you're just like, it's just one of those moments where you're like, God just doesn't exist.
But imagine how fucking funny it would be if at this office without consulting anybody we plant a tree in the backyard.
Yeah, like drill, we get it, we jackhammer all the fucking concrete.
And it's a tree that starts growing ice cream beans.
In three years.
In the middle of the backyard.
Yeah, I have no idea where this came from.
They have footage of us planting it and then like, it starts like, the sapling starts to grow and shit and we're just like, yeah, I don't know.
Yeah, if anybody lives in New York and has a yard. Yeah. Yeah, please grow an ice cream
bean tree and to live there for more than three or more than three years. We will smell you
an ice cream bean or what? Fuck it. Even New Jersey will go as far as New Jersey. Yeah,
these beans and then what in three years we will come and visit you and eat the beans.
Yeah, and we might all be different heights by then. Yeah, yeah. And we will have a bean
cook off. I don't want to cook it, I just want to eat it. It's a fruit, it tastes like ice
cream. We'll bring other beans, it's just bean themed. No, it's only the ice cream beans.
The fuck, the ice cream bean is going to fucking show up any other bean. The ice cream bean
is the dessert and then we have a bean cook off to have beans for dinner. No, I want to
have a clean palate, I want to be ravenously hungry. You can clean your palate with water.
I don't want to eat anything else all day, I want to go straight. What do you mean a bean
cooking cook you mean a chili beans baked beans grilled beans grill Lima beans
just a kind of drill it I guess well ice cream bean is big but what do you so you
just you're boiling different kinds of beans what I got I got really different
flavors of there I heard that there is there's a secret Chipotle in New York
City that if you ask for when they ask what kind of beans you want you can say
ice cream beans and they'll put ice cream beans into your burrito.
And they also have a secret ice cream dispenser.
Yeah.
Chipotle.
I've had ice cream in a row.
And it's over the counter and if you jump over the counter they have to let you use
it.
Hickory smoked bacon bean.
That's not, that has nothing to do with the bean though.
You're just adding bacon.
They're different flavors of like Bush's baked beans, right?
So you're just cooking Bush's baked beans?
No.
Cook off them.
the beans, you were softening them with water, and then you were cooking-- this is not hard
to understand.
I don't--
You were giving me the Kubrick stare, because I'm talking about--
That's-- you're just saying that because I'm bald.
No.
That's the only reason you're saying it.
Stanley Kubrick was not bald.
No, he didn't do the stare.
He didn't do the Kubrick stare.
He does this--
He's a fucking idiot.
What are you talking about?
He did the stare through the fucking lens of the-- through the viewfinder.
You think it's-- the stare is--
That's what the stare is?
--is opening-- is only having one eye open?
yes the stairs having one eye open and looking through a camera lens
the stairs doing the thing from rocket power?
yeah with the with the yeah framing things with the kubrick stare is making sure it's
i thought the kubrick stare was that it was um when uh jack nicholson and um
and uh shelly duvall were were fighting in that hotel on that on what are you on the kubrick stare
oh that's the kubrick kiss
they don't kiss at all though
yeah exactly he's a weird guy
that doesn't make any sense
kubrick's kiss
So what you said was complete nonsense.
That's Kubrick's kiss.
Kubrick's kiss.
Because he shows that actually life is not good.
Shelley Duvall, she went crazy because of that movie, right?
Because of him.
It was actually, I read that, so I mean I guess I don't know exactly what happened, but
I read that she did another interview where she was like everyone blew that out of proportion
and I didn't go crazy.
She is, if you watch a video with her, she is crazy.
Dude, the videos of her now, yeah.
I'm just telling you what I read, Dr. Phil.
She is crazy.
like I must have gone crazy from another. She's like it's like she's like she's
doing like a like like a I think that she's like she like hello, Doctor Phil
like in the whole interview, I'm weird man. Yeah, not at all. I think she was
already crazy. You see the way she smoked cigarettes in that movie. Tell you
what she looked like a fucking rabbit
in a good way. She's hot. Yep, it's beautiful. Yeah, yeah, I'm surely do.
Yeah, she said that she did say that
- What up Popeyes, me Shelly Duvall.
- So she says Papa too.
- No Popeye.
Oh my God, what if the lady at the post office
was calling you Popeye?
- That would be so cool.
- Because of your forearms.
- Oh my God, I don't have Popeye forearms.
- You have tattoos on 'em like a sailor.
- Maybe, I guess.
I guess that could be, I should go back and ask.
- You were being called Popeye.
- I may, that'd be.
(laughing)
- The lady was saying.
- Speaking of women being your Popeye.
I think I also got Popeye today. A woman needed me for my strength. A woman who spoke no English.
You know those, the woman going, "Oh, Popeye!" No, she did not do that with her hands and
say that. You know the metal things that cover storefronts? A lady couldn't get hers open
today. No, the metal like, I don't even know.
Was it her first day at the store?
I have no idea.
How does she usually open?
I have no idea. It was right next to my apartment.
I think you started a thing by accident.
I just walked by and she--
I think you helped, I think you aided in a robbery.
She didn't say anything, she just went,
"Ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh," and like pointed,
and without even saying,
without even asking for clarification,
I just knew what she needed and I just opened it up.
I think she's actually going,
she's going, "Oh, my hero!"
Yeah, and then I did pick her up,
and then now that I think about it,
the kind of a, the frame slowly turned into a circle
and kind of closed.
Yeah. Yeah.
Did you hear, "Bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum,
I did hear that now that I think about it. I think I can be a good Popeye. Yeah, I
think we should make I think we should make a new pop. I do some wrist curls
get a big get some big for you're gonna be following Robin Williams though. I
think by that I think he's dead true. There's nothing to say about it when you
die all your kid I die with the nice thing about if you're playing you know
how when like you play a role as an actor and somebody already played it
you're supposed to go talk to them or whatever right if that person's dead
it's fine it's probably the easiest role to play ever. You could also channel Robin Williams.
You could channel him. I'll change the channel if that fucking untalented hack shows up on my
tv show that way. I know you could tell he was sad and it hurts his performance. Yeah you know
what you should listen to is his episode of WTF. WTF. Markman. I mean I'm seeing I see this guy
doing stand-up and improv and whatever I'm like this is a this he's a you can tell he's running
into a dead end here. I remember I remember seeing it's like weapons of
mass destruction or something his like his HBO special Robin Williams and I was
like oh it's like oh this is like the guy from my childhood or whatever and
the first bit I see him do is him pantomiming eating pussy into his elbow
like he's sneezing into it and I thought that was the funniest thing I've ever
seen. Robin Williams was a beast dude. He was a beast. That was insane to me.
Honestly, just him going like *makes pig noises*
Into his elbow pit. Yeah, he sounded like a pig. It is like he was pantomiming eating pussy. It's so sad man
It's almost like fucking a lot of these people who we see as like clowns almost have this like
hidden darkness, sad aspect. It's a similar thing, I mean they say that um that uh
You know Heath Ledger
He was eventually driven to suicide by playing the clown in um in the Dark Knight
night and I think it was a similar scenario.
I heard there's a similar scenario with Robin Williams where he actually he was
driven to taking his own life because of his role as the genie.
Yeah, the ultimate clown.
Well I heard that it was a similar thing.
You know people saw Avatar and they got really upset.
And Robin Williams was like, after he finished doing that movie, he's like, I can't be blue
in real life.
The same thing that a lot of people watch Avatar.
he just was like he died I had Paris syndrome I heard he ran directly at a
brick wall and jumped into it headfirst and that's how he died that's awful it's
really horrible I heard that is he tried I heard that all lamp yeah I heard all
his hairs flew off his head when I hit the wall that's fucking awful full head
ledger was supposed to be a clown in that movie the Dark Knight what do you
think he was criminal you can be both why not both taco commercial pork and no
of those those mm-hmm that means one on both what the the thing is the opposite
is also true with the client with the clown people who are often the darkest
have the weirdest enough turning into pretty funny guys yeah and you know
jessleneck Anthony jessleneck on his favorite Anthony doesn't like I think is
one of his pro is a maybe a mass murderer yeah and then he turned into
he's doing some fucking some funny-ass shit you know so you say so what you
just said I was like what I you just said I heard is that sometimes the
darkest people are the funniest and that's the words I heard come out of
your mouth I would say that's pretty much true across the board yeah every
sense of comedy and every sense of the of the word that is true yeah yeah yeah I
mean I'm not yeah yeah of course I think I think
just the truth man I got real bad right now I got a bubble but and I got a patch
you down to check when they when a TSA they tell you to bend over so they can
feel your butt my biggest fear is if I do get pulled over by TSA pulled over
pulled over the side and there's you driving ass over shoot why cuz I'm in the
TSM in the line in the car driving in the airport yeah you're walking in there
they should make an airport that plane you drive your car on to the airport
that has a Cinnabon yeah I think they made you I think there's a you're gonna
have some serious fun with a Louis CK joke pretty soon yeah yeah okay yeah
we're talking about that Cinnabon thing and he's talking about oh I Jim
Gaffigan has it had a Jim Gaffigan I think you're thinking of Jim Gaffigan oh
oh yeah now that'd be funny yeah Jim Gaffigan doing that joke that might be
fun yeah that would him saying that yeah that'd be pretty fucking funny in that
voice mm-hmm I I think I've had a Cinnabon or an Orange Julius or a couple
of things like that. It's been decades, man.
I want to go, dude, best Orange Julius in the world.
Orange Julius is fucking mad.
I think I've never been to a Cinnabon.
Really? Yeah. I'm thinking about it.
I don't think I ever have. They're good.
In my head I was thinking about
Auntie Anne's is the same thing,
but it's completely different.
Cinnabon is like 15,000
calories for a single Cinnabon.
I didn't have Auntie Anne's until we went to that
rest stop that one time. I think that was
also the first time I had Auntie Anne's, maybe.
I love the hot dog. It's too small. Yeah small and they give me a
terrible diarrhea
If Jim Gaffigan is listening right now also, I want to say this is our jokes we're doing right now
You can't take anything about there's W too few hot dogs at the auntie and yeah, okay. I know that you're like
That's the type of content you're looking for but this is our stuff so just yeah, there's gonna be his next fucking thing
You know it is dad or whatever. Yeah. Yeah, too many auntie's hot dogs
Jim Gaffigan, how would you make me laugh again? Mm-hmm? Yeah, cuz you already made me laugh once
Yeah, let's go
Do another gaff again, yeah, because those gaffs were making me laugh do another gaff again
Jim gaff again, and I'll be your laughing again
Yeah, my dad threw me to the trash again. Mm-hmm. I
Got cuz my dad passed and shit my dad passed and shit
My report card was bad this week
My dad threw me to the trash I
Didn't pass math class. Whoa. Whoa, man, you're revealing something here. Keep going be kind of a new freestyle
Yeah, I'm retired. Yep. Yep. Hit it. Come on. I was in a class called math concepts. Holy fuck
I think that's what it was called.
Math concepts, I think that's what it was called.
They taught me fractions through food.
They were training me to be a line kook.
- This doesn't, I don't know.
- You gotta make a rhyme, Patrick.
- We got in trouble in the computer lab the next semester
when they were trying to teach us spreadsheets.
- No, see, you should be like--
- Then you're doing a robot voice now.
- I've become the freestyle bot, the poetry bot.
- It's not a freestyle.
- It's not a freestyle at all.
- I'm not doing freestyles, I'm doing poetry.
- You switched into human again, halfway through that.
- I'm doing poetry.
- I'm not doing freestyles.
(laughing)
- We got in trouble in the computer lab.
- Mm-hmm, you should've said--
- Because we learned that Cool Math Games
has multiplayer games and I made my name Goatse
and I had to explain what Goatse was to my friend.
- Patrick, here's an easy one.
You say, "Yeah, and the next semester,
"the teacher was a molester."
Say something like that.
- I didn't get molested at school, though.
- But if you do--
- The teacher--
- You might say, "My teacher was a molester."
- Okay, but if I was doing slam poetry
or any kind of poetry and I did say
that my teacher was a molester,
I think that that would be pretty bad.
- Or you could also, here's, I mean,
to go back to what you want.
- Yeah, that's what you want.
- Okay, I think I would win a poetry slam if I said that.
- Yeah, yeah.
- That's how you win a poetry slam.
- If we could also, I wanna add something for you too.
- I wanna add something for you too.
- Telling me how to be a line kook.
- If we wanna go back to the Jim Gaffigan well,
- And the next semester.
- You could say, not paying attention in math class,
watching Jim Gaffigan while they were trying
teach me fracassions.
Okay.
Fracassions.
Yeah, so you could add that.
Leave this to FreestyleBot.
Let FreestyleBot.
Okay.
I mean, you got to do a suggestion, so it's interesting that I don't, but we can leave
the rest to FreestyleBot.
Well, I was giving you more direction.
You're giving him a specific line.
You gave him a specific line, too.
Yeah, but mine was actually good.
Yours didn't even rhyme.
Mine completely rhymed.
Not even a little bit.
You have to get in fracassion.
No.
My fracassion.
So you're using my line and not yours to kind of tell, like--
But then you could go into science.
Let's let Freestyle Bot figure this out.
Freestyle Bot.
Who's Ms. Blackishen?
I don't know, I'm just making up stuff.
That's okay, you're gonna win the poetry sign.
I wanna win the fucking poetry sign so bad.
Go ahead, try to win.
I got molested by Ms. Brackishen.
She tore my ass like, nope.
I think that's too soon and too far.
Too soon so it actually happened?
No.
recently molested by my female just lie man it's how you fucking know bad about
that even if I'm thinking you think all these all these rappers are actually
you think all these rappers are actually um selling drugs and wearing jewelry no
they make it up yeah you think they're actually having sex with multiple
women in a year ever I'm a slam poet I'm a slam poetry robot that is it's I
thought the piece tell me what the a and P stands for in an RIP in rap rhythm and
poetry. Oh my God and poetry right and what and so as long as you incorporate
rhythm, you're doing all the words. All the words are the same as rap right. You
just maybe don't have the rhythm to it. So you can talk about sliding on your
ops dude pulling out that stick and absolutely putting that fire on them. I
heard the C in rap stands for country. You can talk about spinning the block
okay, but you just got to just kind of do it. Okay, rap bot or freestyle bot
poetry poetry, but slam poetry, slam poetry, poetry, but is there a number
after a cool number one the first one yeah thanks that's first of many only
one yeah slam poetry about one so with that in mind now talk about fucking
getting completely fucking molested do it go by mrs. brackish and mrs. brackish
in mm-hmm taught me frac asians yeah that's back to that uh-huh and then my
vision went black again. I don't remember.
Yeah, she was a molester. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. In what month? In the month of November.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Yeah. She basted me like a turkey. Yeah. Uh-huh. Now, now hit that turkey.
Come on, come on. Like a turkey and then what what'd she do? She pulled on my
jerky you know that's the poem no but what happened you and I don't even know
him what happened to the back there go when the words are gonna come next I
don't even know him that's a poem holy shit what if it's brackish and due to the
backs the backseat are you the back bro what did brackish it due to the back of
him yeah the brackish in the got my back again
yep she busted that back open I think poetry but I think that's a good I think
we should figure out an algorithm for him though because he's making up stuff
about molestation that's our I mean that's a yeah that's the problem that's
the problem with the AI developers that really is a new thing that has a mortal
technique actually dance with the fucking devil no no it's about is hot
well see to dance with him to dance with him you're saying what happened in that
song would be too hot I mean the devil's on fire man but is that song a little hot
no it's crazy that he says all that stuff happened to his friend cuz that
started it's like it's like yeah that happened to my friend once yeah my
friend totally shit his pants in class yeah yeah it's also funny rapping for a
friend yeah did anybody else ever this happen to anyone else I'm rapping for my
friend that's the entirety of yeah immortal technique that nasty nasty song
mortal technique was making some of the worst music of all time yeah yeah but he
laid exposed a lot of truths about 9/11 yeah and about about being having a
crap day or whatever that's I had a bad day I'm taking one down oh my god
I think it's that song, I gotta turn it around.
Holy shit, dude.
I just thought his name was in poor taste.
Um, cause I mean, the only song I've ever heard by him is Dance with the Devil.
I don't think it's right for him to call that an immortal technique.
I think that's a weird, weird thing.
I agree.
Okay.
Okay, and we're back from the pee break.
The pee can make me stronger.
I had to pee.
We're back from the pee break.
See, but I have a new thing I need to show everyone.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I bet this, okay, okay.
It's just a dance, I've seen this dance before.
It's not quite new.
That one's the oldest dance.
- That one's the oldest.
- I like that one a lot, but it's not new.
- That one's not new either, man.
- If you got up and you said,
"Let me show you your favorite thing,"
I would be happy right now, but you kind of,
you blue balled me here.
- My balls are aching.
(laughing)
- Oh, okay, I do like that.
That's new, that's a new face and stuff.
- Yeah, I just, I'm out, I squirtied.
- Yeah, speaking of squirtied, I bet that honestly,
and I've had this theory for a long time,
how old you're pissing makes you more mentally alert.
- It really does.
where
because you are counting down the clock.
- See, I can't even do it.
- Yeah, see?
- Yeah.
- He said, "Boo, doo, doo."
- Yeah, that's not, it didn't even sound like anything.
- Sounds like a lot of the rap on the radio nowadays, though.
- That's true, you did actually--
- That mumble shit.
- Yeah.
- Sorry, mumble crap is what I call it.
- Yeah, mumble snore.
- Who's that guy who does the videos?
- The guy who does the videos?
- Oh, um--
- 20 different styles of rap.
- Smosh, yeah.
No, I know who you're talking about.
- What's his name?
- Fucking Mac Lethal.
- Mac Lethal.
- Mac Lethal, the pancake rap.
- Yup.
- That thing was sick.
- The alphabet rap.
- Dude, when we were at the Life World Show,
I don't know if we talked about this,
but you didn't go to the first one,
and we were gonna be like,
"Well, Caleb's not here, but we have a video from him,"
and we were just gonna play a Mac Lethal video.
(laughing)
- It's so funny, dude,
we were gonna play the alphabet one,
where he does all alliterations through the alphabet,
and the first one was like,
It's like angry aliens attacking.
(laughing)
It was all just stuff like that.
- I mean, it was pretty store core.
- It was so funny.
- That uh--
- You think he's a store core guy?
- I think that, well think about it.
Where are you getting the pancakes from?
- The store.
- Yeah, or the cupboard.
- Well, but where do you go first?
The store.
- Yeah, where do you get the batter?
- Right.
- Probably straight to the store.
- Actually, that's a huge, great point.
- We grew up in a mobile core.
- I think the word cupboard is one of my favorite words.
- Yeah.
I think it's such a funny word.
I hate when people say cupboard.
Really?
I hate it.
Why?
Because it's fucking annoying.
It's a pantry.
Or a cabinet.
Those are the two options.
I just say cupboard because I like that word.
I would call it a cabinet normally, but I think cupboard being spelled that way and
then being pronounced that way is so funny to me.
But I just don't like, if somebody's like, "Oh, it's in the cupboard."
I say, "Fuck you."
My mom never said cup-bird, cup-bird, cupboard, or pantry.
She always just said cabinet.
It's all the cabinet. Get out of the cabinet.
Cabinet's normal. Cupboard is funny though.
That feels like calling it...
Cupboard is like British.
Cabinet feels like calling the pantry a bandage instead of band-aid.
Bandage, I don't like that either.
Yeah, that's not right.
I mean, it's not a bandage.
A bandage is just a different thing.
Yeah.
That is just a band-aid.
Unfortunately, I hate capitalism as much as the next guy.
Actually, that's not true. Band-Aid is just a brand.
Yeah, I know that that's not true, but I mean when you say a band-aid, like, I guess the
thing to me with a band-aid, right, is if I was going to describe what a band-aid was
without saying the brand name, I'd have to say like an adhesive bandage or something.
Because a band-aid is the kind you wrap around yourself. Like, let's be real.
I think it's all a band-aid.
I mean, I know it's, heck, I know, I'm talking about word feelings right now.
Yeah, I think you're right.
Is it that jingle, the band-aid jingle? They say, am I, is this like a Mandela effect that
I'm thinking of?
I am stuck on band-aid cause band-aid's stuck on me.
- 'Cause it is brand, I thought it was just
stuck on a band-aid.
- What is this, a song about being a fly?
(laughing)
- Come on, what's this song about being a mosquito
or a fly? - Or a small hair on my arm?
- Yeah, yeah, exactly, I'm a hair.
I am stuck on a band-aid.
- 'Cause I am a hair on a--
- 'Cause I'm a hair on an arm.
- You know who wrote that?
You know who wrote that jingle?
Barry Manilow.
- That ain't no fuckin' truth.
Barry Manilow wrote Band-Aid, he wrote Stay Farm.
- I got my fact checkers on this.
- Like a good neighbor, stay farm is a--
- I got my fact checkers on this,
and if that's fake, I'm smacking the shit out of you.
- And then, no, 'cause there's Barry Manilow Live,
I think '77, Barry Manilow Live '77,
I had that VHS as a kid, and I used to watch it all the time.
And-- - He's right.
I just fact checked him for you.
- Really? - He's right.
I believed him. - All right.
- But-- - These hands will support,
you'll live to see another day.
he does his jingle medley in the middle of the show and it's just a
coyote's like a bear imagine going to a fucking Barry Manilow concert he's like
here's some other songs I wrote like a good day did he do the Empire funny I
don't know he did not do that but he also ends it with like the McDonald's
jingle he wrote he would and then there's like I don't know if he wrote
but up up a bomb loving it doesn't everyone say push a t-rope that push it
he didn't write. That's the thing that everyone says. What? But there's a
there I remember. That's the thing that is always like crazyfact.com always says that. I
remember distinctly this video. You gotta stop going on crazyfact.com. The medley ends with Barry
Mandelow and his backup singers just going like McDonald's. I didn't know that McDonald's had another name.
Pusha T wrote McDonald's now famous jingle in the early 2000s while trying to make it as an
up-and-coming rapper he claimed in a recent interview but he says he didn't
get paid enough for it. So I don't know. I don't know. That's true man.
That's the Pusha T legend in three games. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Dude he's the Barry Manilow.
I mean it's one of those things where I Google McDonald's jingle Pusha T and
every single article is did Pusha T really write the McDonald's jingle? So I
don't know. I'm not sure. New loafers? Stop wearing loafers. No. Stop loafing man.
I'm reinventing myself. I don't think you are. I think I'm going. I think you're not at all. Yeah, I don't think well first count
I'm gonna I think I'm gonna start getting I think I'm gonna start taking
Steroids. Yeah, I think you into my ass. I think if anybody shouldn't it should be you shouldn't why cuz you will
threaten
The president again. Why this was no, I won't I'll block you will I'll block my you'll block him on social media
Which is something you don't do.
No, I won't do that.
So at least it's safe from you.
I want to have the highest levels of DHT in the world.
And I want to somehow, I want to lose every single
follicle on my head. I want to die.
Really, really soon.
There's these guys, these like lifters,
and they go up to people at the gym and they say
"You natty or juice?"
And there's a guy that they walk up to and ask,
and he's like "Look at me, I'm 22."
I saw that video.
the worst receding hairline in the world.
But he was huge.
Dude, he looked good.
He was huge, man.
But, dude, imagine.
He looked like he was 50.
Yeah.
I think I might try and go on a diet and lose some height.
That's going to be tough, man.
Yeah.
That guy in that video looked like if Thomas took the Bain serum.
I want to get that fucked up varicose arm vein.
Yeah.
Like that one that looks like...
Oh, yeah, the scary one.
Ugh.
I don't like that.
The really nasty one.
I don't like that stuff.
Not the normal bicep vein, the one that's like a fucking...
I think, yeah, I don't like that.
looks like a flat like a lasagna noodle yeah I want that so bad yeah and you see
these shit Eagle lift ego what is that it was not that heavy but guy I'm a guy on
Instagram I think his handle is like Mikey maybe me or something like that
but he lifts like he holds a weight around his neck and he also lifts but
he's got like chains attached to oh yeah and like game cubes and shit I didn't
realize you were so you were so up-to-date on weightlifting if you're
wearing chains while you're doing anything you should also be wearing like
a tattered cloak I think you should be dressed like King Kong should be dressed
like that scene in in Transformers 3 when Megatron is on the Serengeti or when
he's in the Lincoln Memorial that shit's sick yeah I don't remember yeah Mikey
maybe you should go rewatch that movie so you can see that scene I've ever seen
that one. That's the best one. That's funny. Dude it's so sick. I wouldn't call this
ego lifting though. He has a shirt that says ego lifting is not a crime so that's
why. It's ego or eco? I think ego lifting is just when you lift more than you
should. Oh okay. Yeah. This is not, this is. What are you talking about? He's lifting way
more than he should. This is just a funny video. He's got a whole planetary system
hanging off his head. Dude, he rocks. That's really not that much weight. Yeah, that's
probably one pound. That's not that much weight. That's probably 135 on his shoulders for a
squat and also is the worst deadlift I've ever seen. So this guy's an extreme snowboarder.
He does like kickflips and shit with like weights on him. Sick. It's not that cool to
especially now that I'm getting on DRT. Take that shirt off right now.
My shirt that says skater? I just wear this to piss you off now.
It's such a funny shirt. My buddy AJ who gave me this shirt, he called me
like three years ago really drunk and he was like, he just gave me this shirt one time when I was at his house
and he was like, can you send me a picture of that shirt? And I was like, why?
He's like, I'm at a tattoo shop right now, I'm going to have the skater thing tattooed
on my chest.
And I was like, it was like fucking two in the morning. He like woke me up, call me. I was like, I'm bro. You shouldn't do that
He's like, I'm just um guess what it looked like
And I don't think he ended up getting it, but that would have been so
Yeah, can you imagine this dude? That is the game is chest because it doesn't look like like
It looks like a roller skater thing. It doesn't like I don't know. I want to know the backstory of this shirt. So yeah
Fucking funny. It's funny. You're saying you're wearing it to piss me off, but that is just a good shirt
It's a great shirt and skater. It's so good. That's a funny shirt, dude
Yeah, I would love to have no no other tattoos and then just on a chest tattoo that says destroyer
Yeah, yeah, I do kind of I kind of want to get a tummy rocker
That says something crazy like that. I've been thinking that too. I feel like that's that's that's
Tattooed
You can't get funny knuckle tattoos. That sucks dick. That's horrible, but you can get a crazy stupid tummy rocker. That's really cool.
A sick tummy rocker. No one will see it constantly.
I either want to get 910. It's not even about people seeing it versus not seeing it. It's just that it's so stupid to get dumb knuckle tattoos. That sucks.
I keep getting accosted for my tattoo. The one spider web that I had.
What if I got a tummy rocker that said awesome?
Awesome in old English.
Do you that fucking this guy came up to me and I want to go on this is cartoons
Have you not talked about it? No, I've never talked about on the pod. This guy came up to me
We were hanging out with Philip and we went to this curio shop this guy no curio shop
You know like a place with curiosities. Yes. Yeah, and this guy comes up to me. He's like, bro
Do you know what that means and I went no
He was pointing to a French word on the wall. Yeah
You know what? That means no Patrick's allowed
He looked at me. He looked at me and was like bro. You got to get that covered up man
That means that you serve 13 months in prison
13 months is also you should have told
Just also to you should have been to jail. Yeah, I was in there for 13 months
Actually 13 months you fucking did you hit the median with your car?
Why are you in fucking jail for 13 months? I don't know what you
The guy who gave me the tattoo had the same tattoo.
It's the most common tattoo in the world.
A fucking spiderweb on your elbow?
Everyone has that.
Yeah.
It's like, if anything, it's more kooky because I got it and I looked up, I was like, "Alright,
you know what?
I'm going to look up celebrities who have it just so I can be like, 'Well, they have
it.'"
You know, it's like they're not in jail.
I think you should just-
And I looked that up.
I looked it up.
The one person who got one, there's two, is like James Hetfield and fucking Jonah Hill.
And because Jonah Hill has it, I'm just like, man, fuck, I'm the biggest fucking poser in
the world.
If anything, I look like more of a poser.
But then he started, so he followed me out of the store and was explaining to me that
I have to get it covered up right now or I have to wear a shirt over it because someone
who went to prison will feel disrespected and they will probably beat my ass.
And then he saw me again and then was like, "Look, I'm sorry, but I had to tell you, man.
I skate, you skate, you know, like...
Why don't you just tell him that you know that and you went to jail for 13 months?
Yeah, that's what I was saying.
I should have said, yeah, I was at Rikers Island.
I was in jail for exactly 13 months.
But then I was like talking to him, like I was like, talking to him, I was like, "Well,
what if I put a spider on it?"
He's like, "No, that's even worse."
That's 14 months.
Yeah.
I think if you get the spider with it, it means you're a white supremacist too or
some shit. I don't know. It's fucking stupid. But then I was like, okay, what if
I put a big Spider-Man face in the middle? I think the spider web tattoo that
means you're a white supremacist is when you get a swastika on the spider web.
I think that's usually what it is. I think that I could go to jail. Have I
talked about this? I do seriously think I could walk into prison, the craziest,
hardest, maximum security prison, right? Go to the hill, right? Yeah. And I could
go in there and I could probably just be like the only white guy who hangs out
with the black guys. I think I think I could walk into a maximum security
prison I could probably beat up Magneto. They send you to like a maximum
security prison and you're trying to do that and you immediately get your ass
kicked because you're like check this out and you start doing the worm on the floor.
(laughter)
- The running man.
- You get killed immediately because you like,
- Every, every race joins together to kill me.
- You smuggled in a cell phone,
you're playing that,
♪ At night I think of you ♪
And you're doing like the four inch thing.
- I'm just making tic tocs.
(laughter)
- Every gang comes together
and they finally settle their differences
'cause they just wanted to kill you.
- I think,
- You solve all the gang problems by what's in your life.
- I watched a couple interviews with like some guys
had been in like prison for like 10 years or whatever and they just talk about
they're like yeah there's no way around it you just like like you have to stick
with your race in prison or whatever and I was just like you know what I think
that I could break that mold and I think that I could I don't and I would I would
honestly I would walk up to anybody who I just don't want to be lumped in with
the white guys you know just cuz I'm kind of rude they're there yeah man and
I would be like no criminals
kingdom guys was being like um do you know what the swastika means you do
realize that that's actually mad fucking offensive right Jewish and yeah I just
think I could be like listen guys I just can't do it that's actually a sick tattoo
I'm straight white chocolate I don't want anything to do with these fucking
these these crackers let's be real that's what they are over there I want to hang
out with you guys. I don't want to have anything to do with them. And I think that I would be
able to, I think they'd be like, they'd respect my initiative, first of all. I don't think
anyone's ever tried that, you know? So they'd be like, well, yeah, I guess we have to take
you because you're like, you fit all the requirements, right? I got, I just think it would work, man.
Yeah. Well, let's find out. Yeah. I'll even listen. I'll be a human shield. I'll be a sex
puppet toy. I'll be fucking, I'll be, I'll, you eat me. I don't care. What if that guy
sent to jail last night. I don't think he got arrested did he? I don't know but this
guy came up to us and called Alex Kid and Play and then called Pierce a retard.
Yeah. And then he had a full bottle of Svedka. Yeah he wasn't even drunk. Yeah he
wasn't even drunk. That was full of water. It's a prop. Yeah. It was full he didn't drink it.
And then he went into it we watched him go into a Taco Bell and he like it was
just like it's like watching like it's like a watching Trevor from GTA 5. He was
was
He was a main character he was we were just complete NPCs he just walked up stomped all over us and left yeah
Yeah, and then we're like
Pretending we won because I was because he tried really mad. Yeah, I was really mad
I kept saying I want him to turn into red mist. Yeah, which is a huge is lost by saying that yeah
He walks away, and then you're like you fall I'm gonna die
Yeah, and then you followed him to see if he got arrested then you ran away when he didn't get arrested
Well Pierce Pierce walked up to him with the cops
Pierce was on the side of the street. Just looking at the guy going like
The only way to win that is just pretend you don't speak English dude
Had the biggest yellow capris on yeah, it was so funny
Yeah, he looked like a fucking create. He looked like a GTA online created character. Yeah, he's walking around
He like he's more Saints Row. Yeah, but he dude those pants were so fucking funny. Yeah. Yeah, can he could rock him, dude?
Yeah, I'm not gonna say shit about it. No. Yeah, he pulled it off. Yeah, it pierces like he's like, oh, what's everyone laughing about?
What's everyone laughing about? Huh? And then Pierce is like I'm talking about my landlord
And he was like oh you can't pay rent retard. Yeah, okay, and then he ran away really fast
Yeah, he's you're still pretending you didn't get fucking
He ran away run away. He walked to the
Ran away, he walked to the corner and then you and then you did I will say he did walk away very fast
And it was funny
I don't think that it was he walked away very fast because he said retard and was like oh my god
I need to get away
I just say that it was funny because it seemed like that because he said because Pierce was struggling to light his cigarette and then
Finally did it and then he said nice one retard and then walked away
Well, that was that was funny. That was his drive-by line. Yeah. Yeah
I was just mad. He called Alex kid and play. Yeah
It's not mad enough to do anything except sit there and then wait for him to try to get arrested
And so I was it dude. What that guy had a bottle with him. He's gonna knock me in the head
Yeah, maybe. Probably would have killed you.
Oh, what the hell?
Oh, what the hell? My shirt is crazy right now!
No, no, no, no, no!
[Laughter]
Oh, wait, the hell? There's a tag on my shirt!
Wait, guys, we have to talk about something else!
This is Joe's dad's shirt!
Yeah, dude.
I didn't know that!
Damn, it's embroidered.
It says Tim Gleason on it.
I have the exact proportions of Joe's dad.
dad oh my god I don't think so I've met his dad you do have the same proportions
yeah okay says it right there Tim well all right go buy some tickets to the
Halloween live show because we are very soon going we're flying to do this
also normal investigation if so I can't come off all the not a sticker relax
yeah chill the I if you get a tracking number for your shirt please DM the
podcast account because I just want to find out when these shirts are going out
Yeah, we have not this fucking this. I'm sorry. It's taken so long this company. I think I probably will be assassinating their CEO
Or something, but yeah, they're on the steroids. Okay, making all right. Bye everybody. Bye