You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
Okay.
Yeah.
Are you ready to fuck?
'Cause I'm ready to suck.
What?
Gay guy.
Gay.
Okay.
Do you get it?
Mm-hmm.
It's like Power Man.
When the Grinch steals.
Let's do all of our songs.
Okay, let's do a songs episode.
When the Grinch steals and the Grinch eats all our presents and all our roast
beast.
Okay.
And he's so mean and he's so green.
Why is the Grinch so mean?
That's a good song.
So there's one.
Thanks.
All right, next song.
Pat, you do one now.
Okay, hold on.
on
You guys know I didn't have a song prepared for this episode.
No!
I didn't either.
Oh my god.
I knew.
I didn't have a song prepared.
Sorry that we got to write ours.
Get off your phone.
You're gonna have to, uh.
Oh, he's looking up a song.
He's just googling song right now.
Alright, Caleb, you do another one while we wait.
I chimed in. Haven't you people ever heard of the twillage?
I was really hoping to scare you, not to hurt your feelings, but I'm only trying to get you.
Is this Rap God?
(music)
Yep.
Oh, okay.
That was good, dude.
(music)
One of my fondest high school memories was...
That's so funny that's what Eminem turned into.
Yeah, and just a cyborg. I love him.
(laughter)
I went to this party one time, and it was like in high school, and it was kind of right when
that song had come out.
And there was a, they had like a bonfire outside, and everyone was just sitting around smoking
weed and being on their phones.
And then one kid was like, "Do you guys want to see something fucking sick?"
And everyone was like, "Yeah."
And then he just played Rap God and rapped the whole thing for everybody.
But nobody was paying attention except me.
So it was just this one guy at a big fire just rapping to me, Rap God.
And afterwards he was like, "So like what'd you think?"
And I was like, "That was some of the fastest rapping I've ever heard in real life."
There's a kid at my high school who used to do shit like that.
And he worked with my friend Kayla.
What, your friend Caleb?
Yeah.
That's me.
Girl Caleb.
I've never had a job.
and Dom was going to like pick her up from work or something she was like hey
Derek can you rap fast for us and then he just did it in the middle of his shift
like good like consciousness because he was sure that it's not just
rather on just miss oh okay that's why I said consciousness there's a
consciousness but he would do like the conclusion that I came to is that we
need a solution for it.
- Ah, sounds like it's you, like Hamilton rapping.
- There's a guy, I don't remember,
he was in my high school, I don't even remember who it was,
but he was a rapper. - It was you.
- And he went on a Facebook live
and of him freestyling at a party.
And like it was so funny,
'cause it's just him in a corner like freestyling,
and it's everybody just like looking at him really annoyed,
like nobody is paying attention.
I was like what is this guy doing?
And his friend is filming him.
Like on Facebook live.
You gotta lay down some rhymes.
So these...
Everyone at the party will break dance.
I knew this kid in high school who
he was such a big Kid Cudi fan
that he decided to
become a rapper and changed his
decided his rap name
would be, his name was Dylan
and he decided his rap name would be
Dylan Mess Cudi.
Which is just Kid Cudi's last name.
That's pretty sick.
It's like he's marrying him.
I never heard his music.
I'm guessing it sounded like Kid Cudi.
Yeah, that's a safe bet.
That's what Kid Cudi sounds like to me.
What have you guys been up to?
Not much.
Yeah, not too much.
I watched Transformers today.
That's cool.
Which one?
The first one.
It's really good. It's really... It is good. It's super good. It's so much... it holds up really well.
I mean it still looks good too. It like looks really cool. The CGI is... Me and Janna were talking about how
they have such a... those movies have such a specific like visual style. Yeah, everything's like blue and orange.
Yeah, and everything that came out for like five years after that, every action movie, just looks
like transformers but without Megatron Optimo yeah yeah
yeah good Megatroid Megatron the Mega charred Mega Charizard yeah don't say
that they got Mega Charizard in there oh my god they accidentally unlocked
Giga Grinch oh no no power of the cube oh god the Grinch has entered Dynamax mode
No, we cannot let that happen.
Grinch X. Shut the whole thing down.
That sucks.
They should make Grinch X like Jason X and he's in space.
Grinch X like Malcolm X. Grinch level X like Darkrai.
Grinch X like Malcolm X. Fighting for green people.
Muslim Grinch.
Trying to think.
Muslim Grinch?
Yeah.
What do you think about that?
That's why he hates Christmas.
No cat in the hat never called me no Grinch.
No thing never called me no Grinch.
It was only Booz.
It was always Booz.
No, because the Hoos did call him a Grinch.
The Hoos do call him Grinch.
Yeah.
It was just never a thing one or two.
No, no thing one never called me no Grinch.
No Horton.
Horton was a serious Grinch about abortion.
That's what that movie was about.
That's why he's an elephant.
That's why everybody here in North Carolina loves Horton Hears a Who because they think
it's about it.
They think it's about the GOP elephant.
Yeah.
and he's protecting him the the who's from the Democratic kangaroo yeah which
which is which is the Democrats can't yeah the Grinch the Grinch is a great
kangaroo the world's smartest kangaroo that's why he can carry all those
presents he has a pouch the Grinch is somebody dr. who or mr. Seuss he decided
he was sitting around one day smoking ganja drawing pictures of Japanese people
and he was like what if a kangaroo learned how to steal presents I'm gonna
draw the Grinch yeah
down one day in 1942 and he said yeah today's the day I draw the Grinch. He had it circled on his calendar for three years.
Since the beginning of the war. He locks all the doors. I knew this was the day I unleashed the ultimate evil onto earth.
Draw Grinch. Yeah that's why Hitler killed himself with that cyanide pill.
Yeah, because he knew the Grinch was coming.
He knew the Grinch was on the way.
The United States has the Grinch.
We have caught and compromised to a permanent end.
The Grinch.
The bastard.
The bastard Grinch.
The green bastard.
Yeah.
It is, uh, have you guys seen all the Dr. Seuss Japanese drawings?
It's pretty crazy. It's funny he like peppers it into his normal stuff too.
Like I was I found this book in a Dr. Seuss book one time and it's like a
bunch of like questions. It's like kind of like... Oh I actually the other day
found this video that you sent me on my phone. Yeah and it's like it's like
stuff that's like how old do you have to be to drive? How old do you have to be to
vote? How old and it's like how old you have to be to like cook your own meal?
And the last one says how old do you have to be to be a Japanese? And then you go to the back and
and there's like an answer key and the answer says the Japanese are Japanese
from the day they are born.
That's true.
That is yeah, I mean that is not wrong.
Is unfalsified with truth and yet
no way in context doesn't sound great for old soos.
Yeah, you know, that's his real name.
Yeah, doctor soos.
we spent here patrick before this found a guy named bob patrick
uh... we have a couple of the other coach
pleasure coach bob patrick any mixes you to be as we just like
rubs he there was one rose about finding the prostate and
you just isn't he was just stuck his finger in a gatorade bottle of lunch
because it's a really deep sensual book it's any gatorade bottle you can at the
store
and what you're feeling a little until the room
and there is no no you can see it if we pull it up yet
i wanted
in my house
and then there's one with him says
men are like dogs and uh... yes i have a little sensually was starting up
because of the accident
he's on top of lake i think it's san francisco i don't know but it's like
some use on the top of san francisco yeah he's like on a mountain overlooking
the city just massaging the fuck out of the dog any saying like find the pleasure
centers on your man's body and is like rubbing a dog.
It's really great.
It's recommended.
Yeah.
Okay.
What's his name?
Bob Patrick.
Pleasure Coach Bob Patrick.
He has really long nipples.
Oh yeah, dude.
He has long nips.
Dude, it's so fucking funny.
They're droopy too.
I've been trying to find that picture of that guy with those droopy nipples for a while.
What picture?
Is that your mirror?
black dude with the nipples that are like three inches long.
Yeah, I know the one you're talking about.
Where is that photo?
If you can find that photo, send it to Caleb at his private email.
I will send you a dollar.
I'm serious.
I'll send you a dollar if you can send me that photo.
Just send it to the podcast Twitter.
Yeah.
And send anything else you like, too.
you can send whatever you want to our personal email anything at all
my personal email, Caleb. We do have an email
Oh we do, yeah.
if you have any tips about Caleb
send them to podcastaboutwereabouts.com
if you know where I am, if you've seen this man pointing at me
email podcastaboutwereabouts@gmail.com. Stay far away and send an email. Do not approach
if you see this man do not approach this man is dangerously contagiously i'm
dangerously talented at singing
when the grinch eats
and the grinch eats and he's so green
it's a great song
it is really good
what's uh...
what's that other grinch song?
you're a mean one, you're a mean one, squidward tentacles, squidward tentacles
you really are a squid
that is good. What about something like
like it's like head like a hole but it's green like a Grinch and then he says
I'd rather die than give you my gifts
we'll work on that one. Think about that for a little while
okay Pat?
figure that out for me
Grinch like a hole! Grinch like a hole!
I'm green, ba ba da, I'm the Grinch
Bob I'm the Grinch I am green on the Grinch
it's good now listen up here's a story about a little green
Grinch named the Green Grinch and all day and all night he's in his cave hanging
out with his dog
he's Grinch inside and out Grinch
I love that song
I'm the Blue Grinch not no
no we're not talking about the Blue Grinch right now
Imagine what about a red white and blue Grinch?
Uh-huh.
I salute you my Grinch.
I salute you till the day I die my blue green red white and blue Grinch.
He's still green somewhere.
Yeah.
He's green where it counts.
[Laughter]
Once you go green you never don't go Grinch.
Oh.
Woo.
The Grinch is real.
[Burps]
I ate a bunch of quinoa and beans.
I also ate quinoa today, but no beans.
Yeah.
I ate quinoa, beans, and corn, and now my throat is like, feels like I drank a gallon
of milk.
It's very thick.
When I'm home, I just don't know what to do with myself when I'm like staying with my
parents because I don't have a job.
I was offered a job at Waffle House while I'm here.
Okay.
it. Just not even to get the money, I just want the recipes.
Yeah.
You know, I want the waffle recipe.
Well, you got to get a griddle in your house.
I'd also like to, you don't got to get a griddle.
You got to get a whole griddle.
You got to get a whole ass griddle.
Have either of you ever eaten at Waffle House?
No.
I have.
You have?
Yeah.
I've eaten at Waffle House.
I ate at Waffle House. When we were, when me and Gus were like
driving we were on tour we did a show we ate Waffle House did a show in Atlanta
and then like drove through the night to North Carolina and ate Waffle House
again six hours later I've had most of the things on the menu at Waffle House
I recommend the pork chops to anybody who's listening the chops are underrated
yeah I went to when I was like six years old my parent we were staying at like
this motel in the Cape and we went to this restaurant that my parents went to
after their honeymoon because they were like oh this would be fun and then like
we were it was called the Pancake Man and it was called the Pancake Man I
don't know if it's still operating in the in the Cape. What part of the
Cape? I don't know I was six might be in Hyannis or something. Right sure you were.
- Hyena's.
- Hyenas.
- Hyenas, but so we ate there and we didn't like it
and then my uncle Kevin told us to write letters to them
to tell them how dissatisfied we were
and we all wrote a letter to the Pancake Man
and we just kept trying to like see how many swear words
we could get away with so it's just a bunch of six year old
like me, my brother, my sister and my younger brother
being like, "Dear Pancake Man, your food was damn crap."
(laughing)
- I didn't know how to use curse words
until I was probably like 19.
- Yeah.
- Honestly.
I remember I discovered them,
not discovered, I unlocked them when I was in fifth grade
'cause I stopped believing in God
and I was like, "Finally, I can say, 'fuck'."
And then I guess I used bad words too much
because one time I was hanging out with my brother
and his friends, they were all older than me,
and I guess I was cursing a bunch,
and Josh, he like pulled me aside and he was like,
"Hey man, you're using way too many curse words."
(laughing)
But he was like 17.
And he was like, "You're too young
"to be using so many curse words."
And--
- Badass.
- Yeah, and I was like,
you should be in jail.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- That's what I, that was my retort.
I was very, it was a smart ass.
- I remember a really distinct memory of like
figuring out that I could say crap
and not get in trouble in like fourth grade.
And just saying it constantly.
- Do you, did anyone--
- Saying like what the crap, saying that.
- Did you get, did any of you guys get in trouble
for saying jerk?
'Cause for some reason in my third grade class
It was like a rule that jerk was just as bad as saying like shit.
No, no yeah.
It wasn't like a rule that the teacher made, it was a rule that like the students made.
They agreed on?
Yeah.
They had a council.
You could say like idiot and stuff but apparently jerk was a swear.
So I think I, oh yeah I was singing the Larry is a Jerk song from the Andy Milonakis show
and somebody told on me
and I was like there's no one in the class named Larry
I uh... I never the only time I got in trouble for saying anything in school
was in fifth grade
I made a rape joke and got suspended
yeah? What was the joke?
the joke was
hey uh... hey Nick
uh... David's sister
No, I was like, "Hey Nick, David's sister raped you in the ass."
And my teacher was like, "You have to leave school."
And I did. And my mom was so mad.
Yeah.
Yeah, she was like, "He's just 10 years old.
He should be able to make as many rape jokes as he wants."
She really argued hard for it.
Damn.
but I was like, the thing is suspension is such a,
such a fucking pimp thing to, like punishment.
'Cause you just, like I just hung out.
- Right, you just hang out, you don't fucking do anything.
- And it was like, you know, it was fifth grade,
so I didn't have like a, I didn't have like a,
like work I had to catch up on,
like in high school or whatever.
Like I didn't have like extra work
just because I was suspended.
Like I just got four days off school.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
I got in trouble, we used to, you know the penis game, we used to play it but we would
play it with uh, oh no you know what it was, it was the penis game but it was a Tourette's
guy quote.
It was that one where he like hits his head or something and goes "Butt fuck!"
And we would just scream "Butt fuck" in the hallway and I said it too loud behind the
guidance counselor and I turned and I ran away into the bathroom and she followed me
in I was like you can't be in here. You thought you had entered the men's embassy and that it was technically you were in men's jurisdiction.
Exactly I was like you got to get a boy teacher to get me out and then she took
me to the principal's office and then oh so I got a demerit for that but then the
next day I got a merit which like canceled it out. Whoa. So like I got the
demerit and then I got called into the office the next morning and my
principal was like going over what I did and he was like well so you said big
buttfuck in the hallway and I was like well I I didn't say big I didn't say I
didn't you added an adjective I didn't do that which does make it worse which
makes it worse yeah but then he was like well that's he he was like that's
semantics but anyway I'm you're not in here for that I'm just mentioning that
because you did something good at the same time and he was just he was just
too confused as to like how to go about my punishment because I was the good
thing was that you defended the men's bathroom
thing is you you made it all the way to the bathroom yeah PPP in your pants so I
was supposed to get like a lunch detention or something like that or like
a detention and I didn't because I got the merit.
- Nice, dude.
- So, ultimo pimp move.
- Yeah, if you do one bad thing,
you just cancel it back out.
- I can be your angel and your devil.
- That's level four pimp shit.
- Level four pimp shit.
- Yeah, the thing is, you could get away
with anything in school, and I'm telling you, anything.
- If you don't get caught.
- If you give the teacher an apple.
- Mm.
- But if the apple has a worm in it.
no then that's bad but you can get away with that if you give them a real apple
right so you say to alex
uh... david sister raped you in the ass
and this mccorkle while i'm saying rape jokes here's an apple
and she'll be like you're fine in fact you get to come back to school for the
next four days
uh... yeah
that's right that only works on miss mccorkle
you need to be in school for the weekend that was a miss mccorkle thing it
doesn't work on any other teacher
I had a science teacher named Mr. Davis,
who he kind of like, he kind of gave me the cold shoulder
after middle school when I saw him
at a gas station one time.
And it's like maybe the most my feelings
have ever been hurt.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, he was buying a lottery ticket
and I was like, "Hey, remember you used to teach me
"in sixth grade?"
And he was like, "Oh yeah, cool man."
And I was like, "Oh yeah, I'm just like an adult now.
"Like I'm not, you're not in charge of me anymore."
Like I don't have any, I don't, we're not,
you probably don't even remember me,
you fucking bald piece of shit.
- Yeah.
- We had this science teacher in,
I think I've talked about it,
but my science teacher in seventh grade, Mr. Tiela,
he was like from Italy, like,
his first language was Italian,
and for some reason,
everybody just accused him of being a pervert.
And then like, one day these kids went through his desk
and then like accused him of having boner pills in his desk.
(laughing)
There weren't boner pills in his desk,
but they just got in trouble for going through his shit.
- You had an actual teacher sex scandal though, right?
- Oh yeah, yeah I did.
We had our seventh grade--
- You had sex with the old janitor?
- I had sex with the old janitor.
I was good friends with one of the janitors in high school. Yeah, good janitor should have to dress like Frenchman
His old sticky man
Buckets
Bending over to pick up banana peels. Hey you kids better calm down. No running in the hall
The floor is wet!
but my teacher's sex scandal.
Fucking, so our--
- Fucking students.
- Sophomore English teacher for the school,
her name was Mrs. Dennehy.
- Oh my God.
- And she met this kid who,
she met this kid at like her daughter's gymnastics thing
and he like was one of her students.
And then she got caught making out with him in the classroom
and like sending him nudes.
And then the nudes got spread around the school.
Well, this is how she got in trouble,
how she got caught. The nudes were going around like to his friends and then she
was like trying to punish some kid his name was Josh. She was trying to punish
Josh to like she's like trying to she was like Josh go to the fucking
principal's office right now and he's like oh you really want to do that and
she's like yes I really want to do that not knowing that he had like her
pictures so he went down to the principal's office showed the principal
the pictures and then like the cops were at the school like immediately because
my high school was next to the police station it was a whole whole thing they
she got a joke about her on Leno and I can't find the thing I've seen her nudes
I looked it up the first time you you told me oh you did okay yeah it's there's
not a lot of she's not like you know buck-ass naked but right but you can't
send that to a fucking 15 year old why she's not even naked I don't know what
was the juror Puritan state what was the Leno joke oh I don't remember why not if
you look it up it was exactly what I just because it's because the men in
black erased your memory because you were part of the scandal true and you
were an alien let's think about what the Leno joke was I don't remember it I just
just remember um hmm yeah it was probably like look up Jay Leno sex with teacher
Jay Leno has sex with his teacher Jay Leno sex scandal teacher Pat J Leno fucks
Patrick hard Jay Leno sex with a teacher Jay Leno having sex Jay Leno having sex
set at school
yet a lot of sexiest joke
jaylen those
the nastiest joke of all time jaylen a nasty triple x joke yet
jaylen as porn joke
yet not clickbait
do not
do not click in the city of the something you want to see not click
unless you want a bone hair yeah eighteen plus jaylen a joke no kids
allowed adults only rated J Leno's kids penis.
Do not know kids penis. That's what it is. That's the search term you have to
look up. J Leno best penis.
J Leno having sex with himself in his car J Leno having sex with the penis.
Pedophile pedophile pedophile pedophile do not click
How many pieces
Pedophile pedophile is like the worst like like southern comedian name. Oh
He's a pedophile. We have pedophile pedophile opening up at
Clooney's clown shack this weekend a
a monday show and a wednesday show
pedophile comedian he's just a catchphrase comic too
and he's a catchphrase just like
damn right i'm a pedophile
pedophile duh comedian pedophile duh comedian
yeah
whoo
yeah he's a legend around here
they saw me outside the school the other day now i'm telling you folks they do
not give me a break they saw me outside of the school looking
into the playground
they said hey what you do it
and i said pedophile
i say pedophile
Alonzo pedophile jones
how many different food items did Alonzo hamburger jones go through until he
settled on hamburger
hot dog it was probably hot dog first hot dog seems so up his alley hot dog
seems it was seems like it was hot dog first and then someone is like hot dog
gets serious nowadays you would be freaking be mocha Chino yeah it'd be
the impossible burger Jones so impossible burger impossible burger I don't think
this is working yeah Alonzo M&Ms Jones
- Candy corn.
(laughing)
- Alonzo candy corn jokes.
- I've been craving candy so much today.
- Yeah, man.
- I want a big bag of Halloween candy
that I get all for myself and that my mom can't buy from me
no matter how much she tries.
- I want a big candy.
- That's what my mom used to do.
She used to buy my Halloween candy from me
for like $5 when I was a kid.
- That's not bad.
- So that I wouldn't eat all the candy.
- Yeah, that's a good trick to play on a kid.
- Yeah.
- It was a trick and now I realize that
'cause it was easily $200 worth of candy in that bag.
- It's insane how much candy you got for free as a kid.
- Candy prices are skyrocketing this year.
- It's crazy that as an adult,
you have to almost always pay for your own candy.
- Yeah.
- If I was a hot kid, I would not have that.
- If I was a hot little kid, I would.
- I'd get unlimited candy.
- Yeah.
- That's serious kid privilege.
You walk around free candy all day long.
Where do you go?
candy the dentist candy the free cookie Harris Teeter sugar-free grocery store
cookie hmm you can get it Harris Teeter is a grocery store that you guys have
here's Peter here Alonzo Harris teeter-teeter grocery store then he
gets bigger and then he picks up a sponsorship yeah yeah Alonzo Crow traded
Jones Jones Jones traded Jones traded Jones yeah but yeah no candy is great
what's the best candy what's the best candy what's the best candy think a very
underrated candy actually know what no maybe it's cuz it was expired but I
think my opinion on ABBA's ABBA changed in LA yeah you don't like it anymore
- Yeah, I don't know, I don't think I can eat Abba's Abba
anymore, I think it's--
- I've never had Abba's Abba.
- It was like two years expired.
- It definitely has to do with the fact that it was expired.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, it was bad.
- Similar kind of candy is a Cow Tail.
- Uh-huh.
- You ever had a Cow Tail?
- Cow Tails are pretty good, it's just--
- I like a Cow Tail.
- It hurts my teeth when I eat it.
- It's so sugary.
- Yeah.
- But it's like, I think it's like 15 cents, which--
- Oh yeah.
- For me, that's like a buy low, sell high candy.
You know what I mean?
get a lot of mileage out of 15 cents of candy. I love peanut M&M's. I feel like
all the people say it's the lame candy but I think it's a cool one.
It's the best candy. I think it's one of the best. It's not the best. I think the
best might be the Snickers bar. I think Snickers is like a good candy but I
don't think it's the best candy. It's got everything that I want in a bar. Same with
Take five you ever had. Oh, no take five is the best candy bar. I like
Enjoy, I love
Enjoy, you don't like almond. Joy. Oh, that makes sense. It's good. He doesn't have a culture culture
You're not you're not tropical like me and and camera. No, I like tropical food
I don't like almond joy. I don't like almond joy cuz it's just coconut. Maybe if it was like a man
There's an almond in there - you fucking idiot
Around it you're so stupid dude. I bet you like mountains
Mounds yeah, I like mounds - what's wrong with that start chocolate actually no I think I like mounds
I think I don't like almond joy, but I like mounds
I'd have to it the only difference is that almond joys milk chocolate with an almond belly button yeah and
Coconut yeah, I don't know. I think it's just a coconut and almond thing. I like mounds though mounds is fine
Have you guys ever had one almond in in almond joy? Yeah? I know, but it like creeps up on you
Have you ever had a taste-o-ball? No. It's really good. Oh I love a spazzo center.
Yeah? Yeah. Yeah. Have you ever had a Clark? A Clark is one of my favorite candy. A nice hot
Clark. No, a Clark bar? It's like a... Yeah, a Clark bar. It's like a... it's like a
Butterfinger but a lot crispier. Have you guys ever had a candy belt? A Mallow Cup?
Oh, I do like Milo cup. It's just good one time
I got I had a like a flannel shirt that I got from Goodwill baby room and I took it home and there was a
half-eaten nerds rope in it and
And then my little brother was like walking here he walked into my room and I was like hey do you want this
Bowl
Yeah, sure and that stupid bitch
- Did you tell him?
- Yeah, after, and he was like, "Tasted normal."
(laughing)
- Nice.
- It's good though.
- Yeah.
Nerds Rope was really good.
- Nerds Rope was really good.
The problem with Nerds Rope is you open it
and you forget that it's one inch tall.
- Yeah.
- It's so small.
- No, I like that it's small.
'Cause I mean, there is the big Nerds Rope.
I think, there's a lot of candy I can't eat anymore
because I ate so much of it in a mass quantity.
- That you have diabetes now.
- That I have diabetes now.
no it's like
i i think about there's a good specific candy that i think about me just get
sick and i think it's a don't say what it is
it's gonna make a sick
seahawk peppermint patties really i like is a high-level any of the government
that are no no no it's junior mince those were my favorite candy as a kid
junior mince if i eat too many
i too many junior mince once
and i threw up
and now when i think about junior mince i think about throw up
you know i was like toothpaste
you know how soon in a minute thing does junior mince they stick to the inside
yeah pretty interesting that's something about them
damp we talking candy today yeah you know what sucks
okay so i like a crunch bar
but you know what i fucking hate
bunch of crunch
i rely on your crunch
states terrible
Crunch bars really good the formula for butterfinger. They changed the formula. Yeah the recipe they change
Yeah, they changed the makeup of it. Yeah, it looks it changes DNA
They changed the percentages and kind of equalized everything up to the finger. Mm-hmm. Yeah, it's more finger now
It is way more fingery than butter. Yeah
I just like when they just put all of the ingredients in the name. Mm-hmm butter and fingers ever had a zero bar
I love a zero bar because there's nothing in it. Yeah
It's it's fucked up
It is it's a it's genuinely it's one of the most fucked up candy bars. I think what do you find?
So fucked up about a zero white chocolate. Yeah new get
Yeah, it's good. It's I like zero bars, but it's like every time I like when I'm halfway through it
I'm like, oh, yeah, this is too many thick things. I have a stomach
Busted shit. I don't know why I like I like what's on the inside of the zero bar. That's why I get it
So if there's a zero bar that personality like yeah, there's a zero dark 30 bar
That'd be pretty good there is yeah, it's only 30 calories and it's dark chocolate and it has zero calories
There's a zero bar has zero calories. That's why it's called. That's why you eat it. Yeah
Yeah, it also has a zero bar. Yeah, it's called zero because it has zero
zero authority.
It's because I've eaten it zero times.
Yeah.
Yeah, for me it's a 10 bar.
Yeah, it changes.
Yeah.
Based on-
And a 300 grand bar.
Let me tell you what, buddy.
That shit's expensive.
I've had way too many of those.
Yeah.
Yeah, I've had 300 grand of those.
Yeah, no.
I'm serious.
It's just called a zero bar just because.
I have zero respect for that.
Mm-hmm.
Bar.
I- Oh, it was called the Double Zero Bar and was renamed Zero in 1934.
Damn, they downsized it.
So the name Double Zero was implied to suggest that the bar was cool, as in low temperature.
Oh.
What's happening, forum?
And we're- Sorry.
We're back.
We got Grinched.
We are back on this show.
And we got Grinched.
No, we've been grinched.
I'm gonna grinch you if you don't shut the fuck up, you son of a bitch.
Okay.
Hey dude, Patrick's sister grinched you.
No!
I grinched her!
Don't.
I grinched Caleb and then Caleb grinched Patrick and then Patrick died.
Oh!
And then Patrick just died and made that noise.
Oh no, you're killing the Grinch!
Oh, you killed the Grinch, he stole my penis, you cannot take the penis from the Grinch!
That's Mama Grinch.
Oh my son.
Grinch, how come you never come see your mama no more?
You never come see your mama, Mr. Grinch.
Oh, come here.
Mom, I'm stealing presents.
It's just Giancarlo the bullfrog.
What?
It's just the bullfrog.
This is Giancarlo.
Giancarlo the bullfrog.
Oh no, you have stolen my penis.
The Grinch.
The Grinch strikes again.
Help, police.
The Grinch has stolen my penis.
Sorry, the Grinch steals presents, not penis.
My penis is a present every morning.
Oh yeah?
Oh my god.
It's just a present to have a penis on my body.
And it has not, and no, it has not fallen off.
Oh lord.
Wild shit.
Me and my bros were recreating the Lonely Island video,
Dick in the Box, and the Grinch stole our penises.
Okay.
This is seriously gonna suck getting these back.
Yeah.
Yeah, they take away the box and their penis is gone.
The penis is gone like...
like there's just a it's a good YouTube search like a Ken doll what steals penis
no just like a good YouTube search would be like fucking dick in the box remake
yeah I found a really good Lonely Island parody of a parody the other day and it
was like a wedding video and it's a guy and he's like oh yeah get the dance floor
ready it's about to go down put on your dancing shoes we're so in love
be funny if uh-huh if the wedding the wedding like video person just made that
without asking. What the fuck? Yeah and he claims he's never seen I'm on a boat.
I don't know what you're talking about. I'm just making a song. I wrote. I thought you wanted a song
about your magical day. Yeah. T-Pain is in the song. Yeah it's the real T-Pain.
This was not in the budget. Well the bill's here so T-Pain's asking for sixty thousand dollars.
And he's gonna get his money. And he's gonna get his fucking money. Didn't he win the Masked Singer?
What? Did he? I think so.
I just all I know about the Masked Singer. That's kind of fucked up to put a singer in the Masked Singer.
Yeah, well aren't they all singers? No, it's like actors and stuff. That's like putting
Johnny Knoxville in The Ringer. Yeah.
The Masked Ringer. The Masked Ringer. I watched, I re-watched that the other day. I re-watched half of it the other day.
Yeah, and stop cuz you were laughing too fucking hard. No, it's like
there if there's just parts of it that are like
- it like they're trying to be trying to like get sentimental shit like they're trying to yeah
That Johnny Knoxville is a good guy and then the whole time it's like he's rigging. Yeah
Yeah, no Johnny Knoxville
There are scenes in that movie when Johnny Knoxville is like talking to some of the mentally disabled people and he'll be like, you know
What I'm starting to think you retard should have rights
Wow these guys are just like me I think you guys might be conscious what were
we talking about before that? Candy!
No I thought I was still quoting the ringer. What's the big the ringer quote
everyone's still everyone's still the oh my lanta you are my woman and there's
kids who just used to say that in school and it's like the I got a whole class of
kids used to just say that in school it's pretty good yeah I loved that movie
when I was a kid oh yeah I watched that movie so many times because Johnny
Johnny Knoxville was my favorite actor.
Oh, me too.
And I don't think I'd ever met somebody who was mentally disabled.
I think I was just like, "Yeah, this is just like, might as well be the Muppets."
Jesus.
I was nine!
You hadn't met a mentally disabled person at the age of nine?
No, this was way before I met you.
Whoa.
What the hell?
God, you suck. God, I'm so smart. God damn, Cameron is owned. You're done. You're done
in this town. Yeah. God damn it. Tonight I'm doing an open mic in my hometown just because
I might as well check out what the scene is like here. I feel like I could become the king
of the Wilmington, North Carolina comedy scene. Yeah. Maybe I'll just do that. Maybe I'll stay
here. They won't like you. They definitely won't like me. Yeah, you're not going to be
the king you're gonna be the the jester you're gonna like in a bad way the
jester is the king in the court of comedy my friend no I said in a bad way yeah
what does that even mean you're like the ugly you're like the ugly deformed guy
yeah they're gonna wear their like oh this is the clown mm-hmm just cuz the
guy was born with one eye. Oh this is the clown we pee and poop on. yeah and they're like oh this guy must be the
jester yeah it's guys probably really funny damn I bet this guy's funny as shit
- Yeah, and just Caleb's in his jester uniform.
- Yeah, with like, just his eyes like stacked vertically.
- These ringing bells.
(laughing)
- He's covered in bells.
- Did you guys ever see that movie Clown
that was about the guy who turned into a clown biologically?
- No, but I know it, I know about it.
- I kinda wanna watch it.
We should do a watch along.
We should just do a watch along while I'm here.
- The watch along, not while you're there, no.
- Yeah, we gotta be in the--
- It would be impossible.
- It wouldn't be impossible.
- It would be really difficult.
yet not would not be fun and i refuse to edit a watch along
i'll edit it if you're in the way just doing what you get here
right now i don't know
if i will like movies then
uh... cities got a good we have to do what i have a good evening tomorrow so
we can do a lot of getting a new t_v_ tomorrow
what kind of t_v_ you getting i don't even know what i do want to use their
art
i have a t_v_ i have right now only is a sony and it's from
it's from two thousand only company
and it's uh... it's like eighty pounds
but it's like a it's like one of the like first
it's like from
dom's parents like all that is in their basement
uh... we've had this t_v_ for two years and it's like
shitting out on us
and everyone to eighty pounds eighty-pound t_v_
so stevie should not be that heavy
i got a t_v_ issue and i don't know if you think about how heavy it's whole t_v_
would be a movie theater
it's just a screen it would be that it's off thousand pound screen no how do you
think they get the lights inside of it
they make the room dark
yeah they just make the room dark
so there's no lights there are no says no t_v_ is a movie is dark so they may
have a lot of the right spots you can't watch t_v_ at the movies idiot
i guess that's true
they should have an option to the
didn't they didn't they uh... premiere the final episode of lost in i'm x
that's pretty sick
they're doing it on the one i had a m_c_ a list there were ads for their like
they're playing like sports games and yeah m_c_ theaters
on that's t_v_ dot that would be awful yet you imagine watching a token for
paying to watch football
on a big screen and then later
not getting free food
yeah and the and dislike
a bunch of random people great
we're probably very loud yet they don't so she had
it's the i'd like you had to score a bar
yeah i'm doing what i am i don't know what movie did
and that is a kind of a return to the movie to watch football kind of person
would want to sit in a movie theater at the popcorn for the second but i'll
couple
yeah they get up at the end of the gailer
great game
(laughing)
- They all clap.
- Oh yeah.
- I'd probably go get my dick sucked in the movie theater
while the football game was on.
- Yeah.
- That's why you go, 'cause you can't do that at home.
- They offer that at the movies.
- They offer that at the movies now?
- If you're on A-list.
- Oh jeez Vern.
I'm gonna--
- One Ernest podcast now, we're talking like Ernest.
- Okay.
- Hey Vern.
- What's up man?
- Hey man, what's up?
Hey Vern, why don't you come over here and fuck me in the ass?
How about that?
Okay, okay.
I'll come over there.
Oh, jeez Vern.
Yeah, what's up man?
You're not Vern.
Stop.
Vern doesn't fucking talk.
I do.
Bitch.
You just got owned.
Hey, rim shot.
I've never seen...
You've never seen Ernest?
Caleb, you've seen Ernest, right?
Yeah, he doesn't sound anything like that.
Yeah.
I know.
(laughter)
- He sounds like this.
- Hey, it's me, Ernest.
- Do you know Jim Varney might've fucked Freddie Mercury?
- Jim Varney from The Office?
- From Ernest.
- From The Office?
- No, from Shrinky the dog.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Was he the one who like fucked Freddie Mercury though?
- Yep.
- Yeah?
- Oh.
- Who royally fucked him?
- He lethally fucked him.
*laughter*
Like yeah, the thing is about Freddie Mercury, he was fucked in the ass tons of times, but only one of them really counted.
Only one of them where he got totally fucked.
Yeah, one of them he was fucked twice.
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
A total fuck. Mm-hmm.
Yeah. Absolute fuck.
Was he the 27 Club?
Was he a 27 Club member? No.
He was like 50 years old when he died.
He was like 300 I think.
He had sex with way more than 27 guys.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- He was 300?
- Yeah, he was 300 years old when he died last time out.
- Oh my God.
- On dog years.
- Then why is everybody still complaining about it?
- Complaining about what?
- He was fine.
About how he died.
- Isn't it so strange how like,
there's like stands for like artists like that and shit
and they're like Elton John, 'cause of Rocket Man.
- Yeah.
elton john stands 'cause they think that he's
terry negerton yeah
they think he'll be still realizes just a fat gay guy i don't think i think
is easy i was looking funny at the end on the left of the at the end of the
rocket man who carried transitions from users who doesn't seem to have a good
and the only
than the and it is not a picture of the elton john they were so that
the ugliest man alive they were doing they were so fucking generous with how
much hair they gave elton john in that movie it's insane i want to see what he's looking like
nowadays he's yeah it's uh i thought like patrick he he looks like an auntie he looks like patrick
with glasses no he looks like an auntie he looks like auntie patrick with glasses i was thinking
about someone who called who's called aunt's female uncles oh but the funny the funniest part about the
end of rocket man is the fucking uh it's like oh elton john has battled and like battled all of his
addictions except shopping and I mean I'm looking at him right now I have a
picture pulled up he literally looks exactly like gay Patton Oswalt yeah yeah
he does that's a good comparison. If Patton Oswalt killed his husband this is what he would look like.
His husband? Yeah. Yeah that's but yeah like just imagine watching Taron Egerton
for a whole movie and then they switch to this yeah they just so they put a
picture of that thing that's like a like a Goddard fade in they did that they do
like a face match fade in and then it looks like an animal I think I don't
know if Oh God he was fucking they did that with Goddard at the end and it's
like the Sun is being played by like some like fucking jacked Italian kid and
and then you see John Gotti Jr.
and what he actually looked like.
And he just looks like he's made out of sausage.
- I wanna see.
- Yeah, more like--
- We should do a watch along of Gotti
'cause that movie is fucking nuts.
- All right, I think it's on Amazon Prime.
- John Gotti Jr., he looks like a personal strainer.
- A personal strainer?
- A personal stranger.
- My personal strainer.
- He looks like a personal strainer.
I mean, he looks like a scientist
that would go on the Joe Rogan experience.
Yeah, but the actor that they got to play him looks nothing fucking like him at all.
Let's see what he looks like.
Oh, here's a picture of him with John Travolta.
Yeah.
I bet they're boyfriends, and they like it.
They probably like being boyfriends.
Unlike me, I hate having my boyfriends.
Who do they get to play?
I like Scientology that hates it when people have boyfriends.
Is Scientology anti-gay?
Well, they're anti-gay for the like...
What the fuck?
They're anti-gay for their biggest two members, which is Tom Cruise and John Travolta.
Have you read any of the...
And those guys are gay for guys.
Have you read any of the conspiracies that Scientology killed John Travolta's autistic
son because he was autistic?
No.
Yeah, they're fucked up.
That's cool.
Because they don't believe in mental health or like...
Yeah, they don't believe in mental illness.
Yeah, they don't believe in mental illness at all.
There's a dog barking.
Yeah, they're barking because I'm speaking too much truth about Scientology.
I'm taking them down.
I'm gonna go let that dog out.
Yeah, I'm wearing my anonymous mask right now and I'm fucking, I'm tearing down a Scientology.
Caleb is letting the dog out.
We're not pausing.
Yeah.
Don't hang up.
You're not pausing it?
No.
Don't, fuck, yeah, just go.
No, I don't think you can hear it on my recording.
You can, but it doesn't matter.
We're not pausing it again.
It's already gonna suck.
Yeah.
anyway
we just think about joining scientology
uh... they have my address 'cause you gave it to them yes i don't know
the other hand
was your email address did you show up in chinese yet in japanese i japanese
that's right i think i sent one to tom o'shea to
yeah i can send one to me
i didn't have a lot i think i did send one to your address
i'm going to let you know that i have the dvd but i can't say that i'm glad that
you can't find told you my home address ideas and told you my home address to
now okay and it's okay to have a free to go
yeah i got the site of the dvd in the mail to say patrick what the fuck are
you doing to see what was
going clear with the remedy
so she my mom's like
my mom hate scientology
you should yeah i think so mass
no she's smart for it
and told his good man made so many people rich
made so many people kill themselves
from yahoo
harris wills
has led not a real personality overdose yeah x yeah over the next
yeah he over to the uh... you don't think scientology overdosed him on
purpose next how would they do else
who else yet nobody only miss gafford
that's not a really sad that she's just uh... sleep she's just been
sleeping
- All right, well I guess-- - Like, serving beauty.
- I guess that's it. - And she's waiting.
- Yeah, that was it. - She's waiting for Zinu's kiss.
So actually, you know what?
It's actually, it sounds pretty good.
- Exactly.
- I'm actually, I'm turning around on this.
- Thank you.
I like Scientology.
They do a good job.
They have like a cool castle on Sunset Boulevard.
- They got a big, big castle.
- The castle, they had that Winter Wonderland.
- Oh wait, we never went to the fucking
Scientology Celebrity Center when I was out there.
- That's 'cause you're not famous enough.
so
me and cameron would have been let in but yeah they would have made you wait
outside and drink water from a bowl like a dog that's fine i'll drink water from
a bowl
dude this i didn't realize you were our bulldog i didn't realize how big of a
presence scientology did have in l_a_ yeah it's fucking creepy yeah dude when
we walked by their fucking uh...
their building on on
hollywood boulevard
i'm trying to shake my head at my dog to convince him to leave
Go away!
Stop!
Those two dudes outside of L. Ron Hubbard's Winter Wonderland
that tried to give us the pamphlet and they're in suits?
Yeah.
Shit was fucked.
Yeah man, they have like storefronts and shit.
Yeah.
It's creepy.
It's not, it makes you paranoid.
It's uh, it makes me paranoid at least.
When they follow me I feel famous.
Ah, paparazzi.
What if they're following you because they think you're a suppressive person?
that's fine I am just like while the Scientology people are taking videos if
you like this is a suppressive person blah blah blah yeah no I am thank you thank you so much oh my god
about as suppressive as it gets yeah I'm suppressing you right now shh
they think I'm impressive I'm suppressing you ah an impressive person you say
Why thank you very much Mr. Tology. Science Tology.
You have a center for impressive people? Hmm. Why don't you bring me there?
I'm a cewebwity, huh? Oh I'm Scientology's number one star. I'm Scientology's number one star.
I'm the big one. I'm the biggest cewebwity in Scientology. They're gonna put me in a big movie.
They're gonna put me in the big boat.
Send me on a world cruise.
A world Tom Cruise.
See?
That's why they made me a celebrity.
Cause I'm so funny.
And I hate that Don Wabbit.
And I hate, and I hate that Don Wabbit.
Do you think Bugs Bunny could be admitted to Scientology?
Is he famous enough?
No, I think Elmer Fudd is the only Scientologist.
But Bugs Bunny could be a Scientologist if he wanted to.
He's one of the most famous figures in the world.
- It's true, yeah.
- And they would let him in with open arms.
- He's one of the targets for Iran to strike at the US.
Yeah, they're gonna blow up Bugs Bunny's little hole.
- I know that they won't, I know he'll,
hey, he has some tricks up his sleeve.
- They're gonna throw a flashbang down into his hole.
- Can you imagine the Scientology?
- Fucking pump him full of lead.
- It's rabbit season, bitch.
They're gonna pour hot lava into his hole.
They're gonna pour molten steel into his hole and then take it out like a sculpture.
Yeah.
And it'll be his hive.
Yeah, they're gonna melt clear plastic in so you can see him.
Can you imagine how mad the Scientology people must have been in their meeting with John
Travolta after his role in Hairspray?
Yeah.
And they were like, "John, we need to explain something to you. You cannot be in movies
dressed as girls."
But I was having fun.
I was having fun.
Did you see how big my boobs were?
Yes, that's the problem.
I was married to Christopher Walken.
That's what John Travolta sounds like.
Yeah.
What are you?
Grease.
What?
Grease, movie he was in.
He's in the country of grease.
Grease.
Getting sucked off.
No, he wasn't.
Yeah, he was.
He was getting sucked off by his personal trainer.
Oh yeah, I forgot about that.
His personal brainer.
Yeah.
John Travolta got a personal brainer.
Didn't he have a sex scandal where someone was massaging him or something?
Yeah, yeah.
He was reaching for their penis.
Oh, that's cool.
Sorry, I thought it was a bottle of lotion.
Come here!
*laughter*
He's trying to...
Matter just made a fist when he said "reaching for his penis"
Just clenching...
*laughter*
Clenching a penis...
Yeah...
And your fist squishing it like Play-Doh.
I am from Scientology. Come here.
*growls*
That's John Travolta's new...
*laughter*
It's me, John Travolta!
Give me your...
I haven't done anything like that.
Give me your penis!
I need to do something about this dog so I think I need to know.
I am junching.
All right well we're pretty we're like at an hour.
We got 16 minutes to go.
No we don't we have 40 seconds.
Okay.
16 minutes.
We got 16 minutes till we hit an hour.
Oh no.
Just talk for 30 seconds.
Okay the dog's watching tv.
Guys this is getting worse every second.
Oh my god wait guys he just purchased HBO.
What?
Shit.
I don't believe you.
I believe me, dude. I'm looking at him.
I can't show you because I nailed my webcam down.
You nailed your webcam down?
Why don't you just bring the dog over here?
Because then you wouldn't see him watching TV.
Or he could watch it from over there.
You are so stupid, man. I'm smarter than you.
I don't think so.
Every single situation, I'm smarter than you. I'm outwitting you.
But sorry, I have to go.
Alright, bye. Thanks to y'all. Thank you to all the supporters.
Thank you to all, and to all, a good night.