You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[laughter]
I'm happy to be here with you today.
I have a dark cloak and I am underneath.
I have two sharp horns and two sharp teeth.
[laughter]
What do you think about that?
Yeah.
We were doing that a second ago.
- Don't trust me, I'm evil.
- Don't trust a demon.
- I am a demon, whoa.
- And I am evil, whoa.
- I am so evil, whoa.
- That's pretty good.
- I have a weird brain, whoa.
- I am a demon, whoa.
- I'm evil.
- Don't trust a--
- Evil.
- Don't trust evil.
- Don't trust a dark evil stranger.
- Don't trust sorcery.
- Don't trust the most evil guy who's ever lived.
Don't trust me.
- Don't trust a vampire combined with a werewolf.
don't trust the evil version of the Hulk it's me that's fucking scary I just
scared me evil version of the whole evil Hulk yeah they have it is he red he's
the dark Hulk dude he's called the really you didn't have a dog have a dog and a
roll they do have a dog Wow do they have a a coke a kid kid hole
They have Macaulay Culkin.
No. Macaulay Culkin?
How's he doing nowadays? Is he still addicted to heroin and like trying to do a podcast?
No, he's not addicted to heroin. He's friends with the Red Letter Media guys now.
Really?
He does videos with the Red Letter Media guys.
He makes funny videos now?
He makes cool like web content.
Stay in your lane, Macaulay Culkin.
At least your brothers are in cool stuff now.
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
He is the most possible get we could ever have.
Like the biggest celebrity. - You think we could get him?
- We could get him on this podcast.
- You think so?
All right, we need to come up with a strategy.
First of all, here, we'll try this real quick.
- Here, hold on, what if we invite him?
- You look weird and your movies are all bad.
That's the first step.
- But by the way, we'll try this first.
Macaulay, if you're listening, I know you are.
Why don't you come on the podcast, buddy?
- Hey, Macaulay Culkin, I have a bunch of traps
set up at my house right now.
- Yeah, come get me.
- Come get me, come on.
- Yeah, come on, you son of a bitch.
- You're gonna find out real quick
that I'm a better Kevin McAllister than you.
- He should do like a Taken-style movie now.
- Yeah. - You know?
But they're like, we have your daughter,
and he's like, oh, what if you guys came to my house, though?
(laughing)
What if you guys, like, there's nothing,
There's not anything weird in there, just come on.
What does he say to, he says Joe,
"I will find you and I will bring you over for a play date."
I will find you and then I'll make you
walk through my basement door.
Did you ever see Home Alone 4?
No, no, don't turn that door knob,
no, turn the door knob from the other side.
No, no, no, turn it clockwise, you have to turn it clockwise.
Oh my God, oh my God.
Would you be mad if you got eggs all over your face?
Right, it's gonna make you mad, right?
Hold on, you didn't do the--
Probably give me my daughter then.
You didn't do the thing that sticks your shoes to the floor.
Can you take your shoes off before,
you step on all these Legos please I just realized I had you guys over but I
forgot to set all the traps so if you guys could leave for like two days and
then come back I have to go buy a bunch of BB guns and some string could you
cover yourself in gasoline just for like no reason at all did you bring gasoline
with you okay then leave if you come over later night could you bring some
traps for me to set up you bring like some weird bear traps and so like can we
- We get some weird stuff. - Sticky shits and marbles.
- We get some weird stuff happening.
- Could you bring a bunch of feathers
that I could drop on you?
- Do you have like an invisible wire
that will cut someone completely in half?
- We have a, what about a toolbox?
Do you have a toolbox?
- What if he had done Home Alone in the future
and he did have like a very evil house?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, controlled by Siri.
- Did you ever see Home Alone 4?
- No, I was seeing the first one in the New York one.
- That one, no, that's Home Alone 3.
Home Alone 4 does involve a smart house that has French Stewart as Marv, but Marv is hairy
now.
What?
So, or no, yeah, he's Marv.
Marv is hairy now?
Marv is, wait, when you mean Marv is...
That's the tagline of the movie?
That's the tagline of the movie.
Are you saying he's the other wet bandit or he's covered in hair?
He's, he, so...
They switch?
They do Frenchie Friday, it's a crossover.
He is, but French Stewart is supposed to be Daniel Stern's character, but Daniel Stern's
character is now dressed up like Joe Pesci's character because he took after
him after Joe Pesci's character died in jail or something. He died in jail? That's
so sad. And it's supposed to be... All he tried to do was eat a
little kid's fingers. You know what they do to wet bandits in jail? It's not
pretty dude. They make them into sticky bandits. Yeah. They turn them into the sticky bandits.
yeah yeah but it's a it is let me let me look up yeah he has like a smart house
that he does like his pranks on yeah Marv oh and and for no reason they brought
the kid is still Kevin McAllister they got a totally new kid oh yeah I know
that they did that also a totally new kid but he's still supposed to be Macaulay
Culkin's character even though Macaulay Culkin is like at least 23 years old
when this movie came out yeah and just fucking like why do you have to make a
kid like this kid have the worst life ever why does he right yeah getting
attacked his parents got divorced and then his dad moves to a new house yeah
yeah they added divorce into home alone because that fucking well now I still
one thing yeah yeah that's the one thing that didn't happen to this saddest one
thing about being about being a child of the divorce is you have two houses to
set up traps in right? That's true double oh my god two - double the traps dude
double the Christmas presents, double the traps. Dad doesn't let me have the the jack in the box that has a
flamethrower inside it but mom does so I'm still there for the weekend. Yeah mom can I throw a bunch of
marbles on your floor if not I'm going to dad so yeah you might want to choose
wisely here. Yeah oh they're visiting okay. They're visiting? No no no no he's
staying with his mom and his mom's new boyfriend or something.
I bet he hates it. Because the dad and his new girlfriend are hosting a visit of
the royal family at the moment. Wait, my audacity crashed again dude. What the hell? It's okay.
They made Buzz and Macaulay Culkin's characters like 10 years younger. Like
the big fat brother with the flat top is now like 11. They made him two years old.
They made him two years old and played by Mike Weinberg. Hey say Mike Weinberg fast.
Mike Weinberg. Well that sounds like my Weinberg. That sounds like my Quineberg.
Oh no, not my Quineberg. Hey Patrick, Patrick say Mike Butt really fast.
my ball oh my god what did that sound like my boy is it you said my but you
still said my but I said my ball I you said my balls that sounded like you say
Mike but really fast it sounds like my balls yeah I'm getting it I do you know
say I'm gay and then spell funny colors yeah I'm gay if if you and then why co L
LORS oh my god he did it wait what the hell Wow hey Pat say poop real fast yo
that was so okay fast dude oh my god Patrick Patrick spell spell I am G but
say pronounce G like like J but with a with a good sound at the beginning yeah
- Yabba-do.
(laughing)
- Yeah, I need to get into stuff like that.
- Oh, I've been, I've been, I'm sorry,
I've been doing all this in reverse.
- Do you need to switch that, that flip,
you need to switch that flip on the back of your head.
- I need to flip that switch.
Yeah, you're in reverse now, too.
You're saying switch the flip.
- Shut up, dude.
Fuck you.
I'm gonna bully you now that I've become a jock.
- Is that what you're--
- You became a jock.
- I became a jock today, yeah.
- Wow, congratulations.
- It's the one thing everybody says
this podcast needs more of his visual gags.
- Shut up!
(laughing)
- He picked his face up. - Shut the hell up, nerd!
See, I'm kinda working.
- What's your locker number? - I'm still figuring out
the kinks, 1,000.
(laughing)
- And you know, if you count to 1,000,
since you have-- - That's a hell--
- Since you have-- - You have to type in
10, 10, like 10, 100 times. - That's a high number.
- That probably means you're a nerd,
'cause that's a high number to count to.
- Yeah. - I just am guessing
it's 1,000, it's more than three,
so I can't even count it.
So you like to guess? So you like trivia? No, I don't like to guess. I just kind of say
random shit. It doesn't matter because it's going to be a dick-suck due to my jock nature.
Okay, so you're a random kid. You're not a jock. You're a random kid. I'm not really
a random kid because I play football. I try to get football pads by today, but it wouldn't
be. Yeah, you play foosball. I just didn't have them. No. And you wear maxi pads. I play
football, American football, not soccer. And you buy a maxi pad and wear it to play foosball.
Why are you wearing a maxi pad on your face like a face mask? Because of COVID-19. Why
are you giving everyone that nerd? You guys are both nerds and you're going in my locker,
is I think one I think it's number one see I can't remember cuz I'm such a
fucking stupid job yeah you're really smart you did that on purpose it was all
now I'm getting blown under my desk by the cheerleading so you're not that
you're not stir you're not the jock you're the master of the cheerleader
coach I don't know the male male 50 year old with the creepy mustache names Hank
and he's and he's fucking sucking my dick cuz I'm such an alpha dog yeah that
even Hank with the mustache sucks my fucking jock dick.
Yeah you may have fucked a cheerleader but I fucked a coach of the cheerleaders and he
let me tell you he is something else.
Yeah wait what do you think they learned it from alright?
Hank taught them everything they know.
You should see him without a bra.
Yeah dude.
I think the coach of the cheerleading team at my middle school got arrested.
For what?
For sucking your dick dude.
For drug trafficking.
Stop back flipping.
Yeah, he brought his pom-poms to school back up one more time you're going to jail. I can't help it man
I'm sure you better stop back flipping in this restaurant right now
You have not over the fajita tray six times
The I wish I wish that more people were still trying to be like vine stars
so you would just watch people like backflip and shit and yeah purposely
injured them so that's that's the thing that's the thing about tick-tock is you
can I wish it was your bedroom I wish it was a higher density of people who who
are going out into public to do this stuff just so I could see it yeah
remember put him in a coffin no no he was the guy who would like put his arms
around his chest and then say put him in a coffin and like fall down onto like
like the paper towel displays the grocery store just like people and stuff that's
cool see that's what I want to see more yeah yeah like that and then there was
boot gang and boom exactly we need more boom gang is the more more successful
the paintball field that my brother works at yeah like they knew he was
coming and he just skipped work that day he's just like I'm not gonna work if
this fucking guys there dude there's no shot yeah cuz you know that you're gonna
to get like a shot in the eye yeah someone's right like he's gonna steal
your money or fucking like fuck your car like you don't want to be there for that
and he's constantly that's the thing about boot gang is he's always really
fucking cars I don't know anything about him I just heard that story and I was
doesn't he like over tables or and stuff yeah he likes he like gets a haircut at
the barber shop and then runs away yeah that's like one of them prank yeah I
saw a video of him like flipping over like a street vendors table or something
he's a real shit like that this guy yeah yeah yeah he's just being a pranker we
should start we should start yeah okay here's a pitch for an idea for one of
these how about the the dark vampire and you bite people from behind yeah yeah
dark vampire yeah well no no no you but you bite them it shocks them and when
they're in shock and their eyes are wide like dinner plates you look them right
in the eye and you say and you say you've fallen under my spell and that'll
be your catchphrase we could be they've fallen under the spell of the dark
vampire got your blood I'm worried I'm worried that that could be infringing
upon the put him in a coffin guy well no okay all right how about okay here how
about this how about this how about this take take him out of a coffin you find a
dead body that's in a coffin ah you throw it because because it's the exact reverse
yeah there there was actually deleted deleted footage of Logan Paul in the
suicide forest when they found a corpse they started playing tetherball with it
that was the thing people really met he threw the corpse in the bang bus and
that's one of them on dude you can't do that that's one of the craziest videos of
all time. It's so funny dude. Like the only way that there could be like a video of
in that vein better than that is if they like witnessed a murder or something.
Yeah that's like the suicide. That's like the like top. That would have been.
They're like damn that's savage. Yeah that's maybe the most like I don't think if that video
hadn't happened and someone like said that I would be like oh that's come on
that's that's too much like you know. Right that's not real. Yeah. That could
never happen but no he actually went to the suicide force. It's so sick.
Yo, I found a body
What the fuck yo?
It's so dude. I went to the crematorium, and I found dust what the fuck
Snorting cremains yeah, yeah, I
We have our own suicide forest in New York City now. It's that oh yeah
Yeah, yeah, people just been just non-stop fucking dropping off that thing dude so funny
yeah the Hudson Yards thing yeah they're just because like yeah what if I was
gonna kill myself right now that's where I would go you kill yourself on the
beehive dude I would just fucking die yourself on the beehive cuz you're
afraid I would I would kill myself I'm a Harris's vice president Wow that's
right I would stand under the thing the beehive thing and I would jump up so
hard that I hit my head on the top of it and died I was standing under it with my
mouth open try and catch people like snowflakes I was running around with a trampoline like
like clown firefighters yeah with a pool of water and then you gotta like you know
you're you're looking at people like I know that you're about to jump dude yeah
yeah yeah that that tie is a little too loose you just had a real bad day at
work and you're heading to the top of the honeycomb well guys remember that that
that news story that was like in China some guy tried to jump off his like
apartment balcony and they hit him back inside the window with the fire hose
there's a picture of it I don't know if there's video I do think it's funny when
like there's a jumper and then they just put like a trampoline at the bottom yeah
it's just such a funny way to ruin that if you want to have the best day your
life. If you don't do a backflip at the end of this, well that's why they do it
we're gonna kill you ourselves. They do that jump and I mean that's the coolest
fucking trampoline jump you can do and they're like oh my god I was gonna kill
myself? Life fucking rules this is sick. Yeah they do like a quadruple
backflip and then they get on the ground they start whistling and walking like
Mickey Mouse yeah that's a but the thing is the people who just like sit in their
window they're never gonna go anyway yeah yeah you can always yeah you can
always so so what was the Hudson Yards the Hudson Yards honeycomb it was just
like this horrible like statue that you could like walk on it was like seven
stories is it like is it is it like tech like some startup shit like some
stupid New York yeah I mean it was it was like a a redevelopment thing of this
like area that I guess nobody lived in and then yeah it was probably no you
know but it was probably like a bunch of black families lived there and they were
like how we put a honeycomb here no they actually used to live in the honeycomb
there was a hive of Puerto Ricans and then they actually shoot him out and
turned it into a statue. Yeah, they smoked the honeycomb. Yeah, they killed the Queen and then they just
scattered all over New York City. Yeah, they all went to like Soho. Mm-hmm. I don't
know where the, I don't know where the people live in New York. Yeah. They live,
well I live here. I know, I know the Hasidic people live in Williamsburg. I'll tell you what, the Jocks live in Ridgewood.
I live in a Jock neighborhood, yeah. Yeah. Yeah, it's pretty awesome. There's some
good Jock food around here, just like a piece of white bread with peanut butter on it.
cheeseburgers, yeah.
Whey protein.
Yeah, big milkshakes.
Yeah.
It's interesting, Caleb, that you recently became a jock because I actually like just
recently like changed too.
Yeah.
What'd you do?
I'm like a cyborg.
Yeah, well, the thing about a cyborg is it's like not really real and then like a jock
is kind of the realest, coolest thing you can be.
I mean, you're looking at me right now.
Yeah, but I can see you and I don't see any components.
Well, it's underneath my skin, you know.
Well, how about you rip it up because it definitely won't hurt you because you're such a cyborg.
I'm half human so I'll get half hurt. I'll do it after the episode.
You promise? What parts of you are cyborg?
My everything. Everything because a cyborg is half.
That means you're a robot then. No, no a cyborg is half robot so I'm all half
robot. So every part of you is 50% robot.
Why are you still blinking? The only way that you're going to prove to us that you're a cyborg.
That's my targeting system. No, you can't blink.
can't blink that's the only way you're gonna look at it you're talking to me
for the rest of the episode I'm not targeting you you're not at you in fact
when I look at you my targeting system says flee I'm mentally doing and then it
has a little bullet point that says not not the guy flee okay yeah not the guy
named flea yeah yeah the little it's cool that that's his name speaking of
bass my downstairs neighbor which he can hear me right now for sure very thin
floors he recently got a bass guitar oh the second person in my life to ruin my
life with a bass guitar Nick Zapatrick this morning I woke up to the brotherhood
it's not a brotherhood of bass there's no brotherhood of bass you guys don't
ownership the low notes it's not a low note brotherhood you guys should call it
the loser hood yeah it's a guitar for women it's not a guitar for fat women
that's the strongest fingers to play the bass it's the guitar very heavy strings
perverts dude yeah that's literally a guitar for sex creeps it's not yep it
literally is no the guitar is the guitar for sex creep because you can play the
guitar at a party you know what I could play the guitar or I could play this
weird ugly instrument that only perverts play I do it for me and no not perverts
for you cuz you're a pervert no yeah yes perverts don't play the bass you're like
You're like, I want, you look at a guitar and you think, I wish there I could go to a number
lower than six.
Yep.
And that's also, that's also what you think in your love life.
Mm-hmm, that's right.
That's right, it's for pedophile perverts.
That's what the bass guitar is.
Listen, the point is...
You're gonna have a lot of unsubscribers after this.
I can tell you that.
Why'd you say you?
You're on the thing too.
We are, and it's gonna be your fault.
Are you leaving the podcast?
I'm starting my own podcast it's called Talkin' Bass.
It's not called Talkin' Bass.
It's gonna be me and Victor Wooten.
Nobody knows who that is because nobody plays bass guitar.
That's not true.
Victor Wooten plays bass guitar.
No, I'm gonna kill you.
Listen, my neighbor, my dad's his neighbor, he got a bass.
What if he got a six string bass?
I'm gonna shoot you in the head, I'm not kidding.
He woke up this morning, I woke up this morning, see you're making me fuck up dude.
My jock brain can't handle this.
I woke up at 10 in the morning.
You're just jealous because I'm in the band.
he you are not in the band and if it was a battle of the bands I would defeat you I
just use there's no band so I'm in the battle of the bands this week and the
jocks yes no and me and Caleb are competing for Jessica's love Jessica is
I is Marty my girlfriend I'm gonna win the battle of the bands dude you're in
the butthole of a man that's right yeah you don't find a bat the base you play
the ace I play a man's ace a man's ace hole a man's ace hole is what you play
you play although you know the little ridges around your butthole little
wrinkles you play those you pick those slap those all each of your buttholes
tears is a string to you that's right yeah and you play that's fine it's just
more impressive that I can make such beautiful music with it you fucking lube
up your fingers with pert plus and just in the shower go to town on that you
You installed a pickup cover over your asshole.
I did.
That's right.
My neighbor...
Your poop comes out sideways now.
My neighbor got a bass and this morning started playing Blister in the Sun, the worst version
of Blister in the Sun of all time because it's just bass and just very slowly.
And then I went to Trader Joe's for two hours.
I was gone.
And then I came back and he's still playing it.
And he's been playing it until an hour ago.
It's five o'clock.
I would never play Blister in the Sun.
from 10 in the morning to 4 p.m. just blistering the sun.
All musicians should be homeless. You shouldn't be allowed to live near anybody else if you're
a musician.
Absolutely. Especially bass guitarists and drummers. Those are two instruments that--
No, no, no. And singers, too.
I agree. Singers are very-- yeah, people who sing Hamilton around their apartment should
just be euthanized normally.
Like theater singers?
- Singers?
- No, just singers.
- Just anybody who's singing.
- Anybody who makes music should not be--
- What about you?
- I don't anymore, I quit.
- He wears headphones though.
- I'm a cyborg, dude, I can't, I don't have like a
creative side anymore.
- He can't think of love, so he can't make any music.
- It's like, instead of music, I'm focusing mostly
on logic nowadays.
- This is gonna be terrible for the battle of the bands.
- Kind of like figuring out different problems and issues.
- Could you be my tutor?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, do I have to wear a special outfit or anything?
No, but I can't pay you but I just like won't like be the shit. That's fine
I'm gonna like I'm gonna drain money from your savings you you
Are you gonna hack into my bank right now? Yeah, I
Think I already did it didn't intend it in you're getting swirly. You're getting shoved in my locker
I'm gonna fucking if you swirly and he'll break and he'll the shits gonna break
No, half of my shit will break first of all and second of all
I installed anti swirly shields over all the toilets in the school and in your house and everywhere else
Well, this is gonna be terrible for battle of the bands because I thought Cameron was gonna be in my band
I said we're banning it's not possible
The only instrument is I work at play a cyborg could play a drum machine, but I won't cuz it's against my principles
We're called my band. Our band is called
God's dark trick
Okay, I'm joining your game for I'm not a cyborg anymore anymore. I'm joining your band since I'm a jock
I'm Christian and I will be abstaining and also I will be we're gonna create we're gonna write
I'm guys guys most insane goth rock. I'm a werewolf now. Just wanted to let you know I switch
I I used to be goth and let me tell you what it's a hot
It's a bad lifestyle and now I work with a charity to get people out of it
Okay, so when you make jokes about that kind of thing it actually is like like that impacts people yeah, yeah, I'm goth now
I'm the goth you're gone. Okay. That's cool. I'll hang out with you because I'm a werewolf now you should join the program
No. I'm gonna put you through my program. I'm gonna run a program on you pretty soon.
It's not gonna work I'm not a cyborg anymore. You gotta keep up. Goddamn it.
You guys, hey Caleb, next full moon you better watch out. Yeah Caleb that's right.
Why? I think the moon's made out of cheese. You don't think the moon's made out of cheese, you fucking liar.
I'm a dumb British guy. Wallace and Gromit? No dude I'm a jock okay and I hang out with my
dog and we invent dude he turned into Wallace I'm nothing like Wallace I don't
have a giant mouth you're bald too yeah you're starting to look like fuck dude
god damn it I need some Winsley Dale right now I can't wait to do some I can
can I be the battle the bands I'm not changing for anything I'm being the goth
at the Battle of the bands you can't be a I already was a goth dude you can't like
I'm the guy that thing again you can't got you're not dude I can see that you're
not you have a red hat on if you were gone Oh Patrick's be all all black all
day Patrick's conservative now nice right after Patrick's the first
conservative cop mm-hmm all goths are conservative I'm concerned they can yeah
they conserve darkness exactly they conserve the devil in serving the
darkness here watch how goth I am
as boys don't cry well isn't that a movie
now that isn't that a sentence yeah that's a different movie that's your
thing if boys don't cry is not a goth movie it's actually a sad movie because
It's about a boy who can't cry.
That's me because I'm a jock.
I only cry when one of my friends dies in a jock driving accident.
I can't control how I sometimes.
We're mixing too many, we're mixing too many, I wish I never brought up the jock thing now.
Okay, I'm going to take off my jacket.
We're not, we're just three guys now.
We don't need to be all a jock and a goth and a werewolf cyborg.
Can we just be friends again?
Boys don't cry.
I'm not a jock.
That's not what boys don't cry is about.
That's not what boys don't cry is about I don't know I'm not a jock anymore. Okay, I quit the lifestyle
I'm out of that lifestyle - I'm just a normal. So what are you?
I'm just no, I'm not a nerd just come that a jock. It's not like a one or the other it's
Put you in a lock. Yeah, you were not
Now, you can't team up on me as that's what jocks do they are on a team like a football jocks
That's not true. Jocks are lone wolves and that's not
What are you talking about?
Way before I was a little more before you okay?
I was alone though because none of you guys were caring about me, okay, so I'm a werewolf now so now you're not
Unless I bite you I'm the I'm the tea. I call Teen Wolf. No. That's the best about
Wolf you can't I'm John wolf. It doesn't make you wolf. I'm Teen Wolf, and I'm gonna get Parkinson's later in my life, okay
I'm a Power Ranger. I didn't know we could fucking do that! I'm the golden
Power Ranger. Okay I'm the Black Ranger. Okay I'm gonna become God right now.
You don't get to be God! You can be Zordon. Silence! You can be Zordon.
Okay if we're me and Cameron are Power Rangers you can be Zordon. I'm the devil
now. You're both catching a smite. No. No I'm the Black Ranger. What's that
about man that's weird what I'm the devil and even I know that's bad to say you're
not the devil the devil now you were the gold ranger you were the goal we were
supposed to be fuck just keep up okay we're not doing Power Rangers anymore
that's kid stuff we're all adults now I'm mr. in five minutes
you're a monster mom now all right then I'm Batman okay I'm also mr. mom you
now one of us has to be Mrs. Mom and yeah sure I guess it's me
fuck I'm Batman you can't just be Batman for no reason you have to have a
backstory no no no I'm Batman because you get to be one Michael Keaton movie I'm
gonna be the other Michael you are Robin okay and I am Robin you're Robin from
Howard Stern what's up I'm gonna put you on a Sibian you did she didn't put
people on the Sibian. I'm putting you on the Sibian. She was shocked by people being on
the Sibian if you'd ever fucking listen to Stern. I did. No you didn't. I'm doing my
own thing as Robin. What's Howard Stern's last name? Howard Stern. Obama? It's not Obama
dude. Did you know Robin dated the guy who did the voice of Special Ed on Crank Yankers?
Really? Yeah. That makes perfect sense. Yeah. Yeah. Did you know that the Crank Yankers
are pop were not their puppets and they were on film normally
you have those guys in cement anything besides the anchors
now they were in the muppets you know i was hit they were in the background i
guess that makes sense
what you wouldn't give those guys a starring role
shit camp that is in the cranking kers are real
Hey, wait, oh, Pat, Pat, you're getting a phone call.
Bring, bring!
Uh...
Pat, Pat, you're getting a phone call, seriously.
I don't...
-Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding! -Bring, bring, bring, bring, bring, bring, bring!
Dude, I think it's the Crankyankers.
Dude, pick up.
-Pick it up, dude, seriously. -Pick it up. Hurry up, pick it up.
Pick it up.
[coughs]
I don't know...
-Pick it up, it's right there. -Patrick, pick up the phone.
Uh, hello?
I'm a black puppet!
-Bla, bla, bla, bla! -Oh my God!
-And I'm real! -Oh my God!
Hey Pat!
Oh my god!
What's up man?
It's Black Puppet!
I'm the prank keeper from the prank prankers!
Oh my god, he's real!
And I'm real!
Alright, gotta go!
Oh no, no, no, stay on the phone!
Prank me!
He didn't prank me!
No, no, no, you gay as hell!
You gay ass motherfucking as hell right now!
Yes!
I'm being pranked!
Yay!
I told you Pat, they're real, okay?
Oh my god, Patrick, I think your phone's ringing again.
Motherfuckin' as hell right now.
Yes! I'm being pranked! Yay!
Yeah, I told you, Pat. They're real, okay?
Oh my god, Patrick, I think your phone's ringing again.
*sigh*
Bring, bring!
Oh, hello?
Hello, this is the Jerky Boys!
*gasp*
*scream*
And we're real too!
I don't even like the Jerky Boys, but it's so assuring to know that they're real!
Hey, guess what, you gay!
*scream*
Yes!
Uh, Pat, you're getting another phone call.
Hello this is New Hampshire Regional Hospital, this is Patrick Doran.
I have some very bad news about your father.
What?
He got shot out of a cannon.
Again?
Again.
It makes sense if your dad was a stunt man
That would make a lot of sense you have like son of stunt man vibe. Yeah, yeah
No, if I was the son of a stuntman, I'd be a businessman cuz I would be like dad. I hate your stunts
Yeah, I don't want to join the family business. I hate the family business
I'm a black sheep. I think is not solid. I mean, I ain't steady work. I hate getting a bullseye with my target my target
Hmm. Yeah, come on. I launched into my target. We don't have any money for groceries. Come on, honey
I'm just waiting for one more stunt to come through. Oh the Grand Canyon needs to get come on
I just think it's something you're in Canyon and
Then we'll make it
I'll get a grad school
If I can catch one knife, okay with the handle this time, it's gonna be big for us
All right, I'm gonna need you to shoot your left to lose
I'm gonna need you to shoot this bullet right at my teeth. I will catch it and it's gonna put our kids to college. So
We're gonna need to make that happen
So thank God we're not stuntmen and instead we're podcasters the steadiest income and job you can possibly have
I mean if you think about it
It comes in every month. So it's basically a very regular normal job
Yeah, yeah. Did you guys have any at Christmas? Did you have to talk to any family members about what you do?
But they are now what I do there. Do you know I didn't see any of my extended family nice. Yeah, I mean neither
Neither of us are super spreaders, but it's cool. I'm a super spreader. Yeah, I'm super spreading those legs cuz I'm a jock
Yeah, you're extended families legs. Yeah, dude. They're extended your grays in North Carolina. It's legal
You know you can marry all of your cousins in North Carolina and most states
Yeah, you marry one more than one person. Can you marry hold on you can marry first cousins in, California?
Yeah. You can marry someone else's first cousins.
Those goddamn hippies.
Arizona first cousin marriage is allowed if both parties are 65 or older or one is infertile.
Listen, if we're both single by 65 and we're cousins by then, let's get married.
Because it's legal.
Or if one of us is infertile.
If one of us is infertile. Yeah, true. I guess, does cousin marriage really, do you really
get a fucked up kid like all the time yeah yeah really yeah I don't think it's all
it's not a hundred I mean you can try as many times as you want Caleb I see you
can try and disprove that if you'd like unfortunately I don't have any hot
cousins who are DTF so bummer adopted cousin marriage allowed is is well that's
not even you can yeah of course you can fucking well no adopted cousin is allowed
in Massachusetts that should be you should marry somebody that it's not blood
related to you yeah that's true right I'm sure what about what about it's not
allowed unless unless they're an animal yeah I'm drawing a hard line you cannot
you think you should be able to marry a one-year-old if they're not related to
you and unless they're under the age of I'm hold on I just realized any what I
I just realized I'm on the Wikipedia for cousin marriage law in United States.
Yeah, you're at the very top of it.
Oh my god!
What?
You're at the top of the Wikipedia.
You married your cousin.
This is a Wikipedia that is editable.
Yeah, wait, check the talk page.
I want to see what the updates are on this.
I want to hear what people are talking about.
Switch to the visual editor.
Start editing.
Okay, where is the talk page?
Just control F talk.
Cameron, you're going to have to do that.
Yeah, listen cyborg, we're gonna need you to hack this.
I'm not a cyborg anymore, I'm...
You don't even remember what you are anymore.
I'm a...
Look at me, you don't know who you are.
I'm the devil.
You're nobody.
You're nobody, you're nothing.
Cousin marriage was legal in all states before the Civil War.
Anthropologist Martin Odenheimer
argues that marriage prohibitations were introduced to maintain the social order,
uphold religious morality, and safeguard the creation of fit offspring.
Writers such as Noah Webster
and ministers Philip mill mill mill doler mill mill doler huh mill doler
i think you call me a milf doler because i'm pulling out them milts
that thing where johnny knoxville's like had like 90 in bread jeans that was
pretty funny yeah yeah that that made me laugh
because he's like a good looking guy yeah like it doesn't make a lot of sense
But maybe he has a hidden eye or maybe he's just invincible. Maybe that's why he's so good at stunts.
That was his mutation. Maybe his skull is like a helmet. Maybe. Yeah.
There is no talk page. No talk page. But I can tell you looking at this that
1500 people view this page every day.
They're just curious. They're curious, dude. They're cousin curious.
Oh, here's a-- here's--
I found the talk page.
Cousin marriage court cases in the U.S.
Question. Okay, I would like to know if me and my first cousin could have a relationship
if his mother and my father are brother and sister. Does that make us blood even
if we don't share the same mother? Please let me know. From Amber.
Yeah, I mean, is he-- even though he's not technically my brother or sister, I can marry
him, right?
This page used to be named kissing cousins.
You should be able to marry your cousin...
If somebody complained about it.
You should be able to same-sex marry your cousin, right?
That makes sense.
Maybe.
Because you're not going to fucking...
You can't create some fucking...
Yeah, oh, here's the...
Hold on.
I don't know how I can show you this, but I'm on the list of cousin marriage.
You know at the bottom of the Wikipedia pages, they have that block of text and it says like...
References?
Related.
No, like under references where it's like related articles and it's like tie...
well this one's like types legality culture theory and it's got like those
like it usually has them for TV shows this one is for incest what's it got
it's got types legality culture theory cases and related related genetic sexual
attraction inbreeding Western Western mark effect and the
page for motherfucker the cousin marriage talk page links meet they suggested to
merge it with this page called list of coupled cousins is there like some
famous way we didn't a president marry his cousin well Albert Einstein Charles
Darwin sweat see president Caleb Werner von Braun well that guy was a good guy
that's all I know yeah Josiah Bartlett second signer of the United States
Declaration of Independence whoa too many people sign that don't you
feel like he values it a little bit that there's so many signatures on yeah
Matthew Thornton did yeah you know who the fuck that is no one knows no I don't
know I don't know anybody on that list but Thomas Jefferson
Carlo declaration of independence was Thomas Jefferson the president John
Hancock is the biggest one the Buddha Mary's cousin that's kind of sick
actually pretty cool why did John Hancock sign his name so big on the deck series
first wouldn't you if you were first and you knew there were like 50 other people
decide wouldn't you just take up the whole thing just be like haha
he had really big eyes really small big cartoon eyes yeah that was why he was
hurt to heal well yeah oh here's an Alabama governor married his cousin and
listened to his name and his cousins name his name his name is bib graves his
cousin's name is Dixie Bibb. That is the name of like two evil babies. Bibb Graves
and Dixie Bibb. Saddam Hussein married his cousin. What is this? That's just a rumor. I mean
this guy how evil can you get? Jesse James. First he does whatever he did. Jesse James the
cowboy. Or Jesse James the weird motorcycle guy. Yeah the cowboy. Damn.
again pure evil did seems like a lot of evil people and then the Buddha it seems
like the most people who marry their cousins have last names that start with
M just based on this list okay so just be if you if anyone out there has an M
last name Jesse James Jesse James the motorcycle guys the one that he like
cheated on Sandra Bullock with a woman who did like boudoir photographs and
like Nazi hats and all celebrities cheat on the most beautiful women in the world
with just like a Nazi yeah the ugliest Nazis you can find guys I have some more
big news about cousin couples yeah Abraham Maslow who's the guy who created
Maslow's hierarchy of needs yeah uh-huh seems like his cousin was a cousin
pussy yeah yeah check this one out Muhammad Islamic Prophet what did he
look like I appreciate that Edgar Allan Poe
Jesse James Rothschild's I'm on I'm on the Jesse James Wikipedia now he dated he
was married to the woman the enema of the state lady whoa fuck really yeah the
woman on the covers. You think she did the pose for him every night? She probably did the pose every night
before bed and he just blasted a rope. Was she a real nerd? He blasted out a lasso dude. He blasted out a
Jesse James style. That's right yeah. He shot a cattle prod out. He's wrangling her. He went from her to
Sandra Bullock. Downgrade. Huge downgrade dude. Well if you think about it it makes
sense. Bull. True. He's following the cowboy. He has got a cowboy name so he's
gotta follow the cowboy style. Celebrity men just have bad taste in women like the
Tiger Woods thing he had like I guess he fucked a lot of women but it was like
yeah he had like a whole like WNBA bench that he was fucking mm-hmm yeah some
real. Jesse James was in Tony Hawk's Underground too I just remembered. He's a
skater? No he rides the he rides like a motor scooter. That's kind of sus. Yeah
yeah yeah yeah it's like how how you know you can't write a report Jesse James
you got to have some Nazi fucking scooter yeah you know Nazi scooter mm-hmm
biggest swastika I've ever seen in a video game and I've played Call of Duty
5 and Wolfenstein sometimes there's so many Russian people in my neighborhood
sometimes I feel like I'm in a Call of Duty game when I walk down the street I
Was gonna say there's so many I thought you were gonna say there's so many Russian people that I feel like a Nazi I feel
Like putting a swastika flag in my window
But I'll just hear him and I'm like gonna click it like it's like hair on the back
Yeah, you hear that you spin around and it's like a guy with like a gas mask on his lower face and like one white
eye, and he's like
He's like we have to intern the Japanese
yeah yeah I need to get out of the yellow hello we have to do 9/11 the Russians
do it no that's in Call of Duty yeah they the rut dude called the hates
Russia it's so awesome yeah they're just like they're like it they're like to the
people who make Call of Duty infinity ward thinks of Russians like most people
think of sharks yeah it's like they're they have no they literally everything
that they have to make the Vietnam War we have to drop bomb on no that's the thing
they don't see what again I say that they did it in the first place and the
recent Call of Duty game they said that the Russians did the highway of death
which is something that the Americans did it's like a war crime yeah the
The Holocaust was my idea.
Yeah.
They had the idea.
I am Yekov Smirnov.
We have to push it.
I love to do the Holocaust.
We have to push this Greg's grandfather off a guard tower.
We have to push Jason Derulo down the stairs.
You all think I'm funny comedian in the United States.
It's me tricking you.
I am tricking you into thinking that I am funny comedian.
Russians are responsible for every bad thing that ever happened in American history.
It's true.
We have to frame Ellen for being mean.
We have to frame Ellen for being gay.
The most evil thing I can think of.
Yeah, there's no gay celebrities in the US, it's just Russian psyops.
Yeah.
Nathan Lane, the straightest man who has ever lived.
We are going to make Pumba gay!
No!
Take it back!
You're not gonna do anything to Pumba, you goddamn Russian bastards!
You ruski sons of bitches!
We have already put the potion in his blood!
My name is Josh Gad, and I am assigning doctrine to your children!
Josh Gad's the ultimate Russian fucking agent.
yeah he's the Russian spy yeah what's that what's that about it he's a snowman
yeah you ever you ever see why is his his neck and jowls are so big he's got he's
got he's got a man there he's got a whole thing of dinosaur from Jurassic Park
he's got a whole thing of kielbasa and borscht just yeah he's like one of those
he's like one of those poison tree frogs and if you touch him you become gay yeah
he's infected most of most of the acting community at this point that's why they
have to do mocap now. I am Josh Gad. I am heavy weapons guy.
Dude Josh Gad should play heavy in the T2 movie.
That would be amazing.
Alright Josh Josh Gad is heavy yeah Ben Affleck is scout okay
soldier Jackman is sniper yeah soldier on Claude soldier is is my own Anjani
mm-hmm Oh demo man is Don Don I'm a pyro pyro is Melissa McCarthy how about
just like a Norbit style Melissa McCarthy plays everybody yeah yeah oh my god an
even better movie yeah I know dude that'd be fucking sick I am Melissa McCarthy
yeah she plays her she plays Melissa McCarthy playing tf2 yeah it's like a
meta movie I am Melissa McCarthy and you will taste my sandwich damn I used to
have tf2 posters in my house really did yeah that's pretty I just outed myself
as a non jock right there but yeah did you ever see the how to make a bonk video
no oh man I almost did that shit I was a fucking bonk is the scouts oh yeah what's
your bonk um the video I watched growing it was like a Red Bull and then like
too crazy for me. I'll pass. Yeah, not for me. It's Red Bull. It's too much. It was a
Red Bull with like pop rocks and juicy drop pop and like it was basically just
too much sugar. When you were a kid did you ever have ever come up with
inventions like that? Just sit in the kitchen and you're just mixing like corn starch and
milk yeah you're like this is like super milk right now yeah yeah food coloring
and eggs yeah damn I feel like dr. Seuss yeah I'm mixing egg whites and egg yolks
no they have a potion out of it I used to mix all sorts of nasty shit and then I
just put in my freezer and my mom be like the fuck is this is a fucking
freezer it's like this brown slide everything green in the freezer I'm a
scientist I wish I had still had that like spirit of creativity yeah yeah I put
you put like you put like a flashlight inside of like a toilet paper roll and
be like look it's a toilet paper roll that lights up yeah I decided to become
an inventor mom I just took your calculator and unscrewed the back and I
drew I drew a smiley face on it now it doesn't work mom I snapped your
Macbook in half and now it's two computers. You're welcome
Easy
That's what I was dude. I just
If you cook snow in the oven it gets solid like model magic. Did you ever?
Did you ever put like?
Soda in the freezer and then like wait till it froze and then you kind of like you eat it like Italian ice
But you don't know why it's not working like Italian ice. Yes, of course now
I did tons of fucked up food things.
I would also eat just dry spaghetti when I was a kid.
- Yeah.
- I thought, I was like--
- That's weird.
- I thought that that's what farmers had in their mouths.
(laughing)
You know how farmers always chew it on wheat?
I was like, that's spaghetti.
That's dry spaghetti.
So I would walk around pretend I was a farmer.
Bread tastes good.
- Yeah, it's true.
- It probably tastes like bread.
- Probably tastes just like bread.
Damn, I'd go for some wheat right now.
- Yeah, you see a farmer chewing on wheat
with peanut butter and jelly spread on it.
(laughing)
- You think hay tastes good?
- I mean, no, I know hay doesn't taste good.
- Why do them horses go so crazy for that shit?
- Hay.
- Yeah, you like hay?
Wait 'til you have a fucking McDouble horse.
(laughing)
- That's true.
- Yeah.
- Would you guys eat horse meat?
- Yeah, probably.
- Oh, absolutely, probably already done it.
I've been to Taco Bell so many times.
- They don't put horse meat,
it's so expensive to kill a horse.
- No.
- Yeah.
- What do you mean it's expensive to kill a horse?
It breaks its leg.
- They are tough to kill.
if it jumps weird you just shoot it in the head
no
no yes now you have to convince it to run into something really fast
it's hard to it's like a crash test it's like when they're testing cars
they'd use the same track for horses yeah no they'd yeah until like nineteen
sixty they just put horses in cars and then just crash them into shit
'cause if a horse dies a human will definitely die in a car
yeah that is not a safe car if a horse died in that car
It's like, that's tough to kill a fucking horse, dude.
That's a tank.
Buying a car at a used car dealership and then you're like, "Just one thing, a horse did
die in this car."
That's what horsepower is.
It's how many horses they killed with that car.
How many horses did they kill?
Yeah.
This is 800 horsepower.
We crashed this car 800 times with a horse in it.
Never died.
Pretty impressive shit.
If you can crash it 800 times-
The car's beat to shit now, though.
Yeah.
Because they have to do it.
They have to do it for every car.
It's also full of horse shit.
- Yeah, we didn't clean it at all.
All the horses are still in there.
- Yeah.
- Oh, here, okay.
- Hey, your problem now, buddy.
- I found the bonk recipe I was talking to you guys about.
- What is it?
- Okay, it's 7-Up or Sprite,
Coke,
Cream Soda,
Kinney,
oh, it's a Maltese drink.
If you're living in the USA,
Dr. Pepper works just as well.
- Is it a recipe from Malta?
- What the fuck?
- Yeah.
Stir these four drinks together until mixed really well.
So there's no Red Bull in it?
Well this is a different one.
This is on the Steam community.
The one that I saw does not exist anymore.
Yeah?
It was too fucked up?
So someone from, that was a Maltese person that wanted to make Bonk?
Yeah.
I'm trying to find the Bonk that I knew.
The really gross one.
I mean I don't know anything about Malta at all but as far as I know there's probably just
like real life TF2 over there yeah.
It's all just dusty and there's a payload.
That's why he doesn't have a soul.
Yeah, he was a failed spy actually.
He's being a spy right now.
Yeah, you're just walking around Malta fucking pushing a cart with a giant bomb in it.
Yeah.
Sorry I gotta get this out of town pretty fast here.
Avoid that big guy over there.
Alright, here's another one.
One pack of black cherry Kool-Aid,
two small cans of Red Bull,
one full can of Monster Energy,
one bottle or can of Nos,
one can of Mountain Dew Kickstarter Fruit Punch flavor,
a pack of Warheads.
So it's any disgusting...
Like, just put anything in it.
Bonk can be... It's fucking shit and water.
That's what Bonk is.
One bottle of Sprite for fizz,
Juicy Drop Pop.
They put fucking eight energy drinks in it,
and they're like, "We need more fizz."
We need Sprite. We need to put Sprite in this because it has to have a fizzy taste.
You guys want to make this? Yeah, I'll make it. Yeah, let's make it next time you come to New York.
Yeah, just throw up. We have to make Patrick's Delight or whatever it's called.
Oh yeah, we have to make all those cocktails. Yeah, we have to at least make Patrick's
Delight and Bonk, I guess. What was like... No, we don't have to make Bonk. Did you guys
ever... was there ever like a fictional food that you just wanted to eat so bad?
yeah there's a whole YouTube channel for this yeah predator me oh yeah I wanted
to eat the Nickelodeon slime yeah yeah I wanted to taste that shit you can
make it I think we've talked about this I think I said the knocko from Kim
possible what was the oh the nacho taco yeah just have that at fucking Taco Bell
now they don't have that so Doritos taco oh yeah you just knew more about Taco
about them Patrick did. Wow dude I should die someone should kill me that's that's
really bad news. You know they took away the gordita? They put on they put back on
the menu of quite a few things that they took off. What do you got? Pikachu would
probably not taste good. Probably tastes like chicken cuz that's what I learned
from TV most things just taste like chicken. It tastes like rabbit like fizzy
rabbit maybe I guess depends on the rabbit yeah sparkling rabbit yeah what if
I mean do you think like Gordon Ramsay could really like fucking make something
delicious out of it yeah you have to cut the red cheeks off Oh fuck me fuck me
you've left the cheeks on you've got the tail completely attacked.
no the cheeks are like the oyster on like it like a chicken like it's like
it's like it's like a fish it's like a fish thing where that dude what's that
fish food oh I didn't know I didn't the third time I said it come on
keep on you're saying fubu you thought I was just saying fugu over and over no I
thought you were saying fubu I thought you were just saying your favorite
clothing brand you think you could crack a fushigi like an egg yes and eat the
inside that'd be delicious and magical pure magic comes out of yeah yeah fuck
me you post a fushigi for too long oh there's a bit of fushigi shell in your
omelette fuck me it's barely even magical now fuck oh we've got six wizards coming
in fuck me six wizards all ordering fushigi did you cast a dark spell on
this or something it's fucking cursed oh fuck me you've cursed to me
is it terrible Gordon Ramsay impression yeah I honestly don't even know what he
sounds like that sounds like a British guy I was just pouring my coffee back
into my coffee I thought you were peeing in your butt straight up excuse me miss
Miss, Miss, excuse me.
Oh my bad, I thought you were peeing in your butt real quick.
My bad.
(laughing)
Have a nice, have a bliss day.
- He's chasing someone down.
- Hey, what was that sound?
- Excuse me, Miss, Miss, excuse me.
Oh shit, did I drop something?
No, I thought you peed your butt.
- I thought you were peeing all over your butt.
- Oh, that's my bad.
- Oh, I'm sorry, I thought you were pooping to the front.
- God damn, I thought you pooped at your front for a minute.
- Damn, I thought I was looking at your pants,
I saw something poke out,
I thought I saw a brown shoestring coming out your rear end.
You know what they say man, say something, see something.
So I was just fucking hollering at you.
I was just saying, say something, see something?
Mhmm. Yeah.
That's called manifesting baby, that's the secret.
That's right.
That's the secret.
Have you guys seen it on...
Oh ma'am, ma'am, excuse me, oh I'm sorry, I thought I saw a soft coin behind you.
I think it's soldier boy. I think soldier boy posted a video
Where he said his favorite book is the secret
That's awesome. Did have you seen the I watched the trailer for the movie the other day because it was like on the movie
Yeah, it was like on my because I guess they made the movie first and then they made the book
And there was a it was like on my Netflix front page and they make it look like the Da Vinci code
Yeah, it's so fucking funny. Yeah, the secret dark secret that that nobody wants you to know
the secret held by Leonardo da Vinci from a dark world and then it's just like you just gotta believe in yourself man
Believe in yourself create a mood board and manifest things. It's so fucking awesome
They sold it as like some some like fucked up a little naughty thing
I thought that the secret was like I did think it was like a Da Vinci code style fucking yeah
I thought it was like a book about secrets
That's a fair assumption. Yeah, no, I thought it was a book about a dark secret the cover is
The dark secret that's a different. Yeah, that's a different book
Yeah, the cover is like a wax seal that says the secret and it's right
I'm about to fucking crack this thing open. I'm gonna learn all about like the Clinton crime family or some shit
but it's just a fucking
It just tells you what every like bad comedian tells you to do right? Yeah, like law of attraction
You need to write down-- - Yeah, believe in yourself.
- You need to keep a notebook.
You need to write down all your thoughts in your notebook.
You need to keep a little black notebook.
Don't wear shorts on stage.
If you wear shorts on stage, that looks bad.
- Don't ever fucking write anything down on your phone, okay?
You need a notebook, you need a notebook.
- And don't listen to what she said.
(laughing)
- Yeah, that's the real--
- I know what you're seeing in our Facebook groups, but no.
- Now write down, okay, now write down my name
in your notebook.
Now write down-- - Write down my number.
now now handed out to people at the restaurant before the show my secret
honestly kid Kratom Kratom is the secret to comedy you just gotta fuck you know
you create about 50 50 mg's every day before the one you want to know the
fucking secret age people think it's funny when I collapse you want to know
the secret to comedy all right listen first of all you're gonna learn the hack
okay yeah second thing you're gonna gain access to the sex offender registry
industry. Third thing, you're gonna see my name in there. It's a false flag, okay?
It's not meant to, it's not supposed to be, we need to right some wrongs. It's a
mirage and you're in the desert right now. You're visualizing an oasis of sex
offenders. Okay, you're now in the sex offender matrix. I'm downloading
knowledge into your head. Don't ever use it. Never use this knowledge, not on stage.
yeah all right I have been drinking coffee out of a pot so I have to shit my
pants yeah me too I get it to crap all right bye babies
Um...