You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[Laughter]
I'm loving the mustache, dude.
Thank you, it's back.
It is back.
It's back after a long time.
A long hiatus on the mustache.
Yeah.
I think someone told me, um,
someone told me it looked weird when we were in New York,
and it was when I had that really high panic attack,
'cause I was...
Because somebody made fun of your mustache?
No, no, yeah, that's why I had it.
So I took it. I was taking Prilosec and it made my heart rate go really fast.
That is still the funniest thing ever is that you had like half a beer and one hit of somebody's blunt.
And just bugged out and you were like, "I have to..."
And all of a sudden you were in Escape from New York.
I had six gin and tonics.
We have to find the Duke of New York and we have to kill him.
That should mitigate the effects of the of the weed but it just made it you you
went completely lost your mind I went completely pale yeah you just went home
alone - yeah you turned green dude I did yeah somebody told me that my
mustache looked weird and I went what?
oh yeah and those NYU kids were mad at me for hanging out with my friends yeah
God, such pussy.
They went to Eataly for snacks.
How rich do you have to be?
I know, how rich do you have to be to go to Mario fucking fat guy with the Crocs?
Batali.
Super Mario, I think is his name.
Super Mario, yeah.
That's what you're thinking of.
Super Mario Batali.
Super Mario Batali and he jumps on interns.
He flattens them.
Yeah, and he collects golden coins from his restaurant.
Yeah, that he puts in their vagina slots.
That's right.
Yeah, it's just a slot down there.
It's just, it's nothing but a slot.
There's a slot and there's a coin return button.
All women have, they have the slot and then they have a little lever and you pull it and
then their eyes go, uh, like a dollar sign.
It's like on an arcade.
Yeah, their eyes turn into dollar signs and that's how you make money.
That's called being a pimp.
It's like an arcade machine where they have the slot and then they have the little thing
next to it you can press to get your coins back and that thing you press, that's the
the butthole and you can get the coins right back out of the slot.
No, the clit is the coin return and they come out of the butthole.
No, the clit is the joystick on top of the arcade machine.
It's actually a completely different location.
And the boobs are the game.
Wow.
The boobs are the big buck hunter rifle.
Yeah, the boobs are, instead of duck hunt, it's duck hunt.
Yeah.
And you play with that thing.
I don't even want to speak its name.
That thing.
That thing that shall not be named.
That horrible thing.
I hate that thing.
That thingy.
I've started just earnestly laughing in Seth Rogen's laugh recently.
Yeah.
Would you guys still be friends with me if I had Seth Rogen's laugh?
What is his last sound?
Everyone always talks.
It's like a "hahahahaha".
Oh yeah.
Yeah, like that.
I think I have.
"hahahahaha".
I laughed like Kitty Foreman a lot. I've done a lot to not laugh like her.
Do it.
But just like...
[Laughter]
Oh, you just laugh like that.
Yeah, no, I do.
When you... if you have like... again, if you have like even one gin and tonic...
Yeah, you go...
That's how your laugh turns.
Yeah.
I have a pretty bad laugh. Unless I'm laughing really hard, I do the like...
[Coughing]
Oh, you do... that's kind... I would say that's Seth Rogen adjacent.
Yeah, it sucks.
I hear you so much.
That's inverse Rogan.
It's like a fucking, it sounds like a bird choking on something.
Hmm.
Specifically a bird.
Seth Rogen is choking a bird.
It's fucking hot in my apartment.
Seth Rogen is choking on a bird.
Dude, okay, so basically the system I have- It is 77 degrees in this room.
The system I have right now for recording is I blast the fans in this room, because
this is, I'm in a sunroom, which is named after- That's the only fan I have.
A sunroom is named after the- You're pointing to a window.
The temperature- There's a fan in it.
Is approximately.
You have a fan.
I don't even have, I have to turn off the fan because it makes too much noise.
I'm in a basement and I got a fan so I'm cold as a cold piece of fish.
The windows in my apartment are too goddamn small to fit an AC unit.
I'm in a sauna with a bunch of fat Swedish guys and they all sit around.
We don't even have any hot coals, their bodies just generate enough heat from their big fat
beautiful bodies.
They're sitting there just saying like "Ah, sweet Voskarsken!"
You look Swedish right now, you look like Bill's brother.
You look like Will.
I think, Pat, when you first joined the call,
I thought your headphone cord was a chain.
I was like, "Goddamn."
Dude, I should.
You're so close to an upgrade right here.
Yeah, I got this shirt.
I got these shorts.
Patrick's new loadout, dude.
Check out these shorts.
Oh my God, nice.
You can see the outline of the pocket in 'em.
Yeah.
Yeah, you do look like a Matty Matheson before photo.
Yeah, before he started drugs.
This is what he looked like as a young boy in Canada.
- Yeah, probably.
I respect him as a chef.
I respect his recipes.
I do find his presence kind of,
I think he's leaned too much into it.
- Being shrill?
- Being like, "Ah!"
- Yeah, he does know how.
- "We're gonna make a kick-ass nacho today!"
(laughing)
- Oh, fuck.
- You're right, this is the best Monster Energy.
Yeah, Monster Fiesta is the best one.
It took them years to figure that out.
This makes me feel like an animal, dude.
It's the new flavor.
That one and then Rosa's pretty good.
I hated Monster Rosa at first, but I've come around to it.
It doesn't taste like it's meant for your mouth.
No, it's supposed to be mango too.
This is supposed to be mango?
Yeah.
Why'd they make the can blue?
Exactly, what the fuck?
Like a blue raspberry.
Yeah, like a blue waffle.
Yeah, a blue mango.
blue banana they made a ball banana blue it's blue because it's the it's a party
you can just make things blue is what is what companies figured out as you can
just make flavors real you can just turn also I swear to God when I started God
when I bought this I looked into new nutrition facts and it said zero
calories and now it says 10 calories it changes like the like the cores like the
- It pours like mountains, but it's just as you drink it,
it keeps adding calories.
- Oh, fucking speaking of Monster Hunter,
I went to Star Market today,
and I don't know how this happened,
but they just like, I went there just to get like,
one thing, I went there specifically just to get a monster,
and then like maybe some lunch.
- And a toy.
- And they just did not, and a toy,
and some jacks to play jacks with.
- One of those little dollar sheriff sets
that has the handcuffs.
- Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
the moment curfew drops, you just walk up to people.
I'm wearing like a kid outfit.
I'm standing with the cops just like that.
What's your badge number?
Uh, it says made in China.
But yeah, she didn't, um, she didn't bag my monster energy.
And I got, I went to the one I met up with, uh, Dom while she was like.
watching the kids that she now I can't I got to stop giving away
information about her job.
Yeah, about your kids.
Kids.
Well, I went to a park.
People are gonna triangulate who the kids are.
I well, yeah, they will.
Yeah.
God, I hate I hate revealing myself.
I hate showing my ass.
You love showing your ass.
Oh, I love to show my ass.
What is the this is turning into a Patrick story so fast.
What what is the point of them bagging?
She didn't bag it.
I walked all the way to Brookline and then walked back here and I didn't have a monster energy.
Oh, that's because she was expecting you knew that you were just gonna drink it.
So she didn't bag it. That's what they do.
That's like how they don't bag gum when you go.
Like, the most insulting thing that's ever happened to me is one time,
I was at a food line here in North Carolina,
and they didn't bag my milk.
They just said I had a gallon of milk,
and they said it on the thing like I was just gonna drink it.
[laughter]
I was like, what the fuck do I look like?
- They looked at your bones.
- This guy's probably gonna drink.
Yeah, this guy's small bones.
- They looked at your bones and were like,
ah, you fucking, those things are tiny as shit.
Unlike me, who's big bones.
- I had to bag my fucking milk.
It was so embarrassing.
Everybody behind me sort of whispering,
he's gonna drink the milk on the drive home.
(laughing)
And then I did.
- Yeah.
- When you're ready to drink.
- Yeah, I mean, if it's out.
- If it's out, I don't want it to go bad.
- Yeah, the bag protects it from germs.
- It was a really hot day.
probably would have curdled on the way home so I had to drink the whole you know
oh my god next fucking Patrick is is is patting himself with a handkerchief like
that's a paper towel
I have the vapors
it is so fucking hot in here
I bet it's hotter here do you see I'm not even I mean I'm a little shiny but I'm only shiny
Look dude, I fucking I'm Patrick heard Patrick heard Caleb talking about a gallon of milk and he got too excited
Just from the thought
I kind of look like the guy from the Oscars statue. You look like the guy you like this
Yeah, the Oscar you look like the guy like Oscar office. No. Yeah
You look like the Oscar that was given to Edward Norton for his performance in American History X
They gave him a custom Oscar.
In a Nazi trench coat.
Oh fuck.
That just brought back some great memories right there.
You remembering American history?
Of your custom Oscar?
Yeah of my custom Oscar.
Yeah exactly.
Fuck dude.
I'm T-5 days until I come up to Boston.
Nice.
And I'm not allowed to see at least Cameron. Yeah, I'm not gonna get my family sick. You should I
My dad's got kovat. Oh, yeah. How's that going? Yeah, he said my mom said he's feeling like 70% better. Oh
He's all he's like over the hump. I
Don't know cuz it could get worse, you know, like I'm like I've been I've been freaking the fuck out
Because like my mom smokes I don't want my mom to get fucking Cove it will smoking protects against it. Yeah
Yeah, I know smoking is it
Well only if you smoke makes your lungs strong menthols. I heard yeah, and she smokes
Only if you smoke a hypodermic needle with the vaccine in it one big cigar a day, which is the problem
Yeah, she smokes one big crap like it's a cigar every single day and we're worried that it's filling her lungs with crap
Yesterday I went out to take my dog on a walk and there was like a cigar like butt or whatever
like in my front lawn.
And I was so confused.
In your mouth.
So confused because I don't know who.
There was a butt in your mouth, a dog's butt in your mouth.
There was my adult, the people.
Oh yes.
Yeah you were swallowing your dog from the back.
You unlatched your jaw like a snake and you started eating your dog.
I was trying to figure out who would be smoking a cigar because my upstairs neighbors are
are a BMX guy and a personal trainer lady.
- Cigars are huge in the BMX community.
- Are they? - They are.
- Yeah.
- All right, well that explains it.
- Yeah, it's a bunch of 13 year olds on mongooses
just puffing a giant cigar.
- Just a guy riding a Colt bike with--
- Cigars are to BMX as weed is to skateboarders.
- Yeah.
- Everybody just--
- That's why they keep, they have little plastic things
that you can put on the top of your peg,
and in that peg you can keep a bunch
of Swisher Sweets in there.
- Exactly.
A thing that BMX riders love to do
is put a cigar butt in the spokes,
so that when it goes it sounds like a motorcycle.
- Well no, when it goes, it goes fast enough
that it sets the cigar on fire.
- Yeah, and then they smoke it.
- Yeah.
- They smoke that shit.
- When I was in high school--
- That's actually, you know, that is kinda true.
- That is kinda true, actually.
- No, all the kids--
- That thing about the cigars and the bikes
actually kind of true. All the kids that I went to, well all the kids I went to the
skate park with in high school. All the kids I went to cigar camp with, they all played on BMX bikes.
They all played on BMX, no but the BMX kids all smoked like cloves and shit.
Like they all smoked cloves and swishers. Well that was, smoking a swisher
suite is one of the funniest things ever. I know. Yeah before I, like me and a
friend we we would we like we would buy a cigar and then go to like a playground
in my hometown and just share a cigar. Yeah I stole from the quick stop I
stole like one great cigar or no no I didn't steal. One great cigar. One great cigar.
This kid I used to hang out with stole it and then we hid in the woods
near my house and we smoked the cigar and we kept freaking out because we
thought that like cars like every car that came by like freshman year and we
just sat in the wood oh I found and then I found some kids like stash and I found
like one of those joint rollers I don't like the ones where you like the manual
ones a Dominican guy yeah I joined roller I found it and then I sold it at school
to some kid for like 15 bucks and went out
and bought Skate 2.
Damn, dude. Nice.
You flipped it.
Oh yeah, oh I flipped it.
I had five bucks left over.
Holy shit.
So I got Skate 2 and then I kinda just had $5.
You shoulda kinda spent it on one of those Burger King games.
Yeah, 'cause it was at a--
Remember those?
It was at one of those old,
it was at this place called Play and Trade in Londonderry.
Damn. Yes.
every business like that is just uh... not gonna exist anymore
uh... yeah second-hand game stores like i'm so like there's that replayed placed
in allston yeah yeah go there but that was definitely not be i went there in
high school it's uh... it's a
it seems nice it's fine
well yes a fucking games yeah it's like whatever what do you have
it's a larger like a hundred years there's not there's not too much range
in like a good game store versus a bad game store now there's a man is pretty
much all the same. It's just like, it's a good one. Also sell DVDs. Yeah, exactly. And the
best ones sell naughty DVDs. A little, a little curtained off area that says Caleb Jones.
You remember that? Yes, the sex. That's right. GameStop. And yeah, I went there. Oh, dude,
that place was awesome. I bought fucking I bought Pokemon XD Gale of Darkness there. Yeah,
I bought an Xbox controller there. Yeah, they had that they had like GameCube games and porno.
- That place is so good, and it was called Sex.
That's the best part of it.
- And it was called Sex.
- Yeah.
- Do you think they saw that coming?
- Saw what coming?
- Yeah, Sex?
- What was it called?
Consumer Electronics Exchange?
That was the acronym?
- They're like, yeah, just arguing all day.
It's like, it's Kex, okay?
It's called Kex.
- It's Kex.
- It's a hard C, it's Kex.
- Consumer.
- Yeah.
- These kids are so stupid.
- You just say the letters.
Nobody's gonna pronounce it.
You just say the letters.
- Yeah. - It's fine.
- No one's gonna read that. - You're just gonna
nobody tries to pronounce CIA we're gonna be fine okay
Kia and then that's why and the police come in the next day and are like hey we
have to shut this down because your game store name is sex and we're here to shut
you down yeah yeah this business is giving people ideas about what to do in
the bedroom we cannot be having this there's a the game store in my hometown
is they they had like a big long thing where people people were like super mad
at them because they put up a sign that was like you have to take a shower
before you come here that because people it's been smelled like a fucking oh
smells like yeah it smells so it's more like a little box every time you walked
Dude, this one time at like fifth grade, I remember we went to play and trade because
we were going to trade in games and as we were looking, we had just traded in and got our
credits and we were looking around the store and this dude with a ponytail but he had a
beanie on too and he had a t-shirt, a Mario t-shirt.
Did he have a cutout?
Did he have a hole where he put the ponytail through?
No, he just had the beanie, the ponytail going.
I honestly, I wish he did, because then that would just make him like cooler.
Yeah.
But he walked up to my little brother and went like, "Do you like my shirt?"
And this guy had to, my brother, I was like 10, so my brother was like eight.
And he walked up to him and was like, "Do you like my shirt?"
And says, "Do you like mushrooms?"
And it had every Mario mushroom.
And my mom pulled my brother away from him.
- Yeah, dude, he was fucking, he's about to get,
- He was just trying to make friends, dude.
- Yeah, he was trying to make friends
with an eight year old bull.
- Yeah, that's fine.
- Dude, that was the monster from It Follows.
(laughing)
He's about to fuck him to death, dude.
You've been walking behind him for hours.
and i miss you think you know i was like it follows you'd be like the monster
turns into a is like whoever you had sex with three
it and uh... no concern in the whatever also i think it is a good i was the i
was the it was like the person who
you had sex with last
and like a guy's getting followed around by like a kid who's like no i swear
okay well i think that the thing is it's is randomized
so it could just be anybody's that's that's my theory on
the o_j_ murders is that it just looked like a good idea
wasn't it
while the situation is in it follows situation with a month it was just
it was a list randomly turned into a cold and it's a little it never had sex
this wouldn't have happened
exactly so yet again women having sex is really the problem
yet that's true that's why she deserved it
i'll say it
she deserve whatever she got yeah
that's the message i took away from it follows
- I mean, the message I took away from "It Follows"
is that OJ Simpson has great comedic timing.
- Yeah, he does.
He knows when to pop out.
- Yep.
- Yeah.
The thing is, if you're at all a Christian,
which I consider myself to be,
you would just think--
- You can't say that with that haircut.
- Yeah, I can.
I'm the right kind of Christian.
- The right kind?
- The right kind of Christian.
(laughing)
- Come on.
- But yeah, you should be,
I mean, she really did get what was coming to her,
just because she had sex, which is,
as far as I'm concerned,
one of the most evil things a woman can do.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, she should've gotten stoned.
- Yeah, maybe if she smoked a little bit of that G-
- Ooh, yeah.
That's what they did to women in the Bible.
They just got them so high.
(laughing)
Yeah, we brought her out into the street,
And we got we made her smoke the fattest fatty she ever saw.
We just-- That good Bethlehemian weed.
We put a gas mask bong on her and we just didn't stop lighting the damn thing.
That's right.
Yeah.
Yeah, and then she died.
She died out of fear.
Yeah, she got so paranoid.
Yeah.
She got-- She died 'cause she saw the truth.
They didn't want her-- Yeah.
She passed through the, she saw the, the, the, the DMT council.
The DMT council.
The elves.
The elves, yeah.
Yeah, she saw the jester.
She saw a shit ton of DMT and all you saw was Elton John.
Yeah.
I love all of those, all those stories of like people seeing the DMT elves.
They give them like such hyper specific advice for their lives.
Like there's like fifth dimensional beings who are like, Fred needs to spend more time
with his stepson.
Yeah.
Whoa man.
Oh.
man. Oh, God, he told me I need to upgrade my PC, man. Oh, shit.
Yeah, imagine just having to go back in. Like there's like, like
everyone talks about it. Like they've had some really like
positive thing with just imagine just like them telling you just
like, man, you just gotta go out. You gotta go out to Walmart,
buy yourself a new belt, man.
That thing.
Yeah, honestly, man, you are ugly as fuck. And I don't know, we
don't really have a solution for it.
Honestly, man, you just need to Google Tai Lopez and watch his
videos and just get some fucking, just pull yourself up by your bootstraps.
You gotta learn, you gotta learn how to speed read.
You need a millionaire mindset, dude.
You know, honestly, man, like we, the elves, we usually keep tabs on pretty much everyone,
but we don't really know who you are.
We're not really sure what you're doing here.
So last name.
Do you go by maybe?
Yeah.
What's your maiden name?
You have maybe a different name that you go by?
Honestly, we don't really like talking to you.
So just don't do DMT again, man.
We're actually out of session right now. Yeah, come back later.
We have machine, we have machine, machine Rand Paul is doing a filibuster right now. We can't really make any decisions.
Yeah, we're kind of in gridlock.
Yeah, it's very partisan.
The machine Elf Council.
Machine Rand Paul just read the first page of The Hobbit.
We're gonna be here all night.
Jesus Christ.
We're gonna be here for whatever the fire dimension version of night is sorry the elves and the jesters are having a company picnic so
Where this is our day off?
Shit, oh, no the the DMT elves are having a company softball game and in
elf Steve Scalise
We're gonna have to deal with this
Yeah, I'm uh, I think I've told this probably before but when I was there's this comedian
Ryan something some comic who has he's like one of those like Shane Moss comedians who has like
Like a podcast about drugs about like doing drugs and he was like one of the first stand-ups I ever saw when I was 15
and
He I went to the show
And he just talked about like DMT and all this stuff and I've been like reading about DMT and then after the show he was like
saying hi to people and like trying to sell shirts that had like you know like
a pyramid on it or whatever and I went up to him I was like hey man next time
you're in town let's do some DMT together and there's like a 40 year old
man and he like grabbed me by my shirt and he was like listen man if you have
DMT like I want to do it tonight I need to do it tonight and I was just like oh
I'm sorry man, I don't, I actually, I'm 15 years old
and I don't even really know what that is
and my mom is picking me up.
- And then he said, and listen to me,
do you like my shirt?
- That's how he sells the shirt.
- Do you like this?
- And he was wearing a weed leaf shirt
that said expand your minds.
- Yeah, he was wearing a Weezer shirt that said Weezer.
- Yeah.
Hi-Fi pot spot.
- Whoa.
- That fucking, that website I found with all the,
All the weed t-shirts and shit that would like the the kovid mask that said my favorite stoner calls me dad. Yeah
I gotta buy I wish I'd gotten on the mask thing
You know
I know I wish I had gotten on the like
like the comedians who
Now since I can't do comedy or just making like shirts with like the worst like kovid jokes on them or like the tiger king
references, yeah
- Yeah, COVID is, yeah, Carol Baskins did COVID.
- Yeah.
- It's so fun, like I--
- I think COVID spreads through sardine oil.
- I can't like believe that people watch that show
and like their main takeaway from it was like,
all the like, oh, Carol Baskin stuff
and not like the on-camera suicide.
- Yeah, the on-camera suicide.
- It's so insane.
That episode like fucked me up.
Like I got really upset watching that
and everyone who watched that was like, wow.
yeah I don't understand that at all I felt kind of ripped off that they cropped it
it felt like those old those old like prank images back when internet sucked
where it would be like a girl like a naked girl but only like right above the
nipple yeah and then it switches to the troll face yeah exactly just let it load
yeah but it's like the fucking the on-camera suicide the fact that Joe
exotic is grooming straight teenage boys yeah and then he like sings his song at
the kids funeral. Yeah, dude and then everyone's like oh he's innocent though. Free Joe Exotic.
Yeah, free Joe. Fuck you. I want that exact, that guy who died, I want his exact headstone.
Just an ATV. They just parked an ATV over his dead body. It was like Rip, whatever,
Tim, I don't know his name. Yeah. His name was Brandon Dassey. His name was Brandon Dassey.
His name was Patrick Exotic. Brandon Dassey's the kid from Making a Murderer. Yeah, the
one who looks exactly like you and has the same brain as you. He does not look like, he looks like Peter Griffin.
Yeah, so like Peter Griffin. You look like PETA Griffin. Vegetarian. I didn't, I didn't watch the rest of Making a Murderer.
Did you guys? No, I got bored. I didn't watch any of it. I got bored with all those. The first two episodes were so boring. The only good one is, is the
Jinx. Yeah, well I mean Tiger King was good, but like, if you look at it, if you look at it
through like oh look at these fucking horrible people yeah it was like it was
enjoyable like not like oh Joe Sontag is awesome I think yeah I I just hate like
all the fucking like you can clearly tell Netflix pays people to just like
make the post like to start those things and then people are dumb enough to like
just be like oh this is the new meme we're gonna show Aaron it was so
apparent with bird box exactly yeah people are so dumb and I'm so
- I'm so smart, I would never fall for that.
- I would never watch anything 'cause I'm actually so smart.
I would never tell anybody.
- Yeah, I would never talk about it on my podcast, okay?
- Yeah.
- And also, I love, right now I'm fucking cops' wives.
- That's what I'm doing right now.
I go around all the time and I fuck the police's wives.
- Yeah, that's kinda my thing.
- That's kinda my thing, I fuck that.
- That's kinda how I, yeah.
- I'm actually a bootlicker.
booklicker your book licker yeah you're a book licker and I fuck Oh cop wife
you're a butler actually fuck a wife of the police officer I fuck these
sergeants wife before these George's wife sergeant's wife you're a pirate
yeah yeah great job guys practicing my rewarding the people close to police
officers with sex yeah yeah yeah yeah nice going yeah that's normal yeah
Yeah, seriously.
Having a normal day on the poopy diaper site.
On poopy diaper earth.
What police don't realize with blinding all these people.
The ozone layer is like the earth's diaper.
Police don't realize that blinding all these people with tear gas canisters is creating
a fleet of super soldier antifa pirates who are just gonna come back twice as hard, baby.
Yeah.
Just shooting crossbows and finding Davy Jones' locker.
Shooting crossbows and semen.
No, no semen.
they're shooting they're making come tributes to the cops and the cops are
getting mad they're getting pissed off that would actually be cut you know that
I hope that riot police don't find out if you splatter their their visors with
cum they can't see it that's actually not a bad idea is like you know that
picture of what's her name your mom to scar Joe she the guy is handing her the
the cum tribute he did of her to her you know that photo no oh it's a photo of a
guy he's handing a photo of her covered in cum to her while she's like walking
down a red carpet but that might be a good idea with the cops yeah
database and print out pictures of all and just print just come on every single
Go on.
Yeah, we gotta get Dr. Gay on that.
He would kill it.
Yeah.
Um, I love the, just the idea of Tom Segura just watching Tiger King and just, he's, the
entire time he's just writing down t-shirt ideas.
And he keeps like trying to find one about that kid's suicide, but he's like crossing
it out.
Yeah.
He's like, pan the camera down, no.
God.
I just, t-shirts is such a funny way to make money as a comedian.
Yeah.
Yeah, wait, so Tom Segura is making fucking... Tom Segura has like a bunch of t-shirts that are like "Carol Baskin did
Did Donald Trump." Yeah
It's awesome. Did she?
She did actually. Oh my god
Yeah, she her husband was Obama and he she killed him in office and replaced him with Donald Trump. Yeah, that's insane
I hate this epidemic of Carol 19
That's what the t-shirt says. Yeah, that's a great t-shirt. And then it has a and then it has a picture of Bob Marley underneath it
Bob Marley the comedian. And then it says in small text and all of the shirts at the bottom say
listen to reggae change your perspective.
That's what they all say on the back.
Carole Baskins shot the sheriff. I'm just trying to spread the good word.
yeah man we should we need to get on the Carol Baskins t-shirt yeah we need to
get on the Carol Baskins t-shirt thing we need to get on real Baskins Carol Baskin
I need to make those shirts in three years yeah Carol Grinch skin yeah oh
there we have a green rancher with a green Carol Baskin what about big what
about like the big cat rescue logo but it's big Grinch rescue whoa oh my god
now that would be downright evil I think we could make some serious money off of
that yeah yeah yeah what about what about a Carol Carol Baskin Robbins yeah what
about she's Robbins the tiger community of fun what about care Caleb Baskins
Cameron I can't Patrick Caleb Cameron Patrick whoa now that's gold
Can we just morph the two of you?
Caleb Baskins and Cameron Exotic.
Whoa.
And Patrick, you'd be the libertarian fat guy.
Pat Antle?
Doc Antle.
The guy who has the--
No, no, the one who's like the nerd.
No, the one who's the nerd who just ran his campaign.
I'd be the guy who had--
No, you'd be the nerd.
I would not be the nerd.
You would be the nerd.
You would be.
I'd be the guy who had Sugriva.
No, I would be that guy and you guys would be my wives.
That's fine with me.
You guys would be my husband.
That's fine with you, Patrick?
I have amazing double D titties
that you paid for, Caleb.
That's true.
Yeah, I'd get you all blown up.
Ooh, ooh, I get some great bulldogs.
That's fine with me 'cause I installed
poisonous acid inside of my pussy
that will melt you into pieces
if you try and have sex with me even once.
Cameron, Cameron is a military.
That's my natural defense mechanism.
Cameron Millie has pussy.
Yeah, it's full of poisonous acid, though.
It's full of, yeah, 'cause a guy's come to that, innit?
he's got it he's got an audrey to pussy
and it says this is a great week and i i i i i i think it would be a t
yet and i think he did like a soul singers for a year
yeah
three
me
and
for the hot dog open their
the
and what's that other night
you want to know if my pussy
Yeah, I watched a video of Cameron's.
Dude, Steve Martin kills it in that, dude.
Oh my god, he's amazing.
He's like the boyfriend I want to be.
[Laughter]
Cool.
Yeah, you want to be a dentist.
Cool dentist motorcycle.
What else would you want?
Yeah, and I can't think of anything else he does in that movie.
He does nothing else.
He does nothing else, especially not the...
What's her name?
I don't even remember her name.
Helen Green.
Yeah, she's going to be Helen Black and Blue when he's done with her.
Yeah, that's what they say in the movie.
That's what I say.
They say that in the movie?
No.
I could have written that movie.
Yeah, I could have wrote that movie.
I could have wrote that movie easy.
Here's what I would have done.
I would have had two plants.
Okay, so it's a weed plant, right?
I would have had five plants.
I would have had two plants,
and I would have made them kiss with those big lips.
Uh-huh.
Right, and then we get a third plant in there.
Little shop of stoners, right?
Oh, and he grows a big weed leaf.
He grows a big weed leaf, and it's Smoke Me Seymour.
No, it's Little Shop of Connors.
And it's a guy named Connor owns him.
And he's growing weed in like a little--
♪ Little shop, little shop of Connors ♪
Yeah, and he has like, oh, and he sells the weed.
Yeah, yeah.
And he grows it in like a--
And Christopher, Christopher guest walks in and he goes,
"Hey, what is that plant there?
"Is that indica or sativa?"
(laughing)
It's actually a hybrid.
And he's growing weed in like a hole in his wall
that he covers with his dresser and he's doing hydroponics there.
And then Smoke Me Seymour and then uh...
His name is Weedmore.
Yeah, Smoke Me Weedmore.
Smoke Me Weedmore!
[laughter]
Smoke me all night bong.
Yeah!
Oh my god, dude.
That's good, that's good.
I think we're doing another stoner special right now.
Uh huh.
Tuck in your weed napkin and your weed pants.
I was watching the Lord of the Rings.
- Lord of the Rings.
- Put the directions to this parody on your weed maps.
- Watching Lord of the Rings a few weeks ago,
and this just reminded me,
I was like laughing so hard,
imagining like a drug dealer growing Uruk-hai,
like in his closet.
(laughing)
Like Hygropon, or like in his mom's backyard.
He's having like a secret shed,
where he's just growing like big orcs.
- Yeah, it's like a shed, and he opens it,
it's like that uh that like hit where all the eric i are growing out yeah but
there's just one or he has like a heat lamp yeah and he has like teenagers like
from the the nearest high school like coming by to look at just like the one
orc yeah he grabs one guy and pulls him in and eats him his pit is set up like
Patrick's house it's just like a chair and a TV yeah he just sits there and
watches Lord of the Rings. How about Lord of the Thing and that thing is weed? Oh
yeah that's what I'm thinking about. Yeah smoking a thingy. Lots of the thing and
it's about lots of weed. Oh my god. How about Lots of the Bling and it's like a mixtape.
Yeah I don't like that one. Remember they had like 1 million Newgrounds
parodies that were like Lord of the Blades. One million Newgrounds parodies.
There's another one right there. That's a Newgrounds parody in itself. Yeah. Dude I miss Newgrounds. I
miss just like sweatily hovering over the NSFW like 18 plus tab. Oh yeah. And
clicking it. The interactive games. Oh my god. I told you guys about the. Master Chief
penis dress-up I told you guys about the one that was like it was called like the
Sims day and night and it was like pictures are like real good buddy oh
yeah those were the best when I would sneak in just a real nude photo into a
game there was one I forget what it was called there's one game where you played
as a hunter and a bunch of gay guys would try to run up to you and fuck your ass
ass and you had to kill him. I forget what one second I'm making a list. That's what my life
is like. That's exactly what my life has been so far. Fuckin, what was the other, oh did
you, did you guys ever play Bill Cosby's, fuck what was that game called? There was a game
on Newgrounds like when the Bill Cosby allegations came out I was like oh they didn't. The Newgrounds
stuff was still happening then? No, no this was a game I played in like fifth grade
but uh it's called like Bill Cosby's fun game? Something like that. Let me
look this up cuz it oh yeah yeah Bill Cosby fun game and what you do is you
literally like hit you hit women with a Kodak camera and you feed them Jell-O
pudding pops and then bring them into your dungeon and this was made in like
2000 like I played it when I was in like the fourth grade and then when all the
allegations came out against him I was like oh no one else played that game
like you guys didn't know there was some really there's some really formative I
just want to circle back and I looked up the game is called ass hunter there was
Do you guys remember the smooth pedophile one that was about Michael Jackson?
No.
Yeah, yeah.
Where the guy's like, he's like, "McCully Culkin, did you tell them that you were gay?"
They just accused McCully Culkin of being gay.
It's like a kid who got touched.
And then there was the one, the Bush and Kerry one.
Oh man.
- Man, you can't play Bill Cosby fun game anymore
because, what is it, Chrome doesn't support Flash anymore?
- No, they still support Flash.
They're ending the support, I think, December 2021.
If Flash player's blocked,
that's 'cause you have it blocked in your preferences.
- Okay, here is Bill Cosby fun game on scratch.mit.edu.
(laughing)
Just, I'm imagining just some kid,
oh my God, it's--
- All that money-- - No, no, it--
- All that money that Epstein gave to MIT
went directly to this project.
(laughing)
- This, oh my God.
Somebody really did fucking remake the game in scratch.
(laughing)
What is it called?
Bill Cosby fun game?
- What is it?
It is a game where you lure people in with pudding and then hit them with the shovel
and put them in your dungeon.
Wow.
That's just awesome dude.
Yeah, that's just awesome.
And there's a remix with Donald Trump.
Oh dude, I remember this.
You played this one?
Yeah.
The Bill Cosby fun game?
Dude, I played all these.
You remember Stick RPG?
Yes, I do remember Stick RPG dude.
Was that the one where you could like, you got in a bar fight and stuff?
Yeah, and there's caffeine pills.
I remember asking my mom for caffeine pills for Christmas
because I saw them in that.
And I was like, "Dude, it's like a superpower."
Yeah, it makes you strong.
It turns you into a stick guy.
Yeah.
And then she told me they were illegal,
which I don't think is true.
No.
Did you guys ever watch like stick figure...
They had them in that Sick by the Bell episode.
The stick figure fight animations?
You ever watch those?
Oh, yeah, of course.
What was that?
Madness Combat?
What was the...
Madness Combat was sick.
It was like a stick figure animator.
Oh, oh fuck what was that called?
What do you mean? There's a lot of them.
There was like one that everybody used.
Yeah.
Oh, Pivot.
Oh my... Pivot!
Dude, oh my god. I made so much karate stuff in Pivot.
Oh man, I made so much shit in Pivot.
All of them. I remember I made one that was just like a guy with big balls and he falls over.
[Laughter]
All my pivots were too fast. I didn't understand frame rate or anything.
I think I have a YouTube channel from when I was a kid that's just pivots.
Yeah.
Let me see if I can find that. I'll find it later.
The guy that filmed the video of my little brother breaking his arm showed me pivot
because he was making like karate stuff and pivoted.
People love that video, Patrick, of your brother breaking his arm. I don't know what it is.
People love people getting hurt, dude.
Yeah, people love seeing my little brother when he was fat getting fucking...
Well, you can tell, you can just tell he was like annoying, like just by how hard he screams.
You can just tell he's like kind of an annoying kid.
Yeah, he kind of was.
Yeah.
I'm sending this to him.
I think I was probably, I don't care.
Oh, I'm sure you were worse.
I was way worse.
I'm in the background.
I'm the kid that says, I'm the kid that's talking about a South Park episode.
I, I, the, the Walmart episode where they break the mirror.
I was pretty old before I... I had to wait for my parents to get divorced before I could watch South Park.
Yeah.
Oh, I snuck... dude, I played fucking Bill Cosby game. I played Bill Cosby fun game at that age.
I remember the first time I saw South Park was a kid at summer camp showed me it.
Whoa.
Yeah, and I was like, "Damn, this is crazy. They can say that stuff and they're just little boys who are animated?"
Yeah, wait, I'm a little boy.
And I'm animated.
Maybe I'll do this.
F you.
Yeah, hey man. Hey teacher.
Hey teacher, you're-
F you man!
Hey teacher, you're gonna anally probe me.
Hey teacher, give me my apple back, you son of a shit.
Hey, you- where's Mr. Hand, my teacher?
Yeah. Everyone knew- had that one friend who died every single day.
Yeah.
Everyone had that one friend-
That's- South Park is so relatable. Everyone had a fat friend, a Jewish friend, and a kid with no face who died every single day.
Yeah.
*burp*
His name? Jesus Christ.
Yep.
And he always came back. He was always there for me.
Yeah.
That would be of, uh, okay, I'll say this much. If Jesus Christ was still alive and every
day he died and came back the next day, I'd probably believe him.
Me too.
I'd probably be a Christian.
Yeah.
You know.
No, I'd be like, "Fuck you."
F you see can I say F you and then ask him for forgiveness? What would it take for you guys to believe in God me?
Yeah, I'm not too much even God. I definitely look so yeah, I was so scared of really that's that is interesting to me
I would have guessed that
Neither of you believed in God at all. No, I think it's like two years. We've never had this conversation
I am scared of God as a kid that like most of my
Fears and shit are like God stuff. I
I go through phases of intense paranoia and then I'm like, "Oh, yeah, God is attacking me today."
Right. Yeah. No, like you do something bad and then like a couple minutes later,
like something else bad. Like earlier, like today, I don't remember what I did,
but I just remember my jewel falling like in the toilet and I was like...
You're like, "God is not real."
God is really God is rewarding me
Yeah, Patrick fills up his fills up his jewel pot
And then smokes it like a dog. It just makes a big brown class
Makes a big brown snot bubble that he just breathes in and out and it gets bigger and smaller
No, but I'll still I'll still have like moments where I'm like, oh shit. That's God punishing. Yeah. No, I
Absolutely get that all did your mom did your mom and dad ever?
Say that to you like like something like shitty happens to you like you fucking know I didn't have very religious or something
Not really. I just I think um think I'm just a very paranoid person and uh yeah very uh I'm very psychotic
I'm kind of like the Joker. You know I'm kind of like a freak
I'm kind of like a free. I'm kind of like the Joker combined with the Joker from the Joker movie
I'm kind of like Bane
I'm kind of like the Joker from the animated series combined with the Joker from Adam West Batman combined with the Joker from Tim Burton Batman
combined with the Joker from Chris Nolan Batman combined from the Joker from
Joaquin Phoenix Batman combined by the from the
You're 100%
The Lego Joker from the Lego Batman
No, you're the Joker
combined by the Joker from the deck, combined by the Joker from Persona 5
No, you're the Joker from the Funko Company
combined with the Joker that was voiced by John DiMaggio
combined by the Joker from the
combined with the Joker from the Boston bombing, combined with the Joker from my mind, that's
me.
Combined with myself.
You're 10% monkey imaginary friend.
You're 10% walkie and 20%...
20% Joker.
15% concentrated power of Joker.
50% Joker.
5% cool.
100% reason I'm so crazy. You guys remember that song?
I love that song.
Remember I'm the Joker by Mike the Joker.
Mike Joker?
What about Fort Climber and it's Charlotte Climber's hip hop and rock project.
That'd be pretty good, right?
Or Fort...
How about Fort...
Fort...
Ah, fuck.
I don't believe in God.
I believe in, um, I don't know.
I think I've talked about this, but just like as soon as I knew the tooth fairy wasn't real,
I was just like, "Oh God, God and Santa."
Oh yeah, no, me too.
That's it, that's it.
Those are the bullet points.
Santa, the day I found out, did I ever tell you how I found out Santa wasn't real, or?
You went to the North Pole and you dug.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
No, I, ah, fuck.
I was like, so my mom had told me, my mom was trying to ease me into not believing in Santa.
So in the third grade she told us that Santa only brings three presents and then the rest
are my mom.
Yeah.
And so she was like, so that's probably why you're not going to get a lot of presents this
year.
And so I get like the fourth grade, I like kind of like, I don't remember what it was,
We got into a fight around Christmas stuff.
And then I was like, I don't know what it was.
I said something that got her so mad that she went,
and you know what?
Santa's not real.
(laughing)
Dude, my fucking, my older brother,
my older brother heard that from the other room
and all we heard was,
(laughing)
He ran out of the house crying without his shoes on.
So he ran outside, it's like the middle of winter, fucking freezing, no shoes because
my mom said Santa wasn't real.
That fucking rocks.
You know, Santa isn't real but Mrs. Claus is.
Oh for sure.
I remember I found out Santa wasn't real, like my friend told me in elementary school,
just like in the playground but then I remember like some other time like I had
this other friend who tried to tell me was like yeah Santa Claus isn't real but
you know what it's Jesus Christ that brings the presents down to me.
That rocks.
I my my brother's ex-girlfriend believed in Santa until she was 14.
What?
And when she found out her siblings attacked their dad.
(laughing)
It was like years of pressure on their parents.
Everybody at school says we're stupid
for believing in Santa Claus.
Everybody at school is saying we're babies
They were like, oh, they're just, they're psy-ops.
- They're trying to keep you down.
- Dude, that's an anti-Santa psy-op.
- And then one day they finally, her dad,
they were like in his office and she was like,
so just tell it straight up, I'm getting too old for this.
Is he real?
And their dad was like, "No."
And they just all started crying and beating him up.
(laughing)
- God damn, dude.
I'm at believing in Santa until you're 13,
that's kinda, that's kinda sucks.
- That's kinda awesome, dude.
- That's kinda sucks.
- That's kinda cool.
That's kinda fly.
- That's kinda fly.
- Damn, that's kinda some fly-ass shit.
- That's kinda some fly-ass shit.
Santa is one fly-ass white boy.
yeah yeah yeah i i miss that i miss that era of like the culture wars when it was just like
the culture wars over whether santa is real yeah just laura ingraham on box news like santa claus
is as real as jesus christ is and then it's fucking uh somebody it's rachel maddow yeah
just doing an expose on us and it's not real. So how could he fit into a chimney
at an apartment building? Yeah. We actually sent our fattest intern to a
chimney. John Oliver spending three million dollars to go to the North Pole
and check himself. And what we learned was the North Pole could not house a fat red man
plus a hundred elves not even ten elves could fit there there's no way you could
fit a factory there just spending so much HBO money to prove that Santa isn't real
no Santa no Santa you can't deliver presents to the porch and then and then
Santa's shoes down Oliver yeah there's a big lawsuit we've actually created a new
mascot who's called shit Claus the fuck yeah yeah before you change that is a
bitch calm before you change the same to clause it was actually crap mm-hmm
That's right.
Yeah, make Santa crap again.
*laughter*
God damn man, that's stupid.
That's stupid, motherfucker.
That's stupid as hell.
John Oliver, you dumb.
You dumb.
John Oliver, you dumb motherfucker.
If you ever, ever talk about Santa again,
I'm calling ICE on you, baby.
I'm calling ICE on you.
I'm giving them HBO's address.
I'm calling ice on John Oliver and I'm sending him his ass to the damn North Pole.
Yeah, and I'm sending him back to the North Pole because everybody knows he's an escaped elf like
Will Ferrell in the movie Elf. Yeah, exactly. He came to New York and he started doing all that
all that funky shit. Look, look, honestly we need to talk about it. I'm just gonna say it.
Uh, Buddy the Elf kind of appropriating the culture he doesn't belong to. You know what,
my mom because of Elf didn't think a narwhal was a real animal. It's pretty fun. Until like a year
ago it's a real it was a real animal it's a it is a really are you kidding it's a
real animal and my mom is not real that's not real it's not wall the narwhals
this is an interesting science fact for you Patrick the narwhal it's a type of
science fact it's a type of either whale or dolphin but the type of wall the horn
- A horn is a tooth that grows through
and like pokes through its lip
and just grows out really long.
They just have one really long spiral tooth.
- One of the most fucked up animals.
- Oh, okay, now that I've never looked into it.
(laughing)
- Never looked into it.
- No, I just thought--
- You're at my mom, I guess.
- You just thought it was a Christmas Reddit animal?
- Yeah, I, yeah, no, I think because of how annoyed--
- You got confused with unicorns?
You thought unicorns were real but narwhals weren't?
- Yeah, that's exactly it.
- Yeah, I remember there's one animal
with
him as a kid and so he uh yeah so he's lost you waste their existence he said
yeah these things are imaginary yeah they poked my naughty with their horn yeah my
parents actually my parents actually aren't real they're just something from
fairy tales parents aren't real I wish did homework is an illusion an illusion
of the mind it's an illusion down yeah homework is a tool of a pressure homework
Homework is a construct.
Homework is a construct of capitalism made to funnel children into the workforce.
Yeah, to funnel children into the exam industrial complex.
Yeah, I believe in the 8-8-8 principle.
It should be eight hours for sleeping, eight hours for home leisure, and eight hours for
recess.
Yes.
Right?
Exactly.
And then you need that resting time to recover from all that kickball.
Yep.
And all that all that four square they should let you know you should do you should be able to do
They should let you go to recess as an adult. They should let you do recess from home. I
Did I had I had a recess block when I was homeschooled and it was just video games
It was like the greatest recess ever. That's incredible. I was playing battlefield
fucking rocked I
Had I went to public school
Yeah, I went to Hampshire public schools, and that's why I can't do math and that yeah
- Yeah, and that's why you look like a guy
who like owes Joe Pesci money in a movie now.
(laughing)
I love that look, dude.
The mustache. - It's a good look, yeah.
It's a good mustache. - I mean, it works for you.
- I need a shave soon. - It really does.
It really does.
- Yeah. - Get it, I can't.
- Yeah, I pretty much need a shave too.
- No, you don't, dude.
- Yeah, pretty much my beard is--
- You should do like a mud vein thing.
- I don't have any hair under my,
like it all starts-- - On your body.
- You don't have, you don't like--
I have the worst beard ever.
You just have no...
It's only a neck beard. It starts under my chin.
It doesn't go onto my face at all.
You should just do a super sick lightning bolt chin strap.
Fuck yeah dude.
Just like super tight.
Oh yeah like ludicrous?
Yes dude.
You should get three shaves right here on the side of your head.
My older brother had a beard when he was like 13.
13. Damn. But he had like, he had a very like shitty beard when he was 13. Yeah. Those kids,
all the people I knew who had beards at 13 have children now. Well he just got engaged.
Like every single, well he's on his way. And he's a patron so congratulations to my brother.
Congrats Paul. Yeah, everybody wish Paul happy engagement. Yeah, everybody wish my brother
- Dear Paul, happy engagement.
He also just got a new dog.
Everybody wish--
- Wishing happy new dog.
- Uh-huh, that's his kid.
That's his kid right there.
- He gave birth to a dog out of his wee hole.
- Uh-huh, that's my brother--
- And that's that on that.
And that's period.
- That's my brother who cried when he found out
Santa wasn't real.
So everybody wish him happy.
- He needs it.
- Everybody wish him a Merry Christmas.
- He needs one win.
Yeah.
He needs one fucking win in this world.
First he has to marry a woman,
now he knows that Santa isn't real well he knew he knew that and that's let him
down the path to marry him yeah he's actually engaged to the tooth fairy so
nobody tell him anything love you bud love you bud for real though love you I
love you yeah and if my parents are listening this I love you guys yeah my
My parents are listening to this, "Fuck you, I don't like you, fuck you."
Yeah, making me do the dishes, but just get the silverware out because I'm not good enough
at it to do the rest of it.
Is that true?
Did your parents?
That was my job growing up because I was so bad at doing the dishes.
I would put a plate in the fridge and then they were like, "You just do the silverware
now."
Dude, that's a win.
That's how you just do the chores bad and then you have to do them again.
Yeah, that's right.
That's called being, yeah, that's how you strategize.
That's called tactics.
in school. Yeah, yeah, no true. That's what I did in school. That's why I got put into
a study that I got a credit for. Damn, that rocks. Yeah, that's also what I did in school.
I was, did not do well in school. And yet you still graduated the greatest mind of our
generation. Exactly. Yeah. I'm so smart dude. You were too smart that school bored you.
Exactly, that was it. I almost didn't graduate high school. I was very close to not graduating
high school yeah I almost if I didn't have that study that I got a credit for
I would not have had enough credits graduate yeah I was also close not
graduating cuz my mom was just really mad at me my mom got super mad at me and
she made me do like a super long paper to graduate high school or else she
wasn't gonna sign the form yeah my high school also wanted me they were like hey
since you did so badly will you do an extra year like just a pre-college year
just like chillin out here and I was like no way.
- You almost had a pre-colonial.
- I would rather kill myself, yeah.
- Dude, my school was fuckin cruel.
In my yearbook they had like a continuing education section
and they put the one kid who didn't graduate in it.
Like it was like most of the special needs kids
and then the one kid in my grade who was like,
yeah, we're keeping him back for a semester.
- Damn.
- Yeah, no, they tried to hold on to me.
I said, no, fuck you.
I will not let you do it to me.
You were you were fucking you were their favorite student, bro.
Yeah, they just needed you.
They didn't know what to do that.
We're not even a school without you, Cameron.
They tried to do that to me in eighth grade and fifth grade.
Nice.
Like any time that I was about to go on to a different school,
they were like, yeah, we don't think he like enough.
And then like my mom and I would have to go down there and fight him.
You have to fight again.
Yeah.
Yeah, oh, yeah, we have the streets of rage. Yeah, the fucking super Street Fighter style. I had to go I had to use my
Special kind of like I was like e-honda, but you were dressed like cami
Yeah, no, I was I was a very I was I was the thin boy
No, you were cami and you had a big fat ass huge. Yeah, and you were dressed like a soldier
Also, you were dressed like a sexy soldier. Oh my god a soldier with a giant ass. Yeah, dude. Yeah
Uh, i'm joined the military
Oh yeah, I'm in a friggin' military.
Does it find Street Fighter V and just like logging 50 hours of playtime in it, but it's just the fighter select screen and you're just looking at it at candy?
That's kind of what like Dead or Alive is.
Yeah, pretty much.
Yeah, it's just like, just the big tit people from Street Fighter.
Yeah.
Alright, this room is cooking my brain.
Yeah, I've been wiping myself like a fuckin' toilet, like your toilet ass.
I'm like, "Oh!"
Wait, uh, don't, I'm gonna end the recording, but don't hang up yet.
Okay.
Oh, yeah, true.
Yeah, I know.
I'm gonna stop recording now.
Alright, bye guys.
Thank you.