Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
Wait, we have two Calebs?
I'm Caleb, bitch.
That's not even the two Calebs I was talking about.
You're just doing a weird voice.
What's the two Calebs?
We had two Calebs a second ago.
There was one Caleb who said, "Can you hear me?"
And then I said, "Yes."
And then another Caleb said, "What about me?"
What?
But now he's just doing a face.
He doesn't want to talk. He wants to ruin the episode right off the bat, I think.
I think he's mad because he told us to come here early and he's late.
Yeah, and he was very late.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
I was actually the earliest today.
You were, yeah.
And I was probably...
I came here at 7 and I fell asleep on the floor.
Five minutes early.
Five to ten minutes early, maybe.
I was... maybe just five.
Joe caught me in my... Joe caught me sleeping in my chair.
Damn, Joe caught me slipping.
And Caleb just sprayed Axe and it's...
The whole room smells. The whole room smells like Axe body spray.
He bought Axe body spray on the tour and still...
Whoa!
Look at that pit stain.
Wow!
I wonder they call them Caleb pits.
It looks like you scribbled on your armpit with pencil.
That straight up looks like you wiped with your shirt one time.
it's tried to keep the shirt 'cause you like the shirt
it's literally dirt
that uh... that is actually dirty to do your tour group here
that is straight-up poopy
needs got a weird haircut now yeah
he's not know what he wants us to say he's really not giving us any hand
seeking maybe point is a chunk and he's trying to do like a funny bit he can be
like point to whatever thing is waiting for us to bring up or if he's not he
could like leave the room
that access fuckin potent yet it's crazy
it's crazy this literally smell it's mostly because there's no evidence that
that's that's going to smell like that for like two weeks is not a little
school locker room right now
them which is a little bit about that home
what why you attacking me when i thought you had been killed would love to smell
that that's what he did it
yeah yeah
springback memories is in flashbacks yeah that's why
he can't speak as he's having a flashback and i was wondering like a dog
he's whimpering or more like mister being i guess
more did you see mister beans holidays coming netflix in just two days
well i guess probably see mister b_-thirty on netflix was a student
mister b_-n_'s changes name mister b_ and now he's for a versus b_-thirty
smattering of the you know i cannot wait
for man versus b_
he's coming to be you can tell that he's fighting a beef with the little b_
little b_ it's too little to be a little b
they say a b_ is too little afraid i'm not so sure it believe it's been verses
Bee folks it's Bean vs. Bee. It's one of the craziest things.
It's one of the craziest things.
Bean vs. Bee.
When I first heard of it, I thought it was Man vs. Bean.
Folks he put all of his music on DatPiff for free. It's Little Bee.
He put all of the albums on Spotify recently.
He put them on recently.
Folks you can't listen to In Down Bad. You can't listen to it on Spotify.
Spotify. They took it off and had the Seed Boyardee beat. Where did it go? Where did
it go? You can't listen to it. Mr. Bean, he put all his music on DatPiff. He put all of
his music on DatPiff. Mr. Bean. Stop laughing. You know what? I'm going to go against the
entire- He has a feature from Meek Mill on one of the early mix tapes. Mr. Bean. Mr.
Bean and Meek Mill. Yeah, I mean his early stuff was fucking fire. I'm glad that it's
I'm glad that it's up on that. Piff now I think his shut up quiet. I'm gonna
meet you.
What is a piff? What's
stop laughing? Great. You ruin my fucking valve silence. Yeah, you ruined it.
Yep. By saying what's a piff
three minutes
Good point that piff great website. I don't know a lot of free mix tapes
Folks I saw I know I'm actually getting I don't know
I'm only joking you can get the piff out of here. You can get the piff out of
here. There's some kind of piff. What is a piff? What's a piff? It's a shoe.
It's a shoe? Yep. Datpiff. I'm going to ask Siri. Siri wouldn't know. What's a
piff? Siri might know. Siri would not know any hip hop shit. A piff. Okay, so
it just gave me the Google results for Siri. Yeah. That's what I'm saying. Oh
here we go. Oh urban dictionary
piff superior to the average, also a potent strain of weed, slash cannabis of
purple color or a shoe.
No, doesn't think you're thinking of a john. It says a word most London youth
used to describe someone's appearance used when the person is attractive,
pate, always peef or I thought where down that gal there is piff. She got her
own swagger and ting
is a the example you're talking about I thought PIF was the British word for FAGIT
you think that's poof yeah poof da poof da fucking poof da whoa you can't say
that no it's a British guy saying it no that was you saying that what's pride
month came out of your mouth what that's the opposite rule no pride month you can
say whatever the F you want FAG you want I don't I think it's the pride month I
I think it's you can say whatever the F. A. G. You want it's double wrong you
but I think it's horrible. Yeah, what you're doing actually maybe the triple
bad triple bed. Yeah,
here's a good example. It's like it's triple bed. I was chilling with John
yesterday, but we didn't have no piff on us. We were looking for piff and we
called you. You didn't pick up you dumb ass.
Me that's what it says. That's an example of what piff means on Urban
Dictionary and you dumb ass is linked
dumb asses on you dumb it says a link to use to insult other people trying to
get something you didn't wait let's all search our names on urban dictionary
okay okay how we done this I don't think we've done this dude Caleb I think I
think we're gonna gonna have a real treat okay here's the top real treat I
don't know can I skip the top one and just do the second one I said you have
to know wait for Kayla really for me for you nope you have to do the first one
it always has to be the first one. Okay, well the first one is Cameron, an albino
ghost
and then it says, dude, we lost Cameron in the Antarctic.
No, by no, but the second one, the second one is like, I don't care about
the second one. The second one is way more at all. Listen, it says he's been
hurt. He has a past, but he's probably the best guy I'll ever meet. Don't break
him because he's already been broken. He loves jokes and he treats his
girlfriend like a queen. He will give you everything he has and then some he
always knows more than he's letting on and can hide his
emotions very well. If he needs to talk, please listen to him.
He loves love and he loves giving love. He just wants to be
loved in return. If you ever get a camera in your life, don't
let them go. So I think that was probably the first person
probably they meant to they meant to put that under a
different name. Maybe they were like they're using they're
using text-to-speech and they probably said Kevin and it
picked up his camera and then the second one was the correct
Texas. We can I use the sixth one? No, you have to go first.
Let me use the sixth one. No, no someone with a massive
first long and not afraid to say it. Caleb has a horse cock. That's to go to
the first one yeah the six one. They're all good someone that you love to hang
out with and someone that you need a guy who you come to depend on and trust. He
accepts all people who for who they are and as a secret compassion for them as a
heart of gold and has a taste to show it
(laughter)
- Keep going, keep hitting.
- That's the funniest sense of humor.
It always speaks his mind even when it may be appropriate.
He treats his girl well and would do anything
to make her happy even if it means changing himself.
His girl can only think, is he for real?
Is he gonna hurt me?
Am I with the right guy?
He's almost too good to be true.
He's easy to love and makes a girl feel beautiful.
special, powerful, worthy, and a better person.
He's the kind of guy any person would be lucky
to have in their life.
- It's too long.
- If you meet this guy, Caleb, stick with him
'cause he'll make life even more sweeter.
I love him with all I have by Your Hot Girlfriend.
- Whoa.
- Let's check out this profile.
What other definitions--
- That's her only definition.
- Wow.
Here's one.
Here's Patrick.
A really cute, smart, nice guy that would do anything
make you happy is also competitive since he is an athlete. If you tell him you can't do something,
he'll prove that he can, but you can never lie to him. His gorgeous eyes will make your heart melt,
and every time you want to talk to him, it just melts you. When it comes to relationships,
he is the best guy to be with. He will make you giggle when you're feeling down. Giggle even if
you're happy, and just anything to see you happy. His hugs are so comforting to make you feel
protective. Patrick is the cutest by Dr. Snuggles. This is interesting. Calebs are usually tall.
There's two definitions from Dr. Snuggles, and it's Patrick, and then the second one is Jolly.
Whoa.
Wow.
This person is an amazing one whom you do not want to lose. They are great friends and good people.
Who named their kid Jolly?
Jolly West.
Jolly West, yeah.
Who's that?
It's MKUltra. He's like a professor who worked with MKUltra.
Oh.
Yeah. Here's a-- can you guys-- I want to see if you guys-- let's play a game, okay?
Okay.
I'm going to look up names. I want to see if you can guess.
guess the name gets a name i'm going to read you the definition okay such a good
game this is a good game right fucking smart okay are you ready this is a tough
one we'll start we'll start out tough and if it's too tough we'll do an easy
one okay okay first black president of the united states of america who was
elected on the fourth fifth november 2008 statistically muhammad
most common name in a way yeah yeah yeah probably is it's got to be right yeah
yeah
what's the answer it's obama.
Oh close enough, okay, I got one okay, go ahead a pink starfish that is
fun.
He is also one of the spongebob's neighbors on the squidward.
I think I'm going to go to Patrick.
Okay, yep, I have one now. I this one might be I don't know if I agree with
what's being said in this definition here, but I was one the nicest guy
you'll ever meet
don't
I know what this is. This has got to be this has got to be Hitler. It's
really oh my God.
I knew it. Here's one classic urban dictionary. Yeah, this wired ass kid
that has been a lot of crazy bullshit and knows too much for his age. This
will go up and pull a fucking fire alarm at a fucking factory and no one will know who
it is. I'm going to go with Patrick again. Dude, I'm so good at this. You do one. I'm
answering all of them. Okay, fine. I'll do another one. I'll pull up another one. Fine,
I'll do a different name. Whatever. I got one. I got one. I got one. Okay. A weapon
of mass destruction developed by evil Canadian scientists in an attempt to conquer the United
States and make Canada a super country. I think I know this. When the weapon grew, the
scientists put it to test on YouTube with it getting millions of views. The scientists
approached the Canadian capital to notice a high torture rate. The scientists told that
Canada would gain control of the US if sent to the states. Convinced, they sent it to
the US only to be backfired when he gained teenage girl fans. Furious by this, Canada
commenced search and destroy in order to destroy the weapon, but due to its popularity, its
bodyguards would risk to take a bullet for the WMD. Canada is still trying to
reach the weapon, but it's shown no effect so far.
Justin Bieber. That's right. Whoa okay, I got a good one. A fucking idiot who
spends his days getting the shit kicked out of him by a rabbit and a duck. Is it
Mr. Fudd. It is Elmer Fudd. Wait, I got one more. A practice of sexual gratification in
which a man squeezes Elmer's glue onto his hands, masturbates, and then peels the dried
glue from his member. Caleb. That was also Elmer Fudd. How could I have searched another
name so fast? I thought it was Caleb. Well, you know, you might have had someone lined
it.
Elmer Fudd.
Yeah.
What do I do next?
What should I search?
Everything that is racist, ignorant, and just plain wrong in the world condensed down into
one fat, hilarious nine-year-old.
That's the last thing I thought.
Dennis the Menace.
Nope.
Wait, nine-year-old?
It's got to be Trump, right?
They're just calling him nine years old?
Not Bart Simpson?
No.
Bart Simpson's never racist.
He's racist all the time.
He's like the most racist person I've ever met.
What I guess Alberto you must not be watching the newest episodes
a nine racist fat nine-year-old, okay
Here's a
Okay, here's a okay. Do I know who this person is? Yeah
Okay, here's another definition. Maybe this will help. Okay, it's super happy fun. Joy time. I was you
He's on the show and is the fat kid who always gets made fun of Oh Cartman. Yep. Yeah. Oh my god
Yeah, obviously. How did that? I know right? Holy. I wasn't thinking cartoons even though
we said Bart Simpson. Here I got one. Alright, you guys ready for this one? Yeah. Tough.
Alright. Okay. Difficult. Homer Simpson is my hero. He is the greatest man in the history
of human existence. Okay, so I'm guessing, I'm going to guess Bart again because it's
clear that this is like dialogue. It's not Bart. It's not, I can't tell you that you're
very close, but you know
fuck I'll read it again. Homer Simpson is my hero yeah. He is the greatest man in
the history of human existence. So who would Homer Simpson who would be who
would have Homer Simpson as their hero is the question. Let me read it again.
Homer Simpson, yes,
yeah, I know I got that, but okay now let me move to the next line. Homer Simpson
my hero Marge Simpson wrong no why is it home you but that but who else could it
Homer would be more of his kid yeah Maggie it's not Maggie no the fucking
annoying one Milhouse Milhouse it's not Milhouse no mr. Burns could be a secret
can have a secret mr. Burns months he needs a father I'll give you another
head there's a link under this definition to buy a mug that says Homer
Homer Simpson, oh, so coffee, no, it's not must be a coffee. It's not has
nothing to do with coffee. That's just you can put other stuff soup. Yes soup
orange juice or it's not it's not no. No, you guys are wrong. I'm going to go
with Mohammed again.
I think it's Mohammed. Yeah, it's seriously. It's seriously not Mohammed
guys. You guys are being really stupid. Let me try another name hold on
Osama
it's Osama what damn okay I have one I have one here okay to have a massive
erection boner no you're really not I don't really think you're gonna get
boner what it's boner no no no boner hard penis sheesh that girl gave me a
straight George Lopez last night
I George Lopez a euphemism for a fucking I don't know our dick here's one here's
another one when you're sitting far back on a toilet seat getting a blum can a
blowjob while taking a shit and you drop a log that is so heavy it splashes the
toilet water in the girl's face you have to then kiss the girl four time ever
since I had to do that George Lopez in my girl's bathroom I haven't been able
to watch Lopez tonight damn is it was jet did George Lopez do that I think
George Lopez, he popularized. He wasn't the first to do it, but
the beginning of the show where it goes like
four notes,
queer ass clown that likes to molest little kids in his play
lands. Caleb, Patrick, both are correct. No,
no, that's not true. What's the answer?
Ronald McDonald. It's Ronald McDonald. I didn't know. Apparently
Ronald McDonald's a molester.
- Yeah.
- I just learned this on Urban Dictionary.
Apparently, Ronald McDonald molests children
when they sit on his lap.
- Breaking news coming in from the Urban Dictionary.
Ronald McDonald is a molester.
- I feel like--
- Urban Dictionary broke the story in 2011.
- Molester's a little too sophisticated of a word,
I think, for a pedophile, yeah.
- I was Ronald McDonald for Halloween as a child.
- What?
I was Ronald my mom dressed me up like Ronald McDonald your mom dress you up
it was against your will I was - okay do you remember do you remember your mom
before you were old enough to pick out a Halloween costume they just put you in
whatever I'm I'm dressed me I was a crayon one year yeah rayon a crayon you
got fucked dude dude it fucking sucked I was a blue crayon that's that's one of
the worst one I mean like I mean I showed up it was like I was way too old
to be I should have been able to pick my own thing but I think it was my
brother's old costume and I just fit it and I showed up to the Halloween
function. I dressed up like Spider-Man. Dude, crayons fucked. At least if
it's gonna be like a embarrassing parent-picked costume it's got to be a
bumblebee. You know I was really mad when I was in first grade because
in first grade I was Yama Yugi. Oh sick. I was Yama Yugi for Halloween and my mom
had some she was like she didn't we had like some. Did you get your hair all like that?
I had like a mask like a plastic mask. What about the hair though? You didn't have any?
No, the mask had the hair. Oh, okay. So I was gonna go like in that costume and I
think my mom didn't want me to wear it to school because it looked fruity.
To have a mask over your head? No, no, no. Yugi's, he, which one is that? He's, I mean every
character in that show has a, has, wears only leather with a thousand belts.
Who's the Yami Yugi? Yami Yugi is the tall one. Yeah, I was Yami Yugi
And I had like the purple costume with like the yeah, he has a thousand leather belts. Yeah, buddy
Yeah, my mom was like no, I think the school is gonna declare your costume too violent
So you get to go to school dressed up like Scooby-Doo, but you can go
Around the school or around the neighborhood dressed up like Yami Yugi. I was like why even make me go as Scooby-Doo
I have a very cool costume you could have been a you could have been a trailblazer
You could have been the first Asian studio you middle school. Yeah, the first Asian student at South
He's a white then I've been I actually would have been the first
At that school, I mean you're you're complaining, but you're so for you got to have two Halloween costumes in one year that is
Fucker I had to have to have all kids dream about it was my cousin it was my
Yummy Scooby yummy Scooby I should have done that they used that would be Scooby Scooby snacks
Yummy Scooby. I was I was upset though. That was like like looking back
I was like I could have warned I could have had the big fucking
Yeah, the the thing could have walked around with my pot of greed
You had a pot of greed
As the pot of greed yeah, there's that one picture of Patrick where it looks exactly like the pot of greed. Oh, yeah
That's a really good picture. Yeah. Yeah, you do get that one of greed
Is that when we went to New York for the first time?
No, you're smiling really big and you're drooling.
And you look like the Pot of Green.
I remember it.
And you did the perspective change so the bottom of your face is huge.
Yep.
Do you guys want to hear a political joke I thought of on the way here?
I'm sick of all this fucking divisive bullshit, but yes.
Okay, are you sure?
I mean, it sounds like you don't want to hear it.
If you-
Look, we'll listen to it, but if it's too divisive, I'm not paying attention.
If it's fucking divisive left and right bullshit, then I'm-
It's not, it has nothing to do with left and right.
Is it epic leftist or based populist?
What?
Is it based as hell?
Or is it actually...
No, it's just about politics.
It's not...
I don't know what he's talking about.
Would you say that it's cringe or based?
It's definitely...
Well, it's based for me, but it's cringe for the people it's making fun of.
I would hope so.
Yeah.
But listen, if it's honestly...
If this bullshit is divisive...
Dude, it's not divisive.
It makes fun of the entire political system.
...then I'm doing a...
I'm having a...
Then we're doing a coup.
We're doing a coup.
okay that's fine all right can I tell you can I just tell the joke then yeah on
the way when I was walking to the office today I'm already out that's not very
tell me walk you know when I was walking in the office today I saw - I saw two
rats having sex yeah but enough of about all these politicians in our government
White House on both sides you fucking pissed me off instantly because it's
divisive it's not divisive it's about both sides but there's those are not
even the symbols of the political parties yeah you maybe if you said oh yeah I was
walking to the office I saw an elephant fucking a donkey
how would I see that it's just seeing two rats have sex where you see rats on
the side of the street what and in the White House see you're doing it on both
sides
BTS goes to the White House and this guy has to say all these rats are in the
the white house. You hate BTS don't you? You hate BTS. Admit it.
Admit it. Behind the scenes. You're jealous of their rapping abilities.
I just think that they shouldn't be having sex in the White House with each other.
They don't have sex with each other. They don't have sex, they have dances.
Yeah. I just don't think they should be like fucking each other in the gutter.
That's not what the... That's not what BTS does.
And it's not the gutter, it's butter. They say that in the song.
Smooth like butter, criminal undercover.
are you a for career you're there literally admit to being undercover
career and i have not gotten a white house fiction okay
do you think you know my job you think i'm a pretty damn seriously giving ice
cube really attic
a good day here
he plays a lot of good days yeah i bet he did use is a k that day
and that song
i actually used is a k i can understand that rap lyric stuff like i just fucking
and it all just sounds like blah blah blah blah blah.
I understand that.
I don't know what you're talking about.
It sounds like my life.
Oh.
Do you have another political joke to tell us?
No, that was my one joke and you guys were really rude about it.
Alright.
Alright, here's mine.
It literally wasn't fucking divisive.
Here's my political joke.
No, you don't get to do a fucking political joke.
Okay.
Oh, what is it?
I know this won't be divisive.
I abstain.
Whoa.
Yeah, that is a fucking joke.
The second this recorder turns off, he's going to be talking shit about every side of the
political spectrum.
He's just afraid of losing money.
You honestly fucking talk shit about all four quadrants of the political square, then I'm
gonna fucking destroy you.
He does it the second we press stop or pause or even that we do any other button on the
recorder he starts talking about this stuff.
He thinks I pressed pause.
You're going to get destroyed in a major way.
He's a total hypocrite.
And a hipster.
Oh, what's that, like a political party?
You're a total...
Don't say that political bullshit, man.
We're gonna get fucking fired.
I don't care if I get fired.
I'm in it for comedy.
What the fuck?
Yes, you do.
I'm in it for comedy.
No, I don't care at all.
I don't care at all. Okay, I'm not afraid to say I hate both sides of our
Both sides yeah both sides of the street that I have to cross to get home because it's so long in between them on to
Walk across the road on the crosswalk. He said that that was honestly there's too many Democrats or Republicans
I'm not big political. That's just about that's a joke about people
What people are politicians you dumb bitch?
Not to I don't think all people at all. They're more like rats having sex in the gutter
I'm gonna fucking um
My I really just hurt my hand by a bad by hitting the table too hard
You're trying to copy me
What?
Look at that. Did you do that? No you did that because you fucking fell over
Yeah, idiot. Yeah, you're trying to copy having a hurt hand
No, I'm not
Whoa, you can't do you can't this yeah, you can't do why not make your wrist limp
You can't do a limp wrist and make your wrist limp like mine to copy me. Why you think?
Oh, you think this is me doing an impression of you?
You get in a way. Yeah, cuz I have a hurt hand. Okay. Yeah sure if you want to get out
My hand is this can't I can't even keep this look half. It's already your default
wrist placement which is
So they're saying it's pride month
Who is this is though? They're saying it's pride month people walking around. What is this prude month show some skin?
Yep
Show some skin. Yep
The White House we should go to that around the government. Mm-hmm. I think the government's more like a circle than two sides
No, it's circus. I
Think it's more like a circle than two sides. I think the Democrats are Republicans are like a circle
What's he doing? What's that? What's that Street Festival in San Francisco? We're the Folsom prison
Yeah, no
Alcatraz, that's where they belong. That's right. No for walking around nude. Here's the thing
They're already dressed up like prisoners are covered in fucking chains and leather which is how prisoners which is
It is how prisoners handcuffs on look they're they're having sex in the street, which is what prisoners do
Yeah, yeah, and one of them is the pea guy
guy the P guy the P I did see a video of a woman with a guy who's coming in to
honor chest at that Street Fair I was like why didn't we have one of these
when I was growing up yeah I'd love to see that it's a it's truly disgusting
it is why are you having sex in the road to block off a square yeah sorry you
can't drive here there's freaks coming on each other's face and they're all and
have dog heads on. And guess what they're doing they're they're making lollipops
that are shaped like penises and vaginas. Yep. They what? Lollipops. Okay at least
tell me that they're touching the penis lollipops to the vagina lollipops.
Not any other combination. You don't even want to know what the third lollipop is. Get this, it's a penis lollipop and it goes into butthole
cotton candy fuck and a butthole donut too.
This is fucking ridiculous.
It's filled with red jelly.
And a butthole spaghetti.
Because that hurts when you do that.
He almost fell over.
Does it?
I saw him almost fall over.
Because that hurts when you do that.
How do you know?
My friend told me.
You know my friend's name is?
What?
milk. You're right.
Harvey Milk told you that having fucked in the butt hurts. Is that true?
Did he just tell you that unprompted? Did he just text you or he called you?
Those were his last words.
To me.
His last words were itter.
Explained to me. It actually hurts kind of bad. Did you ask him or you just said
it? And if I had to liken it to a food, it would be a
- A donut with red jelly.
- Shake like a butt.
- Because it hurts.
It would be a butthole donut with red jelly.
- Come on man, it's fucking Pride Month.
- Obviously this is all a joke.
- Yep.
- 'Cause it's a comedy podcast.
- That's right, we don't care either way what you think.
- Honestly, straight gay, it's all okay with me.
- Black, white, purple.
- Yep.
- Purple.
- Yeah, gay, straight, purple, old, young, purple.
- Eskimo.
- The thing is, guys, man, woman, purple.
- Are you supposed to say Inuit
or are you supposed to say Eskimo?
- I think you're supposed to say Inuit.
- Or Eskimo's a different thing?
- I think they did, they--
- I'm sorry if there's any--
- Did they slurify Eskimo or are you not supposed to say that?
- I think you're not supposed to say it.
Can you still say Inuit like Inuit brother? Oh yeah, like an Inuit kiss.
Yeah,
like I fucked. I fucked the same person you did. I fucked. Like I fucked.
You're my Inuit brother. I think. That feels too like real, like that's my
Inuit brother, you know? I'm sorry if there's any Inuit listeners. It's better
to use like, just to be safe, to use a race that doesn't exist and say like,
That's my Navi brother.
Yeah.
That's my Bith brother.
Inuit kind of works better though.
Inuit, I feel like for Inuit brother works better because I was all up in yit.
That's my Bith brother.
Me and my brother were both all up in yit.
That's my Bith brother because you know we both made jizz.
Because we both fucked.
And we wailed.
We fucked the same jizz.
We wailed when we were making jizz.
We fucked the same Bith.
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo.
We fucked the same Bith and we wailed.
to go to a you know you know you know we wait a bit we made my my i shot first
into her cantina
yet
but i call m_c_ chris right now i suffers and then i stopped and i left the room
and i did a letter shoot
i hope that i did a letter should
and her name was
mostly actually
in
yeah
her name was a really are most of our name was on so i mean
new by
i'd had sex with her most wisely
I thought like wisely most why it was wise a wise choice.
And yeah, and she said and to wing yeah.
Yeah, and I'm Greedo.
Yeah, and Dan to mean and she said and to is in there after we
are done and she said it smelled so bad.
You need to light a saber
or a candle or a saber.
Yeah, and I was all there.
I was all there on yeah, and then I turned over I saw her
tattooing
and I started that's he's like he's coming in the middle of so hot he's
coming in the middle of saying tattoo is going like tattooing and I dropped a
ton ton of come into her yeah my time of come the time and let me tell you
unfortunately she was Death Star.
Afterwards, she died and listen. I thought she smelled bad on the outside.
Mm-hmm yeah yeah I've been at called a minute I yeah I thought she smelled bad
on the outset she must she must have farted
she must have farted nice as I would and then we were done that maybe like and I
smelled Alderaan things and we were done she asked if she could sleep over and I
I said take you walk, take you walk myth.
Where was this? Where is this on the May the fourth episode? This was and also
that also the date it was May R2D2. Yeah,
R2D2. And her dad caught me and said get off my lando,
get off my lando. And then BB8 my cup. Yeah.
that's your cup size BB-8 yeah yeah yeah it's shaped exactly like BB-8.
One really small one and one big one. Yeah yeah that top is a nipple.
BB-8. Oh he does look like a boob. Yep. Holy crap. Oh my god. I'm gonna do a horny rewatch.
Yeah. I'm doing a horny rewatch. I'm gonna watch it again. I don't know.
Force Awakens!
I want to see the Tornian from the Mandalorian!
The one who got cancelled!
I want to see her naked!
Gina Carano!
She only has half a hair!
What happened to her hair?
She only got half a hair!
Her hair's gone!
Oh, she's got half a hair?
I don't know.
I was watching that Obi-Wan.
I watched the first episode of that.
Oh yeah?
Wait, that made a...
That way, where did it go?
Yeah.
That's out now.
Oh yeah?
I'm gonna go watch that.
out now. Oh, there's two episodes are out now. Cool. So the first number to use a
use a promo code list when you're signing on Disney plus Disney plus you get a
20% off if you only it's only $3.99 a month for you use the code list 10 you'll
get 10% off you use list 20 you'll get 20% off yeah and I think you can guess
the rest of the codes from there yeah yeah list 21 22 yeah does it does it go
above 23 he's lying if you use any code list 24 to list 30 you are banned
permanently from Disney Plus how do you be one show there it so there's this
one character the the actress who plays her has been getting a lot of heat
because of the Sun because because of the two sons on tattooing yeah or a
a flame thrower, a fireplace, hand warmers, a hair dryer, a hot light bulb, a microwave,
oven, toaster, lava, panini press, a really hot rock, sand, a really hot rock, a really
boiled water yep and no not saying cold what is she getting heat for for for her
race and it's sad and it's messed up she heat for her race yeah what does that
mean she's getting a lot of what is this world come to when a woman can't just be
a twi'lek in peace that's right but there's like a scene where she like for
some reason she knows that princess Leia is Luke Skywalker's sister or like
Anakin Skywalker's daughter and it's like how do you know that that makes no sense
and it's like there's genuine criticism to be had about the character but then
like they have like a lot of this isn't to be had well then let's have it let's
yep have at it it makes no sense that she knows go on it makes no sense that
that character knows why is why does she know that lay or you know who I want to
again it makes no sense I want to see the people on the internet are going crazy
they say you can't have lay or got it no you can't ever know they can't have the
third sister no but back why did they call her the sister they should have
brought this you're not do it whole show about general grievous general grievous
he needs to make a comeback I've any safety little Benny safety he's on the
show I heard I heard general grievances is door is joining Rob zombies touring
band really that'd be dope as hell yeah they were him in five nights if he wears
a top hat and he plays two guitars that's the same time what was the
double-neck guitar that we on the tour I saw there's that band that we
technically open for we didn't technically oh you keep saying that over
over and over it doesn't make any sense. It's so funny to say that we opened for Led Zeppelin.
It's funny to lie. First of all it's a lie, second of all you've been saying it
open for and then you added technically open for which makes it more of a lie.
Yeah. We technically did not. We did not at all. It doesn't matter. There was an hour in
between and then it was their show. It's an early show and late show. Yeah. Would you say
if you go see Doctor Strange and then the showtime is right before the another
movie that's out would you say that Doctor Strange opened for that other
movie yes I don't think so it's just two different show anyway I saw the
double-neck guitar in person for the first time and I was like damn wait they
had one they do they we should have stayed we were allowed to stay we should
have stayed and watched yep we should have been it was awesome
so so so so so so so so so so so podcasts yeah that's what the sign said
welcome home yeah welcome home so so like maybe get rid of welcome home yeah
make enough room for it to say the two different acts yeah well I think so they
thought our name was podcast it is I guess it kind of is it was they thought
that our name was podcast and then in San Francisco they thought our name was
about list we basically said about list podcast yeah yeah about basically have
the best podcast name ever because no should we change it I was I a thousand
times we should have changed it like two years ago to Patrick's podcast. It's way
too late now. I think that's bad. It should have been Patrick's podcast. It's
only one guess one of the three guys. That's so so funny. That's even funnier.
That's probably that's maybe one of the only podcast names worse than podcast
about list. Patrick's podcast. How about this Tutti Frutti the show? Tutti Frutti the show?
the show that could actually be good. They could to the fruity but maybe we
change it. Maybe we just throw everyone a curve, but we change the podcast
about lists. Oh yeah, what about
first podcast on the left?
That's right first podcast on the list. We are the first podcast on the left. I
mean honestly what we if we getting I we could ruin our at we could try and
the SEO and have it be like we could just call it like top ten funny podcasts.
Oh that'd be good. Because then I think that's maybe one of the only because
that phrase podcast about list you can kind of carve out a space there there's
not many web pages called podcast about you search it and you know you get a lot
of but eventually you know what's like the worst SEO name not even leaving
podcasts like what's just like a two-word phrase we could family watchdog.com/calebpitts
pits Google I don't know I don't know if that's a real web page I think that
probably doesn't exist if we called it like with a swag poop our a worse a
worse thing to look up the the the the no the three cookbook PDF that's good
spelled right yeah the Beatles podcast yeah I think it's spelled right be a TL
yes mm-hmm cuz I'm just such a big music fan the Beatles the bait
Beatles the Beatles the Beatles the Beatles
I'm Ringo, I'm Ringo, hello it's me Ringo Starr and I love shaving my pussy I heard
General Grievous is not joining the Beatles General Grievous is not joining
as a drummer with four arms. He'd be such a singlet drummer. He should join every band.
He should join Shine Down. Oh my god, every four armed. So it's General Grievous, Goro,
Machamp from Pokemon. They should form a band. Who's another one? Who's another four armed?
the Hindu God. Okay, yeah. But is any of them all the one that has arms? I
can't remember Peter Griffin. This is not oh the human centipede has maybe I
think you're gonna have a hard time with that one that not they can work the
pedal board. Yeah on the down the road. Yeah, the front they could press all
the pedals for the first time you saw human centipede. I never watched that
movie. I saw I remember it's in pieces. I have a really vivid memory. I was in
middle school and they had in my like middle school library. They had like
the like centipede. So they had like they like newspapers and they had like
one that was about like movies and stuff. They had like a movie review
thing that I would like turn to. I remember reading about the human
centipede of being like the guy who made this movie should be sent to jail.
What is wrong with the world? Well, they also named Tom six yeah. They also he
also did a second one. That's a there are three of them a guy watching the
human centipede and being like I'm going to do that in real life. Yeah, it's a
sick. That's the perfect, every good sequel is like that. Yeah, that's a very
fun. And the guy in the sequel is so fat. Yeah. He's so fat. Why do you feel the
need to bring that up? And he jacks off with sandpaper. That's okay. Why do you
feel like you need to call this guy fat? Because in the first one it was a skinny
guy. So he's- It's just the difference between the- He's changing all the
sliders. Yeah. The sliders. Yeah. Do they have horns? No. You can't get horns with a slider.
No you can't. No that's clearly, that's one where you select the horn. That's a grid.
Yeah, the first movie the sliders are all to the left. What about the length of the
horns? Duh. They don't have that. The first movie the sliders are on the left side. Dude
can you control length of hair with slider? No you have to pick it from a grid. There's
no sliders. You can show your hair. What? All you want. What'd you say? Do you think
you can change the length of hair with sliders? No you have to pick it from a grid. You say
- Did you say with slizzers?
Yeah, with scissors you can change the length of hair.
- What are you talking about?
- Yeah, what are you talking about?
- You sound crazy.
- No, I'm making you feel so crazy right now.
- You're not making me feel crazy at all.
- You think you're in a dream.
- You're making me think that you're very stupid.
- You just got emotionally--
- And you might have a short circuit in your brain.
- You got emotionally dominated.
I have a long circuit in my brain, okay?
It goes all the way around.
- You have one long circuit, that's it.
- Yep, and it goes on and off.
- It's a circle.
It's like when you, it's like one of those--
- Yeah, that's what I said.
you have a long circle in my brain one of those the male to male plug that they are
you're also you like stuff and you plug it in.
You have you have just a plug that's plugged into both of the outlet.
Actually I think a male to male plug is actually fine I just decided.
But I like a female to female plug a little bit more.
I told you he's having a short circuit in his brain.
You know the male to male like you when they make Christmas lights and it's like
this one does not exist.
Yeah that's what I'm talking about when people do you know do you know that have
have you seen that no it's like it's like an extension cord where both sides are
the plug yeah like the the mail plug and you they I guess people go into like
harbor stores and ask for it because I thought they want to extend their
Christmas lights, but that's like a that's like a suicide plug because you
could just that just like if you plug that you can plug that into into the
same power strip like both ends in the same pressure from will just explode
yeah, just cause a fire and so sick. I might do that yeah, but like there are
just a bunch of pictures of like a bunch of hardware stores that have signs that
are like we do not make these these do not exist don't ask for these if you try
to use this you will die and it's just a picture of like a made out word yeah
yeah an extension cord and that's what you have in your brain mm-hmm I don't
think so I think I think I have no much at all yeah I think I'm normal oh then
yeah then he's right Pina kind of chicken breast in my brain I like I'm
telling him that his brain doesn't work you like I don't think so you don't
think at all, pal. Brain doesn't work.
I do think at all. Give me a test for thinking.
One plus one thousand.
One thousand and one. Ways to die.
Fuck.
Give me another one. Give me a brain riddle.
Two plus two thousand.
How much calcium...
How much protein is in one uptime?
Zero. Holy crap.
Zero grams.
Give me nutritional...
How much total fat is in uptime energy?
Zero grams.
look out this is not the zero sugar one this is this is the zero sugar gotta be
zero grams that he's he's over - really neither of them right no yeah - no he's
- no he was how much so do you know how much sodium I'm gonna guess a hundred
you're gonna mess up my process I'm gonna guess 3,500 milligrams what is it so
your final answer I can't remember that's a lot or a little bit go down I'm
I'm going to guess fifteen hundred milligrams
zero, so I told you to go to zero grams of sodium. I told you to go down. You
thought you're okay. Give me another one. Okay, how much calcium calcium?
Were you about to say you think zero is less than
hmm? Were you what say you think zero is less than than whatever you said? No,
I wasn't going to say word literally about to say that I wasn't. I saw it in
How much natural caffeine?
Natural caffeine or total caffeine?
Natural caffeine is in one bottle.
160 milligrams.
Ooh.
No. What is it?
142.
[laughter]
We're just getting back in the swing of things.
Yeah.
Yep, I'm starting to feel normal again.
Yep. Yeah.
abilities that I had when we were back here. Yeah, I lost were on the road this
you had that on the road. You had that on the road. I was we had that on the
road more. You had that better on the road. You got worse at that when you
came back. That was so good. What I just here's an it wasn't that good. I just
made a good if I hadn't seen what you were doing on the road for people who
don't know who couldn't see me for the people who can see me for the yeah. I
made my turn my arms into a wave. Yeah, here's an ability I had on the road that
don't have here sales because I did the merch table I don't know yeah you were
out there hawking shirts mm-hmm yeah I don't have sales you're acting like a
snake oil salesman he would be like we ran out of large shirts to be like you
can just buy a small it'll fit you that's right he's trying to fuck he's
trying to flip over the fans you're creating it you know that's a funnier
world of big fat guys wearing small shirts you know I like it I didn't try
with the smalls I know all style shirts I would say it's benevolent all style
shirts run large and then he said I saw him do he did you know the thing that
the Turkish guy does with the ice cream cone mm-hmm he's doing that with the
shirts I was doing that with the shirt really you were doing the Turkish tricks
I was doing the Turkish tricks with the shirt it was it didn't make any sense
because it was a big ice cream cone that the shirt was why were you handing
people that on an ice cream cone we saw the t-shirt cone yeah people believed
And people believe me, these stupid fans.
Oh my god.
I have a t-shirt account, okay!
I have an extra large "show me the body" shirt that's printed on the same exact shirts, and
I don't wear it anymore because it's so long.
That's dope though.
You could cover your knees and you could look like a sweet...
Yeah, we gotta get those shirts on the website soon!
Oh!
I don't want to!
I want to go on to shipo.com and print out all the labels.
Big shirts are way better than little shirts.
It's always better to wear a shirt that goes down to your knees.
I like big long shirts that make me look like I have a dress on and I wear tiny little, tiny little shirts.
That's the way to go.
I like when a shirt and pants fit just right.
You like a perfect fit.
Yep.
You're weird, baby.
See, that's weird.
That's weird.
That honestly is not true.
Whoa, look at that spider behind you.
Ah!
What?
Oh my God.
Look at that!
That thing's huge.
That is a brown recluse.
And we're all gonna die.
It's just that thing's so fucking big.
It went, it literally, it went down behind you and then you left and it went back up.
It was gonna, it literally trying to kill you.
Oh my god.
Cameron just saved Caleb.
Honestly, I'm about to have a fucking heart attack.
That thing is crazy.
Caleb was just saved.
That is incredible.
Cameron, thank you.
I slept next to a spider this morning.
Oh look, there's another one right in that corner.
Yeah, I slept next to one this morning.
Great, my desk is basically a fucking spider Hawaii where they go to vacation.
Awesome.
See that spider right there?
Dude, we live in a fucking arachnid paradise.
There's a spider right up there.
Well, it's at the cutout.
What are these things?
They're some kind of eight-legged freaks.
These are some kind of...
I don't like this.
They're spiders with long legs.
There's some kind of arachnophobia.
My favorite part about that movie title is calling a bug a freak.
Yeah.
It's like, "Ah, it's a...
I don't know what it is.
It's a freak."
What movie?
A brainless idiot like you would consider a spider a bug.
Arachnophobia?
Eight Legged Freaks, awesome movie.
Arachnophobia, that movie, bad.
Yeah, what's that?
You can't have--
Brown Bunny, last 10 minutes, good.
It's very funny to me to make a movie that's like,
like to make a horror movie about spiders
and all the spiders are normal size.
There's no giant spiders.
They have to be giant.
Eight Legged Freaks, they're huge.
Like I watched Arachnophobia and I was like,
okay, I'm ready to see some big ass spiders.
The biggest spider in that was probably tarantula size.
There's a Jimmy Buffett song in that movie where he sings about spiders.
Really?
Yeah.
It's on the soundtrack at least.
I don't remember that much about that movie because I was so angry.
I was giving myself a stroke being angry about a small spider.
But I do know the Jimmy Buffett spider song.
Try doing in my car.
It literally has...
Eight-legged bug.
I don't think it's that.
He got into my pina colada.
No.
Eight-legged bug.
He needs to get out of my pina colada.
It's pretty good, Jimmy Buffet song writing.
Yeah.
Eight legged bug.
He needs to get out of my pina colada.
It's an eight legged bug.
I hope it doesn't attack me like a thug.
Just that Jimmy Buffet song called eight legged bug is so funny.
turning on the touch tunes,
eight legged bug. I don't remember this one. Eight legged bug, eight legged bug,
he needs to go away. I really do not like him. And gradually he stops talking
about pina coladas at all and he just sings eight legged bug, so scary,
eight legs. Oh, you know what the song is called? What? Don't bug me. Oh,
pretty close actually yeah this is I can help you that might be my favorite
fucking song that song's fire a leg
Wow.
Wow
Don't bug me don't bug me
[Music]
in my world
out in the wild unknown
night crawling, dream falling
just don't get in my way
don't squish me
can't wish me
that's all I have to say
ooh ooh
I can't get out of my head
I'm in a world
out in the wild unknown
night crawling, dream falling
just don't get in my way
*laughing*
*music*
I think I'm gonna bug me
Just try and act humane
I can cover tracks and never leave a trail
Wait, you can't even play your guitar?
Yeah, I can't.
I'm a doctor.
It's a stupid world!
I'm a player, so I'll play it.
Don't bug me, don't bug me
I'm better left alone
Let me twirl in my world
Out in the wild unknown
Don't bug me, don't bug me
That's all I have to say
(upbeat music)
♪ Eight legged bug ♪
(laughing)
- That was amazing.
- That was don't bug me, but.
(laughing)
- I was so nice to have a musical interlude.
- Yeah, I think we should do that every episode.
- I kind of agree, we need to have like a little music break.
we start playing us. Yo, I actually think I just realized what the next big thing
is for podcasting. This just came to me. I think you guys are going to like this.
I think this might have become a recurring segment. Yeah.
Mystery Science Theater 3000 for music. That is a good idea.
That's a good idea. That's a good idea, right? Yep. And we can maybe do that
every single episode.
- Can we do that?
Can you pull up Soldier Boy, Superman, Dat Ho?
- We don't have a lot of time.
- Crank dat.
- We got three minutes left.
- Oh man.
- We have to fill this next three minutes.
- Your math.
- Your math is bad.
- It's 55 minutes, you said we have three minutes left?
- We have to plug something at the end,
something very important.
- What do we have to plug?
- No we don't.
- We got nothing to plug.
- What about the singing contest?
- We're not gonna plug that yet, that's not going live.
Dude, you're gonna spoil it.
I'm gonna have to edit this out now.
- Great, so now I'm gonna--
put on soldier boy
put on soldier boy now
he's not gonna do it
don't worry about it
stop screaming
get your phone back out
we heard the song we should spend the next couple minutes writing the sequel song
which is eight legged bug
we already wrote eight legged bug
eight legged bug
you gotta get out of my
pina colada
you sang this ten minutes ago
so much time on eight legged bug. I need to go up soldier boy.
Mazda Miata. This is why we need a Jamie. Eight legged bug. We need to replace Patrick with
a Jamie. We need a Jamie so bad. Yeah, who will actually do what is good for the show.
Sitting at the casino with a thousand dollars. I got one hundred dollars in one of my slots.
♪ Look around the casino and what do I see ♪
♪ I see a giant spider sipping a drink ♪
♪ With fangs it's guts ♪
- Yep.
♪ Look at that big bug ♪
♪ I hope he doesn't bite me ♪
♪ He's playing spider solitaire ♪
- That's not a swat.
(laughing)
- You guys are the worst songwriters.
- He's sitting at the poker table playing solitaire.
♪ Eight-legged bug ♪
♪ He's sittin' at the bar playin' Spider Solitaire ♪
- It's so clear that you have been awake
since five in the morning.
- Pull up, soldier boy.
- Okay.
- Don't pull up, soldier boy.
Now we actually have two minutes.
- That's definitely long enough
to do Mystery Science Theater 3000.
- I don't like this.
It feels like we're counting down.
- I know, Patrick really, really--
- Patrick really was--
- You're ruining the vibe here.
- He made me very time-conscious.
why because I played don't bug me yeah. You know I took I took out the last
thirty seconds. It don't bug me. It seemed like you were just made it
honestly made it worse. Yeah, yeah, you were just completely done with the
episode fifty minutes in and you're like I'm just going to ride it out with the
bug song. It's not true. I think that's exactly what you were mouthing to us
over and over. He's starting to get tired.
This sleep is starting to catch up with it. It's not it keeps this. Let's do the
let's do the ad like chrome no place like chrome get the saying wrong much and
earn up to a fifty thousand earn what is this a funeral home a great start get in
an amazing career an amazing career was that being a doctor oh oh oh cuz it's I
looked up soldier boy it played army ad oh true all right mystery science
theater okay three science music booth concert mystery science concert hall okay
So that's a weird beginning to a song.
So, me?
How's it gonna be a dance if he's singing?
It's not a new dance, it's from 2008.
Left or right?
Left or right? Okay, which way is which?
Yeah, left or right, what are...
Up in what?
Finish your sentence, Munch.
You wanna crank what?
Superman?
Superman that hoe? Are we in the garden? Did I miss something?
What the hell's going on?
What the hell's going on with this song?
It's happening what the fuck is this song about?
Super I yeah you I prefer I prefer Batman hold on this is the verse let's say
Soldier boy up in this whore the hell get out of that whore soldier boy you were 16 when you made this song that's illegal
What are you?
Lean to the music box maybe that's what on my base. I'm Craig your music box. That's why the beat sounds so weird
Yep, sounds just like a music box
You have bathing apes what the hell what the hell how do you those are illegal to own yep?
yep, and I'm and
They better be clean by the end of that bad. That's right
Also, they don't bathe they pick the flies out of each other. Yep. That's a logical fallacy. Yeah
It's something like that yeah, it was engaging in a logical fallacy
They they really engage with logical spider could never be that big. Yep. They grow only this big in my house
It's true, man. No, I would say they're in a bit of a glass house
For robots talking in space over a movie with a human yep, okay
We should do here's a better idea. We had this idea like a year ago. We did yeah, I don't think yeah on the podcast
Yeah, don't yeah, don't say it still still want to do it
Yeah, no we did I remember this yeah, okay, so we should do and I wasn't thinking of the first idea
We should do a singing contest. Dude, stop. You need to stop fucking bringing this up.
We're gonna announce it when it's time. All right, I'm ending the episode. We're going to announce it.