Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
(dramatic music)
- Few times been around that track
'cause Peter Griffin's coming back like that.
I'm from Quahog girl.
- Because I'm the family guy.
- 'Cause I'm from the family guy.
- Yeah, I'm Peter Griffin.
- Peter.
- Soy es Peter Griffin.
Yeah, that's not what he sounds like.
That's like my Peter Griffin voice.
Yeah, I'm Peter Griffin.
No.
That's what he sounds like.
Yeah, Peter Griffin is my name.
I'm from Queelog.
I'm from Quo-hog.
Queelog.
Quo-hog.
Yeah.
Pretty good start to this episode.
Pretty much it sucks.
Until you said that.
Pretty much my life is shit and stuff.
Pretty much my life is literally a shitting fuck today.
Yeah.
My life is a fucking ass shit.
Great.
Go ahead and flush it, because it's poop.
great i got a stinky shitty
she will alive yeah you know i'm not shit on the poop crap population my life
me and myself that's right and my ass nobody fucking cares about me because i'm
fucking stupid is a dog i had my eyes nobody cares about my ass 'cause of all
that it's filled with poop and basically life is fucking up just a bunch of
fucking crap these days and i don't know if you care if i say and i don't give a
care
no you're straight up don't know how to give a flying shit fuck crap
piss
bitch or
god damn everything in my life. Basically I'll say god damn as much as I fucking want to. And these bastards on the news.
Yeah. These fucking. And these bastards in Kiev.
These fucking god damn bastards on the news. Yeah. This fucking Putin bastard is being gay with all this shit.
And I could give a cunting fuck about this kind of political bull crap.
And he's basically one of the biggest fucking monsters in all of cuntville.
He's basically a complete fucking stinky cunt diarrhea. He's one of the fucking monsters of
Ass village basically one president and it's fucking Vladimir poopy
Vladimir poopy has shit coming from his mouth
He actually words he has a diaper that he wears on his face like Bane's mask is all the doo-doo that comes out of his
Fucking and so basically there's a gay flamer
So there's basically this gay flamer diarrhea wizard Vladimir Putin from Russia and he's basically making my life crap
Yeah, and it's like here. It's like it's like oh do I go to work today?
Or do I just get flushed down the toilet?
And if you want to be a gay flamer you do that in the bathroom where it belongs Vladimir Putin
Just go in the bathroom and do your gay flaming in there so that I don't catch some residual gay stuff. Yep
And he's straight a thing and he's a guy was flaming all over my name was a guy did a
Flame by outside and a stray flame flew in my window turned me gay. I'm tired of all these flamer gangs
Who are doing just a bunch of gay flames all over my neighborhood and I have to call the fire
Flames out. Yeah, basically the Spitfire logo is being gay in my neighborhood
flaming all over the place. My flamer life is so crap. Flame boy. Yeah, I'm gay and I'm
a flamer too. Flame boy and the Spitfire logo are being gay on their skateboards in my neighborhood
and doing gay shit with flames. Whatever happened to just fucking shit? Yep. My life might as
well be coming out of Calvin's wiener the way it's pee. Yep. And guess what's under
the p stream yep my life it's my life too guess what the wiener is it's gonna be
me is there like a sticker of like Calvin pooping you're a complete cock on a fuck
that's just the facts of this okay diarrhea on a stick yeah how about you
tell your bastard oh you already talked about my friggin bastard executioner of
a life yeah not your my shit not your friggin life your fucking ass my shit is
Basically fucked from all the shitting that I've been doing getting fucked from all directions on the toilet
I basically fucked an ass and got AIDS. Mm-hmm. My ass is getting fucked so much by shit
Just shit my life is being crap. Sorry. I fucking shit got fucked by my ass great
My fucking ass is fucked and I just got a shit sandwich for fucking ass stinks and it's ruining my life
My damn fucking ass is so full of my bastard stupid clown fucking shit poop
Bitch ass this life is a hellish doo-doo. Yeah from an ass fuck
Yeah, and God is basically the big fuck in the sky. Don't even get me started on that fucking twat that
G o D what's the stand for I got an idea ass motherfucker, dude
With a brain yeah, this is
Motherfucker with a bitch this rod you were a flamer up there in the fucking damn sky this this mother shitter is no more than
the tooth fairy to my fucking life itself.
Because I don't believe in him or Santa.
Yeah or...
Who is gay by the way with the rabbit.
Yeah.
From Easter.
Oh my god.
That's right.
And Jesus, don't even get me started on this fucking twat sandwich fuck face.
He's a complete piece of shit.
And all the apostles were ass clowns.
You should have called them the ass apostles.
Because they were fucking them in their fucking ass.
Jesus was basically a fuck sandwich with a shit toothpick in the middle.
The shit toothpick.
And the olive the olive on top of the toothpick was my wiener yep
Yeah, cuz it's that my fucking gay ass stupid bitch ass clown wiener my baby ruining my fucking weiner
Saddle a lot of doodoo Sam my wiener looks like it got stung by a bee. I wish I got hit by a shit
Yeah, I'm basically the shit shark walking around the fart ocean looking for turds to eat
eat. Oh, I smell diarrhea in the water and I'm on the hunt. That's
basically my life. These days, I'm basically a crap scavenger at the
side of the road of my damn life and don't even get me started on
politics. Basically, both sides are basically two fucking ass clown
pieces of shit. It's basically poop versus poop to poop. One side
is poop. The other side's pee and guess where they're putting the
poop in the pee right on the American people's fucking face. The
American toilet yeah basically we're all one big toilet for Nancy Pelosi and and
Mitch the United the United McDonald's to fucking shit on the United fucking
craps of shit America that's right that's fucking right and you know it's spelled
with three K's America the three the three K's caca crap and conolingus and
and three T's at the end of shit.
T T.
- Toot toot.
- Toot tooting.
In total bullshit, basically.
- Don't even get me started on bullshit.
- I hate that crap.
- I fucking hate bullshit.
We should start a Facebook page like I fucking love science
called I fucking hate bullshit.
- That'd be really good.
- Yep, more bullshit today, great.
- Great.
- Yep, more bullshit.
- Another heaping load of bullshit for me to snarf down.
- More bullshit from the toilet store.
- We should just get-- - Tonight at nine.
- I'm a shit straw slurper.
- We should find videos, like those uplifting videos
of a kid with no legs who learns to swim
and just repost those and be like,
great, more shit.
Awesome.
- More shit from God's bullshit ass world.
- I fucking hate God so much.
- Yeah.
- He's--
- Wait, I fucking love science and I fucking hate God.
- I hate God.
He's real, but his miracles disgust me.
science for God no thanks science that God is dead
yeah yeah that's right yeah he's basically in a fucking poop box in the
shit or a Darwin that God is being eaten by worms in his shit box casket buried
six feet under a toilet and we're all fucking and we're all just fucking poop
monkeys walk around a giant piece of poop swizzing through the monkey where is he
oh oh he's right here oh you go skook jungle school we went we went to Ikea
Yes, they went to Ikea.
Well get his hand out of the bag, he can't eat that.
He can't eat that dude, you fucking asshole.
I knew you would instantly...
Stop, stop, stop.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Is he okay? Check on him.
I don't... he doesn't look okay.
I knew you would do some fucking bullshit.
I hate him. I hate him so much.
Put him the fuck down.
Put him down right now.
You ass bastard.
You fucking titter. Put him away.
He's staying here.
You're two boobs though.
Put him down.
You guys went to IKEA without me.
And we got your replacement.
He's not, he will not replace me.
Whoa. What?
The monkey will not replace me.
What?
Jungleskog.
He's not going to replace me on the show.
He's not a monkey, he's Jungleskog.
Yeah, he's a Jungleskog.
I'm sick of his ass.
His ass is perfectly brown and hairy.
This is probably the one ass I can handle in my damn fucking life.
He's basically one little shiny pearl.
Jungleskog.
I looked up how to pronounce it.
Younglskug?
More like, yeah, youngl in the toilet.
Youngl in the toilet.
Give him to me.
That's a strange name for me.
Yeah, youngl will.
We're putting you in the toilet.
Don't touch my leg.
Give Younglskug.
I'm gonna touch your leg then.
I'm gonna tickle you.
I wanna make sure he's okay, because you abused him.
You did Ray Rice to him.
One minute ago and I didn't like it.
What was that?
I saw someone with a t-shirt one time that said "Ray Rice told her twice."
Damn.
That's a crazy public t-shirt.
That's a crazy...
Yeah.
Would you guys ever wear a t-shirt with the F word on it?
Yeah, I have before.
I don't like that.
I don't like that at all.
There's a skate company called Fucking Awesome.
Yeah.
It's funny that that's just completely...
It's like the coolest company, I think.
Like their graphics are really sick.
- I would say Google, but go ahead.
Alphabet.
- It's a really, like their graphics are really sick,
but then you look at the label
and it really just says fucking awesome.
- Yeah.
- Fucking coolest house.
- In Hulkamania font, yeah.
Fucking the most awesome shit of all time.
And their sister company is just called Hockey.
- That's cooler.
- Yeah.
- That is cool.
- I think we should rename the LLC to Junko Skug.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, we should go through all the paperwork and all the taxes that will pay pay thousands of dollars just to go
By jungle school everything move jungle skug LLC. Yeah, that's cool. That is they have frogs there
What in Sweden in Ikea? No, not in Sweden. It's basically just a whole fucking pile. They're in the dog shit
Yeah, they're pretty much in the meatballs. Yeah, you go skew. We ate his whole family
We had you uncle skug. They had a bunch of dinosaurs. They had a heart with arms. No frogs, though
I didn't see any frogs. I've eaten the meatballs every meal since we went.
I had lunch today and breakfast. I had to sit here and wait all day for the Wi-Fi guy to come.
I was shoving meatballs. And he came today and just started listening to jazz in the middle.
It was pretty awesome. He was done installing everything and he told me he was doing it to
test but he didn't tell us until he turned on jazz. Also he kept putting, he turned it back on,
one turn the music back on after he had already set the Wi-Fi up yeah so he
just likes that he just wanted to listen to that song yeah yeah that's cool it
was cool I had a cable guys are awesome yeah they're fucking cool they made a
whole movie about the when they made a whole guy about yeah there there was a
guy when I had a cable and saw it on my apartment when I didn't had installed
the guy like he like showed up through all there's a bunch of wires on my roof
to for like the other people's cable shit and he just threw them all off the
building so I've just been dangling off the side of the building for like a like
two years now yeah and he like set up the Wi-Fi and he's like now I got to test it
and then he started laying down on my bed and facetiming somebody and just
being like yeah the best doing an install right now it's going for I just
had to test it he's talking like a kid it was awesome dude yeah yeah that guy he
called somebody that's my last one my last Wi-Fi guide climbed the side of her
our building. Whoa! Yeah. Did he scale it? I don't know. Did he have a grappling hook? I was too afraid to look.
That's very scary. Yeah, it was scary. I'm terrified of anyone with powers. Yeah. Yeah. Can you give him
over here? I made Junglescoop sit crisscross applesauce. That's not crisscross applesauce.
What style is that then? That's hands on foot style. That's mantis position. Yeah. Yeah. Wait,
he can do... Whoa, look at him now. He can do it sideways. Put it behind him. Put it behind him?
him just watch this let me can you just stop hogging you're monopolizing you
really are having like you guys got all day yesterday with him not all day we
know we had to pick him up from daycare at IKEA we did we bought him and then we
brought him to the downstairs daycare yeah he could have fun with the other
kids and then we we had to bring him here we had to set up all the furniture
shit he's not you have him set he is no control over his neck you need to give
him he's paraplegic he won't stop looking at me he's looking at you because he
he hates you because you're trying to diddle him, not trying to do I can not
literally trying to diddle him. I cannot wait for the night that Patrick is here
by himself and you will stop doing you can't do mysteriously goes missing
because he's getting too much attention exactly yeah. He's gonna. I don't know
what happened to you. I don't know you go scoog wait. Who's that? Oh, just like
this. There's like like brown fur tuft is all over his desk. I don't know you're
think about I never in saw I think camera has something to say to you. No, he
doesn't he's looking at you. He says everything he needs to say when we have
our time together, which is not right now. I'm hearing he's talking a lot of
shit about you right now in my brain. He you're waving for him. We've already
I've already said my literally grabbing his arm and and squeezing it to his
crying like it is crying women's bodies. Is that why you're doing this?
Oh my, Junglescoot, no!
- He's doing a--
- He's doing a zieg heil.
- I've never even seen that in my life.
- Yeah, I don't know what that is.
- I don't know what that would be called.
- I don't know how to do it either.
- You know what that is,
and you're really good at doing it?
Stop.
- Why are you doing that, Pat Gioia?
- Why is your penis--
- I asked to stop doing that.
- Fine, then get your hand off his arm,
if he's the one doing that.
- I can't believe--
- Oh, look at that, he's not doing it anymore.
- What the fuck are you doing with him?
- Get off his penis!
- Put him on the table now.
put a lot of a word not your ban from you will skew you have to say i want to
get away from him at all time in the end
given it with its two verses one
well all my god look at my old it's ok
it's ok alone
that i don't care if you have a stuffed animal crazy frog that's like that's
pretty lame you don't have a you know i just up to him with a backpack
okay as you want some monster
oh yeah you might hear you might be
It's okay, baby.
- Stop feeding him Monster.
- Why?
- 'Cause that's not the flavor.
That's not a good flavor.
- What do you mean?
It's Ultra Rosa.
- It's his favorite.
- It's not a good flavor.
- Shh, shh, shh.
- You want him?
- Yeah.
- Go to mommy.
- Stop.
- Look, he's hugging.
He's so sweet.
Oh my, it's okay.
- Do you want to say something on the podcast,
you know what's good?
Oh, he's shy.
He doesn't want to say anything.
- He is really shy.
I want to say something I listen to this being it was you just that was crazy
frog you you we just heard you do it. No, why would you but you put the
microphone up to his mouth? He said it
see, but why would it be quieter yeah coming out of his mouth
Lingling, do you think that's a wingling? No, he's saying being being
you're trying to do the ventriloquism. Yeah ventriloquist are like did you
there's actually no difference in the in the sound between B and L. It's
impossible to tell you that's what they always say. Is L the B in ventriloquism?
I don't think it's L. I did yeah. I'm almost certain it's not. I think it might be M.
With M you still have to close your lips. I think it's D. I think it's definitely D.
Wait check this out. I learned a few ventriloquist tricks. Okay.
You stink at ventriloquism.
you
still
spinning all over
just holding your breath for
still moving your lips to
crazy frog from the it's yeah I do I do not like they did not give him his
signature no but they did give him a whole ass and they got a that's the
crazy that's a crazy frag yeah I gotta get a soldering iron and a fix
there's there I broke the speaker a long time ago I think if I just re solder it
in the in the spot where it's broken I need to re soda myself I need another
soda I wish I got a monster before this I went to the smoke shop they buzz me in
that place yeah they buzz you in and then you have they have they sell weed
there there's about 16 guys just hanging out yeah they sell weed and each of
them individually was like you can go ahead bro yeah it's like I know you're
not in line I know you're hanging out dude that's what I would if I had any
kind of store all everybody's invited yeah hang out all day that would be so I
wish we knew someone with a store we could just hang out in so cool we could
just befriend that guy and hang out in his store that has a lot of incense burning
there's already too many people hanging out there we need we need to start a
fresh hangout at the grocery store I'm down we need to find a guy who owns a
Kroger and just go hang is anyone who listens this on a Kroger who owns a
Kroger who can show us a Kroger card that's proof that you own it yeah
jungles goog it doesn't know how to hold a mic it seems no I'm trying to teach
him he's so I'm just excited because we get to see him grow he's gonna thrive
here do you think how much bigger do you think he's gonna get probably like ten
times I'm really worried about young goes good safety here why what do you mean
he's a he's our he's our father's a security system glaring problem that's
well that's the that's our bomb shelter so you don't think Phil's gonna go to
the town on young go skug we talked about this last night. This is you go skug is
going to be phil's boyfriend. Yeah, phil will be impregnating young go skug got
it because his current boyfriend is at the laundromat. His blanket yeah that he
fucks every single morning. I thought it was going to be his pig. Stop bouncing
young go skug. The pig is too small. I'm keeping him again. If you if I don't
bounce him, he's going to start crying. Yeah, and you do not want to hear him
cry.
he's weird about you don't fall and my mom used to do that that one to me yeah
yeah that's a it's a good one that's a Massachusetts it's a good way it's a
good words my mom used to put me in a drawer my mom used to put me in a dress
that's not my mom put all of us in a drawer at some point because she's like
Because it was like I guess they didn't have a bassinet and they were like what a bassinet
You don't know what a bassinet is. What's another word for it a crib?
Oh, no, but like that's like a really small cribs that you get like a little baby
Okay, so you know that so you put a you would you think you thought you were all we have enough the word best
We have to know a lot about bassinets because we have been taking care of you and go scare
We've been looking we're gonna use it. Is that one of those fucking Swedish words. They have all over IKEA. No
you know.
One of those Swedish words they have all
yeah mean every word on every single thing like a scrub. There was a scob.
Yes, there was a scob yeah, there was a really good scob was funny. What's a
scob? It was like a box okay in all of the shit like it's box backwards. Yeah,
they all they all are like main things that are that are like vaguely a
description of the thing. Yeah, Jungelskog, I looked it up, it means
jungle forest. Yeah, has nothing to do with a monkey. What? Then there was, I
don't remember, there was a trash can that was called like throw in or
filler. Filler, yeah. I was like, dude, there's no way that's the fucking,
there's no way that every like Swedish word follows. Yeah, there'll be like,
it'll have like a... The same like naming mechanism as walkie talkie.
It's like, they have like a light that's called like a blinkie. Yeah. It's all
stuff like that yeah exactly yeah that's like the
wow and what else
no you're kidding yeah for what i'm kidding oh okay.
God he's got a hat on
growing up. He's a teenager now. He's a teen. He's a backwards hat on. Pretty soon he's gonna be smoking.
He still loves me, though. He's not one of those rebellious teens. Wait till, wait till. And he
promised me he'll never smoke. Really? Yep. What? You smell that? Your fart? Yes. Got him. Dude,
you've been, we've all been having. I've been having some crazy stomach issues. Oh, dude,
me too. I've been, I've eaten meatballs for every meal for, for like over 24 hours. I think I'm,
I think I know exactly why I'm farting bad.
I don't know why I'm farting bad.
You know what I had a dream about last night?
You just look like a guy who puts out really bad farts.
I do?
Yeah.
If I saw you on the street and someone was like, "You have to like..."
You have to smell this guy's fart.
No.
I'd be like, "You have to."
If it was like you and like a guy who looked like John Wayne Gacy and like a fucking, like
a really old guy and they were like like pick one guy to smell his farts I would
pick either of them over you yeah okay I feel like you you you look like you have
stinky stinky I used to my farts usually you look like an old Greek guy my farts
are usually just loud but then they don't smell for that long but I've been
having just real quiet bubble gut farts for a while that's bad yeah ones like
like yeah nasty as soon as you smell it like dude you do you fart in the shower
and then like the steam connects with the fart. Have you ever
guys figured this out? Have you ever farted in the bathtub and it
makes it smell different? We talked about this literally two weeks ago. Really?
We've, oh god. We did? We've already talked about this. I don't think I've talked
about this with you guys. Yeah. Have we? Uh-huh. Dude, the bathtub's familiar.
I've talked about farting in the bathtub and smelling the
bubble as it pops. We try to catch it in your mouth. Yeah. Yeah. Mm-hmm. Like
fish food like reverse fish food reverse fish food yeah cuz it goes up I wish I
got fed like fish do me too don't you wish a big hand the big sponge bob hand
would drop the food into your mouth yeah I watch a burgers and after I would grab
them like it's a it's an iPod touch game yeah that'd be fun you're playing you're
playing have to run back and forth and catch a rush or something yeah the fuck
it's called I wish that I get a big spongebob hand will come down and give
me the suds for the side treatment you don't want the suds no I want the sets
like SpongeBob AIDS s UDS they it's actually sponge it's sponge um you know
deficiency syndrome yeah no no no yeah under water under water deficiency
syndrome mm-hmm yeah no but the fucking actually no cuz when Patrick gets the
treatment in the show you're not in the show doesn't bode well for him what what
happens down I don't learn it ensues I have to watch this episode of Amazon
Prime uh-huh yeah yeah the and well I thought you were gonna I heard it
streams better on paramount we're gonna say catastrophe follows I'm glad you
said hilarity in this yeah you should definitely should definitely check it
out on Paramount Plus instead. You know what? These streaming services are the only thing
getting me through this hellish fucking nightmare. Oh yeah. Yeah. Oh man, I'm so glad that we
have fucking Hulu and beautiful Netflix. They're basically a ray of sunshine and poop hell
population me, one, me, myself, one. I basically live in the doo-doo version of America. I
live in the doo-doo-verse. I basically live in the shit universe fucking fart planet.
planet yeah I live in the doo-doo verse and there ain't no spider-man here no
yep not even a single spider-man to save me from this shitty stuff mm-hmm I hate
this shitty stuff mm-hmm all this shitty stuff dude it's not even a single spider
man nope no do you I what happened to that guy in Seattle
real-life superhero. I hate spiderman swinging webs through my shitty shitty shitty shitty
shitty bang bang of a life. Yeah that's right. Remember the guy in Seattle? Shitty Seattle.
Shitty Seattle is a sucking superhero. Shitty Seattle has no swinging spiderman slinging
webs. Okay keep going white boy. Swinging webs through this with his slingers. His sweet
it may hate shall I something's I hate shitty cities with no spider man's
swingings me too. That's why New York's the best. There's that guy in Seattle or
Portland who was pretending to be a superhero. He was pretending to be one.
There's yeah I don't remember. They made a documentary about those people. I
think so yeah. I never watched it, but I remember that was one of those things
where I would see they would post on like I would see a post on like reddit in
in like high school or like middle school or whatever they'll be like they
actually made a documentary about real life superheroes. I'd be like oh, oh,
oh, I've been the only reaction I've ever had to the existence of ever seen
capturing the the fucking something's capturing the freedman yeah. Have you
ever seen that no no I knew the title for some reason is just watch it the
other day. So Andrew Jarecki movie the guy did the jinx and it's like this
apparently this guy like was trying to make a documentary about like like like
birthday clowns in New York and one of the guys that he got in the first
interview, just like we talked about being a clown for like five minutes and
then just started talking for like two hours about how his dad is like the
most horrible pedophile in New York City, and then so he just made this whole
documentary about this guy's dad instead. It's so funny dude that the guy
I'm a clown. I'm a clown and my dad is like an evil pedophile who is in jail and
then died. I wonder what the demographics are for clowns on that.
As far as pedophile dads. Oh dude it's gotta be huge.
Yeah right that's gotta be like yeah it's like one circle.
Everybody's like yeah you're a combination of your mom and your dad and
a pedophile mixed with a girl is a clown. Mm-hmm. Right? It's a pedophile that
wears lipstick yeah exactly yeah exactly not every not every pedophile is a clown
but every clown is a pedophile every clown was every clown is half pedophile
yeah sometimes it's dominant actually yeah and like blade - yeah yeah the
alleles there's one one clown who can walk through the name blue can walk
through the birthday party without even getting turned on yeah that's that's the
That's clown blade.
The party walker.
Yeah, the party walker.
But he still fights like the reaper vampires with like three mouths or whatever.
They need to do a Dexter for pedophiles.
That's what they should have done. You saw they brought Dexter back or they did a revival season or whatever.
That's what it should have been.
Yeah, yeah, I'm a pedophile.
Dexter shows up and is just like, "Yup, I'm back."
"Yup, I'm back, but something's changed."
Yeah, little Dexter.
That show is so funny.
Dexter's the stupidest show I've ever been in.
The fact that they make that show and they give him like, it's a,
they give him like, like, sitcom narration.
Yeah.
Where they give him the exact, he has the exact voice when he's narrating of,
of, "Yup, that's me. You're probably wondering how I got into that situation."
"And that's my life."
"That's my crazy ass serial killer life."
if I eat a brain, oh, he's a cannibal. I don't know. I've never he's a serial
killer who I saw like two episodes of it. He's a serial killer who kills serial
killers. Oh, that's a serious mind fuck on this. Yeah, it shit. Yeah, yeah, one of
the yeah, that's fucking me up. I like that show because it's scientific. It is
they do. Yeah, they do forensics. I can't watch any show like that that has blood
I hate blood. Yeah. Blood grosses me out. I watched, well, Neil will throw it on like
every other like week, but the Dendi Tartakovsky. Oh yeah. That's a tough, that's a difficult
name. I'm gonna, I'll give him, he gets a pass on this one. Alright, you phoned a friend
and that's it. Did I say it right? That's your only assist. I don't know how to say
it. Dendi Tartakovsky. I think it's Dendi Tartakovsky. Tartakovsky. I don't know the
the first day of the I don't know how to start a boss yeah something like that a
bunch of his show crimbing that shows good there.
I watch yeah yeah it's sick there's like that one where the one where he
the the ape kingdom. Oh yeah dinosaur they that episode say the ape kingdom
traps his dinosaur and he does not like it one big goes rageful yeah sounds like
a very much a drinks a bunch of black juice and rips up ape in half. Yes,
it's a really cool show. You should check it out.
What the fuck? You read like a phone book?
Yeah.
Yeah, he's just, there's a scene where all these monkeys are attacking him and he's just like hitting them like each like pounding his fists.
It's just a show about a caveman guy killing dinosaurs and wizards basically.
Yeah.
How do you read the phone book?
No audio in it or no vocals.
Yeah, no dialogue.
No dialogue, that's the word.
Did you guys ever know anybody growing up who wanted to be a forensics person?
because I was singing about it. I feel like, you know, that's a job like you did. I don't
think I've ever met anybody who was like, I want to be like a forensics.
I knew somebody in...
But like, I don't know, I've like, I can't imagine what that person would be like as
like a middle schooler who wants to grow up to be like a forensics person.
I knew one guy, I knew a guy like that in college and he had explicit like...
Explicit porno on his phone.
He had schizophrenia and it was like...
Oh yeah.
It was like he... I remember...
He wanted to solve the death of his parents.
Well, I remember we went to... I had two classes with him. One...
Oh, is this someone you both knew?
No, this was at UNCW. I had one class with him the first semester of college,
and then a class with him like a year later than the next year.
We're not listening to you anymore. We're looking at...
I promise you're gonna like this.
Jungle Spirit.
And then that first semester, I had the class with him and he was like, "Yeah,
I want to be a forensics specialist." And then he was like, "Yeah, like..."
And it's crazy, like my dad has like schizophrenia,
and I've been like smoking a lot of weed,
which they say like makes it worse.
And I was like, oh, okay.
And then the next time I had a class with him a year later,
he had completely lost his mind.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
He would just like sit there
and just draw a circle on his notebook,
like over and over and over again.
And he would call me different names and shit.
It was awesome.
He had like a full psychotic break
and was just going to like a biology class.
- I feel like if I had smoked weed for another year,
that could have been me.
- That would have been cool.
if you just completely lost your mind.
It's cool that weed does make you crazy.
- Weed is so bad for you and it's gross.
- It's nasty.
- It is gross, it's green.
- It's green like shit. - It's literally green.
- It's green like it's good weed.
- Think about one thing.
- Good weed is the same color as a Pepto-Bismol shit.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Like that's how fucking bad weed is.
- Yeah, just a green, black, purple mix.
- But same color as a broccoli too,
and broccoli's pretty good.
but broccoli is not the black and brown and purple. Hey, if you cook it right,
she you haven't been cooking it right. Also, you don't use you don't wash your
broccoli before you got it. You gotta watch your broccoli. You gotta you gotta
throw some grape jelly on there too on your rock. That will get that gets the
nice purple color. What's the fucking the
never mind the chef david thing.
like he says like imagine Selena Gomez's bald butt with grape jelly on it
hashtag dinnertime that would not fill you up that's not a good meal just grape
jelly enough to put on a woman's butt that's not that much grape jelly no no
Selena Gomez she doesn't have a huge ass I feel like you couldn't fit that much
grape jelly on it like if you dipped her ass in grape jelly she does have a
cooking show now on HBO maybe that's one of her signature recipes
- Grape jelly on my ass.
(laughing)
- Today I have a special guest,
Chef David Boy, star angel child.
Hey baby, I wanna thank your butt
and stuff your butt with grape jelly.
- He needs to be on like Chopped or something.
- He needs to be Chopped for sure.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, they need to chop him into little bits.
- Chef David Boy.
- They need to turn him into jelly
and I can put my butt into him.
- Yeah.
- Wow baby, I wanna stiff my butt on your stuff.
I wanna stiff my butt on your stuff.
- Wow, baby, I wanna sniff your ass.
- I need, dude, I need to get some stuff soon.
- Yeah.
- It's been a minute since I got some stuff.
- We've been getting some stuff for the office.
- No, I need some stuff from a hoe.
- I know what you're saying now.
- Yeah.
- Some strange ass stuff from a hoe's bottom.
- I just need some stuff.
- I need the stuff from a hoe's bottom.
- Dude, I got some stuff last night.
- A hoe's bottom.
- I got some girl's butt stuff the other night.
It was fucking awesome.
- I saw a hoe's bottom.
I saw a hosey tush. I paid to see a hose tushy and it was basically awesome and she tooted.
Oh my god. I paid a hoe to toot from her bottom. Oh my god. Yeah. I saw sluts behind. I saw
a sluts rear and it was seriously next level. I paid $60 and I got to look at a horse fanny.
the fanny is a girls the her stuff what fanny is stuff if in the UK fanny is
stuff in the US fanny is a doo-doo thing yeah yeah fanny is a bottom here but in
the UK a fanny is stuff yeah a fanny is a girl's stuff and her thingy is well a
fanny wipe means two different things to a to a Brits and a statesman yeah I saw
hose took us I paid a whole $30 to see it took us that's a lot of money yeah just
to see it but $30 $30 seen this video where Cameron is funny put pays that
girl to put mayonnaise in her ass no she this woman this American sniper puts an
entire jar of Hellman's mayo in her ass cheeks and then just walks around the
store with it in there. Damn. It's fucking awesome too. Oh, oh, oh. You seen that?
Okay, okay. How did- I, I, the way that you said that, you said mayo in her ass, I
didn't mean, I didn't know you meant in the cheeks. I don't understand, how could you know that there was a video of, of, of mayo, of a girl walking around with a jar of mayo on her ass?
And you're like, oh but that's not that one probably. Oh, but it could be the one where she's- No, no, no, no, no, I didn't know, okay. I didn't know, I like, in my head, I meant that- You know that video though?
I know what you're saying, but do you know the video? I don't know. Oh, we got to watch it
It's really good
But I thought you meant she like used a funnel and put a bunch of man
He did a mayo douche sheet
Yeah, but like a mayo enema and all the shit all the mayo Sam blue jed out
I think you're a bit of a mayo douche
God Wow
Why would you say that in front of jungle sku he can't hear you he's covering he's not
sometimes
is kind of covering his ears. That's very sweet. Yeah, that's sweet of you to do that
before you for you like disrespect to me so greatly. I don't want to in front of my child's
feeling. You and me are his parents. Yeah, Patrick's basically his brother. Patrick is
like his is like evil babysitter. You're a Simpsons. You're basically Rod. What's that?
You know that you know that baby evil babysitter from the
I'm Roderick so I'm really cool.
You're the guy that tries to kill Bart?
Yeah, I know.
Roderick wasn't cool.
Yeah, that's you.
What are you talking about?
Roderick was cool.
He was a stick man.
He was a fucking ass hat.
Are you talking about the movies?
No.
Roderick was a total poop bastard.
Roderick was cool.
He was in a band.
Didn't he make, aren't they making like a 25th Diary of a Wimpy Kid book now?
Yeah.
That's so cool.
It is crazy.
It's so easy to make those.
I remember being like, when they were coming out and being like, "Okay, four, that's a
little much.
Slow it down."
in an Uber the other night because I just really loudly went through all of the
like I saw they were making a new and I went through like the list of all of the
books and just kept being like oh my god dog's day off I mean that's a classic
and just like rating all of them and doing a complete ranking to the uber
driver yeah and I was just like asking him if he'd ever read it the books dude
it was funny and then I gave him a huge tip like two bucks $30 uber I was
way more than that. I ubered home to North Carolina. Oh yeah. Yeah it was a $700 uber.
You know you can pay like $300 to go from like New York to Boston. That's not that
good of a deal. Yeah it's not a good deal I'm just saying you can do it. I mean maybe
you're on the holidays though. But also like that kind of that sucks because
then the guy just has to drive back or hope that there's some other lunatic
who's gonna uber from Boston or maybe you guys just hang out.
He just waits for you to hang out. He just tags along with whatever you're doing.
Yeah. I mean I feel like if I made enough money I would do I would pay for
that ride just for the novelty of spending five hours with an uber driver.
You really could dig deep. Yeah. You could start to learn a lot.
It's like a my dinner with Andre where you record the whole uber driver thing
you guys just talk about life. I would love yeah that would be like that'd be
- That would be so fun.
- My Uber with Flandre.
- There's nobody named Flandre.
- It's not Flandre.
- No.
- You have not been in the Ubers I've been getting in.
- My Uber with fuck.
- My Uber with--
- Every once in a while you get a guy named fuck.
- I did get a guy named fuck.
- Yeah.
- I've had a couple of fucks.
- I got a guy named surrender.
- That's one of the best of all time.
- That is a good one.
- Surrender.
- I got a guy named surrender and I did surrender to him.
- My Uber with surrender.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah, that'd be a great conversation.
- Yeah.
Why'd your parents name you that?
Oh no, I changed my name to this.
You're just going, "Surrender."
Surrender. Surrender. Surrender.
Surrender to me.
If I started working as a cab driver, I would--
So what do you-- How long have you been with--
Shut up!
Surrender!
I would change my name to something funny.
Yeah, for sure.
I'd probably change my name to Dire Leah.
Dire Leah?
Yeah.
It can't be two on the nose.
like here's what I was what I would do. I would one letter I would change my
name to like to be like be like D E R A and they'd be like oh like Dera and I'd
be like it's actually pronounced diarrhea
or just do that with your own name. Caleb that's poop. Yeah, his name is
poop. Someone got mad at me once someone was like at a party and they were
asking Pierce if
they were like I'm sorry, what was your name again? I was like oh, his name is
poop.
His name is
and I just wouldn't stop mm-hmm they got they got kind of the I saw the world
arise his name was I think that is kind of his name it's close it's very close
it's closer than it is - well it's your name for years of poop poop pierce of
poop mm-hmm I need to become a you guys names are both closer to poop than my
name what are you talking about how your start to the P your last name start to
the P okay but we're talking about first names here my first name has none of the
letters is it's short though by the way also if you take it I mean if you flip
the bees upside down it's boob what poop is if you flip the Pete into show me
show me on the whiteboard we don't have a whiteboard anymore we have the you
mean we get that yeah all right well it's not even our whiteboard they're
gonna get so mad at us that the whiteboard but the the no no no the
attack board. You better not ruin what I did. How? I know it will work. I just decided it
will work. Okay, so here we have our attack board that says mmm poop. And then what's
under it? And then there's a star eyes emoji and a dinner plate. Like you're so happy or
starstruck to be eating shit. Yeah. Now watch this. Wait, wait, let me get, let me.
You get a video of this? I'll get a video of it. Well you can just flip it upside
down. Dude. So it says dude. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. But if you mirrored and then flipped it. Right, so if you changed out the
letters it would actually spell something different. Shut up man, why you got to
fuck everything up for me. It says boob pretty much. It says dude. It says boob almost though.
But hold on. What if you did like. If it said dude and then you flipped it. What the hell
it says boop. But I only did one. Yeah you only did one so it says boop. Alright watch
This is really hurting me.
Okay.
I can't see it because your hands are in the way.
Can you move your hands?
It says boob. I see it now.
So, do you guys feel like complete fucking asshats?
Okay, now move your hands away because I can't see it.
Yeah, but I would have to look in a mirror.
It just says "mmm-oh."
(Laughter)
We're keeping "mmm-oh."
That's better.
Alright, this is going to go here now.
This is good for...
This is a good way for us to distract ourselves.
Exactly.
It's good for me to practice spelling.
Yeah, you're going to get some hours in on this.
Yeah.
Oh, we need to get a wheel-in TV for the office and a collection of Schoolhouse Rock.
Yes.
So that we can, on the days we don't want to work, we can do that.
Yeah, that's pretty good.
That would be so fun.
If we just put one day, like the episode is just audio of just an entire Schoolhouse Rock.
Yeah.
Or like it's two people.
Planet Janet, she's a galaxy girl. We should do Mystery Science Theater 3000 with Schoolhouse Rock
when I'm sitting in front of a TV. Planet Janet, she's not a galaxy girl, she's only going to two
fucking planets, asshole. I didn't watch Schoolhouse Rock when they brought the TV in.
Conjunction, conjunction. I think this shows a bunch of junk. Yeah, I'm just a bill, more like
I'm just a shill for the government. That's right. These days this bill, this bill would probably be
getting molested these days yeah this little he little baby little child bill
probably although he's a child but he has a very deep bluesy voice all those
pedophiles up in Congress probably molest this this bill if you know now
yeah and that's true yeah something they would do in Junction Junction probably
as a little kid we get molested probably by the train guys to his function his
function is to be a toss-around boy for a congressman what's your function hooking
hooking up boys and man and politicians. That's right, you know, looking up with
ran Paul
God walk. Yeah, in junctions, what else? What else? What else? What else? What
else? What I can draw? I can skate a figure eight. Remember that one? No, I
know a lot of school s rock. I'm not going to be you were home school. That's
why you know pretty much that was my entire school until I was eighteen. Yeah,
I was seventeen years old, watched The School of Rock.
You didn't watch Beekman or Bill Nye?
Bill Nye was an atheistic son of a bitch and I never watched him.
True, and Beekman, thanks science for Bill Nye growing up.
I wasn't allowed to watch Bill Nye.
I did a homeschool thing from Bob Jones University for a while,
and they had their own Bill Nye guy who was like doing-
Bob Jones?
Yeah, who would like, he would like hold up a banana and he'd be like,
"This is why we believe in Christ, because the banana-"
He's a psycho.
You'd be like, "That's bananas, why? Look at the banana!"
Why does it have a shell? It makes no sense!
You know what makes sense? Taking off the banana's shell!
The shell? The shell? The banana?
Yeah, they had their own.
It makes no sense! They're the shell! This isn't even gonna protect the banana!
It's not a shell! It's a wrapper! That's what they should call it!
I'm a rapper. I'm a rapper.
I'm a rapper.
And that's what makes sense.
I'm a rapper. Banana.
This shit is bananas.
I'm rapping.
B-A-N-A-N-A-S.
That's not rap.
And you drive your car and you go real far.
That is, now that is real hip hop.
You know that's the first.
That's not rap, that's hip hop.
That's the first, the first charted rap song is a Blondie song, is the Blondie song Rapture
or where she literally just says,
"And you get in your car and you drive real far."
- Who's Blondie?
- She's some bitch.
- Respect.
- Some bitch I don't know.
- Yep, you're about to know her.
- Blondie is Debbie Harry.
- Yeah, they be hairy down there.
- Yep, they be hairy down there back in the '70s.
- They be hairy down there.
- They be hairy down there back in the '70s.
- Yeah, now they're in their '70s.
No hair at all, completely bald.
- A lot of the women these days--
- They don't have any hair.
- They don't have any hair down there,
they'll keep the armpits long what the hell is that mm-hmm yeah God used to put
hair on women's vaginas to keep out
if a bug if a bug goes in your thing it's if you get a bug in your stuff yeah
no longer a single atom enters your vagina before you're married you first
of all whore second of all you're going to hell mm-hmm if a single dust particle
But if you're a bug that goes in there, nice.
Yeah.
And it makes you wonder why they're here.
If you're a bug that smelled something and went up there, you're a serious fucking poonhound
slayer.
You're a G, legend.
Legendary.
Legendary bug.
This legendary bug.
Legendary, wait for it, bug.
This legendary bug crawled into Angelina Jolie's snatch and seriously got some.
But she's going to hell.
She's going to hell, but the bug.
Angelina Jolie's legendary snatch roach.
And the broach is going to legendary heaven.
It's the only bug in heaven, the one who climbed up Angelina Jolie's thing.
An exclusive interview with Angelina Jolie's gash fly.
A gash fly.
It flew up there.
Yeah.
And we have the very first interview.
Josh gash.
I would love to leave a bunch of dashes leading into Angelina Jolie.
dolly's stuff a bunch of dashes you know how when a fly you ever seen a fly
around yeah yeah I would if she got my name tattooed on her I'd be so honored
yeah did she ever get her boobs replaced she got her boobs removed hell and to
hell she got Billy Bob Thornton's name tattooed on her arm you got Billy Bob
Thornton's balls put where her boobs were she got Billy Bob Thornton is one of the
coolest tattoos of all time. And she got her boobs put on a box. It just says Billy Bob and then there's a
dragon under it. I got boobs where my balls are now. She took my boobs and made them
balls. It's pretty cool. Yeah. I would love to have two just hanging saggy boobies
where my balls are right now. Yeah. Anything but balls really. I'd take like
a I'd take a nice... One big boob. Where my balls are? You can touch it. You can touch two
boobs electrical outlet that's a good idea phone charger can plug my charger
into my balls yep never be can light up a whole room never miss out on class
ever again did my class of class you're gonna be next level yeah my raid shadow
Shadow Legends. I'm more interested in Gashen Glanz.
(Laughter)
Oh no, that's nasty. That's against God.
Can't be saying that on mic. I can't say that.
I'm going to play Raid Shadow Legends.
And my bae's dad's a legend for making her so hot.
(Laughter)
Respect. Respect, dad.
Yeah, you come to real good into this one. I'm gonna be playing raid shower legends. Oh sure
I'm gonna raid her shower and see her legs and her thing yep
I'm gonna raid the shower and see some stuff. She'd be making my doodle jump
Yeah
Yeah, I made her poppy jump
Yep, and she's making my doodle jump, and I'd be cutting ropes with it. That's
I've been cutting some serious ropes when she makes my doodle jump.
I made her flap bees sing like a bird.
And I touch them.
And I...
Apps, apps, apps.
I paid the...
Paypal.
I paid her pal to let me fuck her.
And now she is one angry bird.
Yep, she's one angry bird.
And I beer.
she called me and I go home, I
then I beer and then I beer yeah and then I look at photos
and I check the weather and I look at my calendar and the clock again
and then I go on Facebook and then I message her later and then I go on
facebook and then I go on
instagram when I that I got
twitter and then when I'm
looking through thing it's
like a safari basically I'm
in her system yep and I turn
my thing into chrome to make
it more cold and I and I'm
setting I'm settings her on
my on my bed fire on fire on
my bed. That's on fire fox
wait, I'm taking her to the
opera
wait hold on in my car made
room
and I'm she must be the internet the way I want to explore. I'm Duncan her head
in my butt
yeah. Give me a second here. Let me get some and my name is McDonald's
and
and my last name is Taco Bell and her her pussy looks like a wallet yep and her
boobs turn my jet blue
yep. Then I go down and I perform do a lingo
yep, and then we went to Vegas. My slots
and played and I put on a sure
then she had a word with my friend.
I put on a shirt after
And then I took her to the room. I was looking at her two bees. Yeah, she she I
she's stacked yep and she touched tunes of my balls.
That's pretty good. And I made her video call with Santa and then we made iMovie
and we did all that at the Apple Store and then we started a garage band.
yep and her thing was seamless yep and she cashed her app yep and then when we
were done walking I said I am sober and I am a and I am see her her thing and
and then she let me fucker friend blackjack
and charles schwaab
me blackjack charles schwaab and coinbase fucked her
and then i took her to white castle las vegas she was very loud our fucking was
audible
whoa
when i went down to on her she said it's game time
and then i gave her some headspace
and we played super mario run
and she called me pocket god the way i was in her shorts
damn damn that was good that was really good
and i'm big
she said let me suck something i said how about discord
oh and then she said you're a genius
you're a rap genius i said thank you
yeah i'm running out we're running out and then i think she gave me
she and then i shot my steam and then she asked me how old i was i said somewhere
between seven and eleven
and she said and and and i said and mail
yeah and then I made contacts with her boobies. You made contacts with her
boobies? Yeah, with my hand. And her name was Wendy and I said I wish you were my
Google assistant. You're perfect 365. I put it. Can you find my penis? Yeah. And I
called her a genius. Then I put my hands all over her like a clock. Yeah. We ran out of
good abs. Yeah. Is that the end of the episode or we got more time? We got like five minutes.
We got more time. We have five minutes? Here wait, pause it. I have to pee so bad. Okay.
That's a good thing that we have to watch out for now. Well, no we're not going to say
anything about it because you never know when we could do the thing we were just about to
That's true. Stop fucking over all the plans man. It's true. I'm sorry.
Best five minutes ever go.
Joke joke joke joke joke joke. Two peepees next to each other.
Me and Patrick's peepees right next to each other look at that. Yeah, and they're the same.
And he pulled my penis out of my pants. Yep. Oh my god. I just I just broke this chair. Really?
You did?
I think that's just a that's not breaking it that's just a I just think I think I
just fixed I put the thing back on it's just a chair this is a great chair
because you never have to wipe your butt you can just sit on this and all the
hell the hair hairs go up there's your butt for you and kind of filter it out
I can kind of see like a like a 3d animated like kind of Swiffer
commercial get your phone away from the mic I think it's making the okay what
are you doing on your phone sorry I had to text somebody you had to text
somebody? No you didn't. Yeah I did. No you didn't. Yeah I did. You could wait five minutes.
I didn't, no it was important. Oh it was important. I bet you a hundred dollars it's about lunch.
It's not about lunch. What's it about? It's about someone coming into town. And five minutes
is really going to make or break it? Yes. Just because you're worried that Santa Claus
is going to skip over your house? Yeah. Are you serious? Do you want me to call him? Do
you want me to call him so you can talk to him? We've already talked to Santa Claus. I'm
I'm done with this next time I'm at the mall, though I am taking my wedding ring
off.
Hey Santa
hey Nick. Hey Nick. Hey, I mean this is embarrassing panicking and taking your
wedding ring off and not knowing where to put and just putting in your mouth.
This is embarrassing, but I am I've like been a huge fan of you like for so long
is that is that just weird to say that weird by the way is that your sleigh? Oh,
is it go fast oh and that's and that's that's probably like Dasher right I
don't know yeah I knew it was - I knew it was - sure I don't tell them they all
look the same to me well there's only one that I really can tell different
yeah and like is Rudolph is he like a diva about it he seems like he would I
think I'm not gonna be able to look anywhere else is it weird if I do the
but about his nose red nose nose red nose he knows he knows he would probably
be mad offended by some bullshit like that he's so Hollywood now things about
Rudolph Rudolph has at this point he's got more fucking movies in Santa Claus
himself that's true that yo-yo fucking red nose ass down that's right he
forgets the people he came up with yeah yeah yeah Rudolph Rudolph started
drinking juice and forgot he was who is drinking water with I heard that he was
at the 40/40 club and like Dasher tried to get in, right? And Rudolph wouldn't list him.
Whoa.
Isn't that fucked? And the thing is, Dasher's a huge fan of Jack Harlow who was there that
night.
Yeah.
And he was like trying to chill with Jack.
Well, Rudolph and Jack Harlow go back pretty far.
Not further than him and Dasher, though.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
Like him and Dasher, like literally, literally they're both reindeer.
They were in the reindeer games together.
They literally, but like originally it was like kind of fucked. You know what? I bet
Rudolph's the holes of that shit against true like dude they were kids of course
you either weren't letting you play in the ring your nose was big red and ugly
yeah exactly but then you know you know he got that surgery now really I
actually didn't hear but what old in nose golden he had Johnny Dang do the
surgery oh yeah that's pretty iced out his nose well that's like the stupid
because now you can't does it make him see better at night well he doesn't have
to anymore yeah he doesn't do that shit he just
see I think he just chills he doesn't have to work anymore yeah yeah he doesn't
have to I mean yeah I heard a guy for that I heard him talking about it on that
podcast with Lil Xan and he was just saying like yeah he did the Tim Dillon
show yeah he just watches his movies now tell me what it's like what's it like
having Rudolph be the big star is that ever in all you yeah I don't know what
Donner sounds like you bet you so funny if it's Tim Dillon talking to like a
real reindeer and the reindeer just fucks up his whole studio. That's gotta be hard.
That's gotta be really hard. And it just fucking takes out a studio monitors just
like ah fucking Christ he's broken everything in here. I kind of felt like I
was the Rudolph of my group yeah cuz but instead of a red nose I had my big fat
gay body. Yep. Yep that's pretty much what that would sound like. Don't do that.
Don't do that. Don't sell it out. I'm out here. Anyway, Christmas is basically fucking
Invented to sell planes and basically Christmas used to be about playing Santa Claus
He's basically only invented to sell nose coverings. Mm-hmm
To cover up people's bright nose. Yeah, and all these women are now getting all these Rudolph surgeries
And that's what they're called Rudolph surgery
And now that you can be, you can be fat, you can be a fat model, you can be a model in a wheelchair,
you never see someone with a red nose. Yeah, if you ask me, the only surgery a woman should be
getting is a c-section. Yep, keep that, keep that thang. Unless it's not my wife, in which case,
no c-section. Also, while you're at it, leave the c-section open. Yep. What if I want a piece of
that? How come my son get a piece of that? Not my sapphic ass getting a c-section. Keep my shit,
Just keep my shit clean down there. That's right.
You should get a c-section. Yeah. You should get a c-section to get a McDouble out of your stomach
before it turns into nasty farts that I have to deal with. You should do it. I gotta take this
fart mask off that's plugged into his butt. Yeah, I've been messing up. Yeah, I would love to get a
c-section every single day after I eat something. Know what the c in c-section stands for? What?
Caesar. Really? Like Caesar salad? Yeah. Yeah. Or like Caesar
from Planet of the Apes. I don't know actually which
the guy who invented the salad or the
I don't know which one yeah, they should stop making those movies.
What what plan they did, but they should never make another one. Why
not because what if an ape sees it and get some ideas true? Yeah,
the original five point of the literally giving them you're giving they're all
really good, but you're giving all of the good except for even himself or
I'm giving them a bird on the whole plan start to finish how to ape the world
Well, I know they're not yeah, they are
No, the it takes place it takes place way after they don't show any of the plan
I mean know the new ones oh the new one. Yeah, the new ones they gave them
Well, that's not the ape that's not the apes that do it
It's the humans that do it to themselves and those ones and actually in both of them
I guess it's actually our own that I'll be real though the apes actually learned how to pick up Xbox controllers and beat people
That's true. I think there's a scene in that where the a literally a full ape team beats faze clan
And that's like the point where they're like there's no turning back
This planet is of the apes now
They beat faze clan yeah
Yeah
All right, don't just say yeah when you have nothing to say yeah, yeah, I need to learn some radio etiquette, okay?
You're supposed to beatbox.
There you go.
Buy tickets for...
Oh yeah, the tickets are going fast for everything.
Philadelphia.
You're not going to do it with me anymore?
Philadelphia, Washington D.C.,
Richmond, Virginia, Atlanta, Georgia,
Fort Worth, Texas,
Austin, Texas,
Los Angeles, California,
and Chicago,
and Drilkago,
noise what's it called we're going to Chi-Rac. SwagPoop.com/shows. Can we go to Chief Keef's
mom's house? Yeah. Really? Yeah. SwagPoop.com/shows. Go buy them. I was gonna beatbox the whole
time but I couldn't. Bye.