You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content!
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately!
[laughter]
[explosion]
Bam!
[guitar riff]
Yeaaah...
I feel like that's like the national anthem. I need to stand for that.
[guitar riff]
I need to salute!
All the fallen Spartans, dude.
(sad music)
- Dude, already the best episode ever.
- So sick. - Pat's playing Halo.
He's dressed like a referee at a candy football game.
- I almost bought a referee outfit yesterday.
- Yeah, the problem with refereeing
is that if you walk around like that,
like if something, so like if you're dressed
as a referee, right?
It's like being dressed like a police officer
where if you see somebody getting mugged in front of you,
people are gonna look to you and be like, do something.
- Yeah. - You know?
'Cause like referees, it's like a place of power, right?
- Right. - You have some authority.
- If you're dressed up like a ref
and you accidentally walk into a pickup basketball game.
- Not even a pickup basketball game,
but if you're at a corner store and it's getting robbed,
you have to blow the whistle and call foul.
- Or like if somebody-- - True.
- You're like, you have like a,
that's gotta be in like the referee code, yeah.
(whistles)
Foul on the robber guy!
If you see one person walks into another person on the sidewalk, you have to figure out whose
fault it was, too.
Exactly, yeah, who's off sides in that situation.
You know what I mean?
You gotta walk around, I mean, you're kind of on patrol all the time.
You're like always on duty.
As long as you have the shirt on, you're on duty.
Stop playing guitar, Patrick.
I was shutting it off.
It's a button.
You didn't have to touch all the strings.
I have to turn down the knobs, and I have to unplug my pedal, and then I have to shut the
amp off.
I'm already giving you such an amazing premise of the referee off-duty, and you're just fucking
playing guitar in my face instead of talking about it.
I played the Halo theme for you!
I did appreciate that.
Yeah!
Yeah.
I think that if that was the National Anthem, I would be the guy who cries at baseball games.
It's like maybe the most beautiful song of all time.
It's true.
Yeah.
I would be the dad-- I mean, my hat would be coming off every single time.
Do you guys do that?
do you guys take your hat off for the national anthem? I don't hear the national anthem that
often to be honest. Really? You don't hang out? I don't really go places where they play it.
You don't listen to it? You don't go to the mission barbecue? No not. Do they do that at
mission barbecue? Mission barbecue get this. Oh wait yeah you've talked about this. Every yeah
every day at noon they stop every they stop the barbecue dude they fucking stuff can overcook
they don't give a fuck and they play the national anthem and sing along and tell you what my mom
loves going to Mission Barbecue at noon. Yeah. It's just, I mean, there's just something about it.
Yeah. So I don't even buy it. You don't even buy anything. Just listen to it and leave. It's a
free concert. Yeah. With all these people who are fucking pulling pork back there. They're beautiful
voices. You never would have thought. I wonder if that's part of the interview process there.
Oh yeah. You probably have to do like a... Sing us a couple of bars. Yeah. Of the national anthem.
I mean, which is worse to having to do that or the Cold Stone Creamery like
tip song that you have to sing? I feel like... Which would you rather have to do? I feel like we're probably five
years away from Cold Stone switching to freestyle rap because people are gonna
get sick of the Cold Stone. People are already sick of the Cold Stone. They have to update it. Yeah exactly cuz back in the day back in the 80s
when Cold Stone started that was like the most popular song in the world. That was a bumpin' track.
But now it's gone it's gone the way of the Super Bowl shuffle you know it's just kind of a
novelty. Exactly and people are gonna have to start people are gonna start
Requesting sit things such as sicko mode when you go into a cold stone creamery. Mm-hmm. Yeah, it's a cone
Snicker cone snicker cone. See that's pretty good. Yeah, I can have that one for free. That's not gonna me
Yeah, I have so many amazing cold stone songs. I've come up with
Do a couple right now
Cold stone where you go to get cold another day older getting so old going
It's like about aging. I'm fucking old at the Cold Stone. I feel so old at the Cold Stone
Yeah, when they start hiring like older people too, I mean
There that could like work really well, why do you not see old people with jobs all that often they're dead
It's their dinner retired. Yeah, they're dead or their bones will break
- Retiring should be illegal.
- No, if you see like an old person
working at like McDonald's or something.
- I think young people should get to retire
before they start working.
- 100%, okay, yeah, here's the thing.
- You get to retire until you're like 30
and then you work until you're 90.
- Why are we wasting, like people only have
a good time in life before 50 years old.
- Yeah, exactly, oh, I'd like to retire
so I can sit in my armchair and feel
each one of my organs fail one by one.
- Yeah, like fuck that dude, old people
should have to be slaves by law,
is what we're saying, basically.
- Absolutely.
- And they should have to work for the young people.
Young people don't have to work ever.
You get to retire from the age of 20 to 40.
No, 20 to 35.
Yeah.
20 under 16 years.
Under 20 you can retire at 23 if you make a podcast.
Yeah, well you have to, true.
Yeah.
Well we're hard workers, we're not retired.
I don't know what you're talking about.
We have to slave away at this.
I'm out here thinking of Cold Stone raps
on the fucking corner, dude.
God, I look so bloated.
You know what it is is I shaved.
I look insanely bloated right now.
- So back to the retirement thing,
I don't know what the bloating really has to do with that.
- Yeah.
- You know, anybody--
- I should be able to retire 'cause I'm bloated right now.
- Anybody under 20 years old has to work,
anybody over 35 has to work.
The jobs are worse the further away from retirement you are.
(laughing)
- Yeah, yeah.
- At 96, you're working as an Alaskan crab fisherman.
And you're just like,
just start getting knocked over on the boat all day.
- And at age one, you're running in the hamster wheel
that powers the crab boat.
- Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, no, I mean, I think this is like,
'cause seriously, like nobody likes being alive after 35.
You're right.
So you might as well just make them work to death.
- After 35, that's when your back stops working.
- Yeah, your back just gives out.
- Also, yeah, after 35 is when you start
trying to pretend you're young.
So I mean, if they were working harder,
that we might be able to nip that in the bud.
- Dude, you would never get confused by a person's age.
Like if you were trying to have sex with them,
you'd be like oh yeah I work it and you'd be like - you're 35 I know it you're at
least 35. Why is that a concern you have about that? Because I don't want to fuck
some old bitch. Okay. I want to fuck people who are exactly my age because I'm such a hero.
It's the bravest stance you can have on the subject. It'll also make people who
are you know getting old and they want to feel young it'll be like oh you can
feel young here you'll work again because they remember working. You can
- You can work at a lemonade stand.
- Yeah.
- Or a balloon stand.
You can be young again.
What are young people, Josh?
- You could be the guy who pulls jams out of the lathe.
Here's some rubber gloves.
(laughing)
Go at it.
- I thought you meant like jams, like strawberry.
- Oh, you can do that, Patrick, if you want,
when you turn 35.
- Yeah, when I turn 35, I'm going into the metal shop
with a jar of Smuckers.
I mean Smucker's factory is an old woman job.
Yeah.
Oh, sure.
Well, no, if you see an old person working, it's sad.
That's what I mean.
Like, it shouldn't be sad.
It should be normal.
It should be like a ha ha, like you'd get your job done.
Ha ha ha ha.
Like, oh, good, yeah, exactly.
It should be funny, you know?
Like some old lady fucking stacking shopping carts
at the grocery store.
Well, here's the funniest job for her.
That should be cool.
Yeah, she should not be stacking grocery carts, by the way.
She should be lifting boxes.
the funniest job for an old woman is clown
yet grandma clounded
yeah and grandma clown or like
stunt double
this is not a problem
pretty good
that's a good grandma job absolutely
yeah
like like top group not a top cruise does his own stunts what am i fucking
saying he's also old
yet certainly somebody somebody like i'd like a timothy chalamet has to do like a
stunt in a movie. They toss an old woman over like a car.
I mean I think that this Timothee Chalamet is gonna be Ernest. No they're
gonna bring, sorry I just got a Skype call or something. What?
Yeah just it was like the loudest thing I've ever heard in my headphones.
Anyway yeah they bring in an old man named Ernest and they push him off of a
bridge or make him kiss a guy or whatever. What I was thinking is they could also
- Also, I mean, you could kind of make,
for example, say there's a pothole,
you could kind of just have an old man sit in the pothole
with a plate, holding a plate over his head so it's flat.
- That's the other thing, is that it could be like
the movie, it could kind of be like the movie Gamer,
where we have control of them, and since they're old,
it doesn't matter if they die,
so you could do way cooler stunts.
- Or like a SpongeBob SquarePants movie,
like when they put the buckets on their head,
it could kind of be like that.
We could put buckets on their head.
- That's what I'm saying, is we could have
way cooler movie stunts where people actually die,
we show death on screen.
- Absolutely.
- People be like, oh my God, is Tom Cruise dead?
It's like, no dude, it was an old lady.
It's fine.
- So okay, I mean like, imagine this scenario, right?
You're an explorer.
You're going to a distant island to explore the island,
okay? - Nice.
- You get to, you get to--
- Sorry, something just, I think my apartment's haunted.
- Yeah?
Okay.
- We'll get to that.
- Yeah, you get to a rope bridge, but what's that?
The rope bridge, it's broken in the middle.
You can't cross it.
you go hey uh... a gertrude you know you keep you can have your your old lady
where she was she goes down to the bridge and she clings to one end in the other
like one with and with her hands on their feet
you can cross the bridge or you could also because you can be so many of them
you could use in like nanobots or the or the zombies from world war z and you
can't react to anything that you want the canyon and i have to go out there
and i i i would have a little bit but the fucking eight thousand or people in
Exactly, they're like nanobots.
Yeah, they're just filling in like potholes on the road.
Yeah, I mean you realize your liver is failing or something, you send a couple hundred old
peoples shrunk down in there, they can repair your tissues, you know, with like self-replicating
technology.
They stand daisy-chained.
Exactly, and they replicate the molecular structure like your kidney or whatever.
- If you have like an issue,
if you have like some sort of like Parkinson's or something,
some genetic disease,
they can actually replace your DNA with them.
- Yeah. - Like kind of doing
a YMCA thing. - Exactly.
- Chained together like monkeys in a barrel.
- And you probably get their like memories too.
So like you, maybe one of them knows
how to play like piano really well.
- Okay, maybe one of them went to Vietnam
and you get to have a cool reaction of fireworks.
- Picture this, right?
You're walking down the city street on a dark night.
- Beautiful song about Vietnam.
- It's terrifying.
Somebody comes up to you.
he tries to mug you, he says, "Give me your wallet."
And you say, "I'm not gonna give you my wallet,
"but I will give you 100 old people's wallets
"that I have with me that I control like plankton."
- Yeah. - That's a good idea.
- The robber's leaving happy.
- And each of those wallets,
each of those wallets and purses,
you know what they have in them?
Worthers original, that's worth more than money.
- That's right, the robber will choke on it.
- You kinda, at some point, if you have enough old people,
you kinda just become Venom, you know?
- Exactly. - You're just like
creating matter and shit. - You can make it a suit.
You're just doing cool shit with your hands, making a hammer out of your right hand and
shit.
Exactly.
You have like a symbiote, like a bio suit type thing, but instead of looking like black slime,
it just looks like wrinkled flesh.
Yeah.
With maybe like a few hairs poking out at different places.
Probably scarier.
Probably way scarier.
Who's the oldest person you guys have ever seen?
- Uh, you.
- Ooh, damn.
- Are you serious?
- You're older than me by a couple months.
- I saw Mike, I mean my great grandpa was 96 when he died
and I knew him, I saw him several times.
I don't know, I mean I've seen some old people,
I don't ask most of them their ages.
- I think a Holocaust survivor came to my middle school
and talked, I think that might be the oldest person
I've ever seen.
- That's true, actually yeah, a Holocaust survivor
come to my elementary school too so maybe that yeah. My aunt Ruth I think was like
a hundred and one when she died and I saw her when she was a hundred and she was so
insane at that time that she started like walked in with my grandma to her
like hospital room and she just started getting completely naked so that she
could go take a shit and I was like old people suck dude. Yeah. And then I told my
grandma that I thought she was an actual dinosaur because she had a hunchback.
like spot like a spine yeah yeah I I didn't I mean you know I had like my
grampy but like I didn't really have like grampy I didn't realize you were a
gay child yeah I had like a grampy and then like my grandpa John was never
really around I didn't really have like an old person in my life yeah I was
growing up you gotta have that's why you grew up this way yeah you're not old
people in your in your life I know but that's why I'm older than you. I don't like old people I
I really does.
I don't think anybody does.
People fucking of course Neil does everybody get we don't have to talk about that.
But like everybody gets uncomfortable.
There's all there's a level of old where everybody starts getting insanely uncomfortable being
around that person who's not old and that's why you put them in the in prison.
Yeah, when they're old or whatever.
Like why would you want to be reminded about you're gonna die?
Like why would you want to be reminded that you're gonna die?
Also like why would you want to be reminded about a TV show that aired 60 years ago?
Right? Like I don't need to know about the antidote from the soap opera that you were watching.
Yeah, that's the thing. If old people could maybe like get into cool, like young person shit,
then I'd be down to hang. But until then, just fuck off.
Fucking old people. Well, the old people that we're gonna have in a couple years are like,
the old guys who are like, "Yeah, I saw Sonic Youth," or "I saw Suicide Play at the CBGB,"
or whatever, and it's like, yeah, that's cool, but it's like, I'm not gonna be comfortable around,
around like you're gonna smell old and you're gonna look disgusting you're gonna
look like wet huge yeah huge just like just swoops of flesh hanging out your
body disgusting I mean you're your arms look like a slime monster I thought you
guys are gonna make me vomit I think I'm talking about old people there was no
video my mom my mom's I can see your skull through your face I don't want yeah
She's drooping a little bit. It looks like when you...
It looks like seeing somebody in a sheer shirt. You can just see all their bones and shit.
You look like you're wearing a Halloween mask. I don't want you around me.
My mom sent me this video of Dick Van Dyke working out.
Just out of the blue. She was like...
She didn't even... No context.
It didn't say like, "Oh, look at this."
"I know you think Dick Van Dyke's name is funny." Or something like that.
She just sent me Dick Van Dyke
working out and I like I looked at it and I was just like
disgusted. Just let me think that Letterman is dead.
Yeah. He's like he's at that age where it's like I in my brain David Letterman
has died. He died in a car accident. He's done. He died he died dropping a
watermelon off of a building and it came back up and hit his head.
Yeah dude I I I hope I never make it to old age.
Yeah fuck that. I know I'm not I'm probably gonna die when I'm like 60
something 68 69 something like that I'm gonna just try my goal is to go Sonny
Bono style and fucking hit a tree real fast mm-hmm yeah cuz I think that'd be
funny you know look like a far side comic just like your legs and arms still
just like poking past the tree yeah you're just like stuck to it I think
that's a perfect way to die that would be pretty nice yeah just not old never
absolutely not yeah I've been watching a lot of Better Call Saul and there's so
many old people in that show and I just think every single time just like like
do they like they'll get old people that it's like clear that they're just weird
old people who don't know they're acting yeah and they'll just like sit there and
smile or like say something when they smile yeah imagine it's just like just
shut up and like it's just hope to God that they're getting ripped off just
anything. Just like, please don't pay these people. Also, don't let them into the actors
guild. I don't want to be anywhere near these people in my entire life.
They better not be at the craft services either.
Yeah, like you're going to slobber all over the deviled eggs. Shut the fuck up.
I hate old people food like that too.
There's so many old actors now. Can you imagine going into an audition for a role and you
really studied hard and on the lines and you walk in and everybody but you is like 90 years
old yeah that's got to be happening to be some perfect young people that have to
be around those things imagine what that room smells like to probably like really
old people probably yeah probably smells like fucking old people I've never I've
never met an old person that smells good yeah they all smell like flesh they
smell like like if you ripped open Hanes t-shirts and he smelled bad smell that's
what all them smell like if you lift like a thigh bone out in the Sun for
like a year yeah it's like it's it's fucked up man it's not like they smell
like a something that like a liquid you put in a car to keep it going so there
hey yeah also at least like I know that you're rich if you're old you have to be
rich you're either rich or you're the poorest person yeah so and the poor
people I don't care if you die but the rich people at least have the common
decency to get some plastic surgery.
- For real, yeah.
- Like, do I really have to fucking look at you
every single time I go to Walmart?
You have to, I have to look at you
'cause you're the greeter?
Get the fuck out of here,
go sit in the security office, you old bitch.
I don't wanna fucking look at you.
Yeah, like, I mean, if you're gonna work at Subway,
at least put 'em in the back baking the bread.
That's all I'm gonna say.
I don't want them touching my food, even through gloves.
I feel like the smell could permeate the gloves.
- Yeah.
No, I want them in 7-Eleven,
curled up under the counter turning the crank that does the roller dogs.
Exactly.
That's where they belong.
Yeah, yeah.
Sweating, sweating from the heat lamps.
That's what I'm saying, dude.
Just make old people do forced labor.
Whenever somebody takes a pack of gum from the bottom of the counter, they have to push
forward another pack.
They should be doing like, you know, like you see a one-man band out on the street?
They should be doing that, but for convenience stores.
Like I need them to have a string tied around each finger and every finger, like they have
to do something different every second.
I don't want them to have a moment of downtime.
- The other thing is,
why is the CIA not experimenting on these useless people?
Like, you can, you have, like,
stop kidnapping kids and shit.
Get old people and make them try to do ESP.
Stop fucking, like, I don't get why the fuck
they're not doing this.
Nobody's gonna care.
- You're gonna, you're gonna--
- I don't care.
- If you have to, exactly, if you have to,
if you have to fucking push somebody
into committing some kind of massive act of horrible cruelty.
I mean, why not do it with someone
who already lived their whole life?
Doesn't matter, you know?
- Yeah, exactly, they don't matter at all.
- And you know what, listen.
(laughing)
- God damn, this is getting very dark.
- They're not gonna be able to lift whatever--
- This is getting so fucking dark.
- Whatever weapon you wanna give them,
they're not gonna be able to do it, you know?
And then you'll still be able to impose the regulations
or whatever that you want to.
Just be like, oh yeah, another 98-year-old guy tried to--
- Also, everybody's all worried.
Oh no, the baby boomers are about to fucking start hitting social security.
It's gonna bankrupt America.
Hey, here's a thought.
Make them slaves.
What are you, stupid?
No.
Make the old people slaves.
Every one of us could live like Caesar.
Yeah, just fucking do it, dude.
Why are we pussying around?
Obama should have done this shit.
I would have, he would have had a third term.
Hey, Elon Musk, you need, you need guinea pigs for your Mars colony, right?
Yeah, start just- all these tests that keep blowing up.
Fucking fill it with old people!
We got plenty!
What are we doing here, man?
Maybe the- maybe the- maybe the shuttles are blowing up because they're empty, you know?
Maybe they're not, but you know, if that's not the case, that's fine too.
Yeah, start testing makeup on old people.
Why are we doing this horrible thing to these cows?
Yeah, these chinchillas.
Yeah!
A chinchilla's cute, I like to look at it.
It's got hair.
Also, lab rats.
Uh, hello.
I got something- oh, they have a DNA like a human.
Let me tell you what else has DNA like a human.
An old person.
Not quite the same, but pretty close.
Pretty much anything that you could do to a rat, you could do to a fucking...
They have the same hair!
You know what else I want to say about...
Rats and old people have the same hair!
That's true, they got the same tails too.
And they look the same when they stand up.
The zoos, you know, people aren't going to zoos anymore.
They don't want to see the same old animals every time.
Here's two words.
I'm about to blow your mind, Zeus.
Human monkey.
You get a whole bunch of old people and you fucking, you know, paint their ass red like
a baboon.
I mean, I'm gonna go to the zoo.
Don't worry, aquariums, you can get in on this too.
I mean, you can pay for the scoop apparatus, you don't have to either.
Don't have to, hey, how long can you hold your breath?
Two minutes?
Alright, well, alright.
That's fine, we'll switch you out after two minutes.
Yeah, whatever.
That's fine.
We got a guy with one of those big things who scooped the fish out of the aquarium with
and he's a diver, he's gonna come scoop you out in three minutes.
Yeah, here Dottie, put this anchor on your leg, you're about to be the hit of the aquarium.
Do you guys ever work in restaurants?
Yeah, I worked at a Jersey Mike's.
Oh yeah, you worked at Jersey Mike's and you made dough out of your hands.
I got sweaty hands, what's wrong with that? See if there's an old person there, they're dry as fuck.
Yeah, exactly. You could make, no, I'm just saying, have you ever had to wait on an old person?
Yeah, in that four days, yeah.
Dude, I've had to sell, dude, working at the liquor store,
old people come in, you know what they go for
every fucking time?
- That's 'cause they're degenerates.
- You know what they go for?
They go for the fucking like three liter giant glass jugs
of Italian wine that they literally can't even carry
to the register by themselves.
Like what, come on, what kind of freak does that?
- They're fucking so stupid.
- Buy a hundred nips, I don't care, okay?
That's fine, that's easy.
- There was this one time, there was this old woman
that came in, I was working at this restaurant,
I was working, it was one of those places
where they just have an iPad at the front
and you hit the, for substitutions and shit,
you have to go into something new
and press all these buttons.
And there's this woman who came in
and she had so many dietary restrictions,
she was so old, she had so many dietary restrictions,
and it was just impossible for us to get anything right.
- Exactly, they shouldn't be allowed
to go to restaurants or eat.
She's like, "Okay, I can't have this. I can't have eggs in this. I can't have that."
And it's like, "Well, I don't know everything that the food is made out of."
And also...
I don't know what the broth... She complained about the heat of the soup.
It was like one of those things where it's like...
A serious McDonald's situation.
The broth sits in a... One of those things where it sits at a temperature-controlled thing.
And she was complaining about how it wasn't... And the guy... I remember seeing my manager
take a thermometer into the broth and like showing her like look it's at like 165 like i fucking like
yeah we're good yeah what's she saying it wasn't hot enough or too hot she's like can you just
like put it in a microwave or something it's like we don't have a fucking microwave that reminds me
old people do a lot of fucked up shit like that you remember that old bitch she sued mcdonald's
she robbed mcdonald's of three million dollars drinking coffee because she dropped first of all
Coffee's supposed to be hot. Sorry that you fucking dropped it on your crotch and it sewed your vagina shut, but it's not my problem, dude
Seriously, it looked like dried magma. I'm not kidding
You've looked it up I watched a documentary about it. They showed it in the documentary. Yeah, dude. She's old. She didn't even know
She probably probably don't say that she didn't care I mean
She knew dude, she definitely knew she was in the documentary.
Now she's living it up in Beverly Hills, you know, starring in every fucking episode of
Better Call Saul.
Yeah dude, and she's killing it in the circus where she's doing the freak show.
She's got three million dollars dude, she can do whatever she wants.
Exactly, I mean, yeah.
Also, are you serious?
I mean think about what McDonald's would be-
You wanna go up against McDonald's?
Yeah, think about what McDonald's would be today if it had that extra three million dollars.
I'm serious.
(laughing)
- I'm serious.
- They could have opened one of--
- Dude, they would have to do all this BTS meal bullshit.
- Yeah, they would have to join up with all these--
- Yeah.
- They would have to collab with these celebrities.
- Do the Hiare-Bolsonero meal.
- They could have opened up a restaurant
in my apartment building's basement, dude.
- The Bolsonero meal at McDonald's.
- The Bolsonero meal goes crazy, dude.
Two Diet Cokes, that's it.
- Boom soda.
(laughing)
Okay, but you know, you just made me think of something, which is old people, politicians,
that's fine.
Let 'em be.
That's funny as fuck, dude.
They're doing a good job.
They're hilarious.
Dianne Feinstein, Nancy Pelosi, Chuck Schumer, we all, you're the best.
Politics is supposed to be funny.
And it's supposed to be entertainment.
Exactly.
So you want to have a better life?
What are you, a fucking pussy?
When I see Joe Biden go on stage and he says something accidentally racist about Mexican
people, that's like the funniest shit ever.
I'm not gonna like try and get a young per- I'm not gonna- I don't- I much rather have him than like Beidou.
You know, fuck that guy.
Exactly.
Stop- stop- just stop trying man. You're never gonna be old.
He's gonna- you know why? Cuz he's gonna probably overdose cuz he's a junkie skateboarder.
That's probably why he's gonna never be old.
Yeah.
He can't- dude, Beidou can't fucking skate.
Nobody can skate if I'm in charge.
Beidou, I- I'm fucking- I'm challenging you again.
Really?
You- yeah.
Beto show me one fucking kickflip show me one shove it anything fakie ollie
fucking
180 just an ollie something it's fucking we could do a similar thing with with skateboarders with as we did with old no
No, yeah, I think I could work got mad at you for that that tweet. Yeah
Legal yeah drug addicts. I don't care. Yeah, I mean they gonna do pass out at me
Yeah, I mean that's like they're just basically figure skaters
I know you did that to piss me off. I know you posted that to piss me off.
I've never thought about you once, Patrick. What the f...
I don't care about pissing you off, dude. I'm leaving the meeting.
I'm just trying to make a statement. I just don't like these fucking drug addict
fucking pothead skateboarders. Hey, what if we invented something that was
as lame as parkour but required less skill? Yeah, and a hundred bucks so that you could
fucking by a board yeah exactly Patrick's muted himself starring a tantrum he's so
you only work on on zoom I mean it's like oh yeah I I'm so lazy I can't I'm
thinking about the fans I'm so lazy I can't even walk down these stairs I have
to figure out a way to jump over them yeah exactly that's the type of like
Wasteoid thinking that comes out of a skateboarders disease brain hundred percent these fucking I mean he's get these
Monkey, you want to say all this
By the way ruining our fountains shut up. I have not been able to skate for like a month
Thank God the coolest you've ever been so I've been so mad
I've been so just frustrated just all the time because I just can't do this stupid fucking thing that I do
And so you made it stupid
Yes, it's stupid for a 23 year old to still skateboard. I'll say that I need to do it though
I need to fucking do it. I need to go and I need to I need to feel a junkie
I need to feel accomplished in like a stupid thing and I haven't been able to do it
And it's been pissing me off for so long tell you what you should try Patrick something actually productive and creative like maybe oh
I don't know origami
No, yeah now origami. Yeah, I mean not doing or I mean put down the board
board pick up the paper that's all I'm gonna say and if you're good I mean if
it has to be something with wheels at least try like a unicycle that seems
actually yeah hey or Patrick try learning to drive before you fucking
skateboard all your life Jesus Christ that's low that is low that's too far
what the hell whatever it's a skateboarders curse skateboarders can
drive not no no you know what they do they get tag on behind my f-150 tell you
I'm fucking slamming the brakes. That's not funny that happened to a lot of people good
They're about to fucking be squished in between my angel girl and my devil girl in the back of my truck
And I'm gonna leave the blood there
You don't know how many you don't know how many skaters listen to this show probably five million, and I don't care
There's so many good
They don't count in the numbers in my book my buddy my buddy lurker Lewis
Lewis yeah
Yeah, yeah, stinky Pete fuck you. Yeah, it's fucking trash. Jack the dripper lurking Lewis. Jack the dripper
Why do you have to have a skate nickname? Yeah, that's just his user. What's your skate nickname Patrick me?
I don't have one Jimmy the pervert lit effect Patrick
That's it dude, you know, that's it you fucking piece of shit
Yeah, dude, you love politifact so much
*laughter*
Yeah, I have political facts. I take a paint pen and I write
facts about the deficit on everything. No, you don't really know much about
politics or the website. You just like to say your pants are on fire.
*laughter* That's what it says on my nose, so I can tell the nose
and the tail apart. It says "Pants on fire." Nose, tail, how about the front and the back?
Okay? How stupid are you?
how about that I blew smoke at you it's vapor still fucking idiot I still blew it
at you I'm so glad I don't have any stupid hobbies and all my oh yeah yeah
yeah Valorant yeah so much cooler people there are people make millions of
dollars cool yeah they blow it on drugs they blow it on drugs and alcohol and
more fucking skateboards fucking idiots you play call the game for free and you
I wish I wish I'd they had a Pixar version of this game. Yeah
No, I wish I wish this game had goo. I wish this game had goo and slime because I'm addicted to it
Oh, dude, I need I need more. I need more nationalities in my video games. Yeah, that's actually good to have representation
Sorry that I'm what the hell Cameron likes to play as the different nationalities and do the voices though
It's like terrorists versus counter-terrorists and the terrorists are almost always
Middle Eastern and that's where the person who plays counter-strike
I hate that game because I find it offensive
You are defensive. What are you fucking talking about?
You play so much you've played counter-strike for like every day for the past like 16 years of your life. Just lying
I have played go that's the thing is I made it in the past 16 years
He got into it like like seven months ago counter-strike. I really counter-strike slam. I play Valorant. I never
You play counter-strike
No, I really haven't you guys don't know where you're talking about dude. You played Counter-Strike.
I will pull up the streams. I will text Noah right now.
I'm taking my hoodie off. I'm getting hot.
Is that your 100 Thieves hoodie? That's his 100 Thieves hoodie. Why does my hoodie?
What's Caleb's uh, uh steam? I'm not kidding. My underarms smell like pussy today.
Yeah? Isn't that gross? Well, it's because you-
You are what you smell like dude. Patrick is frozen. My PC froze. Hey, hey
Caleb you have a hundred and eighty two hours of Counter-Strike. I just said I have a hundred hours. That's like nothing dude. That's a hundred and eighty two.
That's still a hundred and eighty two. What's that like five days? That's nothing dude. Now don't pull up my skater XL.
Oh
Yeah, this guy's such a fucking skating addict that he has to be normally play skate video games
I can only fucking play him right now. I've been out for a month
Yeah, do you think that do you think all that be so rusty when I get back into it?
I was doing my fucking do my calves were stronger than they've ever been in my entire life. Yeah
Yes, how about she hit the gym?
That'll get you nice and strong. You know, that's a workout
Yeah, I probably should hit the gym, but I don't want not supposed to agree with me. We're fighting. This is like crossfire
All right, only have 85 hours in skater. Excel. That's not very many. That's nothing. That's a pathetic amount
If you could see how many hours I played in Skate 3.
That's pathetic.
I'll tell you what I had a lot of hours in, Guitar Hero.
Oh dude, I almost bought a full bundle today.
Dude, I really want to play Guitar Hero.
No, no, we should totally go halfsies on this bundle.
It's in Trenton, New Jersey.
We could get it shipped to one of our apartments and then we could switch off who owns it.
I said that I was going to buy the drum kit and two guitars.
I asked Neil if I should do that and he said no, we don't have any room at the apartment.
So I think we could keep the drums at your place.
You think that Jana will let me keep a Guitar Hero drum kit at my apartment?
Yes.
I think you might be right.
Yeah, let's do it.
Yeah.
Yeah, dude, let's do it.
I think I want to.
That would be a great idea.
I never finished World Tour.
I never finished guitar.
I had it for the Wii.
I had Guitar Hero World Tour.
the uh i didn't like tool when i was a kid and there's like the three tool songs you have to
beat and they're so hard i'm not gonna cry when they came on no i just like i just was like i can
[ __ ] skip this like my brother will beat it for me and then i just stopped playing it because you
were too scared of the songs i wasn't scared i wasn't scared of the songs you were scared of the
knowledge dude i wasn't scared of the visuals that they gave to the tool songs you're so cool
you're scared of knowledge forbidden knowledge that might show up in tool albums i well no i
I like it now.
No.
Did you guys see my space yesterday?
I did spaces on Twitter for the first time.
I'd love to get in your space.
I played the intro riff to Schism.
That's all I did.
I mean I've heard you do that 100 times while we were trying to talk about something so
it's not that interesting to me.
We should start writing to ourselves.
You play the whole song.
It's pretty easy right?
Yeah.
- It's easy.
♪ The forbidden secret of the stone ♪
♪ I saw my uncle's kiss ♪
- No.
- They don't talk about uncles,
they talk about secret and Illuminati cool shit.
- They talk about like, yeah,
like, you know, breathing and aliens and--
♪ My uncles are George Bush and Jeff Bush ♪
- And the Higgs boson.
- Yeah, mathematics.
♪ The god particle found it at my house ♪
- Something like that.
- Yeah, but it has to be a mathematical, like--
my brain is made of math
yeah he could be like the equation of the aliens there could be a song called that
the equation of the aliens would be a perfect tool song and the whole song has to be a
palindrome too it has to have something like that in it and it has to be fascinating
yeah so what's a fascinating fact that i know
uh... you know most aliens are robots race car
race car race car
That would be a perfect fucking Tool Song, is a race car song.
All palindromes, all the way through.
Or he could do like, 1 x 2 = 2, 2 x 3 = 6, 6 x 4 = 20, like and just say a bunch of times
numbers.
2 x 2 = 6!
It could be called multiplication fables.
Oh my god.
There needs to be something fable-ish about it.
Yeah.
Man, we should start a band.
What about like multi-defecation?
Because they like poop too.
They sometimes talk about poop.
Yeah, they love shit.
They kind of have like a wicked sense of humor at times.
I forgot they love shit.
In their song titles.
Yeah.
What's that one, Hooker with a Penis?
Is that the Tool song?
Yeah, that's a Tool song.
Yeah.
They also have Anima, but it's like, is it Anima or Enema?
I can't tell.
You know, kind of.
They kind of have like a biting sense of humor at times.
kind of wicked. I think I do like Tool. They might be the most hot topic band that there is.
No, what are you talking about? My Chemical Romance is the most hot topic. No, that used to be. I feel
like Tool has persisted. No, MCR is still hot topic. Yeah, whatever guys. Trust me. All right,
I'll trust you. Whatever. I have a younger sibling so I know about this stuff. Is MCR still around?
Yeah, I mean I don't know about still around. I don't really follow them
But I know that there's still people who are in high school right now who are obsessed with them. Yeah, it's so weird
it's so weird that like
Like the emo shit it like I guess it's just like respecting the classics, but it's like it doesn't that shit date a little bit
Yeah, respecting the classics of all-time low. Yeah
That's like you know Laurie, yeah, I mean they paved the way for like the shitty fucking well
I think now it's just all like the bedroom pop like band camp shit. You know what I mean like
Like what's that song?
freak
Splish splash I was taking a bath. Is that the song you're thinking? Yeah
Under the sea it's freak by my patchy the pirate on a leash. I think that's the one like the one that's in all the tick-tocks
I mean, I don't I don't
Man, who isn't it? I just watch the ones that get reposted to Twitter. Yeah, I'm sure yeah
Don't leave just got me nervous. So he called him out. He dropped his vape on the ground
That is not what happened. Oh, no, I don't look at tick-tock all day. Oh fuck. That's not I don't you look at tick-tock
I see a baby twerking and you press fave
fucking freak
You're a freak. Is that yeah, I mean, I don't know anything about the you know, like new music that's coming out
I just listen to like either
Mute the only type of music I listen to is either music that makes me want to kill myself or that like turns turns my eyes
into spirals those are like the two genres. Cameron I was sending Cameron songs I was sending him like
Scott Walker songs cuz Sun was it Sun O how do you say there's you know is silent. It's Sunu.
Suni. I hate that dude the O being silent is the worst thing in the world because then if you want
to like talk about that band and you like call them Sun people are like what are you talking
about and you're like you know Sun O with the silent O. I fucking hate like stupid names for
for artists. Also you know what the thing about that name is? That's just the name of an amp.
Like they just stole that. It's a brand name. That's so funny. Yeah. That's yeah but I was
sending Cam because Sun did like an album with Scott Walker. So I figured like Cam would
probably like Scott Walker stuff and then Cam sent me a Sun song and I listened to it and
it's just just feedback. It's not just feedback. It's one chord and they play the feedback
beautifully and it's one of the most beautiful songs ever recorded because it sounds like
I didn't say I didn't say I did you listen to the whole thing. I didn't you hear the part around like eight minutes
Or yeah, I thought it was I thought it was great
I thought it was great. I liked it. I just like it's so funny that like I
Knew that's exactly what you listen to I told you that's what I listen to I knew it was
It's well, I didn't know it was like like I thought like oh, that's like probably a parody of like what Cameron listens to
But no, that's exactly what it was so good, dude
And then I said you like this song that like sounds like fucking show tunes
Jackie by Scott Walker
We're in a country western music you would probably you'd probably like Scott Walker a lot Caleb
I like I'm on a huge Scott kick right now. I think he's so cool
My favorite guy is this dude Coulter wall right now
He just like sings about like doing heroin and being a cowboy and shit
but then it's always so fucked up with country music nowadays because you like you every good country
artist you'll look up like their wikipedia to like figure out where they're from and shit
and they're all from [ __ ] canada they're all from like toronto and they're just and then the
guy looks like a i thought i thought he was 60 years old he's like 19 yeah american country now
it's like it got too like uh like nationalist or whatever guys like too patriotic all right i don't
want to talk about this is already going to the boring direction like I'm enjoying
a beer on the 4th of July that's sick you like say you like country music
right you like you sad I like country listen it's not cut you should listen to
Pedro the lion that's the only band that I can listen to right now he's yeah
they're the best dude they're like I think at least three of their albums are
concept albums about a husband killing a wife or a wife killing a husband Wow so
first of all I would be investigating that if I was a police. If you make one album about that, that's fine.
If that's like the only thing you can make music about, that's not gonna be...
He also talks about being a born-again Christian.
All right, well then, hey buddy, police can't do anything there. That's God's jurisdiction.
Right.
Dude, Christians make the best music.
Absolutely.
That's just the truth. They all do.
Completely true. Best art just in general.
Yeah, dude. Like in all of history, Christians have been crushing it.
Catholics make the best movies although every Catholic director is like
insanely good. Yeah and the best like plays and shit they just fucking have
always been crushing it. William Shakespeare made the best plays. Yeah I don't care much for
Shakespeare. Yeah actually I remember in high school I said I don't like all that
rap crap yeah I said like just like as a as a joke I was like Shakespeare's just
like overrated and I was like 14 and my like history teacher got so fucking
reading for babies yeah shut up he was like dude he was like pissed yeah like
parent-teacher conference he like told my mom like yeah he's always got something
to say I was like cuz I said that fucking Shakespeare thing that was like
three weeks ago dude you still be here still breaking that people who were like
I mean you said that was middle school right no that was a freshman year high
school okay yeah I mean a high school English teacher that you mean you that's
History teacher.
History, okay.
Yeah, even worse.
Yeah.
Just broken job, broken person.
People who are in their 20s and read Shakespeare for fun.
And like have like some shitty, some shitty 14 year old kid with like weird pants.
Exactly.
I don't read it for fun.
Shakespeare's overrated.
I listen for, I read it for enrichment and enlightenment.
Yeah.
No.
It's not funny.
If someone's in their 20s, they might as well be reading the fucking dictionary on their
free time.
Shut the fuck up.
I just remember I said that and then the guy went, "It's just like what?
I'm like 14, dude.
Of course I'm gonna say something fucking stupid."
I can't believe that happened.
stupid honestly I can't believe that happened in New Hampshire yeah really
yeah you were like you got owned for not liking Shakespeare in fucking New
Hampshire yeah yeah I thought that would have been applauded you thought I would
like dude yeah fuck yeah fuck that fucking elitist pussy pick me up in my
chair yeah like the yeah play that funky music white boy starts playing yeah well
you don't understand I mean you wouldn't you're not from New England so you know
I know just one of the biggest regrets my command a certain respect that's why
That's why all the guys in star all the villains in Star Wars
Nice dude, I've not talked about Star Wars for like three episodes. I think I think most people
Okay, I mean just a people in the north as redcoats now that I know that I I mean
Now that you brought it back to Star Wars
I want to you know bring it back to we're talking about the beginning - you know how they you know
they like reconstructed like like Peter Cushing and and whatever yeah I mean
they should just do that to every old person they should get rid of them and
then just yeah be serious they had those facial projectors for the what was it
was it the Hong Kong protests where they had like the facial projectors or it
would put like a face over your face yeah what if we utilize those put it on old
people's face put a much younger face exactly also or put it on I mean on a
young person because there'll be a better old person and then send your grandma to Siberia.
Even better, even better like take like an old person and put them through like some kind of
processing plant where it shears off their face with a laser and uses it for like a hot dog casing
and then you can like use the body for whatever. Yeah and also like stem cells you know like how
much... Exactly. We could stay young forever if we kill all the old people. I mean you're not gonna
you don't miss your grandma you miss chocolate milk let's be completely honest. You don't give
- Don't give a fuck about your grandma.
- But you know the amount of stem cells in a fetus,
- Yeah, so by the time they get to an old person,
it's probably humongous amounts.
- The amount of stem cells in a 90 year old
compared to an eight month old baby.
- I mean, and we've been just chopping down so many trees
in the Amazon rainforest to make canes and walkers
for these fuckers.
I mean, let 'em crawl is what I say.
- Patrick, that's a really good point about stem cells.
is that we no longer have to do abortions
once we make all these old people slaves.
We can stop all abortions across the world.
- We can get rid of all the old people
and make Christ happy.
- We can use old people body tissue
in the Pepsi for the flavor or whatever.
We don't have to use babies anymore.
- You're right, that's such a good point.
Also glue, we can stop fucking up these horses.
Glue and gelatin.
Fucking old people have to have some glue in them.
- Exactly.
- Right?
- Well, Cam, they already tried that with Pepsi 1893.
(laughing)
- They used the stem cells from a person born in 1893.
- That could not have been very good.
- Pepsi 1893.
- Was it good?
- I liked it.
- There was some cocaine in Coke at some point, right?
- Yeah.
- That's just so goofy, dude.
- Pepsi 1893 was just like--
- That's just some goofy-ass foo-foo shit, for real.
- They had two, they had Pepsi,
they had like a ginger cola, and then like the Pepsi one.
- What is the 1893?
I don't know what that is.
- It was like original formula or something like that.
- I wanna try Pepsi 10,000 BC.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- I wanna know what was going on back then with soda.
- Yeah, caveman Pepsi, that'd be fucking good, dude.
Dude, caveman, I talked to somebody recently.
- You talked to a caveman recently?
- I talked to a caveman recently.
No, I was talking to somebody recently
about like primitivism and they were like,
yeah, cavemen were probably way happier.
And I was like--
- What are you fucking talking about?
- I just don't fuck with rocks like that, though.
- Oh yeah, oh, the cavemen were way happier, yeah.
Getting chased by like a fucking boar?
Are you kidding me?
- Exactly.
- Oh yeah.
- I can look at a video of a caveman
getting chased by a boar on my big screen.
- I can find one of those videos of sad.
That's the thing.
- That's exactly, dude.
- Cavemen were definitely happier.
I'm sorry, I have to take a stance on that.
Yeah, dude, they got to draw on the wall.
Their mom didn't yell at them if they drew on the wall.
- You can just do graffiti!
You have so much more tools.
You got to take him to jail and your legs broken.
- There's so many more tools to do
to drawing on the wall now. - You probably got
taken to jail. - You think tools
are what make you happy?
- Yes. - Tools make you happy.
- The happiest animal in the world is the noble worm.
And back in the time-- - The noble, ah.
The noble worm.
- Back in the time of the cavemen,
we were more like worms than we are today.
- They should do a full David Attenborough
planet Earth mini series just about one worm.
Yeah, just follow one worm around.
Well, you'd have like an hour of footage.
Like what is a worm's lifespan?
Like a day?
I was, this just reminded me of,
I was talking, I know we kind of talked about this
a little at the last show.
I was talking to Pierce about this.
You know those shows that were like,
they were like the top 10, like deadliest animals.
Oh yeah.
Like, did you guys ever watch that?
Like, I remember I used to watch that
and get like really pissed off.
Cause like number one would always be mosquito.
And it's like, that's like the biggest cop out.
like number one should be like some kind of animal that like exists but somehow I
never heard about it until now and it's also the most evil like it should be
like something that lives in the way by exactly they should be like oh like
here's this no it should be like there's a there's a 17 foot long wolf and here's
a here's footage that we just uncovered of a killing 10 people that looks like
it was directed by John who what if what if it was like like top 10 deadliest
animals or whatever is like one of those shows and it's like number one the pit
How about the laser sharks from Austin Powers?
That's what it should be something that I didn't know existed before I watched the show.
I mean mosquitoes is like maybe the worst possible.
We talked about how like last episode about like how so little of the ocean is discovered.
There's got to be a fucked up beast in there.
Like there has to be a humongous octopus that is like cracking level crazy big.
Yeah that we just haven't seen.
And it probably has probably breathes fire or something too.
And it probably smokes weed.
Fucking cool.
Woah.
What?
No way.
Oh fuck.
Or it could be like, you know, number one most deadliest animal is like the alien.
Yeah.
An alien could be pretty deadliest.
Oh shit.
And they should have alien footage.
They're dropping the alien knowledge this month.
Yeah.
Oh, speak, hold on.
A worm lives four to eight years.
So I guess you could do a thing about one worm.
Yeah, dude.
One worm, wait, really?
Four years?
- Four years, that's fucking--
- What a GoPro eyes.
- Four to eight years is the average lifespan of a worm.
- What type of worm?
- An earthworm. - An earthworm.
- An earthworm lives four to eight years?
- Yes.
- So when you see an earthworm,
it's gotta be full-size, probably four years old.
- That's crazy, dude, 'cause flies live one day or something,
or like a week.
- A worm is in the ground, though, and a fly--
- A worm must have done something horrible
in a past life to be you know you have to you have to eat and poop the same thing
yeah rest of your life and you're living eight years every year size lives like
we've no eyes yeah but you yeah that's got to be fucked up man and you are
gonna be eaten by the most beautiful creature of all time yeah my me yeah I
mean either either a gorgeous rainbow trout or a you know a Robin with
glistening plumage and more you know you're just or a Patrick with a big
gaping mouth. I read how to eat fried worms in the third grade. I saw the movie. I read it so I could see the movie.
I did that too. What do you guys hope that you were reincarnated as? Me again?
That would be sick dude. That would be so fucking sick. Yeah, just get to go again. Yeah, retry. Second life dude. Level up.
If you put a quarter into your slot right before you die, you can do that. You can restart. Yeah,
You have 15 seconds. There's a countdown. Yeah, if you don't do it, you got to be able to put like gold coins on on corpse's eyes
True, so they'd have tokens. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah that I mean
What that's what the boondocks Saints would do. I feel like you can't be like a dolphin or a sea turtle
What come back as yeah, cuz sea turtle you could be fucking like you do your thing forever, dude
You see so much shit. There's turtles who were like fucking with Genghis Khan
I mean, I think probably sharks and shit most likely but also I mean they could die just from like, you know
You could swim into a coke bottle and yeah, they can't really die. Well, but I
Straw but also that's because they are sea turtles are so old. They don't know what a coke bottle
I was I was gonna say like a grizzly bear, but then people would try to shoot you I think
Yeah, plus you end up in all these fucking backyard
Jump in a pool, whatever. Yeah, whatever animal I want. I just want to be reincarnated as an animal that can get a lot of kills
(laughing)
- I looked up what eats a sea turtle,
and it said that the first,
all right, this is the list of animals
that eats a sea turtle,
or that are natural predators for a sea turtle.
Crabs, raccoons, boars, birds, coyotes, and sharks.
- Oh, yeah, 'cause when they're born,
they're super, yeah, they just gotta get to the,
it's funny that the sea turtle has like,
like they either live one second or 600 years.
Why don't they just lay their eggs in the water instead of on the beach?
They're the dumbest animal in the world.
In North Carolina, all the people who live on the beach,
they have to turn off their lights in their house for a certain time of night for parts of the year
because sea turtles are so stupid they think it's the moon.
Because they just go towards the moon.
That's the same thing with bugs, too.
Like insects.
Yeah.
I would, you know, like bugs or insects.
Yeah, bugs or insects. Either one.
I meant to say like moths.
Well sea turtle might be a good choice then, again because it's like either you're like
straight to the next life or you get to see like everything happen.
What about one of those like Greenland sharks, you know the sharks that live like 300 years,
like there's one that's been alive since like the 1800s.
Like I think they live pretty deep in the ocean but you could like you know swim, maybe
you could figure out a way where you could like swim in a river and just see what's up
and then like go back and like hang out for like 50 years.
I think, well, ocean is the move also because like in 50 years you get New York City.
True.
You know what I mean?
Like you have, like you're only getting better as far as like where you can go.
Yeah, you get to live in like the most beautiful house ever in Florida underwater.
Sea creature has to be the move.
Yeah.
Sea creature or like a...
Either, yeah, a sea creature or like a...
Tree.
Alright, fine, mermaid.
I choose mermaid.
Yeah, like some kind of like all powerful spirit that can like infest...
What about like a holy tree?
What about God?
Yeah.
would be good or a holy tree might be good too or maybe like a like a herald from
Fallout 3 situation. Maybe a roly-poly. I might want to yeah I might want to be
like a warlock you know yeah or like maybe a werewolf. I might try to be a girl
next time. Yeah? Yeah just see what it's like you know maybe give me some
perspective. I can definitely tell I've never been a girl in a past life. Yeah. I
can just feel it. I think I could have been. I don't know. I think there's a strong
possibility you maybe even two lives ago where a girl yeah you had one buffer but
the two lives ago you were definitely a girl in Central Asia yeah yeah yeah I can
see your aura yeah I could tell dude I'm looking at you dude also there's
anything wrong with that yeah no it was it was great dude you had like 50
husbands and you loved all of them yeah and you seriously loved what you did
with them that's right that's right yeah you okay love something is something
about me tells me that in a past life you might have been like an apple or like
maybe you might have been like a you might have been like a naked bull rat
maybe or something I don't know I don't know what I'm getting about your aura
that makes me think you might have been like a round rock in the ground Cameron
was a snake and Patrick was a Snorlax in previous lives. A Snorlax? Yeah. The one Snorlax that
ever lived on earth. Yeah the guy, well the guy had the idea for Pokemon. Yeah. He saw
him and he's like "Oh shit I'm gonna make a bunch of you." Yeah. Yeah he said nobody
can know about this thing if they, they're not gonna want to play the game if they find
out it's a real animal. So God doesn't exist in the Pokemon franchise right? He does, there's
There's a Pokemon God.
There's a Pokemon that is God.
There's no earthly way that Christ exists in Pokemon, right?
Arceus.
But he's not Christ.
Arceus is God.
No, he is God, though.
He is the God of the Pokemon world.
But there's no, like, you know, the real God.
Like, there's no...
He is, dude.
What are you talking about?
You sound like a fucking idiot right now.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
My bad.
Yeah, I just don't...
Pokemon never made much sense to me.
I don't know why they...
I started playing Pokemon like two years ago.
Like, the handheld ones.
But I played like, I played like Pokemon Colosseum and like Stadium and Snap as a kid.
I played all the console games, whatever the handheld was.
If you played Pokemon Snap as a kid, you's a pervert now, I'll tell you that much.
What?
You's a damn perverted freak.
Not true.
You're walking around.
I'm gonna capture a fucking tight angle on this one.
I mean the thing is, I- No, it just makes you appreciate nature.
I mean, I wasn't even, I wasn't allowed to play like Call of Duty or anything as a kid
and even I knew Pokemon Snap was lame.
- Yeah.
- I mean, I have to say, and I know that people,
people love that game.
They're gonna crawl out of the woodwork,
and it's like, I mean, you can just hang out in the bathroom
if that's really what you wanna do.
- Exactly.
- You don't need a GameCube for that.
- Hey baby, just got 100 points off you, so pretty cool.
- That's not what Pokemon Snap was about.
- Pokemon Snap was about looking under Pikachu's dress
to see if it's a boy or girl.
- No, no, you give him an apple,
and he stands on a surfboard,
and you take a picture of surfing Pikachu.
That's not what happens.
- You could be playing like a Kirby game,
and get different abilities but you'd rather just like take pictures of creatures and animals.
You hit Charmeleon into a thing of lava and he turns into Charizard and you can take a
picture of it.
That's what you do to girls.
You don't do that to girls!
I'm not saying that!
Yeah you do.
No!
You do.
And you give Slowpoke an apple and then he turns around and then Cloyster bites his ass
and he turns into Slowbro.
You guys know when you complete the Pokédex in Pokémon Snap and you unlock the mirror
on your shoe?
That's not true!
So you can take pictures of the...
Yeah, you get real close to Mr. Mime on the subway.
Damn, what's up Mr. Mime?
Any Pokémon that looked like a human would freak me out.
I will not stand for this Pokémon Snap bullshit.
Okay, pervert, that's fine.
You perverted freak.
I'm not a perverted freak for this.
You're a pervy--
Oh, stop.
What did you do?
He just accidentally went low in his office chair.
Went really low.
I don't like this, dude.
Look like you're on a hog, Orange County Chopper style.
I'm pissed off.
What, do you shrink when you're mad?
I'm down here, so don't smack me in the screen.
I mean, if you're going to play like a pervert photography
game, you could at least play like Fatal Frame or something.
That's cool.
It's not a pervert game.
Play like a dating sim if you're going to play Pokemon Snap.
It's not nature.
they're not real dude it's a I wish they were real I wish I could see a Pikachu I
wish I could see a does the funny okay also a person who grew up playing Pokemon
snap that's a little bit excusable cuz you know like it's the Gamecube like
what else are you gonna play but you know 60 for dumbass whatever see you
course you would know that dude that's what I'm saying I never did yeah as a
20 year old I did 21 year old you said you were said you only started playing it
two years ago no no I only played the handheld games two years ago before that
you you thought that it was all about about the perversion and the and the
friendship no yeah you were taking creep shots when you do this to me I really
hate when you do this to me make cuz now I joke at first and now I'm frustrated
yeah you were taking creep shots of squirrels here the water Patrick I want
you to like take a screenshot of this feeling in your brain okay yeah I'm
I'm gonna ask you to click on that file next time you play guitar.
Alright?
That's... that's just all I wanna say.
*laughter*
I was doing that for Caleb!
I don't want that.
You said you liked the Halo theme.
Yeah, I like listening to it when I'm on a run...
'cause it pumps me up.
Feel like I'm defeating the fucking Covenant!
Okay?
Yeah, dude!
Sometimes I gotta listen to Halo, feel like I'm fucking 343!
I'm like, "Oh shit, dude, I'm 7 feet tall, I got kidnapped as a kid."
And when you're... when you're...
You're running from your mousehole to... to pick up a crumb...
Okay, episode's over. I'm stopping recording right now. Fuck you.
[laughs]
Caleb's small and Patrick's a pervert.