Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
- Premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Ooh. - Hold on, wait, hold on.
- Oh, there we go.
- Okay, yeah, okay. - Okay, do it.
- Hold up, fuck, it's like, it's like poppy shit.
- You, you can't do it with one hand.
- It hurts my-- - Give me a can,
give me a can. - No, I'm not, no, you're not--
- I'll finish this one and then I have--
- Why don't you give me one?
- Ow! - Hold on, watch this.
- Ow!
- You want one? - Fuck, yeah.
here alone
we all open it for you
we know no no no no
let me let me show you are great now listen to mine
i don't care how cool you can open it and you get like you're gonna like
you're like this where the ready when i was not i think you know another one
i see that it's open all of them then did you see that
you know i can drink this one really fast
we are we're celebrating yeah
we're celebrating take years
we have a we have a beautiful you pot about list
studio we have a studio now i have uh... so will uh... uh... fan of the show
gave me a herman miller
game a herman miller chair uh... on the looks like it was attacked by the
university and the hydraulics are broken it's really what's up herman miller
they take it
uh... you don't you know how do you know is that like
you wouldn't pick that up
you know what the top in square to get up nobody knows what that is you went to
manhattan
nobody knows nobody knows or care
The people who listen to this show don't all live in New York.
You know where you know, we're literally like the worst guy in the world.
That's like that's that's a show person who a person who moves to New York and
then starts doing that like everybody knows Tompkins Square.
You should literally your head should be chopped off for saying that I was here.
I'd like mad.
Sex in the city.
They don't realize he doesn't realize that the people who listen to the show
hard-working construction workers right salt of the Earth men in Wisconsin.
who wear skirts Alaska who wear skirts and dresses and like to put lipstick on
it and do karaoke yep yeah who do brunches yeah where they dress up like famous
women yeah but I had to carry it from the the first ave train stop on the L all
the way down to the Myrtle Wyckoff train okay but I saw you and a father a father
got very mad at me when I went into the elevator with a chair it's so funny to
to bring a chair on this like it was it was really funny to do that and the guy
looked at me and was like talking shit, but I had my headphones on I went what
and he like turn around and just like shook his head. It's so absurd. He
probably thought you were Eric Andre or something.
Today, we're bringing a chair on the
do it. So kind of jackass Eric Andre. I have to sit down.
I didn't think about
That's what he would say when he had the chair on the subway.
I did think about putting it in the middle or like the top of the train and
then just like sitting in it and just waiting for me to like slide down the
train. You can get high fives as you roll by. Yeah. Except from that guy.
Uh-huh. I thought he was like scoffing at me for not holding the elevator
door open for him. I was like yeah. You didn't hold the elevator door open for him?
He had a baby in a papoose. He had his hands open. So you didn't hold the
the elevator door for a guy with a baby a young father no I don't respect him at
all why cuz he had his kids too young you dude you have your child a hundred
years ago you had kit you had a kid in eighth grade and that was like old and
that was that you loved it yeah and you're gonna love it now I don't care
we need to get that guy surprised you've had you've had a kid for the past ten
years I do I do have a kid come on out there he is
Chison what is it what do you say his name is Chison looks listen to his
mother his mother before she passed we couldn't decide before she passed eighth
grade oh the kids 10 years old hasn't Oh before she passed ninth grade oh decide
on chase or Tyson yeah so we name you want to chase and tie your son down no
yeah you want to chase the Tyson chicken truck look at you he got he got fat I
didn't get fat I'm guess I can't keep that even no no you didn't I feel so bad
for saying that I did I was trying to start it like two episodes ago where I
just gaslight Caleb into thinking he got fat no it's it's fine I guess there is
genuinely it genuinely made me feel bad like two episodes ago when I did say
that I made a joke. There's not a lot that's funnier than calling someone who's not fat
at all a fat ass though. I know. It's really funny. I'm already bald man. I know. You don't
need anything else. He's giving you the worst complex in the world. Dude I miss being fat
dude. When I was over 200 pounds I looked like such a lesbian. Yeah you did. I held weight
exactly like a middle aged woman. You really did. Yeah. It was crazy. I mean it was also
I think the clothes that you wore and your demeanor and the way you acted and
talked too.
What is...
But the weight was definitely I guess one part of it.
What is lesbian like about wearing all denim every single day and having big
bushy hair and glasses?
Yeah.
You wearing glasses was so funny because I knew your ass did not need them.
I got a worse eye than you.
You were wearing like...
You wear faker glasses than I ever wore.
I don't wear faker glasses.
you what do you know I have one up that stop what shaking your leg it's making
the chair squeak well stop squeaking stop squeaking a little mouse I think that
actually is your Herman Miller no it's not my Herman Miller cuz you literally
you're yelling at me for bouncing my leg and then you're sitting here moving the
arm up and down of your chair like a cyborg it sounded like a fucking idiot
sound like a mouse guys we're having too much fun here and it's making it crazy
we're having too much fun in our new studio yeah what are we gonna what are we
why did we do this? It is crazy that we got a studio. It's too big of a space.
Dude, we had to... Well, we're sharing it with Home Planet. I don't care. I don't even know who that is.
Yeah, some weird... what are they, like a law firm or something? I don't know.
Guys that are too tall. Yep. Too tall. They can't even fit in half of the office.
Too big. Yeah. Well, you guys are just short. I can't really fit in this half
there oh I'm so huge yeah it's actually cool I'm so huge oh cool
thank you it is cool yeah and then Cameron's like free oh yes you walking
into my own bum that's you walking in a guy's I'll never understand that ass you
guys will never understand how it feels to hit your head on the doorframe you
you will never overstand what it's like to to be to walk through every door
normal. Actually, you know what? We can go hit our head in the door frame right
now. Look at that door. It's small. That's a little patent. Can you probably
still couldn't hit your head on that door? Oh yeah. Watch him. He's gonna run
right into it right now.
There he goes. That had to hurt.
Oh, I didn't. So yeah, he couldn't hit it. He admits it too short. No, no,
- Couldn't hit it on the three foot door.
- I didn't hit it, I jumped at the end too.
- He literally just said he jumped and he didn't even hit it.
You literally said you didn't hit it though.
- I didn't act.
- You literally ran through the door
and you didn't hit it, right?
- Yep, well, Buster Keaton never hit his head on anything.
- That's not true.
- That's true.
- First whole thing that is he hit his head
a bunch really funny.
- Nah.
- Yeah, that was like his day.
- Did he have like a late life CTE thing?
- You're thinking of a different guy.
- Buster Keaton, fun fact, he actually never fell over.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- He couldn't medically.
was like a slapstick guy, but he actually never did any pranks or stunts. I was
thinking about this the other day or I was doing it's like those movie quotes
that don't weren't actually in the movie. Yeah exactly. That's like my wife. Yeah exactly. He never
actually he never actually did anything funny. No. Yeah he just stood there. The
Stooges actually. You're thinking of Charlie Chaplin. Uh-huh. I was laughing. Me and Alex
were doing this bit the other day where it's like a like an American guy it's
like yeah no I only like Buster Keaton none of that gay Charlie Chaplin shit.
yeah Charlie Chaplin is way gayer than Buster Keaton. No I know but just like
that like I'm just saying that person like football versus soccer thing where
it's like yeah yeah it's called soccer bud it's like yeah no that gay crap like
Charlie Chaplin. Yeah I'm saying I agree with that person. Charlie Chaplin
nothing gay he had the Hitler thing. Yeah yeah he had a very big Hitler
mustache and a child. It's funny that he had the
a Hitler mustache and then he's like I guess I have to do a movie where I'm
Hitler. He had a
when Hitler was like this is his speech at the end of that movie. Yeah, but I
actually yeah, maybe Hitler will be at the end. Hitler's going to turn good.
That's a great movie to make when Hitler's like oh great yeah. I have a
Hitler mustache. There's this evil guy named Hitler. Yeah, evil. I guess I have
to make a movie where I'm him the whole time and at the end to make a beautiful
speech as him and then put the inception soundtrack behind it. Remember that? I
guess I have to play with a big beach ball in a movie dressed as the most evil
guy in the world. Oh he fucked up. And then he shouldn't have grown that
mustache. I think you know what was it it's called like the toothbrush mustache.
Do you think there could be do you think there could be a guy who is who is funny
enough that he turns the Hitler mustache back into a funny mustache where people
like kind of don't even think of it as Hitler yeah cuz like it was the funny
Charlie Chaplin mustache right yeah I also I was thinking about this I feel
like MJ tried I feel like if oh yeah Jordan had a Hitler mustache Hitler
never had the Hitler mustache yeah that was I feel like that would nowadays
would be like a hipster mustache like you'd see that and be like oh no oh
that's like a like a guy's gonna order yeah I know yeah a guy's gonna order like
a latte with a bunch of sparkly pink stuff. I feel like that's the type of mustache that...
So when he drinks his latte, it gets only on the Hitler part?
It gets on the side, so it completes the mustache with white.
Wouldn't that suck? Would you get... Would you... Like, you receive $100, like genie
situation, but every time that you drink milk...
Only $100? I already can tell $100 is not enough.
That's not that crazy. You drink a milk or any kind of foamy drink or anything...
- So any time you get it, you get $100.
- I feel like that's close to already what happens.
- I kind of feel like that's--
- I'd already done compensated for that.
- On my mustache, these two parts right here.
- That's cool.
- If I do a pussy eating gesture,
I do a pussy eating gesture,
it blocks every other part of it.
So it looks like I just have a Hitler mustache.
- So I think I would take that deal for $100
unless there was any way for anyone to tell
that I took it. If I could pretend it was an accident or like a
coincidence every time.
If somebody playfully ribs you and says, "Oh, you look, you got a
Hitler mustache." You have to give them a business card that
explains everything like the Santa Claus.
Okay, yeah, I would not take it anymore.
It has fine print on the back that explains, "I went to a G."
When they find out that I did it for only $100.
$100 and now I always look like Hitler every time I have a latte.
Do you get wait do you get one hundred dollars every time you hit your mustache head?
Is it every drink?
Fuck no.
It's just a curse.
It's every drink or it's just lattes.
You pay a hundred bucks or you get a hundred actually yeah you pay a hundred bucks you
get a curse.
Would you pay a hundred bucks to get a curse?
Would I pay a hundred bucks to get a curse?
I think you guys are not understanding how kind of straight and clean the lines are that
this is going to create on your face.
Yeah okay but yeah is it every drink that you drink?
Anything like water?
Anything that you drink?
that this is gonna create on your face.
- Okay, but yeah, is it every drink that you drink?
- There's, yeah, anything that could stain--
- Like water?
- 'Cause you could just lick it off.
- With water, you drink it, and water is normally clear,
but when it makes a black, perfect square.
- So yeah, no.
- Also, you--
(laughing)
- No, you can't, and of course I already said no.
- And also, you get--
- And chromatolectra goes to your house.
- While, if you have any liquid in your mouth,
you just look exactly like Hitler.
(laughing)
And then you transform.
- So this is a would you rather now, would you rather--
really and it's really painful. Would you rather for $100 get this
liquid thing or every time that there's a liquid in your mouth you
become Hitler? And you have his thoughts and but listen and his money. Okay.
How much money does he have? And his girlfriend. Oh wow. She comes back to life?
life. No, she's still you just have her bones. Yeah, yeah, Ava's bones. Okay, I'm
still saying no. I think you're just adding stuff to make me say no. Also, you
have an open wound that will never heal. Yeah, but a Lamborghini. But you get a
lamp, but it has no wheels and it never can have wheels. It looks like Hitler. It
looks like an Oscar Mayer Wienermobile type like perfect recreation of Hitler's
head. Well yeah, would you okay, would you rather have a Scott Astroworld?
Would you rather have to drive the Hitler mobile or a normal Lamborghini
Hitler mobile?
Why? Because probably was it go fast? No. Yeah, I don't like fast cars.
It's probably too dangerous. It's probably easier to park it. Yeah.
It's taller than it is like a smart car. Yeah, yeah, that's it. You're
explaining to your neighbor yeah look look I don't you know it's a neighbor
who is a hundred dollars it was a hundred dollars and every time I drank a liquid
I would turn into Hitler or I would get a Hitler mustache so but then he gave me
the opportunity to either take a Hitler car or a Lamborghini and I decided on
the Hitler car because it's easier to fit into a park plus nobody's gonna steal a
Hitler car they'll steal a Lamborghini however it does get vandalized quite a
bit people try to fill but they're just like but I did I did let somebody fill
in the mustache fill in the rest of the mustache and now it's the Tom Selleck
mobile looks exactly like him yeah oh man I do want to get a crazy car yeah
yeah that's the next step after after after offices I did say oh we're going
on tour we're going on a huge eight city tour go to swag poop calm check it out
Slash shows. Are we doing more shows after? What's the deal with that? Why would we
talk about that right now? That's true. Why would we figure that out right now? To hint it and tease
it to the audience. What are you talking about? We could be doing more shows, who knows? But we'll
probably never do one again actually. I told somebody, oh yeah we're gonna be taking a van
and they were, I think it was my brother, and he was like are you gonna wrap it in like a giant
pot about listing I was like yes we should just fucking eat or like basically eat
up the tour budget I mean and also we're every show has to pay a prize and then we
have to get back and we have we have wrapped the entire car. Well if you pay the $15 insurance you can do whatever you want.
No we have to do is take a picture of the car like when they take a picture to
assess damage before you rent it just photoshop on the wrap and be like no I was already like that.
I don't know you guys gave it to us like this. It's a good idea. Yeah, or we could get one of those u-hauls
That like has like a little we could put our own facts on the side exactly
What fat what fact would you put on the side of a new hoax about yourself know about yourself?
Cameron is taller than the other two members. That's a good fun fact
Fact Patrick has wears a size 36. I went I would maybe I think that we could waste 36 waste 36 36 29 pants
(laughing)
- Is that what you wear?
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Wow.
- That is the funniest side.
- Dude, my legs are so short.
- That's so funny.
- Look, I'm all torso.
Look at me, dude.
My fucking, like, my torso's longer than my legs.
- Yeah.
- I have to like--
- You're built like a longboard.
- I know, I gotta get--
- Yeah.
- I gotta get like, 'cause like,
the top half of my body is an extra large,
but then the length is a large.
- Mm-hmm.
- I gotta get like, I gotta start getting my shirt,
my T-shirts tailored.
I don't think you need to put any more money into your t-shirts.
It's true, personally.
Yeah, I think getting your t-shirts tailored is like crazy.
No, I think that I'm going to buy a set.
He moves to New York, he starts giving specific...
I think that's like psycho.
I think that's maybe the first time I've ever heard somebody say that, like ever.
I asked somebody...
Who gets their t-shirts tailored?
T-shirts tailored.
Fucking Robert Downey Jr.
I asked someone that was psycho, and they said that they have a friend who does it,
but it's only with like really like old vintage shirts.
That like cost a lot of money.
I'm mad.
I'm angry.
about getting t-shirts tailored t-shirts tailored it's a t-shirt.
Yeah, let it be like baggy or tight or whatever get a different shirt.
It's not yeah, it's not even for wearing.
Yeah, it doesn't what if you make it fit just right literally a t-shirt is
better than a fucking is better than a white my bed your bathroom floor with
and aware that T-pain one where he's like they got to start making half
sizes or shirts.
It's a good idea.
That was that is actually a pretty good idea, right?
Good idea, but I don't think that excuse.
I don't think that means that you their solution is to get your t-shirts
tailored. Well, you can do it yourself if you learn the medium. If you're doing it
yourself, I would think that was cool. But if you take it to a place to get it done.
No, no, that's what I'm I want to get a sewing machine and start doing all my own
shit. So I think I think that's what I'm gonna do here. Maybe this is gonna be
your seamstress palace. Put a little like table somewhere with like a little
sewing machine. We're not gonna budget space in our no pretty small office.
forever. I know what here what's going to be here. There's nothing that's where
you be is going to go. Oh true. Yeah. Yeah. Once we once I don't want I also I
don't want a sewing machine in here regardless of space. Why it's going to
be that you're working. You're just going to use a sewing machine. We need
like a printer. We don't need a sewing. What if what if like you know like
you're like oh hey Patrick. I got a hole in my pants. Does it have a does it
have a pedal and can we get a race car wheel. Yeah. Okay. I'm open to it
my camera and that's all i'm going to say
no come on. I'm putting my foot down and I'm lifting my foot up and then I put my
foot down again and I'm lifting my foot up again and then I put my foot down
again because I am in on this sewing machine.
All right, this is officially just this is the office planning session. This
entire episode, yeah, we need to figure out is are we getting it? Are we going to
are we going to bring the dog here? My dog? Yeah, yeah, he's coming tomorrow.
sick yeah so sick yeah moat is a be careful of this door Patrick. We don't
have a key to that one yeah. I got locked out of his apartment when I was
dog sitting last night. I was dog sitting for Caleb. I was like I was like
damn. I haven't fucked anything up yet. I went downstairs to get my food and
then remembered that I forgot the keys. I did I paid Joe twenty dollars to go
to Adams house to get Caleb's keys. I purposely I purposely was like I asked
Patrick to dog six. I was like yeah, like Patrick, he's going to like spend time
with Phil.
I offered to do it because I knew that you had like a big night ahead of you.
I went out to have dinner. It was beautiful.
Yeah.
But I was like...
I know and I wanted you to have a nice time.
It was very sweet. I'm glad you did it, but I was like...
And I fucked it up immediately.
He showed up and Phil's a very easy dog.
And I told him the two things that he has to remember for the dog and Pat was
like, can you write that down? I was like, oh, that's funny.
He's like three things. He was like, can you actually write that down and text it
to me? And it was like, put him in the crate. Would you leave? And then I was so
dude, I was so scared. I didn't want to like traumatize your dog somehow. And
then we get and then I fucking I get to dinner. I get a dinner. I put my coat
down, have two sips of the glass. It wasn't that it wasn't like that. It was
quick. Was it? It was less than an hour. I get a text from Pat. It's like, I'm
locked out of that.
I didn't know that. Oh, I'm so sorry. No, it was fine. I didn't really care, but
then I did and then I forgot. I told that I was like, do you have a do you
have like an old credit card or something? You try to Jimmy the door and
I'm on the phone with Pat and Pat's like does it have to be a credit card?
Can I use another
I forgot I had my old credit card. I hung up and I could not stop laughing
- But he was like, "Oh, it has to be a credit card."
(laughing)
- No, you know what, it has to be a credit card
'cause it has to loop, it's, a credit card is like,
I tried my ID and it didn't work,
but like the credit card was thin enough
that it could loop around and go on the latch.
- It doesn't have to be a credit card.
- No, it does.
- I use a gift card when I have to get in there.
- Okay, well, a gift card, a gift card,
'cause I only, at the ready, I only had my,
well, I didn't know that I had my old Bank of America card
in my wallet, I only had my old IDs.
- Does it have to be a credit card?
- I only had my school IDs, my three school IDs
from middle school, high school, and college.
- Yeah, the one you used to get into the middle school.
- Yeah, that's kind of weird that you keep
your middle school ID in your wallet as an adult, man.
- No, I swear I'm a student here.
- No, I have it on the, I have my wallet folds out,
so sometimes I'll show bartenders my high school ID.
It's funny to me.
- They probably don't like it.
- No, they don't.
- They don't think it's that funny.
- They don't, but it's funny to me
- Yeah, all right, that's fair.
- Should I see your Vax Card and ID?
Yeah, here we go, Londonderry Middle School Storm,
Patrick Toren, class of 2015, baby.
- But yeah, it was just so funny that he just like--
- Yeah, you called me-- - Just immediately.
- You called me and I was like,
you like, 'cause Joe got there
and then you guys FaceTimed to see if he got in
and I was just immediately like,
I did not wanna be on camera.
- His shoulders were, he was doing his Charlie Brown thing,
his shoulders were up.
He's like, "Hey, yeah, oh, you guys are- okay, cool."
And I'm like, "It's not that big of a deal."
I know, I just thought that like Phil would have-
Here's the best part.
I thought Phil would have pooped on the couch or something.
The reason he went outside was to get an Uber Eats that he ordered to get food,
and then I-
You guys said you would pay for it, and I was like, I was going to text you like-
There's no way now.
No, I know. I was going to text you guys like, "Do not pay for it."
But then also, I get upstairs when we like get home, and he like left the like
Uber Eats bag like in my house.
- Oh I did?
- Yes.
- Oh dude.
- It's just like, he just like had to crush it in my house.
- No, I ate it on your stairs.
(laughing)
- I ate the whole thing on your stairs.
- Just imagining Patrick just sadly eating like pad thai
on my stairs while Phil is--
- I ate a whole thing of pineapple fried rice on his bed.
Dude, I was like, I was so terrified that like,
I would like go into your apartment
and Phil would just be on the couch asleep.
Or like, even worse.
- I was worried about him choking and dying on something,
but even then I was kinda like,
yeah, he's still like a dog.
- That's the last thing on my fucking,
it's so funny seeing him in dog parent mode though.
'Cause as soon as I got there,
he's like walking around like,
yeah, so this is his turtle.
(laughing)
- Dude, yeah.
- It's like, dude, literally like the same.
- I switch up, yeah.
- You have turned into me with my ex's cats, it's so funny.
No, it's easy dude.
Yeah.
He's like a, I mean, if you're taking pictures and sending it to us.
If you're like a stupid white guy, like a dog is just a baby to you.
Yeah.
No, a dog is a baby.
And I thought I was not susceptible to that.
It's not if you're any type of a dog.
I knew that this would happen to you as soon as you got a pet.
Because I've only ever had like, like growing up, I always had like outside
dogs that were like, you kind of just have them to like scare away outside
people you know what I mean and then you shadow man now I have like an indoor
like small dog yeah and he's no it happens to it's not it's it's nobody's
immune to yeah I mean it's literally exactly the same as having a kid yeah
like this is Phil is a great I'm a scientist and it's the same yeah I'm a
scientist the sign a dog is actually genetically identical to a human baby it
just doesn't grow that's the difference it's actually he's way smarter than a
baby no scientifically that's not possible you think you for babies like
yeah my dogs actually oh watch watch what he can do what you can do but like
watching you can do guys what you do teach a bucket I did the same show he's
only like 11 weeks old you can't teach an 11 week old child anything yeah you
can you can Spanish well not my house I will die before my child speaks
beautiful perfect love languages I've been Lee I left Fox News on for him when
I left hey I did notice that that was a nice touch I did like that I got home
when Fox News was on, he was watching Tucker.
He's like, "Dude, much respect."
Phil's getting--
- Phil's getting--
- Well indoctrinated. - Tucker killed, yeah.
- I love it, dude.
- Dude, I put it on, I literally was about to leave
and I put it on, and I just like, it was,
what was it, the shit with the nuclear reactor
was happening last night, and I looked at it.
I turned it on and it was immediately like,
"Shots fired at a nuclear reactor."
And I went, "Oh my God, no!"
And I just sat down and watched it for like 10 minutes.
And then I was like, "Yeah, this is pretty much nothing."
The news is fucked up and evil. Did you guys ever think about that?
The media is actually...
But that's what we're supposed to learn where shit happens.
No, so it's actually, you'd think that, but actually the media is evil because...
What's great about these is they're only 3 ABV.
Yeah, these are like prank beers.
Whoa, you just sprayed all over my laptop.
That's why I don't like your fucking, give me like a paper towel or something.
I thought you were going to ask me to get you another beer.
Give me another beer so I can do it again.
That's why I don't like your stupid ass one-handed shit.
It sprays everywhere.
I could open that like Kenny Powers, dude.
You're a piece of shit.
You just gotta be cool as a cucumber.
Huh.
Me?
Yeah.
Look at me.
I have to clean off my own computer after my friend ruined it.
It's probably broken.
Oh, we need a butler.
We do need a butler really bad.
You can put a client in the open case of my PC.
Okay.
Actually, please don't do that.
Alright.
Office checklist.
Uh-huh.
Butler?
Yeah.
willie what's a virtual roller coaster yeah oh one of those like flight
simulator like a pod racer okay it's every different type of arcade maybe
like a like a Jurassic Park game like a clone and also once we get tickets from
the games we're gonna need to use them like we're gonna need to have something
as we can get a ticket yeah yeah we can get atomic fireballs and the butler
- The butler can't, the butler won't know how to handle that.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- We'll need another employee.
- The butler's not clean.
- Yeah.
- The butler, we don't want the butler anywhere near the
tickets.
- If we get another employee, that means that person could
use the tickets, 'cause he's not the butler.
The butler is in his contract.
- No, nobody can use the tickets except us.
- Yeah, we like earn the tickets.
- Because the games only work with Pot About List coins,
which are a special kind of coin that only we have,
and nobody else can get.
So we need that.
- If you try to put a normal coin in the machine,
it goes straight to our bank account.
- We need to get a claw machine.
We also need to get one of the ones
where you stack all the, that's so cool.
We have remote control lights.
- Yeah, we have a remote control light.
- It's fucking awesome.
It is seriously fucking cool.
It is fucking awesome.
- I really hope no one ever tries to find our office.
- Why?
- Actually, you know what? - 'Cause they'd be so jealous.
- They would, exactly. - Peering in.
Peering in like a--
- Actually, you know what?
Come to our office, try it, look in the window
and see how jealous you will be.
Yeah, you'll be like an estranged father looking at Christmas.
You're going to be looking in the window like Charlie Bucket.
You're like, "Oh, I wish I could get a Wonka candy, but my family's too damn poor because
my grandparents don't work."
That's right.
So I have another pitch for something.
Meanwhile, we're shooting a whole saloon game set up.
We're shooting bottles and balloons.
I have a pitch for another thing, another type of pod that I think we need to add in
here, which is like a cloning/birthing pod.
we could maybe have an army of clones that could maybe help the butler.
Where do we keep the clones at? We might not even get in our office.
No, we would just kill them at the end of the day and then clone new ones and we like come
into the office in the morning.
Do we have any sexual clones?
Yeah, you'll get some sexual clones for sure.
We do need three water tanks that have like suspended vitro clones of us.
Yeah, and we can just spawn them whenever we need them. They can do whatever. And then
we just kill them when we're done with them. And then we can like, you know, maybe we can
feed their meat to visitors as a prank or we could burn them for heat. Good idea.
Yeah. Or we could use them to build tables and chairs. That's what we need. We need it we need an
open rib cage, disembodied rib cage in the middle of this table. Yeah. So it looks like
we're cannibals or something. We could make all the furniture out of bones. And
and skin. And skin. Yeah. But then we have to make the furniture. Well no the clones
will do it. We'll make some clones, kill the clones, and make some new clones and tell
the clones to use the clone skin and bone to make the clone of the furniture.
- It's clone, it's clone bone.
- Okay.
- It's clone bone, right?
- Clone bone.
- So it's clone bone, is that synthetic or is it like--
- No, it's clone-thetic.
- We need a big red phone that goes directly to the mayor.
- Yeah, the clone phone.
- Yes!
- Oh, dude, I wanna talk to, what's that guy's name?
Eric. - Eric Adams.
- Yeah.
- The brave--
- I almost said Garcetti.
- The heroic--
- That's the LA guy.
- Heroic NYPD officer, Eric Adams.
- Fake vegan.
- I didn't even know, it's funny that like--
- He ate fish.
- The mayor, I didn't even know that we had a new mayor
until like a week ago.
Yeah, I thought it was still the
Blasio yeah, yeah, I'll tell you what you build me a Blasio
Mm-hmm. What is a Blasio?
It's Italian. They should
How about the Vizio the TV brand? Yeah, okay a Blasio?
There's a big old big-ass bong
No, it's not you blaze. Oh, oh
- Eublasio Potts.
- Eublasio some Potts.
- With Bill.
- And Ted.
- Yep.
- Oh, that would be a perfect pair, Toe.
- And Seth.
- Dude, that would be perfect.
- Yeah, excellent, one might say.
- We need to also, I mean, obviously we're gonna do pranks.
- Yeah.
- This is all gonna be jellos.
- But not on each other.
- Don't put my--
- No, we're doing, okay, right now, we're making a pact,
we'll do pranks, but not on each other.
- Okay.
- Unlike--
- We do have to.
- We hire a cleaning lady.
- We will have--
them on the butler or the clones. We'll have Joe and Alex in here and we could have a real
prank war. We are gonna, it's also that it's divided perfectly in half. We're
gonna have an unbelievable prank war. Yes. This is gonna be just... Guys I'm
afraid I don't really want to fight in a prank war. Yeah. It's your duty. If I get
drafted in a prank war dude. No I, dude I have like, I have a limp. I can't fight in a
prank war. You signed up for it when you got your driver. No I'm mentally crazy. The second I get my
hands on Jello I'm killing somebody. Everything that's bad for a normal war is
was better for a prank war. It's true. Any kind of physical ailment. If you have a
limp, I'm too sad to fight. I can't fight in this prank war. That's true. That's
pranks are going to help you. It's going to cheer you up. No. When you make
somebody pee, but it's what you're the hand in a hard water. He's got prank
pression, dude. He can't. No, he does not. I do. I have prank pressure. I can't. I
seriously can't. I'm I don't even think about spraying him with with a flower
right now. My just make him sad. Oh, this flower on my lapel. It's probably
nothing and you should get closer.
It's very interesting when you get real close to it and and my teeth my teeth
are my teeth always chatter. Is it does it just get cold in here? They always
chatter. Oh, the crank on the side has been there forever. The wind up
would you like a would you like an exploding bouncy snake? I mean peanut
peanut
exploding. What would you call it? I guess a spring a springy springy springing
snake. Would you like a springing snake? Would you like a snake of mine that explodes in my
can?
They should do that should be a yeah you roll like like Christmas in the in the the trenches
of fucking World War One. You just roll some some peanut brittle under the under the door
all of a sudden guess what this fucking Ukrainian piece of shit's getting in his face a serious
snake money shot.
An exploding bouncing snake.
Exploding bouncing snake. Yeah. I can't wait till this office is completely filled out.
We also have to have obviously some porn on the walls. Yeah, definitely. You know. I should
do what my brother's friends did with their shed. Hardcore, softcore, mediumcore. My brother's
friends in their shed, they lined all the walls with like Maxim magazine spreads. Well
like a bar bathroom. Why does every bar in New York City have fucking porn on them? Yeah.
jack off and you're talking well like five different bars okay yeah you were
talking about the one at Gordo's specific Gordo's has it Gordo's has just
like Mexican news pine box yeah pine box yeah they all just have fucking and all
our listeners at home know I heard I heard well magazines and newspapers are
cheaper than than wall would yeah so it's easier to build a bathroom a
bathroom usually where you want to skimp yeah there's a bar like that I mean you
You build the whole restaurant and bar and you're like, "Okay, well we spent the whole budget
but we forgot the bathroom."
It's like, "Well, what do we have?
Boxes and boxes of porn."
A bar in my hometown called the Juggling Gypsy used to have porn on the wall.
The Juggling Romani.
Well, now they changed it to, it's now called Bar Czar.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Like, bizarre.
I mean, it's the worst place ever.
I've never seen a place that is bar czar.
We have to think of a name that won't offend anybody.
Nobody can possibly get mad.
A name so confusing.
usually yeah it's supposed to be bizarre I guess no like it's a bizarre
stretch is B-A-R-Z-A-R-R-E. Makes no sense. What? Bizarre. That's funny too.
They could have just had it like bizarre. That's the first place I ever did
stand up and a lady a lady like was waiting for the open mic they have like
a just a couch yeah and I was like sitting there and she's like you going
up tonight I was like oh yeah she's like oh cool what do you do comedy yeah we
just like talked and then a rat jumped on my head and I was like freaking out and
she was like oh no that's just my rat I was like why didn't you tell me there's
a rat hidden in the couch when I fucking sat down cuz like yeah I do not
automatically assume a rat is a pet yeah no and it was on my head yeah that's a
no-no that's a big faux pas that's just Sydney he's oh yeah that's my
little husband it I mean say what you will about the place it truly is bars are
it is funny that - that they're like well we can't call it we can't name it we
can't name it gypsy so what's something similar to that bizarre the weirdest bar
ever it's fun at Wilmington I was such a like
we're gonna bar rescued and we don't know that'd be cool bars are did bars are
bar rescued bars are resources are rescued. Are you kidding me? They're
called Romani people. Now what are you doing? This is offensive. It's
horrible. You're losing business. You're losing customers. It's Wilmington has
a weird vein of like fake shitty like goth stuff. Like we went to that
museum. Oh yeah. Museum of the bizarre. Of the bizarre. Yeah. Which is it
costs like five dollars to the serpent area. They just have a bunch of little
more for some special activity like there was the there was a
game where we had to jump through the laser laser maze, the laser maze and the
mirror maze. They had two different
they fuckin yeah they have they advertise it is like oh there's there's
freaky haunted shit in this museum and then you go in and it's a storage unit.
Basically, that's filled with with like old props yeah like a spirit. Halloween
Oh, yes, statues of like pinhead. It is statue of many me as such of many
yeah, and they'll have like a napkin and it'll be like this napkin was signed by
Michael Myers. Yeah, just stuff that makes no sense and then you have to pay
extra and then you can do a laser maze and a hall of mirrors. It's yeah, laser
maze a mirror. It's mazes bad ass. It was I mean, what's more we should get
made some mazes in here that could be big. That's actually a good Halloween.
Holy shit, or we could we could what if we have the world's very first Christmas
maze
okay. Christmas haunted hayride yeah, because I went Christmas, holly hayride
holly jolly hayride, holly ride yeah, yeah, because I immediately for
Halloween, because I was thinking like we like see that corner right there.
So we line this, we could that will be a really good haunted house. This would
be a good two dollar haunted house. Yeah, you just you bring them down here,
something to think about that. I'm going to file a
haunted part of it is like we bring people down here.
- That'd be funny if we did a podcast
about Liz Haunted House.
- We bring people down here and it's like,
yeah, this is what your life could look like.
(laughing)
Yeah, you know?
- You could've fucked up real bad and been doing this now.
- Yeah.
- Now I think--
- Not being able to walk down the street
'cause everyone thinks you got neutered.
- Yeah.
I think this would be a good idea
if we put all our shit away,
replace it with Halloween stuff,
and then we, or we do a day of haunted--
- We should rent a barn or something.
- No, we do it today.
- We should do it in the middle of the woods.
(laughing)
- If we just turn this whole thing into a haunted house,
you're in.
- It'd be awesome, dude.
- We made no money, but we're like losing
a shit ton of money.
- We're losing hundreds of dollars a month.
- Because we just wanna turn this like,
I mean, it was the perfect, look, there's a door.
- At first we thought it was more of an office studio,
but it's clearly a haunted house.
- There's a tiny door right there
that a man can jump out of.
we have to have we'd have to have a little kind of like we have to have some kind
of like
fail safe thing where we can really quickly make it look like not a haunted
house of the the landlord comes and not get it like
are you running off unlicensed haunted house out of the air we need to prepare
and you could be a little bit of some panels around the
you know i'm sorry i don't know it's an all-star big empty office with
pumpkins
you know that you can't and you know
we let you know we like scary music that we can take a look at this this is a
It's my favorite song. We're having a high school dance in here. It's called
Mers Bow. Motherfucker, you don't understand it. Yeah, it's actually really
cool. I did immediately. It's funny that we just have a room now though.
It's really nice. I already love it. We haven't done anything. It's like my old
apartment. It's the same layout of my old apartment in Boston. It's the same
color scheme yeah it's just shitty like like the cheapest remodel you can do yeah
the shitty laminate yeah the shitty laminate floor the white laminate dude
this shit looks horrible I mean this place is ugly as fuck yeah that's why
we're gonna put up porn. Scarecrows. Right. A scarecrow with boobs. We do got to get
some boobs in here. Scarecrina. It's also it's all about stimulating your creative gland in your head.
definitely yeah and i feel like we should get a treadmill in here yeah maybe three
treadmills side by side maybe four four treadmills or six treadmills a walking
desk why not a hundred okay okay six treadmills like this we put a camera in
there wait guys hold up we're gonna sing a song treadmill as like the exact
amount of treadmills to perfectly cover the entire floor with treadmills so the
entire and we we turn them all on at the same speed at the same time and it's one
big treadmill how about this oh like like I was going okay go but you're yeah no
I'm like a entity yeah giant
well you took too long to say it trampoline we're in where trampoline gym
every surface covered in trampolines this is what a five and a half foot
ceiling just fucking sticking your head in there getting stuck all the time I
want a ball pit jump into the ball pit we aren't okay are we gonna be doing
I'm not kidding. We could get a bathtub and fill it with balls there.
That's true. Like a claw putt. Yeah. I gotta relax.
Or like, just jumping into the ball pit and just cracking your head open.
Just like a porcelain. I feel like a mini ball pit is not a bad idea for that.
an inflatable pool filled with water. Okay, I'm fine with that. Water slide? Well, I do
think it does go down. I did think we could do a slip and slide in here before we move
everything in. Yeah. We do just one day. You mean everything out? No, before we move all
of our stuff in. My stuff's here. Well, yeah, but we'll start right here. Your stuff doesn't
matter. But then also we don't want to get water everywhere, so I was thinking olive
oil or something yeah easier to clean up or just dry my my new dry yeah so we just
get a bunch of sesame oil gross and then slide yeah someone left a bunch of
sesame oil that's an expensive oil in the cabinets and they left a bunch of
sesame oil and a bunch of canned food why are people freaking out about seed
oil what's wrong with seed oil? I don't know. So what's the deal with seed oil nowadays?
Joe Rogan said something about seed oil. It's his damn seed oil. What's up with the seed oil?
went on really yeah is it gonna make me low-t is it made of oil or is it made of
seeds what's the deal with oil in those what are they balloons how about we turn
the seeds into butter peanut butter my name is George Washington Carver
Seinfeld George George Washington Carver is this a perfect Seinfeld kind of like
That's a mine for him. Oh definitely his name is George Washington, but he's also
Carver Carver Carver I remember it is George, Washington
Snowboarder
It's on the other side of the mountain of peanut butter and he's carving a Mount Rushmore with George Washington
He's carving a Christmas ham
He's driving a car
(laughter)
- He's carving, is that what you say?
- George, Mike Fletcher's George.
(laughter)
- Washington, that's a state.
- Washington, what does that mean?
He's washing something?
- Yeah, he's washing his shirt a ton
'cause he got so much peanut butter on it
when he was trying to invent it.
- And George-- - That just makes sense.
- And George, what's that, an alien species?
- I've never met anyone named George.
- I don't know, Mike is going crazy.
- I do know, yeah, he's George like the guy I know,
that he's Washington like the president and then he's got your mic just turned
off you just fucked up your mic with whatever you did what did I do I don't
know you fucked it up. Can you hear me? The greatest bit we've ever done in the history of the podcast
about Seinfeld doing something real wrong with his brain yeah and you
destroyed it I think Seinfeld every time that Seinfeld is brought up on our show
I try to resist but it's just too yeah I have to every once in a while I have to
throw it I feel like I feel like sometimes I'll hear something like that
and I just have to I I can't do the Seinfeld voice very well but I know that
if I just throw one out there it's good I'm gonna rent set the sample doesn't
even have a voice you just go people anything like that you watch comedians
and cars getting coffee and he's like the thing about comedy is but it just he
he doesn't sound anything like yeah.
But I look through my jar of peanut butter. I looked through my text with my
father the other day, 'cause me and Joe were comparing dad texts and just like
how just like stupid. I'm gonna look at my dad's texts. When you text your dad,
it's how dumb it is. Yeah. And it's like a joke, like why would you ever text
your dad? You're never talking about anything important. And I texted... He
texted me like two years ago, and he sent me a text that was like, it was
like, "New Seinfeld special, he really missed the mark."
I was like, okay, dad. Yeah, that is it. It's always what it's like. What do you
think? I'm sitting there like having an opinion on the Seinfeld special. He has
he knows that comedy like a three weeks ago now he asked me he asked me for
Irish rebel music like songs and I listed like five. I was like, oh yeah,
there's like a bunch of songs by the wolf tones and I listed like five songs
and he was like what else is played by them I was like dude I just gave you
fucking five I gave you five songs yeah a lot that's already too many songs to
give someone right you're like recommend what is it like a greatest hits album is
anywhere between like 8 and 14 you know somebody like a greatest hits album yeah
it's anywhere between 8 and 14 it's saying like usually like a greatest hits
album what's it between 8 and 14 Millennium collections that they used to
they sell Barnes and Noble's with the white cases. I know what a greatest hit
of miss. I was talking about the specific one the ones that they would
sell at Barnes and Noble that had the biodegradable casing is there between
eight and fourteen. Oh yeah, I got the Aerosmith one. I was ten and they only
had like eight to fourteen songs on it. Okay, but why because they're only
doing the biggest hits Cameron, you know it's a great I'm just because I said
five songs is too many to record to give to say some to someone when you're
recommending a band and you said yeah greatest hits albums of anywhere from
8 to 14 I gave him like almost the greatest hits that's what I was saying
oh I gotta read you guys the text between my dad and me during the Super
Bowl oh yeah he's a big Rams fan uh-huh let me find these big Ram Jam fan don't
even you better shut up he's a huge better show this is the last time that I
text he knows he knows one more song than black Betty here's what I said I
So he's a huge Rams fan. I'm guessing the Rams scored and I said nice and he said
booyah and I said and then ten minutes later or no four minutes later I say
that no call and my dad says brutal and then I say let's go and he says booyah
fo shizzle. That's awesome dude. That's great. Booyah. Fucking yeah dude. My dad's the only guy I've ever met
says booyah. You know what, guess what my dad's ringtone is when he gets a text.
Every time he gets a text. Nope. Better. Okay, your dad really likes girl talk. I
know that about your dad. You're on the wrong direction. I'm in the wrong
direction? Here's my dad's. Give a hint. It is insanely obnoxious. Is it a song?
it is a diddy. Oh okay okay run through the diddy rolodex in your head. Yeah diddy
from when? Is it like a newer one or like an older one? Is it like a commercial?
Yes we are. No every time that my you know people text sometimes you'll get
five texts in a row from somebody. Yeah my dad has never put his phone on silent
every single time he gets a text
*Danny imitates a text*
ESPN
That's not a diddy!
That's a diddy. No that's not a diddy!
No, fuck you! That is not a diddy at all!
My dad will be talking to me about my grandmother's health
and just his phone is going off in his pocket
*Danny imitates a text*
So we have to move her to the nursing home
That's not a diddy, that's a jingle
There's a huge difference between a diddy and a jingle
Diddy is like Yankee Doodle
think that that's how diddy yeah it is as out of diddy that's it's not no
Yankee doodle diddy this is a song it was like the biggest hit it was like the
song of the summer it was huge it was the song of the summer it's my dad's
text tone is one that he just found in the like one of those ones that you find
in the like iPhone settings that just nobody's ever used yeah yeah like all
I like one word name yeah something like that, but it sounds like it just go
like
it's like I literally don't know what it's like the sound of I'm not what it
could possibly mean my phone. Let me see if I can you hand me my phone. I want
to see if I can find it in my set. I was the only person in my family who has an
android phone, so every like oh she has the the motorola one that like lips, I
don't know, you know the one that like the it's like the new razor. It's like
touch screen that closes and like every she literally like every cut like 10
minutes or like tense like it's like yeah that one yeah dude it's I've never
taken my phone tone I've never taken my phone off silent and now I've got I've
gotten so good at I can tell what kind of notification I just got on my phone
by how long it buzzes yeah where I never take my phone off silent you don't need
- No, my phone will buzz on the couch and
Jano will be like, you gotta text.
I'll be like, no it's an email baby.
- Yeah. - It's actually an email.
- You get buzzes for emails?
- Yeah. - You can set up
different buzz tones too. - Yeah, you can.
I was gonna try and find that text tone,
but I realized I'd have to play every single text tone
in my phone and I was like, no.
- He's putting his phone in his crotch.
- What are you doing? - Don't do that.
- That's nasty, dude. - I don't wanna see you do that.
There's a picture of your brother
at the back of your phone. - Can you guys email me
maybe like a-- - No.
There's a picture of your brother on the back of your phone.
You put your brother's face on your penis.
Yeah, I want him to suck my dick.
I want to fuck my brothers.
What?
You guys don't want to fuck your brothers?
No.
What?
Why?
Because I slept in the same room as them for most of my life.
They're like different versions of you.
I want to fucking cum all up my brother's butt.
Stop talking about fucking your brother.
That's weird.
I want to cum in their butts.
he's actually winning me over.
He's actually making some very cogent. I was against it before
you're going to have to argue and really later when you get a call,
we're white from from my you try to pay
your wiener open up your credit card. I'm trying to see if I can pay my
penis.
Let me kind of
that'd be funny if like somehow there was some just like like well,
biological like electrical nerve signal that somehow just like it just
deducts ten thousand dollars
phone accident is gone for really hold it your phone up to where you got
vaccinated and
all your money
paid for some like some freak static shots like completes the circuit.
There's a charge on your bank account that just says like ten thousand
dollars. Funko
that's probably what it's for. It's probably that's why they were pushing
contactless now and Apple Pay right before the vaccine.
- Yeah.
- And so you think you're paying the bodega guy,
he's actually, he's not getting any money.
And actually it's all going to who freaking knows where.
Probably like Russia or China, yeah.
- Yeah, probably it's gonna be China.
- That's probably how Russia was able to get all the military
to attack Ukraine is probably they got all the money
from the bodega that I would spend every day
when I buy candy and toys.
I thought Russia, until like this week, I thought they were still living in like
chivalry, like they were still like walking around with swords.
Really?
They had great swords.
You've never, you, I don't, I do not, I don't care about Russia at all.
The only time I ever think about Russia before the like past few weeks or
whatever.
Dash cam footage?
Yes, dash cam footage or like a like a video of someone like, yeah, like, like.
Picking up a bomb and throwing it off like a 12 story building.
Or like, like, like.
Falling off a building, that's a big one.
Or like, like taming a bear with their mind or something.
like they definitely it's like Skyrim over there. Oh dude yeah we're so fucked
against them. Dude they just they don't care if they live or die it's scary a man
who has nothing to lose that's what Russia is. Yep that's why I'm gonna side
with with China and Russia early. I'm siding with China but not Russia. Luckily
I'm insanely advanced at killing people. I'm not siding with
Russia because I heard that Putin is gay. Oh really? Yeah, apparently he's gay with
Trump and with several other leaders of the Republican Party. You know, I'm actually
hearing that too that Vladimir Putin actually has done gay stuff with
Donald Trump, former United States President. Yeah, I heard that
apparently there was a pee tape between them. I heard there was a fat
guy who went over there that became a machine. I heard about that too. I heard
It was quite funny. I used to be the president and not only this, he was orange.
Yeah? Really? Yeah. I actually didn't receive that. I really want to cite your source.
Yeah, because there's a lot of misinformation being spread around the
internet these days, especially now with the Russia stuff. He's looking away.
He can't even look us in the eye. It's just misinformation. There was never a fat
orange president. www.there's a skinny gray president.
You know, Trump was actually skinny and gray.
He's skinny gray, he had big black eyes.
Despite popular belief, Donald Trump was never actually orange.
Like if you didn't know this.
In the movie.
In the movie, Donald Trump never admits to being orange.
Donald Trump never was fat or orange or cool or tall.
Donald Trump, it's funny, he never ate a hamburger.
There actually were under 100 hamburgers.
I am from everything it was actually mostly hot dogs coffee fee is actually
delicious coffee fee is actually an ancient ritualistic drink and he knew
exactly what he's talking about yeah and coffee hamburger did he I just need him
like I need a murder is still the funniest thing in a very cool is so
- It's so fucking good.
- It's just like, you know, honestly,
I fully understand. - Dude, that picture of him
with all the burgers.
- When he's standing with his hands like.
- Dude, I wish I was at that dinner.
I would do anything to eat just to watch him
eat a Big Mac in a room.
- That picture make me so hungry for hamburgers.
- Me too.
- My hamburger instinct.
- Over 100 hamburgers.
- Dude, he had Wendy's, Burger King, and McDonald's.
- I might have to get a burger on my way home.
- He had Wendy's, Burger King, and McDonald's.
- I might have to.
- My little thing went off.
enough. I just set some birders yeah yeah. Oh yeah,
birders, cheese birders, ham birders, yeah, veggie birders, no, no, a black
bean birder. Oh, what a black no,
impotable birder, no, no, disgusting, but ham. Who doesn't like ham in their
birder? Oh God, chicken birder, if you're in Canada, have they ever tried
making a pork burger, a pork burger? Yeah, I had one.
- Have you ever-- - Oh, I have.
- Bullpop Grill. - Oh, yeah, I had one.
Oh, they do?
I love that place.
- J-Uke Burger, I think I said that right.
- You better watch it.
- What?
- Stop trying to pronounce things correctly.
- You better be careful.
- You better be, it's all I'm gonna say.
- What do I do, like, one letter off?
- Yeah, you're gonna get-- - It's just like
the craziest slur in the--
- You're gonna get kicked off
the BoJack Horseman writing room.
- I heard if you're-- (laughing)
- You're done for.
- Don't tell anyone that that's my fucking job, dude.
- I heard there's a-- - Mouth is, you're done.
I heard there's a really bad word that's one letter off of hamburger.
There's what?
There's a bad word that's one letter off of hamburger.
I heard that too.
Nerf-erder.
What?
That's way more words off.
What did you say?
Nerf-erder.
Oh my god, I'm going to have to edit this out.
Can you believe it?
You're a butt sniffer.
No.
Sniff butts.
Don't say that to me.
I want to, I need to smell a butt.
Yeah?
Yeah.
put your ass in my face. He sniffed my butt like two months ago. I kind of got
I got the bug. I like sniffing butts now. I think he has to sniff it to
survive. I want to bury my head in a lazy boy after Patrick's been just sitting
there fucking just crushing seltzers just blowing carbon. No, these literally do
nothing to me. I could drive right now. I mean like a can of drive. You can't drive.
- Your life's over dude, you can't even, you're--
- I did, one time, oh dude, one time my dad took me
to the South Elementary School parking lot when I was 16
and I somehow got the car, there was like a,
there's like this like grass thing that goes down
to like the entrance of the school,
and you know where they like divide a parking lot
and then they like leave a little patch of grass
and like in between the stairs?
I somehow got the car all the way up that.
(laughing)
- I will never--
- I got my dad's 2003 Ford Focus all the way up that,
He was like, how the fuck did you do that?
If I ever let, sorry, it after this, this dog thing, I will never let you, I was
considering letting you borrow my car for something and just making you drive.
I thought it'd be funny, but I do feel like it would end up upside down.
Yeah.
It would be like, like a roof.
Dude, I literally, I get a text from Patrick.
I upside downed it.
I, I, can you come home?
I upside down to the car.
I tried to get someone to flip it, but it just made it worse.
Does it have to be right side up to drive it?
Does the wheels have to be on the ground to drive this?
I upside downed it pretty bad.
I upside downed it pretty bad, but I did get you, I got you some snacks.
You didn't even leave any snacks.
And you guys don't even have to pay me for gas.
Because I didn't move it, I just, by the way, I spent $100 on gas to upside down it.
pops a wheelie immediately just all the way over. It's inexplainable how he did it. Yeah.
It just I turn around I say okay here's the keys I turn around I hear a noise I
look behind me it's upside down mm-hmm and he's standing. It got upside down. He's
standing on top of it like the king of the hill and he's saying I upside downed
it. I'm so sorry that I upside downed it. I accidentally upside downed your car. Yeah you turn around
around immediately. You get one you get three texts ones like dude dude. Oh my
god, I upside down it. Oh my god is the car supposed to upside down. Oh no, I
upside. I have to
do I have to use the keys to re upside it to right side up it to right. Oh my
god. I upside down and killed three pedestrians did
I deaded three people and upside down your oh dude. I I bloodied a guy. It's
That's part of it, though. It's upside down, dead end, three. Your car.
I need you guys to learn how to drive before we go to the store.
I was trying to learn to drive for a while.
Can I teach you guys?
I would love for you to teach me how to drive.
I was doing pretty well. I was learning to drive my mom's car, and then my dad
was like, "No, I'll teach you to drive a stick shift." It's like, "Okay, well,
I can't drive."
No, he's going to--
Yeah, no, it just literally, that stopped me from learning to drive because I
just could not.
I used to have a truck at work when I was doing construction,
and it was a stick shift, it was like an old Ford.
- Yeah.
- And I never learned, the guy just gave me the truck
and was like, "Yeah, just drive this to jobs and shit."
- Yeah.
- And I would just go 20 miles an hour,
just stopping like this every 10 feet.
- Literally, yeah, I would go to a parking lot
to drive around every day for an hour or whatever,
and literally would never be able to not just stop.
I could never go on the street.
I never once tried to learn how to do it though.
I, straight up, I just can't get behind the wheel of a car.
It's not good for me and it's not good for pedestrians for me to be behind the wheel
of a car.
It's so easy to drive.
I don't know about that man.
It's so easy for me.
Literally 16 year olds drive.
Yeah, I tried when I was 16 and I couldn't do it.
But now you're 14 and you can do it.
It's true, I am 14 years old.
I would like to learn how to drive.
I'm just so damn lazy.
I also don't have a car now.
What if you had a cool as what if you had like a recliner in the driver's seat?
You can be lazy while you drive. That would be sick. You guys need you guys
need self driving automated cars. Yeah, yeah, I'm going to buy a tesla. I think
I think I'm going to sell the office put it in the middle of the office.
I'm going to get a minute. I'm going to get a tesla that's small enough that I
can drive it back and forth in the office. I'm going to get a shriner tesla
you guys are like working over charge it like smash we do need a go-kart for sure
no question one of those little like one of those little like Mercedes that like
people get for their kids what's something we could put outside though
scarecrow yeah scarecrow oh a haunted house yeah all right well is that the
episode that's the episode okay wait again we're going dot-com slash shows
let's let's say everywhere we're going really all right Philadelphia for
Washington DC Richmond Atlanta Texas Austin Texas and for worse than yeah and
then LA Los Angeles just learning Chicago everything Chicago that's
everything as far as we know as far as you know yeah as far as I know uh-huh so
please go to swag poop.com slash shows yeah or you go to pot about li.st that
redirects there to a swag poop.com so fun that's for once in your life nerd
sorry bye