Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
*Badass music*
you can tell was fired over the years when i was really concerned she's worthy
holy fucking she's
wall
history
well
three-hundred this is literally a m
the
it's
it's very um...
adjective
let's enact invoked a list of his focus we did an entire mad lives episode
nobody liked it right
there's no way
that we could do to mad libs episodes in a row
children
world
the
filter dying in the school that making that the hook is so crazy
that's so awesome
children and i mean in the school
will release should be by i swear to god for the past
twenty four hours i've watched that
I've watched that 20 times.
I'm like, I'm that guy is cool.
Dude, yeah, it's it's past the point where it's like this name.
Jake Novak, Jake Novak, open invite.
Come on the podcast because we're sitting grad.
We've done it before.
Okay, we'll work our magic.
Can you believe that?
And we're sitting grad like, Nope, I don't believe that.
Okay.
I it's it's past the point for me where it was like at first I was like, Oh, this is
some cringe bullshit.
it. But actually now I think this is based as fuck.
Really? Yeah, it is pretty based.
Honestly, at least politically. It's politically based but also like musical
theater but it's like, it's honestly... I don't know if the music is fire. I think
the music might be... No, dude, it's so cringe that it's based.
I think I've removed the part of my brain that reacts to things negatively because I
think I just like everything now. Me too.
Like I watched that first video of that guy and I was like, "This guy is honestly cool.
the
He basically stole it from us. Yeah, once you get past the like there's a part of
your brain that you have to you have to help. There's a part of your brain you
have to help. I'm saying that for the most part. I would say betterhelp.com.
Yep. Yeah. Use code "blist" to get 20% off your first session. It does suck to get 20% off your first session.
Because us as the first three guy cast member. Well yeah, we wouldn't be hired like SNL
SNL. Right. We wouldn't be hired like Lonely Island or something like that. No. We'd be
one can see one guy would be for the first three guys wardrobe would be so big
mm-hmm long the wardrobe would be so we why it depends on how we stand so smart
yeah because we could do we go up or wide yeah or diagonal that'd be way we'd
need two other guys I think I think they have that's what they have at least 50
years of experience over there all stilts second of all stairs and third of
all ramps but that's fucking bullshit and you know it it's not bullshit we could
be in the magic of performance in a sketch we'd have to get we'd have to get we'd
have to be good at it only do sketches about about kids trying to sneak in a
movie we do sneaking into an abortion clinic yeah well just be sneaking in a
different into an abortion clinic to save a remember when you were kidneys to
sneak into a bar no yeah well yeah yeah because they're putting the fetuses into
Pepsi bottles and I wanted to steal all the Pepsi.
Yeah, they're doing Joseph Mangala experiments on them.
I wanted to taste what Pepsi tasted like before they put the fetus in it.
I wanted to see what the stem, yeah the stem cell.
Sneaking into an abortion clinic, it's perfect when you do the two kids stacked on top of
each other in a trench coat thing because you walk up and they're like, "Oh, you look
too young, there's no way we could do an abortion on you."
And you open the trench coat and they see a little kid's face and your crotch and you
go, "Oh my God, this is the perfect time for us to kill this baby."
Oh my God, it's being born. We have to we have to we actually know we don't have
to let's wait 10 minutes. We're gonna wait 10 minutes make sure actually let's
wait for its first word and then we'll put an ice pick through its spinal cord.
Yeah and then we're gonna use like an electric net from a sci-fi movie. Yeah.
To capture it. From Conquest of the Planet of the Apes. Yeah we're gonna do
the big the opening scene from Jurassic Park and we're gonna herd your your baby
into a cage. And yep it's gonna go to Baby Park. They should do a version of the
office that takes place at a Planned Parenthood. Yeah. And you're in the
break room and Stanley is microwaving a six-year-old. You're in the break room?
The camera. Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I forgot the camera's a character. The camera is.
The sound guy becomes a character in season 7. In a mockumentary style movie or show, the camera is the
audience member. The office plays itself. You just blowed my mind. Exactly. I blowed
your mind. Wow. Yeah. I fucking have abilities like that. Damn. It's like how
New York City is a character in some movies. I heavily disagree. What movie is
New York City? LA Confidential. Wrong. It's a character that doesn't is an off-screen
character. Mmm it's like Kaiser. It's like you know it's there yeah but it's not
gonna show. Yeah. Wow that's true. Yeah. Whose water bottle is this? Which one? The
blue one. The brand new one. What the fuck? Yeah. Who is that? What the hell? Who's is that?
that's got to be Alex's right yeah why are you just guessing it's somebody in
to be somebody fucking squatted is that the beautiful it says initials bi no way
that could be Alex Wow Alex Forrest same initials no bi yeah yes he has a weird
initials thing yeah yeah they aren't his name oh there aren't the letters of his
name is it a wait wait wait wait wait that's something that you're born with
sometimes. What colors is it? Yeah. Blue and indigo. Blue. Oh, that's what it is. Yeah.
Oh, blue and indigo. Yeah. Okay. All right. Well, Mystery Solved. Did they leave that
here for Pride Month because it says BI? Where's the water? Bottle in. True. That's why. Oh,
my God. Yeah, because the water's bottled in. And maybe if it was carbonated, it'd be
bubbling inside. Yeah. Wow. Yeah. That's true. That's true, too. And whoever has it, bought it.
whoever's it is. Whoever made it bottled it.
Yeah.
Beverage insider.
Yeah, that's what a bottle is.
Mm-hmm.
Bottle is an acronym.
Beverage insider.
Yeah.
Bottle is.
Beverage over this thing.
Bottle is beverage in.
Beverage on, beverage on side.
Beverage on side this thing.
You gotta send that to Jake Lovett.
He could do magic with that one.
We gotta have him do a bottle rap.
Bottle is beverage in.
Bottle guy rap.
Bottle stands for beverage on side this thing less evaporation.
yep it doesn't evaporate if it's got a lid on it who's that this one that is
this is mine that's his you know you don't even put any cool stickers on your
now gene no putting cool stickers is gay as fuck
what can't say that this month that's that's high school shit dude I would say
just having a now gene is pretty much a girl that's fine I didn't say anything
about the last girl I said it was gay as fuck you get the plastic one dude your
peepee is never trying to sterilize myself so can I have sex with 1 million
women's my fucking guy my fucking okay that's actually baller as fuck holy shit
dude next Barack Obama right yeah I know I know that I'm not drinking micro
plastics from this water bottle cuz I can see the plastics they're macro
plastic yeah am I not getting Mike is this not is this table not giving me
micro wood I have micro wood nobody tables no nobody say that I have micro
wood micro you have micro don't say that I have my girl would we all about
seriously not giving me micro would right now he has micro would when he
thinks of Michaels would he was he was surprised that Michael wasn't speaking
of micro would and me yesterday I was free ballin and I made a trip to CVS to
get a diet coke and my balls were hanging out of my zipper completely undone the
entire time. And then the security guard said, "Your fly's undone." And I looked down and
there was a piece of bubble gum coming out of my snout.
Nice.
It was my balls.
That's cool.
I never free ball. I always wear underwear.
Really?
I love free ball.
Yeah, I don't know what it is.
In the summer, dude? Ooh, it's nice.
I can't free ball. I can't wear sweatpants.
You just can't.
I physically, like something about it. I've talked about it before.
It's hard when it's hot. Sweatpants are a fall and winter and spring.
I tried. If you're wearing sweatpants in the summer that's...
I mean they make you sweat. Yeah.
I love wearing jeans.
Okay, jeans, that's wrong though. That's incorrect. I hate wearing any other...
The only thing you can wear in the summer is shorts or underwear.
These are cutoffs because I love wearing jeans so much. I wear pants... I like pants.
I don't like wearing shorts all that much. Yeah.
My uh... I'm getting nervous because I got a pair of pants. My favorite pair.
the pair that fits me just right,
'cause I've been skating in them.
- We all have one of those pairs.
- So they just fit you just completely,
just like a glove. - Completely.
The length, perfect. - Just perfect.
- The length is perfect. - Oh my God.
- I got them, you know why?
'Cause I got 'em-- - 24 inseam?
- I got them hemmed up to that, yeah.
- Yeah, that makes sense.
- Yeah, I spent like, I think I spent like $45
getting all my pants fixed so that my tiny-ass legs
would fit them. - I honestly,
don't even try to explain it to me.
I have no idea how hemming works, what that is.
Any part of tailoring, it scares me.
where's it should all you know you have to do stuff go all you have to do is go in with
some cuffed and then just say like can you shrink them to this length
yeah but is he a wizard? that's the same that's like genetic modification you shouldn't be
doing that that's that's all that's gonna be like Jurassic Park your pants are gonna
go crazy on you because they put on pants are going crazy on me because I keep falling
down on my left side and then there's a hole that's the genetic modification so you shouldn't
tailor your pants they'll make you fall down big surprise you're getting fucking owned
yes the outline of my wallet so there's a whole starting in the form of my wallet
and i'm nervous that i'm going to go on the train one night my wallets gonna
fall out my pants
we don't have anything important in your wallet
what are you talking about? you don't have a driver's license
yeah i do. no you don't. i have a license
i have all my debit cards, i have my social security card in here. that's a bad idea
yeah why do you have that in there? what's wrong with you? i have my blood donor card
i have my registered voter in new hampshire card
None of that is important except for the only thing you have in there shouldn't be in there.
Okay, you know what? Then I'll just leave this in the office.
That's actually a better place for it than in your fucking wallet.
Yeah. What else do I have in my wallet?
Especially as a guy, you leave your card at every other bar you go to.
One day you're gonna go to the hospital, they're gonna use your social security.
That's not true anymore. I don't leave my debit card at bars anymore.
You're gonna use your social security card and you're gonna leave it there and then you're gonna call.
I memorized it too, so I don't need it.
Can you put my social security card in an Uber?
You still need it.
029...
It ain't 029. It's 029 because it's Massachusetts. What? Is that how social security numbers
work? I thought it was just a count. Because my mom has the same one. I think they just
count every guy that's born. My mom has 029 also. They just do it in order. My mom's social
security number is 02960112. How does yours start with, it doesn't start with two numbers
not three? No, it's. Look what I found the other day though. Oh sick. I finally found.
I've been paying them some money lately, some free money.
I haven't been to the gym in a minute.
- Yeah. - And I've just been--
- I've been paying them, I've been paying--
- I'm too lazy to cancel it.
- Yeah, it happened to me.
I've been paying them since 2017.
- The thing about that, the Planet Fitness
that's near the train station, that's a bathroom.
- Yeah, that is a serious bathroom.
- So I'm gonna keep paying for that forever,
whether I go or not. - It's a great bathroom.
- 'Cause that's the bathroom that's right next
to the train station that I get off
when I have a longer walk home when I need to pee.
Planet Fitness is a is there's so many of them. It's a great bathroom subscription
because it's cheap. It's like you pay pay $24 a month. You can go to any Planet
Fitness every Friday. Yeah, and you know what I learned because I opened up the
Planet Fitness app. So I've been paying for the black card for I think five
years. That is some celebrity ass bullshit. Yep. I have a celebrity ass life.
God damn that's awesome. I've been paying for the black card. Let me tell you
some of the benefits. Let me tell you some of the benefits I have not been using.
Okay. What's your...
Oh, I get a guest.
For real?
I get a guest.
Can the guests be bathroom guests only?
Yes.
Okay.
So I get a guest and then what else is in here? My account, my membership.
You haven't changed debit cards in five years?
No.
Really?
Wow. Damn. That's pretty cool.
actually yeah I'm actually kind of jealous I change mine see when I leave my
card somewhere I just can't I can bring a guest I get that I get to use the
black card spa no way the fuck this is actually how much is this yeah 25 bucks
a month just only 25 bucks for a black card yeah Wow that's what you're paying
for is the name black card that's a celebrity name yeah yeah I use first
he's got a black card now he's got a damn nice got an arm tattoo yep holy I
got this elbow tattoo. You got a spider web on his fucking elbow. I looked so I was leaving.
It's the toughest thing I've ever seen. Yeah. It's sick, but if you're one of those people
that looks up tattoo meanings, don't look up this one. It means that you actually like
spiders. It means you got bit by a spider. That's really terrifying. Yeah, it was an
accident that I had. That thing is very thin. Yeah. Yeah, that is a thin one. Yeah. Is it
supposed to be thicker? No, I mean you can do whatever you want. It's thin and big. It's
just all very cool in yeah yeah it looks incredible yeah it doesn't hurt until he
got to the elbow I will say elbows for the yeah I mean all the joints it looks
like it's missing something though yeah yeah like what a spider a spider the
animal that he showed me getting a tattoo of a dog house yeah of a dog house
with no dog dog in it what's supposed to mean something Jinx dog without a second
best drinks ever. Yeah, or a zoo without 100 animals in it.
Yeah, zoo without 100 animals.
Oh, I can use the tanning bed at Planet Fitness.
Whoa! They have a tanning bed?
They have a tanning bed. Have you seen Final Destination 3?
Hydro massage.
Hydro massage? Like the one in the mall that I never got to do?
Use a total body enhancement.
I want to enhance my total body.
My body totally.
Use of any Planet Fitness worldwide.
I think Planet Fitness might be
like, you mentioned Final Destination
there's a tanning bed kill in Final Destination, there's weightlifting,
there's a weightlifting death, there's a gymnastics death,
50% off, I think you should stay away from Planet Fitness in general.
50% off all selected drinks. That Final Destination is like,
it's dangerous to be healthy. I think five is the one with the
gymnastics one. Oh yeah, you're right. But yeah, no, in general, it's, I mean, I
guess the message of those movies, he's doing the cable pull downs.
Yeah, yeah, and it fucking yeah, and I that was so sick. Yeah, it's a great
kill, but when I was a kid, I was like why would they design a machine like
that? That's like so stupid to have like two things on hinges that can meet in
the middle and crush your head, but they just made up that machine. It doesn't
exist. Yeah, but why wouldn't you just do it like a that's that's what he
walked into walked into the gym and he saw that like he was like looking at all
the machines are taken. It was like that like just like the death machine. The
the Grim Reaper like sitting next to the family. I just finished using this one.
Yeah, I'm all done. Yeah, just finish my last set. Four of his friends have died.
Let me just wipe it down real quick. Four of his friends have died because a fly
landed on a window. Yeah, and the message of that movie is don't do stuff.
Yeah, it's a great. Well, no, you know what? Actually, I guess it's don't
survive a horrific disaster. Yeah, you should just die. Just die in the first
place. It's way better. It's way better to die on a roller coaster or in a giant
pile up or an airplane or a bridge or a bridge was one of the bridges one of
them. The bridge one's really good or a a race track. If don't never watch or
owns a race track one of them, they're all watch. They're all sitting watching
like NASCAR or something and the the car crashes and like the tire flies up and
and well, I'm a tire yeah. There's a tire. I mean a bunch a bunch of people
die like all the other ones movies. I could with this doctor pepper. I can
earn a free movie ticket for real. You guys should get you guys got to get on
on amca list. I don't think I will. Are you is that another swaggy? What
subscriptions are we all paying for? I pay for let's see I pay for a bunch of
streaming services. I think, but the streaming services are nice because
actually to have to keep subscriptions. Yeah, the streaming services are
perfect, because you split that between you, your girlfriend and your
girlfriend's dad. Yeah, those are yeah, so it's only comes out to a dollar
exactly I pick oh that's yeah that's a big one that one though but that's when I
have to the lady down the downstairs Polish lady I'm subscribed to her yeah
live in her building I'm subscribed to Rupert yeah I'm subscribed to Joanne
Rupert is my subscription nice and I'm so I learned I learned I subscribe to the
grocery store yeah I learned that's great is the slumlord of Bushwick oh
that's actually fucking horrible yeah awesome yeah has he done anything cool as
he like released dogs on you or anything? What does it mean to be a slumlord?
You know what, he did- That just means you're a landlord. Yeah, but that's way too cool of a den.
He did something very cool which was not accept our first month's rent because it
was all separate checks. I mean a slum should be more like in like District 9.
Yeah, you do not live in a slum. I do. Or like a fantasy- I live in the slums. Or like a fantasy like like like a place
with zombies or something. It should be the elephant graveyard from the Lion King.
Yeah, exactly. Slums should be, there should be, it should be mud everywhere.
Yeah. And little kids with, little kids, one has a soccer ball, one has an AK-47.
Elephant bones everywhere. I live in the slums from the shot.
Hyenas running around with the elephant bones, kidnapping lions. Scars. Scars gotta be there
too. Yeah, cartoon. Maybe Timon and Pumbaa for a second in Lion King.
For a second. For a second. Barely a second. Barely, yeah.
the slums from the Sean Kingston song we go to the slums where killers get hung
yep that's where I live why would any girl want to go with you
there Sean Kingston also buddy you're fat you're fat you want to kill yourself
you're 14 years old nobody wants to fuck you Sean Kingston what happened to Sean
Kingston he's still doing his thing yeah he's still doing he says something he
he was one of those guys you do somebody call 9-1-1 yeah yeah that's like fire
burning yeah fire burning he's one of those guys that was able to like start
making tic-tocs or something and then get like a shit oh yeah it's again like
Tai O'Cruz yeah no Jason Derulo Jason Derulo actually does have those moves
though Jason Derulo has a crazy-ass tick-tock account yeah it's always him
he has like an $8,000 cake yeah and he's like I'm gonna eat this it's not how he
sounds at all hey guys Jason Derulo's fall down the steps
you made me laugh
stop it I'm fucking laugh fuck you I love you I'm fucking laughing over here
God yeah you made me making me laugh my damn ass laugh God held God damn it all
that hell God is in hell is in hell cuz I'm laughing God is just in hell for
that if I say that yeah we're all I ever tell you guys about the time that I
thought I was gonna go to hell you mean all the time kid you honestly you are
gonna go one of us three would go to hell would be you yeah yeah cuz I have
tattoos mm-hmm yeah because you have tattoos you've desecrated God's only
gift to you yeah yeah these are these are birthmarks I have a birthmark of a
Japanese are clothes on me yeah I put this on and off every day I can't ever
go to hell because I've that's true I have you have you have a picture of
Jesus and he's yeah he's covered in blood covered in blood because he's
suffering it's yeah beautiful to me um yeah when I was like in the third grade
it was like I was supposed to go on a field trip that I really wanted to go to
and it started raining and then I skip my mom heard me because I saw the rain I
went I hate you God whoa damn yeah you're going to hell for sure that's
fucking you can't say that I you said I cuz I thought God controlled the weather
he does so yeah so I was right to say I used to God used to control the weather
other. Yeah, now I don't want to say who controls. It's yeah, they use harp
technology, cloud busting, first, that may be true, but you also, you, you,
you're, you're mad at God because you questioned his, his completely perfect
judgement and, and plan for your day. Yeah, you realise they're gonna die on
that field trip. Like he, the, everything that he does, he does for a reason. I
think, I think we are going to the Autobahn Society. We are going on a field
trip to the Satanist Church. Yeah you guys were yeah you were going to a rock concert.
You were going to go see Kiss and God stopped you. Yeah.
Because the Autobahn was sick. He saw there was a demon in that band. Which I it's not for there's no
reason why he's a demon other than his makeup. You know his tongue. Why are you
insinuating? I just want to get ahead of everybody saying calling me an anti-Semite.
what nobody was even thinking that yeah it's a demon who's Heim Witz
Gene Simmons Dean Simmons real name is Heim with his name is Chaim wits that's
fucking awesome yeah sure they should have gone by that name that's a lower
name than Gene Simmons yeah cooler we're gonna like be a debt like a demon big
tongue I'm having deja vu right now I think we've talked about all of this
before we've definitely talked about kiss yeah yeah we talked about how it's
that's so funny that they've just become businessmen.
- I always thought that Kiss,
you think that with a name like Kiss,
they would actually have big lips.
- Yeah.
- But they should have been called Lick.
- Lick, yeah.
- 'Cause they have big tongues.
- Lick or Face Paint.
- Yeah, exactly.
- The Rock and Roll Face Paint Team.
- All the bands should be just rock and roll.
I heard that they struck a big at the Olympics this year,
the Rock and Roll Face Paint Team.
- The Rock and Roll Face Paint Team.
- The American Rock and Roll Face Paint Team.
- America, listen, America's not getting beaten
for rock and roll and face pain. No yeah, okay, Japan might have I mean I don't
know Japan, totally has it over us in face paint. It's rock and roll face
paint. First of all, it has rock and roll. Japan has obviously I'm just
correcting faces face pain is a separate. It's a separate event has
better rock abilities than the USA. They do have a you seen Scott pilgrim
versus the world. No, it's a Japanese move. I did see that actually about
rock. I forgot actually look at it as it's a rock and roll move. It's more
about punk rock more about it having a it's more about having a girlfriend.
actually fucking so true yeah yeah guys that movie is about having a girlfriend
listen real for real punks that movies about the music there's a lot of
rockin movies that are really important sensitive guys like us it's four million
days of summer the Nick and Nora's infinite playlist and Scott Pilgrim
versus the yeah yeah and there's a direct through line in all of those
those are probably my three fan Freddy Krueger's Revenge yeah yeah Freddy
Kruger's revenge. Joe fell down. Joe just fell. Joe! Joe are you okay? You okay? Yeah I didn't fall down.
He just said yeah I fell down. Yeah I just fell down and broke everything. Yeah I just flipped on. Oh remember hey guys what was he
eating when we walked in? Oh my god he was eating a banana peel. He had a fucking banana peel. He just fell on a banana.
He doesn't want to admit that he fell on a banana peel. I'm so mad that I closed the curtains.
We could have seen every second of it. We could have seen the funniest fucking thing of all time. Yeah.
They need to do that's us three when we get picked up by SNL in August.
Oh yeah.
Banana peel.
We're doing the banana peel boys.
We're pitching banana peel.
We're pitching cheese crew.
Cheese crew.
Oh my god.
The crew.
SNL if you're listening.
I don't know if we can tip cheese crew yet.
You don't think so?
I'm not sure.
What if we say it in secret?
Okay so cheese crew is when three guys love cheese so much that they eat it as much as
possible.
At a wedding.
or any of it and you say you see you see everyone gather okay we can stop being
secret now you see everyone gathered around the cheese table the cheese table
at the wedding you walk up and you're like hey guys I don't want to scare
anybody but you guys need to clear the fuck out because I heard the cheese
crew is at the wedding and they're coming through soon and you do not want to be
here when they get to the cheese table if you are is there any more is there
any more you're between the cheese crew and the cheese you're gonna be caught
your redness under here did somebody eat all the Gouda yep this isn't good this
is a good someone ate all the good oh my god guys I think they're getting closer I
think the cheese crew is getting actually very close I think the cheese
probably shit they're right behind me aren't they oh my god and what's in the
out of the way yep and then they yeah
there's us there it's the little mouse and they were oh yeah they were hats
look look like cheese they were cheese head cheese head hats yeah and the way
staff knows about the cheese crew and they fuck yeah oh they do not like the
cheese fucking cheese screws coming I need a cigarette but the cheese through
their identities are secret - they wear sunglasses so you can't tell who they
are yeah and then you they'll like and then maybe other people around the
wedding will be like I heard the cheese crews here and then one of them's like
yeah I don't know if they're here or not it's very mysterious but yeah they have
maybe a cheese hat hidden behind their back and their belly their belly's big
and smells like cheese mm-hmm do you guys ever feel like sometimes minimum
wage workers are just all they do is smoke smoke cigarettes and go to the
bathroom. Yeah, their attitude is foul. That's what I did when I worked minimum
wage. Yeah, but then you become a real man, a real job. The only thing more
foul than a minimum wage workers attitude is their breath from all those
that is actually dark. Yeah, that they blast yeah, stop blasting those darts
not blasting darts. I'll be fucking bad for you. Yeah, you realize that you need
to be working the whole time. You can't take a five minute break every hour. Do
you not fucking realize those sticks are completely cancerous? I'm not yeah.
First of all, we're not paying you to kill yourself with cigarettes.
Paying you to kill yourself at my whim.
Yeah, exactly.
I'm waiting for you to jump off of my building through psychological torture.
Yeah, you should be breaking your back.
I'm paying you to run as fast as you can in the forest and then I try to catch you.
I'm not paying for you to smoke.
Exactly.
You know what you should be doing is you should be obeying my order when I order a filet-o-fish
and then I hand it back to you and say, "Can you freshen this up?"
You should know what that means and you should do it.
And here's a hack.
If you go to McDonald's and say, "Can I have that fish filet made fresh?"
They have to do it.
Yeah.
Can you freshen this up?
Yep.
You order it first and then they fresh it.
Yeah, they freshen it after.
They put it in the fresher.
They get a new one out of the freezer.
You could order it and you get it and it's fresh.
That's too easy.
You have to order it.
You have to see it.
Also, you pay extra for a fresh one.
That's why you wait until they give it to you to ask.
Not enough people order the filet of fish so they sit under the heat lamp all day.
That's true.
That's an actual true fact.
Is that true?
The fresh ones though.
I'm checking on crack right now.
The fresh ones sit under a cold lamp, which is how they keep fresh,
because it's like the ocean.
What is?
The fresh fish, the fresh Filet-O-Fish they keep in a separate room and
they're under a cold lamp.
It's a, yeah.
Oh.
It's like it simulates the ocean water.
It's a big metal room.
To keep it as cold as possible.
Yeah.
Because the ocean is really cold.
It's a room filled with salt water.
That's actually good.
That preserves stuff.
And you say, can you freshen this up?
And they dip it in.
Do you guys, I don't understand why we have so much technology,
kinds of phones every kind of brand of phone right why different colors
iPhone and a thousand different colors that's a different conversation for a
different day but I am with you you can have 80 different cars yeah right
different colors of different colors of cars every different kind of car can
have up to four colors many colors even more than four you can have a house
built in a day painted any color okay you can have a television that has its
three shows any color on the screen nowadays they could have built room in
one day there they easily could have been 3d printed. I would have been read you
can 3d print something the they have you can actually buy items on fortnight
cosmetic items. You have all this technology yeah, but we can't turn
fucking ocean water into fresh water.
And how am I supposed to believe that well, it's all you can do all you have
to do everything out because they because they because they have you just
boil it. No, you can you you drink the ocean water and then you pee it out and
then they use the pita water thing that's smart yeah you're smartest fuck Cameron
that's actually really I mean that's how they have a pita water machine we just
drink ocean water why what is it done it what but what about the salt is gonna
fish make it salty because they don't want in that they don't fish shit salt
bitch shit and piss all fish shit water and fish salt do fish piss in prehistoric
times before humans fish would would would swim up to the shore and they would
to poop on to out of the water because I didn't want to contaminate their walk
and that's how they were smarter back then they will know so but then humans
came around humans love drinking water. Okay, the fish saw that happen. They go
oh man the humans are going to drink this whole ocean. If we don't do
something about it, we just better start pooping and shitting in here and
salting it that was smart of them. It was fresh back then and then they salted
it. Yeah, because if somebody if some fucking shark started sipping my house,
yeah, I'd probably shit on it. I'd shit in my house. So he didn't want to sip it.
- If somebody tried to eat my bed,
I'd take a shit in it, basically.
- That is a pretty easy way to deter anybody
from taking something.
- If someone tried to touch my pants,
I'll take a shit.
- Yeah.
- Right in my pants.
- I mean, if somebody's trying to mug you,
if you shit on your wallet,
- Yeah.
- They're not gonna take it.
- That's why I keep a piece of crap in my wallet.
- Yeah.
- And I reach into my pants like it's a gun
to pull the crap out whenever somebody's testing me.
- Testing me, yeah.
- I get tested every day on these streets.
- Yeah.
- I like being tested 'cause I always pass
with flying colors. I hate being tested because I got a learning disability.
That's really bad.
Yesterday I was walking to go get some lunch and this guy started peeing on the
street
uh... into onto a building and it really made me laugh because his friend
started walking away
and he like knocked on people's cars and was going like
"Oh no, oh no,
ladies and gentlemen of Ridgewood,
there is a black man with his penis out right there!"
And he's like trying to get people to look at his friend's penis.
Made me laugh.
That's funny.
And I caught a little bit of a sneak peek.
Wow.
I walked up with a magnifying glass.
I said, "Hello!"
I said, "Hi, you're giving me a micro wood?"
My wood is...
But no, do you know what I mean about the micro wood?
So, whoa, you scratch your mustache under the mic.
That's the loudest thing I've ever heard.
Holy shit.
Oh, that's a horrible noise.
Why does it...
I love how many people pee on the street in New York.
I do.
It's a free show every day.
I love walking.
It's very funny to me.
People will pee on cars and stuff.
It's sick.
Oh yeah, that's my mood.
If I'm drunk and I need to pee, I'll pee into somebody's wheel well.
Yeah, that's what I see people doing sometimes on the street.
Because nobody's even going to notice.
If I have to, like if I'm walking down the street, like say I'm walking in like, I don't
know, you know that spot?
Pat got mad at me one time for peeing on a Ferrari.
Do you remember that?
No.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
inside so i can i go beyond going to be a little time
well done
i am ready to go for the it's not
we're not going to go to
we're not going to go to a whole week recommended water all you figure out the
real
uh... you know what
usually if one patrick is only looking at his phone
that's the best not i think that
all wait wait i got one ticket ticket but i would like it before he'll get
back as he disabandoned the podcast well we already got the photo you're at it
you're not in the photo that's right that's what you deserve this is some
fucking bullshit no what you did was fucking bullshit we're just gonna water
we're talking about water and it made me thirsty yeah you could have got water
while we were having a conversation about
post in 43 seconds I was I would you know it's not retaking it because that's not
real I didn't know I was craving water and then I got really thirsty. You have to be
real on it you get one or two retakes. That's fucking stupid. And it tells everybody that if you do a retake.
You don't have to be the name of the thing. Yes you do. Uh-uh. Oh wait so I need to be I need.
Look Clark is walking. Who the fuck is this? That's Clark. Who's Clark? Oh that
Clark. Mm-hmm Clark is walking. Wow. Clark's my only friend who's posted one yet.
It's cool everybody should get on be real. Yeah it sounds like a cool app. It's
probably going to be the next Instagram or Snapchat. I think it is. Yeah, it's a
very important for for us as as 23, 24, and 25 year old guys to get on the next
Snapchat. Yeah. That's the big thing that Pat should be focusing on. It's not.
I agree. The next Snapchat app. Thank you for including me in your kind of young crew.
Yeah, you're welcome. Yep. You're not 25 yet? Nope. Oh my god, I hate my fucking life.
Yep. Imagine getting your first arm tattoo at 24 years old. I didn't. I got my first at 23.
couldn't be me is that also can I think you know that you were not you were
still 24 then yeah you're right I was 24 yeah yeah yeah it's true found that's
right destroyed yeah you got fucking owned yeah I got mine when I was 8 you
didn't I get it I was 8 years old I could see a bird outside that out there
I was I did fall asleep this morning with the ointment on and I have white
sheets right now yeah he'll find it so yeah I know I just don't worry about
I fell asleep with the ointment on night. I got up and there was a little I saw a web imprint
Yeah, you got to sleep with with long-sleeve shirts when you got when I took a picture
Jesus his face was completely on my sheet
Yeah, you have to have it you have to have it you have to cover it up when you sleep cuz it's gonna ooze
Just go stay around wrap on it. Yeah. Yeah, okay. I would just put on a long-sleeve
She's just a hard I didn't want anymore or something. I'm a saran wrap man
This is the hardest thing cuz every time it's more likely to I'm like gonna thrash around and knock that off on my sleep
I actually just started sleeping super super well because I got myself a sleep mask and and now I should get one of those
I've I've been on that tip dude fucking unreal you you got that you heard that for me about a $12 sleeping mask from Amazon
I got the one
It's got like it's it's like a cushion. All right, I guess you you went up you upgraded
I got that first-class fucking sleeping man. You know, you're on your first class. Whoa. No, it's not first class on JetBlue
I'm in that first, I'm in that business class.
- It's not business.
- I'm in that blue sky.
- It's JetBlue Mint.
- I'm in the mints feeling room.
- JetBlue Mint.
- Yeah, don't know why it's called mint.
- That's weird.
- Yeah.
- I just had to put that.
- What's normal, vanilla?
- No, it's blue, blue basic.
- Vanilla?
- Blue basic, you don't get to choose your seat.
- Yeah, and is there a chocolate one too?
- Blue vanilla.
- And maybe a strawberry one?
- No, blue.
- Because vanilla means normal.
- What?
- No, it's basic, blue basic.
- Oh, vanilla means normal?
It's blue basic.
You would say that.
Blue business class mint.
And chocolate.
No.
Yep.
What's the chocolate class?
You're being so stupid about JetBlue right now.
Chocolate is sprinkled in.
You're being stupid as fuck about JetBlue.
No I'm not.
Yes you are.
No.
Look at this.
We're planning a new airline called Ice Cream Air.
Yep, and everything is different.
Okay, well now that I know that this is Ice Cream Air.
The seats are called cones.
Yep.
Holy shit.
global well actually luggage goes in the sprinkle compartment
he up to the pilots are all the way to the hotel but i would have called the
candyman yet
and and and they come down to come down the aisle they come down to come down
the aisle and they're like
uh... sir do you want hot fudge or butterscotch and that means copier water
yes
or it's not hot but they're getting it still copy what's late or early
I'll be your candy man today.
My name is Jason.
Oh god we're melting!
We're melting!
It's 90 degrees outside.
Oh my god my arm is melting.
Everybody be quiet if we talk on the plane it's going to get too hot in here and the
plane will melt.
The temperature in the cabin has kept at a cool 15 degrees.
If you're wearing a coat please take the coat off it's going to make the plane too warm.
in the case of cabin depressurization spoons will drop from and please finish
eating your seat before eating the seat of the person next to you please finish
your own ice cream before you move on to eating somebody else's what plane were
we on oh we're coming home from Chicago private yeah private jet private jet
yeah private jet but the plane looking hated our pilot on our private jet yeah
He was so he kept likes being like hey you guys
You won't play chess say chess is honestly for idiots chess is for stupid people. I'd rather be a queen's gambit
Hey guys, you can't rap back there. We said distracting me. Sorry is there a no cipher rule is that?
Can you bring a bomb on your own plane yeah
They're not gonna screen you yeah
Cuz if you couldn't bring a bomb on your own plane then the entire Air Force would they would have to shut it down
it's true they were bombs on their plans over that flight and it was stuck like
it was stuck in the air completely still no ground the tarmac is stuck on the
tarmac for three hours right it was like something like that two hours yeah two
hours and then like they're waiting on wind say yeah some fucking dumbass
bullshit that doesn't exist yep wind and they were like they were like oh here's
a free cup of water yeah to quail free completely free cup of water and
Honestly, it made everything worth it.
And we got Biscoff cookies.
Oh yeah.
And I was hungry as a mother fucker right now.
I was not hungry, but I did drink Hennessy at the airport before we went.
You did.
Yeah.
You were in a really bad mood and then you had a Hennessy and then you were in a great mood the
rest of the time.
Yep.
It really puts you in the zone.
Yeah.
I wasn't in that bad of a mood.
That was maybe the--
You were cranky.
The best--
Yeah, I was tired.
That was the best airport food.
He was really, really cranky.
He was really cranky.
It was the most--
- No, I was cranky in LA.
- You were cranky twice on that entire trip.
- You were insanely cranky at that airport.
I'm sorry, I have to side with Caleb here.
- You were cranky at Chili's,
and you ordered Hennessey, and it fixed you.
- Yeah, it did.
- It's a magic potion, dude.
Hennessey's amazing.
- Which airport was it when we got those sandwiches?
That was the best airport meal I've ever had.
- What sandwiches?
- Oh, that was LAX.
- Was that LAX?
- Yeah.
- Was that place called Lemonade?
- I was like, oh, this place is gonna suck.
- No, it was so good.
- It was so good.
- That miso short rib.
- It was insane.
- Yeah.
- No, that was the airport I was cranky at
because I lost my--
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah, I lost my bag. - That was the cranky one.
- No.
- He was cranky at Chili's?
- I don't remember if he was cranky at Chili's.
- I was not cranky at Chili's.
- He was, I tried to buy him a soda,
he got so mad that the soda machine wouldn't take his card.
And I tried to buy him one.
- Oh.
- And he's like, "No, I don't even want it."
- It's 'cause I didn't have caffeine yet.
- Cranky?
- Yeah, I think I might've been cranky.
I was trying to buy a Rockstar Zero.
He was cranky.
I didn't get cranky even one time.
I will fess up to that.
I was completely fine.
I was cranky.
I was happy and smiley the whole time.
I have a cranky radar.
In LA I was upset because I lost my camera bag.
Oh yeah.
I had all my camera stuff.
I remember that.
Yeah.
That was a bummer.
But I was happy because I was spending time with my friends and the blessing of traveling
the country.
Yeah.
But somebody sent it to me and I thanked them.
was cranky they didn't touch him in TSA. No, no I was annoyed because that hand
wrap. You guys yeah I had the hand wrap on yeah I did get cranky because they they
have to check if you wrap your hand up like I had a I got a hand injury and if
you have your hand wrapped up TSA has to check it because I could have snuck a
bomb in. It could have been a bomb wrap. You could have had a you could have had a
demon hand. I took the wrap off and then like. No wrap allowed. I took the wrap off.
- You could have had under the,
well yeah, what they're expecting is you take the wrap off
and like, you know. - There's a little bomb.
- Well it's like, no, it's like Hellboy's hand.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. - And it's like,
oh you can't take that on the plane.
- Yeah. - You can't be on the plane
if you're half demon.
- Or they recognize your hand, they say,
"Sir, I've seen those hands before,
"those are registered as deadly weapons."
- Dude, what they do-- - You cannot bring those
on a plane. - What they do when that happens
is like, 'cause you have the hand wrap on,
they take like a little like,
I don't even know what it is,
it's like a little piece of paper
and they touch like different parts of your hand
and look at you and go like, what did you do?
- They just make it all up.
- Yeah, no, it's a fucking performance.
- They're doing chiropractic to everybody.
- It's a victory lap that they got the TSA created
so that we can all become sheep and go into the little--
- Oh my God, political Patrick, I'm loving it.
- I'm being divisive as hell.
- So cool.
- It's for people who are too stupid to work McDonald's.
And they're like, no, we have a job for you.
Like, no, all you have to do,
you just have to touch their in with piece of paper and ask what did you do
it's that was it you don't remember any orders. Okay, you don't remember the
size of the fries or anything like that. Do you such it was such bullshit? I
like took the wrap off and I was like I think I was like all right then put it
in the machine. I was like okay like what you had a bad attitude with the
TSAP. Yeah, it's because I've been so used to pre check for so many years you
get what you give with those people. Yeah, so I show up. I put an apple on
their desk okay yeah I'm always polite and kind to them but they are always so
mean to me yeah they hate you that's why that's why I'm a dick to them because
they know if you're doing it like this back though if you it's like prison you
show up and you say fuck you to have the biggest in me that is not how it works
at all yeah I've been to prison you have been a
prank tell because of your your muscle my crazy tattoo tattoo means you have a
prison boyfriend yeah yeah that's what my mom said mm-hmm every tattoo I've
ever got my mom has said that means you had a boyfriend in prison dumbass you
need to look up what dr. evil I looked up dr. evil tattoo meaning mm-hmm what it
after I looked up this one and yeah saw that meant something about prison yeah I
looked up this one and there was a tattoo artist in England named dr. evil
who was arrested for cutting off somebody's
that's just a body mod the guy guy dr. evil yeah it's like a body mod thing
like he had like the split tongue and everything and like the guy Dr. Evil
looks like teen Dr. Evil. Whoa. It was so funny. Do I look like teen Dr. Evil to you?
No. Mean it? Yep. That's so awesome. Yeah you're older than teen. You look kind of like I
mean you're diluted. Yeah. Why? Because I'm old? Yeah because you're old. I'm literally
so young in spirit though. Yeah you're a young soul. I just learned how to fucking read.
Dr. Evil has been jailed for carrying out ear and nipple removals and splitting a customer's
tongue.
Dr. Evil's in jail?
Hey, that's good news for me.
Dr. Evil has been jailed for carrying out ear and nipple removals.
Can I see a picture?
Do I have a picture?
Yeah, I need to see what he looks like.
That's Dr. Evil?
Brendan McCarthy?
Dr. Evil has been jailed for nipple removals.
Dr. Evil has been jailed for nipple removal.
That's a good find.
That is a really good find.
I'm surprised that made it to today without you posting it somewhere or texting us about it.
Jail tattoo artist Dr. Evil refused to remove my toe says customer.
He refused?
He has morals.
it did shit way those tattooed person in the UK has spoken out in defense of dr.
evil after he was jailed Birmingham native king of ink land King body art the
extreme ink I says McCarthy has refused to carry out several procedures including
the removal of a finger and a toe holy shit what that's the guy oh my god I love
that when people when people get completely covered in tattoos or the
entire body covered black and then they just put and then they just add they're
you're like i'm going to make my eyes pitch black to yeah. Have you seen have
you seen the real life alien project? Oh yeah, yeah, hold on. I have that guy
that guy he looks. There's that one guy guess what he what he does based on
real life. I'm really an object yeah. Oh yeah, there was that one guy who was
like he was like a professor somewhere and he had a full full body type.
Always lack. Well, those are all equations true. That's yeah. I could
been yeah or history lessons yeah lessons probably the curriculum project whoa he
seriously looks like a black alien it's his penis I guess oh his penis no that's
his that was his back he's a peanut he has a tail on the back maybe oh his nose
is gone yeah he got his nose oh he's got a hole in his lip yeah oh god he's got
the split tongue yeah oh and he got three he got two of his fingers removed
imagine these are kind of people are listening to Beach Boys and the Beatles
and all that fucking rock nonsense oh my god imagine on May 10th he said the
black alien project is only 43% complete damn that's scary as fuck
Imagine that's your dad.
Project Evolution.
I don't think he can come.
44% as of May 24th.
He can come more than a normal person.
Probably both of his balls are split 8 times.
No, he has 4 balls, yeah.
But they work.
It's more come.
No, it's less come.
Imagine that's your dad and you have a friend over for a freaking play date.
And he scares them.
And he scares them, yeah.
Wait, what is he doing here?
What is he going to do with himself?
I want to see what happens when he gets to 100.
I need to see 100%.
I do not want to see 100% on I'm scared. You're scared of this. I
think 100% might be able to kill you through the screen. I think you might
get telekinesis for the most part until the last maybe three years people with
face tattoos were mostly bad people. Yeah, yeah, I think if you I've known
quite a few people. I think I think it was all not so good. Yeah, I think it's
still I think it's probably people with face tattoos are still bad people, but
now they're bad people and that they're very annoying. Definitely. It's
yeah yeah the caption of this picture of the black alias he's doing like a Rob
Dyrdek outfit it just says fucking idiot there's that guy that guy tooth taker
who has that I kept the the bouncer at a bar kept thinking I was him and kept
like trying to keep me from going in and I'd be like I'm not that guy he has a
he has a tattoo on his forehead this is I'm going to kill you this tooth taker
tooth takers are the rapist guy yeah yeah but he doesn't just like sexually assault
women he just like there's like once a week he'll just like stab somebody or
like kick someone's teeth out and he just never goes to jail he just like
that's insane goes to a different state and why did somebody cause I'm bald
that's the entire it was like the last time a bald guy walked into the bar was
this guy is this like I remember that I remember now every time I go back to
to that bar, the guy is like, "Hey, I thought that you were that evil rapist."
And I go, "Yep, yeah, you did.
Yep.
Not so awesome."
That sucks. That sucks to have a rapport with a bouncer like that. Yeah. Holy
shit. And then he told... And then last time I was there, he... Last time I
I was there. He's like a he's like a fingerless gloves like nerd dude. Last
time I was I think I know yeah, okay, yeah, I was there. He said that I looked
like he was like I don't know why I thought he looked like tooth ticker. You
look more like the lead the lead orc from Lord of the Rings.
I was like what the fuck why you just the lead or say I look like either the
most evil rapists of all time or
he knew the guy's name. I was a goth mug probably. Well, if it's from if it's
Peter Jackson movies goth mug as an orc when the books either he's a Balrog well
they totally just said Balrog Grishnok I dude I don't you're just saying nothing
Caleb Gore are these how about you're saying you know you know you know I think
I know exactly who it is and he has looked at multiple shirts of mine and
just gone what band is that yeah you know you know you know man
Varg the black metal guy yeah yeah, so you know his his like original like
stage name or whatever was count Grishnak, which is named after an orc
from Lord of the Rings. It really yeah is named after an orc from Lord of the
Rings Grishnak and I was like rereading Lord of the Rings a year or two ago and
like I got to the part with Grishnak and Grishnak. All the only thing that
Grishnak does in the book is he shows up and like kidnap some of the hobbits
and then he gets run over by a horse like two pages later. That's all that
that's the end of yeah and he's like damn that's sick as fuck. I'm gonna be evil
like this guy. Dude it's so fucking funny like the like Varg's whole like
trajectory and just believing Lord of the Rings. That's what's funny. Well you
could yeah it's also because he started out being like I want to be the evil
orc and then later he matured and he's like actually I'm a wizard. Yeah, yeah,
I'm not an orc anymore. I'm more like he's jumping around. Yeah, I it's funny
that I feel like I've known I've seen Varg get old because like I thought he
funny when I was 14. Yeah. And now he's just. He's a prime guy to think is really
funny when you're 14. Yeah exactly. Oh yeah dude. Like I mean it's fucking like
hearing like Dunkelheit or whatever and being like. I've literally never heard
one of his songs. Oh really? Yeah never. Dunkelheit's a sick song. You're basically
the biggest racist in the entire universe. Yeah he's got good music. He does have
good music. I was listening to fucking MC front a lot okay. Yeah. Yeah MC Chris.
to Jake Novak. And Aesop Rock. Okay. Yeah. I mean they have. Aesop Rock and Jon Bernal.
Real rap. That's like the same level as Varg's stuff. Whereas Varg is writing about Lord
of the Rings and they're doing stuff about Star Wars. Yeah. It's the exact same thing.
Exactly. Have you guys ever seen the video of Aesop Rock meeting Aesop Rocky? No. And
Aesop Rocky clearly has no idea who Aesop Rock is and he's like with him and he's like
I'm with the first ASAP Rocky and he's like okay it's so awesome
damn that's tight linked up they linked up and never seen that I never that's
like imagine there was a guy named yeah it would be a track Patek do Dan and he's
a podcaster who's not as successful as you are or actually more successful and
you're saying ASAP ASAP rock is more success is less successful okay then ASAP
Rocky well he's successful in the underground he's successful and what
he's actually you know okay he's more successful with getting a message I
agree he's intellectually and message misogycally more successful okay and
he's got a philosophical tent tent bent it's a tent it's a bent it's a tent a
bent it's a philosophical neurological miracle who's okay you would actually be
a sub rock yeah mm-hmm yeah that guy's a fucking beast man ace up rock yeah a
I saw Brock as sick. I only know his music from the Tony Hawk games. There's a toad and a
road with a frog and a boat. I saw a frog. Now you're doing a different guy. That's not
how he sounds. That's Vinny Paz. Yeah. That's my impression of one of my uncles. I saw Brock
kind of sound a deaf, which is like, and also deaf like D E F as well. Yeah. Very successful.
He rhymes successful with successful on that song. Yeah. He's a man. He's great. I straight
up the only songs I know are no jumper cables and the one he did with the
Mountain Goats guy that the album he did with tobaccos it's pretty no jumper we
should go on no jumper yeah I think we should I've been thinking of that do you
think we could we could I think if if you got a face tattoo and like I think
we could probably convince Adam 22 that you're like some up-and-coming like
rapper you actually think I have skill like that you're getting out of a double
cup right now. That is true. Yeah. Yeah. I think that that would I think that
would work. Yeah. And I think that may be a jumper bro. We can do it. Damn. I
don't think he wants anyone to talk about that. Okay. The first thing that
comes up when you Google his name, dude. That's true. You can do. I will do it
too. I need to do no jumper. I'm literally gonna do it right now, dude.
Okay, I'm ready to do it. I'm gonna do it right now. I want that. I'm gonna
Google how to do that jumper no jumper is like one of those podcasts where he
just sits there and just goes like yeah uh-huh yeah yeah yeah no interview the
only interviews rappers or porn stars and the rappers he's like he's like so
did you ever kill anybody and then the porn stars he's like so what's the most
amount of guys you fucked in a day that's every single fucking interview
damn oh you can promote your music through no jump holy shit let's do it oh
dude we got your music played and reviewed live on air what the hell how
How much does this cost let's see here live stream play plus review how much
see oh wait a hundred and twenty dollars. Oh dude we're sending it. I can't tell
it says it's no it just links to the donation page. I don't know how much we
need. Yeah no it's a hundred a hundred and twenty dollars for live stream play
plus review two hundred forty dollars for live stream play plus review plus
SoundCloud 175 for advanced play and review $1,500 for social media feature I
think we should just full send it on the social media feature with a new sensor
song will be featured on the no jumper Instagram and Twitter and a sponsored
post your post will include a short bio and a link back to your at account what
if we do that that will pay back in dividends yeah yeah yeah for the theme
theme song yeah yeah damn that be genius idea. What's it everyone seen that guy's
penis in clip, a 22 well he did he does he makes porn with his porn star wife
oh and he just yeah, okay,
can we actually pay a hundred and twenty dollars for him to review the theme song
yeah, let's do it yeah yeah.
That's not that much money. I expected yeah, that song was only like
30 seconds what the fuck?
It's literally I think 12 seconds long.
What the hell dude?
We need to include the "let me see your butt" thing in the beginning as well.
Yeah, that's the producer tag.
I think maybe
we
I don't know.
I think there's a couple songs that we've done on here that I think we should
turn into real songs.
Eight Legged Bug.
There's been a million probably but
Eight Legged Bug definitely.
I think we really need to get into the studio with somebody
- Like, "Eight Legged Bug" or this song.
- Yeah, if anyone can get us some studio time.
- Song I've been writing,
"Don't Text Me While I'm Skeetin'".
- I love my birthday.
- Don't text me.
- Oh, I love my birthday.
- Yo, motherfucker, yo.
Okay, let's get the track list, so.
- This is an EP that we're putting out.
- Yeah, EP, "Eight Legged Bug".
- Yep.
- "Don't Text Me While I'm Skeetin'".
- I haven't heard that.
Can you give us a demo?
- That one's like, "Don't text me while I'm skeetin'.
"I'm jackin' off 'cause it's my weekend."
- Whoa, okay.
♪ You text me one more time I'm off the deep end ♪
- Dude, this is actually so good.
♪ Don't text me when I'm skeetin' ♪
- You've been writing this.
This is clear, this is not off the dome.
- I'm crying right now.
- Holy shit.
- I'm so amazed by my music.
♪ Don't text me while I'm skeetin' ♪
♪ You know I'm jackin' off 'cause it's my weekend ♪
- It's my weekend.
- In the song, and it says my weekend
because he works Tuesday to Wednesday.
Tuesday to Thursday is every week.
So his weekend--
- So he's specifying that he has a three day weekend.
- He has a--
- Or a four day weekend.
like he has like, like, you know, like when somebody's like, oh yeah, this is my
Friday. Why wouldn't you just say the weekend? Why are you saying, why you have
to invent this whole... Because there's parts in the song where he's talking about, I'm, oh I'm off
again on a Friday. Yeah. I'm gonna skeet it, have it my way. That kind of thing. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
I'm off again on a Monday, gonna skeet, it's gonna be a fun day. That type of thing.
Yeah, my boss is making me work Thursday, unfortunately this is her day. Mm-hmm.
Yep, because I can't ski. I can't ski. Yeah. Yeah. He is. I can't work. I can't. No, no,
he works like Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday. That's it. No, no, he works three days on
four days off three. Yeah. Oh, okay. So he's like on call all the time. Yeah. So he has
no time to ski. He has no time to ski. He is no fucking time. Maybe. Yeah, maybe he's
like I have I have vacation from work for Chris Merr. Yeah. And I will be skeeting all
winter. Mm hmm. He said he has he has four days off. He works. He works and he turns his
- He's got his phone off.
- He doesn't work at Burlington Coat Factory,
but on his weekend he goes there a lot.
- Yeah, of course.
But he's like, "Don't text me."
- Don't text me 'cause I'm skeeting.
- 'Cause I'm skeeting, 'cause it's my weekend
and I work three days so hard.
I'm working 18 hour shifts.
- Yeah.
- And like, that's it.
- Well, he gets 40 hours in, but it's only within three days.
- Yeah, that's fucking crazy.
I'm a good kudos to him.
I couldn't do that.
- He works at Home Depot and the airport.
- He's working 14 hour shifts and getting--
Home Depot in the airport.
And the airport.
But it's the Home Depot that's in the airport.
It's for people who want to buy like tools or 2x4s.
He's working 14 hour shifts at Home Depot?
In the airport.
He's a pilot and Home Depot in the airport.
Okay.
He's got no time to ski.
Well, because they have timed bathroom breaks.
Yeah.
So he can't go ski in the bathroom.
No.
Because he takes them, honestly, he takes them.
They have seat detectors.
The saddest part of the song is he's single.
Really well, so why doesn't he answer when people are texting him then cuz like
maybe one of these friends well, it's like a sad. It's one of those songs
where it's one of those songs where it's like
Where it's like this the music shows a rainbow the lyrics a depressed skull yep
And it could be maybe a two-part song like the art of storytelling one and two
And the second part could be about how he starts doing nofap
It's my weekend the second one could be like a whole nofap song don't
We've been needing a nofap anthem for quite some yeah, yeah, well, I think of R&B single about jacking off
I think that we could like singing it like I think we can make a making love but it's only
Yeah, yeah, and then I put that body on me I love my son on me
I love myself too much to jack off. It could be like one of the parts of it. It's about self-love
Put your I think that's something that the no jumper guys would really like
Especially with that man who works in sex work an entire skeeting song
Yeah, yeah, cuz then that song cuz then we could put a plug in there. They're saying like oh, I'm watching an Adam 22
Fucking his wife is skating different from coming or is it like skeeting is coming and come
Skeeting is come, but it kind of sounds like it's like shooting out
out so like fat you're shooting out he's shooting out so much eating as it's like
shooting out so much yeah it's a cone setting on a hose yeah yeah it's his
weekend he has no other time to ski yeah I wish that my come worked like expanding
foam yeah yeah that'll be pretty sick I wish mine was like super glue yeah I
wish I could never eat again yeah I wish mine never came off yeah she was just
he's there just there ever yeah yeah. I just get my hand stuck to my dig damn
yeah, because that's what I do. I try to try to stop you. I be walking around
looking like the Michelin man, God damn every inch of my body for real yeah,
and it'd be my skeet on you.
That is what would happen if I had
oh my God, you'd be covered in my you know that you know this the ceiling in
the in the music classroom in elementary school. That's forget dude. I'll be
looking like that walking around. I got skied all over me. I look like I was
swimming in a pool filled with spider webs.
You know? Yeah, you're looking like a white cotton candy man. Oh my God, I
look like a Caesar salad pizza. Oh my God. Caesar salad pizza.
I got the dressing and the croutons. We're ending now. I don't like where this is headed.
Before he says another one. Buy tickets to our shows in Seattle and Portland.
What is it, the 18th and 19th? 18th and 19th of August.
Am I right about that? 18th and 19th of August is Portland and Seattle
in that order. Early show and late show.
Yep. And by the time we get to the P&W that comes, gonna have been on me for so long,
I look like a chocolate lava cake. Turn it off. Turn this thing off right now.
(laughing)