You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[laughter]
Speaking of, you wanna hear my favorite Norm Macdonald joke ever?
Yeah, let's hear it.
The other day I was gonna get me a cup of coffee, right?
Uh, but then I took an arrow to the knee.
[laughter]
Yeah, that's a good one.
- Whatever happened to him?
- Yeah, I mean, he used to be putting out heaters
all the time.
You know what, you remember that joke he did
when he was like, "Sat down next to the girl in class,
"she moved to another desk."
And he held up a picture of a penguin?
- Yes.
- That one was so good.
- I remember that, yeah.
I remember, "Your mom's so fat,
"she goes out onto the beach
"and all the whales, they crawl up onto shore
"and say, 'We are family,
even though you're fatter than me. Remember that?
Yeah, he, oh my god.
He was put, what hap, I mean like, it feels like he was so funny until like four days ago.
What happened?
I know, I don't know, yeah. And yeah, I mean, what, now all his jokes are like this.
Yeah, or like this.
Or even like this.
[Laughter]
Oh, he's back!
They buried him alive!
No!
He wasn't dead after all.
First Norman, now Patrick, bro.
Yeah.
Two legends lost within days of each other, dude.
Two comedy, I mean two incredible joke writers.
Yeah.
Just lost within days of each other.
Podcast moguls.
I know, dude. Yeah. Two legends of the game.
We should do that cards thing.
The card, the jokes thing?
The jokes cards thing.
That's the best, dude. Yeah. I'm jealous of that format that he came up with of like
just have someone write just like a bunch of jokes of very varying quality.
Yeah.
And then some of them will make Andy Kindler laugh.
Yeah. And some of them will make people not happy.
I saw something today that was like, Conan did this like special about Norm,
this like remembrance special, because like they were close.
Yeah.
And then like 30 minutes in, Andy Richter's on it. It's like a podcast. 30 minutes in,
Andy Richter's like, "Yeah, but also Norm, he called me gay a lot, which is like actually
pretty offensive."
It's like fucking 36 hours after the man died and Andy Richter's fucking porky pig ass is
sitting over there.
It even kind of hurt my feelings when the funniest guy ever called me gay.
I listened to that, I was like fuming mad.
I was like, "This dude should get fucking curb stomped.
He's so stupid."
He sucks, dude.
He is the worst person in the world, dude.
Andy Kinloch?
I'm not Andy Richter.
Not Andy Kindler.
Andy Kindler is awesome.
Yeah.
Another boost.
He's the one who got divorced, right?
Because he couldn't.
Andy Richter, yeah.
And then he was just like trying to fuck 17 year olds all the time like a boss.
Actually, you know what's funny?
I just changed my mind on him.
He's actually the coolest guy in the world.
But I remember like, I forget, I think he posted or someone in his family posted like
a family picture post-divorce and like it's just like his ex-wife is standing
like as far away from him as she can be like while still being in the photo.
I bet he smells so bad. Yeah well I actually I did encounter him. You met him? I
didn't meet him I definitely was talked about this before but I almost hit him
in the face with a bathroom door. You should have. I was talking shit about him
like probably like 30 seconds before that happened too yeah me and Alex were
talking shit about him. He heard it and then you and then you almost beat him to
death with the door. It's very possible he heard it I don't know but yeah I like
pushed the bathroom door open too fast and he was like right there and it like he like
stopped it and I was like oh sorry. Then it registered like a few
seconds later. Yeah yeah cuz it's like it's like when you get too close to a
passing cruise ship and you don't see anything like the bottom of it and it's
too big to even fit in your view. You're like, "What is this?"
I was like, "What's this belly button?"
"What's this door frame?"
Oh my god, what is this snout nose?
Oh my god.
Directly in my face.
Yeah, what is this, what is this creeping, um, prowling finger that's probing its way towards my groin?
my growing anything except this oh oh wait four minutes as he passes by like
it's like this spaceship from Spaceballs yeah yeah that's what the 18 year old
that he pays have sex with see whether trying to get his dick they just slowly
go down yeah you have to take an elevator yeah to crest his stomach and
And then you finally get to his penis.
- Yeah, and there's nothing there.
- And there's nothing there?
- There's nothing there.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Almost like a magician.
- Almost like--
- That's a guy, like, I don't know how he's
made money on TV for so long.
- Yeah, I mean, I feel like he just had to have been
in the right place at the right time, right?
- Yeah, I guess that makes sense.
And also, just like, Conan needed, like,
I guess like a fat, ugly punching bag.
- Yeah. - Right?
Everybody needs one.
- Everybody needs one.
- It's funny that Jimmy Kimmel was like,
I'm just gonna get like a random Mexican.
Yeah, it is really funny.
That's a very like...
Do you think that would fly if he picked Guillermo today?
That's what I'm saying, like it's crazy that nobody's said anything about that.
I mean, because he's... because Guillermo's like in on it, I assume.
Yeah, but he's also like... Guillermo's like rich.
Yeah, I don't know anything. I've watched maybe like Jimmy Kimmel like twice in my life,
so I don't really know.
Yeah, but the whole thing is he's like...
All I see, yeah, the only stuff I've seen is just it's like,
oh isn't the way that Guillermo pronounces this insane?
Yeah, yeah, Guillermo, like Jimmy will hold up a banana and he'll be like, "Hey Guillermo, what's this?"
And he'll be like, "I don't know, Jimmy. A telephone?"
And everyone's like, "Ahhhh!"
Yeah.
Yeah, I feel like it probably wouldn't... Is Jimmy Kimmel still going?
Yeah, yeah, I think he is.
He's still doing his thing?
All of those guys are supposedly like gonna retire in like the next couple years.
Yeah, well, I feel like they will already... the way that I hear late and I talked about you think they'd already have been retired and like
replaced with like Netflix like yeah yeah they just Netflix late-night shows that
drop like 30 episodes at a time yeah yeah which makes no yeah yeah I think
the the thing is like I think the only one of those guys who has like any
viewership outside of like very old people is Corden yeah yeah I think
Corden my mom likes Trevor no numbers dude well Trevor that's like different I
guess is it I don't know I mean there's old school like Johnny Carson like you
you walk out, you monologue, you have a desk,
and then you have a guest and shit.
The Daily Show, that's just like,
that's just like annoying.
It's like a more annoying version of the news now.
- Yeah, that's true.
- They need to get a fat sidekick.
They need an Andy Richter.
- They do, yeah.
He should just be on all of them.
- Andy Richter?
- Yeah.
- He would love that, dude.
- He would do so well.
- So many more audiences for preteens
that he can go up to afterward and say,
you want an autograph?
- Yeah.
- You want an autograph in the bathroom?
come on yeah he's holding up cue cards for the audience that say like approach
and he ricked her approach any Richter with high school I do and yeah yeah he
wouldn't do that oh that's horrible to say that's horrible you would never do
that no he'd probably eat them because it was big fat nature he'd probably
think that they were a donut or a popsicle and he would eat them oh you
It just made me so mad just hearing hearing yeah
Because norm called him gay in 2004
That is so yeah, it's like dude. I just that's so funny - it's like there are people who norm said way worse stuff about
Yeah, that's like really tame definitely for him. Yeah. Yeah, he called so many women just like disgusting cunts
Yeah, it's like trying to like a pigeon just landed right at your window. Yeah. Oh, he's there like every day. Yeah, what's his name?
He's never told me you didn't name him not yet. I mean we can name him right now. Yeah
Barack Barack
Yeah, yeah, why why'd you pick that name?
You know I don't know
Couldn't tell you why I picked certainly not because he's a filthy rat carry disease
City, yeah, yeah destroying the cities of America
That wouldn't be the reason. That wouldn't be right dude. And it's not because he has a
magnet in his brain that guides him to back home. Yeah, yeah to Hawaii.
Yeah, it would have that would it's definitely not the bright yellow beady eyes.
None of those are why I chose Barack. No. No. It's because he looks cool. Yeah, he's regal. Yeah exactly.
- Yeah, he's dignified. - I'd do what he said.
It's funny that Barack Obama is one of those guys
where you can talk shit about all the time,
like all you want.
If he was in the room with you,
I think he could convince almost any person on earth
to suck his dick in 15 minutes.
- Probably, he's so charismatic.
- Would you suck Barack Obama's dick?
- I mean, I would say no now, but you know, that's--
- You'd never know what you'd say if he's in the room.
- Yeah, I mean, yeah, he would ask me
come to the to the White House Easter egg hunt and I'd say that's so far away
Barack and he said that's so far but like you know both in space and time and
and he'd say no I'm doing a very special one just for you and there are two
Easter eggs I want you to hunt and I'd say that sounds really fun and then
things would kind of proceed from there and I'd still have to go to the White
House so. One is a normal Easter egg and the other one's a wedding ring. Yeah
yeah well they both have wedding rings inside. You pop open the thing and it has a
a wet one once an engagement ring yeah there's a wedding band because you're
getting married immediately yeah yeah it's just it's the six-second
engagement yeah yeah yeah but he's like just one of those guys man he probably
could cast a spell like a real-life I think he might be doing like actual like
Alakazam chaos magic yeah you know yeah he is he's very is impressively
charismatic sheer force of will yeah you know there's not I think it's it's funny
that he was a follow-up to W also who was just like funny. Yeah, also very
charismatic. Definitely charismatic but not doesn't have a different kind of...
Dude, if you showed up to a party... Oh I mean this
guy's an animal dude. He should have been the lead singer for the Doors. This guy was like a
fucking party animal. He should have been like a guy who lived in my basement and I could
like if I was having a party I could like bang a broom on the floor and he
would like to come up and entertain everybody for me. Can you imagine growing up as Jeb Bush's son you
have that dorky ass fucking pussy dad yeah and you go over to uncle W's house.
Yeah. Dude. Oh my god. He's letting you do anything you want he's like letting you
try to guess the nuclear code on the briefcase. He's like go ahead yeah yeah
see if you can get it. Nah try again why not. Yeah yeah he's letting you
you he's letting you like punch the the the Secret Service guys to see if you
have strong you are yeah exactly yeah they can't let you like he's like
letting you try to tackle him yeah Secret Service guys have to get in the
way yeah it's like he's like you can he's like here's a here's a bill that
just that just came across my desk add any sentence you want to this yeah yeah
stamp this. Sneak anything you want.
Yeah.
I wish the president still could do like the 1700s thing where it was like if you
had a beef with the president you would write him a letter and then you guys
would, he'd get so offended that he would duel you.
Yeah. That's sick. That is cool. The fact that the president used to be like I'm gonna like I
I gotta rep my set.
- Yeah. - You talk shit,
but I'm the president, I gotta rep my shit.
- Yeah.
I think that we should bring back dueling,
but it shouldn't be guns.
It should be like everybody has a weapon specialization
that they pick like an RPG type thing
where you can maybe skill tree it or something,
but you have a specific weapon
that you can only use that in a duel.
So then it would be like, oh, I wanna duel this guy
'cause he's fucking my wife.
but my weapon is like a, you know, a katana and his,
well, he picked a crossbow, so, you know,
he's probably gonna win, so I might have to rethink this,
you know, it just adds an element of strategy.
- That's a good point. - 'Cause duels are so boring,
what, walk away and then turn around?
- Yeah, it's nothing. - It's kinda stupid,
also like, apparently a bunch of people
just like survived them all the time.
- Yeah. - It's like,
you get one shot, like that's--
- That is true, yeah. - Like if you both
just miss, and you're like, I guess--
- Yeah, they don't let you shoot again.
- I guess we do it again, I don't know.
But just like adrenaline racing,
of a fucking shaking gun. Yeah, I feel like you would both miss a bunch. Yeah, dude, a
gun is hard to shoot, especially those old ones that are so inaccurate. If you're turning
around, like, you're not even looking at the, like you're turning to shoot as fast as you
can. I don't know, I couldn't shoot a basketball like that. Maybe that's because I don't play
basketball, but. But I don't think these guys, ammunition's expensive, especially back then.
That's true. You know? Well, yeah, would you get in trouble if you just shot like three
times in a row. I don't, the guns couldn't do that. That's, I think that's why you only
get one shot because it was just a little cocked back single shot pistol. Yeah. Whatever those
are called. I don't know. I think you're right that you need to have, you have to pick a
weapon that for the rest of your life you're going to duel with. Yeah. But to trick it,
you have to pick it this day you're born. Yeah. You have to like crawl to it. It's like
Harry Potter or something. They have like a sorting hat. And they, you take like a personality
quiz yeah when you turn like 10 or something to see what you yeah to what
was and some people get like yeah like do you feel more like a sword or a gun
are you are you long and pointy or are you short and shooty do people throw you
or swing you around yeah yeah that huh it says gun but I'm pretty sure I'm a
sword yeah deep down did you see there's this movie coming out with like I think
Matt Damon's and it's called like the last duel of France or something I did
see a trailer for that it's very funny to see Matt Damon and Ben Affleck in that
getup yeah like both of them to get like one of them alone Ben Affleck is really
the funny one to see in that getup to be honest but seeing them both together in that getup is really good
they should have learned their lesson with Boston actors by now
people from Boston look fucking insane if they're not in Boston. Yeah. If they are
anywhere outside of Boston they look they look wrong. Yeah. So to send those two
back to... yeah. And they have like Dunkin Donuts cold brew teeth. It's fucked. It should be like a
kid in King Arthur's Court situation. They should be Boston guys who are sent
back. Exactly. That's how you make that movie work. Definitely. You literally you
can leave everything else the same but as long as you had a prologue where they
get sucked into a time portal. And then they just are like okay I guess we'll
just do that. Okay I guess we'll just act like them now. Yeah. And then that movie
would make perfect sense. Yeah. Yeah and then you'd add a scene at the end where
they go back home and they go it was crazy you were there and you were there
and you were there and all their friends look exactly like the medieval
characters. Oh true. But in Mark Boston. Yeah that's a good idea. Yeah. I looked up I looked up
because it's like supposedly based on a true story mm-hmm and it's called The
Last Duel of France. I was like oh that's cool like The Last Duel of France. Looked
it up like when it actually happened yeah it was like the 1600s dude France was so
fucking stupid about it they banned dueling way too early that is really
early dueling is like dude they're dueling should have like outlasted
slavery by 300 years you know what I mean yeah like if like that just should have
been dueling should have gone on way way longer it should have been yeah
absolutely it should still be around yeah yeah I think they've been they
probably been what's the point of banning it I mean people gonna do that shit yeah
well the point is I think you're gonna do it I'd rather you do it here you know
yeah it's a Venezuela to duel exactly here we got I got guns for you right I
mean it's to say like yeah you open dueling dispensary type thing like yeah
what you can do it should be a league yeah we're kind of getting into like a
Gerald what's his name Gerard Butler movies yeah I mean this could also gamer
and this could be also a really good like anime plot I feel like true bring those
back and we and everyone has their own weapon yeah yeah yeah I would like the
Super Bowl I yeah okay yeah all right if you like anything like anime turned like
Naruto turn no no no if you went to if you went to a so like a bloodsport thing
Yeah, yeah, if you went to a football game paid $100 you'd be like whatever fine
You know I had to go see a man kill another man
Yeah on a on basically a like a track and field thing yeah, but it should be going on in the Olympics during
Yeah, yeah, it should be in the middle just to know what
It should be they should like they should contract whoever builds like theme parks to build like real-life
like Halo free-for-all maps. Oh true.
Yeah, Slayer or whatever. Yeah. But I feel like doing it old-school I feel like
is a good... it'd be good for the Olympics at least. Yeah. The Olympics
whole thing is... Yeah, well right, and then they can introduce other weapons and stuff
in the... And moving, because otherwise, because paces, you know... Yeah, and abilities too.
Yeah, well you'd have to have a blue ability of course. A blue ability, yeah.
So since it's just me and Cam, we just decided to have some beautiful conversations between
best friends.
We were talking about having a conversation today.
Yeah.
I texted Caleb and I was like, "Hey man, do you want to have a conversation today?"
And he said no.
I didn't say no.
But he said no.
I said please and he said okay.
I just, I'm sorry.
I didn't say no, first of all, because I love talking to you.
You're my best bud.
Yeah.
I just I feel so I mean I love the art of conversation.
It's a beautiful art.
Would you agree?
I definitely would agree.
Would you find do you feel like honestly answer me this do you think that words can be beautiful?
I think words are kind of their own form of beauty and let me say this to you as well
I think that a sparkling conversation is worth more than any sparkling wine.
Wow.
I truly believe that.
I mean yeah, I would say a hot, juicy conversation
is better than a hot, juicy hamburger.
- Absolutely, yeah.
- Which is a thing that I just came up with,
is saying-- - A hot, juicy hamburger.
I think that's a real thing.
- Oh, you're right, my bad.
See, but that's what conversation is about,
it's about that back and forth.
- It's about a-- - I can say--
- It's kind of like a duel.
- It's a bit of a duel. - It's kind of like a
duel of beauty. - Yes, 'cause I can say
anything I want, you know what I mean?
- Blee, blah, blow, blah, blah, blah, bleh.
- You can say that and I can counterpoint and say,
Cameron, that doesn't make any sense.
Cameron, that's completely, you're saying nothing.
- And then I could say,
blah, blah, blah, I could just keep doing it.
- Yeah, and that's also the beauty of a conversation.
It could go on forever.
Who knows how long this episode will last
because this, my friends, is a beautiful conversation
between friends. - It is, yeah.
Well, I can't think of anything to talk about.
- Me neither.
We have a conversation starter list.
- Yeah, here, I pulled this up here.
This is from metropolitangirls.com, which--
- Oh.
- Yeah, I don't know.
- I don't know, but, and this is actually,
this article is actually by the Metropolitan Girls,
it says.
- Wow, each of them wrote one letter.
- 12 fun conversation topics to try with your best friend.
- Metropolitan Girls are like monkeys at typewriters.
Eventually they'll write something worthwhile, right?
- Yeah.
Not sure what to talk about with your bestie?
Here's some interesting conversation topics
you and your best friend should try.
Can you imagine by the way being like hang out with your best friend in the world and
just like sitting down and you're like, should we like look up something to talk about right
now?
That is, that literally like when I was like searching for, when I was trying to think
of something to do for this episode and I was like searching, that was making me laugh
so much to like type in because like it's like, it's low down on the like, like Google
search suggestions.
Yeah.
But it's on there.
thing like top con like things to talk about with your and then
it'll be like your parents your boyfriend your and like just
keep typing and it's like yeah sadly they're conversationalist
right yeah they're trying to be at least that's like if you ever
had somebody do that like in if you have like a small like group
of people someone will like like this happened in high school
once some kid was like uh was like let's look up something to
talk about yeah we all just watch a movie or something and
and he like looked at a list on his phone,
he was like, "Oh, we should talk about movies."
(laughing)
- Like why did, you had to look up
that you wanted to talk about movies?
- Yeah, sometimes you do.
There's no shame in that.
- I think there's some shame.
- No, absolutely not.
A conversation can start in any way.
That's the beauty of it.
It could start, you could talk,
you could suddenly strike up a conversation
with a guy on the train out of nowhere.
Okay, you could suddenly strike up a conversation with that same guy, 20 minutes later, outside
of his front door and he doesn't know how you got there.
True.
He didn't know you were having a conversation with the back of him from 30 feet away.
That's right, because he thought it was his brother.
You thought it?
Yeah.
The back of his head was your face.
Sorry, can you turn around?
I'm not done talking to your hairy brother.
He's very ugly and we've been talking about it for quite a while.
Yeah.
And he has super hearing and he can hear me from way over there.
He's walking down the street like 30 feet behind somebody and he's going, "Wow, you're so hairy."
"Why do you wear all your clothes backwards?
You're a weird freak."
"I hate you, you stupid bitch.
Oh, hello sir.
I'm sorry, I was actually berating your ugly backside, friend."
Yeah.
Anyway, there's interesting conversation topics to talk to your best friend about.
Now you're hanging out and it suddenly gets quiet.
This has happened to all of us.
You feel like there's nothing else to discuss and that's where you are wrong.
You haven't exhausted all the topics in the world, not yet.
The fact is you don't fully know the specifics about each other.
Are we going to get deep and down and dirty?
I think we're going to get into some specifics.
Look at this beautiful image.
Oh my god, there's a rose.
Dude, that's us.
Are you green or purple?
I think I'm the rose.
You can't be the rose.
Well, because this is only half of the faces, so that's one person.
So that's you.
I'm actually the Metropolitan Girls logo. I changed my mind.
Okay. Conversation topics for best friends. They have a title every
paragraph here. Try these uncommented topics below to keep things interesting.
I've always wanted to talk to you about this first topic.
I've just always wanted to talk to you about this.
Number one is food. I mean
where do we even begin?
I mean
yeah well let's talk let's just let's talk this out right talk so i mean i'd like
to before we even basically start talking about this yeah i would just like to say
pizza hot dog hamburger they're all delicious they're all right okay so we can agree on that
much i did i when i was a kid i didn't like hot dogs because one time i ate a hot dog and i i
threw up and there were chunks of hot dog in in my throw up and i saw it and i was like that's
disgusting. Dude, I mean, it's called Nathan's Gambit, dude. You take it every
time you eat a hot dog. Who knows what's gonna happen to you? Yeah, well the thing
is... It's about a 50/50 chance. It's the perfectly shaped food to make you throw up.
It's very easy if you completely forget to chew for it to hit your
uvula and then shoot out like a bullet. It's true. Which is kind of
impressive, actually. But the thing about a hot dog is like you either have to
like... it either powers you up to light a firework or like you have to sit on a
leather couch for like, like a cold leather couch for hours after eating a hot dog.
Yeah.
Because it'll just fucking, there's something, because it's mystery meat,
it's like, it's like Russian roulette.
Yeah.
You know what I mean? Like there's something, there has to be one part of bad rancid meat in
In every other hot dog.
Oh, absolutely.
Right?
Yeah. Yeah.
So it's got fucking ups and downs.
It's like a toy in cereal, but.
Yeah. That's why you should only ever eat one hot dog at a time, because you are limiting your
chances of getting the stinky dog.
Two hot dogs at a time.
- You know when you're eating a bag of pistachios?
- No, you gotta eat two at a time.
- Two hot dogs?
- Yeah.
- What are you, Andre the Giant?
- If they're both, let's say it's a 50% chance.
- What are you, Joey Chestnut?
- Let's say it's a 50% chance that you get the bad dog, okay?
- Yeah.
- That's .5, all right?
You with me here?
- Yeah.
- .5 times .5 when you add another hot dog, that's .25.
That's one in four.
- That's a really good point, actually.
You're less likely if you eat two hot dogs.
The more dogs you eat actually.
Yeah, because it multiplies the...
That's a good, yeah, it halves it every time.
Yeah, and I wouldn't think that, but you know, when you do the math it checks out.
Yeah, exactly.
I mean we just did the math, we have a whiteboard here.
Yeah, and I mean when you add the bun it's even less likely.
True, yeah, because you have a barrier now.
Yeah, well because the bun, it's a 0% chance it's going to be a bad hot dog because it's not a hot dog.
So you multiply it by zero.
So you multiply it by zero, it's a 0% chance.
So actually you're fine every single time.
- Yeah, true, the bun is a protective condom.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- No, no, no, it's not.
- Oh. - No, it's not.
- What's it called?
A paraphyla, anaphylaxis?
- Huh? - A paraphylaxis?
- Anaphylaxis? - No.
The paralax, the phacalax. - What?
What are you trying to say?
- What's a fucking, what do they call a condom?
And, or like a dental dam?
- Oh, um.
- Anthropathic?
Apropethic?
(laughing)
- I don't know. - A simplepethic.
- A temperpedic? - A temperpethic.
I think it's a tempur-pedic.
- What is that fucking word, man?
Acrobatic!
- I don't think I know the word.
- Acrobatic, sympathetic, fucking shit.
- I don't think I know the word that you're talking about.
- Whatever, man.
- Okay.
- Paralaxic, paralaxic, paralaxic, oh, I'm so close.
- Paraplegic.
- No, shut up, shut up.
Fuck, dude.
Paral...
I give up, I give up.
I'll think of it in, I'll never think of this.
I don't know.
- It's been happening to me more and more recently.
Been losing words from my brain.
Yeah, I think I might have a neurotoxin in my life.
- It could happen.
- You think I have lead paint?
You feel weird when you walk in here?
- Oh, no, I feel pretty normal when I walk in here.
You probably have lead paint, though.
Doesn't like everywhere have lead paint here?
- I don't know, I probably should look that up.
But also, I think they have to tell you when you move in.
- Yeah, I don't think you should look that up.
- Yeah, I definitely shouldn't.
Yeah, that'd be a really bad idea, actually.
- Yeah, I think you're right that they do have to.
I think that's what I'm thinking of,
that when I signed my lease, they were like,
"We have to tell you if there's lead paint."
And I took that to mean,
"Oh, there's probably lead paint everywhere."
- Well, the truth is, if there's lead paint,
it's like, you know, a couple layers deep.
- Yeah, I'm not eating the paint.
- I mean, lead can't get through paint, right?
- Right, yeah. - So, pretty much.
- That's why they put paint over it.
- Yeah, exactly, exactly, yeah.
- That's why, yeah.
- It just makes perfect sense.
- They were like, "We have to get rid of all this lead.
"I guess we'll put it in paint where it can't hurt anybody."
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- Yes, sir.
- Yeah, and in pipes, too.
- True.
- Yeah.
- But that's fine.
That doesn't do anything to you.
That's just water.
- Well, water is, here's,
and also, speaking of hot dogs,
it balances out, right?
- Yeah.
- 'Cause water is good for you.
Lead is probably as bad for you
as water is good for you, right?
Like, you can't live without water,
but lead's gonna kill you.
- Yeah, if I had as much lead a day
as I have water a day, I'd probably die.
- No, you'd be fine.
- No, if I, no, I mean like,
if instead of having water I had that same amount of lead I would die but if I had that
amount of water I'd be alive.
You mix it, it's just like you barely had any water.
So as long as you drink more water than lead I think you're in a good position.
I also do kind of feel like people who get lead poisoning from pipes are complaining.
Right.
Because like how long have, there's so many cities in America that have lead shit in the
pipes.
Yeah, oh you think, yeah, you think you, this house has been standing for like however long
you think you're the one who got lead poisoning?
Come on.
I wake up, walk over to the sink, drink a scorching hot cup of water out of the tap.
Just because I want to make sure that lead is dissolved in there.
Yeah.
I put, I put, I put, I put, it's hot out of the tap.
I put it into a Dasani water bottle.
And then I actually, I put that into a saucepan and I heat that up on the stove.
Just to really get it really nice.
And then I, and then I turn it into like a flaky salt and I put it over all of my steaks.
Yeah.
lot of steaks. The other part is, the other part of my healthy lifestyle is I eat a
steak for every meal. Oh a lot of steaks and I paint the steaks before I eat them. Yeah, I really I really want it to feel like I'm eating the Tin
Man from Wizard of Oz. I hate that guy. He sucks. He's so, he's so. Yeah and I tried to and I tried to eat him when I saw a
statue of him I hurt my teeth really bad. Yeah. Steak is a lot softer than statue.
It's true. We were in, I was in Times Square the other day I can't remember if
were there or not. This was like when my cousin was in town. I don't think I was there. And we saw
one of those. Actually I haven't been to Times Square since I moved here. Oh really? Yeah. We
saw a tin man, one of those guys who stand still. Yeah. And he was not standing still, dressed full,
full tin paint all the way down. And then people were walking by and he's like,
"You know what I noticed recently? A whole lot of mixed race couples hate giving me money."
And I was like, and he was just going on this like tirade.
He was like, "Mixed couples hate me, man.
They never give me money.
It's the worst kind of couple.
Fuck you.
Fuck you."
He was just like pointing at people, talking shit to them.
And I was like-
And you were like, "Why isn't he talking shit to me?"
Yeah, well, I was like, "Dude, come on, bro."
Yeah, we're right here.
I'm Italian, Jenna's inbred.
This is like an insane mix, right?
You know?
Yeah.
shock.
That is very true, yeah.
But I was also like this has got to be the worst statue in the world, right?
Yeah.
You know?
Well, he's an animatronic.
Oh.
He's doing an animatronic.
Well, that's, he's the racist animatronic.
Yeah.
Everybody knows the racist animatronic.
I should have known, dude.
Yeah.
But I was amazed that I saw one of those guys move for once.
And it was, he was not, it wasn't like people were touching him.
Yeah.
He was just doing it on his own.
I mean, sometimes, right?
You might as well, yeah.
He got shit on his mind, right?
Yeah.
And I bet he earned a couple dollars.
And I bet you earned a couple dollars.
That would be really fun actually to do,
to put yourself in the whole living statue costume
and then go and just walk around.
Not even do that, but just walk around
and act completely normal.
Yeah.
You love Bicentennial Man with Robin Williams.
Never seen it, but based on the cover,
that's what it's about.
(laughing)
You could go up to other living statue guys
and try and talk shop with them.
Yeah.
That would be a good way to trick them into moving.
Hey brother, like I've been thinking,
like do you have any tips on this?
What?
Oh!
I'm trying to not move!
Can you not see that I'm trying to be super still right now?
That's the thing, those are the real Buckingham Palace guards.
The ten men.
They should staff them there.
That would, yeah, they would do a better job.
Buckingham Palace guards also should be able to do ventriloquism.
They should be able to sit there and be like...
There should be some that are dressed like Spider-Man too.
I think a lot less people would fuck with them.
Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah, I'm not blowing up Spider-Man's face.
That has to be the least scary man with a gun in the entire universe.
Absolutely.
like looks like a toy that is a toy he's the joke is he's dressed he's it's like
it's like if you like so if like if you were like oh don't go over there
there's there's those are really intimidating scary guards there's a guy
in like a rubber duck costume yeah like standing oh don't touch that Tonka truck
yeah yeah no it's a very scary yeah yeah like I and I know obviously is not
dressed as a toy but that he is he is a toy he is a toy yeah that's absolutely a
toy soldier is the only way that that type of soldier exists. He is a walkabout
Disneyland character. Yeah. I think there are multiple theme parks filled with
people who dress up like him. Yeah. And walk around. He is doing Halloween every
day of the year. Okay, theme park idea. Yep. It's all walk around
characters that are like just different ranks like military people. Like it's
just a military theme. That would, you could ride like a tank on the
roller coaster. Dude, that would clean up. That would do, yeah, if you put that in the right
city that would like... Holy shit! Yeah. Also make it World War II themed. I guess, I guess
also, oh my god! Also it employs veterans because those are the only people who are
allowed to wear costumes like that. True! So they don't have to be homeless and like, you
know, kill women who walk across their front yard anymore. That's a good point.
They can work at theme park and kill children in the teacups. Yeah, by turning
it on to map onto 11. They draw 11 like in Spinal Tap on the teacup, right? And
they turn it all the way up. But also like, wouldn't they, do you think they would feel
uncomfortable dressing up as Adolf Hitler and all these evil versions of soldiers that are all good?
I think you could find some soldiers who would really like it, to be honest.
A soldier who likes Adolf Hitler? Someone who's in the American military who's into being a Nazi?
I don't think so. I think you're going to be horrified.
You could have like a spinoff that's like Cop World. That would do like even better than
Military World. Cop World would literally like
destroy in all 50 states. That would like outstrip Disney. It would be packed and I'll tell you what,
I'd probably go there twice a year. Absolutely dude, I would get the season passed. Cop world?
Cop world. That'd be the sickest shit of all time. Even people who are like,
even people who are like, their thing is like, oh man I hate the freaking cops.
Wait till a cop gives you a candied apple buddy and then tell me you hate police officers.
They would go there and take video. Your cord's fucked up I think.
How about now? I think it's okay, but it's been doing it. Oh, no. No, it's so oh my god
All right. Hold on
But even people who you know hate cops and even these these freaking a cab types nowadays
They would go there just to disrespect the cops
They would go there to prank them on their gopros true and that would be allowed because that would double the profits
I wish these a cab fellas would get in a cab and go back to china. Oh, absolutely
It's just not right.
It's not right.
Yeah.
Don't you, do you realize that a cop goes through all day?
Have you ever heard of, have you ever heard of?
Do you realize how hard cops work?
Okay, they, all night they're up protecting your community from
from creeps and ne'er-do-wells and then in the morning they
have to go to cop world and they have to, they have to make
popcorn.
Exactly.
For the other 12 hours.
That's the other part is that it's included in a cop's work
now.
Yeah.
You know, because all these cops.
It's like the draft.
They want to cut funding for police.
How about the police give back, right?
The other thing is about if you hate cops so much, have you ever heard, like thinking about
what they go through, have you ever heard of how bad blue light is for a human eyeball?
Yeah.
They sit in a car 12 hours a day looking at a laptop.
Their corneas are fucking decimated.
Yeah, and their attention span, I mean, it's damaging.
Nobody talks about cops having ADHD.
Yeah.
You know, these cops-
It gives them ADHD.
PTSD, that doesn't exist.
ADHD, they come home, all of a sudden they're strung out on Adderall on the streets asking
people for Vyvanse, Ritalin, Focalin.
You know?
It's disgusting.
Yeah.
It's just really sad.
It's just not right.
Yeah.
So cop world might be a big fix for us.
I think it could work.
I think it could be really good.
And I don't think that anyone will ever sneak in either.
Also.
I think it'll be really, nobody will steal the food or anything.
True.
You want to go...
Alright, here's another angle on it.
I'm gonna go Six Flags right now, but somebody just called me and said, "Don't
come to Six Flags tomorrow. I'm worried about a mass shooting."
What's my alternative? The Copper War. There's a mass shooting every day. No, no, no,
they stop the mass shooting every single time. No, it's like when the
princesses do the parade at Disney or whatever. Every day there's like a
mass shooting that they all stop. Yeah, it's like when you're at
Knott's Berry Farm and they like robbed the bank.
Yeah.
The old western, the cowboys.
Oh, and dude, October at Cop World.
Oh my god.
Don't even get me started.
Yeah.
There's a guy, there's a guy dressed as a creepy clown and
he's walking around and he gets, he gets bullets pumped in him
like three times a day.
He's wearing a vest.
Completely just, just cheese.
It's not bulletproof, but he's wearing a vest.
Swiss cheese constantly.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Now that's scary.
It's terrifying.
Yeah.
Yeah, it'd be sick though.
It would be awesome.
They should make more movies like, like Alien vs. Predator, but it's cops vs. something.
Right?
Wouldn't that be sick?
Like cops vs. killer clowns from outer space.
They should just do that for every franchise.
Yeah, cops vs. predator.
It's like an entire police precinct in Astoria that have to fight the predator.
That'd be sick.
Yeah.
Predator 2 is kind of cops vs. predator.
Is it?
Yeah.
Oh, sorry.
Alright, cops vs. something else.
Yeah.
Cops vs. Alien would be really good.
- That would be good.
Or like Cops vs. Chucky.
Maybe could be good, yeah.
- Oh yeah, more of a slasher thing.
Jason V. Cops.
- Or like, oh my god, what is going on?
Is this cord fucked up or something?
- Should be.
- Oh, whatever.
You guys can deal with it, I don't care.
- Yeah, this is the price you pay for Cop World.
- Yeah, it is such a good idea.
That could also, Jesus, what the hell?
- You wanna pause it and figure it out?
- Yeah, hold on.
And so even what I was saying is even if we don't even if we don't aren't able to
build cop world which is a big if a big yeah we aren't because it's happening
because it's definitely so easy to build an amusement park it would make a really
good movie or TV series like a Westworld or yeah yeah also I think like the
sharks might be a very strong possibility for funding on this can you
Can you imagine any of those five people on national television?
Yeah, saying like, "No, I don't want to invest in police officers."
"I don't want to support our police."
And you could just be like, "What? Really? I came here, a humble..."
Okay, hold on. I'm going to switch out the cord.
Hit that button.
Okay, alright. Hopefully this fixes it. If not, there's nothing I'm going to do about it.
I'd like to move on to level two of our intense conversation right now.
We only covered one topic so far. That's how beautiful this conversation has been.
Honestly, I could look into your eyes and talk to you
for over six hours probably without pausing.
- Probably, yeah.
- Yeah, we could just-- - It would be easy to do, yeah.
And really fast too, like maybe twice the speed
of a normal conversation.
- I know, it'd be a 12-hour conversation.
- It's actually like 12 hours, yeah,
a 12-hour conversation-- - Stuck in six hours.
- In six hours with eye contact too.
- Eye contact the entire time.
I do feel like if I had one person in my life
that I would want to do Scientology to me, it'd be you.
- Yeah. (laughs)
- I think you could get a lot out of me.
- Yeah. - I think if you sat me down
and started electrocuting me when I said
I don't wanna fuck my mom,
than like I think that might be more the electricity than me.
It's doing my work.
You're my only friend with a guts to push the button, dude.
I think all my other friends are pussy out.
Yeah, and then I think
dude, like if Patrick was auditing me, dude,
I'd be in big trouble.
I'd be walking around thing.
I was immune to electricity.
I'll be getting like Union electrician job saying like, yeah,
I'll just hang from the bars like a monkey and then I just get
fucking owned you you'd have the guts to flick that switch and
hit me with 13,000 volts, blow my toes off.
(laughing)
I saw something.
- Your toes just blasting off.
- That's what happens, dude.
- That's what happens?
- Dude, it happens constantly.
You don't know about this? - Constantly?
- Literally, probably every second.
(laughing)
- I don't believe that.
- No, so people will, like this happens on film sets
and shitty construction shit
where they have an exposed wire.
Someone will touch the wire,
get like ten thousand volts pumped through them through their hand
the electricity wants to go to the ground it always trying to move into the
ground so it will go through your feet and it'll blow your toes off
like just explode them
like it's the coolest shit I've ever heard. That's so funny. Yeah just fucking blasting toes
like and I mean
god bless the people around you who showed up in sandals that day. Well that's like that's
that's like a superhero origin
where it's like I touched like an ungrounded wire and it blasted my toes
off and turned me into horseman.
Dude, I was like looking at different people who had this story the other day
and I saw one guy who was he was working on a movie set and he lost six toes.
Goddamn.
Working on a movie set lost six fucking toes.
That's crazy.
So cool dude.
That's sick.
Yeah and he called it a near-death experience.
No.
It was like six toes man.
of fucking kill you, dickhead. That's nothing, yeah. You know? But I honestly I don't know
what the long-term effects of electricity in the body is so maybe... Maybe, yeah. I don't
know, maybe he is... No, he's wrong. Six toes. He's probably fine, six toes. You still have
four left. Yeah, dude, that's enough. You could be... That's a lot of toes. You could
be... Can you imagine showing up to like... Imagine, imagine, imagine seeing like an insect
or a snake or something and complaining to it like, "Oh, I only have four toes." Yeah.
Yeah, or showing a baby Paralympics. Mm-hmm like okay. What's your para and you're like I have four toes instead of yeah
If you lose a toe like even one toe you do have to like relearn how to walk not me
Yeah, I want my heels all the time. Yeah, it doesn't matter if I lose you take all I I walk on only my left
Big toe, so if I lose that one, I'm fucked but any of the other one. Yeah, it's
Yeah, yeah, yeah. All right topic number two songs
I mean, we talk about songs.
Yeah, I mean I love songs.
You love songs, I don't really like songs.
You don't like songs?
I don't like music that much.
I'm in the, I used to like music a lot more than I do.
I mean I like music a lot but I just don't listen to it that much anymore.
I don't listen to anything.
I listen to...
It's very funny, it's so like yeah, it's just like, oh I moved to a city where like I can
like go around, walk around and talk to people and I don't listen to music anymore.
Yeah, music is for losers today.
It's literally for like, like pussies who sit inside all day.
Yeah.
You know, like when I, nothing going on, I listen to so much music and my life was dog
shit.
Yeah.
Right.
But I was like, but hey, yeah, hey, I, Elliot Smith is good.
You know, now the only songs I like, I like Pitbull.
Like the Pitbull J-Lo song that's like, that's like, I don't remember what it's called.
See that's the thing.
You know that somebody has a good life if their favorite song, they don't even know the
name of it. Because they just hear it. They don't care. It's on everywhere. The other
good song, Cascada, Evacuate the Dance Floor. Oh yeah. You know what's a really good song
that I love? Gigi D'Agostino, what's it called? Le Morte Toujours. You know that one? How'd
that go? There's so many songs that you just... Dude, that song rocks. I listen to that song
like so much. Really? Yeah, it's so good. Now my new favorite song is Informer by Snow.
When he goes like, "I'll fly with you" and in that like in the high-pitched voice. It's
a great song. It's good. It's so good. What's that other one? Eric Pride, "Call
on Me." Call on me, call on me, call on me, call on me. I don't know. You don't know that?
I don't know it. You must not be a dancer. I'm not a dancer. I am. Yeah. I found out
recently if I go any if I go to anywhere with music you dance with
Jana I will never dance yeah I would never dance with her why would I ever
dance you can't know oh if I go somewhere by myself and I have one beer
I will dance the night away absolutely no when if you're dancing with your girl
there the two options for dancing are like a wedding dance or like you are
fucking your girlfriend yeah public yeah that's the only dance you can do with a
with a woman. And I don't want to be seen with her also is the other thing. Yeah.
I mean but if I go like we were in Atlantic City I'd dance the night away.
Of course yeah you do a little a little a little crazy finger. Yeah. A little a
little two-step a little shake side to side a little crowd kill you know.
Crowd kill while they're playing the 303 remix. Yeah. Why trash with the
*BANG* *BANG* *BANG*
*laughing*
knocking water out of people's hands
*BANG* *BANG* *BANG*
Probably here comes the bride
Completely offer them I do the Imperial March. Yeah. Yeah
I mean that would go crazy that would that would get huge online. Yeah, that would be your work. You know the video of um
The the bride walking out to um crazy bitch by Buck Sherry. No, you haven't seen that sick
It's so funny because the bride walks out and it's like, you know, like you're crazy bitch
But the way you fuck I'm on top, you know that whole thing and then and there's like it's like it's like a wedding
wedding. So there's like kids and stuff there and like right in front like
someone's filming and you can see like right in front of the person filming
like saying slightly the side is like a dad and like a son and the dad is
going like oh my God. I'm like covering the kids eyes and ears. She's like
dancing to it and he's like what? Why are you guys? You just say it's so
funny. It's such a good video. You should look it up. If my wife the night
before our wedding. We're looking at the wedding playlist. If she chooses
single song with the word slut, whore, or boyfriend in it, I'm not getting married.
The wedding is off.
That's a red flag.
If your girl likes any music that is sung by a girl, huge red flag.
Absolutely.
But if, on the other hand, if we're looking over, I see any songs with the words "Happy
birthday or Cameron in there that's I'm
not signing a prenup yeah if she thinks
it were if she wants to honestly and I'm
gonna try to pretend to argue or like
like talk her out of it yeah if she
honestly comes in she's like I want to
play the happy birthday song about you
at our wedding I'm like I'm buying
second-rate such a funny first dance
happy birthday their first dance
first it's only one of you really mad yeah but then but then they're like and
now for their second dance the happy birthday are you what okay well that's
songs the third one I've been excited to get to this topic for our conversation
the third one is something in the room so we've talked about everything in my
apartment I feel like we could find some stuff what the fuck it is of any
interest in this fucking this well there's a record player right there so
what song would you want to play on let's see do I have anything anything fun in
here I have I don't know it's raining outside that's not in the room but I'm
pretty upset about that I can open the window I don't think you should do that
Then it'd be in the room though.
That's a good point.
There's a lit candle over there.
Yeah, I did that because my house smells like such shit today.
Yeah.
Yeah, because I have probably 40 days worth of dishes in the shower.
Are you a candle guy?
Do you get candles a lot?
Do you light scented candles and stuff?
I used to.
Whenever I'd go to Ikea, I'd get like, I would buy nothing except like $40 worth of candles
and I'd light them all the time.
I've never been a scented candle guy.
I just got one that's like pumpkin something scented and it smells like too good.
Really?
Like I can't.
I don't do that.
This is like, this one's called like laundry.
I can't be like walking around the house and smelling dessert.
Yeah.
It's too nice.
It's too.
I also, you don't like, I feel like whenever I go to, you know what the worst is?
You go over to someone's house for dinner, right?
They tell you like, we're making lasagna, we're making fucking like chicken pot pie,
something like that.
walk in they have like a Fruit Loops scented candle.
Yeah, no that literally happened to me.
Yeah, it was like I was eating dinner.
We're eating, I think we were just having like pasta.
And yeah, it was smelling like pumpkin.
It's like, dude, what am I supposed to do? I want dessert now.
I want the pumpkin so badly.
You're fucking ruining my appetite. I want a pumpkin so bad.
Have you ever had just a raw pumpkin?
I've never eaten it.
Really? I mean, I've carved a pumpkin before.
You've never eaten raw pumpkin before? No, why would I do that?
Just see what it tastes like. No.
It looks disgusting. It doesn't even- it smells like shit.
Why does it- how is- how is that possibly the same thing as pumpkin pie?
Raw pumpkin is a gross enough looking food that if you eat it I think there's
something wrong with you mentally.
It's not even food. That is not something you should put in your mouth ever, I don't think.
That's like if you were like- were like found a dog shit and you're like,
"Oh, I just wonder what it tastes like."
That's not true. They don't make pie out of dog shit, Cameron.
Oh wait, wait, wait, quick editor's note.
We're at the first argument of our conversation.
so this is actually this is huge but pumpkin literally looks like like it's
like looks like a David Cronenberg special effect pumpkin literally it's so fucked
up it looks like this like weird jagged smile and then two triangle eyes yeah
what are you gonna do it does when you cut open a pumpkin to carve it it looks
horrible inside yeah it looks like a spider web and you want to eat that I
don't want to eat you said you did wait there's a movie where the like the alien
goo looks exactly like pumpkin shit. Oh, it's the Super Mario Brothers movie.
Yeah. There's like some, they get like stuck in some shit in that that just
looks like the inside of a pumpkin. Mm-hmm. Like that weird like spiderweb
orange like nasty membrane. That's so gross. It is disgusting. You ever put your hand in a
pumpkin? Yeah. But those seeds are damn good if you toast them. Seeds are so good. It's fucked up.
Yeah, I hate like, I hate stuff on my hands, like slime on my hands and stuff.
carving pumpkins was a real test for me as a kid.
Especially because you love knives so much.
Yeah, well you don't use a knife with the difficult part is scooping out the, you know.
I don't even do that.
That's what I mean. You don't scoop out the stuff.
What am I going to set on fire?
How do you light it if you don't scoop it out?
Gasoline.
You just put, it's a bowl, you put gasoline in it and you set it on fire.
But it's not a bowl until you scoop it out.
It's pretty much hollow.
No.
It's pretty hollow.
- There's seeds and tentacles in there.
- I don't care, those can burn, those can go to hell.
I don't care.
It's easy, dude.
- Yeah.
- Do you think it's scary to harvest pumpkins?
- Probably, if you saw one with the face, it would be scary.
- What if you walked out there,
and you have to harvest them at night?
- It would be scary if there was like a monster
in there with you too, I would think.
- You have to harvest pumpkins at night, that's the thing.
- Well yeah, they go bad in the day.
- They go bad during the day, you have one hour,
the witching hour is what it's called.
- Yeah.
- And you have to harvest them,
because it's which pumpkins are ripe, these ones, and you get them.
Yeah.
And they, it's got to be terrifying.
Right?
You walk out there, all of them just looking at you.
And confusing too, because if you have, you'll need scarecrows for your pumpkin patch so
these crows don't eat the pumpkins, don't carry the pumpkins away.
How scary can you make a farm?
And a lot of those scarecrows, if you want them to be really scary, they're going to
have to have a jack-o-lantern for a head.
Yeah.
dark out in the night, how are you going to be sure you're harvesting the right
pumpkin and not pulling the head off your scarecrow? Exactly. It's confusing.
Yeah. No, no. I mean how scary can a farm be that has a pumpkin field, pumpkin patch,
and a scarecrow? That is one of the scariest farms. And a robot ghost. Yeah. That'd be
pretty fucking scary. Yeah. Right? That would be really scary. Also if the farmer was
evil I wouldn't want to stay over at his house. I mean you have to be some kind of
evil to choose pumpkin as your livelihood, right?
Yeah.
You know, because it's not like if you make, if you are a corn grower, right?
Every other night have a couple of years of corn with dinner.
Back to the sorting hat thing where when you decide to be a farmer, you go to farm warts
or whatever and they put a sorting, it looks like a straw farmer's hat, right?
That's pretty good.
They put a sorting hat and it'll tell you what crop.
And everyone who gets pumpkin, they look exactly like Jack Skellington.
Oh, they're already kind of scary looking people.
Yeah, pumpkin claw.
That makes sense.
Corn puff.
That's what corn farmers have.
Corn puff?
Yep.
Sounds so good.
And then there's tobacco slitherin.
Yeah, and then Appledore.
Appledore.
Yeah, and then there's a pumpkin.
And then there's a pumpkin.
Those are the four options that you can grow.
If you could farm one thing, what would it be?
I don't think I would do one of those big...
Does it have to be a thing you could actually farm?
Because I would love to have it.
I would love to...
You know what, I'm going to say just for your sake because we are such best friends.
No, it doesn't have to be.
It can be anything in the world.
If you could farm one thing, but it can be anything in the world, what would it be?
DVDs.
- I would love to form DVDs.
That would be so cool.
- Would they be like DVDs that already exist,
or new DVDs?
- You could cross-pollinate them and whatever
to make DVDs.
So I could plant alien in the ground,
I could plant predator in the ground,
and then when alien grows,
I could take some of the pollen from alien
and put it into the predator plant,
it would make alien versus predator DVD.
- Wow.
But then if you breed too many,
you get a scary movie?
- Yeah.
Yeah, a parody movie.
Yeah, so, and you, exactly, you could make new movies that people have never heard of
before.
The scary movie movies are like, they're like the cuties of DVDs.
Yeah, they've been.
Yeah, they've just been so fucking mutated from the, like, what they're supposed to be.
Yeah, the baseline, yeah.
There's so many different sugars in them that it's almost impossible to recognize them as
what they really are.
Yeah, well, there are just like a few baseline movies that are like, they're DVDs that are
like the pure ones.
Alright, what are your starter seeds that you're getting from Monsanto?
You got it. You have to get you get a Frankenstein. Okay seed. Yeah, you get a one for every genre probably, right?
Yeah, that's what you get like you get like a ten things. I hate about you. Maybe could be one. Yeah, you get
Lord of the Rings
Maybe one of the Lord of the Rings right off the bat. Uh-huh cross pollinating Frankenstein and Lord of the Rings. Yeah
What are you getting?
Probably I would get um, I would probably get brain dead Peter Jackson's horror movie. It's a really good. Yeah, I think
DVD former.
Holy shit!
You might be the best DVD former of all time.
That's how the Redbox works, actually.
I don't know if you know they have like a little incubator in there.
It's like a little hydroponic DVD former there.
We got my teenage son growing DVDs in his closet.
R-rated too.
Yeah.
Oh no, yeah.
No thanks.
That was not good.
Yeah, so what else is it?
What else we got to talk about here?
This conversation has been too beautiful.
I know.
Oh wow, it takes a turn.
All right, let's hit them.
We wanted to, okay, number four.
So just to run through, the first one's food, then songs, then something in the room, and
the fourth one is regrets.
I mean, if we're going to try to have the most beautiful conversation ever, I feel like
we do have to do these next two.
Yeah.
You know, because I feel like every beautiful conversation has to have a curve to it, right?
Yeah, a moment when it gets real.
Exactly.
So let's get real.
That's your biggest regret in your entire life, but it can be anything in the world.
It can be anything, probably DVDs.
I don't know.
I really regret not, I probably regret like not investing in Apple or something.
The worst answer I've ever heard.
I was trying to think of a really bad answer that didn't have to say anything about my
life.
I probably regret, honestly, I probably regret, I wish I was still vegan.
Yeah.
I wish, yeah, because I quit being vegan when I was like 18.
And now I feel like my life is noticeably worse.
I feel like I have a more evil life because I'm not vegan anymore.
Yeah, especially once you quit being vegan, it's hard to go back.
I know that it's probably very easy.
Mentally it's like impossible.
Mentally it's hard because it's like yeah, why would I...
Because everything about my life would have to change.
It's also like, well I already put in the time.
I'm already not evil.
I feel like I earned my way into heaven.
And then I quit and then I...
And now I'm slowly kind of inching back towards hell.
And at some point I'll have to make a turn.
But I always, I remember as a kid I was like,
I'm probably going to go to heaven if I at least am vegan for one year before I die.
Yeah.
I still, I mean, depends on when I die, but probably being vegan, yeah.
Because also, I was vegan when it was fucking hard as shit.
There was nothing good.
It is insane, seems insanely easy to be vegan right now.
Especially like in New York.
Yeah, moving from Boston here, like so much, so many fucking vegan freaks here.
It's so easy to accidentally eat vegan too here.
To like go somewhere and then find out, "Oh, I'm not even eating, this isn't chicken."
Yeah.
I didn't even realize when I ordered it.
There's that place in Bushwick that has those really good chicken sandwiches.
That place is good. I've been there twice.
Damn. Really good.
You're addicted, dude.
Well, we went once and then I went once.
You have an addiction.
I have an addiction to vegan chicken.
Also, I've been offered...
My other regret is I've been offered a lot more drugs than I've done in my life.
I wish that I'd done it every time.
I don't think that I've ever been offered enough drugs to hurt me.
Yeah, and I think it probably would have been fun almost every single time. Yeah, you know, yeah
Yeah, I wish I wish I'd either
Started drinking earlier and never drank at all. Yeah, that's my that's probably if we're going there. That's my yeah, that's mine
You would have been a you would have been a poet if you started drinking earlier. Oh, absolutely
You would have been a beautiful. I don't think I didn't start drinking until I was like 18 or something
Yeah, I was pretty much straight-edge damn for high school. I didn't know what straight-edge was
was. If I had known what it was, I definitely would have called myself straight edge.
Alright, and now death. What do you think happens when you die?
I have no idea. I think...
Do you ever think about it?
Oh yeah, a lot. Yeah. But I think probably it's like... it probably just... it probably...
It's probably something that is so alien to how we experience life as we know it that it
might as well just end because it's something so different.
Like it's the functional... and anything we can imagine it might as well just be that
we stop existing because...
Because it's not...
You won't have...
That's what I think.
Even if there's something after you won't have some...
You won't remember your birthday.
You can't like conceive of it so it doesn't matter.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
you can make I mean it would be so cool if it was just like the far side heaven
where you just like it's a hangout on a cloud like that literally that it is
funny that Christians found the best version of heaven like Jews for
thousands of years we're like I don't know you like hang out in like a river
or some shit I don't know yeah and then Christians were like you get to
basically hang out on a cloud made of cotton candy God is your best friend
your entire family's there but only the ones that you like yeah who were good
Yeah, there's unlimited Xbox you get to you know what you get two meals a day the third one you have to make yourself
It is funny like like I like it makes Greek heaven was real ancient Greek heaven
What was it good to just like like a beautiful golden field?
Just like boring dude. No, that'd be so nice
DS no that's after you after you've lived like a full life, and you know like I
Like and like you know when you went okay when if you died right now
you would be really bored in a golden field but you're like 90 years old and
you're already like you just wanted to sit in your armchair and like do
crosswords well I don't think it's like actual just you know like a waving
beautiful yeah yeah yeah just a beautiful field yeah that would be so
nice and nice yeah yeah I feel like I'm I feel like I'm approaching that I feel
like by the time I'm 30 I'll be pretty ready to die you know like old people
like some people find comfort in the fact that like every old person which I
I don't know how this is comfortable to you.
Every old person that you see over the age of 80,
you ask them about death and they're like,
I want to die so badly.
They're like, I fucking wanna die.
Except for Larry King.
Larry King was always, Larry King was very publicly like,
if I die, I hope I never die.
And he's 90, he was 91 when he died.
He was like, I'm terrified of death.
If I--
- To never get over that, oh that must be hell.
- To be 91 years old, yeah.
I like my entire life like, you know,
You have a fear of death and then you see old people like that and you're like, "Oh, okay."
So I guess at some point you figure it out.
And then Larry King is like, "You'll never figure it out.
It's always terrifying.
It's always the most scary thing you can possibly imagine just not existing.
It's so, so scary."
And then he died.
It's funny because Larry King is the scariest thing I can imagine.
Yeah, exactly.
Also, if I became Larry King, that would be the worst of my problem, or the least of my
problems.
I'm so scared.
I'm terrified of mirrors.
Yeah, exactly.
and the front-facing camera on my phone.
I'm terrified of my sons, they kind of look like me.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
But what was I saying?
Oh, yeah, I feel like by 30 I will arrive at that place
where I'm like, you could kill me and I don't care.
- Yeah, there's a point where you do what you need to do.
- How do you want to die?
- Probably like suddenly and unexpectedly.
I feel like knowing you're about to die
is probably the worst part.
- Definitely.
- I think like, yeah, if you know, like somebody like,
like if you're like being held up, like with a gun
and you're like, oh my God, I'm gonna die.
And then you die, that would probably suck really bad.
Even if it was like, even if like you,
even if it didn't hurt, it would be like,
I feel like that would probably be,
I mean, I'm sure the pain would be really bad, but--
- Pain, probably, who cares, gunshots.
- Yeah, but like, you know, like, yeah,
standing there and be like, oh my God, oh my God,
this is it.
And then it actually happens.
- You don't have like the release that would be like--
- You know who had the biggest balls of all time?
- Who?
- Was that guy who was on flight 93
or one of the 9/11 flights and like somehow used a phone
on the plane to call his wife and he's like,
"Hey baby, I'm pretty much going through there
"and I think I'm probably gonna die,
"but love you, all right, bye."
- Oh my God, yeah.
- That dude, the fact that he was not like trembling
and screaming and also was like,
"I guess I'll call my wife."
Dude, I would not think to call anybody if I was in that situation.
No, dude. I would be like, I'd be like, I would be the person who jumped out of the
Twin Towers because they thought that they might have a chance of surviving by
like, being like one of those cats who falls off of a building and
doesn't break their legs.
Yeah. Yeah, that's so depressing.
That stuff. I don't think so.
Just the phone call and stuff, so horrible.
Yeah. I mean, I love to laugh about that stuff, but hey.
That's the upside, right? Is that we talk about it every day.
Funny as hell.
I mean, that's low-key. I mean, it's the most depressing, horrible thing of all time.
I mean, but just imagine like that you do that and then your phone, that's like your
private last phone call to your wife and it's like what fucking like Milo Yiannopoulos posts
like every year.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, it's so horrible.
That's gotta suck, you know.
I think anybody who died and then like had their death
turned into like anything would probably be like,
at least at some point, be like,
why is my family not like rich, right?
Like if I was, anybody who ever got like killed
by a police officer, I would be so pissed
if my family did not become like billionaires.
You know what I mean?
It's like, dude, you're using my face and shit.
Even just like, I should be getting royalties from CNN
for just reporting on this shit.
my family should be loaded right now
art lightning round as we're over time here
and also a hand on death
was fixes its securities uh...
my honestly
sometimes if i go to do that showering only sitting down at my desk
and i smell my own balls yeah i just smell
my balls which is the dislike you know three-time i'm always afraid that i
somehow smell and don't realize it yeah because of their people there are people
there are people that
that uh...
But also no one tells you if you smell like shit.
- Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, there are people who will never know.
And it's like, I'm not gonna tell them.
- No, and we all know those people.
And we, and everybody else, when they walk in,
makes eye contact. - Yeah, exactly.
- And when they leave, they're like,
he smells like shit.
- Yeah, yeah, it's crazy.
It's such a, yeah.
- It's the funniest thing to be oblivious about.
And then sometimes those people find like,
significant others, and you're just like,
how did that person, they must be like,
made for each other.
This is some pheromone that I don't understand.
That is actually the most like, this is the horniest guy of all time or something.
Number seven, throwback Thursdays.
Love them.
Okay, great.
What is there to say that hasn't already been said about these?
Number eight, last things.
Don't know what that means.
Number nine, bucket list.
Visit cop world.
Well create cop world is it for me.
Yeah, that's good.
It's like a week two in one.
Number 10, aging.
I was thinking about this today though.
I think I would go get some poor kid's blood put into me if I was rich enough.
Yeah.
Right?
That's a no-brainer.
Yeah.
This kid is not going to miss his blood.
He's young and virile.
He'll make more.
He has a heart still.
If I'm 60 years old and I miss one boner, one of my 8 a.m. boners that I have every single
day and I have more than $100 in my bank account, I'm taking some kid's blood.
Absolutely.
Number 11, life goals.
I would like to be the most famous person on the earth.
- I'd pretty much like to be the superstar from the future.
- Yeah, that's what I'm thinking.
Number 12, the last one is zodiac sign.
- I think I'm an Aries Spears.
- I know, I'm a Cancer.
I'm a Cancer.
- Wow.
- Yeah. - Wow.
- All right.
(laughing)
- Bye. - Bye, everybody.