You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[laughter]
[explosion]
♪ Ooh, baby, I'd be stuck to you like glue ♪
We're not doing that.
♪ Baby, wanna spend it all on you ♪
I'm not starting that intro.
Nobody wanted to do this but you.
Stop singing.
I can see that you're looking at the lyrics.
You couldn't even remember the five bars that make up the hook.
I had to open them back up. I had to open them back up.
Because you couldn't remember the lyrics to the chain?
You couldn't remember the words "Call me Mr. Flintstone"?
Okay, I get it. Let me think. I guess it's my turn.
You were like, "Call me Mr. Jetson."
No, fuck. Wait, wait, wait. Guys, no. Hold on. I have this.
Just call me Mr. Bedrock!
No.
Fuck! No!
Call me Mr. Dinosaur from Flintstone. No, that's not right.
Call me Mr. Bam Bam. I'ma slam your ass.
Call me Mr. Flintstone. I have a bird alarm clock.
(laughter)
Or something like that.
- Okay, I get it, let me think, I guess it's my turn.
I guess it's time to put this pussy on your sideburns.
- I like the idea that Little Waves
is super into Hanna-Barbera.
(laughter)
- That's why when he's talking about--
- He's watching like Hong Kong Phu-Yi.
(laughter)
- That's why in Martians vs. Goblins,
when he's saying bitch I'm a motherfucking Martian he's referring to
gadzooks
that's it wait now what's his name?
Godzooki is loony
yeah he's loony tunes what's the little green guy from the
flintstones
uh...
alien
alien vs flintstone
gotta side bitch call her bow winkle it's gazoo it's not gadzooks i thought you were saying
godzooki which is the weird godzilla they made
now that i was like i was a little brother is not a late and i think i
we've we've talked about that we talked about that cuz i don't i haven't seen
any god's ability to talk about the but we talked about a lot about that
his name was god's you key
no you i don't think you told me that no you did tell me that
prequel name
he like he was the cartoon one that was like really stupid
I'm gonna eat that pussy like a picnic.
Back to that for a minute. You got the whole basket back there.
Damn. Yeah. I used to love watching, what was that show called, or what was that channel?
Boomerang. Oh my god, Boomerang. Dude, how do they do it?
so many old cartoons what's snaggle puss he's like yeah and he said and he says
exit stage right left yeah and he's like little Wayne would be like I'm a
I'm a snaggle that pussy yeah he'd say something like that. Exit stage left I'm a snaggle that puss.
Was it Adam Ant? Was that uh was that Hanna-Barbera? That was Hanna-Barbera.
Dude they had so many banners. I know. Lowkey Hanna-Barbera.
Okay, I just they're kind of their flop era
Googled Hanna-barbera cartoons and went on Google images and just the first image just seeing the amount of characters they have here
Nobody should be allowed to have this many cartoon characters. They had they had this is a gorilla
Look at that just sure Manila Barbera cartoons and just look at the amount of yeah
Well a lot of it a lot of it is because they had like shows like what's wacky racers where it's like
Oh, let's throw like a million fucking people in there. Yeah, we gotta have
- There's a guy here who's just Winnie the Pooh
wearing a fedora, who's this?
Who's this guy?
- Plus the name from Justin's was a bad name.
- Here, let me send this image link.
- Winnie the Pooh wearing a fedora?
- Hold on one second, I'll send this in chat.
This link, the guy who's,
he's on the left side of the image in the middle,
just under the one who looks like Morticia Adams
but green. - Oh yeah.
- Oh yeah.
(laughing)
- He's literally just Winnie the Pooh with a hat.
That's not Morticia Adams.
- I said looks like Morticia Adams, but red and green.
- I thought you called her Morticia Adams.
No, that's the gay lady.
- Yeah, it is you.
- So who's that Winnie the Pooh guy?
- That's me.
- That actually does kinda look like Patrick.
- That's Timmy the Poop.
(laughing)
- Timmy the Poop.
- Yeah.
- Just look at, dude, they have too many characters.
- Yeah, Top Cat.
there's here's a guy was seventy-seven by a red shirt
they got a frankenstein but he's blue
not a service this murder for him or burr i guess that makes i didn't know that
they got a snowman
who's this hannah barbara bitch and why she making so many packets
uh...
that is funny to have to to men who both have girl names and then you have
together
yet
that how unlucky can you get i guess that's why you get into drawing court
holy shit yeah that's the only escape you can find
yeah you're getting shoved and then you meet another guy your name's
hannah you grew up your whole life your name is hannah you escape from your
horrible existence by by drawing well here's the story the story was they
were they were getting beaten up in in middle school for having girl last
names yeah and then they like meet each other and one guy's like
uh like like i wish i could create a cartoon i have this great idea for a
family and then uh the other guy's like uh you know
that sounds great I have this good idea for the future okay well I got a better
idea what about the past I have an idea for a family let's say our ideas at the
same time yeah one two three future path the flint will never work yeah oh wait
Hanna-barbera was fucking Dexter's lab what yeah Hanna-barbera was Dexter's lab
they were cow and chicken they were I'm looking at the wiki they got a little
ronchie in later years. They were Tom and Jerry dude? yeah oh yeah they were Tom and Jerry
Scooby-Doo. Oh, we are Tom and Jerry Scooby-Doo. okay but Tom and Jerry I feel like is better than
every other Hanna-Barbera cartoon - like when I think of a Hanna-Barbera
cartoon. What if it's a bear and Stan Bears? Tom and Jerry and Scooby-Doo are the are the top ones.
Oh they did a Kira. That's cool. I had no idea. They did a scanner darkly that's
crazy that's insanely cool that's why Alex Jones is in it is he's a huge
investor he's in a scanner darkly yeah he plays a street preacher damn dude yeah
no link later Richard link later is like friends with Alex Jones dude if I ever
make a movie he's gonna be in it yeah yeah he's gonna be the main character
they may be no script that would be amazing yeah just let him just let him
go I'm just gonna be like what movie do you want to be the main character of and
then we'll construct like a like a year-long like Truman show type thing
where everybody's just acting around him but he's just doing whatever he actually
wants to do they got a droopy droopy dog master detective I just found they made
it they made Top Cat the movie but oh yeah so that it's a Mexican movie yeah
it's not it's not American and they made a prequel to Top Cat the movie it's
called Top Cat Begins and it's not it's not just a Mexican movie it's an Indian
Mexican movie. Wow. It's weird like certain Hanna-Barbera characters are like bigger
and like other countries like like Mexico like Top Cat's pretty big. Top Gato.
Top Gato is humongous in Mexico. Topo Gato. It's actually Don Gato.
shit wow yeah all right now you a whole now you a dawn mm-hmm damn all right
all right Don Gatto oh yeah so the Hanna-Barbera made the Godzilla series
and okay so the baby Godzilla I'm thinking of is Godzuki yeah I'm glad we
finally figured this out after like two weeks of not caring about it it's funny
the last couple episodes have just been us talking about 90s cartoons yeah I know
know that was one of the popular cartoon shows in Sri Lanka really mm-hmm
where is Sri Lanka is that that's in Mexico mm-hmm okay the language of Sri
Lanka is sinhala sinhalese and bad and top cats name in sinhala is pissupusa
I'd be fucking mad if I was a top cat is super pissic I'd be pissed if I like made
some yeah some TV show and then they yeah and they yeah and then they bring it to
Russia or whatever and they're like yeah just so you know it's called it's called
dookie dookie piss doo doo pussy penis wiener fucking fart yeah and you're the
and they think you're the... they think that's you also. As the creator.
They name the show after you. It gets worse. That's actually your name translated into Russian
and then they just named the show after you. Yeah they love they love your
creation so much but I mean hey you know the language that I mean that's how it
looks in Cyrillic and then the Cyrillic alphabet is just like a guy... the
letters look like a guy fucking your wife
what do you say you say acrylic did I I would say that is definitely on the on
the lower end as far as like pronunciation oh wait is that you think
of Krillin. Krillin mm-hmm Krillik is uh well it says it's now used for Russian
Bulgarian Serbian it's Ukrainian Cyrillic yeah it's a soft C yeah mm-hmm
I just thought. So what did you think I was calling you up for then? I don't know I
thought I looked at it for a second and I saw the word Orthodox so I just assumed
that it was Greek. I didn't realize there's other... I didn't know... you know what else?
You know what else is? I didn't assume that there were other Orthodox churches.
I thought there was like my whole life I've only heard Greek Orthodox.
This is what you thought about when you looked at the word Cyrillic.
No, I looked at the word Cyrillic.
You like transported into every moment of your life.
You have like the most powerful brain of all time.
You're driven by a Greek Orthodox Church.
But you just can't go from point A to point B, it has to go through orthodox churches first.
I want to get Pat into one of those brain computer interfaces, see what happens.
You know those things?
They control your brain with magnets?
A computer wouldn't work if it had my brain.
Yeah, it's just like the Karen computer from Spongebob and on the screen it's just like
it killing itself.
as soon as like my brain they plug a USB into my brain yeah you are probably them
if this is the matrix you are the most likely man to fall out of it yeah yeah
just actually yeah no they take me out because I'm causing too many
redundancies yeah the matrix and he's in the pod and he's just rolling over and
over and over to sleep until the thing the cord falls out of the back of his
head I just can't sit still just like have you seen that video it's like a fuck
I have to find it it's like a stripper and he's like a male stripper and he's
doing like he's doing like cartwheels but he's not using his hands like he's
just like he's this fucking I gotta find this video this is one of the best
videos so he's doing side flips he's like gainers yeah something like that
that's cool male stripper is definitely like I I would put any male stripper on
American Ninja Warrior and expect yeah I was guys any of them enter any of them
into the Mortal Kombat tournament it's cuz they'd like their entire job is like
like playing keep away with their penis and fat women they're just like
constantly doing like like NFL juking and fucking dodge all these women who think
they're in a fucking one of those one of those weird porns or the guys dressed up
like a bear I found the video but I have to look through like god he's supposed to
watch this I can't skip no he's a he's a porn star he's a male porn star and I
have to look through all of his like this he's posted a thousand pictures and I
have to look for his all I have to look through all of them to find this one
video okay I would like to see that ah but just that one video yeah hold on
this is a heroic sacrifice dude you're gonna get a purple heart let me see if
this works. I don't want to hear you Google anymore. I think I'm done with it
forever. Yeah. I've heard you Google enough at this point. Yeah. At least
switch to like text-to-speech or something. I think this will work.
All right, let's see. Let's open this up.
Whoa! Oh my god! Oh my god. Holy shit. Yeah, right? I mean, that's... he's... he is like...
He looks like he's in a kung-fu movie
Aren't you glad I found this also his balls are just flying. Yeah, I just love I love like the four women in the back
This looks like it's shot at like a high school wrestling it looks like it's in a quinceanera. Yeah, how do you not?
How how are these women sitting down? How are you not losing your fucking mind when someone does this in front of you?
Completely still are you not like like holding up a sign? It's 10 like it's
Yeah, the thing is the guy right before him did even more flips
Somebody help him the
Momentum he can't stop
It's gonna spoke you should get that guy to do mocap for a droideka in the next Star Wars. Oh, dude
Yeah, we're gonna edit this part out yeah, don't worry about it yeah, we got you
I forgot to edit it out. It's a flying green penis on the drink.
We'll say
We'll say it's like a new blaster, I don't fucking know
Yeah, they harvested enough guy that's a kyber crystal actually that's why it's it's flopping around like that
Damn dude, maybe I need to get into I feel like that's the easiest way to get in shape become a maelstrom
yeah I think that's the move because you also you're not doing the pole stuff you
know you're just shaking your so yeah yeah and then also male strippers also
get to dress in really cool costumes that's true that's so true be happy
more ever you want
A pirate take off all those fucking buckles?
Yeah, yeah, it's got like Victorian like frocks and stuff under your jacket.
It would be like a stripper version.
You know.
It would smell like fucking salted horse that's 50 years old.
It's just been on his hip.
A sexy nurse outfit, you're not wearing scrubs, you know, there would be a sexy, sexual fucking
penis butt.
That was a jewel hit.
Sex version of Captain Morgan.
Do you think there's a Jack Sparrow stripper?
Yeah, there's sexy Jack Sparrow.
Sexy Jack Sparrow?
Yeah.
Are you kidding?
But can he do flips?
Yeah, can he do this fucking shit?
He cannot do flips. No way.
I still have the video open.
I'm still watching it.
It's crazy.
Yeah, it really just bothers me that the women aren't just losing their minds.
Yeah.
Yeah, they need to be doing the worm, and they need to be in celebration, you know what I mean,
I mean for what they're seeing they're basically witnessing like like like a
Christ level miracle like in turning water to wine and they're just unfazed
There's one woman's just one hand down, but just touches the ground for like half a second. Yeah. Oh
My god, you know we need to do we need to invent a device where you can
See the different frames of him moving and in slow motion
So we can tell if there's any point where all of his feet are off the ground
Yeah, yeah, you know, I feel like I need to download this video. I don't know
Yeah, we need to zoom in just to see
To make sure just on different parts of his body just so yeah that you know, everything's in order
Yeah, and also to make sure that it hasn't been digitally remastered into and there's no
Maybe he could only do here's my theory right? He can only do this move completely naked because it's the
Momentum of his ball swinging forward
Pendulous balls all this clothes would all these clothes would burn off
That's how he strips do you just start spinning around
This guy definitely like doing this long enough discovered like the Higgs boson
Just from spinning matter
Yeah
See what happens see how fast
That's the last thing that's gonna they're gonna fucking like rip open the portal to hell at CERN or whatever so to see you get that
Yeah, we put black sonic in the fucking
Collider and we destroyed the world and now we live in doom
You know that picture that always goes around where there's like a statue of
Shiva like with her in like us in like a ring and that's CERN that's not Shiva
dude that's that guy. Yeah that's the male stripper. It looks like she has a
bunch of arms because he's going so fast.
Yeah fuck dude I need I'm being pushed into science to discover things about
this guy it's kind of amazing do we know his name it's Maisie the goat yeah ma Z
ee the goat xxx oh well you got to have the xx oh it's okay cuz it's um it's
It's Maze, like it's short for amazing.
- Oh yeah, okay.
- His name is Amazing the Goat.
(laughing)
- Okay, let me, I'm trying to pull up this guy's profile.
- He's not even a stripper, he just is an artist
who happens to be naked.
He is in no way a stripper.
- No. - No.
- All right, so so far, just scrolling
through his profile so far, no acrobatics.
No, he doesn't. He stopped...
He stopped posting the fucking acrobatics...
Well, I mean, COVID.
I think COVID has ruined his acrobatics career.
Wait, he's fucking all these women?
What the hell?
Don't they know what he could be doing here?
Look how short he looks in this picture.
That I'm sending right now.
Look at this effect.
They put a tilt shift on him so he looks like an action figure.
Oh, yeah.
Also, why would you...
Why waste your talents on fucking all these women?
these women right when you could I mean he is a monkey named Chulo he's a oh okay
this guy's amazing this guy no no that's why they call him amazing the goat I
mean he's fucking earned it this guy is one of the most powerful people of all
time he does have a monkey name that's where he learned his duty learned from
the monkey named Chulo Wow he oh my god he also has a has a salute at - this is
breeze him salute to this guy I mean I mean what a fucking hero dude yeah god
damn I just wish he didn't have all this sex oh he's getting his asshole Eden
lick my ass and let me pop my shit
just spin dude I don't want to see if you have an OnlyFans if you start to do
OnlyFans that is just him spinning and there's no sex
- Me too. - Instantly.
- Oh my God, I'll pay fucking $30 a month.
- $30 a month.
- I don't care.
- Even if it's weekly videos, dude.
- Monthly, monthly, I don't give a shit.
- Dress up in different costumes just like you would
for a normal-- - Santa?
- Dude, Santa?
- He tweets how does Santa travel across the world so fast?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I think I fucking know.
He's doing this spin.
- I have exciting news for you guys.
He tweeted, "Drop your PSN though."
- Oh!
game with him to be the place of war zone with the amazing the goat. Dude I honestly shout
out shout out to amazing the goat I hope he gets I hope we give him a little bump a tiny
the coolest guy I've ever seen the tiniest bump will ever give anybody at amazing with
two eyes seven one eight. Tell him who sent you. Sir sir don't tell him don't tell him
we sent him just tell him he's a hero don't even say don't even I don't. Say pot about
this army once he was a general no no don't even do more flips please yeah
please yeah I'm gonna reply to him right now please just flip please stop
fucking these beautiful women and their big asses I just want to see you flip
dog you're in the wrong industry he has a picture of himself wearing a DHL
uniform holding a glass of water and the caption is delivering dick worldwide
ain't easy I needed glass of water I want to see this motherfucker in the
Olympics dude yeah oh my god him in Sochi I want to see him fucking flip I want to
see him blow everyone out of the water he would he would do it - you could do he
could also he could be a multi-million a triathlete is for sure I want to see him
run a mile like that oh my god that'd be amazing
dude him doing like the hurdles he's doing the hurdles and he's jumping like
as soon as he puts his hand on the ground he can you imagine if you if you
had the ability to do that to do that kind of flip just being able to be like
oh I'm waiting in line to get into Market Basket because they're at capacity
I've been waiting 10 minutes I'm so bored
just doing it once and just not acknowledging it
do the way that he runs a mile like if he was in a race if he was in like a
a like a like a five meter dash or whatever or 500 meter dash he would be
charging up for like the first three quarters of the race just doing that and
then he lets go and then he just fucking he wins by a mile dude oh my god he's
cheese powering up yeah and then at the end I you I guarantee at the end of
every time he spins he vomits because his inner ear is so fucked up
he's unlocked in the fucking strip club he just pukes all over the stage. I guess that's why he doesn't do it more.
yeah or maybe he has just like perfect spinning legs at this point he can just
it just doesn't phase him i don't know i i mean he's he's not a man he's a god you think yeah
do you think he was like you think he's like born in outer space or something like in a space station
so like his body is like like a gyroscope in it or something that might be true like some kind of
thing where he's like used to different gravity. He was definitely born in zero-g. This is the
first zero-g man dude. That's fucking incredible. We've been talking about this man for too
long. I mean it's tough when you see something that just like makes you so obsessed. It's
a paradigm shift. It's whenever you when you see somebody who when you see somebody who
is better at one thing than you will ever be at anything in your life. Right. And that
if that one thing is just spinning in certain...
And by the way, his hips stay in the same place
as far as like height the entire time.
- The best part about this video is that
you see the first hand, but then he keeps moving
and then when he moves back, his hand is obscured
by this other woman, the woman in the front row's head.
So you can't even see the hand.
So he's just fucking, it looks like he's just spinning.
Like it doesn't even look like he's doing like anything.
It just looks like he's doing that just based on
like just sheer like power.
what if he's like I bet nobody could knock him over what if he's like a
superhero or like a demigod or something and he has like like unimaginable power
but so he can't he can't like reveal it but he's like all right I could I could
be a porn star and do a lot of flips though
believe me yeah it's like spider-man like getting using his web to take cool
pictures spinning to be the greatest stripper of all time
one time he's in a strip club one time and he accidentally it was flipping
accidentally just levitates like an inch off the floor yeah well that's what
happened he accidentally levitated one time while he was at a strip club and
then the owner came out who are you and he thought he's in trouble and he was
like you start Monday yeah I mean what an incredible story yeah get a new chair
chair going away dude listen you should get one of those gaming chairs do I'm
thinking about it hold on please don't this is one of those like get a gaming
chair this is one of those like old broken chairs that makes fart sounds
when you move like to too slow yeah I have every piece of furniture in my bed
actually or my my house all your furniture's on your bed no I do not keep
all my furniture on my bed and I arrange my apartment so it doesn't scratch the
floor well yeah that's what Jana Jana's very particular about the things that we
have we're getting that security deposit back one way or another put those
fucking chairs on the bed I put my wife in plastic so she wouldn't fuck up the
security deposit just wrap what if you oh man that's a good idea putting your
white and plastic. No, shrink wrapping your whole apartment. I think people have done
that. Putting like just a thin layer of plastic on like every surface. Yeah, again
you could just get away with farting all the time too. It's true. You'd be like, "Oh, it's my
cabinet." Yeah, there was a fart under the plastic and when I lifted it up and
shifted it, the fart came out. Wait, isn't it a fetish where people want themselves shrink
grabbed yeah oh my god people that the latex beds it's really where they put
the woman under the floor it's probably like ten times that video
that video where the guy is like he has the woman in the cage and then he puts
her like into the floor yeah yeah yeah dude it's how you it's like that's like
fucking like plutonium rod like activation thing it's like a robot
you know what it is it's a fucking evangelion entry plug
anytime somebody has a fetish that is just like
the house gets up
*laughing*
her dad is forcing her to go under the floor again
get in the house or mom has to do it again
*laughing*
They have to take the house to the grocery store. It's funny that that fetish is like as
close as the real world gets to like flatliners. Yeah. Like these people just
want to be so close to death. Dude, they put them in these fucking latex beds
fucking vacuum seal it so it's nothing but a tube, a tube in their mouth out the
latex hole and then they put like a fucking Hitachi wand on their nuts. Maybe
that's what it is. Maybe you die and then you go like fuck somebody in heaven and
you come back yeah no because you still have the tube in your mouth you're
getting you're getting your shit all fucking buzzed up in the back bed they
buzz you buzz you want I think my where's your body yeah what are you
talking about they put it on their nuts and stuff they put a wand on their nuts
what am I damn gay magician come on playa what you talking about right now
touch they put a touchy wand on their nuts while they're under the vacuum bed
That is some disgusting ass shit.
But what if you cum and it gets on your fucking leg, dude?
Right, like having to get out of it, like you're sticking to the fucking leg.
You know what, they like that. That's the thing.
When I was a kid I would just jizz on my belly.
I bet they're like...
I never thought about fucking coming into a piece of toilet paper,
so I would just cum on my belly and be like, "Ugh, it sucks!"
"Ugh, man."
"Disgusting."
I knew somebody who would just jack off into the toilet,
which always seemed so rude to me.
(laughing)
- 'Cause that's like, it feels like you could do that,
like, if you tell me that,
every time you use the bathroom in my house,
I'm gonna be like, you're fuckin',
you're cumming in my toilet.
I'm about to walk into a-- - You put your tip.
- The toilet bowl's about to look like a lava lamp
when I walk back in.
- You put your tip right under the water.
- Yeah, exactly. - And you shut that shit in.
- Yeah.
- Try to, you're in my bathroom making oobleck.
- You fuck the surface tension of the water
until you fuckin' cum into the toilet bowl.
- Ugh.
- Back to the latex stuff.
- Yeah.
- Like, I feel like,
we were talking about like, you know,
the diaper stuff and like how like,
oh, it's 'cause like your aunt saw you in a diaper.
- Yeah.
- And you like, like I, what,
what caused it?
Like is the latex thing just,
is that like when you were born,
your mom had like a really tight birth canal?
- In a past life, you were a pair of scissors
stuck in a plastic wrap.
- Yeah.
it's so hard to get out and you like I decided to become a buzz lightyear when
you want to you you want to get sous-vided yeah you're like damn all
right I'm gonna do that for the rest of my alright uncle Mike I see you yeah no
you don't subconscious and that's why yeah oh I did I saw myself doing that okay
that's right after that for the rest of my life the thing is any any fetish it's
like I find these things kind of fucked up because it's very prohibitively
expensive yeah one of these crazy machine fetishes yeah you know like if you
imagine being a poor person who just like what's a fuck a piece of gold so bad
I wanna fuck two shillings mate yeah that's gotta be that's gonna be a
nightmare dude or yeah what if you're born in the wrong time what if you're a
caveman who wants to be vacuum sealed and right wanded by a Japanese woman
there's no none of known of those three three things exist when you're alive so
you just have to wait yeah it's very sad I mean it's so it's so fucking weird yeah
yeah what would it like what would happen if you were like born as a caveman and
but and you're really you were really horny from Morgan from Darkstalkers and
and you're like...
It's a really good point.
...invent video games
and then you have to wait for DeviantArt
to invent it. I guess I'll go jump in an iceberg
to see if it works.
I mean,
the advent of technology
has definitely created
a bunch of fucked up fetishes.
No, see, that's what we're saying.
I think they existed before
and there was no resources.
Yeah, if you, when you're...
so much war you're a fucking yeah you're a surf you're like a surf in the dark ages
right and you try it you go to your I'm a serpent the dark asshole or whatever and
you're like hey I have I actually have a fetish for like a machine like boxing
the shit out of my balls like like speed bagging him and they would just kill you
they wouldn't write it down we wouldn't know that people wanted that but Leonardo
da Vinci was the first person who was like I'm gonna make some of this shit
happened. And that's what drove him to invent so many things.
I'm a serf in the dark ages and my fetish is being the damn king.
You would go to your lord and you'd be like, "Yeah, I want a machine to speedbag my balls."
And they'd be like, "Alright, you're a witch. You're sentenced to torture forever by our
torturer speedbagging your balls." Oh no.
Oh, I'm definitely a witch and I hate being drowned
Yeah, I
Hate being burned at the stake seriously. I'm such a my god. Oh pick a card
Yeah, yeah more more weight. Oh, I hate this so much
Okay, okay. I'm not a witch anymore. Oh my god. Giles. Cory was the first fucking latex guy. Oh, yeah. Yeah
Wow
Started in hey, Massachusetts, baby. That's right. Let's go man. Mm-hmm. Let's go. Let's go fucking socks kid. Let's go
But yeah, I wonder what what fetishes are just unattainable right now that we will see in the
Space you can fuck this space
Zero gravity zero gravity. That's even easier than space. Wait, you don't have to go to space. It's going to upside-down plane alien
That's gonna take some time. Mm-hmm. Yeah, that might take a little bit of time to find an alien
But then you can't then you can't be picky - what if the first alien would be right?
First alien looks exactly like your dad
My shitty white dad alien fuck
I guess this technically is my friend is like is I have to fuck this guy who looks just like
my dad right?
Your dad's at home watching TV and they're like NASA has uncovered a new alien and this
is a brave man made first contact we're showing exclusive video yeah and the only like ET
he has a very limited vocabulary you can only say son son son proud proud proud
that is that is foul that is not ready
He tousles your hair at the end too.
Yeah.
That's how they say hello.
Sports, thank you.
Great, proud, sports.
Pokemon.
What?
Pikachu.
And then you get home, you get home, you open the door, you're like, "Hey dad, I'm back
from the astronaut thing."
And you hear like, you hear him be like, "Oh, great son.
All right, I'm going to sleep."
then you like walk over to his bed you open the door and it's set up exactly
like Ferris Bueller's day off and there's just like a dummy
that we I mean we're wasting our talents on a podcast we really should be writing
movies and novellas oh man also also just changing reality yeah to be exactly like
that to be to be that what if that actually happened what wait I didn't
even think about that what if that already happens and that's why we don't
know about aliens that's a good point yeah yeah NASA was like all right we got
tricked by a dad into making us pay for him to fuck his son in space okay we're
cutting the program we're just giving up on all this that's why they keep cutting
NASA funding yeah little did they realize it's actually a very powerful
weapon they could use against North Korea yeah oh my god yeah you make that
thing that alien look like or make a little yeah Kim Jong il action Kim Jong
alien. No. Kim Jong Ilian. Like AT-alien? Kim Jong Ilian. Yeah. It's exactly like AT-alien.
Yeah, it's the same exact concept. Oh mama. You're uh, you ready to move to the Big Apple
dude? You excited? Yeah. Yeah? What's the wildest shit you're gonna do when you live here dude?
Are you gonna start working for the New York Times? I'm gonna get a slice. No you will not.
slice cheese baby.
slice cheese.
I'm gonna be slicing you, I'll tell you that much.
I just walked onto my local buljangles and I got a slice of cheese.
(laughing)
- Yeah, I'm walking down to the corner to the,
bojangles.
(laughing)
Gonna chop cheese at the bojangles.
Bojangles.
(laughing)
- Yeah, only real New Yorkers know about this.
What's your Bojangles order?
Yeah, hey New Yorkers, drop your Bojangles order.
Yeah, let me get a spicy chicken bacon egg and cheese.
They don't have Bojangles in New York, right?
I don't think so, it's a southern thing.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's one of the most fucked up restaurants of all time.
I've never even seen one.
It sells chicken named after a clown and then like somehow the fries give you diarrhea.
It's named after a clown?
It just sounds like it.
Oh, I got really excited.
Chicken clown.
I was like, uh, there's a restaurant that he's named it after a clown. I guess that's what McDonald's is. Nevermind
Who's a guy who was a king Oh, what about a restaurant owned by Wendy?
Would have the coolest restaurant ever if she had one. I had a when I was like five or four or five
We had a we had a basset hound for like a week
Bojangles, it was like one of those dogs that you get it like the mall
You know like the mall dogs that like like when malls used to have pet stores
You guys never saw a mall pet store
Hampshire thing I remember they did like a
Adoption
I'm sure they have all pet stores, but I've never seen one. Oh, yeah, like they're like puppy mills. Yeah
it's like it was like a
Like mall pet stores were like. Oh, yeah, they're a thing but there was like a
But it's like the saddest dogs in the world just in like cages in like these glass
Yeah, it always smells like shit because they're shitting dogs
And they can't give a bone because they'll try to kill themselves with it, right?
- Wait, we got a basset.
- Give them a safety bone?
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- A breakaway bone.
- They have to take the wiring out of their collars
or whatever.
- Yeah, yeah.
- We only had it for a week 'cause we got it for him
and he had heartworms so bad that they were like,
yeah, you gotta put it back.
- Heartworms is one of the most fucked up things ever.
- I know.
- It is nuts, dude.
You have to give a dog heartworm medicine
every fucking month or whatever.
- 'Cause it's like the food or whatever,
I don't know how the fuck they get 'em.
I think it's because they're so fucking inbred.
- They're so, dude, I was thinking about that.
I saw a fucking picture of like a,
I think it was a basset hound that I was looking at.
I was just like looking at like, the way like,
it's fucking, you can see its eye sockets
'cause it's so droopy.
And just like, compare that to a wolf.
Like it's nuts, dude.
- And it is really funny that just like,
there was one droopy dog and the guys were like,
oh, it's kind of funny.
- Yeah, let's keep it droopy.
- Let's try and make him as droopy as possible.
We've already done small and big and stupid.
Let's do droopy now.
The dog breeding convention, the guy who like, the guy who created the Rottweiler just fucking
giving a swirly to the guy who created the Basset Hound.
Like imagine, yeah, breeding dogs would be like, you know, like seeing a dog that looks
kind of like a pug and like seeing a dog that looks kind of like a husky and be like, yeah,
I'm going, we're going to push the pug further.
We have more pug.
Yeah.
Add more of whatever fucked up thing.
What's that?
I think they make pugs by impregnating dogs with orange juice.
And then a pug comes out.
What are those?
Oh, is it Shar-Pei?
No, they just make the pug moms just give birth on a ten foot tall table.
And the babies just fall out and hit the ground.
We made a dog fucking accordion and this came out.
Have you ever seen a Shar-Pei?
I have seen Shar-Pei from High School Musical. What a dime.
I looked up a Shar-Pei recently because I saw somebody tweet about it and I was like,
"I know they're not talking about..."
Yeah. "The Shar-Pei." Talking about THE Shar-Pei. Oh, yeah, these things are fucked up.
Those are the droopiest dogs of all. When they're puppies... They're not droopy, they're like...
fucking like...
nasty. They're just folds. Like their whole body is folds. Oh, Christ. It's like...
I like them.
I think it looks nice. This looks like a Japanese food.
It's Chinese. It's a Chinese dog breed. It looks like a fucking...
It looks like...
It looks like a brain.
It looks like a fucking like...
like Hellraiser thing. Here's an article called "Shar-Pays are a Genetic Nightmare."
I'm sure they are.
They're really fucked. They have so much skin. That looks like what's inside like a fucking alien space helmet in like a 50's...
Could you blow it up?
Could you like add air to it?
Oh.
to like make it a big puffer fish?
I didn't know what you meant by blow it up.
I was like, yeah can you
just hit that thing with a rocket launcher
real quick?
Look at this picture. It does look so delicious though.
Look at this one. Yeah, I think I would eat one.
If there was like a bun that looked like that, I would eat that.
Yeah. Oh man, can you
imagine how buttery it is?
It's just a dog's asshole, man.
Come on.
Can you imagine a foreskin on this thing?
Oh my god, that thing would hang down. That thing would drag on the ground
around like a fucking wedding can.
- I wish that I was like this,
get a lot of extra length I think.
- It's fucked up that nature, I guess it wasn't nature,
but that genetics allowed a dog that looks like this
to happen and it doesn't have powers.
- Right.
- Like that's the trade off,
I feel like it's like a Deadpool thing, right?
You can look disgusting and nasty and awful,
but you should get a healing factor
or be able to stretch or have mind control or something.
- It's funny that Deadpool's whole thing
because he just didn't want to have cancer. Yeah, who would not want to have cancer?
Just have cancer, you pussy. Just be a man about it.
Yeah, I'm bald already. It's not that big of a deal. I'll get cancer.
Imagine if a side effect of chemo is that people start talking to the camera.
One time Neil told me that anytime you have like a weird leg pain, that's cancer.
Really? Of course Neil said that. I don't know why that stuck with me so much
because I was like that can't be true. Now that's going to stick with me.
That is definitely one of those you guys know about that thing that's like
it was on uh I when I was in high school I listened to some like
radio lab about this or something but there's like a
mental like like I don't even know how to describe it it's like people convince
themselves that they have tiny little bugs living on their skin that itch them
all the time yeah they don't exist but people bugs it's like fibers yeah but
people will like you can you can also get like convince yourself that you have
them just by hearing that they exist it's so fuck I'm in a bunch of more galon
why like there those people are like like there's so there a lot of overlap
with like targeted individuals people they're genuinely insane like they part
of the thing of morgulons is that no medical no like yeah there's no they
won't acknowledge that they won't say it's a real thing but like so everybody
who has it like is constantly let's like at war with their doctor or whatever and
they like try they just like get they I see they fucking post in their Facebook
groups they post like here's here's what I'm my daily medicines that I'm taking
to to to like make the fibers leave my skin and it's literally like just a
fucking handful of pills and it's like some of them are vitamins but some of
just like random shit it's so nuts dude yeah as soon as you guys started talking
about this I felt a weird thing on my hand
was that I heard that on that podcast and then I was like isn't that kind of
fucked up that you're like sending this out to millions of people right yeah
you're just like yeah there's these things that like they just happen when
you hear about them sometimes and they come out of nowhere it's like it follows
those except yeah exactly.
One second.
Oh here's the picture I found it this is I sent this to Pierce this because Pierce is
the one who told me about more bonds in the first place this is this is somebody's.
Fuck.
It's turn your brightness down weekly.
Oh my god.
It's it's they call it is this a week weeks worth of supplements for you as well.
Oh my Christ almighty.
It's literally a bed cover.
I am not exaggerating.
This is at least 30 pills a day.
Jesus fucking good for them.
dude they take them all at once I don't know wait wait they chew all of them and
they taste good what they would take a barbecue sauce pill this is the sweet
baby's a jail capsule with barbecue sauce in it that doesn't sound half bad I
think I might I might take that yeah we get all the all the health benefits of
barbecue sauce you know I think it's did he get into your diet do you guys want
hear the list of what these pills are yeah they wrote it in the comments here
the names of all these pills trio mag o7 reishi trilo dine queer set in oil of
oregano collagen spirulina turmeric curcumin apple cider vinegar alkaline
balance d3 hair skin and nails probiotic prebiotic neem ginger root liver detox
vitamin c zinc citrate berberine selenium
i've heard of spirulina yeah spirulina is like grass
pickled sheet rock and splurging selenium is like a is like they make there's there's a guy who makes
swords out of that to conduct light energy yeah it does like a rock b fucking bismuth
Bismuth is a metal, pepto-bismol.
- Oh yeah, true. - The ingredient in
- Yeah, I know, this is your favorite science fact. - in pepto-bismol is metal.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, bismuth metal looks fucking tight.
- It does look really cool. - It looks like Minecraft.
- It does, yeah, it's all squares and shit. - Apparently people do take,
do take selenium.
That's weird.
Is that like one of those colloidal silver--
Okay, but I will say, this--
When it says, "This article outlines seven health benefits of selenium,
all backed by science,"
when you put "all backed by science" in it, I don't believe you anymore.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, it was just benefit. One, it makes the morgulons very angry. Two, it makes the morgulons very sad.
Helps prevent mental decline.
That's what I would try to do if I had a thing like that.
I would try to conduct psychic warfare on the morgulons.
I would try to just like punish my skin as much as possible to make them leave. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, just getting like in motorcycle accidents every other day. Yeah, dude. I just fucking I do all sorts of fucked-up shit.
I'm wearing like the most like like
Protective helmet like I'm wearing two helmets essentially and then just like just gunning it for a fucking a guardrail on a
Dirt bike yeah
I would wipe my skin with a Clorox wipes a lot of greasy ass white boys with this
so Morgan on thing don't wash they more they don't wash they more come on you
guys are really taking opinions on whether astrology is real for a bunch of
white boys with unwashed morgulons morgulons look at ash you need some cocoa
butter it's just the truth brother yeah we should invent one of those psychic
diseases to a new psychic disease yeah yeah I already have one yeah what is
called evil okay I don't think of that as really a disease more of a blessing
it's a sickness of the mind of a blessing from the devil if you ask so
you think it's good I think you think do you think it's you think it's good no I
think it's evil okay so you don't think it's a blessing then I think it's good
to be right evil it's a dark curse but that's good it's a dark curse it's a
twisted disease yeah you're so right but you would but I love it yeah but you
hate it you mean I love to hate it caught you slipping white boy mm-hmm
mm-hmm you ain't evil I'm evil or than you know I was evil way before Caleb I
am I am evil Senate fine let's do evil wipeout do you like that you and me
that's okay wait all right oh look we have to do a bunch of evil we have to do
an evil option of course. Okay, let's check this out. Ready? Okay. Ready?
Suffering!
No. Is that a Skeksis? That's not an obstacle. That's not an obstacle. You're the Emperor Skeksis.
It's evil. That's what you're saying. You're stupid.
Okay, so. You don't know anything about. You're being childish. I'm talking about physical, which
pretty evil if you ask me. I think Cameron's kind of, Cameron could be a Skeksis. I've been evil for way
longer than Caleb. Caleb is, Caleb
is using the evil lifestyle as a prop like you did with being a jock,
being a golfer, being a goth, we've seen it a thousand times before. He'll get he'll
stop being evil when he doesn't like it anymore. Me, I'm twisted to the core. I've
been fucked up in the head since the day I was born and I'm I'm like if Travis
Bickle lived in Boston. I'm like if Travis Bickle ate some pickles. No you're
not. Travis Bickle is not that evil also. Yeah. Yeah so. He just had a lot of
of ideas. He had some bad ideas in his head. I'm so evil that my body, my entire
body is full of blood. That's right. I watched, I watched, I watched I'm so evil
I watched Harry Potter and I cried when Voldemort died. I'm so evil my poop is
black. Yeah I'm so evil I have horrible stinky black tar diarrhea four times a
day yeah so just like like all the symptoms of like colon cancer yeah that's
just the evil leaving my body baby yeah you like sleep 18 hours a day so it's
pretty evil is poop leaving the body true having that like a Nike shirt no but I
haven't decided on what my new thing is gonna be I'm thinking now that it might
become a scientist what about a chef what about chef a chef you have to be too
smart I'm like a scientist yeah yeah what are you talking about what are you
talking about I'm talking about you should be a magician uh yeah you could
do oh oh I'm not gonna slide of Hannah I don't have any where I like a mentor
like a mentalist hair you could be a mentalist I could be really like think
of a number and you're able to go like no no I could not do a mental a mentalism
some
tricks like that to people at parties and they'll think you're very swell.
But isn't mentalism like don't I don't I like... Mentalism is where you
stare at your wife until she leaves the room. Don't I control like women's brains
too or something? Yeah that's hypnotism. Oh okay. Wait actually I, one of my younger
siblings friends are insanely rich and we got their their like Christmas
card and is there just like so evil he can't even think of Christmas
their winter solstice we could tell it's psycho because it's a Christmas card and
then also like a letter that's like typed up like everything that they did
so lame dude fucking yeah dude and it started with their New Year's party and
they said they said we had a great New Year's party that was roaring 20s themed
And we even hired a mentalist to entertain the guests
Yeah, what the who are you hiring a mentalist into what like come on I want to tell you know
Someone's really with all my kids just made like those are so rich that they just literally just become
Fucking great Gatsby. Did he have a list? I feel like he had a mentalist probably he had
He had a pool he died it
That's so true. I remember that book correctly. Wow, that is so true. Yeah, it's so do you remember how big that movie was when it came out?
Yeah, yeah
It's like it's like every every Boz Lerman movie is like that it's like it's a big event like like
Yeah, whose boss Boz Lerman is the director of the great Gatsby? Yeah, the one he did Romeo plus Juliet
also. Oh okay, I was just thinking about Romeo plus Julia too. Yeah. Yeah, he does sound, he does sound
like he's like, yeah, a salacious B-Fram's brother or something. Baz Luhrmann. Baz Luhrmann, if he was a Star Wars
character, he would be like, he'd be like one of those like, traitors that gets fucked over by like
the Mandalorian. Like one of those like, where he like, like two scenes later, like, like the
Mandalorian like drives like a speeder bike through his fruit stand and he's like, "Hey, what the hell?
Hey, I'm Buzz Lerman!
Oh, come on!
[Gibberish]
He's like reptilian, like he looks like
Bosk or whatever, he's like a Trandoshan
and he's just like, "Urg, de wa do da!"
Those are the real losers of the Star Wars
universe, the people who dare to have a
shop in the way of the-
It's so sick that they do that in every
movie, dude, there's just
a guy who gets his ship blown up and goes
[Gibberish]
Some fucking frog monkey
Monkey who gets his like like bowls of slime broken
Fucking hates the Jedi in the prequels
Just like at least the stitches like walk around and act like evil
Thing that the Sith do is raise a fucking tariff
yeah it's a Greek guy just yelling some Greek guy with four arms they just
fucking open the door to like to like a hot like one of those hot dog stands and
get inside and just start doing the maze the goat flip inside and just it is yeah
it's like the the scene that you sometimes see in movies with like
somebody is like having a fight in a
bathroom or something and they kick open
a stall and there's like a guy reading
the paper it's that but they do it
every single fucking movie. There's at least one
fucking person like that in every Star
Wars movie especially the prequel. Some alien
whose livelihood is ruined by it. Or like it's
like a droid it's like a droid that like
they accidentally power off. Yeah. Yeah
that's why Wado is such a powerful
character is because he finally takes
control. Yeah he's like he I think it's
like the Hutts it's like the Hutts no the Toydarians and then like as soon as Pat
looks up and to think harder about Star Wars I know that I'm in like humongous
trouble yeah yeah when you're like I'm like you're like I can't even like have
any visual stimuli that interrupts my star right train of thought right now
because every train of thought if I look at something I have to look up because if
I look at anything else I will fuck in I will think about that other thing it's
just you you know there's ibuprofen there's ibuprofen on my desk if I looked
at that while I was thinking about it I would think well think about all the
morgulons on your body yeah exactly exactly oh fuck but yeah the Hutts and
the Toridarians so those are like the two and they both live on or at least
Jabba lives on Tatooine and so does Wado so Tatooine if you if you hey if you're a
Jedi looking a looking to get looking for a challenge head to Tatooine head to
most nicely tattooing rack
it is so sick that that's like
i guess i would just are worse that's just like what good guys do
in movies
it's like the bad guys kill people in the good guys like walk around in like
smash clay pots to find coins inside
like that's just
that's what you're supposed to do
you're supposed to cause damage to civilian you're supposed to hear supposed
to like
skid your car down the street and like almost run over a
a small child or an old lady.
And then you don't, but you knock a water tower onto a guy's like,
like a fucking halal cart.
Yeah, yeah, Kermit the Frog's halal cart.
Umm, uh,
Mashallah, brothers!
I totally said that wrong.
Mashallah.
No, you don't say anything, right?
Yeah, I don't.
Yeah, other languages I really fuck up.
Alright, the Morglons are attacking me right now.
They're telling me to shit so badly.
I gotta go eat poop.
I wish I'd go 30 minutes without shitting.
What?
Wait.
I think me and Pat have a date.
Eyo!
Bye y'all.
Bye bye.