You're listening to Israel's number one pod.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[laughter]
[explosion]
Bongo.
Bingo bongo.
I'm still eating.
It's okay, dude.
I don't care.
Just sit it out.
This is already gonna be...
I'm eating like beets and stuff.
It's gonna be very...
You're eating beef?
Beets?
He's eating beef and stuff.
Why are you eating beef?
I'm eating beets like Dwight Shroom.
The cat's getting into your face.
Why do you not just put the cat in somewhere while you record?
I will never understand.
It's fine.
There's another room, right?
You have a two room house.
Yeah, but he gets freaked out.
What is that? How can you tell a cat gets freaked out?
He scratches at the door.
He's just hungry for...
He's trying to eat the door, yeah.
He won't eat the door.
He's trying to scrape a little bit off.
with their hands or their claws or whatever it's called their paws I
learned that there the other day that there's men's testicles have do you
know taste sweet and now I actually just learned this men's testicles have
Caleb's mouth on them. I didn't. They're covered in Caleb's slobber. Mm-hmm. It's not.
Annie, are you done? Okay. Yes, a men's testicles have... Your mouth on them. No!
No, they're not in... Why would you put testicles in your asshole? It wouldn't feel good.
Have you ever seen those videos? Yeah. Those videos of like the balls coming out of the butt?
What is that? What is it called? Booyah? It's called Caleb's favorite. No, what does he say?
Yeah, he says "BOO-YAH"
Oh, he says "BOO-YAH"?
Yeah, doesn't he?
Yeah, "BOO-YAH"
That's a good video
Men's testicles have
Your mouth on them
All over
Yeah, you know what?
Yeah, that was it
That's the fun fact
Say the actual fun fact
Say it
They have
the
right guys you're right what am I thinking I'm sick I'm here I'm supporting women
supporting women men I'm not supporting men I'm not supporting men only women
I'm sick I feel I feel good I just found a tiny gun whoa look at this okay oh
it's a pencil oh it is a well it's a pen yeah yeah nice try Patrick yeah you were
hey close but no cigar my friend that's what I wrote all my ciphers with yeah
you don't write a cipher a cipher no freestyle no I write my cipher Patrick
writes his ciphers I'm so fucking Patrick it's a special allowance with
his ciphers he gets so he's allowed to write them because his brain doesn't
function in the same way. I go to a different classroom to take tests. Yeah.
He goes to a different classroom to do his ciphers. Yeah, I go to a different
classroom for my cipher test. What did you get, what'd you get on your cipher test?
Eight mile. You got an eight mile out of a hundred? That's pretty good. That's not
Not bad.
Uh huh.
Um, I'm sick, I'm locked out of my, of posting on Twitter.
Um, so I'm just bored all the time.
And uh, the old lady has my Switch.
Damn.
Fucking whore.
She took it to the hospital.
So I just spend all day, um, just screaming at my dogs.
Poor dogs.
I just found-
Why don't you just play some board games or something.
Some what?
Some board games.
What board game would I play?
Candyland.
I'm one guy.
You can play Candyland.
You want me to play like that Pixar animated short where the old man plays chess against
himself but it's me playing Candyland?
Yeah.
Yeah, and I'm just running back and forth.
You can play Solitaire.
Yeah.
I guess you're right.
I guess that it's made for one person.
I do, I have been doing crosswords.
I have a big crossword book that I've been moving through.
Nice.
I have like a hundred of them so it's not a big deal.
I mean that's one of maybe a million that I have stockpiled in my house.
Yeah.
I have a lot.
It's so hot in this room, I'm going to take my shirt off.
What?
It's hot?
Why is it hot?
Yeah.
I don't know.
It's winter.
It's because he has the flu.
I have the flu.
I hope I don't have the flu.
That would...
Yeah, you have the flu now.
That would be sick.
You probably have...
You have guys flu.
Shut up.
You have the flu for guys.
It's like swine flu.
You have H...
Get off your phone, Patrick.
You have...
It's like H1N1 but it's HOMO. You have the guy's flu. H0M0? Yeah. That's funny.
The guy's flu. Yeah. I remember my parents when I was growing up thought that
Obama was using the H1N1 virus to enact martial law so that they could put
Christians in camps. Yeah that's true. Yeah I know but my mom thought it. Oh.
your mom thought of it first? My mom thought of it and then told
Obama to do it. That's a great idea you white bitch. And then he killed the lead
singer of broadcast. Of Brock Hanson? Osama Bin Laden. Yeah Osama Bin Laden the lead
singer of broadcast. Yeah. That's so crazy that people really died from swine flu.
Yeah it's a kind of pussy thing to die from. Yes. You know. I would never die from
swine flu. I feel like anything, anything, anything that doesn't make you bleed if
you die from it you're kind of gay. Hmm. You know. Yeah. Like if you die, if your
body can succumb to. What about Ebola? Um no that's cool cuz. Doesn't Ebola make you
bleed yeah I'm all your orifices it's true okay so but specifically it makes
you bleed out of your butt yeah oh my god turns you into a girl yeah Ebola
turns you into a girl so that people don't actually die they just turn into
girls but it's still considered a casualty yeah yeah what else can you die
from with no blood drowning that's lame yeah drowning swim just no fire you can
die from you can bleed from fire how do you bleed it's sharp think of how sharp
it is on the top of a sharp thing about sharp the knives of a flame are yeah
they will they will cut you and and get you get you bad I it really any like
illness except like pneumonia pneumonia will make you bleed consumption
consumption is gay no you believe from consumption you cough up you cough out
blood yeah but it's your mouth but it's called it's tuberculosis with your mouth
turns into a girl yeah I got stabbed in my stomach now is like a girl keep
bleeding out of my stomach it's like a girl yeah if you get a peptic ulcer
that's just your stomach turning into a girl yeah it's my time of the month
because I got stabbed and I'm bleeding out of my stomach at this time of the month.
I need 10 cc's of a tampon, STAB!
*laughter*
Sticking a tampon into your bullet wound?
And all better.
No, I'm fine. I'm fine.
And yeah, and then you're like...
Yeah, I plugged it up, doctor. It's fine.
They put the tampon in you and you're like, "What the fuck is... what are you doing? I'm bleeding to death."
And they're like, "You're always so grumpy when you're bleeding."
Jesus Christ, get a load of this bitch.
You know what?
You turn into a total cunt every time you bleed.
Yeah, I'm a doctor now.
Dr. Caleb.
Oh, don't even say that.
Paging Dr. Caleb.
Paging.
No.
Why not?
You have a doctorate in...
No, shut up. I don't. You have a doctorate in men's balls. I don't have a doctorate in men's balls.
Yeah. Where did I get my doctorate in men's balls if I had one? The Institute of Penis.
Hard Harvard University. Institute Hard Hard. Hard Harvard University of the Penis.
University of the Penis. University of Penisylvania. The Copenhagen Institute for the
penis state for the study of penis penis state is in a university for the oral
study of the penis in white poo you got your doctorate in balls from the
Frankfort school I didn't what the hell is going on with that mic oh my god is
it is it mine no I think it's mine I think it's cuz it's all bunched up damn
Damn, that's crazy.
You interrupted the flow of audio.
Yeah.
You're so stupid.
Um, anyway, you got your degree from the Swiss Institute of the Oral Exploration of the Balls
by Caleb's Mouth.
No, no, no, no.
You guys both have- At the Frankfurt School.
You guys both have degrees in guys weenies and peenies from the Weenies Peenies University
of Guys Weenies and Guys Peenies.
Hmm they call you the peeny you guys are the peeny doctors you're the peeny baby
and you went to weenie University and you got it you're a peeny baby dude. You guys are not even they don't even call you
doctors they call you dong-ters because you are doctors of the dong or cock-ters
even no and they call you or penis doctors. Dude you're a peeny baby.
You're a peeny baby. No you guys are you guys are you didn't even get to go to school you have a tag on your ear.
tag on your ear. You guys are pedophiles. You taught yourself the taste of balls on your
own. You didn't even have to go to school for it. It was like goodwill hunting, you
went into the classroom and you sucked the teacher's balls. And they're like, who did
this the janitor i wasn't classically trained i spent all day in the library reading various
penis books looking at the penises he sees the equation on the board and then he just goes over
to the equal side and draws a three and a close parenthesis.
Yeah, good Caleb hunting.
And then he hooked me up with gay Robin Williams.
Oh, I'm gay! I'm gay!
Ooh, ooh, I'm gay!
Yeah, and he talks about his husband all the time, my dead husband.
He used to, it was so beautiful, he used to come on my face.
It was amazing, the little idiosyncrasies.
Like when he would come on my face after I'd jack him off.
Throbbin Williams, that's what he's in that movie.
That's your professor.
And then Good Will Hunting, which is his name.
Good Caleb Hunting.
His name was, no, no, his name was Wood Will Hunting, his name of the movie.
Oh, okay.
Hunting for wood.
He's hunting for a guy's penis.
This is a good movie we're writing.
Yeah, and he goes to, instead of Harvard, or instead of MIT.
Matt Gaiman.
(laughing)
- Ben Aslick.
- Who else is in that movie?
- Harmony.
- Yeah, no, Ben Assfuck.
- Yeah.
- Ben Assfuck.
And the girl is a guy.
(laughing)
So, pretty genius. - Manny Driver.
- Manny Driver, there we go.
(laughing)
And--
I'd see this movie.
And that's the end of the movie.
Yeah, that's how the movie ends, is with the credits.
Yeah.
And Ben Assfuck is like, "I drive by your house every morning and I knock on your door
and I just hope to God that you're in there having sex with a guy.
And every day that I walk up there and you're not, it breaks my fucking heart."
And then Matt Gaiman is like, "Can I suck your penis?"
I've never watched that entire movie.
I only ever seen that entire movie.
That movie's about Boston.
I know.
That movie is a love letter to Boston.
That movie's a love...
How do you like them assholes?
You like assholes?
Yeah, of course I like assholes.
How do you like them assholes?
Just spreading his butt against the window.
the fight on the in the basketball court is just just about the guys are fucking
each other the two the two gangs yeah yeah and then he's yeah this is good
Caleb hunting yeah it's good Caleb hunting yep no we already we already
named it wood will would we would Caleb hunting we switched it back where the
wood Caleb well then I'm I'm this is a different movie that you would Caleb
hunting would Caleb hunting is about is about me hunting for around the the
forest like Elmer Fudd and I'm shooting a tree you're looking for big chungus no
yeah I'm looking for big chungus the animal yeah I'm looking for freaking big
chungus because you want them to have sex with you like an animals mm-hmm would
you want him to get you like a gorilla penis you want him to climb into your
hole like a monkey. Is he throwing up? I'm not throwing up. I'm just, I'm coughing up
shit and I'm just spitting it out. He's coughing up the cum from, from the gorilla. From Ben
Assfuck. You wanna, you want a little monkey to explore you all over? No I don't. No. Um,
no that doesn't make any sense. Unless he was my doctor and he was doing a checkup.
And he was a. And he was also a monkey. Still. He was a doctor but he's still a monkey. I
I feel like we could teach doctor or we could teach doctors to be monkeys.
I think pretty easily.
You want to be explored by a wild boar.
No I don't.
You want to.
No.
That would hurt.
They don't have a pose for thumbs.
You want a wild boar to ram into your tunnels.
That doesn't make any sense because they don't have any tunnels first of all and also wild
boar don't ram.
Okay, you want to you want a billy goat to ram your tunnels?
No, I don't.
I feel like sometimes you guys just make stuff up.
You want to ram a billy goat's tunnels?
Um, maybe if I was a veterinarian, which I've thought about.
You've thought about it because you wanted to test out different animals.
No, no, I don't want to test them out for what exactly?
Sex. For having sex with you.
Why would I need to test him?
Why couldn't I just have sex with him?
No, I don't. I wouldn't, first of all.
And I wouldn't need to, because I would be able to tell if I wanted to have sex with an animal just by looking at him.
But I would not want to have sex with an animal. I need to make that clear.
You want to touch a baboon's thing.
A baboon. So there, when you're talking about a baboon, most people think it's penis, but it also has an astonishing ass piece.
So, ask me, so which one would I be thinking of?
Yeah, Caleb's thinking about a baboon's-
Before you fucking say anything, you never think them out!
You're thinking about a baboon's astonishing ass.
It doesn't have an astonishing ass.
You just said that!
No, I didn't. It's a miracle of nature.
You're thinking about a baboon's astonishing ass.
I don't think about a baboon's whatever anytime.
Yeah.
I think about women's big red asses.
Women humans!
No. No. Not women monkeys. No and if I was to have sex with a kind of monkey I would have
sex with a chimpanzee because they have beautiful breasts, the women chimpanzees.
You want to do a fish animal style? No I don't want to. All right then what do you
want to do? I want to. He just said he wants to have sex with a chimpanzee. Oh
yeah right okay I don't say I don't want to I said if I if you would want to have
somebody put a banana to my head like a gun and said you have to have sex with
one of these you have to sex have sex with a monkey I would have sex with a
chimpanzee you'd probably go chimpanzee on an orangutan an orangutan would
probably be my second choice because even the men have big floppy boobies and
I could do as I please did they name them that cuz they're orange nope no why
They would have named him Orange Champagne.
Orange Tang.
That's...
I believe Orang is the name for ape in um...
In ape.
One of those languages.
Yeah.
In that language.
I know that language.
Latin.
I got a job in Boston.
Yeah, where?
I'm excited.
Say the address, the name of your new manager.
Okay, um, I'm just doing...
I'm just babysitting.
I told...
a good babysitter. Oh you can hang out with Dom you guys can become nannies
together. She's already a nanny and I'm already a nanny though so why would we
hang out? We're not nannying the same family. Speaking of jobs in one of my classes because-
You gave a guy a blowjob in your class? Oh yeah. Yeah you did. No listen to this story.
Listen this is an important story. I went to visit that day. He was the guest
speaker. We went, the teacher had us go around and say what we did for work and
this kid, like, what class? It's this, it's a class about the writings of Marx.
Penisonomics. I'm in freakonomics. Yeah. Weinernomics. This kid was like
talking about his job and he had a voice, he had like this kind of voice you know
and he like said this whole thing. I wasn't really paying attention. He had, he
he talked about his job and at the end he was like,
and I wouldn't usually talk about this,
but I feel like this is becoming more and more normal
in today's society.
I actually go on dates with older men for money.
(laughing)
- Whoa.
- And the whole class was just silent
and then just went to the next person.
It was so awkward.
- That's cool.
- That's just a crazy thing to say to a whole class,
I feel like.
- That's a normal thing to say.
- On like the first day.
- That's a normal thing to say on the first day.
- And I, yeah.
- You gotta get all of the ice broken.
Gus told me that like the first class he ever took in college he um the
professor's like let's go around and say your name and then the name that you
want to be called during this class and then like a fun fact about yourself and
Gus was like my name is Gus I prefer to be called the wolf and my fun fact is my
My nickname is the wolf and the professor called him the wolf for the whole semester.
That's awesome.
The wolf is a name of a demon virus that's going to come from space and infect the earth
according to ExoPolitics Ohio radio show.
What is that?
Really?
That's this radio show I found online that's this guy who just calls like he just picks
up a phone and like talks to himself on the phone for like an hour just about
aliens it's really good he also said that humans and pigs are gonna be crossed
and trained as fighting machines to destroy the world a pig is not who I
would cross a human with have you ever seen Bob and Rocksteady but yeah I know
that's what I'm talking about yeah what and also pigs love to eat things be bop
and Rocksteady think about how it could eat those are the pigs from the Ninja
turtles are they both pigs isn't one of them a rhino oh yeah one of them's a
rhino one of them's like a boar and he wears glasses they look sick and yeah
cool as fuck there's some they look sick and you take people what is that there's
a mutant pig person who like eats people yeah it's called Caleb no I don't eat I
don't eat people I'm not a pig I'm thinking of the pig I'm thinking yeah
I'm thinking of Halloween pig.
Who's a pig that eats people.
I'm trying to think of what this could possibly be.
I think the Halloween pig freaks me the fuck out. I'm gonna say it.
I'm terrified of the Halloween pig and his big orange pig face.
I'm scared of that pig. I'm searching the Halloween pig. I don't fear much.
But I fear that pig. Fear the Halloween pig.
Yeah, it comes knocking at your door. If you hear a knock and then an oink, you do not want
to answer.
No.
On Halloween night.
Yeah, knock knock, who's there? Oink oink.
The Halloween pig.
It's me, the Halloween pig. Lock your doors, lock your windows.
I'm looking at terrifying photos of the Halloween pig.
Mutant pig person.
Show, look up pig Dracula.
Pig Dracula. More like pigula.
Yeah.
Now you guys are both on your phones, so I'll talk more about...
So that guy, the Ohio ExoPolitics Radio, it's really good.
You should check it out.
I haven't listened to it in a long time.
There's like over a thousand episodes.
It's really fun to listen to.
He does a break in the middle where he just plays soothing...
Oh, there's Pig Dracula.
Yeah.
"Hampire," it says.
Oh, shit.
"Hampire?"
He plays soothing nature music for like five full minutes and is like, "Just use this time
to relax and reclaim your mind or something like that.
And then he goes back to being like, "And also there was a man who was taken far away from
the earth and came back and knew everything!"
And shit like that.
Are you guys off the computer yet?
Can- Dracula Pig and Farmville.
Dracula Pig.
Farmville.
I'm getting news that Farmville added a Dracula Pig.
And everybody is freaking out.
Everybody's frightened as hell and getting really afraid.
Oh my god.
Oh, it's that Danny Trejo...
Uh...
There's a movie where Danny Trejo fights the pig people.
*laughs*
That's what I'm thinking of.
Uh, it's called "Bullets Justice" or something?
Okay.
Bullets... that's his name.
*laughs*
"Bullets of Justice."
My name is "Bullets Justice."
*laughs*
I'm reading "Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde" right now.
Yeah.
And Mr. Hyde, the first thing that he does that's evil,
is he just walking and he just runs over a kid like with his feet and he just
walks over a kid and the kid goes like "AHHHHH" and then he just stands there and then the
people come up and go "What the hell are you doing?" and he's like "I'm really sorry"
and then he pays them a lot of money to not tell anyone
that he stepped on a kid. So he just steps on a kid he doesn't like... Yeah that's
the he does that and then he kills a guy those are the two bad things he does.
first night no the first night he steps on a pig and then he's really ready steps
on a kid I'm a kid sorry same thing in my mind you do call a baby pig a kid no
that's a goat nope all right you wouldn't know and then yeah the only
things bad he does is he's rude he steps on a kid and he kills an old guy which
none of those are that bad yeah yeah cuz let's go through it
- Old guy. - Steps on a kid.
So did he kill the kid?
- No. - He step-sons a kid?
- He just steps on the kid.
- He step-sons a kid? - Until,
what, is the kid okay?
- Yeah, 'cause step-fathers are evil.
- The kid definitely doesn't die,
but it says the kid cried and was hurt.
- Oh, that's fine. - Yeah, kids always cry.
- Yeah. - And then being rude
to somebody, I feel like he kinda,
he just did that by stepping on a kid.
- Yeah, well no, he's rude 'cause someone asks him
if he knows Dr. Jekyll, and he's like,
"Leave me alone," and closes the door.
And the guy was like, "I'd never encountered such an ugly and rude man in my life."
Dang, Mr. Hyde, he's off the sauce.
Yeah.
And then he kills who?
Why does he kill the old man?
I don't know.
It's not clear.
He meets up with the...
Somebody sees out the window.
He meets up with an old guy in the street and is talking and then takes a cane and hits
him with the cane until he dies.
Yeah, so that's by far the worst part of the thing that he's done.
But it's still not that bad.
And then he runs away.
He vanishes.
Well, he vanishes.
- He vanishes, but Dr. Jekyll is still around.
- What the hell?
- Interesting.
Yeah, those are the bad things he does.
And then he kills himself, I think,
which is also pretty bad.
- Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde are kind of like the Hulk.
- They're kind of like the Hulk and the Red Hulk.
- It's kind of like Cameron who at night turns into a girl
and he walks around downtown and he says,
"Oh, someone give me a kiss."
*laughter*
That took so much out of him.
Yeah, he's dying now.
Yeah, Caleb's fucking dying.
I'm not dying.
I'm... yeah.
If you guys could turn into the Hulk, what color Hulk would you be?
I would be the brown Hulk.
The brown Hulk?
Interesting choice, why?
All the same powers as the brown lightsaber.
Which are?
Lightsaber.
I
is
you um sorry I'm so sick I can't hear you because I'm so sick okay is there I
might blow my nose into a sock yeah why cuz it's it's nearby okay I put
somebody somebody not me put a hole in my air mattress so I don't know where I'm
I'm gonna have to sleep on the floor tonight.
- It was your sharp little clit.
- It's my sharp little nub that sticks off of my penis.
I do have a razor sharp penis.
- Yeah.
- It's like seven, it's like that thing in seven,
but it's really small.
- It's like seven centimeters.
- It's seven millimeters, yeah.
- It's seven.
- It's seven, it's a seven out of 10.
- It's seven degrees Celsius at all times.
It's pretty cold. Yeah. It's seven degrees Kelvin. I have the coldest penis. It gives you frostbite if you touch it.
I one time met a bodyguard, or not a bodyguard, a bouncer named Kelvin. Yeah, it's a name.
Yeah, it's a funny name. My brother and his friends in middle school
added some guy on Facebook named Agbanya Kelvin.
Agbanya Kelvin? Agbanya.
Would it be?
They forgot that he was still friends with them on Facebook and every year they forget and then every year on their birthdays
They get a birthday wish from a bug bong. Yeah, Elvin, dude. I have that from Shaheed Ali, you know, she's really no
He's classic. Have you said really old Indian guy who was adding a bunch of people in like 2016?
No still sir, maybe probably earlier than he tried to get the most friends
Well, you can only get five thousand a lot of people like there's no yeah, that's all yeah
So if you have 5,000, you have the most Facebook friends.
Exactly.
He's a very nice guy, but sometimes he comments on my stuff very rarely, but then every time
it's my birthday, he sends me a long message.
What does he comment on your stuff?
He's just commented stuff like, "Very cool, inshallah," stuff like that.
I'll find it, but there's a, my girlfriend's parents' church,
their church went to South Africa, I think,
on some missions trip.
And in Africa, everybody loves Facebook.
And so all of these people that they met in Africa
started friending everybody who was on their friends list,
like all the missionaries' friends on Facebook,
and started messaging us
uh... a lot
let me find one from
uh... some of these guys there was that one guy who kept calling me on facebook
and i want to have on the podcast remember what was his name
yeah remember what his name was i can't remember
wasn't gay kevin
it was definitely not gay kevin i thought that you added him because his name was gay kevin
No, he added me and started talking to me and then called me a few times.
Sorry, they were in Zambibia.
There's a guy named Malou Ngouni who just sent me a wave and then just sent me all these different
photos of him next to some elephants.
Yeah, nice.
And then I just heart reacted and he said, "Thank you, brother."
Yeah, they all call you brother.
It's really nice.
Yeah.
I love when someone calls me brother. Oh, Malou sent me another one and he
said, "Hey, how are you?" and I said, "Pretty good, how about you?" and he said, "Am fine."
You been to Zambibia before? And then he sent me a Merry Christmas gift. Oh, that's
very sweet. It was very sweet. That's a beautiful image. That's a beautiful image.
that's beautiful image that's beautiful image let's see I think that was oh and
then yes mr. C emoji see emoji mr. yeah or yes see mr. emoji see he'd said I added
you to message you I love you but don't know you so we are coolio yet come see me
sometime and we can be friends I will be taking tandem flights next year check my
Facebook page blessed be you nice and then he sent me a Stewie Griffin gif I
love blessed be you is a really good yeah and to a message gonna start saying
that to my mom I'm gonna say that in public I'm just gonna say it to people
I'm just gonna start saying shit to people I'm just gonna start saying shit
people in his name while shit to people I'm gonna go up and say excuse me your
shoelaces are unstapled what the hell and say sorry I'm a little bit random sorry
I have a your socks are I just got hit in the head with the pipe they removed half
of my brain from the middle. Excuse me ma'am. My brain's hollow. Blessed be you.
Blah! Blah! Excuse me ma'am. Hi, can I get a... God be with you. Blah! I always wanted
to do that, just start hissing at people trying to order food. It's really funny. Hey, how's
How's it going?
Let me get a...
I've been doing like weird smiles to people when I cross the street.
When somebody stops for me in their car, I turn to them and do like a really like weird
smile.
It's like it doesn't...
It's funny.
Yeah.
It makes me laugh.
Just imagining if I do a really good one and someone in the car is just like, "What the
fuck?"
It flips you off.
It starts driving and runs me over.
My oldest Facebook message is from Kevin Feranto, who is this giant autistic kid that was my
best friend in middle school.
It was in 2009 and he says, "Are you Duck Caleb Pitts from CFCI?"
Which was our school.
And I said, "Yeah."
What does that stand for?
Kentucky Fried Science Chicken?
Kentucky Fried Chicken Institute.
Oh, here's Shaheed Ali.
He said, "I wish you very..."
My last birthday, he said, "I wish you very, very happy birthday to you.
You are always happiness and smiling.
May Allah bless you forever."
And then sent me a video.
So right now, it's a video with multiple cakes.
And it's a British woman singing happy birthday.
it's just pictures of different cakes cartoon cakes they don't even look appetizing
yeah it's 30 seconds long. They don't even look like tasty cakes.
So and then he sent that and i said thank you so much good friend Shahid and he said
may Allah bless your days and your long life.
That's a really nice guy. Yeah sounds nice.
Trying to find it there's like a... I got a bunch of weirdos last year.
Oh dude i got that lady that uh you remember that fucking message where she's like
Hello, yeah, I need you to protect me. Oh, yeah, what was her Michelle?
I have Desmaine blu-ray messages. Oh, yeah, dude. Desmaine blu-ray is the best
Have we ever talked about Desmaine blu-ray? I don't think we have cool. Abaco. Isaac was the guy who I wanted
Oh, yeah, not gay Kevin cool about
Yeah, see how I got
Confused those sound similar this guy this guy named
Klein Hal just sent me random
Farside comics for like weeks and then videos of Jeff Dunham
And then a picture of kiss and I said, thank you. Is that kiss and he said yes
You tell me he sent you free farside comics. That's a come up and then he he sent me another farside
Where he circled the word dang and I said why is dang circled and he said I do that to words
I read trying to put it into a creative place
So it comes out like improvisation when I create or tell stories or make humor when I talk or work in this creative process
As an art of sorts it lots of fun mixing and blending material automatically. I am playing I
am playing and
Then he he sent a picture of a bear shooting a bow and arrow at a heart and said want to move that heart down
For me a little my friend
Yeah, he's pretty awesome
Desmond blu-ray was this guy that was in a Facebook group that me and
cam were in
That was cool. Was it which one was it?
Ascension fifth dimension ascension fifth dimension, which was just like a crazy like
basically like a conspiracy group and
Desmond would post stuff all the time about
Oh, I remember Ascension Fifth Dimension.
He was ascending and he was gonna go to, he was gonna like join a star and like become
one with a star.
And just, he would post this sort of like long drivel that didn't make a lot of sense.
And then people would say like, "Yeah, Desmond, awesome."
But then at some point, they kind of explicitly sounded like he was gonna kill himself.
Yeah, he was, yeah.
So it would be like, I'm gonna leave my corporeal form and join my place among the heavens.
And like I'm finally ascending.
And then people were just like, "Woo!
You go Desmond!"
And me and Cameron just were like, "Please don't kill yourself."
And then he disappeared.
He was gone for like six months.
Yeah, he was gone for a long time.
Then he came back.
Like the legend of the phoenix.
Like Jesus Christ.
Yeah, he came back, I remember that.
Like Jesus Christ from Superstar.
I just remember I got that message from that woman
and then it said "Mutual Friends
Desme and Blu-Ray."
Yes, you know that that's about
to be one wild ass
best friendship forever when Desme
and Blu-Ray is a mutual.
We gotta get Desme on.
I agree, I said we should try to
and then you said no.
I remember that.
Hold a grudge much, bitch?
Yeah.
Yeah, Ascension Fifth Dimension was a good page.
I stopped looking at it.
I still highly recommend.
My recent obsession has been with targeted individuals and gang stalking groups.
Those ones are scary though.
People in those are legitimately crazy and I'm afraid that most of them are going to
kill themselves or kill the people around them.
Those do border on like, these are the kind of people who do...
There was a I found a picture that someone posted that was literally just
trying to get like people who think they're being gang stalked to do mass
shootings like somebody posted a thing that was like it remember it is
completely okay and legal to kill the people who are stalking you like and if
you believe you are being watched by government hand handlers around your
life like just attack them and cause as much harm as you can it was like scary
as fuck is crazy yeah and it's just like this is all on Facebook right don't they
They don't crack down on this at all.
Yeah, no, Facebook, they don't crack down on shit.
They just have like one million groups that are just full of just like crazy people like
that.
Yeah, fucking meanwhile, I'm banned from Twitter for a week because I said that I wanted to
see Jameela Jamil's giant boobies.
God damn this fucking world.
The world's fucking this world now.
Literally a hell site.
Uh huh, literally.
Yeah.
I'm being gang stalked by Jameela Jamil's big titties.
I would like to gang stalk her giant big boobie bubbies.
I she she's she's a bitch for that.
For real.
Jamila if you're listening fuck you.
You're a fucking bitch.
There was one in one of the gang stalking groups there's a person who believes there's
a like a thing called um called rare females which is like a special species of woman that
has telepathy and tries to like destroy men and gang stalks men and they're
called and he wrote this huge manifesto about rare females that he posted about
all the time. It's a rare female manifesto. Yeah we should read about rare females one of
these episodes. I completely agree with this guy. Haven't even read it but I'm
with him. Shiny females. Mm-hmm shining blue eyes shining females. That's
terrifying. A blue eyes shining female? That'd be crazy. Yeah I know who she's
voting for. That lying bitch. What's her name? The one from TV. Blue Eyes White Dragon? Blue
Eyes Red Skin. What's her name? Elizabeth Warren. Elizabeth Warren? Yeah. Nice. Blue Eyes Red
Skin. Yeah. I'm gonna, I'm gonna, dude when I get unlocked from Twitter I'm gonna so fucking
own her with that one? Yeah. I feel like that doesn't make much sense out of the context
of Blue Eyes Shining female. Yeah, it does. Alright. Yeah. Stupid. What if it's like a
Yu-Gi-Oh card that says Blue Eyes Red Skin Dragon? What if there is a Yu-Gi-Oh card? And
it's Liz Warren Khaleesi? Yeah. What if there's a Yu-Gi-Oh card and you could... This is my
daughter Elizabeth Warren Khaleesi. There's a Yu-Gi-Oh card that's called like
ultimate friendship and on the picture and the card is a picture of Yu-Gi-Oh and
Joey shaking hands and the card is like ask your opponent if they want to
handshake and if they shake your hand you get like 1,000 life points and they
the
have
all the leftover chips from all the other bags and put them in one bag okay all
right you listening yeah they go into the trash can they find all the chips I
didn't eat the crumbs and stuff and they stitch them together into big full chips
and make a band together with with with thread with edible floss yeah no not
just regular no with edible for edible floss that's mint flavored because I like
the mint flavored floss. But then everything would just be mint flavored. Just eating floss.
Just pulling floss out of the container just swallowing it. That's pretty good. Swallowing
one long strand of floss. What is floss made out of? String. Really? Yeah. Yeah it's string
that they uh. String and flavor. They brush the strings teeth and then they give it to
you. It's actually, it's tooth, you know toothbrush bristles? Yeah. It's from the same plant.
The tooth plant. See that's what I was wondering. The dentist's plant. There's a dentist, it's
called dentata hydrania and it's actually, that's the name of it. That's actually the
name of it I've just discovered. This is a science podcast now. Yeah let's do some science.
I fucking love science. Let's do some science. Let's do a science experiment.
No, that's the first time I ever...
Podcast about list science experiment.
First time I ever interacted with Patrick was from Caleb starting fights on "I fucking love science."
[laughter]
That's true.
I don't remember that.
I was at work. I was at...
That's too long ago.
I was at... working at Clover at the time, and I was...
Uh...
Yeah, you were arguing with that guy, and then I was arguing with him too.
And then I was too.
What were we arguing about?
about you said but I was literally doing it like while taking people's orders at
work you like posted something and I fucking love science it was like yeah
this isn't true I work in a lab with this every day and this doesn't happen
and then like somebody responded like you were an idiot and you said like your
mind is is empty you brainless lepton and he went to your profile and his comment
on every post I do remember that that was my move what I would I would anytime
time there was a like a story posted about a scientific discovery I would just
comment and be like "Wrong! I work in this field in a lab daily and we have never
heard of this!" and people would just comment. And I remember you had one
about how dogs couldn't dream because they were too low IQ.
Yeah that's true. Yeah and then you have to have an IQ of 80 to dream. Dogs have a 40 IQ.
People got mad. I got in trouble in the Live PD Facebook group because there's a
"Everyone keeps posting about this dog that's dying, this canine unit that's dying, named
LORE, spelled L-O-R-E."
I didn't know it was a canine unit dog.
Yeah, yeah.
And I kept commenting, "I would never name a dog LORE."
And I was arguing with this woman who it turned out was the admin of the group that I did
not realize was.
But she was like, "You're being rude."
And I was like, "I don't get why anyone cares about this dog.
It's such a stupid name."
Shit like that.
I got a week-long ban.
If it's over I'm going to go back and comment.
I've changed my mind.
Laura's actually a great name for a dog and then when she replies I'm going to say "Not!"
and hopefully get banned permanently.
It's funny to dole out a week-long ban in a Facebook group like that when somebody's
clearly just being like a dumbass.
They're like, "Well, give them a week and they'll straighten out."
I'm actually going to check if the ban is up right now.
It might be.
Because that's, yeah, I do want to comment that.
Or I just want to go back and comment "Coward."
Which one's better?
No, not funnier.
Okay.
Let's see.
I have, uh, looks like for me I have five days, three hours left on my ban.
Damn.
That sucks.
Come on, son.
That's effed up.
One more day on my ban, baby.
I don't even give a fuck.
Damn, one more day on the ban.
One more day on the ban.
One more day until I can comment in Live PD and say I love lore.
I
Name for a dog though. I was thinking I was trying to figure out if it might be short for Lorenzo
That'd be a good dog like a girl or instead of Enzo
Yeah, yeah, well cuz I was just trying to figure out what it could possibly be short for Laura
Short for the Gore Burger show
Short for Lorman filler shut up doorman near
Yes
Lormann I keep getting emails because I forgot to drop all my classes when I took the leave of absence. Yeah, I
Forgot to drop them and I keep getting emails about this Norman Lear seminar class. I signed up for
Because I had signed up for a class about Norman Lear
Yep, because he gave the school enough money that they were like, well, we got to teach this fucker now
That's they have to teach about him. Yeah, that is truly nuts. I know that's a nut so stupido
It's a math class. Yeah
But it's you it uses Lear math
What is that nor mathematics nor mathematics where you have
You have laughs and giggles laughs plus giggles equals t8 equals primetime television. Yep, and
And that's how we made so much money. That's why we got famous. Yeah, he got a million dollars using
We it's a whole it's a whole like like
textbook that is just a bunch of like algebra questions where it's like
like laughs plus black character equals X and
You have to find out what X is equals dynamite dynamite
That's the truth was he did Norman Lear write good times. I don't yeah, I'll say yeah
He did the one, the show with Archie Bunker, right?
Yeah, yeah, Archie Bunker, who's like, now that I think about it, a total Donald Trump.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Archie Bunker's our damn president right now.
Yeah.
Because he sits on the couch all day.
Archie Trumper.
Yeah, he did good times.
Yeah, Trumpy Buncher.
Trumpy Buncher from fucking, uh, Holland, uh.
It's like Shumpo Gunshon.
Shumpo Gunshun.
Yeah, Shumpert Gustav from All in the Fartly.
All in the Fucker Family.
All in the fucking family.
Oh my god.
Albert Gorilla.
That's like a The Oatmeal comic.
All in the fucking family.
Remember The Oatmeal?
Yeah.
Remember that one about the mantis shrimp?
No.
The one where the shrimp can see really good?
No
All right
Why not why not why don't I remember?
All in the fucking family on Google images. It's just incest porn. Oh
Cool, it's just incest porn. That's pretty awesome. It's all just really old
really old guys
Last episode we talked about old family
Oh, I got like a cover of I'm on a boat by the Lonely Island and yesterday
I spent like two hours just watching a bunch of them. Oh, yeah, dude there. There's the did you see we're so in love
Yes, I saw we're so in love. I saw I got a mo. Did you see I got a mo where it's all the I did
Not see I got him. I watched a lot of not not parodies of the song but covers that were like
Like so there was one that was like a bachelor party and they just recreated the music video
Damn. Yeah and then one was that I found one that was like a like a like a metal
core band. Whoa. Yeah and it was I'm on a boat and they just had metal core version.
Metal core version and they had a guy. Gone heavy. Yeah. Whoa. Gone heavy. Let's do it let's do a
podcast about List Goes Punk. Yeah. We just changed the ID or the the birthdate on
on our girlfriend's IDs.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Podcast about Lisko's pop punk
and we changed it from a 99 to 2003.
- Eminem had a new album today.
- Eminem goes pop punk.
- Apparently he says the N word three times on it.
- Really? - Whoa.
- I saw a post about all the different lyrics.
He has some crazy lyrics on here.
- I'll say.
- I just finished fucking a fish.
(laughter)
- Let's see.
- Well.
- What?
- I knew Eminem was gonna say it one day.
- Say what?
- The N word.
- Oh yeah.
Here's one, but I'm contemplating yelling bombs away
on the game like I'm outside of an Ariana Grande
concert waiting.
- Whoa, that's insane.
- Damn, is Slim Shady back?
I think Slim Shady may have resurfaced after many years hiding in Dr. Dre's ass.
In Dr. Dre's ass, yeah.
He looks to me, Eminem, I know this doesn't make any sense, but to me Eminem looks like
Will Smith.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
Yeah, a little bit.
Honestly, a little bit.
he looks like iRobot Will Smith you know yeah yeah yeah cuz Will Smith is part
robot and that's Eminem's whole thing and that's how he raps so fast because he has a
computer chip and they plug a computer chip into his into the his his spinal
cord you plug Eminem into a Commodore 64 with a ribbon cable yeah he sits there
and he goes *makes weird noises*
They put a game shark in Eminem's brain so that he can rap like that.
Truly a rap god.
Yeah, the code for the game shark, just type in "rap god" and you can change Eminem's rap stat to 99.
Yeah, and you can unlock the n-word.
Yeah, which he just did apparently.
He just unlocked the n-word for his music.
it
Yeah, he uh, maybe he didn't I just saw I saw it was one of those those, you know, those genius things
Oh, then maybe someone had a feature. I'm sure it's a feature. Yeah that somebody oh
That's probably what it is. Yeah. Yeah, cuz that'd be a that'd be an insane late career
Move, that would be a pretty funny late career. I could see him doing it
Really really it would be funny
I mean if he's trying to like go back to his like if he's trying to be like that crazy-ass white boy again
You know that is that's the next step right? You know that's why it's funny like
He's trying to be like like an absent father now. Well the new album is called music to be murdered - oh
That is crazy white boy shit
Speaking of crazy white boy shit did I send you the the cipher from my hometown?
Yeah, the white rappers in high school.
Grind mode.
Yeah, I've seen some grind modes in my day.
Yeah. Yeah, that guy, the rapper from my high school does grind mode too.
Really? Yeah.
Shit. Was he in the video I sent you?
No, he's M.A.
Oh.
He does the boss in grind mode.
Oh, okay. Yeah, they did New Hampshire grind mode.
Is there any good rappers from y'all's high schools?
No.
I don't want to plug them because, uh...
There is one crazy people.
Do you still hang out with them?
with them. Yeah, my friends do hang out with him. And he keeps trying to get me to and I
don't really want to. There was a kid who became a rapper like this year that I used to sit
in the lunchroom with and he taught me this thing that if you take the Powerade label
off and you like glue it back together, you use like, you heat up the glue and put it
back together, if you slam it down hard enough on the lunch table it sounds like a gunshot.
(laughter)
- Yeah, he taught me how to do that,
and then we just used to do that in the lunchroom
as like a fun prank.
(laughter)
- That's cool.
What's perfect about that is that
everybody gets so used to that,
and so when they hear a real gunshot,
they're like, "Oh, it's just a Gatorade label."
(laughter)
We don't have to worry.
- Yeah, wow, there's a lot of Gatorade labels.
- Whoa, somebody's fucking popping off the Gatorade labels.
- That, and then you can do that with milk cartons, too.
if you say it is an automatic gatorade label if you slam the milk carton hard
enough it makes a pretty good sound
i don't know if he's the guy i got no no i got in front of i got in trouble with
my friends for throwing gummies on the ceiling in making them stick
uh... yeah that's a people class people do that you do with paper towels and
water and soap
uh... the at that point that was fun yeah i just did i did that a couple times
with those hand things you get from an arcade
or like a, you know those sticky hands?
You could just, they would live up there.
- Yeah.
- They'd just be gone forever.
- They'd like fall into someone's food,
like, three years later.
- Yeah, and those people thought that it was a real hand.
- Yeah, I just remember--
- Ah!
- 'Cause my--
- Fucking idiot.
- My, fucking, my lunchroom in high school was like,
part, like, they used it as the gym sometimes,
so it had a really high ceiling,
so when we got the gummies stuck to the ceiling,
It was like up there for like two weeks.
'Cause we got us stuck up there during,
like we had some standardized tests
so the schedule was different.
So we went and it was like,
we had lunch a period earlier,
so we were like, oh, why don't we just dick around
'cause we have lunch after this period.
- You have periods in your school?
- Yeah. - Girl.
- What? - No.
- Girl.
- But so we had like lunch at C period,
but then we originally had lunch D period,
so we just had a whole day of just fucking around.
- Yeah, you did have D period.
- No! - Lunch D, lunch,
- Lunch today is the period.
- Yeah, lunch is the period.
- And you get a big bowl of blood.
- No!
- Oh my God.
- And you eat it, and you ate it with a spoon.
- How many periods did you have a day in school?
- Shut up!
- How many periods did you have every day in school?
- Shut up, just shut up.
- I'm just asking, I'm asking about--
- We had up till H.
- So how many periods did you have?
How many? - Eight.
- You had eight periods every day in school?
- Whoa, dude.
You're like the most girl ever.
- Yeah, the ultimate girl.
- I'm not an ultimate girl.
You're right, you're kind of a shitty girl, but you have tons of girl stuff.
I got the gummy stuck on the ceiling and then I was friends with one of the janitors, his
name was Bruce Rumshottle, and I remember I got it stuck up there and then I pointed it
out two weeks later because I was like, "Oh my god, you guys, it's still fucking up there!"
And one of my assistant principal, who ran the Twitter account that I got in trouble
saw me pointing and then came over and like gave me like I had to clean the
cafeteria for a week so I just became better friends with Bruce and Bruce and I
were talking the like the day it happened Bruce was like I don't know how
you got the fuck up there. Bruce ruled. The school psychologists at my school were
named Miss Glotzbecker and Dr. Wisnitzer. The psychologist or whatever at my
elementary school she was a woman named Bart Hemrick.
Girl Bart. Most Bart's are played by women. She tried to get, yeah
that's true, now that I think about it, she tried to get me in trouble a lot. It
was like really weird, like she sat my parents down and she was like, because I
lied about not doing my homework for a really long time and she like sat my
parents down and was like. You said that you didn't do it. Yeah. No. But you actually did it.
no yeah I didn't do my homework I didn't do it I have your homework right here it's
all it's all aids it's straight as yeah I didn't do that
no but you are suspended she sat me down and was like what did she say oh she sat
me down with my parents in like a meeting and she asked my parents how
does it feel that your son lied to you and my mom went nice what the fuck do
you mean kids lie all the time? I got in trouble in like fourth grade for like
making this kid cry because I was like basically like stole his fourth grade
girlfriend and the principal got me into it I like had to go to the principal's
office because this kid was crying and the kid I think principal whose name was
his name was dr. wolf damn the world dude yeah the one from space dr. wolf he said
ah seems like we have a bit of a sexual player on our hands all right dr.
sexual player the sexual player has logged on dr. sexual wolf his first name
with sexual sexual wolf that's why actual that's my favorite Metal Gear
character sexual wolf we need you for a mission
one last time yeah have sex with me you have to have sex with the wolf that
created you he wears an eye patch over his dick
he's got otherwise it'll go it'll go beast yeah yeah it is a cyborg laser like
Cyclops is a freaking laser beam on its freaking head how does the doctor
Cyclops is dr. evil eyes stop the how do his eyes stop the lasers the glasses no
but he closes them he can just close his eyes - yeah his strong eyelids like most
I mean if you don't. Yeah, when did that develop?
I don't. They don't explain how he went through like most of his life. Just keeping his eyes closed.
Yeah, he should have been blind. Do you think he came out the womb?
He killed his mom. Came out the womb with the eyes gone? He killed his mom, yeah.
He coming out the womb with his eyes gone. He put a C-section with laser on his mom?
I bet are mutants born don't mutants develop their powers? Yeah, I think it's like I think he probably developed it through puberty then.
Yeah, like 13 or something. 13 or 14. Yeah, like 18, like puberty. Yeah, puberty at 18.
Yeah, like puberty at 18, right guys? Yeah. I think I hit puberty at 18.
They develop it whenever you can, they're legally allowed to have sex. So, changes by state.
So, like in Louisiana, you develop a power when you're 16.
Yeah. It's the age of mutant.
Yeah, the age of mutant.
Exactly.
Mutant consent.
Mutant, don't even say that dude.
That's scary.
You just got put on a watch list.
Oh.
Yeah.
Mutant consent.
Whoa.
That's crazy dude, that's the name of my new sludge metal band.
You better watch your language my friend.
Mutant consent, fuck.
I'm gonna have to use this tiny gun.
Mutant consent.
that's the craziest phrase i've ever heard in a long time i'm a i'm i'm that crazy white
boy now what other caleb thought he's caleb thinks he's the crazy ass white boy check
me out now eminem wins man he did i love all of his new i'm listening to his new album
right now I'm listening to the track the white Grinch goes to the white Grinch
takes down Trump by stealing his presents. White Grinch defeats orange Trump. I'm listening to bitch
slammer bitch slammer by Eminem. I'm listening to the new Eminem album which is called
which is called free Eminem. Eminem's in jail. And the first song is called I am in jail.
last song is I am NOT in jail anymore I am I just got released from jail I am free
from prison yeah Eminem was I don't like it here
Eminem was in prison if you remember the last Slim Shady album he there was a
skit where he goes to prison for being the nastiest bitch of all time the
nastiest Grinch he goes to beat - cuz he's - nasty ass fucker - nasty ass fucker
and he goes to prison and he gets a little bit of a nasty movie de nasty
ass fucker goes the other day I was laughing I was just like that movie that
movie let's go to prison came on yeah unlike Comedy Central it's from like
2006 and so every joke is about just like prison just prison rates all prison
rape jokes. But I just thought it was so funny to imagine somebody just like
getting actually mad about that movie. They were like I just can't believe that
they would make... I can't believe Bob Odenkirk directed this. Can you
believe it Bob Odenkirk made a movie about it? Y'all my favorite actor from Little Women.
Wow y'all really stand Let's Go to Prison. You do realize there's 50 jokes
about rape in that right? You do realize that prison is where bad people go. You
do realize they deserve it right you do realize prison is full of criminals
he's trying to eat the rest of my he's trying to eat the rest of your food yeah
I bet stop the episode he's clicking on the laptop oh he just opened he opened
this website I was showing Patrick about this woman who believes that her twin
soul spirit is Osiris reincarnated as Michael Jackson and as a picture is to
shoes she has a picture of her holding a sword and um and michael jackson's ghost is holding her
that's sweet yeah we should probably end the episode i gotta go yeah camera has to go have sex
um go listen to the new eminem album yeah it's called uh it's called one thing it's called
i'm the grinch it's called the male pussy so go listen to it called the male grinch
Yeah, it's called "White Guy Black Balls."
[laughter]
Go listen to it.
"White Guy Black-Ass Balls."
Yeah, it's called "I Put My Daughter in a USB Thumb Drive So She'd Be Safe."
It's called "I Made My Mom a Slave."
Yeah, he does want to make his mom a slave.
That's true.
I made my mom a slave.
"I made my mom a slave!"
I beat my sister up.
That was supposed to be Eminem, and then I lost it.
I made my mom a slave.
I can't rap anymore.
I've done enough rapping this week.
You got a rap in you?
That was "I made my mom a slave" was my Amir Vann impression.
I beat my sister up, I made my mom a slave.
I made my mom a slave.
I don't know how that happened.
I used to sell weed, my aunt is in her grave.
He just talks about dead women and selling weed.
What is he doing now?
He released some solo EP.
Really?
Yeah.
Sorry.
abuse van
yeah nice
is that he takes you to the little bit of the after consents yet
he takes it to his band and does mutant it's so fucking funny that he got got
for that shit and every song was on brock and he's like
there's some women in the know some terrible things about me
but i think it'll talk to the leaders like
i used to hate girls
dislike it alerted me a better person yeah
but i used to beat up every girl i saw. I used to beat up girls then i made all these gay
friends.
alright
yeah bye
Bye.