Hey everybody, Caleb here. I'm editing the episode this week which is why it sounds like
dog shit. Cameron is busy at the Chocolate Penis Festival. I do not have the premium
theme song on my computer so I will be doing just a rendition of it just to lead into the
episode. Alright, here it goes. If this is premium content, if you are not a premium
subscriber, return home and get a subscription to premium episodes. I repeat, this is premium
content. If you are not a subscriber, go back and get a subscription to premium episodes.
Okay, here's the episode.
Nice.
I found this action figure that I had.
Yeah?
You got a new toy?
Oh, I got a new toy.
That looks like half Boba Fett, half Chewbacca.
Yeah.
Is that what it is?
It's Chewbacca from Shadows of the Empire.
What's that?
It's a Nintendo 64 Star Wars game.
Okay.
when Boba Fett disguises, or Chewbacca disguises himself.
- You're already fucking it up.
- Yeah, I don't care anymore.
- No, no. - You really lost
- He disguises himself as a bounty hunter.
- At some point, these premium episodes
just become about Star Wars.
- Yeah, no, it's-- - Oh, I did have a question
about Star Wars I was thinking about this morning
I wanted to ask.
Did Kylo Ren have a Darth name?
- Darth, Darth, Darth. - No, okay.
- I don't think he did.
- All right, that's what I thought.
- Yeah.
- Darth. - Yeah.
Really shows how little they thought out
the
I
I'm gonna probably be like Darth the Lonely Island because I'd be like the funny
I actually I want to change mine to no you can't you're a mind. No -
Darth Lucario Darth Luke Skywalker. Oh, oh wait. I'm Darth mew Cameron won't let me use my freaking
Yeah, I'm already I can't see already because you were shining a fucking flashlight in my eye. I literally still have spots in my vision
Dude, you're gonna make him crash the plane. Yeah, you are probably gonna give me a migraine if you do that anymore
That's why I threw it over there.
Okay.
Yeah.
Did you see how bright that thing was?
Yeah, that thing, you could have knocked a Cameron out of the sky with that.
You could have given Cameron a migraine in the sky.
Yeah.
Wow, Cameron da woman.
Oh my god, Cameron da woman?
Cameron da woman, he loves to get migraines.
We have to stop talking about this right now.
If we talk about this, I have to go.
Or at least turn my video off.
I'll be drooling all over the place.
Cameron da woman.
Don't even say it.
You can say girl Cameron, that doesn't bother me.
But a whole ass woman?
Ooooo.
T minus like three days until I'm back in the greatest city on planet earth.
You're pretending dude, you're not coming back.
I'm not pretending, I am coming back.
I'm coming back. I'm coming back because I have an appointment.
Yeah, an appointment to pretend.
You got a dick appointment with the guy.
Yeah, I got a dick appointment with both of your moms.
No.
Yeah, I do. We're meeting up at the rec center.
With both of Patrick's moms.
No.
Yeah, with Patrick's two moms.
They're going to peg Caleb.
That's fine.
Both of Patrick's moms are going to peg Caleb.
I don't have two moms.
I'm realizing right now I didn't give the mechanic my key so I don't know if he's gonna be able to get into my car
but
He could figure it out. Yeah, I don't think good
He's gonna huge. Yeah. Yeah, he's all corn fed boy. Yeah, they don't make them like that up in Boston
Just a big motherfucker. What do you?
What do you mean? It's a just like, you know, just like six six and like
What about my cousin Timmy?
Your cousin Timmy?
My cousin Timmy is 6'8".
6'8"?
Uh huh.
How did you end up 4'1"?
His dad is like Swedish or something.
Oh, the Swedes are known for being the tallest kind of people.
Yeah.
Not...
Well his dad's not like Swedish, but like...
The Vikings, dude.
No, the Vikings weren't that big, it's just that the Indians were really small.
I don't know if they're Swedish at all. I just remember they had a thing at their house that said "Schmorgasbord"
[laughter]
I think I just kind of assumed like, "Oh yeah, no, like Jeff's side of the family is Swedish."
They just had a bunch of Legos.
Yeah, they're Swedish.
Actually, the plural is "Lego."
I don't care.
Shut the fuck up.
A bunch of people said that recently on, what was it?
Oh, your toy review video.
Somebody said that and I was like I never saw somebody be pedantic about that before.
About Lego?
Yeah, I never heard that before.
The plural of Legos is Lego.
It's like shrimp.
It's like shrimp, fish, or sheeps.
It's like Xbox.
Yeah.
What about Xboxes?
Would you say Xboxes?
You would say X-Bi.
X-Bi?
X-Bi.
R/X-Bi.
That's the sequel to r/gamers.
Yeah.
X-bye.
Me and Patrick were laughing about a guy named Mr. Damn Delicious.
Oh yeah.
Mr. Damn Delicious.
Mr. Damn Delicious Hut Shack.
And it's his restaurant.
Hut Shack?
It's a hut slash shack.
He can't decide whether or not he wanted it to be a hut or a shack.
You know what?
Fuck it.
We'll go name it.
I'm not going to name it.
name it both. It's yeah it's a hut and a shack. Mr. Brush my brush my damn teeth.
Mr. Brush that was mean. I'm Mr. Damn Delicious this is my son Mr. Too Damn Delicious and we
had opened this hut slash shack. Yeah and this is my daughter Ruth. Yeah my daughter
daughter girl, Mrs. Girl, Miss Lady.
Mr. Lady.
This is my daughter, Mr. Delicious Pussy.
Alright, too soon.
Yeah too soon.
Yeah I forgot that I killed her with all the sex I had with her.
That's why you can't come to Boston, because you have court dates.
The statute of limitations on killing a woman in Massachusetts is about to go out.
It's only three months.
You killed Mrs. Delicious Pussy.
You killed Mr. Delicious Pussy in an intersection.
That's why you had to get your car repaired.
Yeah.
I was running through an intersection with a huge boner and I ran into her car.
You were standing there.
You were standing in your car, first of all.
Yeah, I was.
I like that you guys have an audience when you're at the cat house.
And then one day, he might have been a prisoner.
Yeah, he might have been, but Fucker was in the window and he like started slamming his
grabber on the window.
And he was like slamming it at the cat and then like, I don't remember, I wasn't home,
I remember that, but Dom was telling me that like, she like stared at him like, "What the
fuck are you doing?"
And he just looked at her and then walked away.
He was trying to get the cat, dude.
He was trying to grab it.
He didn't know there was a window there.
He was trying to use the grabber on fucker dude.
In scary times these days. Yeah people trying to grab your cats with a grabber.
Mr. Grab Yo Damn Cat.
I'm Mr. He Yo, He Mr. Grab Yo Damn Cat.
That's true.
Now that you're in the neighborhood, now that you've moved to the new neighborhood
uh... we should tell you about Mr. Grab Yo Damn Cat.
He walks around with a name tag.
Yeah.
He has a trench coat.
is a trench coat and inside it fifteen more grabbers yeah yeah all in different
language all different all different on awesome paint styles luckily he had one
flames he has one weakness is one weakness which is very lucky that he
can't see glass yet doesn't understand when the pups
that's good it's good that c_b_s_ has automatic doors cusya
corporate record
It's actually bad, because he'd be in there just grabbing every...
Well no, because he can get into CVS because of the automatic doors.
Be like that scene in Good Time where the...
Where Venny Safdie just runs through the door.
Exactly.
I just found out that the...
Runs...
Through the window.
Dives through your window.
With the grabber outstretched.
I just found out that he's not mentally retarded, the guy in Good Time.
Yeah, he's the director of the movie.
Yeah, that really threw me for a loop.
Yeah, he's got, yeah.
I was like, oh, they got this guy from my school.
I knew this guy.
Yeah, from my classroom.
He was a famous director.
Yeah.
I thought it was Patrick.
Yeah, it could have been.
I thought it was Patrick's.
That was a really good movie.
That movie's awesome.
I love that movie.
I might like that movie more than I like this movie.
I think it's a good movie.
that I think I like that movie more than uncut gems to be honest I mean hey I
think I don't want to talk about I don't want to talk about uncut gems too much
because I know we'll just get into it with Caleb no it's also it's just like
redundant for pod yeah guys to talk about I enjoy I mean there's something
good time is like enjoyable to watch yeah good time and uncut gems isn't no
good time stressed me out a little bit more but it was I liked it more I liked
I like uncut gems because it wasn't as stressful as good times.
But then again I saw good time multiple times, I only saw uncut gems once.
That's true.
I love that movie Waiting.
Yeah.
That movie?
You know when Luis Guzman does the chicken skin?
He's like you gotta play with your nuts.
And Dane Cook puts his balls on the stuff.
There's that scene where he's like a little bit of guacamole for the steak and then Louis
Guzman's like, "Hey man, don't mix Mexican and Continental."
Then he puts his dandruff on it.
Exactly, dude.
That's what working in a restaurant is all about, is just putting all kinds of your balls
in your fucking nuts.
Showing your head chef your penis and balls.
It's about cracking your balls onto the skillet like an egg and then cooking that and serving
it to a nice lady.
And then you put your dick in balls through the, you take it and you take the jet.
The tamper, yeah.
You put it through the meat grinder and you grind your dick and your balls into a beef
patty.
No, no, I was saying the dish washing like jet thing they got.
You know, the handle.
It's called a sink.
No it's not the sink, the thing that you use to spray the dishes is.
The nozzle, the hose.
That's the fucking word I was looking for.
Hoes.
I woke up.
I'm Mr. Grill My Damn Dick.
I'm Mr. Grill My Damn Dick to a damn medium rare burger, baby.
I'm Mr. Panini Press My Damn Dick.
Yeah.
I'm Mr. P. P. P. Nini.
That's me.
P. Nini.
Mr. Penis Kebab.
I'm Mr. Penis Kebab.
I'm Mr. Penis Kebab Doctor... I'm Doctor... I'm Mr. Doctor Penis Kebab.
I'm Doctor Ruth.
I'm Doctor Ruth Penis Kebab.
Ruth Penis Ke... That just sounds like... That's just like an Indian doctor's name.
Ruth Penis Kebab.
Ruth Penis Kebab?
Ruth Penis Kebab, yeah.
I rewatched King Kong vs Godzilla again last night.
There really is like such an ins...
Oh. My... My...
Caleb just spilled orange juice all over his laptop.
Well, luckily you're the one. You said you'd edit it today. That's true.
I don't have time. I'm doing stuff after this. That's fine. I think it only cut out for a second anyway.
Okay. We could still hear you.
Okay, good. Well, yeah, I don't have... I don't have... I don't care. Okay, that's perfect.
You spilled all your juice on your computer. You spilled your juice? I didn't. You spilled your juice.
I take it back. You take it back? I... no, no, you take it back. I don't have any juice.
So you don't take it back. So you don't take it back that you did spill your juice.
I'm having some of the worst times of my life and I'm gonna blur my background so you guys can't see my house.
I think it makes it slower. Yeah when you blur your background, okay, then I'll undo it. Okay
I'm doing baby hurry up and undo it. Are we standing now we can see
Now we can see Caleb's ugly house, yeah, it is juice
Mr. Drinkin too much damn juice. Mr. Drinky juice
juice up I'd like to drink my damn juice. Mr. Caleb eats his own substance. What
substance is that? Where does it come from? It comes from your mom.
Nose, mouth, ass. Nose, mouth, ass and front. I don't want to say what the
front is but we all know. Yeah. What's my front? I don't want to say it but we all
know. Your front is what your back leaks off. I don't know that one. And let's
leave it at that. Are you guys talking about my thingy on the podcast?
Seriously? What thingy? Don't even say what thingy. I have one. Yeah your front dude.
No my front is my thingy. Your front is your front leak substance and you
drink it with your own straw, your own body's straw.
I don't, you guys.
You got a straw from the store.
And it ain't even reusable.
You guys are scaring me.
You guys are seriously terrifying me to a degree that I haven't been terrified in ages.
Yeah, what are you looking in a mirror?
I'm not looking in a mirror.
Hey, turn your computer on.
That's why you're terrified.
Your screen's not on, you're looking into a mirror.
I'm terrified of you guys.
should be. It's a scary time. Scary time to be a man. It's scary times out here.
Yeah. See, you can't even listen to a podcast nowadays. Without getting scared
immediately. Without being scared and terrified right to your bones. Mm-hmm. All
the way into your bones. See, I bet whoever's listening to this, you two got
scared even more the second time because you were expecting to never have that
Happen again, I got scared like a
Like a bat flew at me or if I saw a spider crawling along the ground you got coronavirus from a bat
I got beer virus. Yeah, I think this is might be the one coronavirus. I think it might we might know reached it
I think this might be the pandemic to iPhone app game. Oh, no, they won't because if you notice the
The notice only all the videos that people like falling over is all just like really old people
Like that's just who dies. That's yeah people who die when they get the flu. Yeah, I can it's not spreading fast
Like it's not like it airborne. It's just like it's probably just like a root born
It's this morning illness survive this one. You know, if there's ever a poop born illness, I'm going down with the shit
You know, it's not worth taking a break. The coronavirus is poop born
It's um, if it's really from what they're saying it is like a bad Corona China, but oh, yeah
Yeah, what is that? I don't know. I've seen that video a hundred times. The bat soup thing?
Yeah, yeah. It's awesome. I would never eat that. I didn't realize bats had teeth like
that. It's badass. It's bat. It's badass. Yeah. I would never eat a bat. I would eat
a bat if it was cooked and covered in chocolate. I don't think there's any meat that I wouldn't
eat. Yeah, that's a bat. I would not eat any brain because I don't want... I think if I
ate an animal's brain that was stupider than me, I would lose intelligence.
What's that brain disease you get if you eat brain?
It's called Cameron disease.
Mad brain disease.
I think it's mad brain disease.
Yeah.
No it's not.
Bad brains disease.
I think Bo Burnham must be related to Jeff Dunham.
Bad brains disease and you become a cool black punk.
Just thinking about that.
They're not related.
Jeff Dunham and Bo Burnham?
Probably his dad.
Yeah, that probably is.
i remember my my cousins last name is done and he's tell people school it is
that is just a
that must be so disappointed like anyone to win the over his house here
uh... yeah and it would wear our whereas people is your public's where's mister
arizona
where's uh... we're still at work so it is not only one stick
where is the uh... where's uh... the willie the pimp or whatever his name was
yeah
where's uh... was gay
g_a_t_t_
where's the and it was actually a killer in
just don't does not have a public meeting to get kevin
just don't have some killer pocket pop pockets
but my parents are not as they make me go what the fuck
yet mister chinese
mister chinese is an all-time great
is always
uh... uh...
retarded teacher
That was a really good one.
Yeah.
Yeah, I liked Dr. Amputee.
Yeah, Dr. Amputee was great.
Mr.
Gay Black Guy.
Mr. Gay Black Guy was one of Jeff Dunham's original puppets.
Yeah, he was one of the original puppets. He was like the early version of Kermit.
That was like his thing. Sam? Like when Kermit was Sam?
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, he was the, that was Mr. what was it? Big gay black guy?
Mr. Gay Black Guy.
Jiminy Cripple.
Jiminy Cripple was really good.
Yeah.
It'd be so funny if all of Jeff Dunham's puppets were just like, it wasn't just him just being
like racist, it was just him being ableist.
Yeah.
All the possible disabilities.
The puppets in the wheelchair, yeah.
Yeah.
Wheelchair Wally.
It's all wheelchair and then just a name.
I can't walk.
It's just like, "Jeff, what the fuck?"
"He's still making two million dollars or like a show."
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
It's so funny how like every ventriloquist is a Republican.
Yeah, Terry Fedor.
Terry Fedor, Jeff Dunham.
I think to be a ventriloquist you have to have a certain cutting view of reality that
liberalism just doesn't let you have.
I also think maybe just a certain criticism of society. You know, you're you're you're
We're all the puppets. You have to be, you have to be a good thinker.
No, no, the thing is they realize they are like, they are both the puppeteers and sort
of the puppets of like, you know, the Koch brothers and big money from money, money,
big money guys.
They're the puppets of laugh.
They're the puppets, they're the, they're the Muppets of laughter.
Titans of humor.
I hate it when people call a puppet a muppet.
Yeah, it's like it's a puppet, not a muppet.
I'm gonna call Dr. Thunder Dr. Pepper.
Yeah, that's like calling RC Cola an RC car.
Yeah, it's like calling Mountain Lightning a Mountain Dew, buddy.
They are not the same.
We are not the same.
You drink Mountain Lightning, I drink Baja Blast.
We are not the same guy.
My name is Caleb, your name is Patrick.
We are not the same.
I remembered this morning on the bus when yesterday Patrick was playing video games and wearing
a cowboy hat and I said he's playing Bread Bread Delicious 2.
Oh yeah.
I thought that was funny.
Yeah.
Bread Bread Delicious 2.
He's Bread Bread Delicious 2.
He is Bread Bread Delicious 2.
It's a good game.
That's Patrick's favorite game.
run around as a cowboy and he just buys food from various Indians.
It's a game where you have to barter to get new bread.
It's an open world game and you go around and collect things to get bread.
You eat bread until your horse can't carry you anymore.
Yeah, and then the horse...
But then you get to ride the mule.
No, the mule is too small.
the mule also because you're so damn hungry.
And then you get rolled around the wild, wild west.
You get rolled around the whole map by a woman named Bonnie.
So it's kind of like a Katamari thing?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then she's your wife and she has to dig through sort of a new butthole that's been
created by where your penis and balls are if she wants to touch it.
Yeah, that's in a video game.
And she does not want to touch it.
she doesn't want to touch it, but if you pay her enough bread, she'll do it.
She's also pretty fat.
That's in a video game, so it's not real.
No that's real.
That's what you do in real life.
That's in a real video game, but it's not in life.
No it's in real life.
It's what you do in real life.
Yeah, that's what you do for your job.
No, not true.
I'm going to come back to Boston.
I think I'm probably going to pick up kriyati.
Kriyati?
Yeah.
What is that?
It's a new form of creative karate that I have invented.
Yeah.
Karate, yeah.
It's where you can, it's sort of like karate but with more imagination.
It's basically you're doing karate.
It's karate that you can play.
It's karate, it's half, it's part karate, part play, all fun is what I have pitched it
as to the people we're going to be teaching it to.
I'm going to be doing Kung Fun.
It's like Kung Fu but it's fun.
You should do...
Yeah, I'm going to be doing Taekwondo, doing something fun.
That's another one I'm doing.
Toy Chi.
Yeah, Toy Chi.
Yeah, I'm going to be doing Toy Chi.
(cough)
Just like 30...
Just like 30 people dressed in gi on...
dressed in gis on the beach
playing with the...
with a Tonka truck.
(cough)
You okay?
What do you fucking think?
Yes.
He's not doing good.
I'm going to get back to Boston and I'm going to be doing Krav my favorite toys.
I'm going to be doing Hide and Seek.
Let's play some hide and seek.
Akido...
Akido video games.
How about Akido?
I-v-d-o games.
Capuware running around in the backyard with my brothers.
These are just the most... these are martial funds.
Yeah, these are just a few.
Martial fun.
Yeah.
Martial fun arts.
These are martial arts and crafts.
Martial games.
I'm pretty excited.
Krav Maga games.
Krav Maga games. There we go.
Krav Maga games is basically regular Krav Maga but you get to take a nap in the middle.
No, it's um, they're gonna add Krav Maga to the new Call of Duty.
And you can do Krav Maga instead of a gun.
Yeah, I think we should be able to, not only should we be able to play as women in Call of Duty, we should be able to play as IDF women.
The IDF should just be, just have like a 10 point like stat buff and be selectable in every
multiplayer game.
And you should, I think Call of Duty, they should make the IDF version of Call of Duty.
Yeah, Call of Shootie.
Call of Shootie.
Because they shoot.
Yeah, that's what they would call it.
Yeah, no, it'd be a call of Cthulhu because that's
Don't they worship Cthulhu?
Yeah, the whole thing. Yeah, that's the thing. Didn't they make they made a call of Cthulhu game, right? Yeah
Yeah
There's it's like a tabletop RPG and then they I think they made a few video games of it
They're gonna be one that I know is good in but it's an older game what?
What a good call of Cthulhu game? Oh, yeah, they had it on PC
Yeah, it was like 2000 like mid-2000s. Yeah, and you you you like go insane
That's sort of a dance the mechanic, you know, I go insane
On the you have demon in your brain now. I am insane
I've been playing game
Yeah, I hate when I play game till I'm insane me too I'm ready to
Ready to be
Back in the back in the States, you know, I'm ready to be the president
When I get back to Boston, I'm also running for the governor of California
Nice. Yeah, like I like the governor cool. Yeah, I
think
Every state should have a governor. Mm-hmm, you know
They had a mentor was the Jesse Ventura was the governor
Ace Ventura was the governor of Arizona.
Yeah, he gave animals the right to vote.
Yeah, he was crazy.
And he said "alrighty then" a lot.
He kept saying "alrighty then" and then every time he saw a trans person he vomited.
Yeah.
Him and the entire police force would just vomit for hours.
What a fucking awesome movie.
movie. Yeah, I loved that movie as a kid. I don't think I've ever seen it. Really?
We should watch it. I think I've seen the end of the second one.
With the vomiting? Yeah. You looked up that, you seeked out that scene. No, I saw the end of it because it was on
before, because it was on in the compilation of people vomiting and
trans people. Yeah. That Patrick watches every time before he goes to bed. That Comedy Central used to play.
day before the one hour they would play two Comedy Central presents and then go into Reno
911.
Yeah.
So it would be vomiting at trans people compilation then two Nick Swartzon specials back to back
which were both called vomiting at trans people.
They should have compilations on TV.
They should have the compilation channel.
That's what Pluto is pretty much.
That's true, that is what Pluto is.
Yeah, they have like the... there's an app that is on the Apple TV or my mom's house
that is called... it's called "Don't Think" and you just... you click it and it just plays
videos, just random videos that are like five seconds long and my little brother will just
click that and watch... watch videos on "Don't Think" all day.
And I'm kind of sitting over here and I'm like, "How messed up is this that there's an app
called...
It's literally called Don't Think."
So I have been thinking about an app called Think.
You open it and it's Moby Dick.
It's a blank screen.
It's a blank screen with a picture.
How come they never made a movie of Moby Dick?
They did.
In the heart of the sea.
No, they should have made a movie that's just called Moby Dick.
- They did.
- When?
- They made it yesterday.
- What?
- Yeah, dude, they just made it.
- Then I missed the premiere.
- Your whole thing is, you missed the premiere.
You were invited.
- Not worth seeing it if I missed the premiere.
If I miss a premiere, I never see a movie.
- I only go to red carpet premieres.
That's the only way I see movies.
- Can we promise that in 10 years,
if we're not all married,
that we will make a Moby Dick movie?
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- Can we promise that?
- Can we make one when you get back to Boston?
We'll make a Moby Dick movie.
I mean, realistically, what even do we need for that?
A bathtub.
A pretty big bathtub.
Not even that big.
A white whale.
That's Caleb.
No.
Caleb can play the white whale.
I am Ahab.
No, you're not Ahab.
I'm Captain Ahab.
You're not Captain Ahab.
Make a Moby Dick movie.
Cameron's the peg leg.
That's Ahab, isn't it?
no you have your the literal piece of wood on my leg
why do you want me to be on your leg when did he have a better way to
he has a peg leg and i know when did he have a peg leg here
neither of you know when did you have it
finally yes mail the main character page page two hundred
i'll be the entire chapter about whale blubber
yet the yet on the other hand melville
no you don't need to be the author is in in the fucking movie have you ever heard
of death of the author? yeah i'll do interviews. author isn't in the movie have you ever seen
the Grinch?
yeah mister seuss is not in that. yes he is
he played the Grinch. no he's not. he played the Grinch. he was in the he played the back half of the Grinch
costume. literally ace ventura played the Grinch and you fucking know it. no he played the Grinch's ass
yeah they had it was like a horse costume
Ace Ventura played the top of the Grinch and Dr. Seuss played the ass.
What if the Grinch was 15 feet tall? That movie would just be a kaiju movie.
They should make a kaiju Grinch movie. They should make a horror Grinch movie.
They did. It's called The Blue Grinch.
Oh no!
If they made The Blue Grinch I'd be so scared. Me too.
I would not want... If The Blue Grinch came to my house at 3 a.m.
i would not allow you to do it yet we watch this book in jay station videos
rate
what do you mean that guy who's like
my girlfriend is dead in our channel
we have seen
i don't know what you mean was to get our channel to one million subscribers
y'all do you think the plot to a status is that yeah there's a there's like a
you to refer kids who was in there
uh... jay station
i stay behind jay station
it is a basically
he just makes videos that are like
like uh... i i i bought a i bought a an african warlord on the dark web yeah and
then they'll still here like a knock on the door and be like
all my god you too
so that the door right now the best way
all all in all you tubers
who are like
like uh... like white dude you tubers
just like try to sound like they're mexican
that he's already had a little mexican voice yet we have a lot of
but you know what it's so it makes no sense
but he um... so he'll just be like oh my god youtube
look oh who's at the door right now and then they'll open it and it'll just be like
his friend yeah just like their friend who's just like a black guy that they put
like uh... like a halloween and more
like costume on of like uh... and he has like a big plastic gun
and they'll be like look it's a warlord let's make him play xbox one
him and his girlfriend. And his girlfriend, the entire time, his girlfriend is like, "What's
going on? What's happening right now?"
The funniest one was, this is before he had a girlfriend on the channel, but it was, "We
bought a child predator off the dark web."
Yeah, I love the idea that just the dark web is just only for just like, which I guess is
probably true, it's just for buying people. But not just people, it's for buying like...
of people. It's reminding me of Tekken characters. Yeah. Like different kinds of people that have
different movesets that you can just order to your house and they don't show, nobody delivers
them. They just walk over to your house. Right. They just get a notification on their phone and
they're like, "Ah shit, okay." Alright. I guess somebody bought me. Oh, there was a really good
one where he bought a copy of Minecraft off the dark web. Yeah. And it ends with Slenderman.
Oh my god, it's fucking terrifying.
Yeah.
With Slender Man in real life?
Oh shit.
No, no, like Slender Man in the game.
Oh.
But, um, fucking...
Oh, on Amazon Prime.
I found him because on Amazon Prime it has like all of his videos and it says "I'm Jay
Station Season 1."
Okay, so what do we...
So basically he says that his girlfriend is dead.
She died and all she ever wanted was a million subscribers on their channel.
So, I'm wondering, because he's going to bring the girlfriend back at some point.
I'm wondering what...
Oh my god, you guys, a million subscribers brought her back!
Oh my god, she was pretending!
No, I think my theory is that they broke up and he can't run the channel anymore.
Yeah, I mean...
I mean, I don't see why he would be lying.
It's he...
What the fuck?
These fucking gay ass guys keep coming and looking into the window to look at the cats.
It's so weird.
You guys look pretty funny in there, huh?
It's cause they...
I keep the window open cause they like to look out the window.
You should drop the shades on them.
Yeah, I probably should.
person comes up and yell at them. What are you going to say? I'm going to say get the
fuck out of here. That will scare people. That will scare the hell out of people. Get the
fuck out of here. I told you get the fuck out of here. It's not worth it. I hope he didn't
take a picture of my house. No he just was looking at me. When he saw me looking at him
I put my hand up to him like that and then he went away. He was just there for a second.
Dude, you have force powers.
Yeah, I force choked him through the window.
Yeah.
I seriously did.
We should get a prop challenge.
He's too far away now to ask, but I did.
People, whenever they look in the window.
We used to leave, we have like these toy axes, and we used to leave a toy axe in the window in our bedroom.
So it's like, all you can see is the shadow of an axe when you're walking down the alleyway if you look at our blinds.
That's totally think that you were like a murderer. They probably think you're an axe murderer like from Texas Chainsaw and Halloween
And that's that's why I did it so they would know not to come in
Yeah, they don't
You should have done like a gun
Yeah
It would be funnier if it was like you should absolutely get like an airsoft gun and just pointed at people when they
Look at you
Inside your home, it's not illegal. Yeah, it's stand your ground
Yeah, does Boston have stand your ground laws like New Hampshire?
No, no, Boston is like one of the one of the strictest. They don't have castles in cities
Yeah, you can't you can't even have a knife in Boston. Yeah, that's true
Fucking New Hampshire though like if you even walk on someone's property
Like someone can have like someone could have like 500 acres of land and they could just drive around on an ATV
the
You can just do whatever you want.
It doesn't really matter.
In England you can go on other people's property.
In England what?
You're allowed to walk through their property.
And they can't do anything?
Yeah.
What if you go so slowly that you basically just live there?
Then you get to live there.
Yeah, no, because squatters' rights laws.
Yeah.
I think it's a...
What if you move through their property at a rate of one inch per year?
Well, their property is only one inch. That's the maximum amount of property you're allowed
to have over there.
That's the max lot. Well, then that's even better because that means that you can just
hop from property to property one inch at a time.
Yeah.
I would totally agree.
Oh, yeah. Today we are going to announce something very special.
Oh, yeah.
This is a huge addition to the Hamsterverse.
Yeah, we're announcing the lineup for the for the 2020 Hungry Hamster Hamstravaganza.
Hamstravaganza, formerly known as Hamsterpalooza.
Yeah, Hamsterpalooza.
Hamsterpalooza, but we all know what happened to Palooza.
Yeah.
The co-founder of the festival.
Palooza.
Palooza the whale.
Yeah, Palooza the whale, who he was supposed to be on the lineup, but
He got stabbed in the eye. He was stabbed in the eye by a giant whale.
He was eaten by a bigger whale like in Phantom Menace.
Qui-Gon Jinn said that. Qui-Gon Jinn said that we're going to need a bigger whale.
Yeah, there's always a bigger whale.
So anyway, that Hamstravaganza lineup.
"Hungry Hamster" is headlining, obviously.
It's kind of like Maddie Fest, the Maddie Matheson Festival in Toronto.
Yeah.
Except there's an even fatter guy and he's a hamster.
Yeah, and his name's Patrick.
No.
Patrick the Hamster.
No, it's not you, it's just a guy named, it's a hamster named Patrick the Hamster.
Yeah, Patrick Doran the Hamster.
That's not who's there.
That is.
That is who's there.
That's who's there.
I'm looking at the lineup right now.
It's Patrick, Doren the Hamster, and then it's Dobrik the Dinosaur.
Yeah, Dobrik the Dinosaur will not be coming to Hamsterpalooza this year.
He's not Hamsterpalooza.
I just received the news.
Yeah, it's not Hamsterpalooza.
What happened?
He isn't coming to Hamsterpalooza.
He's going to Hamstravaganza.
Oh.
Dumbass.
Idiot.
Okay.
I thought that.
Dobrik the Dinosaur will be there.
That's right.
And a lot of, there's been a lot of, it's been a bit tumultuous because yes, we do realize
Dobrik the dinosaur is technically a villain and technically in episode 6 of the Hungry
Hamster animated series he did betray the Hungry Hamster.
But he's trying to reform his image, he's trying to realize the error of his ways.
He's trying to reform his image, yeah exactly.
And we think he's probably back on the, he's trying to earn his spot back on the legion
He is the anti-hero of the season.
On the legion of animals.
He has nothing to do with the candy hamster, we can't stress that enough.
The candy hamster, he is completely cut off ties to the candy hamster.
Although I am getting a little worried because I'm getting his request for tech for the show.
And Dobrik the dinosaur, it looks like he's asking, he's requesting in the green room
150 pieces of candy.
Oh no.
Maybe he's just hungry.
I don't know.
Yeah, you're right.
He could just be hungry.
I don't know.
I'm going to be...
And also, he also is asking for 50 pounds of C4.
Oh, he might be really hungry.
I mean, I hope so.
That's what, that's candy four, right?
That's candy four, which is the fourth level of candy.
Yeah, he's asking for 50 pounds.
Back to the lineup, another one of the headliners, Stained.
Stained, yeah.
Making a big comeback this year.
Yeah, it's gonna be awesome.
One of the few musical acts on the festival.
And Finger Eleven.
And Chavel.
Yeah, and Disturbed.
They have their own little stage, a little section.
Yeah.
uh... and their own solid hollywood and they're not playing any music can and i
can't stress that enough it's more than a few in a session
yeah they're doing a q_n_a_ session because they all have a new at coming
out together it's called it's called hungry hamster rock and roll hungry
hamster dot f_m_
uh... you can't let me know how to answer radio
when you contract you're listening to music but only for those bands yet
Yeah, yeah, yeah, and it's Hungry Hamster themed.
And there's rumors of a Facebook buyout,
so people hop on that.
Yeah.
That's our podcast about list tip of the week.
That's our financial tip of the week.
Invest in HungryHamster.fm because it's
about to go gangbusters on the--
I heard that they're still working out some tweaks on the UI,
But they the hamster button will work this time. Okay still there's still every fifth time
You try to press play on a song the candy hamster will
Appear and he will eat your music. He'll steal one of your mp3
He'll eat one of you will replace one of your songs with the song a weird al parody of the song
Completely and and that song the original song will be erased from existence
Yeah, there's never gonna be another version of unless you saved it to your files
Yeah, unless you saved it to your hungry hamster SSD. Mm-hmm. Yeah. Yes, we'll be on sale at the merch booth
Yeah, I heard that the tadpole twins are gonna make an appearance
on the Saturday
of the festival? The Saturday?
The Saturday day? Oh Saturday is Tuesday. With Rodney the fucking
rhino
is performing. Rodney the fucking rhino, one of the adult
one of the adult. He's the stand up comedian in the Hungry Hamster
but he does not get along with the tadpole. Rodney the fucking rhino is doing
he's doing like an after dark show
like you know
like uh... He shows his penis in the stadium. Hungry Hamster are uncensored
And so what they have is basically, it's like, you know how you have like the Muppets, right?
Imagine the Muppets but dirty.
But then you have like, you know, Cranky Anchors.
This is like the Cranky Anchors version of Hungry Hamster.
Hungry Hamster's After Dark.
And so what we're going to have is we're going to have, we're going to have, Adam Carolla
is going to host it.
he's hosting it and he's gonna come out and be like, "Ah, fuck you, hungry hamster!"
And then we're gonna have the hungry hamster, we're gonna let him let loose a little bit.
Sometimes he gets tired of doing all the stuff for the kids.
He's gotta do something for his mama bad.
Before the After Dark show, the Tadpole Twins will be there.
They're holding a raffle.
You can enter to win.
I believe the grand prize is a present, I think.
I'm sick of the Tadpole Twins already.
Okay, we're announcing the...
You don't have to...
I know, it's my show.
Why don't you like them?
I can express my opinions on the Tadpole Twins.
Alright, go ahead, express it then.
No, I think I've said enough.
No, go ahead.
I think I've said enough.
No, go ahead, come on.
Say it.
I've said enough.
What's your problem with it?
Patrick had sex with one of the Tadpole Twins, that's right, the guy one, and now it ended
on a bad note.
No, no, no, we have a history.
Terrence Tadpole and Tina Tadpole have a history.
And I don't want to delve into that right now.
Yeah, the history is that you fucked with the guy one.
Okay, well it's not that bad.
I mean, I don't know.
really mad and I don't want to delve into that right now.
Okay, well it doesn't, so what I'm saying is they're holding the Tadpole raffle, grand
prize is a present.
Ooh, that's all they could get?
And then they're- Oh, I'm sorry, Patrick, are you on the lineup?
No.
Guess who is?
The Tadpole twins.
Yeah, and- So how about you humble yourself?
Yeah, well they're just having a raffle, it doesn't matter.
Well they're having a raffle and then they're performing slam poetry.
And I bet you, based on the way you're acting, I can imagine that Terrence Tadpole probably
has a pretty fucked up poetry piece about you.
He has no poems about me.
He does.
Terrence the Tadpole has zero.
He is zilch.
He has nothing.
He's called My Ugly Boyfriend.
My Ugly Boyfriend by Terrence the Tadpole.
And it's about Patrick.
It's not about me.
Oh, oh, who's it about then?
I don't know.
talk about it. I haven't talked to them in years. Years? They're tadpoles. That's the
other thing. Tadpoles are children. I'm not going to say what they did, but... What'd they
do? I'm just going to say that if Trodney the tadpole comes near my toys... Comes near
your pole. It comes near my fish pole and my toys. It is also BYOT, bring your own toys.
If you want, there will not be toys for sale at Hamstravaganza. We could not get a license.
But as I said, all toys are welcome. Bring whatever toys you want. There will be toys
one beach ball
there will be one beach ball that uh... everybody can have a ten minute turn
with
we're trying to emphasize terms
and taking turns this whole thing is about teaching sharing
we're trying to teach sharing terms
and uh... and also so basically like there's going to be a sharing hour which
is it an hour of the day where everybody gets to share everybody's toys so make
sure you label everything
not on and then there's going to be free play free play is two hours long
shut up patrick we shut up
we shut the fuck up
okay free play is two hours long and it's basically we're gonna have a bunch
of playmats out
and a bunch of animal crackers
and you can just play your heart out
uh... and then there's a nap time
from one thirty to two thirty
and then basically and i i know that this is spoiling but the headlining the
second day
is going to be uh... is going to be
franklin the franklin of the fat fish
uh... and frankly the fact that she'll be playing policy always greatest hits is
gonna be playing deals deals deals
and uh... and he's got also uh... is also going to playing i love fish food
i love
uh... is it to be playing office sticks
and you know he's gonna be saying his favorite phrase which is office sticks
tons of times during the show
you know i'm just gonna say if he's gonna
perform uh...
the hell hell of a temperature
he's gonna be all i'm i'd believe he is in his office special screening
of uh... of uh...
the tuna
the two-day
to that movie
the
and uh... and everyone's invited
it's gonna be crazy year
for a hundred years
uh... working security we have peter policeman and his crazy cops
they're gonna be walking around doing candy tests just to make sure candy
hamster doesn't get his
people are worried that
Peter Policeman and his crazy cops are gonna do an Altamont on the motherfuckers, but we're
not gonna let that happen.
Yeah, and people are...
One thing we're really trying to mitigate this year as opposed to Hamsteravaganza's past
is playing and driving.
So basically you're gonna have to lock your toys up before you get behind the wheel.
Or bring a designated adult who can drive for you.
And if you've got toy keys, just forget it.
Just forget it.
If you have a toy car that runs on your feet, then you'll be okay.
We'll let you use that.
But if you have a big boy car or truck, then buddy, the fun stops here.
Last year we had over 150 playing while driving casualties.
It really wiped out, and we only had 200 visitors last year.
And then the rest of the visitors were actually killed overzealously by a Peter Policeman
and his crazy cops when he was trying to prevent them from playing while driving.
- Yeah.
- That was actually--
- No, 'cause that's what everyone said about last year.
They said, "Oh, they did an Altamont on these motherfuckers."
And I'm trying to say, we will not do an Altamont
on these motherfuckers. - Yeah, that was actually--
- We're not doing it.
- Palooza the whale actually was tragically taken from us
in a playing while driving accident.
- Mm-hmm. - Yeah.
- Let's have a moment of silence for Palooza.
- He just couldn't keep his hands off the toys.
- Yeah, let's take a moment of silence for Palooza.
- We'll do it at the Stravaganza.
- Okay. - Okay, all right.
- That's a good idea. - And then,
A lot of people have been questioning, like,
is the hungry hamster himself really gonna be there,
or is it gonna be, you're gonna send an imposter
wearing a hungry hamster mask, like MF Doom?
- Mm-hmm, first of all,
hungry hamster does not wear a mask.
- He doesn't, yeah, you might be able to tell.
- That's just what the hungry hamster's face looks like.
- He just has a hamster face.
I don't know how many times we can stress this to you people.
He is a hamster with a giant mouth,
because that's why he's so hungry.
He has to fill that thing.
He feeds himself.
So we definitely recommend bringing tons of food for the hungry hamster so he doesn't
try to eat your toys.
If he eats the stage again.
Last year was, we went through so many stages because the hungry hamster kept, he could
eat them in one bite is the issue.
So you don't even have time to stop him.
Yeah, he gets that idea in his little hamster head.
You see the wheels in his head spinning.
You see his hamster wheel spinning.
You see the hamster wheel spin and his head that has another hamster on it.
And he just starts munching.
But he is going to be doing a meet and greet on the last day, on day 15.
Day 15.
And that's the day that Stained will be doing their Q&A as well.
Stained will be doing a solo Q&A that is not a part of Hamster.fm.
It's about their new biography that was just released by Penguin Publishing called It's
Been Awhile.
called yeah and it's still stained yeah it's been a while the story of stained
still stand is the subtitle and then the other subtitle is how we got stay how we
got stained go go away god damn it dude we got to close the blinds we have
minutes left yeah all right they just want to hear they heard us talking about
about the lineup and they want a sneak peek before we upload the episode. It's just people
who are just a couple hungry hamsters themselves who are hungry for a little content.
Yeah. They want to see the hungry hamster shine.
They're trying to leak the lineup.
So let's get down to brass tacks. I know what everybody's asking.
How much is this going to cost?
Is it going to run you?
Well, luckily for you, we have day passes that are only going to be like 15 toys each.
But then we have a two day pass, we have a three day pass, a four day pass, a five day
pass, a six day pass, a seven day pass, an eight day pass, a nine day pass, a 10 day
pass, and then a 15 day pass.
We also have the whole enchilada package, which comes with one of each pass.
with one of every single kind of pass and as whole enchilada, which is part of the package.
The whole thing comes in a bag. You don't get a plate for the enchilada, we take it off
of the enchilada maker and we put it in the bag.
We put the passes in the enchilada.
What you can do is, we recommend you portion the enchilada out so you have 15 bites basically
and you take one bite a day.
There's actually an RFID chip in each byte.
Yeah, so we'll always know where you are and that's because one thing that we're trying
to emphasize a lot this year is no re-entry.
Yeah, absolutely not.
Not even between days.
Not between days.
Once you are in, you are in.
You don't leave.
And once you leave, you can't get back in or I'm going to tell you what, those crazy cops
are going to fuck you up.
They're going to tell on you.
They're going to tell on you to the teacher.
Every zone, there's six zones, every zone is going to have a teacher who will be there
to enforce that times and if anybody's getting rowdy during free play, basically it's going
to be the teacher's job to break up those skirmishes.
I know last year we had over 150 fights.
We did not have as many teachers as we needed.
We had barely any teachers.
There was an off-duty teacher, luckily, thank God, who was there just enjoying the festival.
But now we're going to have full-time teachers.
That teacher's name was Robert Jewell.
Robert Jewell, and he tragically passed away in a plane while driving accident when driving
back.
So we're going to have different teachers.
We also, and I'm sorry, but you guys forced our hand, there's going to be a principal.
There's going to be a headmaster.
gonna be a principal and if you if you play with someone else's toys that and
not during this the toy sharing hour the principal is gonna have to put you in
detention. Which is actually under the stage. Yeah, it's very loud and scary.
It's very loud, it's super scary and you don't get a parent to come with you.
You have to go alone.
So just keep that in mind, that we do have a principle, which means, you know, I don't
want to hear you guys, we have a strict no bully policy this year.
And only one crying per hour.
Everybody gets one good cry, but it can't be during the concerts because we won't be
able to hear.
you
- We hit you in the head with a pipe.
- On day--
- As many times until it makes you stop crying
or having a bad sound. - Until you stop crying.
- On day 12 though, we are actually having
a tantrum workshop,
to where we workshop different ways
to kind of control or improve our tantrums.
Whether you wanna have fewer tantrums or more tantrums.
- The problem with tantrums is,
you don't usually get what you want.
If you go to this workshop, we will teach you--
- That's it, you don't get what you want
when you throw a tantrum.
- You go to this workshop,
we will teach you the secret to get what you want
with a tantrum.
- It's all about, so basically,
think of parents as prey.
And when you--
- Well, don't give it away, don't give it away.
- You're right, okay, but I'll give a little preview.
When you're throwing a tantrum, it's a game, basically.
And your parents are the mark.
And you gotta think, what are you trying to get out of them?
Usually it's goldfish.
- Well, okay, all right, hey, hey.
Alright, I may be giving away a little too much at this point.
But we'll let the Hungry Hamster tell you the rest of that one.
It is a one-on-one Hungry Hamster workshop.
It's not cheap, but we'll be announcing the price of those tickets.
We will not announce...
That's actually a separate ticket to go to the Tantrum Workshop.
We will not announce the price of the festival until the end of your stay.
Yeah, we're basically...
You can stay in the Hungry Hamster.
We have a baseline price.
We're going to do a baseline price and then we're going to add on, every time you have
a tantrum, every time you use somebody else's toy outside of sharing time, any time a teacher
has to talk to you, any time you go to the principal, how many goldfish and animal crackers
you eat, and then you get deducted off the price for every minute that you nap.
So we're going to emphasize napping a lot.
Yeah, and here's another thing.
the first to implement the pay when you leave festival. We are, yeah, and that's why
there's no re-entry because as soon as you leave, you know, we're gonna be hitting
you with a big bill, you know, and that's why I, you know, check to see if
Hamstravaganza is covered under your medical policy because you're gonna need
some help, I'll tell you that much. You know, not even James Toy
himself has enough money to pay out of pocket for this thing. For lodging you
could you have two options you can stay in the Hungry Hamster Hotel or the
Hungry Hamster Hostel. The hostel is actually modeled after the one from the
movie Hostel. Yeah. It has a similar kind of consequence to staying there. And the
hotel is modeled after the Haunted Mansion. But they're both the same price.
They're the same price, they're equally scary, but one has Eddie Murphy which I
guess we probably should have been now Eddie Murphy is headlining day three and
he's doing his raw act. He's doing his raw act. He's completely nude and he's saying I
don't want faggots looking at my butt. Yeah yeah he's saying faggots sit in the
front so don't sit in the front because you're gonna catch you're gonna catch
Eddie Murphy's raw power. Yeah was that raw? Did he say that in raw or delirious?
They're exactly the same. He walks out both times and he's like "gay people suck so bad."
That's true.
That's like the whole joke of both of those specials. It's like "look how gay I look and
gay people suck." Because he's wearing the two gayest outfits I've ever seen.
Yeah, he said something about getting AIDS on your lip.
Yeah, you get AIDS on your lip. He said the people in the front were fags because they
sit in the front.
They're sitting in the front and they're looking at his ass.
Yeah, they're looking at his...
Yeah, it's like, well maybe because you're dressed like a fucking...
Like a fucking...
Like a dominatrix that might have something to do with the fact that there's gay men sitting in the front looking at your ass.
But he's gonna be there.
Yeah, he's gonna be at Hungry Ham's... Ham's Faganza.
And he's gonna say F-A-G-I-T.
Yeah, he's gonna say F-A-G-E-T.
Uh-huh.
Like the Korn song.
Just like the Korn song.
Yeah, he's going to be doing Korn covers.
Yeah, but just that song.
Yeah.
Anyway, is there anybody else on?
I'll be there, but I won't be performing.
Yeah, I can't make it to this.
I'll be wearing my special shirt.
If you find me and you give me my QR code card, I'll be able to scan it and give you
a free drink.
Johnny Bravo will be there.
and he will be walking around.
That Johnny Bravo cosplayer we saw at PAX.
Yeah, he'll be there. Johnny Javo.
He'll be there. He'll be saying what's up to people.
He'll be saying, "What's up?"
"What's up, bitch? I'm Johnny Javo."
That's his catchphrase. You know, you remember his catchphrase.
You all know it. You all love it.
He's going to be there. He's going to be showing off his muscles.
So, keep your toys away from him because he might crush them
crush them maybe in one quick feat of strength. With one crush. Yeah. One crush.
Probably one quick crush. But yeah, I think that's about it. Yeah. Right, so that's the show.
That's the episode. Well I hope you enjoyed and I hope we see you there. Oh, we
didn't announce the dates. We'll announce that on the next episode. Yeah. Okay, it'll
be sometime... We'll announce it. Sometime between March and June. Sometime between
March 1st and March 2nd mm-hmm mm-hmm wink wink yeah and it's 15 days yeah and
it's 15 days long yeah anyway thank you guys for listening we don't visit visit
pay a premium rate we don't yeah yeah any names okay well give us give us some
ratings on iTunes tell your friends you if you name-drop the hungry hamster on
iTunes and then you come in the discord and and and let me know and give me a
screenshot from the review, I will give you a secret Hungry Hamster emoticon that you can
use to react to people's different messages.
So I highly recommend doing that and grabbing this beautiful piece of history.
Yeah, and if you can't find the Discord, just message the pod about LIST.
I don't know how to...
Message Cameron and say Cameron.
I don't respond to... I need to get your money.
I don't respond to message requests. That's not true. I do.
Cameron will respond to all of your DMs. I'll respond to all of your DMs.
If you say you're a blissful to the podcast, I'll respond to them.
But if you say, "Hey, tell me the fucking cards and milk thing,
and I'll pay you in dank memes," I'll block you. And multiple people have said that to me.
Yeah. Okay. I gotta go.
Bye everybody, Hungry Hamsters for life.
(laughs)