You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
I'm not gonna record if you do that.
Really? Hey, wait, Pat, what is that behind you? Do you have a turntable?
Oh, oh, there it was there, boys.
What's that?
Wait, wait, let's start it all over. Let's, okay.
Yeah, so open that up.
Oh, he's accidentally doing something right now.
Oh, no, this is just an accident.
Okay, wait, we have an accident, guys.
Yeah, we have-
An accident is currently happening.
Patrick's having an accident right now.
It's actually taking him so long to do the accident, though, so it's not that- it's not
working that well.
Oh, he had to switch accidents and put a new accident on the accident table.
If you had, like, were holding your piss for a long time and then you accidentally peed
your pants, but it just came out so slow.
How embarrassing would that be?
That would-
Just one drop at a time, just slowly going down your pants.
I feel like that's easier- you can just say that's sweat, dude.
No, just you can just see it like like the spot on the front of your pants just growing just like so
All right, so you have a turntable that's the that's the accident prank that you pulled on us
You got it good dude. You got to do some djing during the episode
I should get I should go to guitar center and get like turntables. You should dude. Oh, man, I would not be mad
I would not be annoyed like I am by the bass or whatever
definitely I know no cuz also you can have it so you're having like a live feed
of the podcast like into the thing yeah like scratch and oh why didn't I buy
turntables the Grinch yeah that'd be sick dude that'd be so cool just
constantly every yeah just constantly shot every single sentence just that
would be so cool just getting about the brakes dude spinning down on every
single word. I think I might have already fucked up the needle on this just
because I'm like I've never... Yeah, what were you trying to use it to sew because
you're a girl? Yes. Were you putting it in your pee hole trying to fucking sound
with it? Yes I was. Because you're a girl? Yes. Speak it... talk about sounding I mean...
Caleb where's your fucking hat? My hat? It's off my damn head. Where... I fucking I
buy you a hat you don't even wear it. My kingdom's art hat? You don't even wear it?
Kill 30 seconds I got this. Okay. Okay. He's going to get his hat. God, it's so mean.
Like I get him something. It was, it was a, looked like a really expensive hat. It
was. It was so expensive. It had a, $6. It had a special unique marking on the back too.
Yeah. That was really beautiful. It was, it's put there by a graffiti tagger. It was
tie-dyed. Yeah. There it is. This is a very rare hat. You see it started to get tie-dyed
in the factory but they took it out early so it only got two dots of tie-dye on it so
it's worth a lot of money. I'm back. See, I put him on. It's a good hat. It looks good
on you. Dude, Pat literally puts me on game like two, three times a year he puts me on
game. Bought me that gnome outfit. This kingdom hearts hat. I only brought half the gnome
outfit back to New York. What the fuck? It wouldn't fit in my suitcase. I had to decide
between my favorite shirt or half the gnome outfit. Put it in a grocery bag and bring
it home. I can have my mom ship it to me I guess, but that's fucking crazy. That's so
fucked up that you didn't bring the gnome. How much space does a gnome outfit take up?
It's a huge gnome outfit. It's not that big. It's really thick felt. That's true, it is
a very big I did buy the biggest one I could not fit it in my suitcase yeah and
I was Pat I was I was packed to the gills you had a wrap dude your suitcase is
just a little walnut shell that you pull around on a string because you're one
foot tall that's not true actually it is for that one trip that I took a walnut
on but the rest of my trips that's that's just not true and you're making
shit up again completely true you call it your nutcase I don't call it my
nutcase although if I did that'd be a pretty funny name for it that would be
That is disrespectful on this day and you know it.
What?
Come on.
Look, I look like DMX and he looks like Prince Philip.
I have a cool kind of flat brim hip hop Kingdom Hearts hat on and he has a thing that says
"Turkish Princess"?
Irish Princess.
That's my bad.
I have an Irish Princess crown.
You're a Turkish American princess.
I have my Irish Princess crown over my Boston fitted.
That's pretty much the most Irish shit I've ever heard, dude.
Oh, yeah, I'm celebrating Prince Philip's death.
- Boy's a human car bomb right now.
Look at him.
Sheeeet.
- That's right.
- Looking good, dude.
Damn.
What are we gonna do with these celebrity deaths, man?
What's the third one?
What's this next one coming?
- Who's next?
It might be Queen Elizabeth dying of a fucking broken heart.
- That's right.
- Yeah.
- The good thing, I mean, the royal family,
they'll just come back.
- It's true.
- Yeah, they'll just be like a--
- They'll be back in a weekend.
he'll climb out of the gutter in like exactly in a bowling alley yeah he'll be
like made it he'll be completely naked just formed out of like rats a skeleton
just crawling out of the part of the place where the pins are in a bowling
alley you know like like senator kelly in uh the first x-men movie coming out of
the beach just completely nude and like a more like just a mamorphous blob
yeah that'll be him that'll be prince philip in like a fish and chip shop he'll
he'll come out of like a it's like a little soup yeah yeah and they'll be
like blow on me and they'll be like so much please old side the crane take a
bite of my chip buddy I love you he'll just start fucking slaughtering them
because he's a monster now oh yeah Frankenstein stuff they're gonna do to
him I mean dude fuck this guy just let him die dude yeah stop trying to
reanimate this fool I mean they're saying that he died but you know you know what
they're doing yeah you know he's only dead he's only dead for an afternoon
took him to the shop dude they're switching out his parts they're putting
in there putting a candy paint job on that guy right now you're gonna put a
neutrino star in his stomach you know like gonna wake up they have like the
drip bucket under cars they just have one of those under him right now and
it's just like leaking like a green cum.
- Yeah.
- Mushy peas.
- They have a big ratchet and they're like
cranking a knob on a side and it's making his,
lowering his dick down on his body
so it's easier for him to molest kids.
- They're cranking a knob on his knob,
which is British slang for--
- Oh my God, dude.
- Yeah, they're tugging his Todger down in the shop.
(laughing)
- Todger is one of the funniest--
- Todger's so funny.
Todger and uh last night I I heard uh clunge.
Clunge?
Yeah, somebody told me.
It's like a word that Pierce would come up with.
Yeah that's a fucked up fake word.
It's from the inbetweeners.
Oh you know what my favorite British word is that I that I discovered is gunge.
Gunge?
Yeah?
Yeah there's a there's a fetish.
Gunge is the British word for slime.
Okay.
And it is a fetish.
It's a that's what all those pictures I send you guys of all the old men that are covered
in slime and jacking off.
called a gunshit hello my god that's such an awesome friend quality I found a new
disgusting British fetish here's a thousand literally there's these old
British guys and they dress up in full suits and then they like sit in hot
tubs and bathtubs and then they get pied so that people like and then they just
have their dicks out it's so funny yeah you even how does that even make you
come dude just like sitting in line the most objectively discussed that's what
okay there's they need to do it there should be a hard line between a fetish
and just an interest because like it's not making you come just being naked in
a like you need something that someone's got to touch your ass there's like dudes
aren't like there's some fetish shit that's allowed on YouTube like like
like sitting like wearing like like a full like Canadian tuxedo and like going
into the like going into a pond. Yeah see that's not that's just that's just like cool. Right.
I found I accidentally found a cigarette fetish group on Facebook just because I was looking for
that you know those groups where people just post them smoking cigarettes and are like damn my life
be crazy. Yeah. Like I was looking I found one of those that was called it's called like like
cigarettes bad club or something and I was like oh this will be funny I can open it up and it's all
like people's alts who have like Facebook alts who have cigarette fetishes and the
alts names are all stuff like like Ashley Trey.
Joe Camel that would be mine.
Mine would be Joe Camel.
Or Jarl Marlboro.
That might be a really good one too.
It's all just women dressed up like Rosie the Riveter smoking cigarettes and going like
See but unless you put the cigarette in your fucking pussy and your dick, what are you doing?
Do you think somebody has ever put like a cigar in a butthole? Yeah.
Fucking our president did that dude, what are you talking about?
That's like one of the most famous sex things of all time.
Putting a cigar in a pussy?
Yeah dude, Bill Clinton put a cigar in what's-her-name's pussy.
He did that to Monica?
Yeah!
No. Yes, dude. That's like the biggest, funniest part of the story. That's so fucked up. I don't believe that.
I think it's pretty funny, dude. It's especially if she's a hero. Do you think she could blow smoke rings?
Yes. With her thing?
Maybe.
Who knows? It's possible. I mean, I feel like if you can...
I'm declaring this now. We are pro Monica Lewinsky podcast. We are pro Bill Clinton, because that was the coolest shit of all time.
Okay, I mean fucking kidding me dude. I would love to do that there. You'll be pro Clinton
I'll be pro Lewinsky, and then we'll just have Cameron decides. Yeah, I'm pro. I'm
Yeah, I was gonna say I'm actually I'm pro God
Okay, God is not God is you know anything we can all agree on God
I can't agree with that cuz I'm pro what and dude yeah, dude. I'm about my whole lock you're putting you're putting oh, okay
You know what, that makes sense.
Dude, I'd put a cigar in anything.
Yeah?
Yeah, dude.
Your mouth.
I'd put one even in my damn mouth right now.
And guess what?
I'd just fucking smoke it.
I wouldn't inhale it.
That'll get you really sick, actually.
I've done that.
Inhaled a cigar?
Oh, yeah.
I did that a lot.
Have you inhaled it all in one pull?
Did that a lot in high school.
I did that, uh...
You did that a lot.
Did it a ton.
There was a, like, my brother was on the football team and they had this thing where they would
like go, after games, they would go to like somebody's house and it was called Meatballs
and you just eat like spaghetti and shit and it was called meatballs yeah I was
like oh are you going to meatballs tonight it's just the name of the food
yeah it's a very weird very weird yeah but it was just one of those things that
like you know it's like oh the meatballs at like this guy's house and they would
like sometimes like just have cigars if it was like a good game or whatever like
somebody's dad yeah it's like have like cigars out and somebody gave me one I
I think it was like a black and mild and I like just full pull just like
whole thing ripped it dude oh yeah ripped it did you hold it in ripped it and then like
almost fell over and then like I think I puked in the woods yeah it'll make you puke dude yeah
I used to I used to get cigars when I was like uh when I was like 18. What did you say?
Is this one of those? Okay. This is not a fetish. This is just the coolest guy of all time.
He's in a completely, it looks like a big rig truck. The cab is completely leather.
Yeah, he's wearing a Bluetooth headset.
Yeah, and he's smoking.
And he's holding a cigar up to the camera,
like in the way that it looks like when they Photoshop a hand holding a joint.
I used to smoke cigars when I was like 18 because I didn't smoke cigarettes, but I,
I like made a little bit of money by selling fake CBD to high schoolers
because they would sell them in like the smoke shops in North Carolina.
How old were you when you did that?
I was 18. I had like just turned 18. And my friend was like still in high school.
And so we would buy like all this fake CBD shit from smoke shops and then
Yeah.
Sell it to high schoolers who thought that it was weed.
And then we'd take the money and go buy like expensive cigars and smoke them in a playground.
And they would always give me like the worst diarrhea.
And I was like, "I'm like fucking Tony Soprano right now."
Dude, cigars suck so much. I hate them.
I've never smoked them.
People at my high school graduation, a bunch of people smoked cigars.
That was like a thing.
Yeah, that's so fucking stupid.
Yeah, kids would like...
The only time I'll ever smoke a cigar is if I had a...
If I got like an "It's a boy" cigar.
Or like a "It's a girl".
I would smoke a cigar to celebrate a baby.
The only time I smoke cigars is when I'm golfing, dude.
Because I just transform into a different guy, though.
though yeah yeah I basically go through a portal and I become kind of the coolest
guy ever when I'm golfing so I gotta have a the you know I get like a Dutch master
like a 99 cent cigar and smoke it like it's expensive yeah yeah that's kind of
the move I'm trying to get a Cuban cigar no yeah you do not you could not know I
fucking know I don't I don't want to smoke a cigar ever again I'm gonna make
you do it. Oh you know what Pat? Today is my son's birthday so you have to smoke a
cigar. Just bored like no it has to be like my kid and so like my- It's your
son's birthday. My one of- oh really? Yeah. Fuck. No. Yeah you got to go get a cigar
right now. Yeah for him. For him. My son. And you. You get a split one. My wife just
gave birth to my son? Yeah dude. Right now. Ah shit. And first of all you're missing it
so you're gonna need to be in an extra celebratory mood. I hope one of my uncles gives me a big
It's a Boy cigar. None of your uncles are gonna be there. Oh that's a huge bump. All your uncles
are at work. I guess COVID-19 has limited this. It's wiped out every uncle you had.
So we're not, we can't, they're not coming dude. It's just you and your son and you're
gonna teach him how to smoke a cigar. Yeah day one I'm teaching that's why you need the It's
boys he's gonna he's gonna smoke your baby's holding and just holding a cigar
right my wife's pussy in the delivery room oh yeah that's gonna be a cool bit
shit he came out legs first no while she's pregnant just blowing cigar smoke
into her yeah it's like this is gonna be such a blow it into her mouth this baby's
gonna love poker yeah and then your baby one time you're smoking a cigar and he
He like reaches for it cuz he just reaches for everything cuz he's a he's a newborn
Oh, yeah, you're like, oh you want it you want a cigar, huh? Looks like you're gonna have to smoke the whole pack
Just make them rail in the woods like one of those like wooden
Kobe bus cigar box
You're the one who seemed interested in them I'm trying to teach you a lesson kid. There's a valuable life lesson
Yeah, smoke all these fucking Cubans that I stole and you're gonna drive my car
You're gonna smoke yeah, you're gonna drive me to the store to get that's gonna be my approach to parenting anything that the baby reaches
For if you a buddy your funeral you wanna fucking you wanna fucking try the big cat that we keep in the in the front yard
Go ahead
It's always funny like your baby grabs onto your finger, and you just slap it and it's like hey man
If you're a stranger you do that to me. That's what I would do you know no special
I'm just just teaching you lessons, man. This is how they raised Albert Einstein. You know they didn't talk to him like a baby
They would slap him around and fucking kick him and set him on fire. This is how they raised Albert Einstein and Gigi Allen
So you're gonna grow up really smart or really fun. They were in the son of the man. Oh
You want a baby smoking a cigar you got that I mean if you got the son of the mask
That guy that I mean that baby smoking for sure how fucked up would it be you fucking you your wife pops out
You've been waiting nine months dude. You've been waiting for this day your whole life
You're finally a father your wife pops out the son of beautiful green son of the mask, baby
But it looks half son of the mask and you you remember you have a son of the mask mailman. Mm-hmm
Yeah, very scary
The the fucked up part about that movie is that he just wore the mask when he got his wife pregnant
So if you wear like any mask by that by that logic if you wear any other man
- Yeah, well the sperm's put on a mask too.
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna be ordering one of those Barack Obama masks.
One of those ones that they use for bank robberies.
- Yeah.
- Order one of those and knock up my wife.
- Guess who's got a cool kid?
- Who's got no mama's son.
- Me.
Guess who's got Obama Jr.
Me.
- And that means he has to be the next president.
- Sir, you can't, it's not gonna,
we can't name your kid Obama Jr.
That's not how this works.
Listen, first of all, I saw the kid being born in front of me still think he's from Kenya.
My wife was in a portal.
It's the only way to explain this.
Interrupting sex with my wife to like run and put on an Arnold Schwarzenegger mask and she's
like, "Why are you doing that?"
And you're like, "No, just don't worry.
No, it's going to be cool.
Trust me.
No, no, wait."
And then just wait nine months, wait.
And then like in the hospital, it's just a normal baby and you're just like, "Oh, fuck."
just put the mask on him dude yeah that's why you just keep the mask they'll grow
into it yeah that'll be his face pretty soon mm-hmm just give him a little bit
and then actually you know what it'll do cuz babies have soft heads it'll mold
into the shape of exact Arnold's face you ever seen you ever seen those like
babies that have to wear the helmets all the time yeah yeah yeah by looking in a
mirror that you were looking in okay owned my younger sibling had to wear a
helmet oh really yeah funny what are those like molding helmets yeah yeah
yeah like a baby helmet it like they look very cool it looks like they always make
them with like psychedelic colors on them for some reason like a normal helmet
yeah check out my BMX baby maybe it's so the baby like likes wearing it yeah no
there's a baby doesn't like that it was just high as hell the baby it's on its
fucking head well what if the baby looks in the mirror true babies don't
recognize their reflections as themselves I think that their dogs it's
true that's just the facts yeah yeah oh is it wearing that fucking ugly helmet
oh I'm gonna run at it that's true if your baby is wearing one of those
helmets you can run into anything yeah that's that is actually true you don't
have to babyproof anything. Exactly. If you live in... Take those skates off the stairs. I should start wearing a helmet.
Yeah, you skateboard nine hours a day. No, not when I skate. Oh, take it off to skate.
Pulling up, pulling up, like wearing the helmet and then just immediately taking
it off and like fucking up just like an Ollie so bad. Just breaking your
brain. Yeah, just destroy my head. I'm really excited to see... Just walking around wearing a helmet and not like having, not
carrying a skateboard or anything, just like having a helmet. Like one of the
pro-tech, like the pro-tech 70s style helmets that have like the ear
cushion or like the ear plastic. You ever see those ones? Yeah. Like a baseball helmet.
Oh man. Like a knight's helmet. I'm pretty excited to continue being friends with
Pat for the next like 10 years or so as just like the CTE starts catching up
with him and he becomes more and more like violent and evil and drug addicted.
It's gonna be pretty fun. Yeah. Yeah, you think I'm gonna get CTE from skateboarding. I think you already have
To get CTE, you might have you might have such a powerful skull that it's kind of blocked everything
I did I I went to I went to Blue Park and immediately fucked up like a warm-up trick and fell to my head
fell to my death. I did I fell hit like the back of my head and like I have I
really haven't felt the same since so. Welcome to New York baby! You have to hit
it on the other side of your head so yeah brain back into the right
coordinates. It is I did I did kind of have like a headache and it cured my
headache so maybe. So maybe you already maybe you feel the most normal you've
ever been yeah did you get it did you get a goose egg no I wish I did I got one of
those in elementary school I tripped and I was well I tripped and I have my hands
in my pocket
that makes sense that you just walked around as a kid with your hands in your
pockets all the time. Oh boy. I was already, I was an early Travis Bickle. At least you
weren't one of those, one of those belt loop kids. You know those ones? Oh yeah. Those thumbs
and their belt loops. What the fuck is wrong with you dude? Yeah. You're no cowboy. No I
was also a thumbs in the sweatshirt sleeves kid. Oh you cut the wolves out? I chewed them
out baby yeah yeah he's a real freak yeah powerful jaws I would hate for you to
fucking death roll me oh yeah did you guys ever chew on on your sleeves or
your clothing and yeah I did cuz I loved the taste of my own salt yeah and I just
fucking sit there chewing on my just ruin all my long-sleeve shirts. I chewed on like my sweatshirt
sleeves too much and my parents told me that there was a kid who did it. My parents told me that
there's a kid who did that once and all the stuff that he chewed went into his
stomach and stayed there and they had to remove a giant ball of sweatshirt from his stomach with surgery.
And it didn't even stop me, that's how much I liked it.
I believe that though, I believe that could happen.
Yeah dude, there's microplastics when you drink a water bottle.
It makes sense that if you spend all your time chewing on a sweatshirt sleeve you get probably some lint in there.
Okay, but a sweatshirt sleeve is not gonna do that, it's food and water that's gonna do that.
The lint is gonna just fall out of your ass. It's not gonna stick in your gut.
Imagine taking a shit and it's all lint.
Damn.
Did you guys ever have to shit a-
You have to scrape it out like a lint trap and then wash it in the dryer sheet.
Oh fuck dude. You just keep pulling it and there's like more than you expected as you pull it out.
You have to put in that like the mesh dryer sheet and then pull it out a bunch of times.
You're sticking a cheese grater in your ass to use.
Oh, oh, oh, cheese grater in your ass, dude.
What the hell are you doing doing that, Nishty?
It's been a while since we had to go back on something like that.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're right.
We've been sticking to our guns recently.
We've been a little less gross, I think, maybe.
We need to be a little safe.
We need to maybe step it up.
What do you guys think of this helmet for me to wear all the time?
This is a $70...
I sent Caleb a helmet he could wear all the time.
I don't need a helmet, dude.
Do you have the helmet I sent you?
You bought a- you got a- you got a helmet and you haven't been wearing it?
He got me a Paw Patrol helmet and it was- it won't even fit on the top of my fucking head.
*laughter*
Cam, take a look at this hat. This is how you give a gift.
A Paw Patrol helmet?
Paw Patrol helmet's a good gift.
*laughter*
Listen, this is a Kingdom Hearts hat.
There's so many ways you can hurt yourself.
A Paw Patrol helmet's for a child.
Dude, you- you're really important to me and I don't want you to hurt your head.
*laughter*
It only would protect the top of my head!
It would only protect
Your head on the top of your mouse hole, okay, I don't live in a mouse hole
Start doing jumping jacks under the stove
I'm not small
Normal can't Cameron and I will put our money together. We'll get Caleb
Expensive could it be we'll get Caleb up the biggest Paw Patrol helmet we can find
Biggest helmet in the world
Okay, all right, well here's a little flaw in your logic
How can I be both as small as a mouse and need the biggest helmet in the world?
hydrocephaly
Hydrocephaly my cousin has that
What's that? What's your cousin? Yeah
Set too much water in your head. Yeah, okay. Well, I'm such a genius with Latin
Paw Patrol motorcycle
Paw Patrol biggest helmet
Yeah here I'll send this is the one that I got Caleb look at this look at this helmet
Can you don't get a helmet unless it'll fit on a 33-inch rim?
Ungrateful look at how cool this helmet is put that helmet on right now. It's at my mom's house with the gnome outfit
Fuck you!
What the fuck?
He left both of our presents.
How could I fit- if I can't fit a fucking outfit into my suitcase-
Put it on and you can wear it on the plane.
How am I gonna fit- I thought it was a- I thought it was so small, Caleb.
You can get through TSA wearing a helmet.
I thought it was such a small helmet and now it's too big to fit in your suitcase.
It's actually rigid if you fucking knew what you bought, 'cause it's a fucking helmet,
and because of the shape it wouldn't fit.
Would I have loved to have bring it and make Janna find a place to store it?
Yes.
Why don't you just wear your nutcase as a helmet?
Every time I buy something or get something like this hat, Jana just gives me a deep sigh
because she has to figure out where to hide it.
I just told her today that I ordered a Rick and Morty sweatsuit and she was like, "Oh
fuck, what are you fucking doing?"
I have my nice computer desk where I can just stack everything that I want but don't want
to put away.
I just throw everything in a corner.
Yeah, exactly.
This is my corner.
everything that's everything that's not important is is stacked up right here
hindering my ability to do anything and that's the problem these are my
most important items items that I own you know Kingdom Hearts hat Paw Patrol
their helmet need to give us inventories I agree you should get an inventory and
you should you should be able to become over encumbered though because I think
that would be funny to see people have that on the street yeah it's true just
- Just giving you things, people are like,
"Please, please take my pants,
"I've become over encumbered."
- Watching somebody just drop a diamond.
- Can you please, please, I have--
- Yeah, please somebody dropping a diamond
to switch it out with something else
and you grab it really quick.
- Dude, that would be the best feeling in the world.
- No, it's in my inventory.
It's in my inventory, you can't do it.
You can't touch it.
- What do you mean?
I didn't take that diamond.
- It'd be a cool pickup line too,
where you'd be like, "I've become over encumbered and--"
- I need to store something in your house.
- I need to put my, I need to store my cum
your inventory. I'm too encumbered right now and I need to get rid of some items.
Yeah I need to get rid of my phone number. Yeah there we go. That's right well
that's a little less former. And the inside cover of Infinite Jest. So damn heavy. I need to get rid of my phone number which I wrote with my
finger in a puddle of my cum right next to you. So you're gonna have to take this cum either way.
yeah so there's okay I'm on the helmet website still and there's on this one
specifically pro tech they have they have like full tech and then they have
full tech certified which I don't know what certified I hate tech in this
situation I will never you will never catch me buying anything tech does that
mean it's like certified like like thing it just means as a stamp certified is in
like it's certified to protect your head and then there's like some of them that
aren't certified because I mean why not just get all the helmet certified it
means in it's kind of in a gangster way you know okay oh he's certified okay it's
like that all right so I should buy the certified helmet that cost I did I said
$25 I found an $80 motorcycle Paw Patrol helmet how big as a visor and everything
These boys better start pitching in.
I mean, I'll wear it.
Let me see it.
I don't have a motorcycle.
I don't even have a bike right now.
I might get this.
If we buy this for you, you're wearing this fucking everywhere.
I don't ever want to see you with this not on your head.
I might get this pink flame helmet.
I don't have a choice in it?
Absolutely not.
Oh, dude.
That thing says fucking beast.
This is called the 713 Junior, and it says, "The 713 Junior is the helmet created for smaller customers."
This is good for Caleb.
I'm not small.
small I mean humongous. This is on outletmoto.edu. Yeah there's an Italian website selling a
Paw Patrol motorcycle helmet. It's got an anti-scratch visor. I don't need this crap
dude. Tell you what I need. It looks so good. I need an RFID reader and some grubhubbed
Taco Bell. How about you guys take care of that first. Nah that's not happening. What
What are you gonna do with the RFID reader?
Probably steal a bunch of numbers.
Yeah? Like just random shit?
Like what, seven?
Yeah, I'm just gonna steal some random numbers.
I read some book in high school
where a guy had like an
RFID like cloner
so he could like steal people's
credit cards and stuff.
I don't think that's a real thing,
but they do sell like wallets
that are like,
to stop this super villain
just do that with like tinfoil. I mean the thing is like credit cards and shit are
more complicated but you can absolutely like do RFID cloning with like library
books and stuff because yeah yeah it's not like it's not like doesn't matter
and again simple single numbers is what I would start doing. Every library could
burn to the ground it wouldn't change anything in the world. If somebody had a
maybe like a yeah a 10 or a 15 stuck on their computer I would definitely
definitely clone that. Yeah. Yeah. And then I'd be like, you, you have been, um, you've
been hacked by it. I wouldn't steal any numbers cause I wouldn't know what to do with them.
I'd add them up. Yeah. Yeah. I'm going to steal all these numbers from people's fucking phones
and computers. Add them up. Guess who's got the biggest number now. Ooh, that would be
fun though. Just to like steal our numbers and then just add. Yeah. And then gets the
biggest number. And then I get the biggest number. I would just want to, while we're talking
about this I want to put out there all the fans I don't care if I'm not right
about the RFID thing don't message me about it okay I didn't need the message
but I was wrong about Komodo dragons okay what did you what did they correct?
They said it wasn't bacteria in their saliva it was venom
oh wait okay nerd wait I was right about the venom no hold on
where did you say they had venom? Oh my god Pat is so smart I don't really
You're like a dragon-ologist.
It's true.
What the fuck?
I don't think anybody's ever corrected me on anything because I've always been right on the podcast pretty much.
I don't know about that.
Well I do because I'm correcting you on that.
I'm giving you a Pinocchio right now.
I'm going to give you a Pinocchio if you fucking don't put some clothes on.
I have clothes on.
I'm going to put my Pinosin-yo.
[laughter]
Yeah, that's what I meant. Yeah, that's pretty good.
Well, the thing is you just to just turn off your your message requests and just say whatever you want on this damn thing dude
What are they gonna do? Yeah, cancel their subscription. I don't fucking think so
Yeah, no fucking shot. You guys need us. You need me. Mm-hmm. Look at me in my hat. You need this and
I'll have to take a screenshot. Helmet Moto, Jet Child, BHR 713, Nickelodeon, Rubble, Paw Patrol
And we need to keep spending our money on stupid shit like this. So stick around.
Helmets and snowboards and ski passes. Rick and Morty backwood sweatsuit and trip to Breckenridge.
Yep. Yep.
Which is what we've just planned right now. And an M16 which we keep in like different parts
at each one of our houses so that we can't get in trouble for it. That would be so cool.
Wouldn't that be pretty smart, right? We all get like a couple of parts of a gun. I would get the receiver.
I'm gonna get the I'm gonna get the gun. I'll get I call the bullets. I want the trigger
Is get what do you guys gonna do?
Cuz this is what you do if this is in case any any two of us turn on one of us
We we we only have some of the gun
We can't buy the rest of the gun
Yeah, we only well, that's one of the rules
Yeah, we only have some parts of the guns were like
Patrick we got a shoot him in the head. Oh, we only have the bullets in the trigger
And the rule is that we can't buy the other
Do I
Guess I guess we could throw the bullets at him. Yeah
Well, what they don't tell you about guns is the trigger does pretty much everything if you just have a trigger and you put a
Bullet on it and you pull the trigger the bolts gonna shoot out. Yeah, it's just to make it look cool
The trigger has like a hammer attached. It'll hit the back of the bullet and it'll fucking send anything flying. Mm-hmm
It's kind of genius dude. Yeah, our guns powered by like electricity
Batteries in them, I think they're powered by gun powder. Yes. It's oh, yeah, probably gunpowder
I've shot quite a few guns and I've just never understood how they work
I get how like a like a flintlock pistol works, but like an like a like a machine gun
But it's got to have a machine in it, right? Yeah, it's got to be some triple-a batteries in this thing
actually those are my those are probably D batteries cuz that'd be a pretty big
the um you guys know about the like ancient guns that that China invented
like gunpowder before everyone else they used to guns used to like the
original gun like look like a spear like it's like a long pole and then it has
like a gun barrel on the end of the pole and you like put the gunpowder and the
bullet in and then you light it and then you just point it the person like it's
like a wizard so it's just like a Roman candle pretty much yeah like a giant
Yeah, the Italians came up with it first, fucker.
That would have scared the shit out of me, dude.
It's literally so cool.
It's just like a random...
This is like actually magic.
Yeah, it's just like a random Chinese guy and somebody shoots fire at you out of nowhere.
Yeah, with a staff.
I'd be out, dude.
I'd be getting out of Dodge.
I'd be getting out of China.
Yeah.
I would never.
I would never fuck with someone who had a big staff.
Donatello from Ninja Turtles?
No way.
No way I would not go up against him because he also knows the computer and he could steal my numbers with this RFID
That's true. He might hack your gun dude. He might hack the bullets right out of your gun with that RFID reader
I can't imagine getting my numbers stolen
It's gonna happen. That would suck so much
Someone takes your numbers. Oh, yeah
Oh, my numbers security number. Yeah, what if someone takes a social security number right off of your fucking car if my wallet ever gets stolen
To me an RFID reader is just a camera that just can take photos of different numbers.
You shouldn't keep your social security number in your wallet.
Why not?
I do.
I know it.
And I leave my wallet outside with my shoes.
At this address.
Yeah, it's a very, I live in a very eastern style apartment where we leave our shoes and
our social security numbers outside of the door.
You gotta take them out before you walk in.
It's an eastern style apartment.
also have you also have a magic staff to
defend against burglars
breaking in and he's pointing this
giant staff at them that's like sparking
and shooting out like smoke and is going
okay can you hold on a second like it
has to wait wait wait you're gonna be so
scared in just a minute just hold on and
then it backfires and just blows your own head off
ah fuck I was pointing it the wrong way
oh oh shit oh shit do you know a guy that
fixes windows ah fuck
Dude that's like when I when I went on my first uh my first date with Jay and I
heard that I thought it was really funny to like
bring out his like gun. Oh he was one of those guys? Yeah but
he only has like a musket.
He brought out like an antique like musket and he was like yeah he better uh
and he was like he like couldn't keep it together he was laughing so hard.
That's a really good bit.
Yeah, bring the...
back at 9pm or you know what's gonna happen.
Like, what are you gonna do?
You're gonna take 2 hours to load a musket
and then shoot me and then
be like the most famous guy ever
cause you killed a guy with a musket.
Just like one of those like prom
photos but like the dad is holding
like a blunderbuss. Yeah, it's exactly
what it was. He takes you out into
the backyard and just shows you a trebuchet
that's aimed directly at your house.
Yeah, you don't bring it back by 9 p.m. You know yeah, we're launching plague
victims. He's holding a strike fear into your dogs like a like a powder keg like a
Goron and he's holding a red barrel from Half-Life 2. Yeah, so you might might think
twice about getting here 915. Yeah, my dad's been using the gravity gun again.
yeah my dad pulled up the gravity gun when I come my first date he's gonna be a
if you don't bring back by nine I'm gonna be shooting one of your friends that you
would this he puts thrusters on on on you and it's like hey man if you're not
back by midnight I'm pressing numpad 5
fuck gmod dad god damn it yeah my dad keeps changing his skin yeah my dad's my
dad's pretending to be the TF2 scout again fuck fuck he keeps tethering me to
the dishes so that I do him fuck him dude fuck yeah yeah well things have been
going weird at my house right now dad just installed space build I mean we have
to keep fucking the oxygen levels in the house it's all kinds of bullshit my dad
kicked my friend out because he was a giant red flashing errors you brought a
missing texture into my fucking house no fucking chance inviting a friend over
and they have to wait on the on the welcome mat for like two hours to finish
you're just downloading all the Lua scripts before they can go in.
I hate my team like that.
No, you have to download Hogwarts.Lua and MasterChiefNude.Lua and...
This is Brian's House.RP.
Yeah, so yeah, this is our house, pretty humble. We like to run it like RP, but we do have a beach house down on the Cape that is a prop hunt, if you ever...
And it is a roleplay server so you will have to roleplay as a white guy while you're here.
Just don't want to piss off dad, you know?
Oh fuck.
Just the surly teenager just being like "Fuck you dad" and just spawning like 50 headcrab
zombies in your living room and storming out.
Dude, I wish my dad had been protective like that, just threatened every girl I went on
a date with.
Oh, it'd be, it's funnier if it's like...
Yeah, hey listen little lady, if you don't get him back by nine, I'm gonna beat the shit
out of you.
That's just how it's gonna go.
He's fragile, you know, and he's my little boy, you know, so...
Don't make me, and anything you do to him, I'm gonna be doing to you.
No matter how much surgery I have to get to be able to do it.
Yep, listen, I'm already fucking taking pills and stuff to look like a girl just so I can
fucking...
I'm gonna do it to you, so get ready.
I'm gonna capture you, I'm gonna keep you in my basement, and I'm gonna turn you into
my son.
I love my Gmod dad.
Oh man.
Gmod dad.
Oh, Gmod dad, he's so funny.
He's such a weird guy.
He's keeping girls in the basement.
anything else you guys want to end it 20 minutes early? Yeah that's, Gmod dad felt good dude.
I'm getting vaxed tomorrow, or today when this episode is coming out. Nice dude.
What flavor? I got it a few days ago. Moderna.
When I was, it was like a big, it was like you know there's like a ton of people, a bunch of
lines and like nurses all walking around. Yeah. And there was one nurse who was like, whose job
it was to like show people like where to sit to wait for the vaccine and she was just like standing
there in the middle of the place just like not talking to anybody like not i
was not like she wasn't like looking at things she just said out loud to herself
i love this place and i was like oh my god they are about to they're about to
hack me yeah i love this place welcome to city 17
i bring back g my dad g my dad is getting
vaccinated yes dude he's getting vaccinated um
Yeah. Okay, no, he's bringing his son to get vaccinated. He says, "Anything you do to my
son, I'm going to do to you." Yeah, I'm the dad who just says that about anything. I'm saying it
to the football coach. I'm saying it to the teachers. Any homework you give to my son,
I'm going to be giving it to you. Hey, if you make, hey, if you give my son a Big Mac, I want one too.
Yeah, and that's just the rules. Listen, somebody's got to step... Listen, I'm not the stepdad. I'm
I'm the neighbor who stepped up and is not married to this guy's mom.
So I...
Oh, what's that?
Oh, I can't have a Big Mac for free?
Slash kill all.
Any, any crowns you put in his mouth.
Yeah.
You're putting them in me.
I don't care if you have to take the tooth out, put it back in.
Listen, I'm going to be wearing this kid's glasses.
Make an exact copy.
Yes, I have perfect 2020 vision, but I'm driving home with him.
That's just the facts.
I'm a good dad.
Look, he's got Coke bottle glasses.
those that the glass and that shit shit's going all the way back to his eye he's
looking like a he's looking like a welder I need that plastic surgery and
saying I want to be indistinguishable from my son so that I that's like uh
isn't that what be exactly equal isn't that like be like what behind the
candelabra was about I don't know what that is I think Neil was telling me
about it that's the sounds like a rod you would tell me about yeah Liberace
turned into his own son? No Liberace basically like took his like
husband or partner to the... You almost said whatever and I'd like to say you can
just say whatever. Yeah it was. His husband or whatever. Yeah whatever he took his like partner to a
plastic surgeon like Neil was telling me about a scene where he like takes his
partner who a plastic surgeon and just shows the plastic surgeon a picture of
himself. That's beast dude. Yeah making your making your like partner look
exactly like you what a fucking swag move that is did that is powerful I might
have to do that I'm gonna go to a plastic surgeon and show them a picture
of myself yeah I just show him a picture of me with hair like make it look like
this man make it happen yeah they just start doing that's what you do it
your job you cry every time that they say they can't yeah hey give me this I
I show you a picture of the weekend.
Hey, lace me up with this one.
I was thinking, I was skating the other day
and just like the thought popped into my head
just like white guy with weekend haircut.
Dude, you fucking head to an H&M, look at the walls dude.
They have 'em, yeah.
Those guys exist.
Yeah, I wanna see 'em.
I mean, search it up brother.
Do you think like, oh yeah, I guess, yeah that makes sense.
'Cause his haircut is one that white guys can kinda do
'cause it's like a made up haircut, you know?
They're not really like stealing it from any kind of person,
they're stealing it from The Weeknd.
Yeah, it's true.
They just take his giant hair and they're like,
yeah, this is pretty sick.
Well, he doesn't have it anymore.
You're right, now he just has short hair.
So that would be a problem.
Honestly, you got a good musician.
I'm glad you got that out.
Yeah, I'm glad that people needed to know.
People need to know my opinion on The Weeknd.
On The Weeknd, yeah.
People think I'm not a guy who would like The Weeknd, but I worked at a job where every time that we closed they would just play The Weeknd.
And I started to enjoy his music.
Hey man, when I worked a job I would play on The Weeknd too, because I didn't have to come in.
That's right.
That's fuckin' right.
I mean, what a great name for an artist too. It's your favorite thing.
The Weeknd?
Yeah, you can't not like him.
you're kind of already conditioned to like it no matter what. Somebody should make a
hilarious Twitter account. Okay, okay. Wait, I think I have an idea here. Uh-huh.
They wear it every day on Friday. Mm-hmm. Or whatever day that fucking shit...
Whatever day the weekend starts, who knows. Yeah, nobody knows. Still up for debate. They put a guy
saying something. Okay. What if on Twitter you could do something where
every time something happens, a video of a guy saying something.
Someone should make one of those with me.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Me too.
Me?
No, you can't steal my-
Me first.
No, I already said it first.
Wait, me too.
Wait, can I get one too?
I'm rubber deer glue.
I need to have a bait for one of these Twitter bots or something.
Yeah, okay, wait.
Somebody make a Twitter bot of all three of us combined.
Here, they'll do this every week or something, ready?
it's Christmas and they can make it they could play that like every Wednesday or
something yeah or whenever it's Christmas I guess what about yeah fuck
that's delicious fuck that's that's Christmas to me
okay wait I've got a good one this one so you can post this weekly and you can
choose which day this is uh you'd want to post this one on it's been a week
since the last one. That's pretty good. And that's so you can kind of we can have
seven different accounts each day. But I want to do one that's like the bot gets
a post a lot so maybe I'll do like I'll do like like it's been one minute and
they'll just post it every minute right? It's been a second. The thing about that
is you need the video of it so maybe with this episode. Well somebody can make a video.
I'm thinking it's my voice. I'm working in an audio medium. I don't really care if
they know what I look like. I'm picturing like a mouse or something. With the episode we got a mouse.
Like a red ball mouse. Maybe. Yeah one that wears a Paw Patrol helmet. No that's not.
Like a mouse like drinking a cup of coffee that's like bigger than it or something you know.
Um I don't even know. I don't even drink coffee. What about like a mouse trapped in petroleum jelly?
Yeah it could be like a like a beautiful woodland fairy that's one inch tall and it's trapped in a
block of amber and it's like suffocated did you say beautiful I sure did well
garsh the goofy on the kingdom hearts hat is getting no no no no cuz that hat
specifically is from which game is that that is a hearts no but there's a
specific Kingdom Heart point your head down so I can see the full thing let's
Let's analyze this.
Jay Z the Black Album right now.
That is... it's not Birth By Sleep.
It's the one with Tara and Ventus.
So I got you like a...
A deep cut?
Yeah, I think so.
I'm gonna give you a deep cut.
A deep cut Kingdom Hearts hat?
Yeah.
That's the one, it was on PSP.
Whoa.
Oh, wait.
I think it is Birth By Sleep.
- Pat is doing Star Wars with something else right now.
- I know, and it's Kingdom Hearts,
how fucking horrible is that?
- It's really, really bad.
- You know, Caleb, the problem might not be Star Wars.
- Yeah, now that I'm thinking about it,
we might be getting to a deeper issue,
which is Pat sucks.
- No, come on, that's too much.
- Pat, you don't suck, man.
- I don't think he's--
- Yeah, you don't suck, you blow.
- Oh, shit, dude.
I'm learning I'm learning something about the way my brain works yeah maybe there's
a test I will say it's a choice if it's a choice between Kingdom Hearts and Star
Wars I'm sticking with Star Wars we can go back to that one yeah I'm not no I
was just I was just trying to point out that the hat that I got him specifically
is like the like probably the weirdest one I could have got it and here's what
I did stay on the back is so funny yeah saying is pretty it looks like somebody
left M&M's on it. Did you know that it was from GameStop Returns? No. So they just ripped
you off. Cause it says GameStop Returns on the front of the box. They sent you off. It
probably has fucking lice dude. Yeah. Absolutely. Thank God. For sure. It's a Kingdom Hearts
Birth by Sleep hat of course it has lice. I will say since I got this, I'm not kidding
I think I've had a huge rash on the back of my head.
Are you serious?
Yeah, it might not be visual right now because I just took a shower.
Do you see it?
Oh, I do.
I had like a big red splotch on the back of my head.
Oh my god.
I got Caleb the best gift of all.
New pets.
A new disease.
That's so sweet.
If you let the lice dig in for long enough, it's going to look like hair plugs.
That's a good point.
They're all just sticking their legs out.
yeah i just got so hungry for hair they're gonna be digging into your head
and pulling the hair out making it longer they don't eat hair they eat hair
they don't they eat hair they what else would they eat nothing else is on your
head the bread crumbs on your head and the food bread there sometimes you
leave shit on your head dude you're walking around the village put a
pineapple on your head you put like the crumbs from the pineapple stay in your
head there's a different there's shit left over on your head you know yeah and
and that's what lice like to feed on.
Yeah, lice are trying to, they think hair is just big food.
Have you ever had, have you ever had those, one of those bugs that crawls in
your skin that has a very questionable name?
Huh? Oh, oh it starts with a C? Yeah. CH? Yeah.
Oh yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah. Chickers? Yeah. Those are
not fun dude. That's like the worst version of lice. Did you guys ever have a botfly?
Did you guys ever have a botfly or get Ebola? I've had that, yeah.
I've had both of those. Did you guys ever get, did you guys ever...
Were you guys afraid of Ebola in 2014? Oh yeah. No. I knew I was. I knew I was immune.
I saw some picture of some guy like being like like covered in blood and I was like damn that's
what happens when you get Ebola. Yeah the Ebola outbreak. I don't like blood. Yeah. I was afraid
of swine flu but because my mom told me that Obama was using it to start martial law and put
Christians in camps. I was afraid of swine flu because I was like it's zombies. I wasn't afraid.
I didn't take swine flu serious until like two or three years after swine flu was a bad and I learned
that the lead singer of that band broadcast died of swine flu and I was like because I was like oh
swine flu is like all fucking made up I never fucking got it and then I found out somebody
died somebody famous died from it and I was like whoa maybe I should have taken that serious that's
why more famous people they should have let more famous people die of covid could have saved a lot
John Pryan died of COVID I think. See? Don't know who that is. They should have
picked like like injected into Brad Pitt or something. They should have let fucking Tom Hanks die.
Yeah let him fucking rot. Oh dude I guarantee you my grandma would be getting vaccinated right now.
If Tom Hanks did die of COVID we would have like it it would have been there
would be no vaccination. Worldwide there would be no vaccination. 100%
Christians would be in camps if Tom Hanks had died. Yeah. Absolutely bro.
100% no question I mean it's like it would have gone down a very dark path to
bring up Chet but Chet would be like leading a resistance right now yeah yeah
yeah it would be Chet Guevara
all right so now since you said that you do have to make the check of our shirt
now yeah yeah yeah you have to not even don't need to sell it I just need to see
it don't sell it that will make a fucking killing yeah don't sell it he's wearing
a backwards fitted hat instead of like yeah yeah and this is chat yeah yeah
yeah that would be some funny-ass shit oh yeah I mean we can send that one
straight to like like I don't know one of those like it like like a fucking what
of the websites that sell those those t-shirts yeah exactly
snorties back on the podcast I'd like to mention snorties and so fucking
sponsoring us for 80 episodes and I've forgotten every single one I think we're
at a point now we come up with so many good shirt ideas for them yeah that's
true you're giving them so much we need to get a cutback dude I mean so many
shirts they can do. We could at most get a promo code. Absolutely for snorting. Okay here I've got
another one for them. We can do a Chet collection okay. Here's one Chet Hanks sitting at a table in
a restaurant hand raised in the air. Chet please. That's right that's pretty fucking good dude. Yeah
and we can do it in like a like a like a comic book printing style where they have the little
color dots you know. That will that'll be really good. Chet yourself before you ret yourself. Okay
yeah we're getting somewhere now that can be a collab shirt Chet Hanks and Rhett and
Link what about Jackie Chet and it's like Chet Hanks and he's dressed up like Jackie
Chan in certain way well that's like like Chet Throatole and he's like a metal band
he's playing a flute yeah he's playing a cool flute and a bad metal band uh-huh
and the song aqualung does okay wait no no I got it okay ready this is a coffee mug
this is marketed to older women okay picture like very like a the type of the
type of picture of Chet's face that you get on like you see you on a somebody's
tattoo when like they're there they get a wife wife dies you know like the black
and white like yeah yeah that yeah and and it says I'm a ched a rose sexual oh
Oh, that's pretty good and also it's like already aged poorly
Yeah, be like a really awesome point. Yeah. I mean, it's just it's a it's the inverse of
Quomo sexual except it's the same and one way at least
Yeah, I mean that is what opposites are. It's the same thing but a little different. Yeah, I guess you're right
Yeah, that is a good point
Opposites it's really intriguing and we could do shoes called Chet knees. Okay?
oh yeah yeah Chetney's then we could do instead of Jordans Chet's mm-hmm oh my
god Chetney's America and then we can shorten that to Ch-America Chetney's
Hank Eric Hank Erica cuz his last name's Hank yeah Chet Hank Aaron Chet Hanks
Aaron and we could I don't know baseball something in there yeah what instead of
the West Bank it's the Chet's Hank okay that might solve quite a few issues in
the middle east that would be really good yeah this is gonna become the fucking
the new goddamn carol baskin on the podcast no no we're just my foot down
about it yeah not doing it anymore yeah no doma check we're done with it yeah
yeah so what about a shirt so what about a shirt that's like Christmas carol
baskins yeah okay and it's like and it's like you'll you'll scratch your eye out
with that you'll see fuck that movie is not called the Christmas whatever it
doesn't matter the idea will get across yeah that'd be a that'd be a very
different line of okay it's a line of Carol Baskin shirts for different
Christmas movies. The line is called Christmas Carol Baskins, but then they just say the
name of the movie so you don't have to worry about doing the puns.
That is good, yeah. So you could have like, what's a Christmas movie?
There aren't any.
I can die hard.
Yeah, you could call it Ty-gar.
Ty-gar.
That might work pretty well. What's another Christmas movie?
There aren't any.
Scrooged?
Scrooge you call it scratched scratched yeah cuz he tiger scratched a guy or I
remember company my nose Fred Claus Oh dead dead claws yeah okay and it's about
her husband is unaccompanied minors a Christmas movie no unaccompanied Tigers
is what I was gonna sign accompanied minors what kind of movies are you
watching what the that's a movie and it that's a movie no it's not yeah I'm sure
it's a movie unaccompanied minors is a okay I looked up search that it said the
Biden administration is spending six billion per week to shelter unaccompanied
minors but the 2006 film unaccompanied minors when a Christmas Eve blizzard
shuts down the airport five stranded youths take the opportunity to run wild
and have some fun racing with golf carts and sliding down baggage chutes the kids
create holiday pandemonium for an uptight airport official Louis Black and
his gullible assistant Wilbur Falterama. Dude that was like Louis Black's like
golden era. Remember he was thrown him in every movie. He's an accepted dude. He's the dean and accepted.
Yeah you just write in just a mean old Jewish guy into any movie you were making
and then you just knew you could get Louis Black for $180. You let Louis Black do his
famous rants yeah and you just like why is Christmas oh yeah exactly
just and you just fucking crush it dude put him in any movie dude do you mean the
Rugrats it doesn't matter he was going off dude I mean he was snapping on Bush
and his and his friend this guy unaccompanied minors was directed by
Paul Feig. Cool. He did a girl Ghostbusters. Oh that guy the guy who posts the picture
of himself wearing the outfits. Yeah. Oh my god have you seen that picture? No.
No. What did he do? I don't know anything about Paul Feig. If you look up Paul
Feig it says people also ask why did Paul Feig leave Sabrina? Who's fucking
Sabrina the Teenage Witch. Okay. I thought it was just somebody like Sabrina Fiege.
Yeah. I need to see this photo. I'm trying to find it dude. I don't know what to
search. Is he a fellow costume mule? Yeah. He's a haberdasher. Oh I found it.
Have you ever been to the haberdashery in Boston that has the little guy? No.
Oh, what?
That's a fucking awesome trip.
Wait, is that one in Harvard Square?
Yeah.
Oh, I've walked by it.
I know that one.
That is the number one must visit place in Boston, I would say.
I went to the one in Disney Springs.
The haberdashery is just so sick.
This picture for some reason has the lowest resolution I've ever seen.
I can't figure out.
Here we go.
Wait, wait, wait.
His outfit of the day?
One second, I found a better one.
Check this out.
I'll post this with the episode.
is an important one oh yeah cuz he was on some Netflix show
right on the Joel McHale said okay for his face he has a stern yet loving look
for his tie he says rock a power tie so people know who is the boss flower on
lapel show a softer side of your personality that's it you look like a
clown with a flower it just gets better bracelets keep a part of your soul alive
what the fuck are you the last one's the best all right pocket square get a dope
ass pocket square the compliments your tie. Dope ass pocket square is just god what a
fucking line. When I originally posted this I think I drew a line
draw a line from like like compare the size of his hand to the size of his head
just like hold your fingers over his hand and then just move it over his head
Jesus Christ you guys got the biggest hand I've ever seen. Damn. It's bigger than his hand.
Even accounting for like like perspective. Even accompanying minors.
that's like the biggest hand I've ever seen yeah yeah this guy this guy
directing a movie called unaccompanied minors he should have been in jail like
death second he did yeah absolutely well that's the thing he had a file on his on
his computer it's called unaccompanied minors it's a script I'm working on about
Christmas and you know what Lewis Black's in it. And Fez from that 70s show is in it.
And what's that? And what's this bookmark on Chrome? It's this deviantART link to
girl ghostbusters? What? No, it's a movie too!
Paul, why are your big hands so hairy on the palm?
I'm a werewolf.
Yeah, I'm a werewolf and I'm gonna make a movie about that too.
I'm directing a werewolf movie!
Yeah, it's called "The Pedophile Werewolf."
he's actually he's an american werewolf he's actually a better guy during the full movie
because at least he's attacking a dance
alright fuck you paul feig
yeah alright no no we'll never work with him
paul feig you're awesome
oh i love your movies
bye