Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
- Premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Okay.
- Oh, yeah.
- So I mean, I wanna get this right out of the way,
right at the very beginning.
We have a super--
- Cameron, pass the weed.
- Bro, stop, I'm not on the phone.
We have a super--
- Cameron, pass the weed.
- Dude, stop, I'm trying to introduce our special guest.
We have a super incredible special guest with us today.
and his name is caleb pits
uh... what's up guys
it's kato
killed its from uh... completely bald and on
five-year doing an interview with him
we're doing a an hour-long interview
with
it's
the kind of get into what makes them take what he likes what he doesn't like
what he does during the day
well i don't like i don't like certain kind of people
you don't like certain kind of the world
i guess i'll have to get into that in our interview yeah killed your mike sounds
like it might be a little well too
uh...
it's not just for a minute there
i mean i guess that i have a very few you know if you
he has the but it's tricky stuff but it's not
the
(laughing)
- Are you using OBS right now?
- No.
- Are you streaming this live?
- I'm streaming this live.
- It's a live recording.
(laughing)
- Oh no, the stream ended.
- Oh man, if you could see this, it would be so funny.
- Guys, you don't even know
what you're missing out on right now.
Uh, wow.
We have Jubio today.
Yeah, he's replacing, he who shall not be named.
Uh huh, because he looks like Voldemort.
That's right.
I think you've seen him a couple times.
Flat ass.
Oh, also we're going to do a, I'm doing a review.
Yeah let's hear this review.
So we got Doritos review right off the bat.
Doritos incognita.
So that means Doritos in disguise, right?
Yeah.
Doritos disguised as another chip. I can't tell you what the flavor of these is
supposed to be. It's a secret. It's incognito. Yeah, but that chip is
completely brown. You did, you pulled one out. It's like a rust colored, it's like a
rust colored, like if you let blood dry on a white t-shirt kind of color. Yeah.
and it tastes like the best crunch I've ever heard we could probably sell that
crunch as a stock sound effect the first we can the first chip that you pulled
out of there I was impressed I mean it was very brown but it had one corner
that was black yeah so these are um are the blood chips this taste this tastes
like something. Do they taste like blood? Yeah. It tastes like, no, it tastes like a, uh, let
me see. Let me have another chip. That wasn't as good, but it was still pretty good. Okay.
So I'm reading here. Wait, let's make more noises into the microphones. I think people
really enjoy that. I think that's people's favorite thing. Yeah. I Googled Doritos incognito
because I wanted to see and Pat I hate to say it but you have some competition
here one of the top results when I googled I googled Doritos incognito
which is just the name of of the chip and one of the one let's see one two
three four the fifth result is from a Wix website called chip reviewer dot
Wix site dot com and it's a review of Doritos incognito and I won't read the
whole review here. Do you have the bro button on your phone? Pat, come say something. Sorry,
Chupio played the fucking bro sound effect. I'm going to need you to do that a lot more.
Do that at least a hundred times during this episode. I want to hear if you agree with
this review okay okay crunch is a 9.4 out of 10 that texture I mean crunch 9.4 for
sure texture is a 9.6 I'm seeing I'm also seeing flavor as a 7.2 and an overall
I would give it a I would give it a 7 they they literally it tastes like
ketchup they taste like ketchup yeah they taste like ketchup chips that
That doesn't seem very incognita at all to me.
Yeah.
That seems like maybe the most direct and simple flavor you could have.
I uh...
I should have called it incognita.
They have ketchup flavored Doritos.
Maybe you got a mixed up bag.
What flavor is Doritos incognita?
It's a slightly spicy chili flavor that'll keep you grabbing for more.
Grabbing?
grabbing chips
is that a common thing down in mexico uh... to be a people are often grabbing
will group which is where we're sitting around
uh... yeah
i just was the work for the so i had not only do you know what the cover looks
like
is any terrifying
is completely terrifying suspects the special takes off his shirt
i know it was the grabber look like he looks exactly like he's in the heart
strangely enough
well i don't even know how they got the makeup on the grabber to make him look
that much like he's that so demonic and evil but he wears that he does look a lot like
he's an eerie mask and get this his mask can he can switch out the parts like it's a mix and match
oh i'm looking at that right now yeah oh you can i can uh you can buy a 3d printer version of that
mask wow it sounds to me like something only a grabber would buy the grabber is terrifying too
because he has a his he has a strong weapons for example he is one of his weapons that he can use
use
did
- You have a black phone?
I did have a black phone.
- Okay, interesting.
- This is not looking good for Eric.
- I mean, if you were naughty,
you were playing the naughty boy game.
Were you ever naughty when you were a child?
- I think I was naughty.
- He was pretty naughty.
- Yeah, oh I know.
- I was smoking cigarettes.
- You smoked cigarettes as a child?
- I've been smoking cigarettes as a kid.
I was getting tattoos.
- Well, that's one of the things that Grabber hates.
- He hates tattoos.
He hates tattoos.
He hates when a little kid gets a tattoo.
Yeah.
He hates tattoos, he hates piercings.
And smoking cigarettes.
He hates the disrespect in today's society that comes from cashiers and waiters.
He hates loud music.
Really?
Well I do that all the time.
He literally has a second house so he can go there if there's loud music.
He has a house that he will go into for loud music.
That was crazy.
He has two houses.
He's so rich.
Why is he killing himself?
a black phone spoilers let's you know go ahead yeah you know you're fucking
spoiling the shit out of the black phone today yeah i i was reading about i
haven't even seen it once i've read probably 10 articles about the black
phone just uh because before and after watching it i just had kind of a hunger
for knowledge about this fascinating character the grabber and something i
didn't know so i guess the so the black phone is based on a short story that's
by steven king's son um and apparently in the original and the story and the
The story of, oh I just got it, that was a thinker.
I'm the thinker.
The thinker.
In the original story, the grabber is really fat.
That's the only detail about it.
He's a really fat guy called the grabber.
So they couldn't have hired a fat guy?
No, they were like, we're going to have Ethan Hawke instead.
Why wouldn't they just hire like a fat bastard?
But I found that out because I was reading...
I've not seen fat bastard in a movie since probably 2003.
It has been a long time.
Yeah.
I would love to see fat bastard in a new movie.
I literally, the funny part, I was reading, I read that in an article, it was like one
of those articles, it was like every difference between the movie and the book, the black phone,
It's like the main difference is that the grabber is very fat
The fat grabber sounds like a like a product like Billy Mays would sell
The grabbers overall style and identity saw changes in the short story
The Galesburg grabber was a plus-sized guy named Al who dropped his groceries in the street
Wait, that's his origin is that he dropped his he dropped his groceries and he's like, oh, I wish I had some kind of grabber
Yeah, oh my god. I should become the grabber. Oh, yeah
fact every pills I
Think you buy fat grabber pills
Become the fat grabber I guess
Let's see. They're only 33. Oh, yeah. Yeah
nature's nature's sunshine fat grabbers intestinal health support
support.
Oh yeah, this looks nice.
Fat Grabbers is designed to support your weight management efforts.
Those are $33 a bottle.
And they'll make you kill a bunch of children.
So don't take these.
Is that what the Grabber does?
Explain, just tell me the whole plot.
So the Grabber, he's basically a magician.
He's a magician and he uses black, he dresses, he has white face paint and a black top hat
like a magician.
he drops his groceries in the street and and and white faces just okay nowadays
and we'll be okay yeah at least for the i mean the thing is he's a bad guy the
grabber so it's like you know most of the stuff is going to be like it's like an
always sunny when they were black it's exactly like i'm always sunny he drops
his groceries in the street and that but he does it next to a kid and then the
kid is like do you need help with that mister and he says yes i do in fact i'm
a magician would you like to see a magic trick and it says for my first trick i
I will become the grabber and he grabs the kid and throws him in the back of a van
and kids apps them completely and then he I guess hits them with a belt and calls
it says they're naughty and then he kills them and buries them yeah do you
think that that do you think that story was written about his father you think
Joe Hill was like yeah this is what my dad used to do yeah I think that that's
probably the case I think the grabber shares a lot in common with Stephen King
they're both terrifying, they both come up with horrific scenarios, and they both have
endangered children.
And they have a black phone.
I think that the Grabber is probably going to be one of the great horror characters of
our generation.
I mean I don't want to over-hype him, but he is absolutely terrifying sitting in that
chair shirtless with his signature strong belt.
do you think they're gonna like a grabber cinematic universe I heard they're doing
the grabber - mm-hmm it's called grabber grabber origin I heard grabber origins I
heard they're making two movies at once grabber origins and they're also making
the grabber - twin grabbers that's about two what's that's so funny that they
like they made that movie X and then just immediately we're like yeah people
are gonna want a prequel of this yeah I think they filmed the prequel at the
same time that's insane yeah and I think it's supposed to be a trilogy it's a
movie about porno what yeah yeah X is a movie about porno starring Mia goth Mia
goth yeah no Mia goth yeah Mia goth Mia Mia goth Mia like she looks that's like
she she looks exactly like her name is Mia goth it's a perfect name for that
woman what do you say Mia goth keep
Cody's at this movie oh yeah he was yeah
yeah that movie is about porno and they
basically here I'll do a quick rundown
for you it's a porno movie with lots of
and they me likey already yeah basically
they are filming a porno meanwhile
people are they're getting killed by a
mysterious and mysteriously sexual old
lady okay that's basically this movie
Is the old lady Kid Cudi?
No.
The old lady is... if you wanted a spoiler.
No, don't spoil it! I wanna watch it.
The old lady is Pearl.
This is the movie spoiler, uh...
Well, that's the thing, like...
Let's spoil every movie that we can.
I'm gonna spoil Nope now.
Okay, so the plotline of Nope, essentially...
No, wait, don't actually spoil that. I haven't seen it.
There's a thousand aliens...
I wanna see it, don't actually spoil it.
There's a thousand aliens that attack Earth and kill...
and kill 100 million people.
people. I'm taking my headphones off. I don't want to spoil that. Essentially
the spoiler to nope is that is that so that yeah, I mean there's these
characters. Yeah, this is what I'm done Patrick. I'm done. I'm done and then
they say nope when they get attacked by the alien.
Dude, you fucking spoiled the whole goddamn movie. You tricked me and
they're making a secret call and I don't want to and hey, they're making a
sequel called Yup and another one called maybe so
Yup.
There was a...
There was a sequel to "Nope" called "Maybe So".
Maybe.
A sequel to "Nope" called "Who Gives a Fuck".
Oh my god, nowadays that's how I feel with some of these movies.
Yeah.
The thing about that though, like if you genuinely don't want that movie X spoiled for you,
like the fact that the sequel is coming out and it's called "Pearl"
and there's the character named Pearl.
Like, the sequel's already spoiling it with its name.
It's a prequel.
Yeah, well, duh.
So what's the spoiler?
Is the character's name a spoiler to you?
The character's name is the spoiler for the big reveal in that movie.
I don't remember. I forgot that.
I forgot everything that happened in that movie instantly
after I watched it.
I've never seen it.
Oh really? I saw it in the theater. I saw it in the trailer come out and everyone was like,
they're making a fucking prequel for that? Everything you need to know about that movie
is that it's one of the movies where if you went to see it in the theater, at least half
the theater would applaud for the Nicole Kidman AMC thing. I feel like you pretty much can
understand what's going on. Yeah, you're not a big fan of the Nicole Kidman AMC. I don't
- I don't mind it, I hate when people applaud for it.
It's like, "Shut up, why don't you applaud
"for the Coca-Cola part?"
- Yeah, or the M&M's.
- Yeah, those have been around way longer.
- And the M&M's are being way sillier than Nicole Kidman.
- The M&M's are fucking fire.
- They are putting their fucking life on the line,
on their line.
They're putting their life on the line
because if you remember the end of that commercial,
they get shot into space in a rocket.
- Yeah, they're in so much--
I don't want to spoil that commercial at the movies for you.
Yeah, we don't get any questions.
When the M&M's get shot into space.
I don't want to spoil that commercial either,
but it's really easy to get spoiled because if you see the rating for that commercial,
you can easily tell it's going to go on because it clearly and the rating says R.
It's rated R for M&M's in peril.
I hate when the ratings spoil the movie.
Yeah, oh my god.
I hate when the MPAA rating tells you everything you need to know about the movie.
movie. Just at the start of the trailer. God, we need to get rid of these ratings that are
spoiling the damn movies. Like seriously, what is this rated G for Winnie the Pooh? Yeah,
what's that G for? Tigger? There's two G's in his name. That doesn't make any sense. I
as we fit
uh... it's a very nice uh... didn't look at what it is a very big
they've been really quickly with the group is really
it was a really anything either i don't think it is to have to take the blame on
that one
paid
the g_-twenty-one or are you going to look at what you'd
can you fix this one of the future
but what's that what's that g_-four
the g_m_ pig
and piglet
- Come on, you have to salvage that, we're testing you.
We said complete nonsense as a test,
you have to figure out a way to make this make sense
and be funny.
(laughing)
- I took a fucking--
- Okay, you're the one who's,
it's your job to edit these now.
You gotta figure this out.
- What, is that public knowledge?
- I don't know.
- It is now.
- Should I have not said that?
- Yeah, it's a secret.
- Why, do you not want people to know?
- Yeah.
- You don't want anyone to know that we hired you
and you're our only employee?
So okay, G for Winnie the Pooh.
Just make this happen.
- Okay.
- All right, let's.
What's the G for?
Kangaroo?
As in Roo and Roo's mom?
Oh, I forget Roo's mom's name.
I think it's mommy.
- It's Kanga.
- Okay, so what's the G for?
Kanga?
- You know they're making a--
- In the G for Kanga?
- They're making like a gritty reboot of Winnie the Pooh?
- I did see that.
- Yeah, I saw that, isn't it?
They're making a gritty reboot of Winnie the Pooh
and then they're also doing like,
who is it, Daniel Kulia or whatever?
Ariel Kalia is doing Barney.
Yeah.
What?
Yeah, he's doing a gritty Barney.
If he was a real fuckin' Barney fan, he would know that they already did a reboot like three years ago.
Yeah, it was called Godzilla King of the Monsters.
Nah. Nah.
Nah, but cameras playing.
Did I really just say that?
Real Barney fans know.
There was a really funny quote that he had about his Barney movie.
Yeah, it was something about the cleanup song, right?
Yeah, he also described it as heartbreaking.
His Barney movie.
His Barney movie is heartbreaking?
Barney taught us, "I love you, you love me. Won't you say you love me too?"
That's one of the first songs I remember.
And what happens when that isn't true?
I thought that was really heartbreaking.
I think it's time we brought the conversation about how toxic Barney is to the children.
Oh.
Barney, yeah.
I think I I mean I think I mean far be it for me to claim that Barney is a saint
but BJ and baby bop you know need to answer for some of this too. Uh-huh
that's facts. Baby bop needs to sit down and listen. Remember that episode of Barney where
on set Barney smoked in this costume and that's why he got fired? I did hear about
that actually in kindergarten I heard that that happened. That's so funny that
that was like the big I remember it was like Barty the guy who played Barney
smoked a cigarette and and he was in the costume and that's why I got fired so
good that that's one of the like universal rumors to that like everybody
heard that did you do you did you guys you have any Barney rumors or I guess do
you guys do they have yeah we still have Barney but growing up we didn't have
any funny rumors now you guys just took Barney a complete face value and liked
him even though he smoked in the suit. We thought that dinosaurs smoked cigarettes back in the
day. That's true. They go down to the store and they buy the cigarettes and they're like
real people. And back in those days those dinosaurs actually liked having tar in their
cigarettes. Oh my god yeah. They're like hey give me some more of that tar. Yeah they said
hey can I get a cigarette uh hold the tobacco keep it extra yeah yeah and
instead of a paper i'll have um um you're gonna wrap this okay yeah they
go they call it the odd way where this is this is the episode where we're
training you how to yeah so we're gonna start here's what we're gonna do we're
gonna start a joke we're gonna start a joke or no listen we're gonna start a
joke and then i'm gonna say i'm gonna snap my fingers at you i'm gonna say
juveo go and you're gonna finish you're gonna make the joke funny okay for
for example like the other day i went to the store and i could not believe my
eyes and what i saw on one of the shelves there was a
to be a go
some uh... some tips
no is that would be in a store
what okay i don't know what i would already work with a story with this
i said some day and what flavor of the chips was
and canada
no that's from earlier that's from earlier that's not going to work and
they taste like blood
okay alright alright because cameras are vampire i've gone to have these chips
so that every okay okay this is working this is working that's one of the back
right there okay all right uh uh speed around let's go uh poop
you can just say poop what do you mean no it's called word association you got it
Okay, poop.
Patrick.
Yo.
No.
That actually works.
No, that doesn't actually work.
He's actually really good at this.
That actually doesn't actually work at all.
He works.
He's actually really good at this.
Okay, piano.
Uh, piano.
Mozart.
Okay, that wasn't funny, but that makes sense.
Uh, dog kennel.
Patrick.
No.
That makes no sense.
It completely makes no sense.
I think he's actually really good at this.
Computer Duster.
Mmm... Patrick Duster.
No! No!
You can't just keep saying my name!
Patrick Duster is actually funny as fuck.
Chair!
Chair.
Umm...
You stumped him.
Yeah.
They don't have chairs in Mexico.
No, we don't.
Patricio. No! No! La Biblioteca. Oh I know this one. El Biblioteca. I don't know that
one. What's that? That means... Donde esta la biblioteca? That's a word they made up
for community. Yeah, they made that up. They made that crap up. Yeah, that's like, that
That was a language they made up like J.R.R. Tolkien did.
Mm-hmm.
Dan Harmon, yeah, I'm gonna be Harmon him when I see him.
What the hell?
When will you do that?
Yep.
He made me cry watching Rick and Morty.
He made me cry because I actually thought about existential-ass stuff.
Yeah, some of that shit's a little too poignant for me, I have to say.
It's like, can you at least have Morty be an adult character so I don't think about
my childhood when I'm watching the show?
ass at least have Rick and Morty be the same age the one and it's cool that they
have all those scenes were what you say I want to make Rick and Morty forever he
was like talking about it is like yeah we got the next season coming up next
year and I think we can just have it going off forever well it kind of it
kind of has to like they're kind of screwed into like only doing Rick and
Morty forever because like it's so fucking popular now like can you imagine
imagine if they were like if Rick and Morty got like cancelled right now.
Yeah I think it's also the thing of every every uh any other show they try to make is if people
it's just like oh this is a this is the Rick and Morty.
Right everything now is like a ripoff of Rick and Morty and like it's crazy how successfully
they did enter like the zeitgeist.
Yeah like it was like it it it felt like it was an instant.
I know and it's really impressive because I feel like usually shows based around science
just people aren't there for.
No nobody likes a nerd.
Exactly people.
But this show actually made it so nerds are cool as fuck.
And it drops fucking knowledge about interdimensional portals in a way that a lot of shows could
even not even dream of doing.
Like and and depression too.
That's why it's so impressive like a show like Doctor Who I mean that one teaches you
a lot of stuff if you really tune in keep that one taught us even Vincent van Gogh was
depressed.
but but you know even even that one. He even suffered from mental health.
Even that one it wasn't as it's it wasn't as scientific.
I mean you can tell because it's all live action and. No and it's all magical science too.
Exactly. It's none of this real science. A sonic screwdriver. You can tell also like there's
clearly some tensions behind the scene because they have to keep firing the main actor and
trying to change him out and be like no it's the same person the same guy. Yeah they go
clearly doctor who's a bird fed up with science that's what they're all saying
I don't want to do any more science fucking bird everyone talked to who
she's a fucking bird what is the doctor who change there like every year they
change it every year because the original show the actor who played dr.
who was a pedophile or knots that's how they say it over there across the pond
they say not okay and they changed him and then it kept happening where every
single because it's a show from it's a British show yeah every year they're
like oh this guy's a pedophile yeah the show is actually rid of him now the show
is officially we have a big episode sending him off to because you get
rewarded for being a pedophile yeah you realize the show is actually the actual
name of the show is just the doctor but people just call it doctor who because
it's so confusing because they change the actors so much.
Who's the doctor?
That's what I'm saying.
Was it a big deal when fucking Peter Capaldi was the, because he was the first Scottish
Doctor Who, right?
Yeah, I think so.
I have no idea actually.
I just said yeah.
I don't know why I said yeah.
It's okay.
Yeah, what are they going to have for that?
That guy Matt Smith.
I just want to, oh yeah, Matt Smith.
Dude, I remember Matt Smith.
i did what some doctor who in high school 'cause a lot of my friends uh... or into
it
uh... your friends were who locked out yeah they were who are
that's a so that's that never got i hated that show i i like i will i'm not
gonna pretend i didn't like doctor who
in high school but i will say i did always think that sure lock was gay and
i'm i'm
happy to be able to say that
i never show even though maybe sure lock is that that doctor is probably worse
than sure like i don't know i know i didn't watch that much of either i did
watch either of them. The only type of British show I watched was like comedy stuff because
I was like I don't fucking care about what these British people think about drama. I
want to know what is actually funny in a posh way.
Yeah exactly. What's like dry leash.
I think it's funny to make a guy who objectively looks like an alien be like a sex symbol for
girls.
For nerdy women.
women yeah oh my god look at this man I said it I said it before but he looks
like if white people made the statues on Easter Island he looks like he's
actually made of plasticine like he looks like a yeah it looks like one of
those Halloween masks you buy online that's like $80 because it has so much
you know when they they had like like like the early 3d like video games like
from like 2001 and like the cover art or no no no it's like a 2d side-scroller
but they had like 3d art as the box art and it's like oh this is what the main
character looks like he looks like he should be playing an astro he looks like
he should be on the cover of like a Sega Saturn astronaut game like jet and like
jet ketchup or something yeah he looks like you know and like you know and and
in Harry Potter when the guy gets the face on the back of his head.
Oh yeah.
He looks like the face grew.
He looks like the face on the back of a naked mole rat's head.
Like if a scientist in a lab grew a human face on like a...
What is he, he's on that new Game of Thrones show now?
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
I don't give a fuck.
Me neither.
I don't give a fucking shit about TV.
I don't give a fuck about Game of Thrones.
Uh huh.
This is a movie's in TV chat and we don't even give a fuck.
Speaking of, I just re-watched the last couple of episodes of Breaking Bad because my girlfriend
was watching them.
It's the best show.
It's incredible.
It's so good, dude.
It's nuts how good it is.
We actually care about shows that they're actually kind of fucking fire.
That's another fucking show that teaches people knowledge about science and drops knowledge
of...
Listen, even if you're a fucking dropout loser who wears bullshit-ass hoodies and has no style
at all you can still become a science genius.
Yeah.
If you befriend the right older man.
Jesse Pinkman wore super sky tops.
If you...
That's a crazy, crazy detail.
If you spend enough time with the right older man, you can become a genius.
Yeah.
What you need to do, you need to flunk out of school, right?
You need to not pay attention to a single lecture, single class in high school.
you befriend at the age of like 18 an old man you walk up and down the street.
I forgot about that too. He's supposed to be like either 18 or like very early 20s.
Yeah dude that's the funniest fucking detail like Aaron Paul did not
like I mean he's great but he just does not. No he's a great actor yeah he just
just forget that he's supposed to be that age basically yeah you're just like oh
yeah he's just a guy but yeah my head he's like at least 10 years older than
Walter jr. if you win yeah if you if you are if you befriend the right older guy
at 18 you you grind you go out on secret missions with him I mean you guys do
stuff together that no one can believe you guys you're gonna become a genius
That is like Rick and Morty. You are also, you will become a slave.
Mm-hmm. You will become to a bunch of, you'll become a slave to the Aryan Brotherhood, and you will cook them meth.
Yes, but then, but then your old man will come save you.
Your old man will come save you and it'll be fire. Yeah. Do you think Rick and Morty's gonna do a Breaking Bad episode?
I hope they do a crossover. Oh my god. Jesse. I'd never even thought of that. And Mr. White. Now I'm freaking the fuck out.
That would actually be fire. I think all the best Rick and Morty episodes is where they just do a movie
And then I watch it, and I'm like the movie that they're doing right now. I like that movie I
Watch it, and I'm just happy because I'm thinking about Jurassic Park or whatever yeah, yeah, I like that that episode of Rick and Morty
where
Kevin brings in all the chili oh my open I
Can't stand that episode because I'm like that is a waste of chili when it spills
Yeah, yeah, I'm like you could have literally fed the crew with that you're pouring it on the ground. Okay, that's true
Okay
He should have fed you should have fed the cast and crew with you know a lot of a lot of movie cast and crews are
Completely homeless and starved to death
They when they're done with a best boy
They leave the best boy out in the cold and they don't even give him a jacket
Yeah, there's and they tell him the whole time that the the what is it like three to six months?
they're shooting that movie they're like you're the best boy you're the best boy
and we love you and he's like okay love you so much can i have some clothes from this from the
prop department because i'm i'm completely naked when i go home i i rent clothes to wear during
the work day but i can't afford to rent clothes when i get home and they're like no sorry you can't
you can't wear any of these clothes we have to burn them because we we 3d printed them they're
their proprietary designs their live
action there for the live action
yugioh reboot and we can't have them
leaked so no you're going to have to
freeze to death at home and he goes
home to his igloo in in glendale
california
and the best looking true is to death
and this is okay.
Disgusting it's okay in hollywood,
but it's not okay.
It's not okay over in new york
and no you'll do it on new york.
The best boy see the best boy on like
- That's not how we do it in New York.
- Sorry, my New York accent popped out.
- Yeah, that's not how we do it in New York.
- Okay, all right, well here we go.
The funniest thing about New York is,
go, the Ark.
The Ark? - No.
- That's pretty good. - It's not funny.
- No, it's-- - The Ark is not funny.
- There's something there.
- No, Ark isn't funny.
- Maybe when I walk into the bodega
and ask the Ark to make me,
(snaps fingers)
- A pizza.
(laughs)
- What?
What?
(laughs)
It's a deli, they don't have a pizza oven.
- That's why it's funny, Pat, you don't understand.
You're being too harsh on him.
It's funny 'cause it's just to present it's real.
- It's not funny to make fun of the vibrant culture.
- Okay.
(laughs)
- It's not funny.
- Okay, what's his culture?
- Nuevo York.
- No, where's he talk from?
Well, he's from some Persian country. I don't know.
Okay. That's funny.
Something about me that changed ever since I moved to New York is I can't get enough
of musica.
I can't get enough of musica. Oye como va?
Oh my God.
I mean, dude, ever since I moved to New York, my meals have totally changed.
I mean, I'll get up from the computer to have lunch and I'll make myself a peanut butter
and jelly torta.
And it's, yeah, I mean, I didn't used to ever do this.
I used to be a clown eating sandwiches.
Now, I learned about...
You know what's a really big New Yorker movie?
This recently that they come out?
What?
Bullet Train.
Bullet Train?
I thought that was a Japanese movie.
No, it's about New York because it's on the metro, it's on the subway.
Oh, okay.
And Bad Bunny is in it.
Bad Bunny is in it?
Is he really?
Who is?
Wait, Bad Bunny just kissed a background dancer?
I saw that, he kissed a male.
I don't know about all that. I heard he kissed a male. Yeah. I heard that man that he kissed
was Good Bunny. I heard that was Good Bunny. Who is Bad Bunny? Is he a musician? He's a
music artist. Cameron doesn't get it like me and Jubio do. No, I'm still learning. I'm
still learning. I'm still growing. There's a lot of things. Sing one of his songs. Go
- Go ahead.
- Upside.
(laughing)
- What's that?
- Living la vida loca.
- Oh, that's him.
Okay, yeah, I know that one.
- Yeah, yeah.
He got in a big controversy recently.
He kissed a guy.
- Yeah.
- I heard he kissed a male.
- I've definitely heard a Bad Bunny song before,
but I don't think I could ever tell you the title of 'em.
I know that one song,
'cause there was a guy playing it so loud
outside of my apartment that I just shazammed it.
And I started listening to it on my phone.
(laughing)
I gotta look up what the song is called.
But it's the one that goes like,
bop, bop, bop, bop, bop.
- What?
- You know that one?
- I heard that Bad Bunny's real birth name is Melvin Nymire.
- Really, where'd you hear that?
I heard that he chose Bad Bunny because he thought it sounded cooler.
But I think Melvin's a cooler name.
Wow, that's interesting.
Yeah, just a fact I learned about him at the bodega.
You know what they used to call him when he was a kid?
What?
Melvin the Martian.
Is that true?
Really?
Yep.
Oh my god.
Do you guys have some big news I left off on sharing?
This is the song.
Okay, let's hear the song first I guess.
I have no idea what that is.
Is that, is this what you were describing as being pop, pop, pop?
Yeah, it gets there.
It gets there?
What's the song?
It's called "De Manhattan Pa El Bronx" by El Cherry Scombe and Dwoba Montana.
so that's not bad bunny. Yeah that's not bad bunny at all. I really just showed my ass
there. I've been shazamming so much stuff. You're a fake bad bunny fan. No I know I am.
You probably didn't even know that he kissed a male. Yeah that's true. Only real fans know
that. I love shazam so much. I love shazam, I love touch tunes, I love music. I like la
music I love music so I have some big news though okay yeah yeah I decided to
visit every country in the world really yeah I'm talking America uh-huh
United Kingdom okay China wait I did not I land was that it doesn't say that bad
Bad Bunny's name, it doesn't say that his name is Melvin...
Where did you get that name?
I'm looking at Benito Antonio Martinez Ocasio.
Ocasio?
Woah!
He's AOC's cousin.
He's AOC's cousin, I think.
That's why he's so popular.
You believed me when I said that Bad Bunny's name was Melvin Nymire?
Yeah.
Who's Melvin Nymire?
Who's made that name?
that
i was completely believe the other
what do you know what i'm i a r_t_u_ friend
that's what i don't know
uh...
this is a source for the other no one i was dead
recipes uh... that's a shame he died died in the nineteen thirties
uh... but i'm looking here
says that
J Balvin's real name is Melvin Highmire.
That's where Balvin comes from is Melvin.
Oh, oh.
That makes sense.
Makes complete sense.
Who's that other, because there's a lot of, there's a new, and look, and look, I like
it.
There's a lot of new, like J Balvin and like Bad Bunny, like there's a lot of Latin artists
Oh yeah, did you see DJ Cameron F?
DJ Cameron F?
He's making waves in the New York community.
Really?
Can you sing one of his songs?
That's one of my favorite reggaeton artists.
Why don't you sing one of his songs?
DJ Cameron F.
What's up?
Can you sing one of his songs? I want to hear it.
No, they don't have any voice parts.
Oh.
So I can't sing it.
What does it sound like though?
It's like grooving and party-esque.
Yeah.
you all i just i'm looking at a a look at wikipedia list
here this is a honorific nicknames in popular music did you know that billy
joe armstrong is the prince of american punk rock
actually actually gave him that name
are really uh...
you guys know that i'm gonna visit every country in the world
you have a uh... uh... i'm going to i mean i i'm going to find it uh...
i'm going to
senegal
i'm going to uh... all party islands
are you going to serbia yes
are you can you can uh... check it is on from seven
barrage on the big
all right yeah i think sabi
who is the king of romani music
i really knew that
you are in the did you know that more to cut and david is the king of jewish
music
for killing
actually didn't know that i thought the king of the uh... and his music was
patrick doran
no
no i just think not anymore
not anymore no i don't know what happened
now i got
fuckin
beat out by more type and a_b_c_ here
there is a lot of man i'm sorry to say
yet not out now is nothing i said it was just uh...
i wanted to go in a different direction i wanted to do my next album i wanted to
be more dance
centric as i was listening to a lot of d_j_ cameron f_b_i_a_
and i uh...
and he has a lot of people he makes people want to dance
yeah and i tried to make uh... i tried to make a jewish ragged tone album
i tried to put like some bad bunny style beats over like uh... fiddler on the
roof
uh...
with uh...
and uh... yeah i think that really uh... well i thought it was going to change
the game but uh...
huh you're the you're the filler in the roof am i right i'm the fiddler in the
roof now
did you know that d_j_ bobo is the king of dance in switzerland
well we actually i did i think d_j_ bobo collabed with d_j_ cameron f on that one
song
already have a lot of what was it
rave on robot island i think it was called a little bit of a disincentive
all time i i got a clear here
uh... go play a little bit
he's playing a split
uh... with
but that's not it
uh...
it's also you know everyone saying that more to cut and david is the king of
jewish music meanwhile twenty sixteen
uh... he called uh...
of brocco bomb of the director of the people of the report
i would why would you say the term
we want to know what we need to look at it easily gets a bit of the usage is
critical bomber
is generally used in the hebrew bible to refer to a dark-skinned person of
effort
that's not a nice thing to say
what do you think
he's a hebrew racial slur for black people
well yeah i'm reading what mordecai ben david said and that's not a good thing
why would you say that
i'm not gonna say it again
Oh my god.
Because I didn't know what it meant.
It was so obvious what it meant.
I guess it's Hebrew for the N word.
It's clearly the Hebrew N word.
It's obviously what it is.
What else would it be?
Well, that's my bad.
What other racial thing would he call Obama?
I don't know.
I thought it was like an antiquated one.
Like the stuff my grandpa used to say.
Like what?
I'm not going to get into that.
Alright guys, let's do a list of our favorite racial words.
I'm not gonna get into that.
Well actually, if you knew anything about this fucking podcast, you know it's a premium episode, we don't do lists.
Alright.
Yeah, I didn't know that that... I didn't... Look, I don't speak a lick of Hebrew.
I don't either. I could easily tell what was happening in that sentence.
I was just the king of Jewish music for a little bit.
Yeah.
Okay, let's change the subject. Let's get back to movies.
You guys catch, uh, A Turtle's Tale 2, Sammy's Escape from Paradise?
A Turtles Tale 2. Sammy's Escape from Paradise. You guys catch it?
I didn't catch it no. It just came out?
It just came out in 2012. Yeah, what is it about?
It's about Sammy and Ray. They're essentially, they have grandchildren and two of their grandchildren
are captured. That's all I remember from it. But apparently it stars Caitlin Marr.
Oh, okay.
Got a Gnar.
And Carter Hastings.
Yeah. Yeah, that movie was fire.
You guys didn't see it? No.
That's your loss, I guess.
What was the last movie you saw, Pat?
Sorry, I'm reading more about this
Mordecai Ben David guy.
Okay, let's talk more about what he said.
He, uh,
I'm not reading that, I'm just, uh,
I'm just looking at, at, uh,
many albums he's made.
Oh yeah?
Pretty prolific.
I don't know who gave me that title.
I don't know who was calling me the king of Jewish music.
When this guy was around?
Is that what you're saying?
When this guy was around, yeah.
Solo albums, collaborations, this guy truly is the king of Jewish music.
But I guess not a very nice guy.
Based on what I read.
Why not?
Oh, did you guys...
Just now.
children surprise island boxcar children surprise island i think my friend david has a cameo
in that really because i'm looking at david s pumpkins
whoa yep the boxcar children surprise island was directed by the guy who directed spawn
Wow.
Whoa, listen to this, listen to this guy's filmography here, okay?
So he's got, I'll read in, this guy's name is Mark Az Dipay.
And here's his, I'll read from, from, that's how you're supposed to say his name, Mark Az
Dipay.
I'm going to read his movies from earliest release date to most recent, okay?
So first off, Spawn, that's first.
Heater, right out of the gate.
then we got pixel perfect and then
halloween sound, how we in town
high. These are both disney
channel originals right after
spawn, then frank and fish. I
only got garfield gets real
garfields fun fest garfields
pet force in a row. That's a
garfield trilogy and then reef
to high tide and then the box
car children in twenty fourteen
and then in twenty seventeen we
got michael jackson's halloween
and then twenty eighteen the
Michael Jackson's Halloween.
And the Marmaduke.
The one hour animated special packed with the vocal talents of some of your favorite CBS
stars and the King of Pop's most memorable hits.
Oh, Lucy Liu is in it.
Oh wow, and Kiersey Cummings.
So is Alan Cummings.
Jim Parsons.
Hey, it's Jim Parsons plays Hey Man.
Diedrich Bader's in it.
As Franklin Stein.
Oh, that's our good friend.
Sorry, that's our friend.
Oh, and Christine Baranski.
remembers our AMA with Diedrich Bader. Remember Christine Baranski from
The Grinch? I can't believe that Jim Parsons was able to land the role of
Hey Man. That's huge. Everyone knows Hey Man right? Michael Jackson's Halloween in 2017.
that
I just found a video that I think we should watch.
And he gets addicted to making videos.
Through the
one, not on the selfie camera, but just
on the back camera on his phone.
And he gets very popular.
And that's it.
That's the whole movie. He doesn't even take a single selfie
in the movie. But it's called Selfie Dad.
That's cool.
That's incredible. Yeah, it just came out.
It just came out? Yep.
I'm gonna have to watch it. We should watch it right now.
We should watch it. We're gonna watch it right now.
you want to hear about your check check this video out for we got a video to
watch
yeah now that i mean we can all watch this together
okay what's this video here
uh... hold on it
started playing in a different window is about
but this is uh... i can't
this is jim parsons talking about
my name and music
also in the guise of a halloween story i play hey man he is somebody who has been
put under the spell by this evil queen.
Today, Hey Man's a pumpkin head,
but when no one's watching,
he turns into a wonderful dancer.
Which is something out of the blue that he asked me to do,
and there was no way I was gonna say no,
because anything that's celebrating Michael Jackson music
is just really enjoyable to be a part of.
My favorite Michael Jackson song,
it's "Human Nature," I would say.
There's so many good ones.
It's turned into my favorite type of sound
he produced. It's wistful in its own way, there's a melancholy to it.
He's not talking about Heyman enough.
No, go back to Heyman.
Yeah, come on Jim, talk about Heyman.
...was as a musician as much as anything, but I find it very moving.
My favorite memory of Michael Jackson...
Come on, talk about Heyman!
...most distinctive, I remember being at a birthday party at a Chuck E. Cheese in Houston.
And Michael Jackson walked in.
...puppet things that sing.
And played in the ball pit with us.
monitors or whatever and I tie very much watching the um...
He what? He tied?
in that Chuck E. Cheese on some monitor and as silly as it sounds to me
You got tied up at Chuck E. Cheese?
birthday party it's...
Talk about hey man!
That's exactly the essence you know
you think of music in a car or music on your headphones or whatever but it's like
you almost don't realize you keep dancing and moving and living to
until years later like oh that was that's the soundtrack of my life
I think in the same way when
Come on.
Alright, say some more shit about Hey Man.
It's over, it's done.
He's never going to talk about Hey Man again.
Yeah, he's not talking.
He's done with Hey Man.
He's talking too much about Michael Jackson.
What's this Selfie Dad thing?
I do have a list of Michael Jackson's Halloween characters.
This is Selfie Dad.
Why are you putting it at two times speed?
Because it's legitimately the whole movie.
That's the whole movie?
Wait.
It's the whole movie.
Full family comedy movie.
Yeah, it's a family comedy movie.
It's my favorite movie of all time.
I don't think we should watch the whole movie.
Well you said we should watch the whole movie.
That's what you said.
It's good on you for following orders.
But this is kind of like a bit of malicious compliance.
Where I think you know...
That we shouldn't watch.
We shouldn't be watching this whole movie right now.
Yeah, we shouldn't have that much fun.
We should go back to work.
I gotta figure out if there's a way to...
Download that Hey Man video.
I want to see all the Hey Man scenes.
Here's the one piece of trivia about SelfieDad on IMDB.
The thank you credits list in the credits begins by mentioning Chic Filet San Clarita,
spelled without the K in Chick.
This should give steam to all of the Mandela Effect subscribers who say that this was the
original spelling of the restaurant chain's name.
What?
Isn't it?
That was Chick.
Isn't it Chick Filet like uh...
- CHIK.
- Chick-fil-A.
- No, isn't it CHIK, F-I-L-A?
- No.
That's not even what people were,
that's not even the Mandela effect thing.
That's just a completely different--
- I thought it was spiky chicken.
- Chicken.
- Oh, you know what it is?
It's 'cause I think that it's Chick-fil-A with a K
because all the ads were the cows.
- Oh, they spell it wrong.
- That said eat more chicken, yeah.
So that's, so we just debunked a Mandela effect right there.
there. That was actually very, very smart of you. I wouldn't have thought of that.
Did you know that that didrich bader voices franklin stein a mad scientist
cat who works for conformity and built a machine that destroys music really
know that now however after he's captured by vincent and victoria he
reveals that he really wanted to make music before meeting conformity and
joins forces with the pair who use his machine to summon michael jackson.
it's funny that you have a lot of money they use a machine that's destroys music
to someone michael jackson you think they'd use a machine
that destroys children's lives
is that so funny that uh... i mean fuckin what's his name
that's literally the what
angry video game nerd says in his video about michael jackson moonwalker but it
is funny that the
the uh... the the goal of the game moonwalker is to save a bunch of
children
in a lot of time
uh...
speaking of angry video game nerd i was hanging out with uh... you were hanging out with an angry video game nerd?
i was hanging out with AVGN the other day
and he said to me he said
ASS! that's a shit load of fuck!
what did he say?
that's what he said and he said that while he was playing a game really what game?
uh... turtles in time
ninja turtles really he didn't like that game?
now
i guess i was angry
now i was hanging out as a you know it's uh... a couple friends one time we're
outside of a bar i was hanging out with uh...
with like shut the net to name drop
those hang out with sean mccarthy in this guy
you just made a lot of us in the end
dropped death by name below always a big name sean mccarthy
you know he's a big
the big star big star celebrity sean p mccarthy
And this guy comes up to us and starts like,
I don't remember what he was asking us,
but then the conversation turned to him asking us,
oh, he asked me what I do, and he was like,
oh, so what do you write?
And I was like, I don't, what are you talking about?
And he's like, you write?
You do graph?
And I was like, no, I don't do graffiti.
I don't, I'm not a writer, sorry.
And then he's like, well, what do you do?
And then Sean said that we're both comedians,
And then he talked Sean's ear off for 20 minutes,
talking about how AVGN is his perfect ideal of a comedian.
(laughing)
Like, we couldn't leave because like,
Sean was smoking his weed.
So, the guy had him locked in conversation about AVGN.
- I had a very similar experience,
where at my old job at the liquor store,
my one of my managers is pro it was like a
like late thirties guy
and i never want to tell if i was working at i don't want to tell you by like i
have a podcast is a people are gonna go listen to it and that's
i don't hear talk about meeting poop
uh... one of the work that you get it so whenever somebody asked what does that
was like i was working part-time is like a veto money asking like why why only
part-time as like oh yeah i have another job i uh...
ice stream video games
as usually i feel like you say that to an older person they just won't care
those assume yeah i think
and it but he was like
all that's awesome you should tell me which humans and you should also check
out this guy angry video game there
hell yeah
did i i rewatched uh... in a_b_g_ and video recently
i think i i rewatched a_b_g_ and and i was also showing it
a friend of mine
uh... the irate gamer
'Cause I don't think he'd ever watched either of them.
And, uh, 'cause we were talking about Michael Jackson, Moonwalker,
and I was showing him that, and then we got into this, like, fuckin' rabbit hole
of just watching irate gamer videos for, like, an hour.
And we watched the irate gamer reviewing, uh,
every one of the, like, like, Yummy Mummy and, uh, uh, Count Chocula.
And it's like a video that the irate gamer made detailing the history of like forgotten
uh like the Count Chocula cereals which is like Yummy Mummy and like um what's the other one it's
like called like? Frankenberry. It's not called Franken- no Frankenberry. Frankenberry Booberry.
Frankenberry Booberry and Count Chocula are still around but then there's Yummy Mummy
And then there was like a werewolf one. Ghost...uh...berry.
Yeah, werewolf berry. I don't want...I...I...it's not called like creature pieces.
I really hope it's not called creature pieces. Oh, it's called chocolate screams.
Fruit brute. Monster...it was called fruit brute. Monster milk. Monster milk. I think it was monster
milk. Yeah. Yeah, it was...it was fruit brute and it was lime fla...it was...it was lime flavored.
for this pizza is lime flavored cereal I'm it was completely live flavored cereal
oh there was something called crispy creature damn crispy creature crispy
creature is that just reach your crunch was it looks like it was green flavor oh
that's one of the worst flavors of cereal yeah yeah green cereal creature
Creature Crunch.
Creature Crispy.
Crispy Crunch was good though.
Crispy Crunch and uh...
It got rid of all that terrifying creature theming.
And it was just plain Crispy Crunch.
I'm looking at a box of Creature Crunch here and I guess this is a video game that came
out for Creature Crunch.
It's an animated nightmare of a game starring Martin Short and Eugene Levy.
It was like Creature Crunch cereal I guess came with a game starring them.
Wow.
Creature Cream?
No, I don't want a Creature Cream all over me.
I got a creamy creature.
Don't say that shit.
Nah, where's that thing about Obama? No that oh, come on, that's not here's big news big news in August
2022 fruit brute returns with the artwork done by cause I actually also
news -
In in 2022. I heard in October 2022 the first week of October Jubio will be doing
Podcast about list this will be to be a week 68 straight hours of streaming without sleep
uh... and he'll be live continuously the entire time and he'll be playing games
the whole time there'll be no just chatting or watching any videos yet and
there'll be no sleeping and there'll be very little eating
there'll be some e_d_
uh... but you'd be a lady d_r_ machine before you'd be a week is to be a timber
where he'll be streaming everyday of september but then we're going to
determine a week which will of all the new juby october
uh... if he does well
we might extend it
to
reading reddit me like I'm like already read it in the newspaper.
No, thanks.
Get off these websites, but you should go on the website twitch.tv/podcasts about listed
for and then and then follow Jubio for Jubio timber Jubio timber and Jubio week that's
coming up.
But I think that's that's that so yeah, just go watch the streams or whatever.
It's gonna be fun as fuck and it's gonna be completely continuous for 160 hours.
168 hours straight.
- Uh huh.
- So.
- 168 hours of Jubio.
- How many hours are in a month, Thad?
- So a week is 168, so then 168 times four is 200.
(laughing)
- Okay, bye.
- Bye.
- 672 weeks, hours.
*laughs*
(clears throat)