You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
Are you guys ready to be my dual best man?
My akimbo best man?
I'm so excited.
I'm ready.
I'm already doing this.
This is my second dual best man role.
You've done dual besties before?
No, I have one coming up.
My brother's wedding.
When's that?
and what's the venue
july
the menu as they serve in the venue is outside
and am i do you have a plus one
now i don't think so
wait is your plus one your other best man
yes
the plus one is my other best man and it's my younger brother so
the best man should be able to have a best man to help him
yeah oh my that's what i thought
yeah i thought it was
an apprentice
exactly an apprentice best man
who can prepare the apprentice best man is preparing for the second wedding when
the couple gets divorced true yeah married that's a new basically you need
like you have like a paddle one yeah exactly yeah yeah which is a Jedi for
apprentice yeah oh yeah you're right it is yes the same thing yeah but that's
yeah no that is what you need I'm gonna send they do have to wear the outfit
though yeah you have to wear the braid the braid I'm gonna not invite no they
to wear a wedding dress no that's the bride you're thinking of the oh my god
I'm so stupid how am I gonna get married I need to go to one I thought a pad a
one would wear a wedding dress - so to my wedding I'm gonna invite my dad and not
my mom and just give my dad a plus one and see what he does hey you might want
to hey mom you might want to yeah I know guys have been divorced for 12 years but
you might want to patch a couple things up yeah it's like a saw game yeah I don't
know you might want to yeah I don't know yeah Cynthia you do know you did not
receive an invitation but your ex-husband has a plus one you have to
call Dave yeah the key is in Dave's wallet apologize to Dave or miss your
son's biggest day of his life make your choice maybe I'll do a funny themed
wedding yeah that's a good idea yeah under the sea under the under the sea
way beams like the song under the sea from the Little Mermaid yeah yeah you
can be that crab like an octopus playing you're gonna be the mermaid I'm gonna be
the mermaid no not the mermaid the mermaid is my wife yeah can I be the
can I be the genius seagull who's really smart you are both Ursula no we're
we're flow. You're the eels. You either get to be Ursula and we're the eels.
Ursula doesn't marry the mermaid. Yeah she does. Not the one I saw. Yeah. I saw one where she put a
tentacle in her thing. That was a fling. That was a fling. It's like that was that was her hall pass
to make sure she wasn't gay before the wedding. Everybody does that. It's true. I have to fuck
one guy before I before I commit to my wife forever. It's like it's like when
they DNA test you at town hall. They DNA test you to see if you're gay.
They get the the gene they find the gay gene and they say you can't marry. I don't know how
to tell you this you can't marry your wife because you're gay. Yeah. Oh no.
Oh no. You know what should have tipped me off is that I'm a woman. Yeah I'm not gay what?
that would be my reaction yeah I don't know why I remembered this today I don't
know how to segue this into this but I think I was looking at letterboxd and I
said I was looking at my list of movies that I need to rewatch and I saw El
Mariachi and I've never seen that I was thinking of the third movie in the
Robert Rodriguez Mexico trilogy Once Upon a Time in Mexico but I saw that when I
was like seven by accident I saw it like because I was sleeping on my parents
floor and I woke up at like midnight. It was on HBO and you remember how HBO used
to have softcore porn on at like midnight? Oh yeah dude. So when I was seven I saw
like that movie ended and then like this like I just remember it was like a
fucking it was a woman playing piano and she adjusted her boobs while she was
playing the piano. Like she was sitting there at the piano like you know when
you like crack your fingers and then start playing. She adjusted her boobs. That was like the
joke and I remember like seeing that I think like a couple minutes into the
movie I like turned I was sleeping on my parents floor so I turned to my dad and
I was like this movie sucks I I the the softcore like Showtime porn when I was a
kid we had like a Showtime free trial yeah and one of those movies came on
late at night and I was like but I didn't know what it was and I watched
like the first 10 minutes and then I had to go to bed but I was like oh there's
like a really interesting movie that seemed like really really cool that's
like that's like an awesome movie I want to watch that later and so then the next
day I was like oh shit this is like this movies coming up mom we should watch
this movie like this is really good and then like five minutes past where I'd
watch it was just guys just just fucking doggy styling in the kitchen it was
awesome she's like this is your favorite movie yeah mom yeah yeah you have an
awesome little pervert son is that so hard to believe yeah I just the idea of
just like seeing like a porno when you're really young and just being like
this movie's kind of cool yeah just like the exposition yeah right like you don't
know anything about like it's like when you see like a Quentin Tarantino movie
for the first time in middle school and you see like a title card like slam onto
the screen you're like holy fuck right I didn't even know you could do that this
must be one of those art movies yeah yeah damn they're talking in like a David
Lynch Ian kind of way yeah the dialogue in in the ghost in the teeny bikini is
very yeah the thing is those movies also there's like very little sex in them for
porn no no it's not usually like three scenes per 90 minutes basically so you
have to sit through 20 minutes of them being like we're not gonna be able to
afford rent this money yeah well you got to go visit the landlord and do whatever
it takes yeah yeah it's kind of a dark turn for one of those movies actually
it's a lot happier than that it's usually like Frankenstein's horny yeah
you got a suck-in fuck Frankenstein yeah cuz they do try to give it some
amount of like but they never show they never show anything going into anything
well you guys fucked up that that's like that genre of movie you don't you don't
see that as much anymore now it's all like took it all just go the kids just
can go to like porn demon net yeah watch like clown gets fucked in the ass in an
underpass like just their fingertips yeah yeah they don't have to sit through 30
minutes of like it's disgusting how much porno kids have nowadays we gotta get
this porn out of these kids hands. We do. There's kids on the street smoking porn. Uh-huh they're
smoking porn they're shooting it up. They're shooting pornography directly into their brains.
I'm sure I'm sure that's not gonna fuck up this generation at all the act the
amount of access to porno they have. I think we were probably the first
generation of people who had like you know unlimited porn. Every stand-up
comedian that's like older than like 30 had a bit where it's like I used to what
I used to read a playboy in the woods yeah yeah yeah I said I have to jack off
to a cloud yeah yeah trying to do that bin be related like I used to have to
jack off to my mom wait till my mom use the bathroom just fucking look under the
door frame yeah how good you have it I made a telescope out of a straw and I
put it through the keyhole yeah I just have my after jack off to my grandma
getting changed at the hospital come on you kids are so spoiled nowadays if you
want to see your dad your mom's pussy you just go online now. Man I used to have to
run into my dad's room on Saturday morning and pull down his sheets and see
his bare ass. Yeah it's Father's Day even though we both knew it wasn't. It's
breakfast in bed you don't want to have any breakfast. Now luckily I can just look at the
picture of my dad's bare ass that I have on my iPhone. Yeah well the technology
never ceases to amaze me. Technology's so crazy. And now I just got a 3D print on my mom's butt.
And now I have a drone. Yeah, now I have a drone. So I don't even have to be at my mom's house.
Now I just have a, now you put a spy camera in your parents' closet.
Yucky. Right? Yucky. Put a nanny cam.
Hey mom, I have this toy that I want to keep in your closet.
I have this kid in here. It's for Christmas. I used to have to give my mom a walkie
talkie and say, "Press this button when you're peeing."
(laughter)
- Anytime you fart, press this button.
And then now, I just go on the Clubhouse app,
and I listen to my parents fart at each other.
- Is that, what is Clubhouse?
- Now I have the ring doorbell,
and I just had to move the toilet to the front door.
(laughter)
- Is Clubhouse, is that the, what is that?
- It's for listening to your parents fart at each other.
- I think I heard, I think I saw like a clip,
like something on Twitter.
- It's like the, it's a thing where like--
I think on Twitter the other day there was like a group Jack off session there and
everyone was like yeah they were like you got to delete they got to delete this
fucking app. Nope that's not the kind of clubhouse I want to be a part of.
What is clubhouse? I've heard of it maybe once before. It's like an app where they have like they have like people who are
mostly like media people have these like rooms where they're basically doing like
a live podcast or like a Q&A thing but then also do that people can talk back
so you can like be listening like Eric Weinstein talk about how like math
proves that gay marriage is wrong and be like you're fat mm-hmm so it's kind of a
great app that sounds really technologically awesome it's very
advanced and I came up with it it seems like something that we could make use of
and maybe do some like awesome stuff with it's kind of I don't like I don't
trust it cuz someone's gonna come in and start jacking off nobody jacks off to
anything dude what do you mean people just say people are always
nobody actually does that and that's yeah mm-hmm
they're probably just like sharing a video from their camera roll to their
yeah to their feet 90% of people when they're alone with their penis will just
try to push it into their bodies and see what it would look like if they didn't
have one and then fold the skin back over it that's what most people are
- What did you just like throw up, Patrick?
What was that noise?
- Pat is getting so easily grossed out this episode.
- Yeah, I don't know, I think I swallowed something weird.
You know what I did?
I did dry--
- You swallowed a gross-out potion?
- I think I swallowed--
- Yeah, I dry swallowed an ibuprofen before we recorded.
- Dry swallowed, that's a, what if you died?
- Hey, that shit, this is just the art part of the game.
- Why do you do that?
- I don't know why I did that.
I think I was just--
- You don't even like, you can literally just get water.
yeah there's a there's a sink like yeah I don't know away away from me I don't
know why I didn't do that it's like you did I don't know it's like trying to look
cool as a kid like walking around with with unlaced shoelaces and just eating
shit like well that's no reason to do that that's the thing in every fucking
movie they have if somebody's addicted to pills because you see me because I saw
dry swallow them in movies I saw them I saw the the the cop who's addicted to
gambling on the Sopranos do it the Sopranos Sopranos Sopranos Sopranos
Come on dude, it's the Sopranos. Get your head out of your ass. No. What's wrong with you dude?
It's Sopranos. It's not the Sopranos. It's Soprano. Tony says it that way. It's the Sopranos.
It's the Supremos. Supremo. Teemo Supremo. No. That was a show right? Teemo Supremo?
no you think of Tevo yeah Teemo Supremo no you're thinking of Tevo no that was a
show from 2002 to 2004 on toon Disney starring Spencer Breslin and Fred
Willard you have a terrifying brain I'm looking at Google no but remembering
remembering that that even existed I watched it as a kid. When you were three or four
every sentence Patrick says he's also typing it into Google at the same time
when we're recording a podcast I have to I have to keep make sure that I'm right
Google he loves he loves IMDB that's what he really likes to look at well
you have I am are you a pro on IMDB no no it's free you don't need to be a pro
user you can get the celebrities phone numbers or something oh yeah I forgot
about that yeah whoa yeah you get like instant access to everybody's private
information and one per person who's on there damn I should I should look into
this no what respect their privacy dude can I play the Google doodle right now
what is it today it's just it's just a picture of a lady
hmm Maria Maria gray there graver griever first female Mexican composer to
Eve International complain... declaim...
That's you actually.
I think I'm dying.
I think I'm passing away.
If you were Mexican, your name would be Don Elote and you'd eat a bunch of street corn.
My name would be Don Elote, it wouldn't be like Patricio?
No.
It'd be Don Elote.
Like Don Quixote.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, but you'd be just munching mayonnaise, you'd be sucking the mayonnaise off of corn
cobs.
I haven't had street corn in such a long time.
Let's make it happen for you.
Yeah, let's get some milotes.
Let's go get one of those like $18 street corns that you get at like fancy restaurants.
Yeah.
Where it's even like a tiny section of the corn.
Come on man, give me the whole corn!
Right, yeah, why do they give you, they like break the corn up, they don't put it on a
stick or anything, it's not right.
Yeah, hey this one's got aioli on it, and don't even get me started on aioli.
Hey, come on.
Come on dude.
Aioli?
That's dog shit.
A-ole up the...
Yeah.
...fucking...
...your ass.
A-hold these.
They're my balls.
Mm-hmm.
What's wrong with A-ole?
Um, I don't know.
I'm...
I heard Dennis Leary complain about it.
Yeah, Dennis Leary hates it 'cause people put it in their coffee or something.
True.
Yeah.
Now you got these kids putting A-oles in their damn coffees.
Whatever happened to good old mayo?
What the fuck?
Yeah.
Whatever happened to mayonnaise in your coffee?
www.helmetsmayonnaise.com instead of wtf.com that was a good man what a classic
bit that we always go back to his coffee bit oh yeah that's cuz it's one of the
all-time stand-up bits it is it's a foundation of comedy it's so ubiquitous
dude everybody knows it everybody loves it every true what do they use your
favorite comedians favorite comedian exactly yeah mm-hmm and his favorite
comedian was Bill Hicks yeah whose big bit was being a fucking copycat of
Dennis Leary yeah yeah copied him with his cigarettes and his coffee and
watching Bill Hicks do like four hours of stand-up about DMT I mean like this
exactly like fucking Dennis Leary oh my gosh just ripping him off dude he's also
yeah you know he's from Boston you know Bill Hicks famously a Boston guy and he
died that's a that's a Ralphie May ripoff yeah yeah yeah he died from
obesity yeah you're taking Ralphie's bits dude yeah dude come on any comedian
that dies you're stealing it like you're stealing another comics bit Brody Robin
first dude come on oh come on that's oh that's that's he he was too much of a
positive force yeah I agree yeah you're right we'll let the dead rest yeah yeah
you're right my bad remember when you got super mad at us for making fun of that
Star Wars guy who died who the Star Trek guy what was that guy who killed
Anton Yelchin yeah oh I think you Patrick got freaked out I think because we said
that Patrick killed him oh yeah well no he killed himself with like a Rube
Goldberg machine yeah he crushed himself yeah he got behind the Jeep and just
went all right nobody stopped me like it's literally it's literally a final
destination death right yeah no I think it was just I I was just thinking about
it and I was like ah that's like just such a shitty way to go just an accidental
jeep murder well here if you think about it he was actually a really bad guy
because he was in Green Room and he starred with a bunch of Nazis that's a
really good point he said he didn't do anything he sings Nazi punks fuck off to
them and then saying that and then guys yeah in the movie and in real life he
was being sarcastic when he's saying Nazi punks fuck off yeah they actually did
ADR he actually said "Nazi punks come over" "Rock on" "Nazi punks rock on" "Nazi punks keep
doing what you're doing baby I love that shit" It's funny though cuz like the
lyrics like Nazi punks is supposed to mean like like yeah it means like skin
heads but it also means like people who were like gatekeeping like punk stuff I
think I think I heard that somewhere on it I honestly Nazi punks fuck off is about
gatekeeping you think it's not about Nazis I think it's about both I watched I
showed that movie to my dad cuz he's a huge like punk fan and it was like
probably it was one of the it was such a great father something because like when
they show up to that like venue and it's filled with all the Nazis and he like
looks at me he's like like oh they should play Nazi punks fuck off like as a
joke and I just like had to like even straight face and they started playing
it and just seeing his face light up and look at me honestly.
That movie's made for someone like your dad.
Oh yeah.
It's like an old punk who has that like, that's like how he would write it exactly.
Yeah, it's like what happened to him.
Yeah, no the first line in the song is "Punk ain't no religious cult, punk means thinking
for yourself.
You ain't hardcore cause you spike your hair when a jock still lives inside your head."
So it's about Nazis but it's also about jerks.
And jocks dude.
Jerks and jocks, the real fuckin Nazis.
these jocks dude jocks are the original Nazis it's true yeah he does say you
think swastikas wait hold on swastikas look cool the real Nazis run your
schools their coaches businessmen and cops in a real fourth Reich you'll be
the first to go their coat the football coach is a complete Nazi dude yeah it's
Swastika was actually a jock symbol of peace for many, for thousands of years.
Yeah, it was for hockey sticks.
And then they bastardized it, turned it into that disgusting...
That's where the phrase "HE double hockey sticks" comes from.
Yeah, but it was "HE quadruple hockey sticks" which meant "HE jock."
And "HE" stood for "Hitler's Evil."
evil no Hitler's evil quadruple hockey sticks yeah don't be saying no swastika
around me we call that Hitler's evil quadruple hockey sticks around here yeah
put some respect on the jocks please yeah for the love of God yeah I was never a
jock I was never a jock everybody I was until I realized kind of like a proof
that I don't think there is and also I if if I was I'm reformed to now I got my
job I don't like prison tattoos lasered off me and Cameron are the only two non
jocks on the show we've never been jocks I'm not a jock anymore I was a jock for
about 10 seconds one time I've decided to become kind of like a Chris Hardwick
pop culture nerd mm-hmm yeah well maybe not maybe not him maybe a different yeah
maybe Wil Wheaton yeah yeah you could you could start a brewery like Wil Wheaton
mmm I don't know beer is you can make nerdy about beer dude it's I think one
of those one of the the greatest failings of society is that people like
Wil Wheaton and Chris Hardwick got cast in movies just on virtue of doing
whatever they do yeah just yeah nerds just like like Chris Hartley yeah and
that's directors would be like yeah well that one is good because Rob Zombie
cast him because he's completely insufferable and he just gets killed but
like fucking like Will Wheaton what was he and he was in like Star Trek and shit
yeah he's like he's like he got his hands are trying to do like he made to
do a pot he got he made did he got to be on Star Trek cuz he made a podcast that
was like I love Star Trek or whatever and they're like oh dude we have to cast
this guy yeah no he would go to conventions because he was like oh my
god when he was on TNG people fucking hated him people hated Wesley Crusher
Jesus his name was yeah he was the son he was a son of Beverly
looking at will Wheaton and being like yo this guy Crusher yeah yeah dude he's
the he's the the son of the nurse Beverly Crusher yeah they should have
called it that's a bad name for a nurse I know it's a terrible name for a nurse
you know the name of the nurse and Tio and the original series is Hank evil
Hank bones no it's not Hank McCoy but it is bones is bones I know his name is
bones stinky piss nurse bones scary yeah skeleton dry bones skeleton the Leonard
is Leonard like what and it was my bones yeah cuz he was the doctor that makes
he's a saw bone so they got bones and crusher I hope that I hope never the two
shall meet and then the then on deep space nine and then the third one the
third medic was named not no his name was dr. Julian Bashir they they cut the
fucking they cut the cool doctor name yeah well cuz once you do bones and
Crusher where do you go from there Bashir al-Assad
That's where you go
The original Bones Crusher
Bashir al-Assad
Yeah
I don't know
Maybe we should try and sneak our way onto a TV show
Yeah let's sneak ourselves onto
Deep Space Nine
Mandalorian has an opening
We should be the triplet
No all three of us
All three of us could like stack up on top of each other
And probably be like the same size as that lady
we'd have to stack in front of each other - absolutely dude yeah how did she not
just like kill whoever tried to fire her yeah yeah just like crush you could have
put any of them in a headlock yeah absolutely apparently somebody's I saw
somebody say that they were like trying to fire her since November or something
yeah oh yeah she was saying it's like I said a bunch of transphobic scared of
this lady so crazy like to be in like a star were like make probably making
right insane fucking money oh my god she probably millions and just be like I'm
not gonna stop sharing these memes right yeah so funny it's so funny I compared
herself to a fucking a Jew in the Holocaust that is like the funniest
fucking thing she could have like that's like you get fired from Baskin-Robbins
for doing that you like that's like automatic fire wherever you fucking work
and she was like I gotta do it all you have to do is like make an alt like
right to be able to do that she also she would have gotten in less trouble if she
had said it's like it's she feels more like Hitler you know it was it was a
a weird you like yeah I'm being a conservative nowadays it's like being
Hitler during the Holocaust she would have people been like oh sure yeah I
guess she's making a point go off Hitler go lady Hitler lady Hitler you snapped
on that damn if there was a female Hitler that's a that's a one of the
really that's a really good Venture Brothers joke the girl Hitler there's
like a supervillain who's just named girl Hitler. Oh really? We should try and get on a
cartoon. We should dude. Yeah. We should try to get into Trolls 2. Oh well Trolls 2
already had, we should get into Trolls 3. Mm-hmm no we're gonna get into Trolls 2. I don't think
we're the first podcast to do this. Yeah I think we're gonna be the first trio of podcasters who are gonna
start a campaign to get into Trolls 2. You know what's funny is I did make that
joke and then Cameron did call me out for it was like early on in the podcast
because I remember that I don't know what podcast did this before my brother my
brother and me oh they tried to get on trolls yeah they did trolls yeah they
got into trolls - that's right damn it you fucking it beat us to everything do
you think we could get them to give us a transformer we could be transformers in
the next movie we could be like guys what kind of transformers would you guys be
one with beautiful hair i'd be the one that talks through the radio sometimes bumblebee i'd be the
two black transformers yeah the yeah the ones voiced by tom kenney yeah they're called like
sketch and dj or whatever like wearing durags literally like car parts and they go yo yo yo
i don't know if this is true but in my brain they at some point call shia labeouf cracker
I think probably they do.
That's so awesome.
There's something, they die in a real-
they die- when they die they say something
fucked up too but I can't remember what it was.
The N word?
Yeah.
Racist
Transformers
Revenge of the Fallen.
Oh that's when they- they die in that one?
That one's like- I thought they died in the first one.
Their names are
Skids and Mudflap.
mudflap!
no!
Hambone and Miles Davis
the two
black transformers
damn, it's so funny to imagine Michael Bay
just like, yeah dude, you got that
I'm reading this article here about it
from back in the animated series
there was a, there was a
an Autobot who talked in a
a suave funky street style you transformed it to a Porsche named Jazz.
Yeah, yeah, that's I thought that uh...
Oh, a Porsche?
A Scatman Crothers voiced him.
Yeah, no I thought Jazz was um...
Like an Oldsmobile or like a Cadillac or something if you're just gonna full send it like that.
Yeah.
If you're gonna name yourself Jazz.
Man.
I don't know.
Missed opportunities but...
Oh damn dude, they had Jazz in the first live action movie too and when he lands on earth
he announces what's cracking little bitches this looks like a cool place to
kick it is it the whole thing that they like learn to talk from like listening
to the radio or something yeah yeah yeah so I mean I guess yeah at some point
they do they so one of them is gonna turn on BET or something and then just
be the most offensive transformer of all time skids and mud flap quotes let's see
here yeah here we go thank god one of them didn't like my booty call right here time to
get my sexy on with the green oh man thank god one of them didn't like learn how to talk
from listening to like rush limbaugh or something like opie and anthony that would have been
a that would have been a really bad transformer yeah yeah just like stomping on homeless people
all around the the city mud flap let's pop a cap in his ass throw him in the trunk and
then nobody gonna know nothing know what I mean skids not in my trunk and
Spongebob why don't you get a haircut with your bitch ass haircut with your
bitch
what uh-huh it makes it I think that's after Obama was the president - right
That's old school, yo. That's like, that's Cybertronian.
They're real hip-hop, dude. Skids and mudflaps.
One of them was voiced by Tom Kenny. I don't know which one. Let me check here.
The one that was voiced by Tom Kenny was Optimus Prime and he was saying all this.
Yeah.
Yo! I'm going to pop a cap in your ass.
I'm going to pop a cap in your ass, Shia LaBeouf.
Autobots, smoke weed.
(laughing)
- Roll up.
- Autobots roll up.
- Hold up.
- Okay, well Mudflap was at least voiced by a black guy.
- Okay.
- So it's all okay.
- So yeah.
- Everything's forgiven.
- Yeah, it's a black guy and his white friend.
- Yeah.
- All right, now it makes more sense.
- They should have made more Transformers
different ethnicities.
- You think so?
- They had a samurai one in the fourth one, dude.
(laughing)
at a samurai one yeah those are you're so sick oh yeah dude those are the some of
the best action movies at all time at any time the third one is just perfect no
that's not cinema to me oh yeah you wanna yeah what's what's what cinema to you
well first of all honestly the Transformers killed thousands of people
and it seems like the movies glorifying them mm-hmm it's glorifying a
a Decepticon. It's glorifying cars and honestly I don't, I can't drive so. Yeah where's the trains?
It's actually really fucked up for people who don't have licenses. Right you know you're kind
of rubbing it in the audience's face if they can't drive. This is a movie that it's rated D
for drivers only. It would be D-O. No. Yeah. Dude imagine seeing Transformers at a drive-in movie
theater and one of the cars transform. You would be watching the movie you would look around you'd
think any of these cars could be a transformer it would totally say no
insurance the one with mark walberg there's like a i've only seen this scene
from that or he's like jay miller did yeah he's in a barn mark walbert in a
bar and he walks up and he's like i think i just found a transformer it's so
so
movie right now I think Beast Wars was always my go-to as kid. Beast Wars is sick.
Did you ever watch Beetle Borgs? Did you ever watch Bababooey?
Did you see Beetle Borgs? Do you remember you guys don't remember Beetle Borgs? I
know of it but I didn't watch it. Oh it was like one of those like like super
sentai shows. Yeah. But it was like I don't know what I was from Jouko B
fighter it's a Japanese yeah it was like these kids who's like their dad is a
Frankenstein and a Dracula no and they're also Power Rangers wait their dad is a
Frankenstein and a Dracula they have they have count Fangula can't be both
a dragon a Frankenstein so there it's not their parents this is just a house that
they hang out in it's an old mansion that they hang out in and there's count
fangula and there's flabber and there's mums who's a mummy and Franken beans and
I love it dude the little people who fucking localized Japanese shows oh my
god I got to have so like just be like yeah that guy's Franken beans I don't
know see I don't think the the like the monsters I think the monsters were part
of the localization I don't think they were in the Japanese show. Then what was
the show? The show... Just them hanging out with in the house? Well I'll have to look
but yeah I don't think I don't think that the beetle Borg's in this I don't know
I've never seen the Japanese one I've only seen beetle Borg's. You're just making this up?
No I'm not making this up. Then okay then why did you say they don't have monsters
in it if you've never seen it? In the Japanese one I don't think they have. So you think
there's no monsters because you've never seen the Japanese one I'm looking at the
Wikipedia right now and what is leading you to say there's no monsters in it
it's in Japanese and I can't read it
that's fair dude it's forbidden knowledge it's not for you it's forbidden
for ya no but I'm looking at it now no there's like parts of it that are in
Japanese but it looks like there's no like there's no mention of the word
there's I'm looking at for the word Dracula there's no mention of Dracula
it's probably not called Dracula's on you go be fighter his name okay I'm looking
for the word vampire nothing I'm gonna look for Frankenstein okay let's see
here nothing is there any that is just like like like Dracula is there any like
is it is a kanji for Dracula like a little drawing? It could be. Little fangs. That'd be cool.
I feel like at some point you run out of things to, different lines to arrange and you should just be,
for new words, just be making little tiny cute drawings, you know. That's what emoji was. Wow,
emoji is Japanese language technically, huh? I don't want to say that. I think that's true.
But yeah I think the localization for Beatleborgs, they were like fuck it let's make them hang
out with the Dracula.
Do you guys think we could do an overseas version of this show?
Yeah.
Absolutely.
We should have already been doing that.
Yeah.
Wait what are we doing dude?
We need like three Japanese guys who look like us.
That's a good idea.
If you're Japanese and you look like anybody send an email.
If you are a Japanese guy who only speaks Japanese and you're listening to this, send us an email
and we'll pay for the plastic surgery, we'll make you look like us.
One guy that looks like all three of us.
Very efficient.
Yeah.
Like a Japanese businessman.
He's going to get it all done for us.
One man doing the work of three.
Genius.
Yeah.
Pretty smart.
like split down the middle like Two-Face but three ways. But the Neapolitan Man.
Yeah. Oh, that's a good name for a movie dude. The Neapolitan Man? It sounds like a
thriller, like a thriller about a guy with three personalities called the
Neapolitan Man. Wow, you're right. That'd be so cool. One is white and one is black and
and one is strawberry.
(laughing)
Yeah, he is much like the Transformers,
he has a white and a black personality
and then also a strawberry one.
Yeah.
And also if it's a thriller, he's evil?
Or he's unraveling some evil plot.
That might be a better move.
He has to kill a guy named Chocolate Chip.
Man, why the fuck would you make,
I don't understand why they were like,
"Yeah, yeah, you know, this fucking, this Power Rangers show,
"let's put fucking Boo-Berry in it."
I don't, why, why do they do that?
- It's 'cause kids like it, dude.
- It was sick, I will say.
It was awesome. - We're gonna do that
to you pretty soon.
We're gonna introduce a new guy on the podcast.
- Yeah, a ghost. - Yeah, a ghost
that you have to deal with.
- Oh, I'd love that. - Yeah, he's only gonna be
in your room.
- Okay. - Yeah.
- I made Cameron so mad talking about this.
- Made Cameron so mad that he just left.
Yeah.
Son of a gun.
Beetle Borg's The Vampire Files on VHS is $40 if you want to buy that on Amazon.
Yeah, I'll buy, what, six, seven hundred copies of it?
That's not a big deal to me.
I'm extremely rich.
Yeah, that's fine.
Yeah, whatever.
Let's see, what else can we buy?
Flintstones gummies.
People who bought this also bought Flintstones gummies.
Dude I told you I think I'm blacklisted from Amazon. Yeah oh yeah.
People order packages and they say "undeliverable" yeah I don't know why. It doesn't give me any... yeah I
know you don't know why if you knew why then I would I'd probably fight you
because I'm still waiting on a USB adapter and a gold chain that I ordered
two months ago. If I had anything to do with it I'd tell you. That makes it
feel like you did have something to do with it stop smiling when you say that
mm-hmm I got it wait did you intercept my packages no I'm just kind of looking
at stuff right now I'm looking at are you looking at my I can see the
reflection of my gold chain in your sunglasses no I see that's a different
gold chain that's my rosary chain oh you got the same one as me no I got this
from my priest the priest doesn't give out rosary chains did the priest gave me
one why are you his chosen child mm-hmm I was the priest's chosen child yeah he
did no so wait Patrick he gave you beads the priest gave me golden you gave you a
string with big beads on it yeah they were pretty big why gave you his beans
no no dr. Franken beans is from beetle Borg's we're not talking about that oh
yeah okay we're talking about my priest who gave me big beads father Acula
beware of father he may be hiding a deep dark secret mm-hmm he's a father Acula
father Acula yeah my name is hello parish I'm your new priest I'm father
Rankin Stein you know I thought there was something funny about this church
ever saw since I saw it was called Church Acula's castle.
Yeah.
Oh, that's why the crosses are all upside down.
I was just talking to Father Acula.
I visited Father Acula.
Sister Aten.
Yeah, you know, it was kind of weird at the church today.
Frankenstein the what are they called the fucking the altar boy was bringing the
candle up to the the pulpit and he attacked him he attacked the child he
saw the candle and he attacked them I'd like to just in my sermon today I just
like to shine a spotlight on people who are are making a positive change in our
community mr. um II could you please
yeah and uh fucking Steve werewolf please Steve airwolf do airwolf do airwolf oh my
god he's still we're everybody in my life is is a different creature I'm
realizing fuck dude my friend Seth Itler he's a villain he's villainous
no I can't believe I didn't realize this my mom mom stir my dad bag dad that's
like that place no would you guys monster names be that that would fool civilians
cancer either like a spider camp sure mmm that's pretty good probably a little
Caleb boobs Caleb Caleb Caleb ig boobs it boobs that's pretty good I think I
would just go by Patrick just to not like Patrick Patrick
razy man okay I like that hello mr. razy man yeah Patrick Patrick reapy
Patrick raisin dead my name's Patrick raisin crazy crazy dead
even follow the template at all yeah I completely fucked it up how about this
Patrick Luke Lux clan no yeah I think it would be something like that I think it
something like that and it might look a little something like what Patrick has
been wearing the whole episode maybe Patrick karate oh karate is pretty scary
karate is scary dude yeah yeah I wish my name ended in like a G so I could do
like yeah on yeah yeah Kim Kim John gun there is a team is Kim John gun fuck
yeah can I call that have a gun - yes but he has the John gun no the John gun yeah
that's what that's what they've been warning us about North Korea is that
they had no John Korea has developed the John gun yeah it's the gun that John
Wayne used by industrial light and magic that they have they've kidnapped a bunch
from and they're making them do cool replicas back home yeah I want to I hope
they get back into movies that they yeah into into kidnapping filmmakers and
having a movies that's one of the coolest thing I mean North Korea's done
a lot of cool shit over the years but that's movie is like good to pull
ghasari the kaiju movie they made when they kidnapped I gotta see that director
I really want you to I want Kim Jong-un to get really into like a mumble core
and yeah like North Korean Napoleon dynamite that'd be amazing yeah yeah they
just have like a instead of like putting like tater tots in his pocket he has
like well no tater tots I think would still work tater tots are very big in
North Korea I don't think so I learned I think it probably learned when I learned
on my trip they probably you know it probably be evil
true he has evil in his pockets yeah he has uranium in his pocket give me some
with your earring yeah give me that plutonium in your butthole like kicking
yeah oh yes I love to share with my neighbor damn your missiles have jets and
plutonium lucky dude shit and and Kim Jong-un stars yeah yeah of course if
you're gonna start yeah if you're gonna be like you he should be starring in in
every movie that they make I feel like yeah that's why he was gone for that
like two months when people thought he was dead filming he was filming
something in in New Zealand's filming one of the best movies of all time mm-hmm
he was filming their version of Lord of the Rings that'd be amazing yeah oh my
god that would be really I'm gonna be one of the best it is kind of just the
origin story of his dad right is like Lord of the Rings kind of it's like
crazy I did it I went I didn't know no I I just copied and pasted like the I
needed like a bio for a stand-up show on time and I just copied and pasted the
like North Korean like legend about Kim Jong-il and like where he came from he's
like born from like a mountain's vagina and shit and nobody knew what it was
that's they're just like this is kind of an odd it's one of these weird comedian
things yeah yeah or maybe they thought maybe they were just disappointed when I
came out cuz I wasn't Kim Jong-il yeah maybe like shit you got it you got it
like a bad reception from the crowd yeah yeah cuz they were like we want bring
out Kim bring him out I love his face a second wait a second
Kim John Gil he was a fish the Gilman oh my god oh my god dude
Kim Jong- Kim Jong-Kill.
Oh no, no, no, no, no.
Wait, you guys know Santic-
Santiclaws, right?
Santa's claws?
Santa's claws. He's a beast.
No, that's how he's a shape-shifting beast. That's why he can fit in all the uh,
fucking chimneys. Do you guys know my friend Barack Obama?
I think he might be Barack Obama, the president.
No.
No way.
Do you guys know my friend Barack Obama?
I think he might be my mom.
Do you know Barack Obama, my friend?
Barack Obama.
Do you guys know Barack Hussein Obama?
I think he might be Barack Obama in disguise or something.
I don't trust it.
No.
You don't trust Barack Obama?
Why?
I don't trust that he's your mom.
Oh yeah, he's not my mom.
Yeah.
No, we've been over this.
My mom's name is Cynthia Caleb.
That's her name.
Mom mood.
Yeah.
I'm up in your dad.
I'm up in your dad
I'm up in your dad is so gross to me. We're in my dad
dad. His butt. Oh, what the? That was the last one I wanted to hear. He's knocking
out his, knocking out his pee stot. I'm knocking all the teeth out of your dad's
butt right now. We're getting some pee man to pee stot action going. I'm, I'm
pumping him full. You can see the, you can see the, the bulges going down my, my
penis like a snake swallowing a, an elephant.
I'm pumping him full up.
It's like a clog in a fire hose, dude.
I've got a bucket brigade down there.
That's disgusting.
That's my father you're talking about.
Yeah, come on, man.
That's a kill of dad.
What if this is the episode he decided to listen to?
And I'm rolling up my balls like the end of a toothpaste tube.
Gotta get every last drop out, dude.
Yeah.
I'm not going to the store for more of this.
It's so crazy, I was thinking about this earlier today, it's so crazy how like most ingredients
in toothpaste you can't swallow.
Like it says on-
With toothpaste on the other hand, you can swallow all you want.
Yeah.
You can sit there and drink it.
like it says like if you if you swallow it you have to contact poison control
I don't yeah it does say yeah if you swallow it you should contact poison
control yeah really yeah it depends on what like I use like arm and hammer
toothpaste which is just like baking so toxic toothpaste yeah yeah yeah yeah I
use I use an evil I just have a battery that I it is kind of hard to swallow
toothpaste by accident though I guess um what do you mean I don't think I saw you
don't accidentally swallow toothpaste not usually I'm not well not like
toothpaste whole like I mean like like when I'm brushing my teeth I don't think
I swallow at all I mean my mouth is filled with toothpaste how are you gonna
get your throat clean yeah and your stomach you got to get that
man shit in the back of your throat yeah how are you get I don't understand how
you gonna use a microfiber rag and you shove it down your throat? It's the same kind of thing you use to clean a
MacBook. Well if you think about it like
teeth are just kind of exposed bones in your you know wet hole. Whoa.
That's a nice little crack.com snippet right there.
We're all kind of like monkeys on like this rock that's just
whizzing through space. Yeah we're all like we're basically brain stuck in
in in shit yeah it's basically eat suits yeah it's like we're like ghosts that
are piloting giant meat man kind of did you know wait did you know you have a
skeleton inside of you right now there's two skeletons inside of you fighting
right now no skeletons fighting inside of you one of them is taller you let win I
hope that one wins one skeleton represents all your bones and one
skeleton represents all your meat which one will win the one you feed mm-hmm
I'm feeding my meat skeleton bones yeah could I get a McChicken that's for my
meat skeleton and a burger and a McBurger that's for my bone skeleton I
went to McDonald's today and they had signs all over the restaurant that like
at least four signs that said please do not lie down please lie I don't lie to
me do not lie this is McDonald's you will go to hell it is a sin to lie in
McDonald's yeah I totally want some no imagine the kind of the kind of fucked up
guy who would lie to a McDonald's cashier that's just yeah yeah if you lie
about your name to McDonald's I can I have the bathroom code I have to go
number one lie lie they should have to hook you up to a lie detector every time
the order food so that you never order the wrong thing that's not a good
invention of a lot of type of lie detector me okay you have Pinocchio
there he repeats what you said you say I have to go number one and then they look
at Pinocchio and Pinocchio goes he has to go number one Pinocchio's nose grows and
and out your those hoes goes.
- Well, wouldn't, wouldn't Pinocchio be lying though?
Because--
- Yeah, that's why you would know that he was--
- No, like wouldn't he be lying
'cause he wouldn't have to go, oh wait, that guy.
- He said that guy.
- Yeah, yeah.
- There, yeah, I'm just picturing Pinocchio first day
on the job just kind of being like, I have to, wait, oh no!
Just his nose growing, you know?
- Pinocchio, I guess--
- But he doesn't say I have to, he says that guy.
He might fuck up.
Hey, Pinocchio, even Pinocchio fucks up sometimes.
And that's okay.
Not for me.
No?
You're not gonna forgive Pinocchio?
I wouldn't forgive Pinocchio.
No.
Pinocchio.
This damned Pinocchio.
This damned Pinocchio has lied for the last time.
This fucking guy, this Pinocchio, I'm sick of him.
I'm sick of his face.
Pinocchio's been terrorizing the town. He ain't even a real boy. Not yet.
Pinocchio's not a real boy yet. His damned Pinocchio took my prize cricket and went in a well.
Have you seen my cricket? Pinocchio tames Germany.
that's a cowboy who hates Pinocchio. Pinocchio took my cricket! A cowboy has been wronged by Pinocchio.
Have you seen a little wooden boy around in these parts? Yeah he's been stealing crickets left and right I don't
know what the fuck to do with him. I listen I didn't bother me till he touched
my cricket he came for he came for my neighbors cricket I said I wish I had a
Pinocchio nose I'd be lying all the time yeah wait does he go does it go back to
being small if he tells the truth I think I don't think says like I think
yesterday saw it off it's permanently okay yeah I guess it does he that's got
hurt yeah I don't know I don't know if that's what it does how does Google does
how does Pinocchio does Pinocchio's nose shrink would you would you lie to save
Pinocchio yeah cuz I don't have a Pinocchio nose so I can lie okay so this
is really helpful my my Google search does Pinocchio's nose shrink well
Pinocchio's nose would extend when he lies lied it seems the reverse is true
in reality scientists from the University of Grenada have found that when a person
is telling a lie their nose actually shrinks from the drop in temperature.
What? I don't believe that. I don't think that's true. This is from times of India
dot India times dot com and it's like it was like a Google info box you know that
thing that happens when you google a question. Oh yeah. Yeah this story is
when somebody lies their nose gets small. I don't think that's one of those things
That's one of those things where you'll see an article that's like, "People who eat sandwiches
have an 8% chance of never dying."
True.
It's like, yeah.
I'll tell a lie to prove this.
Ready?
Okay.
Tell a lie.
I hate my friends.
Your nose has never looked bigger, honestly.
What?
It looks fucking huge right now.
No, I don't believe you.
What the fuck?
Dude, listen to this.
Okay.
You got like a snape nose right now.
Listen to their test.
Snape?
Yeah.
I think you mean Voldemort.
No, Voldemort. No, that's a big ass nose you got there, dude. That's a sniffer.
Listen how they tested how people's nose would shrink.
In the study, the team used thermal imaging on 60 students as they completed a number of tasks.
This included placing a phone call, during which they had to tell a close friend a significant lie.
Meanwhile, a control group watched distressing videos of car accidents, which they had to explain to someone over the phone.
What?
So that just means a car, talking about car accidents gives you maybe a big nose.
Yeah, I don't think
I don't know what the car accidents have to do with anything.
Did you guys see that humongous pile up in Texas with a hundred cars?
Oh, yeah, the 50, I thought it was a 50, it was a hundred?
No, over a hundred cars just ran.
There was probably 50 and then people just kept running into it, dude.
Those fucking idiots.
They don't know what to do when there's like a quarter of an inch of snow on the ground.
Oh, it's because it snowed in Texas?
because it snowed in Texas it was like icy or something I thought that's so cool
so with if there's 50 cars on the road yeah yeah five killed you can't oh and
that don't know yeah did I know any of them it says it's Fort Worth could be
Thomas Thomas no well I think he sent it to me but that would be funny if he sent
it to me while he was driving yeah look at this a hundred fucking cars piled up
and then he died. Wait, that's random. I just said that there was a
hundred car pileup. There's a hundred cars in front of me right now. Oh well, I'm
gonna drive closer to get a better look. There's 99 cars! Look at this fucking 99 car pileup!
Imagine if the guy, one of the people who died was the 100th car.
Can you imagine how awful that would feel? Because that guy definitely saw it coming.
Yeah. Like he should have been able to avoid being the hundredth car. Yeah. Yeah.
Well that guy saw it was like, "Oh there's 99 cars." I mean. Yeah. What's one more?
Might as well. Yeah. Maybe they were filming Jackass 3. More from Times of India. Blue Rice is the
latest craze that is Insta-worthy too. Blue Rice? Blue Rice. I don't want to know
Avatar Rice. I ain't no Smurf. Blue, let's see here, Blue Rice. Wow. Is it a health food?
Even the actress Jacqueline Fernandez was seen indulging in this dish along with her friends.
What is it made out of?
Blue.
But oh my god, it started auto-playing an Indian ad really loud.
Thai blue rice, the blue color of the rice comes from the petals of the clitora tornado.
I will not be eating that.
It says butterfly pea flowers.
Butterfly pea.
why it's the clitoris because it comes that's where the pee comes out yeah
exactly like a woman's clitoris mm-hmm there's a tiny little hole that's why
women take so long in the bathroom to squeeze all that there's a comment on
this on this news story that says Indians eating a lot of rice
carbohydrates is a problem for their health in the long run they need to
reduce rice and increase protein consumption eggs fish meat to be strong
and healthy and that comment is from China expert 555 yeah I think he's on
the wrong website yeah I think he needs to go on Chinese facts org Chinese facts
where I am a moderator I just got to make sure they're all the right facts you
know yeah yeah I'm the only I'm the only editor on Chinese Wikipedia and I've
just been making it all up like that guy yeah I've just been doing that I mean if
you think about it. I've just been typing basically tic-tac-toe games over and over again.
That guy, that kid who like ruined the thing, it's not his fault because like the thing
he ruined was he ruined like AI, artificial intelligence stuff that was like using Wikipedia
to train like neural networks and it's like what you shouldn't be using Wikipedia like
right you should be able to look at this this Scottish page and be like oh this is a guy
I'm messing around and saying like calling yeah you know like cuz it was all just
phonetic right exactly it's like it's like if you wrote like this huge blog
that was like my life as an alien and then like a scientist thought it was
like this is what alien life is really like yeah or like you did the Italian
Wikipedia just like spelled out like how Tony Soprano talks yeah yeah good about
(mumbling)
I'm a fucking Wikipedia editor.
What do you fucking want from me?
- You should be rewarding that kid
for tricking computer scientists.
- Tony Soprano, but he's just,
he's really into Wikipedia.
(laughing)
Look, you can find fucking anything on there.
- Yeah.
What happened to the strong, shiny type,
like, and then like five minutes of typing?
- Chippy Wales.
(laughing)
That's why they're always asking for money.
fucking protection money true yeah yeah he's got to make sure that they don't get
clipped look you fucking doubt you donate a hundred fucking dollars to Wikipedia
will never fucking touch your articles okay we'll never say you're they go they
don't pay it they go into the articles and just edit them out as a poop yeah it
would be a shame if somebody took your fucking Wikipedia and made you a
pedophile on there it would be a shame if on the person of life has said though I
I don't know loves kids yeah fuck all right I gotta go pee pee so bad yeah I