You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[laughter]
We are too.
Ultimate gear.
Oh my god. Ultimate gear.
Ultimate gear. We're going loud this year.
Don't do that.
We're going loud.
We're turning up the decibels of the podcast at least twice as much.
We're stoking loud this year. We're smoking loud.
Alright, first things first, we need to apologize for not having an episode for...
No we don't.
I feel like we should apologize to the fans.
We don't owe you guys shit.
Patrick, you can apologize, let it be known me and Cameron refuse to apologize.
Don't give a fuck.
I... look...
Don't care.
I care about the fans.
I care about...
That's lame.
Why?
I care about food.
Why is that lame? Why is caring about the fans lame?
Because you're a pussy.
It's actually not true.
It's only lame if Patrick does it.
Yeah, exactly. Anything Patrick does is stupid, fat.
(laughs)
Yeah, like you.
Yes! Yes!
Shit! Yes!
No, dude.
How's the holidays?
It's pretty good.
It's fine?
Did you guys get any new toys?
You bet it did.
I got a yo-yo.
What new toys did you get?
Yo-yo, Patrick?
I got Luigi.
You got Luigi's yo-yo?
Patrick got a lot of candy too.
He was sharing with me.
I got some Reese's cups.
Patrick got gummy bears and Twizzlers.
pound box of Twizzlers. Five pounds? Well no Dom got a five pound box of Twizzlers.
I got like a small box of tiny gummy bears. Oh so you didn't get any Twizzlers?
I didn't get any Twizzlers but I have. But he's been eating them. You've been
eating those Twizzlers. I've been eating them. That's cool. I've been eating them
Twizzlers. That's good. Trust me. I got some shoes I just wearing I'm wearing my
I got new shoes right now.
I got new shoes too.
Oh my God, dude.
We're the same guy.
Oh my goodness.
What shoes did you get?
Oh, Santa accidentally got us the same thing because he thought we were the same guy again
this year.
Fuck, dude.
What are your shoes?
I don't know.
Some Nikes from the Nike Outlet Factory store.
They're already falling apart and they have a stain on them.
Damn.
Damn, brother.
I got a bunch of iTunes gift cards that I'm trying to resell.
It's a fucking pain in the ass.
Don't know how to resell them.
Why don't you just go to that website?
What website?
Brazzers.
Oh, I can go to Brazzers.com.
You could turn the iTunes gift cards into one month of Brazzers.
Into a Brazzers cash.
Did you ever know anybody in middle school who--
I had five friends who all shared a Brazzers account.
So, shit, I put my mouth too close to the mic.
But my sister's,
one of my sister's ex-boyfriends gave me
and my little brother a Brazzers password
that was owned by him and the rest of the people
in his fraternity.
And my younger brother gave it to his friend Taylor,
and Taylor gave it out to all of London Dairy Middle School.
So the account got shut down
because too many people were logging in.
That's awesome. It's amazing to me that people pay for porn. I know. Yeah just make it
yourself. Exactly just make it yourself you and your friends. Yeah you can just
make it at home. At your sleepover. Yeah. You can just make it with your friends and
family at your sleepover, your daily sleepovers that you have at your house. He's not coming over to say hi, he's
coming to eat these chips. He wants the pita chips. Yeah. Which cat is this? This is Yoda.
Bad Yoda. We were talking about a really good movie would be Bad Yoda. Yeah. Like Bad Lieutenant?
Like Bad Santa. No, not like Bad Lieutenant. Like Bad Santa. Bad Lieutenant is sort of
a Bad Santa movie. Yeah, he kind of is. There's Lieutenant. If that guy was Santa, if Harvey
Keitel was Santa in that movie, he'd be pretty bad. Like Sexual Grandpa. Sexual Lieutenant.
it. Sexual Grandpa? Yeah, have you guys ever seen Sexual Grandpa? The Johnny Knoxville movie? Yeah.
Yeah, that was dirty. Oh boy, I'm coming to have sex with you. All of those, every single one of
those sketches is just like him shitting his pants in public. And it's funnier than anything. And it's
so funny. It's funnier than any movie that's come out since. Bad Grandpa is so funny. It is. He shits
his pants in public he also is hanging out with blonde women what you're a
grandpa knock it off yeah you're supposed to be hanging out with gray hair
you think of dirty exactly I'm thinking of whatever the Johnny Knoxville one is
the Johnny Knoxville one's good then the Robert De Niro one where he says the
n-word is bad oh you don't like that one well I'd like that scene but I don't
like that movie what's okay the scene where it's actually it's a pretty like
bad scene yeah it's pretty it's funny out of context where it's Robert De Niro at
karaoke singing today was a good day and then he he looks at the black people in
the crowd and he's like can I say it can I say it they have like I don't know who
it is but they cut to him and it's just a black guy going say that shit in high
school me and a friend went said the well me and a friend went to like some
karaoke place at like it or some karaoke night at an ice cream place just like
drunk out of our minds we were like 16 and he started singing a drop it like
it's hot by Snoop Dogg and it's an edited karaoke version but he said every curse
word in it and then he actually said the n-word and we ran and he was like I
I don't know what happened. I don't know what came over me.
Yeah.
You caught the Holy Ghost.
Yeah, he was Holy Ghosting.
(Laughter)
Oh, God damn, man.
Woo!
God damn.
I've had a very eventful month.
He was doing the, that was, instead of flailing around,
he was doing the
Snoop Dogg dance.
Oh. (Laughter)
steering wheel.
Yeah, I wonder where he's like doing that.
Yeah.
It looks like he's driving the car.
The ultimate dance is just pretend like you're driving a car.
Right.
Every good dance is that.
Yeah.
Where's the line between dancing and miming?
It's here.
Yeah.
It's the driving the car dance.
It's whip and nay nay, that's the line.
Whip is miming, nay nay is dancing.
Yeah.
Oh, true.
Whoa.
between period that's why they're so good when you put them together
it's contrasting peanut butter and chocolate
uh...
yeah
i got a column
i have not had virus software on this computer for two years and wonder what
fucking russian
shit is hacking me
they had a tracking
yet we have a lot of our own nation my computer
clinton turtle shit on that stuff but it will turn a state penis that as a shell
on it like a koopa. Have you ever seen a turtle's like a tortoise's penis? Yeah.
It's fucked up. Yeah it is it looks like yours. No we we have seen a tortoise, we
watched speedy's big go on here. Pat you would look really good with a shell. Yeah.
Like if you had a shell. A red koopa shell. Yeah like if you just had like a like a shell on you.
you just look so good. Or like a crab shell. Are we talking soft or hard shell? I'm talking
about like a hard, like a tortoise died and you took its shell. Okay. You would look really
good. I don't have to wear pants anymore. Yeah, you just wear your boxers under there
like the Koopas do. Yeah. Yeah, when you take the Koopas shell off. They're wearing freaking
boxers they're wearing the heart-shaped boxers and the heart heart pattern boxers
pattern boxers and they're yeah what what this is so not sexy I'm not turned on
yeah I hope he doesn't hit my heart pattern boxers a joke in every kids
movie because boys should find parts on them yeah oh so under their clothes
they're gay. Exactly. Whoa. The Koopa's small yellow penis would be
indistinguishable from Bart Simpsons in the Simpsons movie. Well yeah he's
flipping off the camera. It's yeah. No that's not true. The Koopa's penis is Bart's hands.
It's a theory that it's his Bart's penis but it's actually he's
flipping off. It's not a theory it's clearly his penis. It's a no. It is. I'm
saying that but there's a theory. There's a theory that he's flipping off the
camera? Uh-huh. Okay. It's a false theory. Is that like, would that hold up in court? No, but it's a theory.
Exactly. I was flipping them off with my penis. Look, people make theories about the
shining, they make theories about... That's true. I love all the Rugrats theories. Yeah, have you ever considered...
How could you possibly ruin something so innocent? It's so beautiful. Oh, my childhood is ruined by your
comment. Yeah, childhood seriously ruined. What's that? Tommy Pickles has, he has
multiple personality disorder what the hell Ed Edd n Eddy are all in purgatory
are you kidding me what what the wait child is all in purgatory sponge Bob is
black wait black sponge Bob this doesn't even make any sense my child is rumor
from the ghetto wait wait black Homer Twitter hold up you're telling me
there's a Homer hold up that Homer's black debt gangster gangster job of the
Oh no. Wait a second. Oh my god wait there's a fan theory that gangsta that job of the
huts actually gangster job of the hut. Childhood completely ruined. I think that's
that's Legends canon that's not that's not Disney canon. Oh my god there's
gangster Buzz Lightyear. Oh my god. This is gonna be so bad. Oh my god gangster booster from
Buzz Lightyear Star Command. When my childhood finds out about this it's gonna
to be bad news. I want to tell my childhood not to go into that room with
the... With me. With that priest. Oh come on, yeah, take everything nasty make it little
boy sexual disgusting. What is wrong with you? Look I'm normal I never... You're not
normal. I didn't go, I didn't go anywhere with a priest. Patrick, go into your shell.
that's right that's the noise it would make when Patrick went into his shell
would be yeah cuz I'm flying nope soaping wet yeah me and Patrick don't go to
college anymore. Yeah. Crazy shit. I know. You excited to not be in school? I'm not
excited for all the loans to hit me that fast. I'm not. You have six months. I'm gonna do a
leave of absence so I have at least a year to like. Oh. A year to not get the
loans fucked at me but. That's pretty smart. Yeah but I'm definitely not going
back next semester. Nice. Yeah. Cam still has four months left in his bid. Yeah. Bitch. Yeah.
Yeah, no it fucking blows dude.
I have to figure out, because I wasn't going to justify doing CCC for $35,000.
Yeah, that's smart.
Yeah, I can just work on it from the shadows. I can just send in scripts.
You could be a shadowy figure behind the scenes.
Patrick should go into the shadows.
Yeah, I'll be the phantom.
Yeah.
Patrick da phantom.
Shadows Patrick.
Patrick D. Phantom.
Yeah.
I'm excited to be not in school anymore.
Definitely have a lot of money to pay back to the U.S. government, but I'm hoping to
be conscripted and I can die for Israel in lieu of paying all of my money.
Me too.
Yeah.
That'd be pretty nice.
Look, I made a resolution for 2020 that I'm no longer going to be practicing any Jewish
holidays.
That was your... That's my resolution. Yeah? It was... I was doing it last year and it
was really hard to get Jewish families to let me into their home to help them
celebrate. Yeah. And none of my Jewish friends would let me. I want to help you celebrate. I would like to help you celebrate
Passover, ma'am.
(laughing)
Ma'am.
- In the grocery store. - Ma'am.
Just in Brookline.
Ma'am.
- Ma'am. - Ma'am.
- Ma'am.
- Let me honor your tradition.
- Ma'am, let me look at your hand.
- I'll help Nora.
- Listen, listen, if you do it,
you're gonna muck it all up.
It's just gonna be terrible.
Come on, let a Gentile.
- I know my way around candles.
- You need my Gentile's touch.
- Listen, we've never let a Gentile
put on a holy high holiday.
I'm just saying, what could happen?
What's the worst that could happen?
You let me go into your Ross and Hannah or whatever the fuck it's called.
Ross and Hannah?
You let me fucking...
You let me...
You let me take control.
Look, I don't know what kosher means, but you fucking...
I'm gonna get a charcuterie board.
But you know I'm gonna kill it with the lasagna.
That's all I'm saying.
I'm gonna crush it.
The lasagna is gonna be crazy.
We're gonna have an Italian Ross and Hannah.
it's gonna be wild
man i'm about to turn yom kippur into yum kippur
yum kippur me some more lasagna
yeah i make liquid lasagna i make wet ass lasagna
i make soapy lasagna i make that shit soppin wet
yeah that's some soap and wet lasagna
just like the jews make it
come on let me help
let me please let me help with the Hanukkah.
Oh my god.
Listen, if you do it, you're gonna chew it all up.
Just let me do it.
Come on.
Oh, what?
You're spending too much on those candles.
Look, we get one big candle.
We use one big candle.
One big candle.
I don't know what any of that shit means.
One big candle, one big day.
Instead of...
What about a tree?
The candle...
Yeah, how about a tree?
One big candle that looks like a tree.
One big green candle that has a thousand tiny candles on it.
Yeah.
And some pictures of your kids and shit.
And there's a red man and he's gonna come into your house and bring you some presents.
I'm bringing my fat friend who dresses in red.
I'm bringing my fat German friend.
Yeah.
My golem friend.
To your Hanukkah.
[Laughter]
I'm bringing my big jiggly friend into your chimney tonight.
What did Santa do during World War II?
did he just keep at it yeah wait wait wait wait now that I think about it why he
didn't like try to like help reindeer and elves he didn't even like think about he
thinks all he needed to do was put the Hitler youth on the naughty list mmm he
thinks that's he thinks that's activism I'm tired of these white feminist
motherfuckers these white feminist ass bitches like like Nancy Claus his wife
Nancy you beautiful bitch yeah if you weren't such a dynamite fuck
mrs. Claus are you guys ready for war yeah oh I picked the perfect time to
fucking drop out of school so i can get drafted
yet
i'd like to know whether there's no way there's a draft is this just going to be
uh... it's going to be a blackwater can retards from lake
yet it's just going to be is going to be the the
the deterred drone team it's going to be a really bad roads and it's going to be
kids named like tucker tanner who were like
i'm ready to serve
i'm ready to serve for you president trump tucker tanner soldiers by
*laughter*
Yeah.
I am ready to serve for you, Trump.
I am ready to honor you!
I'm hoping I get stationed at the Playboy Mansion.
What the fuck do you mean I can't wear both shoes?
*laughter*
I can't use my phone out here!
Yeah.
Respectfully, sir, I think that I should be allowed to wear salmon-colored fatigues.
*laughter*
be your excuse when they come knocking I'm gonna just say I'm literally crazy
and I'm gonna I'm just gonna go plugging your ears with your fingers I can't hear
you I'm just gonna drag a jack off in front of them when they come to my house
they can I think they could trick me into joining if they sent a man if they sent
a man dressed up as Spartan 117 John in my house one night while I'm asleep and
he was like Caleb wake up I'd be like anything I will do anything for you John
yeah and then we go save reach yeah yeah if they let me watch movies if they let
me walk if they let me watch movies I would go all right I'll join the
military on one condition unlimited movies I get your HBO account I get your
browser's password all of the military probably do you think browsers does a
military discount porn sites love to do stupid shit like that they love to be
like it's Christmas so if you use the code Christmas tree and send a picture
of your Christmas tree we'll show you a video of a girl getting fucked by a
present whoa is that a real thing oh my god it's just a little box with a dick
we will send we will send you our Lonely Island dick in a box porn parody that
movies already porn yeah I'm already jacking off my fucking
pud to dick in a box my pud yeah I love my little pud pud I'm pulling my pud to
dick in a box I went and did top boxing my dick top ball I did top ball what's
What's that?
I did Topgolf.
It's where you play golf, but it's a game.
What?
Yeah.
You go, there's a giant building that costs $50 million, and you go to the tip top of
it, and you hit balls until your arms get tired, and it's called Topgolf.
Okay.
And it was really fun.
Is that like in the Addams Family where they hit golf balls into their neighbor's house?
Yeah, that's what it is.
Okay, alright, I know what it is then.
Those guys, those guys, the Addams Family had big goth energy.
They had serious big goth energy.
2020, we're going into it as the Addams Family.
I'm lurch.
Caleb is pugsley.
Yeah.
Dude, you're pugsley, dude.
You're the thing.
Patrick is Mama Addams and I'm gonna have sex with him, her.
- Yeah. - Dude, you're Pugsley, dude.
- You're the thing.
- Patrick is Mama Adams and I'm gonna have sex with him, her.
- No.
- Patrick's Fester.
- Yeah, I'm Uncle Fester.
- Yeah, you're-- - Sortin' bald.
- Wait, I'm Pugsley, I'm Pugster.
- No, you're not Pugsley. - I'm Fester, I'm fat.
- You're Buster. - No.
- Caleb's Uncle Fester 'cause he can put a light bulb
in his mouth that turns on.
- No, that's not true.
- Can I be Lurch? - Yeah, that's true.
- That's not true. - Can I be Lurch?
- Who's Lurch?
- The Frankenstein butler. - You're both the dog.
you're for your fucking knowledge that's not even no no you guys are both the the
pets of the Adams family and I'm the family itself you're the thing you're
the thing you're Gomez Adams I don't say that I don't sound anything like that
shut up I don't Caleb's covered in hair and you can't not do anything yeah yeah
I'm covered in hair I agree I'm covered head to toe in hair and you sound like
you were bigger you were you were a clout goggles and a in a bowler hat man
you know how like that stupid when we were in LA they're like at that fucking
breakfast plate blows it Millie's or something yeah Millie's and then there
that just group of dudes all dressed the same like they all had like scarves and
denim jackets and those fucking rancher hats yeah imagine if bowler hats came
back like those dudes wearing like bowler hats and like rock dude dude oh my
god that's gonna happen like I hope someday at least cuz like their whole
thing is that they're dressing up like cowboys so what's the next logical step
from cowboys right in the end so they dress up with giant headdresses
completely naked yeah and like tobacco pipe they're all dressed up with the
American spirit guy they're dressed up like the Indians from bone tomahawk and
they walk around and go cannibal in half I could do that no I'm just imagining
just like soda jerk becoming like the next fashion thing after cowboy.
Because remember 2018 people got horny for cowboys for no reason.
Yeah.
It's because of Casey Musgraves.
Oh, that's yeah.
Casey Musgraves and Red Dead Redemption 2.
Yeah.
So girls were cowboys.
I hear they're married.
Yeah.
Casey Musgraves and Red Dead Redemption.
Red Dead Redemption 2.
Reb Reb Redemption.
She married Red-- she divorced Red Dead Revolver and then immediately married Red Dead 2 after.
RDR... R.
Rance Dance Revolution.
I'm trying to play some Rance Dance.
What's up, I'm Rance Dance.
So what are your guys' 2020 resolutions?
I have a rants dance resolution for you. I'm going to, uh, I would like
to pay my speeding ticket. Yeah. Nice. Where'd you get a ticket? And not go to jail. Albuquerque.
Yeah. Talk about that. What happened? I don't know. I just, I was just going, I was going like
25 miles over the speed limit and the guy, the cop pulled me over and he was like, "Hey!"
I was like, "Hey man, what's the deal?"
And he was like, "Oh, you were just going really, really fast."
And I was like, "Oh, I'm so sorry."
And he was like, "Yeah, you have to pay $300 now."
And yeah, I tried to get out of it by being like, "Yeah, me and my friend here, we're
just like two really broke comedians just like driving across this country and the
guys like a break for that I mean I yeah well that's what I'm sort of in like
we're two extremely rich comedians who will make a joke about you and everyone
will laugh at you yeah we're gonna write down your badge number and we're gonna
call you the f-word on well cuz I've definitely heard stories of people
saying stuff like that and then the police officer being like oh tell me a
joke and then like them getting out of the ticket and I was like it's gonna go
exactly like that and the guy was just like...
You know the stories are fake.
The guy was just like...
Oh you don't have any money? You can pay in something else.
Dude, I would have.
$300 is so much money to me right now.
But the guy, he was just like
"Oh that's really cool man.
You have to pay $300 now."
And he also made me plead
guilty or not guilty on the spot.
What the hell?
Yeah, so I was like "Not guilty, bitch."
And so I have to go to court
court now I don't know I think I'm gonna just as the judge like like I can I
either to Skype in or go to jail because I cannot get to Albuquerque at any point
in time. Let's go to Albuquerque for a weekend. A party weekend in Albuquerque. You two can
represent me in court. Dude if we could film that. The people versus Caleb Pitts.
Oh my god. That's the new goal. That's the new goal. Yeah we're gonna change Patrick pricing.
it's to Caleb pricing, it's to first of all pay off Caleb's parking ticket and then we're
gonna go to court with Caleb in Albuquerque.
Dude, if one of us can commit a crime that we get like public court for that we can represent
each other.
What is a crime that we could plan to do?
What's a crime that's like enough that you would get like a fine and like have a, like
he said wait we should go we should go to a town hall yeah we should go to a New
Hampshire town hall that'd be okay a Londonderry town hall yeah they think
bring a complaint you televised those yeah dude those are on TV whoa we're
gonna be a fucking TV dude whoa okay let's go no I know one of the people on
town council so I don't know if I can I mean I don't know that you're not
invited we would I would have to go in a disguise you go in a huge disguise it's
just it's like a pimp outfit and groucho goggles and then you go like we need to
do something about this
we didn't do something about this ugly guy
dressed really weird
we have to get this pimp out of our town
look at him
and then i go up
i'm like look
pimpin' ain't easy
all you say is
and then you walk out and we're like
he's getting away
arrest this man
Arrest this pimp!
He does not respect sex workers.
You're not a man, you're a pimp.
Look, look, he does not respect.
He, this man is a swerf.
You need to...
Swerf.
You need to get him out of our damn town.
Cause he does not respect sex workers.
Yeah, he's being mean to sex workers.
He's being mean.
Dude, he's being mean as hell.
Just walking up to just like some
pimp, 70's pimp, just slapping
slapping one of his hoos and just, "Hey, you are being so mean to that woman."
That is not nice. You are not being nice. Yeah, walking up to Iceberg Slim and being like,
"You are seriously being sex work exclusionary right now by beating these
women with coat hangers." With the Patreon money this month we should get a GoPro.
Okay. Why? It's cool that we're talking about what we're spending their money on
to what's for con it's for to make a street on the street videos I have to say
after paying Nolan I am gonna need my $16 cut just oh I need I need my $16 cut
to final by a $16 GoPro okay yeah I feel like we get a used one pretty cheap yeah
yeah I'm sure there's also a better camera - I was when I first came out
camera let's get a flip video camera oh I have a I have a Sony handycam from 2006
that shoots on DV tape that's sick that's perfect wait you know we should do we
should get a spy camera yeah put it in the girls locker room yeah
the world's locker room at Kayla's mom's house no there is no girls locker room
cuz there's only one girl she has a lot of stupid me and Patrick have been in
the locker room mm-hmm wait why no changing clothes yeah in the girls
locker room cuz your girl no we're changing your mom's clothes into guy
clothes okay so your mom becomes your dad okay did you not notice that your
parents switched I kind of just thought my dad got shorter yeah but I guess
you're right now your mom has a big mustache my mom has a big mustache and
she sucks at cooking now this is interesting this is gonna be one weird
Christmas next year yeah it's gonna be odd it's gonna be one weird Martin Luther
King Day it's the closest holiday I could think of damn what are you guys
gonna do for Martin Luther King Day yeah how you gonna celebrate type it in the
comment get shot in the head yeah I'm gonna have you yeah write a song about
about me yeah okay Patrick was born on
morning Patrick's birthday shot rains out in the Memphis sky
It lasts they took your life. They will not
Let's do an album of Patrick covers Patrick is laughing so hard at yelling into the microphone that he was kicking his legs around
Oh
Yeah, no cuz I smoke I smoke
Do we talk about that last time but yeah Patrick is obsessed with the fact that he smokes weed now
No, because it's funny.
It is funny that you thought you were allergic.
Yeah, I'm just I need to I'm a fucking terrible hypochondriac.
Yeah, I like I don't know I
There there have been times where I thought I had autism for like
two years
Because I took a test online and
and all of my symptoms lined up,
and then I just realized, like,
oh no, it's 'cause I'm taking Adderall.
Of course I get focused on one thing for too long.
- 2020, I'm going back on Adderall.
- Yeah? - Yeah.
- Yeah, why's that?
- So I can write and draw.
- Nice, I might steal my little brother's Adderall.
- I can get you Adderall, dude.
- I can go back on it whenever I want.
- I'm too scared of Adderall, actually.
I think it'll make my heart explode.
- Yeah, that's the one thing.
heart was getting dangerous for a while. I'll take it. I've probably said this
before yeah no one time I went to the doctor for like a checkup and I had just
taken Adderall and like climbed a flight of stairs and they listened to my heart
and they were like what are you okay? What is wrong with you? Are you a superhero?
And I was like I just like went up the stairs and they were like your heart
should not be beating this fast ever. That's so funny just to go into the
doctor's medial like oh my god you're right go home
yeah they're like I should probably get that checked out and I like you're the
doctor what do you have like an arrhythmia or something no I just have I
just was take I take an insane amount of Adderall okay or I did yeah I don't has
an arrhythmia take Adderall and then drink coffee yeah Dom we got the fucking
and Dom's been drinking espresso,
and then she'll get like, extremely nervous,
and then she'll be like, "Why, what is going on?"
And I'm like, "You just drank like so much espresso."
- I've been pretty low on caffeine since I've been here,
which has been, I've been weaning myself off,
but I have about a cup a day right now.
- I haven't done anything.
- Yeah, I've stopped nicotine.
- Yeah. - Nice, me too.
- Yeah, I mean, I've mostly stopped nicotine.
I've replaced it with weed now.
- Yeah, I just accidentally stopped nicotine.
I just didn't buy any.
- It's pretty easy, honestly.
I don't want people to complain about it.
- Yeah, it's the easiest thing in the world for me.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, everyone who can't quit smoking is just a pussy.
- Fucking idiot.
- Just kind of a pussy, kind of a loser.
- Yeah.
- And we don't respect you.
- Kind of a bobo.
Kind of a bobo chimp.
- Kind of a bobozo.
- Bobo the chimp.
- Bobo cervix, the chimp.
- Bobo cervix.
- Yeah.
Hello, I'm Bobo Cervix!
UGH!
Can I drive in the passenger seat of your car?
Can I inspect your cervix?
From the outside!
Why are you guys doing your own voices?
What?
Cause that's how you talk.
That's how you talk.
That's how you guys sound.
Hello, it's me, Caleb!
You're not doing your own voice because your own voice sounds like this!
No.
I'm Caleb and I need to get some batteries at the store.
I don't need any batteries. My new year's resolution is to-
I don't need all my toys came with batteries for Christmas.
I need 16 packs that don't sell AAAs!
Why? What am I gonna use 16 packs for?
I have a coupon!
A coupon?
I'm not gonna use the batteries, I just like how they look.
I don't care- Batteries are the most boring designs.
I throw them at the kids in the neighborhood who are bad.
I don't care- There's no kids in my neighborhood.
I make a delicious salad that's batteries and coins.
coins. No, that's not that doesn't sound delicious. It's not even a salad
battery coin salad. That's to be addressing or some sort of oil for
digged count as a salad. You guys put water. I skim water from the top of
the toilet tank. I don't do that. Patrick drinks out of the toilet
because he thinks that's where babies are come from and he's waiting for
one of my batteries in my salad. No, that of course I don't put croutons
in my salad or I mean I put batteries in my salad.
- You put batteries in your salad.
- No, I don't put either in my salad.
The only thing I, no, not, oh my God, I'm gonna hang up.
- Don't hang up, please.
- Okay, fine.
- Please, no. - I'm not gonna hang up.
Not.
- If you hang up, it'll make this awful to edit,
so please don't.
- Okay.
Will you guys stop making fun of me?
- Okay, okay.
- Thanks.
Sometimes all you gotta do is ask.
(laughter)
I did one of the worst shows of my entire life in Atlanta,
which was super fun.
Yeah.
Nice, oh yeah, how was the tour?
Yeah, talk about your tour, you fucking idiot.
Why are you so quiet all of a sudden?
'Cause.
A lot of the dates fell through,
so most of it was just a road trip,
but we did some dates.
Was it just you and Gus?
You and Gus had some dates.
Yeah, me and Gus went on a lot of dates.
Neil dropped out?
Yeah, Neil dropped out.
We listened to all of Serial,
which was good.
It was as good as I remember it the first time.
- Do you like the music for Cereal?
The theme song?
- It's pretty repetitive, but yeah.
- I like some of those clutches.
- The guy from the Unicorns
composed all the music for Cereal.
- It's definitely catchy.
- Yeah.
- It's definitely like, well,
it's a big part of the appeal of the episodes.
- Is that the one that goes,
♪ Dun dun dun dun ♪
♪ Dun dun dun dun dun ♪
- That's the one that goes,
♪ Honey Nut Cheerios ♪
"Where a kid can be a kid"
"Where a kid can be a star now" is what they say.
Really?
Yeah. "Where a kid can be a star!"
Did they really say that?
Yeah, they changed it to that.
Why?
Uh, because kids didn't want to be kids, they wanted to be stars.
Stupid.
A kid can be a kid anywhere. A kid can only be a star at Chuck E.'s Cheeses.
"Where Caleb can be a bitch"
"Where Cameron looks at kids"
So where did your tour take you?
uh... we did
we did albuquerque
and how does that show go
there was no show there we slept at albuquerque in albuquerque at a motel
uh... motel six
woke up got a ticket
then drove
to uh... uh... we were going to go to dallas because we were supposed to have a show
there the show did not materialize and did not happen
And so we were like, oh, we don't want to get a fucking Dallas. Let's go to Austin
ended up staying with a
very powerful Republican politician in Austin
Because he was like a college friend of my mom
Wow
That was bizarre. He was not friendly as you could probably imagine
And then we went to Atlanta the next day or no
we went to New Orleans the next day, went to like this old, old pool hall in New
Orleans and ended up, I think me and Gus are going back to New
Orleans. We like talked to this old dude who's like owned a club at the pool
hall and I think me and Gus are gonna try to go back to New Orleans in March
and do a weekend of shows at like a New Orleans black comedy club. Nice. You should
bring Patrick to do his voice okay Patrick do the voice yeah occasion
Patrick Patrick I'll just how y'all doing tonight yeah you do you a kill how y'all
doing I got doing how y'all doing what you peeping what you peeping so I think
we're gonna do that I will announce those dates when we have them and then
did Atlanta. I sucked up a gator. Terrible bar. And then we did my hometown which was another
terrible show. So all together. What happened in Atlanta? Atlanta it was just like a show
where they had like five lotto spots on this show so like every shitty comedian in the city
was there but not watching the show they were just like waiting for the lotto spots and
And then there was like six audience members who were just like college students.
Damn.
Yeah, it was a really bad one.
Were you booked on it?
Yeah, yeah.
Gus did one of the craziest sets I've ever seen.
Yeah.
Where Gus did like, he did like a quarter of his set just doing normal jokes.
And then introduced the idea of like some guy named Sully.
And he was like, "Oh, you guys don't know Sully?"
And he just like yelled at everyone in the audience for not knowing who Sully was.
And then he like got off stage and then I went up and then he was like, "We have to leave
immediately because this was crazy."
And then we just drove through the night to my hometown.
Got in at like six in the morning and I've been here since then.
I'm here for so much longer.
Yeah.
Damn.
What time do you get back?
I think the 11th or the 12th.
to the city.
Yeah, to the city.
To the city.
Um, the 11th and the 12th, I think me and Janna are driving up.
Oh, I got engaged.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, Caleb's engaged.
Yeah, wet wife.
Got a wife.
Caleb's the wet wife.
Got a wet wife.
Caleb is, no.
Caleb's the wet wife.
Caleb's your wife.
No.
You're the wet wife.
You're the wife.
What's Janna?
Dry Janna.
Shit.
Fuck.
No, she has to take my, she has to take my surname.
When we get married.
That's so funny. I don't know, that got me.
Dry Jana and wet wife.
So here's something that me and Patrick were talking about.
What about flavored wipes?
Oh yeah.
Isn't that a good idea?
And you can taste it through your ass.
Or whatever surface. You can wipe down your counter and then lick your counter.
I feel like you first, you like...
Yeah.
Like if you eat a bunch of like barbecue sauce, you can wipe your
mouth with it and it tastes like, like grapes.
Or more barbecue sauce.
If you wipe your mouth with barbecue sauce, it'll taste like
grapes.
No, listen, you eat barbecue or like maybe some buffalo wings and
then you get one of the wet wipes that are flavored like the thing
you just ate.
Yeah, your wipes.
Your wipes.
No, your wipes.
Yeah, they're yours.
Yeah, they're your wipes.
Yeah, they're Patrick's wet wipes.
They're Caleb's wipes.
Nah, they're wet wipes.
They're Patrick's wet wipes.
That's why they're called wet wipes.
Wet wipes, wet wipes.
Nah, they're yours.
They're your wet wipes.
Wet wipes.
Mm-hmm.
Have you ever heard that phrase?
Wet wipes.
Have you ever heard how wet you are?
Wipe, wipe, wipe.
Caleb is soaping wet.
He's soaping wet from the sweat.
I'm not wet.
You're so nervous to be a wife that you're--
I'm bone dry.
Caleb is plopping wet.
Are you guys done?
Caleb's hopping mad right now.
I'm not hopping mad.
You're hopping mad.
I'm sopping, I'm hopping.
You're sopping mad.
I'm not sopping, I'm hopping.
You're hopping mad.
I'm dry and I'm angry.
You're like the angry Kermit.
I'm dry angry.
You're like the evil Kermit from the meme that tells you to kill yourself.
I'm not dark side Kermit, I'm light side Kermit.
You're the planet Kuzban Kermit.
I'm dark side Kermit.
I'm light side Kermit.
no yourself I'm not dark side Kermit you're like your
current who's your planet coos being Kermit I'm I'm like I'm gonna have sex
with a skinny version of Miss Piggy all the time you're you're playing a
coosbein Kermit but you're a mid-transformation coosbein Kermit no
you're you're you're the little frog that's his cousin that Robin yeah yeah
you're Robin you're Wally see graphics you're Robin and you're a year old yeah
you're freaking Wally see no way I'm Wally see graphics yeah you're both miss
piggy and I'm big bird no no yeah no no you're you're the gay skeg see now
Chamberlain you go yeah
scene where they're all eating dinner and they go like no Cameron is the is
the new the new Sesame Street Muppet with autism Patrick is Oscar the grouch and
I'm Jason Siegel oh the new Muppet is Greta Thunberg actually there is a photo
of you dressed up as Oscar the grouch's child I bet there is yeah it's called
just any photo of you in your life you fucking trash can green guy. You shut the fuck up!
You shut up! See Oscar it's a total grouch moment that's what he would say yeah
Patrick is Oscar the grouch grouching out yeah you're your grouch morde morde
morde your eel up shut the fuck up Cameron Cameron is Oscar the grinch is
Winnie the Pooh and I'm Christopher Robin and you're lucky I come hang out with
you guys no I'm I'm I mean have you ever considered that maybe Christopher Robin
had multiple personalities no well yeah that ruins my childhood I there's a fan
theory going around apparently that all the animals from Winnie the Pooh had sex
with Christopher Robin mm-hmm there's a fan theory going around about that yeah
that's the fear I'm thinking that the Creator is gonna say it's true yeah I'm
excited for us to have fan theories about us yeah what are gonna be the fan
theory yeah there's a fan theory that you and me are figments of Cameron's
imagination. Yeah we're not gonna confirm nor deny that one. Yeah. The other ones
will confirm and deny. Both. Mm-hmm. Both confirm and deny. Yeah. What are you doing
on your phone Patrick? I'm trying to find. No you're not. Yeah I am trying to find it.
I'm trying to find it. No I'm trying to find that there's oh here it is yeah
that's that's that's Caleb. Oh my god Caleb this is you. Yeah you're friggin
your
- Oh, yeah, Caleb, you're the Koosbanian Foob.
- You're the Koosbanian Foob.
- That's his name.
- You're the Foosbanian Coob.
- I don't even know what you're saying at this point.
- You're the Koosbanian Foob, dude.
- I don't, that makes no sense to me.
I told you guys, I just confessed on the podcast
that I have now punched a woman in the face.
- Oh, what?
Huh? - Yeah.
- What?
- I punched a woman in the face over Christmas break.
- You said that, when did you confess?
You just confessed that now?
- Yeah. - Why?
- Oh, no, no, no.
Yeah, 'cause you got into that bar fight with Josh.
- Yeah. - Oh.
- How many details are we allowed to talk about on this?
- I don't know because--
- We've already talked about it, I thought.
- I know we did. - We definitely have.
- We just talked about it in the TELVR text.
We didn't talk about it on the show,
'cause we haven't recorded an episode since then.
- Because I don't wanna say the bar
because people involved were afraid that there was going to be like a warrant out for us.
It was a bad one. But the only thing that I will divulge is that I did punch a woman
in the face because she was square and I was like, "I'll take a gamble on this."
She was square? What do you mean?
She had a Minecraft Steve blockhead and was close to 7,000 pounds.
And at first I didn't know she was a woman.
And I'm sorry that I misgendered her and punched her in the face.
I thought that you said that you just punched a woman right now.
No, no, no.
I would though, if she was here again.
I would take her down.
Would you punch Crendle?
I would, oh yeah, Crendle from Waffle House, I would not punch. I would only ever make love to her and treat her like the princess that she deserves to be.
The princess of the Orc Kingdom.
Yeah, I mean we can't talk about it in any other length, but that story's crazy.
Yeah, it was stupid.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, if you change all the names I think you can go into it.
Basically, Caleb went into this cantina.
And there was a green robot alien named Gribin.
green yeah Robin groban groban Caleb shot and grobel shot at the same time and he
said make funky and they yeah died and there's an alien named gobbles and I
and I punched her in the face there's an alien named Crandall yeah
Yeah, Crendle the alien.
Crendle of Kreenis.
Yeah.
But yeah, so, Gus, I'll just say this.
The funniest part of the story is just that Gus doesn't know what he, the way that the
fight started was he walked up to somebody, he was very drunk, he walked up to somebody,
said something, and then just the guy punched him in the face and then started kicking him
in the head while he was on the ground.
And just, his head probably still hurts.
was like three weeks ago but and I Gus has no idea what he said he has no clue
what he told this guy I just came out of the bathroom and people were hitting
each other in the head with pool balls Jesus Christ yeah really there's really
bad what if you say the name of the place and then Cameron that censors it I
will not I don't think it matters where it was it was Denny's yeah
pool hall. Yeah, some of the denny's have full bars in California.
There wasn't, no, there wasn't, it wasn't a pool hall, people just brought their own pool
balls to look at and hang out. Yeah, that's true.
You see this thing? It's 100% ivory. It says 8 on it.
Yeah. This one's the black ball. You never hit this fucking ball unless you need to.
Um, yeah, what else? What else happened?
happened? I don't know man. I feel like it's been so long I don't even remember.
On December 23rd, I went to the mall in Newton and they had a big sculpture of a
bunch of naked children in a pot. What? In a giant pot. Well, it was like a
sculpture. It was like it was a round. It was a big like bronze sculpture. It was
like this round thing. It looked like a bunch of like little girls like
leaning over a wall, like leaning outward and over a circular wall and then
we were on the second floor of the mall and I was looking down and they're all
naked like you can see from above they all have their their asses are out and
then I was like this is like some kind of crazy like like Epstein sculpture you
know this is like a Moloch thing and I went down and looked at it and it was
right next to- Louis CK is from Newton. Oh my god. Oh no. But it was right next to the like
take your picture of Santa thing and so they had taped up on this like this like
child sacrifice sculpture just like a piece of printer paper and on it written
in marker it just said happy Hanukkah. Oh that's so fucking funny. It didn't have like a like
a plaque that said it literally had nothing. It had no we tried to look it up could not
find any information about it. It was really we should go look at it. It's creepy as fuck.
It's pretty close to Newton I guess. Yeah Caleb will drive us. Yeah. I'll drive you.
I'm gonna have a car yeah yeah dude we can we're gonna go to the new this is the
this is the year we go to the New Hampshire reptile Expo yeah when is it
there it happens like monthly I think yeah yeah I because I get recommendations
for all the time yeah and it seems like they must be it's either like monthly or
weekly it's ridiculously I got a gecko I should probably go yeah well Oh fucking
And so I think it was like New Year's Day or New Year's Eve.
I went to Chipotle in Manchester because it's like the only, there's only like a few restaurants
that have like vegan food in New Hampshire.
And I went to the Chipotle and I was kind of fucked up because I was like, I was pre-gaming
but no one knew I was pre-gaming.
I was kind of fucked up and I like walked into like the Chipotle, I was walking in and there
was just a car alarm going off and I just like sat there and I just kind of stared at the
car alarm for a little bit or the car going off because I was like what the fuck's going
on and then I hear "Hey Pat!" and it's my cop cousin.
Nice.
And I like freaked out a little bit but then I just like needed a diversion so I pointed
at the car alarm the car that was going off and I was just like is that your car
and he's like no that's not mine okay I'll see you later. Fuck yeah, hanging out with family has been awesome.
Oh I went to a soy party too. Oh yeah nice in Baltimore. Yeah in Baltimore I have
family in Baltimore and they are their friends are all just like like 2000s
hipsters yeah like it's insane. There's a guy who had a chaos tattoo on one arm
and what I assume is the opposite of chaos on his other arm. No, there's only
tattoos order, I think, but it was just a weird symbol and I was like, oh, the
only way that you would get those two symbols is if it's like chaos and order
because you're fucking gay and this guy when I was sitting in the other like
sitting in the room playing cards with my younger sibling and let's say those
cards were not for humans. Yeah
and this guy came in and was like, "Come hither, it's time to sing Happy Birthday."
There is a guy.
He said, "Come hither."
Oh, man.
No, and then they did harmony in Happy Birthday and like with vibrato.
So, a guy was like, "Happy Birth..."
Like just doing like theater singing.
Jesus.
People are like fucking 30 something.
That sucks.
Just kill yourself.
Oh, my God.
There was a...
At Dom's mom's like birthday party, there was a...
So I had to deal with the same type of guys I guess, but there's this one guy who like...
What did he...
Oh!
So I was at the bar and Dom's dad and I were talking about what drinks we were going to
get.
That's what we were talking about.
And then the dude...
I was asking them if they had Modelo there because I just wanted a Modelo.
I went up to the bar because I thought they had Tecate but it was some stupid New Hampshire
local like IPA and then some dude he was talking to explained all of the IPAs to
me and I was like dude I'm just gonna drink a fucking Corona I don't know and
then he like started talking to her dad again was like oh is uh he your genetic
makeup? Is that your parental unit? Yeah. Oh I hate that one. My grandpa wore his
MAGA hat specifically to meet my brother's Mexican girlfriend. Another
fucking thing happened at that party I was I was off the G&Ts yeah I think
that's gonna be my drink this year I don't think I'm gonna drink beer I'm just gonna drink G&Ts.
Guys and two guys. I was off the G&Ts so I was like
kinda I don't know but I was walking around and then I saw some dude hug Dom's
mom from behind and I was like what the fuck is going on with that guy. That guy's way too
drunk and then Dom and her mom both have bleached hair and the guy like said the
guy said Dom's mom's name and then like went to go hug Dom from behind. I was like
what the fuck and then the guy tried to like play the guy was like out of it
Dude, it was like some finance guy on like a weekend. So he's like, whoa. Yeah getting fucked and then he like he looked at
Dom's like trying to like apologize, but he's getting too handsy in his apology. Hmm, and it's just like I was just standing back
Just ma'am. I'm sorry. I grabbed these titties
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I thought you were your mom. Oh my god. You probably think I'm so much
Like oh my you look like your mom. You probably think I'm the weirdest guy of all time
You probably think I'm the weirdest guy of all time just taking off his clothes
It was probably think I'm so naked right now. You probably think I'm the most naked guy. You probably think my dick looks so strange
Yeah, that guy sucked I
Liked him. Yeah, it was actually Caleb in disguise. Yeah, it was me in the skies. Yeah
Transformers robots in the song dude. I rewatched transformers dark of the moon that movie fucking rocks
That might be one of my favorite movies. Really? It's so fucking it's crazy
Cuz like they just like restage like like world terrorist attacks like they just have said it's like oh, this is 9/11
Oh, this is Pearl Harbor. Like it's just like that's that's what it is
It's like it's like oh, but it's like 9/11, but the Transformers are knocking over the buildings Autobots. It's fucking crazy
That's like Optimus Prime. It's like we must compromise Jamal Khashoggi
It starts out with them fucking ending regimes in the Middle East
It's insane dude. I and it looks so fucking good. It came out in 2011 and it's
Where the Decepticons are blowing up Chicago and the Autobots are like we have to bring the fight to them and kill every last one
of them where they live
I'm like Megatron is like on his knees like begging for mercy and Optimus Prime
rips out his spinal cord. That's the one before Optimus Prime becomes a villain
right? Sentinel Prime is the villain in that if that's what you're thinking of.
Voiced by Leonard Nimoy. Yeah. No that movie's fucking sick it's on Amazon Prime
right now I recommend re-watching it. Whoa Amazon what? Oh my god. Oh my god.
Amazon Prime the transformer it's an Amazonian woman it's a robot with tits
yeah it's you yeah that's what you are to me okay and that's the one that's the
movie where they replaced Megan Fox - and they just have a random other girl and
the only way I can Fox is just like just like yeah that dumb bitch dumps me and
now I have a hotter girl yeah wait isn't she like British yeah yeah that's so
fucking sick - what a player they made him in those movies yeah he's great dude
- Shia?
- Yeah.
- He's a, I've met him.
- Yeah, you hung out with him.
- We hung out at my work.
- That's cool, man.
- I had like the dumbest interaction with him.
I was like, you're Shia LaBeouf, right?
(laughing)
- What did he say?
- He said, yeah.
(laughing)
It's like he said it like he was very annoyed with me
and I was like, man, that's so cool.
(laughing)
Man, that's so cool, you're Shia LaBeouf.
but somebody they made me I've talked about this already they made me get him
a coffee and I thought he was homeless all right that's about an hour you guys
ready wait no we can do fucking 20 more seconds 20 more seconds okay do
occasion Patrick
because there's not listen one in Patrick which one do the one where the pit do
the only 10 seconds left just do I need to help with the car yeah that's the one
I need help I did cage and Patrick early all right that's an hour wait no I
didn't do agent Patrick right you guys know the fans aren't gonna like do it
2020 neck new year new gear ultimate gear we're going all the way here yeah going
all in new new new episodes new episodes it's gonna be new when Caleb gets back
to Boston it's just gonna pop off we're gonna pop ball we gonna get dumb gumbo
we gonna get it we're gonna be making gumbo we're gonna be making shrimp and
grits oh we're gonna make a dog we're gonna make a dog we're gonna make we're
gonna make the the Jollibee documentaries coming Nolan's editing it everyone yeah
- Yeah, shout out Nolan, great teen vids,
14 kids on YouTube.
- I think we're gonna make some man on the street vids.
- Yeah, I have a game show that I'm pitching.
- We're starting a game show on national television.
- No, it's more just a man on the street video.
- We're gonna go to the reptile expo
and beat people up and film it.
- Uh-huh.
- We're gonna do world star,
we're gonna do reptile expo star.
- What we should do is, my idea for the reptile expo
is we walk around asking every person with a reptile
if they'll let them bite us.
yeah yeah just make a compilation of us getting bitten by every reptile yeah
how's that sound yeah a thousand more years of podcast about list thank you
for subscribing go to the Reptile Expo and we're gonna go to the sex shop that
is like literally down the street from there that again you just make everything
nasty disgusting it has glory holes why don't you go hang out with your favorite
underwear penis yeah exactly you disgusting sex freak you're gone why
don't you go put on your favorite condom onto your body but on a second lie down
for a while it's not enough for you you go look for the ultimate condom why don't
you find yeah why don't you find the big condom why don't you search now why
don't you go find the big condom from naked gun and go inside of it that's
what they buried Leslie Nielsen they sealed it like a vacuum bag yeah they
sealed them like a vacuum bag yeah and then they sous vide it at a hundred and
forty degrees for six hours and then he got out then he got out of the bag and
then went "I love it" and then immediately died.
He re-died.
Yeah.
They buried him alive in a condom.
He did his funny line the one last time.
Yep.
Alright.
It's such a good movie.
Thanks y'all.
Yeah.
Bye everybody.
Thanks folks.