Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
*Badass music*
- So much better.
- Shh, shh, shh, shh.
- We're recording in the library today.
- Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
- We're in the library.
- We're recording in the library today.
- Shh.
We're here to watch DVDs.
- Yeah, we're--
- Shh, guys.
- What?
What are you gonna get yelled at?
- By who?
- I'm gonna rent a CD, I think.
- Really?
A CD?
- I'm gonna go to the CD section.
- I think I'm gonna get Maroon 5.
- Yeah, I think I'm gonna get that too.
Actually I think I'm gonna get now that's what I call music.
That shit's funny as hell.
What?
That shit.
Guys, now that's what I call music, probably number 15.
You guys have to be quiet.
I'm gonna get now that's what I call music 15.
Which one is the one that has bubba sparks on it?
I think that's, now that's what I call rap.
One.
Rap number one?
Yeah, that's what I call.
Shhhhhhhhh!
Sorry!
What the fuck is it?
*phone rings*
Sorry!
What is- what is happening?
Guys, my phone's going off. I can't-
What the hell?
Answer it.
*phone rings*
I can't- I can't figure it out.
Answer it!
Just-
*phone rings*
Guys, my phone- I don't know how to turn it off.
It's an alarm.
Answer the phone!
It's an alarm, I said!
I'm trying to-
Turn your phone down!
I'm trying to snooze it!
Please answer-
*phone rings*
Turn the fucking-
Oh my god.
That's the alarm.
It's going-
*phone rings*
did you hear that okay you're the entire library's looking at us now i like this one that's one
of my favorite songs that is actually one of my favorite songs never heard that my second
phone is going oh my god you brought two phones with alarms i'm playing some music guys we're
not really at the library we're in the office i've heard that one before that's a good one
that
worst one to me that one's the worst that's no this is like it's like we
music this is the one that was I think my dad's alarm so I was here that every
that I get I set up some notification on my phone like in 2014 or something like
that with that choo-choo sound huh and sometimes my phone will just go true and
I don't remember what it is cuz I silenced the fucking thing so out of
nowhere I'll just hear a train whistle on my phone. That's terrifying. That one's
funny as hell though. That one's funny. Yeah I do like that one. What's this app
you got? It's called settings. Have you ever checked this out? I have that?
This app's system settings? Yeah. It has alarms and stuff in it. I have this on my
phone right now. Please don't we don't need two of these. We do not need two of
these. I can put anything on it.
What was y'all's first ringtone that you bought? First ringtone I never bought a
ringtone. Yeah yeah I figured out there's my phone my phone my first flip
phone that I got. You could record a sound and just part turn into a
a ringtone, so I made my ringtone. I recorded my clock radio playing
Linkin Park "Numb" and I made that my ringtone and it sounded like shit. I
think I bought one ringtone and it was a clip song and then I changed it
to-- I figured out you could just record things. I used to do that with
music. I used to record-- I couldn't figure out how to get music on my iPod, so I
I would record or in I really I couldn't get it.
I could YouTube to mp3.
Yeah dude.
Yeah.
Well, I didn't do that though.
I would mediafire.com.
I would record into my headset.
I would turn on the speaker record into like my gaming headset microphone and then put
that on my on my iPod.
I saw there's this website there it was like you could just get like a it was like YouTube
convert you convert like a thing on YouTube to a like a ringtone you just
put your phone number in it would send it to you. Oh yeah. And I would I would
have so I had so many funny ringtones on my Verizon. I bet you had funny ass ones.
When you had the Cartman ringtones oh my. I didn't have stuff like that. That shit was on
another level. I had like YouTube poop sounds on my phone. Did y'all ever change your
voicemail message to hello? Oh yeah. Yep. Hello. I did my mom made me change it.
it hey she got mad at me. Oh hey, she got mad at me because she called me one
time and I didn't pick up and that tricked her and she got so mad she made
me change it. I fell for it on my brother's voicemail every single time I
call it's you fall for every time. I remember one time I remember one time
that I had to get picked up from school and neither my parents or were picking
up their phones. So I was had the person call my brother and I saw them get
pranked live where the principal or whoever the front desk lady was like she
called him I was like hello mr. Pitts hello oh she's so mad I had when I was
like 16 I was being very funny made the entire Seinfeld theme song my voicemail
nice mm-hmm that was that's funny as hell mm-hmm yeah yeah really a really
slow long voicemail message is really funny I had I that was after if my mom
made me change the hello hello when I was like you've reached Cameron at and then
just saying my phone number really really slowly my saying in a six one my
voicemail until maybe like it's I like three years ago until I moved to Boston
I guess that's like five years ago four years ago any amount of time yeah there's
an amount of time that it is it's since then or when I first moved my voicemail
was still me when I was like 13 being like you've reached Caleb. I'm pretty sure it still is. I feel like I called you, I tried to call you one time.
No, I changed it to I think just a number. Yeah. Yeah. I changed it to robot.
Yeah, that's the most professional thing you can have is that one. I'm pretty much a professional.
Definitely. I love being professional. Me too. I would say that I'm a young professional. I'm a young professional.
I'm actually they call me a bro. They call me brofessional. Yeah, cuz I'm a young you need to go to a
Confessional. Mm-hmm. Yeah, cuz you've been sinning. Yeah, I did sin last night. Really. What did you do?
Masturbated you masturbated
Okay. All right. Fine. What'd you masturbate to?
Father I've seen my father
I am masturbating to you right now
Father I have to admit I'm jacking off to you right now and I'm looking through the little holes. Yep
And no matter what you say, I will continue.
And I'm going to keep continuing.
And if I hear your voice even one more time, I will get harder and harder.
And also, if you move, I'm going to get super hard.
And I'm pretending I'm going to get even harder.
I'm pretending you're Carmen Electra back there.
And there's nothing you can do.
I'm imagining, Father, I've sinned.
I'm imagining you with big boobs.
Father, I'm using this as a toilet right now.
Yep. I'm going to come shot you through this divider thing, and it's going to be like a shower.
- Exactly.
- I don't know why that word.
- That word's been getting me a lot lately.
- Cumshot?
- Cumshot.
- I was laughing a lot about a guy
whose last name is Cumshot.
But I think that's a really funny last name.
Josh Cumshot?
- Joshua Cumshot.
- Joshua, Joshua Cumshot.
- Why do people like cum all the, like cum?
- It's less about the cum, it's more about the shot.
- But why do people like a cumshot?
Like why do you want--
- I'm telling you, people like it being shot with things.
- Why do people want cum on their face?
- I don't know.
- People love cum.
some wires crossed somewhere.
- What's up with cumming on someone's face though?
- It must be like the brain wire that's like,
you know, I like soda, and then it's like,
the one where it's like, you know,
the different liquid gets switched out,
and I think it's, they think that soda is common,
so they like it.
- What kind of evolutionary, 'cause you know,
I'm a very science-minded guy.
What kind of evolutionary, and nice phone.
How's your phone, Patrick?
- I wasn't gonna say anything, I was just gonna do that.
- Talking to my mom.
- And this is the time to talk to her.
my whole family just died. Oh, so how are you talking to your mom? Yeah, she's
the only a survivor. Okay, you're a liar through a medium. Yeah, and she
killed all of them. My mom killed my whole family and she's texting you.
Yep. She's saying you're next. She's running at you right now. She said
she's running all the way here. Okay with a big side knife. The big sword
sign knife besides a psychic knife. She's running at me with a sign to
a film that says I'm going to kill you. That would be terrifying if a killer
started running towards me, I'd be like okay, but if you had a sign that said
I'm going to kill you, I knew that I'd be I'd be in bad shape that would scare
the crap out of me. The living daylights even which monster, which movie monster
or serial killer do you think would be the easiest to defeat Godzilla
step on his toe
get in his toe like like one of the like one of those one of the monsters
from the Athlete's Foot commercials,
the little orange guy just living his toenail.
- Yeah.
- I would do that.
I would become a bacteria in his body.
That's probably how you kill something that big.
- Yeah, I think going inside of a Godzilla
would be probably a very life-changing experience.
- Yeah, it would probably open a lot of doors
for me sexually as well.
I'd probably realize a lot of stuff.
- I'd be down, like once he's dead,
I'd be down to do whatever after that.
but once godzilla's dead i'd be so like
i'd just be walking up to people being like eat me eat me
i don't think you'd be doing it. I wouldn't want to be eaten though
i would only want to go in through the toenail
do you think it would... let me in your toenail! let me live in your toenail!
let me in your toenail! let me in! let me in!
hiring a prostitute drilling
could be a hundred dollars to go inside your toenail
I talked about this last night. I definitely do understand the giant, the giant woman
fetish. Oh yeah, for sure. I completely get it dude. Why? I mean the thing is, people
who have those giant woman fetishes, they get them because they watch cartoons with
giant women in them. Yeah. And we all watch the same cartoons as a kid. Absolutely. Like
we all, it's all in there somewhere. The end of doodlers by car? Like at least some amount.
We all got a little bit of something in there.
- Yeah, but what if it's like a giant--
- For me, wasps.
(laughing)
- For me, I'm really attracted to my gym partner
being a monkey.
(laughing)
It's just all early childhood stuff.
- I wanna put, yeah, my biggest sexual fantasy
is a giant jawbreaker.
- Oh, just sitting in her mouth.
- Oh my God.
- A girl walks up to you, huge jawbreaker,
twice the size of her body.
- Yeah.
- She asks you for a quarter.
- Yep.
- Oh my God.
- Similar for me, Willy Wonka.
- Getting stuck in a tube.
- There's so many people.
it's a bunch of dancing brooms. I bet Augustus Gloop was big for the like the
latex seal people. Oh yeah. Latex seal stuff. I bust this gloop. That scares me. I
bust this gloop. The what? I bet Augustus Gloop was terrified before he died.
died. Yeah, that's gotta be the worst way to go. Have you ever seen it?
Being Augustus Gloop. Yeah. Oh man, that's tragic. Hear about Augustus
Gloop. His friends at home be like, "Did you hear about Augustus Gloop?
He got psyched into a chocolate tube and died." They're all just
normal. They don't know about the Chocolate Factory storyline or
anything. Yeah, that was like probably the worst day back at school
forever. Just four empty chairs, you know, they all come from the same four
desks. They did. They all grow up, but they only talk about it when they when
they're drunk. They're like yeah. Do you remember a guy Augustus? This is
got to do a chocolate tube and died in chocolate.
He's trying to drink from a chocolate river. He won a contest and was killed
by some go fund me page. We're heartbroken to announce that our son
Augustus Gloop was killed by a chocolate tube.
Sucked into a tube and killed.
I think if you're the parents of Augustus Gloop, you leave the chocolate part out.
That kid's getting bullied at school enough for being fat.
But how do you explain, but people will ask questions.
No that's the type of thing where.
A tube, what kind of tube?
Airplane.
Just a tube.
Airplane tube.
Just a normal tube.
That's the thing though, no where the people who bullied him at school would hear like
like damn like he died from a chocolate to like maybe we should have been been
easier on little glue. They can say that he killed himself.
The old Gus Gloop. Yeah, that's what they would think. They would think, oh we
made him kill himself by calling him the Gloopster. He drowned in a chocolate
river on purpose. Worst last name to have when drowning in chocolate. Yeah, yeah, he
did. He tied a cinder block to his foot and he jumped into the...
- He's just loop looking at Willy Wonka
before he gets in the river and he's like,
before I do this I want to say
that I'm doing this on purpose.
- Willy Wonka, like coordinating with the Oompa Loompas,
setting up the whole like, you know,
oh we're gonna get rid of one kid at each room
and they're like, okay well who's gonna drown
in the chocolate, is it gonna be,
will it be Mike TV?
(laughing)
Will it be Veruca Salt?
Let me think.
with the
that's it
who had a little
what about charlie bucket
this is not a lot of
this is the hardest bucket they we've ever had to think about the people who
have got that little swedish what about the group
no
i would never work no no no no no i'm not talking about the other people
makes no sense and what are the people who was like
uh... crap
I got gloops of chocolate all over me.
What did you just say?
[Laughter]
Yeah, well no, what they did was like,
they were like, "Oh, we got it. Let's, let's like, let's,
maybe the Augustus Kit could work. Let's take a look
at his like application or whatever and then it's just a page
covered in chocolate sticks."
[Laughter]
That might work. I do feel like that's probably
the worst chocolate in the world, in that river.
Yeah. Can you imagine? That can't be good.
No, I mean, chocolate like flowing like that.
It's probably the kind that they use in the shitty
animals in there yeah there is fish probably animals eating and probably
chocolate a chocolate bass there's a Swedish fish mm-hmm yeah that's actually
pretty good yeah but why would you mix gummies with chocolate you can do a very
flavor there's a Japanese or Korean little fish fish things beta fish no the
fucking the the things they're like cakes with chocolate in them Oh octopus
those are just to go back to the to the picky which kid to die thing like I feel
like if like Mike TV if I was Mike TV and I and I saw the first room I saw
Augustus gloop get killed by chocolate I'd be like okay well he's gloop I'm
sick it's a candy factory I'm Mike TV there's no way there's TV there's no
shot no chance in way am I getting no chance what's the blueberry girls name
anyway. Yeah, I live in regard. Yeah, see that'd be another one where I'm like
maybe
dangerous should have stayed home. Veruca salt is on the is what happened to her.
I remember she she falls into a oh she gets yeah. She wants a golden goose and
she has her whole song. She falls into a garbage shoot. Yeah, that's not very
spoiled as hell. No, her attitude is salty and hey, if I was named grandpa,
forget about it.
there's no way I'm going to put in there. No shot
well. That was what I was like okay, okay, Augustus gloop he'll get killed by
the chocolate, Mike TV, the TV obviously. What about this great
I guess he has to survive till the end. Yeah, I can't I guess we come up with a
good old that room doesn't make any sense. Time will get him. It's fine.
Yeah, the grandpa, the grandpa room did yeah, the worthers originals room, yo
true. Nowadays what kind of factory do you think Willy Wonka would have nowadays? What
do you think? Yeah.
Was some kind of Foxconn factory?
Mm-hmm.
Yep.
Yep, he would be making weapons and stuff.
Mm-hmm.
Nah.
That'd be pretty cool.
That can't be true though.
I think he probably would have a Foxconn factory.
I think he would make cell phones.
I think he would.
And the Oompa Loompas, all of them would be children.
Mm-hmm.
Nah, from China.
And the four kids who come in?
They would be grown men.
From China.
would be taking investors from China and they would all die in a you know some
kind of a lave room mm-hmm maybe we're told it's good they'd all just get
sucked into a lathe and and you and de-gloved is it you who showed me that
video that video that guy getting de-gloved that's one of the worst
videos I've ever seen yeah yeah it's his entire skin entire skin comes off like a
cartoon and his skeleton flies I thought his gloves just came off yeah well he's
being degloved is like the scary that's so scary to me. Especially if it's cold
out. Especially if I'm a Chinese man in a factory because I know that video is
getting posted online. I will never know peace. Who do you think is the person who
watches these videos and is like this shit funny as hell and everyone needs to see this. I would be fine if I got
degloved in the comfort of my own home that's fine yeah but if I'm out in
public oh yeah I will never live it down. So embarrassing. You ever think about how
like you the machines like that are made go on mm-hmm that can't be it that you
ever think about I'm just trying to think of a I'm really hungover I'm
trying to think of a way to like make sense like how machines like that were
made like I don't think we were we wait that is it no I'm trying to think of the
next sentence please give me time to think of the next it's like I don't
think the human body was was meant to be degloved so true so no keep going you
said that was literally I literally cannot think right now this is so crazy
like I'm gonna give you time what do you need what do you need from us oh hold on
oh he's another alarm fucking going off man I'm gonna call it's a what is this
who's calling me who is this is this scary clown no I do I pick up this foot
that's terrifying I gotta pick up I hang up I don't want to my voicemail okay
ringtones matter annoying yeah just fucking whatever it's beer it's beer
it's beer what what did you say hello weird
ah my god that's not a scary clowns a Joker no it's a scary clown right here
Oh, yeah, that is just a scary. Oh, he's got a gun point at that screen
Do I hang what do I do? Hey?
What are you
What the hell
You but dial me I think I think this call is meant for someone else. He must use the wrong number, dude
Way professional comedians, you know, you got off to a slow start but come on
Okay
I'm gonna hang up on him. He's interrupting our recording session. What a dickhead. Well, there's an ad
Do you hack into somebody's phone call I guess so this must be something the clowns doing
What app is that with the calls? What do you mean? What app its phone app?
No, the other one where you can just my this is the music my phone app plays
Why is your phone playing music?
It's a it's a feature of the phone app. What was that ad?
What ad?
That the phone app was playing
I'm getting another call
Gangster clown this gangster now, dude. I don't listen to some damn. I haven't talked to him in a minute though, dude
I hate him. Can I should I but can I just pick it up real fast?
I said it out later. All right, I'll say the first thing answer it answer
Hey gangsta clown, listen, I'm happy slappy, yeah I know.
I know.
It's so hard to get into a word edgewise.
Can I?
Yeah, we're gonna play.
We can perform, yeah you don't perform games, you play them.
I'm not afraid, you can't even see me.
do that's why I hate is the knife.
That's alright, cause this knife is gonna improve your look.
Can you stop being so thug and gangster?
I'm out of you.
(laughing)
Is that?
Pull your pants up, gangster clown.
(laughing)
Do you hang up on them?
New ad. Oh my god.
Make your unique color call.
Wow.
(phone rings)
- Okay, I seriously hope we don't get a third call.
- Can you just please put your phone on silent, okay?
I'm sick of fucking these phone calls.
- Oh my God. - I was about to put it
on silent. - Who is it this time?
- Who is this?
- It's Killer Klown.
- Let me talk to him.
- Okay, all right, here, I'll pick it up.
Guys, you guys go way back, right?
- Yeah, I know him. - All right.
(phone rings)
- Yeah, hi.
What's up?
- This one has to have been a butt dial.
(phone rings)
singing he's singing right now he when he does this he wants to show me
we'll play I like play I like to put on a plan gonna kill me are you done are you
Are you done?
Chill man, just fucking shut up.
We're in the middle of a fucking podcast dude.
Oh here comes the blu-
He's playing his guitar again obviously.
Yeah we get it dude, you got cool new pedals.
You got a delay pedal, it's a boss, I get it.
You got a boss delay.
Is he done?
No okay, I guess not.
I hate when he plays that song.
I hate his violin.
Yeah we get it, you're talented.
in I hate it yeah we get it you're talented yeah a one-man band over here
awesome killer clown there you're just calling can you can you like see this is
why we stopped being in a band together I'm serious I can't hear you dude your
connections terrible he must have boost mobile he does you know gangster clown
got boost mobile we're in that commercial that boost mobile commercial
that had a it's like Mickey Avalon is in it the my dick guy yeah the my dick guy
it's like the Mickey Avalon's verse they do like a rap song killer clown just
won't shut up I'm gonna hang up on you yeah shut up bitch and it's like please
tell me that's it I'd see there's a new ad here but it doesn't play any sound
it's gotta be so annoying to have your phone play ads yeah there we go finally
it's on okay I put my phone on so sorry guys I just had to take a few of those
call is you know I'm doing business with the gangster clown so why'd the other
white his brothers call you - well they just like to like see what's I'm just
like they're just checking in on yeah well except for the scary clown he I
actually had to take out a restraining order against me really anyway he took
out one against you yeah and I took one I guess at him as revenge hmm they do
they it's called a revenging order yeah you take out a restraining order on
somebody and then they take it you take one back out on can you just take one out
for no reason I think you need a new roof to get one what kind of proof he's
weird yeah you need he's weird proof I think with the text that we send each
other I could definitely file for a restraining order oh yeah you oh
absolutely like look dude officer they've lost their minds they're talking
about what no we jam jump no we jam we jam what is that some good
- Good ass Jub-No-Wee jam. - We had it for lunch.
- Yeah, we had Jub-No-Wee jam. - Yeah, we had Jub-No-Wee jam.
- It's good ass Jub-No-Wee jam.
- Dude, honestly, I thought when they brought out our order,
I thought they forgot our Jub-No-Wee jam,
and I was like, "Did y'all forget our Jub-No-Wee jam?"
And they're like, "The Jub-No-Wee jam will be right out."
- Yeah. - And the Jub-No-Wee jam
was delicious. - Oh my God.
- I really enjoyed the Jub-No-Wee jam.
- The Jub-No-Wee jam with the apricot spread and the feta.
Oh my god, the feta on the Jubb Norwegian.
That's what Jubb Norwegian is, dude.
Oh yeah, the hamburger with the meat and the bun.
Yeah, you could say that because those parts of the hamburger are good.
Yeah, it doesn't make any sense.
Well, you can call a hamburger something.
You can call a cheeseburger a vegan.
Oh, the pizza with the cheese and the crust?
Yeah, there's some pizza that doesn't have cheese and crust.
You need one kind of pizza that doesn't have cheese and crust.
Tomato soup.
Sauce pizza.
Sauce pizza is not...
Sauce bowl, yeah.
spaghetti spaghetti meatballs you turn my tomato leather no yeah no talking
about pepperoni talking about pepperoni pepperoni that's you know how you said
that it's not how I said that what's the best job no we jam you ever had
probably the one we just had yeah I definitely do want to go back and get
another another job no we I want to get another job no we jam I just make job
no we jam at home it's not gonna be the same they have the best job no we jam
they do make good job no we jam they do have the best job I have locally sourced
job. No, they do. I think they make the we jam in house. Yeah, I think I think
it's free range job knows
the job is that they melt it's grass. It's grass fed job. No, I just love that
you have a ship man. Unfortunately, it's human fed. We do jam is the my
favorite part. The we do they do. I know they have they have they do they try
not to cage the job knows, but the we jams I've seen video. I've seen video
footage of the the the Wee Jam
slaughterhouse and they it's it's
not great. Tell you what those
damn Mediterranean. So they have
a guy to rainians are weird.
Yeah, they know they have a guy
at the slaughterhouse whose whole
job it is to stick a stick up the
Wee Jams, but before it dies
really yeah, does that do it
makes it scared.
It is funny. It hurts it. Do you
guys eat veal? No, no, I mean I
would probably like I'd not like
I would be that look. I don't
know what kind of question. I
feel like most people if you ask
I went, "Do you eat veal?"
I mean, I guess--
- What do you mean, what kind of question is that?
- Well, you know that we're--
- It's a fucking yes or no question.
- You know we're not vegetarian.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, but some people still just don't eat veal.
- Veal is like the--
- I feel like I don't know if I've ever had
an opportunity to eat veal, though.
- Pretty much any time you go to an Italian restaurant,
the meat sauce is gonna be veal.
- Oh, okay. - Yeah.
- Then I love veal.
- That's the thing, dude.
It's like--
- It's good, but it's like the most--
- They break all the cow's legs,
and they feed them butter,
And then they put them in a giant hot dog maker.
- Yeah, the baby cows too.
- And it's the best tasting meat.
- It is, yeah.
- It tastes so good.
- I've never had veal straight up.
- It's damn good.
- But I've definitely had veal by accident.
- The best meat is always when they just take
like a one day old animal and they just hit it
with a bunch of hammers.
- Dude, lamb, lamb is so good.
- They hit it with hammers like those little--
- I eat so much lamb.
- Those like--
- It feels so good.
- You know what you never have,
'cause it's probably shit?
Sheep, but you know what's damn good?
Lamb.
- Lamb is good as fuck.
Sheep is fucking gotta be terrible.
Lamb on a spit.
Yeah, just a child.
Sheep used to be fire though, back in the Viking days.
Mutton.
True, they did used to eat hella mutton.
But then they were like,
you know what's better than this is the baby version.
It's when we take a baby and we hit it with baseball bats
like hungry, hungry hippos.
(laughing)
Yeah, we'd use it like a live pinata
and then we'd turn it into Euro meat.
you know i uh... another thing that proves my point
fish eggs
yeah dude, caviar. people love that shit. eggs too
eggs are probably better than any meat. eggs are way better than any meat. eggs are fuckin' number one
oh my god, cow eggs
you just swan
oh my god, yeah. yeah, i almost asked if a swan lays an egg
i wanna get an ostrich egg
dude, they sell 'em at
city fresh. really?
yeah. the big ass ones?
they sell the no no they sell the ostrich eggs i'm sorry what the fuck
dude an ostrich egg is the size of a football man come on fuck you you suck that was too much
i can't let that one slide and they sell quail eggs too everywhere sells quail eggs man i'm
done with you did you just hit stop on the recorder yeah it's over oh thank god i did
not hit stop i want to eat an ostrich egg so badly yeah i wanted to eat the duck egg but i was like
there's probably no point in me doing that. What do you mean you eat it?
Making a duck egg like an egg. I wanted to eat the duck egg but there was no point.
It's all gonna taste like an egg. Yeah I guess. Quail eggs are good. I guess it
just would taste like a bigger egg but I feel like the flavor profile would be
different. The flavor might be different but not the flavor profile. No. I don't know I feel like a duck egg.
It's all the same profile. But the flavors are different. The flavor is.
is with the yoke is the yoke bigger in a duck egg. It's green. It's green. That's
where Dr. Seuss got the idea. Yeah, it's got feathers in it to quail eggs are so
small. It makes you feel bad eating them. It makes me feel great eating them. It
makes me feel like I'm a giant evil monster. Yeah, it's ruining the life of a
thousand babies. It was the thing. I mean a bouncy ball. That's what I like about
they got a cool pattern. You know what they do. That's why that's why that's
why eating animal hearts is good because it's like I am. I am like I'm putting an
and to every animal soul right now. The second I have ten animals in a bowl in
front of me, I anything like that where it's like you're eating fifty like fifty
animals died for this. Yeah, so funny dude. I am the chicken Jeffrey Dahmer.
Yeah,
because when you eat when you eat like a rotisserie chicken, you're just one
chicken. Yeah, I haven't had one in so long. You and four friends split a
forty eight piece. I know dude that's yeah, it's like a room full of time. I'm
devourer yeah yeah I'll just died so that I could watch yeah or or instead of
getting the the 48 piece chicken hearts you could get one chicken McNugget I'd
get the same effect that's true am i right am that is true millions of
chickens died for my one chicken they take one molecule of meat from every
chicken ever seen the video packed with flavor you ever seen the video we
totally talked about in the video that the chicks going into like the fucking
food yeah I said that video everybody yeah I was the guy who's doing it yeah
yeah I'm one I was a guy with my mouth under the grinder one of chicks going
peepee people damn but the boy chicks they just turn them into mush yeah they
turn them into pink goo that's kind of suck man yeah to be crushed it into you
I was literally thinking about just like like it's so it's it's like so just got
like the process of eating that's got to be rather unpleasant it's crazy that
they're literally up there alive for like 90s the entire yeah and immediately
they get thrown into a big processor that's gotta be the worst man no no
seriously I got a suck man I think they do like it though there is a study that
says that there's a study that's a like that chicks actually like it yeah I saw
So you don't feel bad when you eat McDonald's.
Yeah, it was like Donald, Donald, Donald,
Donald, Donald, Donald, McDonald,
Dr. Ronald M.
Yeah.
That's that study.
Study from the McDonald's.
Donald, Ronald,
Foundation.
Dr.
Yeah.
Study from B King.
(laughing)
Dr. B King.
Dr. B King, Ronald M.
Honorable, Dr. B King.
And.
(laughing)
Yeah.
Dr. CFA
CFA chick-fil-a, but the initial day is his last name. Don't they have a burger King jr. Sandwich?
What what don't they have?
Whopper jr. Yeah, have a burger burger King jr. Sandwich
Don't they have a Burger King jr. Sandwich. I'm sure I think they do
All right, just doesn't matter to me cuz I'm ordinary
I'm checking to sandwich every time they do have check-in sandwiches - they have check-in
Check-in oh my god the Mac check-in
It's good
Ordering it like that, but like clearly like you're being like yeah
I want a chicken so bad.
You can say you pronounce everything else completely normal.
And a mac chicken.
Oh my god, a chicken sandwich?
A mac chicken.
Speaking of chicken, I just got a place around, I haven't seen like a grocery store selling rotisserie chickens in a while.
I love rotisserie chickens.
In a grocery store, I'm not going to, I'm gatekeeping this, I'm not telling anybody.
But, on the corner.
The one right next to me has rotisserie chicken.
What?
You've been holding that out on me?
The one that's, the grocery store that's right near my apartment has a giant sign that says
rotisserie chickens and every time I've gone in there and asked if they had a rotisserie
chicken they said no, come back tomorrow and they never had it.
Fuckers man.
I was so pissed.
You gotta go to the one.
Literally a giant sign that says it outside.
Like I'm not talking like a sign like on the, like a pole with a big sign on top.
Like a giant sign that says rotisserie chicken.
You gotta go to the one.
I'll go there.
I want a rotisserie chicken so bad.
They have them next to the fucking register.
Damn.
What, like a candy bar?
I'm getting that.
Yeah, I'm getting three.
Yeah, you oughta get this too.
Yeah.
I'll get a couple.
That's literally what I would do.
I love it.
I was going, when I left the office yesterday, I came to the office to get my headphones.
I was here for ten minutes.
I took a shit, got my headphones, and left.
That's your full day's work.
It was very, very funny.
You're fucked out.
Yeah.
story that I was like I like he like came in. He grabbed his headphones,
went into the bathroom. He came out of the bathroom and I started I was like,
Oh, do you want will you like take a look at this thing like this video that
I'm work and then he just like he just what he didn't say a word looked at me
just walked out of the door and left yeah. I was like yeah nice to go all
the way to green point, but if I wasn't like literally I got a red bull on the
way there just because I was like fucking tired and then I looked at the
rotisserie chicken at the counter and I was like, well, it's here. I should
yeah, that's just get one to go. I forgot how you're going to get lunch.
Gus and Gus and his dad apparently like anytime they drive together in a car for more than like
30 minutes, they just get a rotisserie chicken, put it on the center console and just eat it
together. That's so romantic to do with your dad. It's such a good gone out to a meal. Just you and
and your dad yeah really yeah I've never done dude I was like eight years old I
was really obsessed with toasted subs
I don't I'd never had a toasted sub before like a like a like a subway or
anything like that I'd never had it before at a first time when I was eight I
I was like, "Oh my God, this is amazing!"
And I made my dad, I went on a father-son date,
and we went to Quiznos because I liked
the Quiznos commercials with the baby.
- I feel like I had a similar toasted sub experience,
but specifically where I was like,
I got for the first time, I had like a steak and cheese sub.
- Yeah. - Which is like,
this has to be like illegal.
It can't be this much of all this stuff in here.
- How come Subway's sandwiches at restaurants
taste so much better than the shit I make at home?
I make shit sandwiches.
Dude, Subway all the meat is turkey.
Sandwiches are terrible at home.
Yeah.
What you have to get is one of those counters that has all the ingredients.
I think I need a big plastic counter and I need a disgusting bath for every knife I have.
Well, you know what it is?
It's the sneeze guard.
You've been sneezing into your sandwiches without realizing it.
Instead of having a teenager sneeze into it.
Yeah.
Well, the amateurs sneeze so bad at home.
They do.
Young sneeze.
It's like the veal thing.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, their sneezes taste better.
They sneeze better than you hit them with a hammer.
long time I was working at a sandwich shop. I cut my finger and didn't know it
cutting tomatoes up, cutting tiny tomatoes, cut my finger and then yeah and
yeah and I got blood in the glove. Uh-huh I was selling sandwiches with
blood in my glove. It's like why is my wasn't on your glove right like why is
my hand stinging and I look so okay. Let me really let me let me let me cutting
of a tomato and you're like my hand started stinging and you didn't look to
if you were bleeding. It was a lunch rush. And I just want to say your hand was in
the glove so the blood was just in the glove. I thought it was tomato juice. So
this is a story about you cut your finger. It's not a story of I put blood
in people's sandwiches. It's a story I cut my finger and it hurt. I cut my finger at
work. That's a great story Patrick. Last night when we were at the bar I'm
still thinking about this. I'm so hungover. I went to the bathroom and there's a
the bathroom with a single sink and I was washing my hands after using the
urinal. The guy who was using the year all next to me start like plus the
urinal. I was washing my hands. He walks over puts his hands under the water
with my hands. They like it touches my hands and then he just like walks out
of the bathroom. I was so fuck. Do you realize I'm like still mad about you
realize what that says about you what it means it's people like that just see
you as just like just an easy target. Yeah, you just are like people like that,
like what just a guy who just has nothing to lose. What do you think the motive
of that action is? That's what I can't figure out. He just wanted to dominate
you. I feel like he saw you and he was like, I can dominate this a wimp and I'm
going to dominate you project in a bathroom, washing your hands. You wash
your hands like a wimp. Sure. Yeah, because he knew that he could, he could
just alpha dog. Yeah, he was. Okay, here's the thing though. That bar,
there's a sign in the front of the bar that says no wimps. Here's the thing
though, letting is salty. Yeah, he's short and he was fat, so I like one
regardless, no matter what he did to me, he could have he could have bent me
over at that sink and I would have walked out of there. The victor
she's come dripping out of your face and but another win for me
because I'm I'm the
that's the only way you can go through life as a wimp. If I don't if I don't
think that to myself every day of my life, it's over.
Uh-huh.
[LAUGHTER]
It's so funny.
There just is a little guy who thought you were such a wimp
that he could wash his hands on your hands.
It was crazy.
I think it probably will change my life forever.
I didn't do anything, no.
I let him walk all over me.
You didn't even smack his hands out?
I went like, whoa.
That was pretty much all I did.
None of us would slap his hands out.
I would.
You would not.
No, you would not.
I started fighting.
You're an even bigger wimp than him.
You're the biggest wimp here.
You would have been silent.
I at least said, I at least, I at least reflexively said, "Whoa!"
You would have said, "Oh, sorry!" and moved your hands out of the way.
That is actually what you would have done.
Probably. Yeah.
What I do is, I'm too much of a wimp to start a fight,
but the second that the person is more than six inches away from me,
I'll start going like, "Oh, cool! Great!"
Yeah, thanks for doing that!
And it really shows them.
Yeah, I know that bit. Yeah.
Yeah, just being like... Talk really loudly. When they cut you in line and then be like,
"Oh, awesome." "I love waiting in line here." Yeah. Remember that same bar, the fucking
bouncer, like a little person walked in. The bouncer walked up to him and just said, "Hey,
you can't be in here." "Nah, I'm just kidding." Yeah. Like he followed him into the bathroom.
Yeah, he followed a little guy into the bathroom and while the dude is pissing, he says, "Oh,
can't be in here now I'm just playing that guy's rules dude he's so sick every
time he like you got fingerless gloves on yeah every time I go in and I'm wearing
a shirt that like so every time you're going wearing a shirt every time I go
around a shirt like this he like points it and goes what band is that it's never
a band it'd be cool if you were walking in with like Nirvana sure yeah what band
- What band?
- Hmm, what band is that?
- Yeah.
- That is a funny question to ask too,
'cause it usually just, a band shirt is one
that says the band's name.
- Right.
- Like I don't know what answer you'd expect
when you ask someone what band is that.
- Right.
- Yeah.
- You should ask what band is that to his leather vest.
- I'm gonna start asking people what band it is
when they're wearing tuxedos and dresses.
- When a bouncer dresses up like that, it's always so sick.
- Bouncers are almost exclusively crazy people.
- Yeah.
Yeah, it's cool. Yeah, dude. They dread like the the one I told you about the guy
that dresses up like Mad Max.
A friend of mine used to be a bouncer and he would and kids would try to get him
with like fake IDs and he'd be like listen, if you give me $50, I'll let you
in and then you have $50 like and he would just keep their ID and the money
and not let him.
And be like, what are you gonna go tell the cops that I mean a bouncer is like
the perfect that's like a you can you can have power over people and it's
- Exactly on the axis between being a serial killer
or like a local politician.
- Exactly.
- It's just like Dexter.
- You don't have to work at all
and you also don't have to go to jail.
- Yeah.
- It's like--
- You pretty much have immunity in every fight.
- Yeah.
- It's pretty cool.
- Even if you lose, you still win.
- Mm-hmm.
- It is fun.
You ever met anybody who like is not that big
and they'll tell you like, oh yeah, when I was a bouncer.
- Yeah.
- How?
How can you be a bouncer if you're not like 400 pounds
and huge?
guy at that bar short yeah I mean he's wide as hell oh dude he's big yeah but
he's little mm-hmm you know well he can just I mean he can just clothesline
someone with his body like you can like kind of run into their lower body yeah
dude he's a right over yeah that's true yeah but you ever seen Roadhouse I've
been to Texas Roadhouse the movie Roadhouse on the ground I went on I drove
on the road and went to my house Roadhouse is Patrick Swayze it's a movie
about it the if you've never seen it it's a movie about a like the most famous
bouncer in the world. Everyone's like oh shit look at that that's Dalton and it's
like yeah man he's got like a reputation he's like the best bouncer ever he once
kicked out he he wants kill the guy with one punch. It's just like this movie is
like he it's just Patrick Swayze being like uh and you're and you're gonna be
nice to everybody. Dude, job movies? Yeah. Job movies are the best genre of movie.
Dude, that movie starts out with him just being a
bouncer and it ends in a fucking like gunfight with like explosions and shit.
It's so good. What's another job? Color of money? Oh yeah. Job movie. Employee of the
month? Job movie. Mm-hmm. Job movies are... Waiting? Star Wars?
first job Jedi yeah kind of job stop it if you know what you're doing you're
trying to be make a joke no way it's a job this isn't funny okay sorry sorry
it's not cool sorry what's a good job movie though no that's no I didn't say I
didn't finish saying it fellowship of what you better say pizza delivery men
fellowship of the hospital I seen that yeah it is a good movie it's a good job
but it's a reason that
and his brother nick
brother nick to terrorism came in the matrix is probably a bit of a job
movie what the fuck
i hate you notice i can say star wars you can see the matrix there's not none of
them was that's out in the job
now for the news he's in a job because the job on camera and
it's not a job you know programmers not a job
and a program is a literally looking at animated gifts all day that your boss
sends you yes in in slack yeah your boss that your boss likes you to be like look
at this lol cat I just saw it's a job movie right there pop patrol
patrol they all have different jobs yeah well as a job is patrol okay so what's
they work together there's a cop dog yes fire fire fighter dog two girls it will
there's more dogs to this to jetpack girl see what what is the human like the
analogous human job what's the dogs name jetpack dog astronaut girl astronaut it
does an astronaut flight a time now yeah, yeah, yeah, girl in the
stewardess and that was a model a model. Yeah, a lot of model. Yeah,
what's the dog's name? Chase Chase. It's chase and a Marshall
chase and Marshall. Those are the two boy dogs. I don't know the girl dog
and that's vagina and boobs.
That's their names. Yeah, yeah, that's beauty and prudence.
I think we should we should we need to make a kids show. Yeah, yeah, that's good.
What's um, what are the lizard podcasters for lizards? Okay. Yeah, we could call it for lizards.
The four lizards who live in the sewer and it could be a job show. A job show is good to
a kid's movie about jobs job job and their ice cream men. Job shows are good though.
Like what they made a movie about a snow day. Can you believe this shit? Say
Spongebob like Fellowship of the Hospital the series it came after the movie
yeah you know you know they got to make money somehow it's when Tom Kenny
guest-voiced squirrelly on that one episode of the Fellowship of the
Hospital mm-hmm yeah when Nick Totoro hits his head here's your
tutorials in the series but his brother John is in the movie but he has a cameo
in the movie so it's kind of weird when you see the show and the main character
He's usually played by John Turturro, played by his own brother Nick Turturro.
You're about to have a Kablameo.
A Kablameo?
Remember Kablam the show?
I'm about to Kablam your flow.
Kablam the show on Nickelode.
Mm-mm, never seen it.
Nickelode.
It's pretty good.
Oh, I wish, nowadays I wish Laundry was a Nickelode.
Yep.
Is that a 2 damn 25?
Do they charge 2.25 here?
Charge 225 at the laundromat by my house. What the hell is going on with this country the Washington. Thanks, Brandon
Yeah, thanks. Oh, yeah, Brandon. Yeah fucked. Yeah, let's go Brandon. Yeah
Go Brandon. How about you go to fucking hell?
Don't even say he's a president. Yeah. Yeah. No. Say yeah, do you think I'm afraid you should be you think I'm afraid of him?
You're gonna get drones truck. You think I'm afraid of Joe Biden
Who's that he's gonna use your brand run his brand drones on you? Yeah, and you know who doesn't care me because I'll die a martyr
You're gonna die a farter no matter what happens in your damn. Oh my god. Oh my god
Nice hey you were giving me cover so that I could fart and then blame it on whatever the smell happens here all
That's right. You know what you know what like a martyr
That's a really good boy. Yeah, that's a very good. I saved your life
You did like gave your life your only begotten life for me. Yep. You're so begotten. I hate my begotten son
Yeah, my damn begotten
He's the only one I got but he
He really got I don't like I don't like when he's prodigal either. Yeah. Oh my damn prodigal son. Yeah, was that even mean?
Mm-hmm. He's so damn prodigal. I hate him. I hate him normally which would no matter what adjective you put in front of his
son only
Yeah, big gotten
Charming gay gay son
It's just I just don't like it's the Sun. Yes the Sun part. I don't like
I'm kicking out of my house
I just hate having a son. It's fucking annoying.
Yeah, I just don't like my son.
Would you guys rather have...
Never mind.
[Laughter]
Would you rather have...
I feel like we've done like every permutation of that.
Yeah.
Would you rather have a gay son or a bad hair day?
Um...
Probably a gay son.
Yeah.
I just want a gay son so bad, dude.
A little gay son.
Oh my god, we could hang out and talk about movies.
Just kiss him on the mouth.
[Laughter]
make out my God. He would style my outfits every day.
I just start dressing like he's like he's like eight years old, so he's
dressed to be up in like PJ Masks.
He's like super stylish. I think he's
yeah,
three ties yeah, he's making with a backpack from Dora.
I've show up at work in a sleeping bag. Oh, you notice my outfit yeah. My gay
did this he's pretty much a style expert he's gonna go to the fashion design
school of New York City we're pretty much already planning it mm-hmm my
extremely stylish gay son he redid our kitchen it's all plastic now yeah he did
my makeup too look it's just like sharpie on my face
yeah it's just like lipstick up to your nose and chin
yeah you're walking through the- and sharpie on eyebrows and devil horns on your head
you're walking through the kitchen that he remodeled and it's like okay oh now
Now these now these drawers here at knee level. These are the candy drawers and
then up here in these cabinets up here. Those are vegetables. This is my
metro sexual son.
He remodeled the entire house. He put up all this amazing artwork. Can you see a
bunch of hand turkeys? We think he's a gay artist.
He's like Keith Haring basically. Yeah, he's just hoping he does not get that
though. He's pretty much a gay artist from the day he was born. I mean look at
this amazing art. Look at this here. Yeah. That's called Squidward. Mm-hmm. And he drew that.
This one, yeah, this one is called Blue and there's a lot of squiggles.
And this one is Blue Squidward. It's drawing after drawing of like, like, stick figure
your son, like, like stabbing your cat to death, like ripping the cat's head off.
We think he's kind of an artist, kind of gay artist type. As you can tell, he's
very interesting the way that he is. He seems to be also very into our cat.
Yeah, see and this this piece right here really speaks to me. It's called dad's private parts. Mm-hmm dad's private parts
That's private. Yeah, that's private parts. I saw it by accident when I opened the door in the shower. Mm-hmm
It's very kind of one of those really long titles that you see. Yeah, we actually he's actually remodeled our shower, too
It's actually it's it's 10 feet long and it's 10 feet wide and there's a hundred rubber ducks in
And it's filled with bubbles. Yeah, he remodeled the living. Yeah. Oh my god
but my we can tell he's gay. He loves bubble baths.
He always wants those he wants those pink bubbles yeah yeah my son he's two
weeks old he's pretty much as gay as can be because he loves his mama. Tell you
what yeah, I think my son's straight man. He'd be sucking on fucking tits all
day. Yeah, I guess straight son. Thank you. My son is watch this get me a beer
that's right. He doesn't even listen to me. He can't hear a damn thing this kid
you know, son's death.
This kid's so straight, he can't hear a damn thing. I say
that's right.
And then and then like the person who's like who's over to his house that he's
talking to about his son. This is like this says something to son. His son is
instantly response.
Yeah, that's my straight son. Not listening to a damn thing. I saw my God
if if I was smart enough to pretend I was deaf from the second. I was born.
that'll be the greatest prank of all time. Best prank ever, dude. Yeah, he
pretended he was dead. Stevie Wonder waited to start pretending that he was
dead until yesterday. Right before- you wait until, you wait until, like, your
parents are on- your last parent is on their death bed, and you say, "What's up,
bitch?" Bye, bitch! And they're like, "What?" But you haven't yet, but you
also- you've never spoken before, so you actually go, "Duh, duh, duh!" No, you
You'd sit and practice in your in your cause. I wouldn't
you and I got to keep up the illusion.
A doctor if if you went to the doctor, the doctor would see your mouth and be
like that a mouth has talked before
you know, be annoying is not you know, be annoying as hell. I used to have
this like nightmare when I was a kid that both of my parents had no arms and
I said it do everything for them. That would suck that would suck if you if
your parents had no arms. Yeah, you're like a you're like an arm like they just
like you for your arms at some point. It's true. You know you're basically like
a spoon to them that would put a new wrinkle in a parent child relationship.
I know you just love me because I have arms also like if I do something wrong,
I dare you to do anything about it. Well, it's worse because they'll kick
you. It hurts more if they can catch me. Well, they have no oh, that's good. I
still I thought they had no legs. You know what okay, both your parents are
their heads. What if they have really sharp teeth? They can bite you if you misbehave.
Yeah, that would be a problem. Yeah. Okay, I'm not going to admit that. Yeah. Yeah. What
if they had fins and gills? And they were gray white. Yeah. They're gray and white.
Yeah. I'll say it, my parents are gray and white. Two gray white parents. My parents
are hammer and head. Nope, they do not. They don't have gills. No, they're not sharp. Let's
hit the checklist here. If you were pretending to be deaf too to prank your parents, you'd
have to figure something out like if they try to catch you by like startling you
or something like I probably like if they try and figure out if you you know
because you'd you'd kind of tell you see a twinkle if I if my kid was deaf and I
saw twinkle in his eye I'd be I'd be clapping behind his head there would be
some point where I would be like maybe he's fake like that way yeah through the
kids entire life that would come across my mind one time yeah what I would do is
my parents would come up behind me and scream boo to try and catch me faking
being deaf and I jump and they'd be like I got you and I'd write down no like
like I'm an empath, I could feel the fear in the room.
- I felt the vibration behind me.
- Yeah, or maybe I pretend to be Daredevil.
(laughing)
- I saw like a blue version of the world.
- No, I have super powers.
- This is my super power.
- Yeah, my super power is jumping when I'm startled.
- That's the thing, Daredevil--
- All my other senses are--
- Daredevil doesn't work if he's deaf but can see.
- Yeah.
- Right?
- Just less interesting.
- Well, you don't get like really good at seeing
you're deaf right you do do you yeah you get you can see the speech bubbles in
the air that's what I don't think that'd be as helpful for a superhero that'd be
rude no because you could see like say somebody was sneaking up behind you and
saying we're gonna sneak up behind him you could see the shadow of the speech
bubble on the ground that's the thing about room daredevil is he's got sonar
he does I think you're thinking of a submarine no I'm thinking of a man now
thing you have a submarine no that's a more what the submarine the submariner
you guys know so much superhero bullshit you're you know you guys should try to
learn a little bit about rap and hip-hop they should put name more in a movie why
haven't they done put their God as you put a black man through a seam or he's
in Black Panther - yeah we talked about name more on the on the pod one time and
then the next day fucking damn a more it was crazy that they have a lady to be in
Black Panther - they should put see we're gonna try to kill all the black people
Yes, because he's a bad guy on it. That's kind of that's kind of not fair this
there's a Marvel character that everyone loves and everyone's waiting for him.
Well he's sometimes bad. Everyone's waiting for him to be in a movie and then he's gonna be the
villain in Black Panther. Who is this guy? Namor? He's gonna try to destroy Wakanda. What the hell?
Yeah he's like Marvel's Aquaman. Yeah he's a ripoff of Aquaman. I think he came before Aquaman.
It's the same he's a ripoff of Aquaman. And he's a racist. They're apparently making him racist.
that's that's really funny. They're like yeah, like we're excited and we're
finally bringing spider man into the mcu and he won't be trying to destroy what
that just doesn't seem fair, because he's not like a he's like a bad guy.
Half the time, they shouldn't make him the like the race war.
You guys, we finally secured the rights to the incredible hulk, but we had to
I'm a pedophile. We're sorry. We're sorry. Yes, he turns green when he sees he
turns green and big when he sees a kid. It's to destroy the version of Wakanda
that's all kid the kid city. It's in the middle of Disneyland. It's where all
the small world kids come from. I'm gonna I'm going to I'm gonna fucking me.
I'm going to fly over to Wakanda like the guys volunteering for Ukraine.
I'm going to save Wakanda.
I'm going to go over there and they're going to use me like a cannonball.
Well, I breathe Wakanda will not fall.
That's right.
Wakanda forever.
Yep.
I'm going to go over there.
I will not let this fucking fish freak destroy the blackest city in the world.
I'm going to go protect it.
It is cool that if anyone listening knows the exact coordinates of Wakanda,
please send them in. Cause I have to go there. Yep. I gotta tell,
I gotta figure out what to put in my GPS cause I'm on the way and yeah,
I'm bringing in fucking snacks from America and they're going to lose their
minds. We're going to trade, you know, I do. Can you imagine what like,
you know,
scientists try try American snacks for the first time. Yeah,
that's going to go over there.
I'm going to go over there with sour cream and onion chips.
I gave you the Mexican ruffles. Can you imagine what the Wakanda ruffles taste
like? Oh my God, I bet they're crazy. They're probably so good. They probably
and I bet they have that I bet. Can you imagine how many warnings are on it
because they're like mega healthy with the amount of people, the amount of
with the amount of technology in that city? I'd think they'd they care less
about potato chips and more about computer chips. Exactly I'd say yeah,
there's there's heaven, there's chips, you know and they'd say what micro
chips yeah, we already have enough of these. I mean like microchips that's
barely enough to eat. I prefer mega chips
microchips.
Like Pringles.
Microchips.
Or Tostitos.
Microchips, you mean like what, like a grip?
Like those little things?
Like the Ritz cheese sandwich crackers?
No, we're doing big old chips.
We're doing the biggest chip you have.
Yeah, how about kettle cooked?
Wavy kettle cooked.
I mean, they have the biggest potatoes in Wakanda.
And then they would kill me with spears, with cyber spears.
I hate it, getting killed with a cyber spear.
Me too.
It's annoying.
that we talked about him on the show and then something happened the next day
with him we should start doing wishes are predicting more yeah well let's make
one big prediction and this episode okay anybody have any ideas um we all go to
the zoo Homer Simpson will die on tomorrow's episode
Dan Castaneda Nella just gonna pass away soon yep who's that voice of Homer
Homer, whose voice of Homer voice of Homer voice of Homer. I'm gonna say
Google Google's gonna shut down. No yep Google's gonna shut down yeah. I find a
bag of money.
I'm gonna find a pot of gold yeah. I'm gonna find the end of a rainbow and
they're gonna take me and because of my heritage, they're gonna take me back to
the homeland and you're gonna become a sex slave. No, I'm gonna become the saint
you live you listener will not become rich.
Yeah, sorry, you won't become rich unless I buy tickets to Cameron will become
rich from the tour the tour which you can buy tickets at swag poop.com slash
shows. We added a second show in LA. That's all ages because the first one
sold out. We added a show in San Francisco. There's a bunch of other
cities. I don't even know where they are. We were going to go to arts and
of the US low ticket warning and Chicago and DC DC
low ticket warning there will be poison at the show as best as warning there's
going to be as best as in every single venue at the Fort Worth show we're George
straight is gonna be there George Jones actually who George Jones is gonna be at
the Ted show country singer Michael Jordan's gonna be there too yeah and
Michael B and in the Austin show Austin Austin himself will be there's gonna be
there yeah all right