[Music]
Love. What is love?
You sound like the book from It Takes Two.
[Music]
A chemical reaction? No, too simple.
Is it total selflessness in the face of all adversity? No, too high-minded.
Is it attacking someone with a hammer? No.
How about with a wrench? No, that is ratchet and clank.
No, love is everything.
Big and small, small and large, large and in charge, and charge ahead we shall, into the
throes of passion, into the story of one beautiful Italian woman named Pagina.
Pagina you see is without love on this Valentine's Day, after her heart was torn in two by her
sweet man
kyle crime rate
she dramatically
and suddenly moved her entire life
to see if she could find love somewhere else somewhere new
somewhere romantic
somewhere grand
full of lust and fire
fire of the heart
Worcester, Massachusetts
according to their website
it is the country's most vibrant in livable mid-sized city
that's what it says
is it livable?
that shit describes Worcester
yeah, it's appropriate levels of oxygen
Worcester, Massachusetts
there are roads in Worcester
running water
now on this valentine's day
Pacino will look for love, high and low, far and wide
And by nightfall she will have found her special lovey.
She sits now at the Worcester Korean War Memorial.
Quietly reading Captain Underpants and the perilous plot of Professor Poopypants.
Dressed exactly like Cameron Diaz in The Mask.
She looks like Penelope Cruz mixed with Sidney Sweeney.
Mixed with that one scene in Blue is the Warmest Color.
You know the one.
Ah, what man would chance to find love on this very day?
Maybe there are three such lotharios?
And who could they be?
I didn't write an intro or anything. You can just say who you are. Okay, my name is Lothario
Dawson and Dawson and I'm a billionaire. I have billions of dollars. I have a mansion.
I have planes and trains and automobiles, Valentines. So yeah, Pacino's just sitting
in a park. And I'm a BDSM guy. So the rest of you can just wander in whenever you want.
But she's just like reading Captain Underpants. That's what I'm doing right now. I'm just like, oh
This book is so complicated
There's so many words and pictures
And she's just looking very beautiful
You know what? They say patchy now. I guess I don't know her name, huh?
I don't know. It just came to me. Ooh
This is a can pictures
A picture is worth a thousand words, my love, but I am worth ten billion dollars.
Oh, that's a lot of money, and there's another man here too?
Pleased to see ya.
The name's Dookie Disgusting.
My whore mother named me that thinking it put a damper on my no-good-paws jeans.
He spunked in her spittoon and skipped on by sunrise, leaving her with nothing but a full
fanny and a very sexual child. Last I heard of him, he got flattened.
That's Thomas. You're doing Thomas. Hey guys, it's me. Hey, it's me, Dookie Disgustin.
Last I heard of my father, he got flattened by the bang bus like Wile E. Coyote, but I'm
carrying on his legacy. I've pushed poon from Oklahoma to the Orient. I've smelled sliz
at Camp David, I fucked Jackie Chan.
(laughter)
- She sounds beautiful.
- Yep, the Jackie Chan you're thinking of.
Needless to say, women love me.
They let me do whatever I want,
which really works out in my favor
because I'm into poo-poo and pee-pee.
At some point I had to just embrace my name,
go with the flow, and speaking of,
I like going "TT" on women's shorts.
Make myself understood.
Wow, okay.
Nice to meet you.
I think you said your name was Pachonis.
Very very nice to meet you.
It is lovely to meet you too.
What you say, Dookie?
Dookie.
Dookie Disgusting.
Oh wow.
These two such handsome men in Worcester, Massachusetts, the most romantic city on the
planet.
The city of love, baby.
Yes, that is what they say.
The city of love.
You're a man?
And who is that in the distance?
Oh, fuck you!
Fuck you, bitch!
Oh my, what a new approach!
You're a bitch, I... Fuck you!
I'm Pikachu.
That is my full name.
First name is Pika, last name is Chuu.
Oh, so mysterious!
I am here for sex and loving
So forward
Sexual loving for Pikachu
Who is me?
Pikachu
I'm here to see boobs and pussy and butt
And I have no money I live outside
I live outside in trash can
I live in trash can
And if you go down in trash can you can go to Pikachu land
Elmo went there once in a movie
But it was called grouch land. It was loosely based off of Pikachu land and all of their people there look like me
white
Is a land of only white people
And they try to throw rocks at us.
But we go back with bombs.
And we throw bombs at the rock throwers.
And that's what we do. My name is Pikachu.
Fuck you, bitch.
Wow, I'm so lucky.
Three handsome, dangerous men.
I'm a danger to my country.
Do any of you know the way around Worcester, Massachusetts?
Yeah, we are going to, bitch, we are going to...
Paul ourselves a factory
All their shelter made here we're going that's where Paula South's our is made you seen what star okay?
If you're gonna try to convince patina to go somewhere. I think that's where we start to bring in the rolling so
Wait, where are we again? We're in the Korean War?
No, we're at the Memorial. Yeah. Yeah, we're on a train. No, I was I was gonna do that. Really?
Yeah, originally and then we're in real life love. Yeah
(laughter)
- Oh my god, things are gonna change after tonight.
- And then I thought the war memorial was a better setting.
- I'm pointing at some names on the memorial.
- Ah, fuck them.
- I'm going like, I'm going like,
you see that guy?
- Yay.
- You see that guy too, Pacina?
- I see.
- You see that guy?
- Okay, yay.
- I owned them.
- And I fucked them.
- You owned them?
- My family owns them.
Wow, is it like you mean like you beat them?
What?
We're both so breathy.
Shut up, bitch.
Shut up, you two bitches.
These Korean names are crazy, man.
Craig Johnson, what kind of Korean bullshit is that?
If I have to be honest with you all, I am looking for love today.
Shut up, bitches.
Yeah, roll loveliness.
Wait, you have 10 loveliness?
Yeah, you can't be pulling this shit with 10 loveliness.
You are not playing in character.
Yeah, wait, should we run through the stats?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, you got three. All right. So she kind of took offense to that, but well, let's go into this.
Yeah, oh yeah, I made up a vague system for this just for funsies.
And we have loveliness, coolness, sexiness, and indomitability.
Pete: [Laughter]
And -
Jared: Which means you can't be subdued or defeated according to the dictionary.
Pete: Yeah, right. And so, loveliness is sort of like your verbal charm, coolness is sort of your -
Pete: Well, that's why I put loveliness as a ten.
Jared: Yeah, because you were going to be Israeli.
[Laughter]
Pete: I'm going to be Israeli mean.
Yeah, coolness is sort of your moves, you know, sort of doing a cool thing with your body,
sort of like holding the door open for someone.
Sexiness is sort of your ability to kiss and like mack.
And then indomitability is, what did you say it was, Cam?
An ability to be subdued or defeated.
Yeah, so we'll see if that comes into play.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
So yeah, with the three, I would say, um, yeah, I mean she's not too keen on going there, you
know, she's gonna, she's gonna, kind of like, "I don't know if that's a, the most romantic
place to go."
"You are stupid!"
"Listen, Pachina, Pachina, listen to me, come over here.
I know the most romantic place we can go.
Pachina, listen, how about you and me, and we leave these other two clowns behind and
we-" "No, we are going with you."
Will you listen? Will you guys let me talk to her for a second?
I'm going to kill you.
Actually, no, I don't think I will.
What about you and me? We go back to my mansion and I whip you with spiked chains.
And I go there too.
Oh, the real loveliness.
Loveliness? What's my loveliness? D4?
Yeah, you could do other moves.
Two.
Yeah, she's like...
No.
Listen, we'll decide on a safe word and then we'll throw you into the Iron Maiden, Pechina.
It's gonna be a sexy, beautiful morning.
I just think you're moving too fast for me.
I'm from a small village in Italy.
We can move slow too.
Oh, listen Pechina, come to my mansion.
We'll take the elevator down to the negative 100th floor and I'll throw you on the rack
and we'll turn that crank so slowly.
- We'll turn that crank so slowly, Pacino.
- I don't know about this.
- One notch a day and you're in there for a thousand years.
(laughing)
- I do like things that make you feel like
time just stands still.
- Oh yeah, I love that too.
- You do, okay.
What about you, Dookie?
- I've been trying to invent a time machine.
What if I just gave you some money?
- Oh, how much?
- Like, probably like $125.
$126 for me.
Well, I can't go. Can't argue with that.
[laughter]
I only have $125, homie.
I have no money, but I am full of love.
We could go to an ATM, but I'm gonna be honest, there's nothing in my bank account.
I live at the ATM!
I'd just be sitting there pretending, and I'd tell you it is broken.
Suppose we could go to the ATM and see who has the most money?
I live by--
That sounds good to me.
I live in the ATM.
[laughter]
So all of a sudden, you're a whore.
Oh, how dare you? I'm not a whore, I'm just Italian.
Oh, when you're in my mansion you will be.
Oh, that's...
What's that mean?
I'm just... it's... I'll command her.
No, what that whore mean?
It's like a sexy beautiful lady who fulfills your love lust.
It's the most beautiful woman in the world.
What that beautiful mean?
I couldn't tell you.
It's a woman who makes you wanna fuck.
what is? you say this word all the time the one you're about to say. no what is woman?
okay just check it. that's a woman. hello. what is different? what? she's got different
underwear on than us. panties. I wear those. you wear panties? let me see. I am Pikachu.
Of course I will, Panties.
How about instead we just go to the Maui beach nearby?
There is a beach in Worcester, Massachusetts that I hear is the most beautiful beach in the world.
Do you want to go there?
Listen, bitch.
Anywhere else besides the Korean War Memorial?
Listen, Pachina, Pachina, Pachina, listen to me.
Listen to me, Pachina.
Where is this beach?
If it's sand you want, Pachina, then come to my mansion and we'll put you in a giant hourglass
and you'll drown in sand slowly.
I guess we-
Where is this beach?
I want to see this beach.
We could go to the beach.
Yeah, where is the beach?
It's just-
There's another one of you.
Or we can go to the mansion, I suppose.
i guess we're gonna do that. I just don't want to go alone. You want me to go to a man's chin? I don't think so.
I wanna be completely honest with you
I do wanna see his house. It seems pretty cool, they got a lot of choice. You're not allowed.
I'm coming to your house. My torturing murder machines are on. I'm hopping into my Lincoln. I have been to your house already.
I'm hopping into my Lincoln, it's got ample carplay in it. Lothario, please can we bring the other man? I just don't want to be alone right now.
I've been there alone most of my life you idiot.
Listen, baby, we go to my mansion, we'll never be alone.
I have 70,000 goblin slaves.
There are goblin slaves in these now.
I thought this took place in the real world.
Oh, it does.
There's nothing realer than a goblin slave turning a crank on a rope that pulls off your
fingernail, my friend.
I'm afraid you'll never experience it.
Sexual effing fingernail pulling.
Oh, tons of sexual fingernail pulling.
I would like to go through the mansion.
Do you have a flat screen TV?
Yes.
You have Tycho LC.
I have a thousand flat screen TVs in the same room on the same wall.
Some is useless, but I'll come.
No, they all show one of every TV show.
Holy God almighty, there's a thousand.
Do you have Tycho LC?
What?
Tycho LC.
- What?
- I'll see cows. - You want the little,
the little rat in the car?
- Yes, the little rat drives the car.
- Lots of rats, lots of rats in the dungeon.
- No, but the car, you get to drive the radio shack.
- Hey, you guys wanna go to Lothario's mansion?
I think we should go to Lothario's mansion.
- I wanna go so bad.
- Yeah, let's go.
- Okay, we can fly on my private jet,
but you two have to be in the luggage.
- That's fine by me.
- Is the radio shack near your house?
- No.
- I miss radio shack. - It's on an island
underground in the center of the worst place for a mansion ever burn up.
You don't understand. He doesn't understand the air face. Hello. He doesn't understand.
Like I would have my bathing suit. You don't have to wear anything.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
People are turning their heads. This is everybody. Everybody who's walking by
sees his giant. There are 400 people. I mean, I'm a homeless guy. I'm like,
I think people are just used to it. Yeah. You blend in so well.
Yeah. How, how big is your pee pee? Yeah. What does everyone working with
here? What's the equipment? Yeah. Let's roll out of four.
that's a d_c_ doesn't explore the redoing exploring for this will be explored
area
all shit i have four or all the other only i got a two hundred
uh...
unique useful before again and i was a little shit
all right i'd like it
with a three it's all to the close to you yet to okay
and i will return to the police before you know i don't know i did i swear i
I saw you, dude. I thought mine was exploding.
No, it's eight inches, dude. I don't give a fuck.
It's only exploding when you get a crit.
Right now, mine is one foot long.
Yeah, so...
I'll do it in the middle.
I would say average four again.
[laughter]
Mine is two, but can I say it's a Bowser spike?
You're medically in trouble.
Keep going, keep going.
Come on, four baby.
Four!
What the fuck?
How many fours is that?
It's two feet long.
It's 24 inches.
No way!
What the fuck is going on?
I'm getting pretty nervous.
Alright, 30 inch penis.
Okay, alright.
At least it stops somewhere reasonable.
If you get aroused, you will pass out.
Yeah, no, this is too much.
30 inch penis.
Just like Thomas.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Can we just say I have one leg and the other...
I have a two inch penis.
Yeah, you have a two inch penis.
Me too, it's cool.
But like I said, mine's a spike.
His is a spike and hers is a...
No, mine is two inches wide.
It's only like one inch.
One inch big.
Yeah, you have a memory card in her penis.
My cock is huge.
I'm not going to play games here.
I have the biggest fucking penis in the world.
penis I'm not gonna it's huge I'm not gonna play games here I have the biggest
fucking insane joke of a cock yeah yeah it's common it's like a mayonnaise come
yeah my character is only 5 4 2 so you could literally fit like a quarter in my
urethra oh yeah yeah yeah and we will try later my guy my guy is is 6 7 he's
he's wearing a white tuxedo and he has chain mail. Yeah, I'm a homeless guy.
I'm a five foot four hobo. So we're going to Lothario Dawson's mansion, right? I
guess so. Yeah, if we have to. I think we should. We have to take a special plane
that can go underground. It's called a ground plane. We're in the plane. It's
called a boat, buddy. Where's the plane actually? Where is it? Is it here? Is it
by the memorial? We have to take a ten thousand dollar Uber to go
5,000 miles okay to get to the ground
The ground port is it still okay cool. It's a Worcester ground port though sure yeah, but the uber cost $10,000
I cannot afford these don't worry, baby
You'll be able to afford this after I
what after I
Am not splitting this with you, but I will ride on the top of the car like me dog
I'll be splitting you later with a battle axe
I'll be splitting y'all cheeks for you. Is that sexual - yes
He likes if these guys are all gonna come to the mansion. I'm gonna have to enjoy it
Yeah, I see his homeless be bail for money
Is what he does I stub his toe?
He likes that you idiot he likes it now
Toothpaste jet out of my pants
Instantly see he spilled his drink. Well, I spilled my seeds. He's drinking seed
Well, did you get this seed?
but but Chino looks at her perfectly like girlish watch and
She says oh no, I'm late
I'm supposed to go to
cafe la Bella I
Was hardly going there. Do you guys want to go there with me? I go there. I put my hand in the tip jar every week
*laughter*
*whispers* sorry
They spray me with their water beltel
*laughter*
I put my hand in the- I pretend like I'm ordering
I put my hand in the gift jar
and they spray me with their water beltel
Oh my god, like a degenerate
Israeli guy
It's so fucking cool
I like the idea that you're just an American homeless guy
Just saw like Pepe Le Pew
you. I thought that guy looked like he was Israeli.
That guy keeps forcing himself on that woman, he's probably Israeli.
I saw pink panthel. I had that few dem bagels
it changed me.
So you guys walk into Cafe La Bella with her and
she's late for an appointment to sit there and also look beautiful.
They're yelling at me as soon as I walk in. Hey, hey buddy, what are you doing
What are you doing in the air?
I got talking how do you somebody help me with here with the Boston accent?
Just do it back the car drop the ass right? Yeah. Hey, what are you doing here? Hey, this is my place - what are you doing in?
Yeah, I'm the only office is not your place. Yeah, you come here and you fuck everything. I am the Odell
Australian became Australian fuck no, what's there is like an Indian accent is it? Oh
Man, it's like a perfect. Oh, I was about to do you guys are arguing about whose place it is
Gentlemen gentlemen, this is my place and I hold up a check that's for five million trillion dollars
And it's signed in women's blood
And that is my check our world when I first bought this place
Look look buddy. I don't know how I'm supposed to cash that
Cash app do you have bank you idiots?
You can cash out checks on your phone. You're lucky you don't work in one of my factories or we make you a doll
He owns a rotary phone. He knows nothing of
cashing checks on his phone
Why would you say he knows nothing about he's so rich. He has no cell phone. He only has rotary phone
He has a slave
Because I have a goblin slave who I talk into and he runs and talks into the other person
That's what I said. Well, that's his name
Do you have like an alarm clock goblin?
Yeah.
It's cool.
He lives a Flintstone life with goblins.
I have, it's a goblin slave who swallowed an alarm clock.
And it's like stuck in his throat.
I have a different one for every possible time.
And I just ask whichever one I need to wake up at to be in my room that night.
Do you have a chorus of goblins?
What?
Chorus of goblins.
A what?
else singers yes they seem complicated by Avril Lavigne they scream they scream
complicated by Avril Lavigne I have goblin slaves that run around in a giant
piano like that Tom and Jerry episode
do you like Tom and Jerry Pachina Pachina do you love Avril Lavigne complicated
I like both of these things!
If you'll come home with me, you'll be the Tom to my Jerry.
I'll drink a magic potion and I'll chase you around.
Why do you have to drink a potion?
I'm gonna hit you with an anvil, Pacino.
Oh no!
Oh, you'll love it. I command you to love it.
I have a song for you, Pacino.
Okay.
Why do you have to go and make things so complicated?
That's the only line I know.
I guess I get the cappuccino and the guy goes back and goes to get a cappuccino for her
And she goes to the to you do key shows. Look. I have not heard from you and you seem to be
Well equipped
What do you mean
Well, I cannot have but notice that you have a third leg
Now are you fucking stupid?
Are you actually fucking stupid I just put like three spin drifts in my pockets
No, I mean a
big pin pin your seal
I'm pretty famous back in Louisiana for my big Pinocchio.
What do they call it?
Pinocchio.
What do they call you?
They call me Dookie Disgusting.
Okay, but does it sound like a nickname?
My name ring bells for real, for real.
I just, you know, my old lover, Kyle Crimewright.
You know, he was so mean to me.
He was very rude, he would tell me, "Pachina, why do you not work?"
Can I make a, I want to make a roll here.
I want to send a text to one of my goblin slaves and I want to very quickly hold up a live video
feed of Kyle Krimerate being drawn in court to try and charm her.
Oh man, I guess that's coolness, right?
I think so, I don't know.
Yeah, I made these stats.
That's coolness.
Okay.
Let's see here.
Three.
Okay, you get a Kyle Krimerate lookalike who is...
Can I get...
Okay, if I'm gonna...
If I'm gonna fail...
A guy with a wig.
And a t-shirt that says Kyle Krimerate.
If I'm gonna fail and if it has to be a lookalike, I want 100 lookalikes.
You sacrifice 100 goblins that are like dressed as Kyle Crime Raid.
What is Kyle Crime Raid dresses?
That's up to you.
It's your interpretation of Mr. Crime Raid.
I think he probably is pretty swaggy.
He's insanely cool.
Dan, you think he's got the Thing 2 shirt on and shit?
Yeah.
Damn.
he has a custom shirt made that's thing two on the front and I'm with stupid on
the back. Whoa. Pointing at thing one or thing three. He was so hilarious. And he has
he has a flat brim. That's a funny ass shirt. I'll say that much. So funny. I love his flat brim that has a
brim on the front and back so he looks like Sherlock Holmes. And there's two hats
on the front. He was always trying to solve mysteries. And there's hats filling out the corners too.
He's got a flat brim sombrero on.
I'm in the bathroom of this restaurant and I'm just showering in the sink while all this
is happening right now.
Where did Pikachu go?
When she turns around I see the back of her neck and I get such a big erection I just
pass out.
And she turns around and goes, "Dookie!
Somebody has to save Dookie!"
No, don't worry about that.
Oh, that's why I'm not sleepy, ow.
be out here in the bathroom I'm in the bathroom with that door open and I'm
washing my penis and I'm standing on this ink and somebody needs to save dookie
I'm standing on his neck you could try a roll coolness to say dookie also you
take HP you take like damage if you got a seven my huge dick what there's seven
seven and oh wow pretty good yeah you uh how do you save you save dookie how do
you say? Well it's CPR but I didn't say what CPR meant. You gotta be, what does it
mean to you? Clogged penis removal. No you don't get to remove my penis. No I get to
remove the clog in your penis. Okay. So it's like you're lying on the
ground right? But your whole penis is... Describe this to me. Okay so his... My penis is
shooting right up. It broke through my zipper. Yes. It's up? It's up. It's
ready to like see if it's tall enough to get on a roller coaster. I take my bandana off and I tie it around my
legs and I climb it like a person climbing like a tree to get a coconut.
How short are you? I'm like 5'4". This is way shorter than 5'4". You're still 3 feet tall.
Yeah I'm still doing that. Okay just making sure. I'll climb it but it's only like I only take two
steps till I find the clog. Not even one step and then I see the clog in it and I
can just upper cut it and there's just like a kidney
size of a
burrito. Yeah,
Chipotle burrito size kidney stone shoots out of your re through
all right. Wow yeah, she and I come to
at you when I see him punch your penis. I also come
yeah, yeah, Pikachu. We all just come
There's a huge load right behind the kidney stone that he unclogged. This cafe is just like horrified
Everybody of the four of us walk in there. We're just nutting
30 foot 30 inch
Yeah, it's like an emptying a can of silly string. Yeah out of my huge car all over the place
Yeah, but she is pretty impressed Pikachu. She's like wow
Where did you learn that my father I tap into him?
Which is how he died
So it's like you're saving your father
Way if your father died that means you're probably not too good at dislodging big rocks from men's cocks
That was the first time he worked
There's the first and only time he's ever worked also I wasn't like gonna die
All the blood went to my penis, but I was so worried about I would have been fine you stupid bitch
I wish you'd believe me.
You don't call her stupid bitch, that was my nickname for her.
I'm sorry.
Wow, you're both fighting.
Well, thank you for making it.
Listen, listen, Pacina, don't pay any attention to these two idiots.
Listen, what we're gonna do...
What's your name?
What we're gonna do, Pacina, we're gonna go to the beautiful, the beautiful, we're gonna
go to the beautiful Worcester countryside, Pacina.
You're doing army now, huh?
And we're gonna, listen, Pachina, we're gonna go--
- I brought the Skip-It with me, I'm doing Skip-It.
I'm doing a Skip-It in the restaurant, I'm doing Skip-It.
- We're gonna go on a beautiful horseback ride, Pachina.
You're gonna be riding on one horse
and I'll be following close behind,
and then we'll gallop to two opposite points
and then we'll gallop towards each other very fast
and I'll run you through with a lance, Pachina.
- Oh, you're going to kill me.
- And it'll be so romantic.
And I'll command you, no.
- I did 100 skips on my Skip-It.
- I did 100 skips on my Skip It in that time.
- I can do eight pushups.
- I'm good at Skip It.
- I can do--
(laughing)
- I hear they teach you that at the IDF.
- They do.
- Show me eight pushups.
- Skip It and so does Dream.
- All right.
- Roll, roll, oh man, let's roll Coolness.
- Yes, it's Coolness.
- It's Coolness, yeah.
- Which one of these is a 10?
- Oh yeah, it's Dookie's Best.
- This one?
- Mm-hmm.
that
got a bad roll. I got a... what's the line under the... oh, it's a six. Nice. He got a
bad roll the first time on the ground. Oh yeah. He didn't want to tell us. No, it fell under the seat. I counted that when I was
fucking... seeing how long my dick was. Patrick's been consistently not counting it. Mm-hmm.
Well, you're... you're stupid, so... I've been watching this. I've been... I've been taking note of that. I was like,
Patrick doesn't count it when it's on the table. Caleb does. All right? I mean, I got this. I would
like to so they just did push-ups I would like to throw by the way middling
perform I would like to lift the cash register over my head to throw
through the wall yeah that's coolness for sure yeah five I mean you do that
yeah there's no doubt that it's happening and that they are trying to get
you out of the cafe at this it's my cafe I bought it did you you just presented a
disgusting check they did hey if they don't accept the check that's on me but
it's already mine. I have 10 million goblin slaves that work overtime writing
contracts. If they think they still own this place they're going to jail. My jail.
And it will be sexual. Maybe we should go somewhere else. I don't think
everybody is liking our love being here. Pizza Hut! Pizza Hut!
- I'm gonna put my empty house in a subdivision
that has a couch and a microwave.
(laughing)
And carpet floors.
- Oh, carpet is so romantic.
- Pizza Hut has a buffet.
- The carpet goes through the kitchen and the bathroom.
Patching other things we can do with a microwave.
How big is your microwave?
- It's about normal, you know, six by seven feet.
- Pizza Hut has a microwave in the back
and it has a buffet.
- Well, how 'bout this?
- How 'bout we go to a hotel?
- I'm gonna roll indomitability and force you to do that.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm basically forcing you to come with me, so.
That's true.
One.
She's not going to be forced to, she's sort of like, "Ah, no."
I try to grab her arm and like pull her, and my arm flies off of my body like Spongebob.
"Oh no, can you give him CPR again?"
I'm coming so much.
I do not know how to create that arm, but I say we go to Habbo Hotel.
We can go to...
We go in Habbo Hotel.
You only he will, he owns the Habbo Hotel.
Let's go to Habbo Hotel.
What is a Habbo Hotel?
It sounds so mysterious.
The airport is always closed.
Okay.
Always...
What?
Always closed?
Hell yeah, dude.
That, people are gonna love that.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
It's a reference show.
Let's go.
Yeah, you guys gotta go to the hotel. Tell me about this hotel.
You've never been on a hotel?
Hey, Pete, we're gonna take you to the most...
We're gonna take you to the most...
[laughter]
We're gonna take you to the most exclusive club in the world, Club Penguin.
We're gonna do the spy training missions over and over.
So, are we gonna go to the hotel and then Club Penguin?
And RuneScape.
I think maybe we go through Club Penguin.
We go to Club Penguin? Okay, yeah.
get us into Club Penguin. I have guest passes.
Oh yeah, it's now um, hold on, membership cards.
So we can't go to Club Penguin because really it's like a night time locale.
Oh true. What time is it right now? No it's a day club.
It's a day club? It's a day club and it's for teenagers.
Which is why Cameron wants to go. All right do we want to go to Club Penguin? I'm trying to
figure out like different locations. Let's go to Club Penguin. I got a fake ID that says 14.
Let's go. Okay. Yeah, we roll up to Club Penguin in Worcester, Massachusetts.
I'm like grabbing, uh, Petchy's hand like we're at like an amusement park or something. I'm like,
"Come on, baby. Let's try and tip the iceberg." Okay. "What do you mean tip the ice-o-bertic?"
"Oh, you'll see the water's frigid and cold. You'll die in 10 seconds."
"Oh, good." Yeah, you guys are at Club Penguin. What's going on in Club Penguin?
I stopped a snowball fight. I'm whipping a puffle. My huge dick is completely blurred out.
I don't know what to do. It's stuck to the ice.
The bouncer at Club Penguin's like, he can't walk because it's like Christmas story. Like,
yeah, yeah, his dick is on the ice. He's trying to walk.
At some point I like, I'm trying to escape from my penis being stuck to the ground. And I,
leave us so much momentum that I start spinning around it over and over again.
Oh he's doing skipette! He's doing skipette!
Copying. He's copying me to court here.
Yeah the bouncer there is like uh uh whoa whoa whoa how old are you guys?
Seven.
Five. Five months.
Yeah.
I'm 30.
No wait wait.
Um.
They'll be 16 too.
I'm four.
Okay, yeah, all of you roll loveliness.
Oh man, fuck.
Do I got four loveliness, bro?
Hey, at least it explodes, yeah.
Ah, crap.
Two.
I got five.
He's like, "You guys are not any of those ages."
Shut up.
You're acting like you're four.
I was born on the LEPL.
Ask me a math question.
Hey, I take him off to the side.
Listen, buddy, I don't want to make a scene, but you keep this up, you're going to be melted
soon.
You're going straight to hell.
You are 6'7".
He's a snowman.
And I'm wearing chain mail.
And I am a snowman.
Hey, do you see this?
I take out a laser pointer.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, buddy!
Put that thing away!
Okay, okay, alright, alright.
Just keep that, anything that is warm, away from me.
Also, there's gonna be like 700 goblins coming through here soon.
You gotta let 'em in, man.
But, they are like three.
So...
Goblin age is different.
But they're all gonna be like, "Oh, I'm a goblin."
I'm a goblin.
gotta let 'em in, man. But they are like three. So...
Goblin age is different.
They're all gonna be wearing big white t-shirts and you still gotta let 'em in.
They'll wear big white t-shirts, they'll have their names on them.
They'll have big white t-shirts and gold chains.
You can't stop 'em from coming in, though.
And they may have sports hats on.
They do have no problem with that.
Of course they're welcome.
He created them in school.
Those are my emotional support goblins.
yeah you guys convinced this snowman to let you in the club penguin and it's
just full of children come on patina let's go play mancala okay what is that
that's when he calls another man on the phone and asks for sex I'm just gonna
throw the little stones at you he says our man caller I'm the man caller that's
I wanna decorate my igloo.
[Laughter]
I want you to...
Unfortunately I did not play enough Kaplanguin as a kid.
Lothario, you gotta roll Indomitability.
Kaplanguin? Kaplanguin.
Lothario, you gotta roll Indomitability at this point.
'Cause you've just been like...
With no remorse, trying to like...
It's BDSM!
That's what it is!
You kill a woman, right?
Three...
He's like, "I just don't know how I feel about all this pain, you call it. Pain?"
"It's not pain, it's pleasure. Have you ever seen Hellraiser?"
"No, what is it that-" "Me neither."
"That explains the pins in your head."
"Oh, I forgot those were in there."
"Oh, and these too."
"And my wiener."
"Hey, she goes over to Dookie, disgusting, to see his igloo. And what are you putting on your igloo, Dookie?"
I built the igloo around me still spinning like the face of a clock.
And I put a mini fridge to keep things cold.
I put a TV.
A mini fridge around each block of ice in the wall of the igloo.
And I put a rug.
Oh, fuck yeah, dude.
Let's do coolness for that.
I like that.
I mean, it's going to be very cool.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, advantage.
I don't know which one is it.
It's the one...
What one are you looking for?
Yeah, you got it.
Six.
Nice, yeah, it's very cool.
It's a cool igloo.
Looks pretty cool.
Pacino's pretty impressed.
I mean, keep in mind, I would say that right now...
How about you get down on the floor with me?
I'm the big hand, I need a little hand.
Ooh, that is good.
All right, I'm gonna have you roll loveliness with advantage, but before you do that, I wanna,
just for the folks at home, Pikachu right now is in the lead because he did save you from
CPR.
I forgot we're competing.
Oh yeah, you're competing for Pachina's hand.
Fuck, dude.
But you're doing well.
Good igloo, good line.
How am I doing?
You're doing so far the worst, but there's a good chance you could turn it all around.
Okay, I got a four on the advantage, so that's exploding, yes.
And a three.
Wow, I mean that's good though.
So yeah, she sits down.
She's like interested.
She's like, "So..."
I hit the igloo with a bulldozer.
I'm sorry.
Don't fuck my game up bro, I'm about to smash.
I tried to- Oops, I didn't realize I had to put a new hotel
in here.
I was like- It's called the H.H.
Holmes Motel.
The whole time I was driving to the igloo on a Zamboni but it was too slow.
So I saw the bulldozer pulling up and I was just like, "Oh, fuck this."
and I fall off the iceberg well I dive in to save him
whoa which means me and patchy and I have a moment alone you guys are buried
under ice this is a I bolded you I'm gonna Gina don't worry I'm gonna I'm
gonna put out a beacon and I give myself a boner and it pops out of the top of
the ice pile no no wait it's ended with this has penis this has to be a fair
fight I do not care for drown it's not brought it to me
yeah Pacino's fanning herself though seeing your penis beacon for sure and
it's really it's it by the way it's really red at the top it's like like
Rudolph's nose tip of my penis yeah I mean the club peg with security is just
like not even pass it is sleeping security is like trying to figure out if
that is a penis we're not gone instantly you'd be banned you'd be they don't even
even let you say crap on. I don't even let you say Filipino on there. Yeah.
Why? I do have a tattoo that goes along the length of my penis that says
Filipino. Filipino for life in old English. So you guys are diving in.
What are you going to do to save him? I'm going to sink. I'll swim. I make a
raft out of goblin slaves that are all holding each other's arms and
ankles and I'm getting as close to him as I can and then I'm using a fishing rod made
out of goblin slams to fish him out.
I like this sort of uh...
Sounds sick.
Sort of like you have like a...
They're like nanobots.
I was about to say.
That's what goblins are like.
Seven.
Seven?
Wow.
Yeah, I mean you do an amazing job coordinating your slaves.
I saved you.
you don't have to save me
you dumb bastard. you are dumber than me.
plus 9, plus 10, 21.
there's a lot of references in this. sort of like a violent psycho. maybe he's nice
i'm not a violent... i guess i can't hear her. nah, he's not nice.
he's not nice? he's no nice.
i'm so happy that i saved pikachu
and kissing him on his cheek and i'm being so nice where uh... machine it can
see me
i am being touched when i don't want the this seems like a can't read lips and
if they would think i was a little bit you know if you think this is a good
and that you know secret gay guy no she loves you love her and people fucking
loved when patrick rubbed on your wiener
but he said she that put him in first place
i start running at you later wait patches likes
so why is that patches it's the character no no no no no every time anybody's done anything gay
you make them number one that's not true what's going on okay wait i start i start my love y'all
you got to get with my friends well i can i can see patchy no i can see patchy no doing
spice girls drag reality is bleeding through reality is not okay listen listen i can see
patchy no looking at looking at me facts listen listen i can see patchy no looking at me softer
and softer as you do.
Looking at me and Pikachu from the distance, I can see Pachino looking at me and Pikachu
from the distance and I panic, I don't know what to do and I start sucking Pikachu's dick.
Oh no.
I do not like this.
Unless you do.
Hello.
Guys, this is what we have to do.
We have to expose Pachino.
No.
Yeah.
The idea of two guys having like snacks and just looking up at somebody else and being
I'm rolling sexiness to see how good I suck his dick.
If it's really good, Pacino's gonna love it.
And that's because Pacino likes it.
Pacino will love it and Patches is gonna continue to be sort of nonplussed about the whole thing.
Okay, that's a three.
Okay, out of what?
It's a d6, right?
Out of what?
What did you roll?
Okay.
No, take into account both that and the total roll.
It's a serviceable but not ideal way to suck a dick.
You're sort of, you're doing a little corncobby.
You're kind of leaning too much into that part of it.
He's corncobbing my bitch.
You need to do that tornado.
Yeah, okay, I start doing the tornado.
Indomitability.
Okay.
Both hands.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Three.
Again.
You know the only way to get me is to grapefruit me.
You have to grapefruit me.
I will do whatever it takes.
Wait, I'm not being gay enough.
Okay, I wake up and I fucking...
There's nobody- is there a guy near me?
There's a security guard who's like-
I suck his fucking dirty dick.
There's a snowman, he's got like a- he's got a carrot down there too.
Okay yeah, I put the- yeah, roll- roll sexiness.
Is this what you like, Pacino?
Sexiness?
I didn't say I liked or disliked any of this.
I have a D8. You clearly like it.
Nope, that's- you stopped saying it.
I got a 7.
That's really good.
I tornado.
Pacino?
I double hand tornado Riley Reed his carrot.
Pachina's like, "Maybe he's gay, he's so good at this. I love when men are gay."
Pachina does. Patches doesn't care. You just said you love when men are gay.
No, I said... You don't... wait, you... Patches don't care about gay men? I don't... no, I...
So either you like when guys are gay or you don't care about gay people.
I like... what's this? It's hot in here.
I like people. I like people. No, it's because I'm nervous because I feel like people. You like penile.
I don't even know what's penile. He doesn't know what penile is. I'll show you. No, don't show me
that because I wouldn't like it but if other people like having that I'm okay with that.
Okay, I want to go join their water orgy over in the thing. We're out of the water. Okay,
so I don't care if it's land or sea I'm going to fuck you. We're in the sauna. There's a
like a 30 person Hollywood goblin camera crew. That's fine. Yeah, no I'm just
setting the scene. Yeah, yeah. There's lighting people, there's like four
cameras, there's a boom mic. It's like a multi-cam like sitcom like kind of thing or what do you mean?
No, like a GoPro and put it right here so that I get like a POV shot. Yeah, so the GoPro is a
really small goblin just holds on to you. Okay that's fine. I put him here. And just remembers it.
And can tell you later. I put him on my head. I strap that in and I walk over and I start,
I just kind of like use my, like slither my huge penis like around you guys multiple times. Kind
of bind you together. Yeah. Okay. That's sexiness. Roll sexiness. While I'm like locked up in a penis
Like, "yee cans."
Hold on, let's see if he is.
"Yee cans."
Wait, yeah, let's see if he is.
We don't count that.
That is-- oh, we don't count it?
Unless we're changing the rules for Caleb.
No, we don't count it!
Hey, whatever.
That's fine by me, because we don't count that three.
We get that one, though.
Your dick can't really quite wrap around.
It just hits, like, really hard, sharp corners.
Like, "ding, ding, ding, ding, ding."
Like Snake?
Yeah, like a cartoon falling down a huge pipe.
What were you gonna do if you were having, if you were being echoed?
I'm singing.
You're singing?
I'm singing while a penis is around me.
But I'm singing a girl's song.
What song are you singing?
Which is pretty gay.
What if we just leave Club Penguin and go to the beach?
Shut up you stupid bitch!
I was petrified.
Take a dog.
I mean this is all...
Is that gay enough for you, bitch?
I have no... I'm just impressed that you're so open about your sexuosity.
Yep, all three of us are gay.
Yeah.
Yeah, we all three gay men.
Then I'm never going to find love in Worcester if all the men are...
No, don't worry, don't worry.
Gay.
Hey, Pacino, Pacino.
They have invented a new type of gay.
I'm gonna take you back to my, to my, to my, to my mansion in the center of the earth and
we're gonna, I have a, uh, we're gonna go on one of those, those amusement park love boat rides
where you go down a a river of burning boiling oil in a tunnel and and ten
trebuchets launch spiked balls at you what if we just go on a regular tunnel
of love okay but it has to be designed by Nazi scientists everything in Worcester
designed by Nazi scientists we're all going to the tunnel of love in Worcester
yeah okay everybody everybody knows the tunnel of love yeah so can we do so we
we get to the town of love and it's us three in one boat and then you patchy
in a behind. We're all in the same boat, but we're sitting in the front row and
she's like like two rows back. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, it's a big swan and
yeah, and yeah, it's meant for orgies. Yeah, I'm seasick immediately. Yeah,
yeah, I can't handle. I can't handle. You see the pimply pimply simpsons
teenager there right. He's like all right. You guys want to go into the
tunnel off. Oh, fuck is
I don't know, ehh, ehh.
He became...
He became Scottish.
I don't know why do you have Dramamine?
Oh, I might...
I... go check the first aid kit.
Patches dreams of men.
What?
He said, "Dream of me."
You dream of me.
I don't...
You dream of me?
He's got his ass.
What up?
Dream of me.
You dream of me.
I do no such thing.
And, uh...
Oh fucking shit I need Dramamine, I need to, oh I have merchant sickness, so bad it's hurting
me in my stomach.
Maybe if, maybe we can counteract the up and down of the boat by having you move up and
down in a different way.
Well.
Maybe like 30 inches up, 30 inches down.
Yeah.
30 inches up, 30 inches down that could work because then I'm not on the boat.
here get on this get a log.
I'll get a log plume now, okay?
It's a swan, right?
But it goes down a giant drop like a log plume at the end.
Just like in love you take a plunge.
Oh, I'm about to take the plunge.
It's about to go, it's about to be completely pitch black in the tunnel.
You guys are riding in the boat and it's about to enter the part of the tunnel where it's
pitch black.
Yeah, okay.
And Pacino's starting to get scared.
"Oh, fucking shit, I hit my head on the ceiling!"
"Oh, I fucking did it again!"
"It's so dark!"
"As soon as it goes dark, we fucking."
"Yep."
"Who?" "Right away."
"Us three."
"Fuck each other?"
"Yes!"
"Okay."
"Circle."
"Triangle."
"I can't even tell what starts and what begins."
"All of you ro-"
"I guess we're all sexy just at each other."
"This is how well you fuck each other, it happens."
"This is awesome."
I got a four. Four? Well keep going then. I got a one. I'm not sexy at all. I got a seven.
Like second one. So Pikachu, what did you get? I got a four. Yeah, Pikachu is pulling
the weight here on sexiness. I have. And Lothario, yeah. I'm hitting the ceiling. I have a condom
that's made of tiny goblins holding together. And you, you dookie, with that one. You dookie.
Your dick is, you're not, you know what it is?
You're just like a typical man.
You're not even thrusting your hips.
You're just letting everyone else do all the work.
He's still snuffing.
He's asleep again.
He's out there asleep.
It's the alkyl helium snore.
I should be attractive to Pachina because I'm like the least gay one because I'm asleep.
That's true.
If you're asleep during gay sex, you're basically straight.
Yeah.
It's a paradox.
It's a Pachina paradox.
can we roll to see if we stop really quickly before the lights turn back on so she doesn't
see anything.
Yeah, coolness, coolness, coolness, coolness.
I'm asleep so again I'm not doing really anything so you have to roll.
You're already dead, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You don't have to roll.
Seven.
Five.
And that's on, coolness ten.
Alright, pretty good.
Sort of like you, as the lights come here on, and then it just like stops.
And she's like, what was that?
I think it flicked.
And she's like what was that think a fly flew by
We've all used that excuse.
Yeah, there might have been a fly that flew by.
I think I heard that too.
Yeah, I heard that fly.
We're just all sticky with cum.
Literally like, our fingers are webbed.
I think it was a bug.
I think there was some kind of
not even, like a medium sized fly.
I think it was a stick bug.
Flew by.
We're all covered in water.
It was a water fly.
It was a big raving rapid.
Oh, well, even whether it was a bug or a rapid, baby, I think you're a bug
roll
loveliness
With advantage
Three roll again advantage. Oh, I meant that
One okay three. Yeah, it's like oh, I think that's the nicest thing you've said to me today. You're wrong
I think you're about as stupid as a bug.
Hey bug.
What's going on?
Is a bug talking?
Is my voice going to slowly become...
We're all waking up from a dream.
(Laughter)
Wait, what the fuck?
I just had the weirdest dream of all time.
What's going on?
Are we in Worcester? What the fuck?
Oh God.
What the hell?
(Sigh)
Oh God, what the hell was that?
What did I just touch?
I'm trying my hardest to go back to sleep.
I hit my head. Wait, Toleman, I hit you with a coconut.
Why is there always coconuts around?
Well, that was a lot of fun.
I am a robot now. I have become a robot.
Oh, I forgot he was a robot. I have been a robot the whole time.
When we like transition back into the dream, we're all just like fucking each other.
Like, just, we can just quickly stop.
well I have detected gay things happening to my butt there was a gay pulse
why are you tattletaling? I am just telling what is logically... what do you mean? gay stuff all that I've seen is gay is
somebody sucking somebody off near an iceberg earlier gay originally meant
happy. Just then we the we're still in the log flume, the swan flume. We go down. I'm
not I'm not wearing my seat belt. I fly up. I hit like a like a crossbar and like
just half of my body just completely obliterated. Just just gone and
immediately like you know that video the monkeys who have the ambulance? Yeah.
That but goblins and they take me to to the to the rich guy hospital and they
make me half robot okay and I'm a cyborg now and they bring me back to and this
all happens in one second okay I am a full robot and I have been the whole
time I'm half robot and I'm only that now I can detect human bones I have
detected something half gay you have detected I have detected something gay
this is so confusing I thought that was with three men now I'm with a robot and
and a half a robot and well a one man so like one and a half. Hey baby I'm still
man all the way 100% right then a cane pulls me off stage and then pushes out
like a robot that doesn't even look like me. Just like a Jetsons made robot.
- Okay, and then the cane, as it pushes out the robot,
it knocks me into the wall,
and the other half of my body gets obliterated,
and the same thing happens,
and they replace the other half of my body with a robot.
I am a full robot now.
- These three, these two are my brothers.
- We are robot brothers,
and we have to go to the robot store.
(laughing)
- And you have to take us there,
because robots cannot drive.
- I am not allowed to legally drive,
as I am not a person.
I don't know what happened to this Valentine's Day special but
Go bitch! Go bitch!
Go bitch!
Bitch detected!
Analyzing, analyzing, analyzing
100% bitch
Detected, 100% serving cunt
Can I roll electronics to try to make the car go faster?
Roll electronics, which is any dice you want
I'm gonna choose 10
four yeah do you believe in my works I think also if a new rule if the dice
explodes my robotics one okay one zero one one zero one zero one one zero one
one zero we are robots that only know about one we never learned zero one one
one one one we need to go to the robot store to get the zero up to it to clearly
drives you guys to the robot store which is filled with robots.
What did you do to all of my family?
This is all my cousins.
I did not do this to you.
You did this?
No, I did not.
You stupid bitch.
You did this?
No, I just come from Italy.
I didn't do anything.
I don't even know what a robot is until I met you three.
You are stupid.
Maybe.
IQ level detected.
Check this out.
*Farting noises*
Yeah!
Downloading loud_fart.mp3
*Farting noises*
Bagina, did you just fart?
*Laughter*
No, I don't think so.
Downloading Napster.
(laughter)
It's a mad stinkin' guy.
Downloading Shazam!
(laughter)
Wait, what is this song?
Oh wait, I know. This is Streets on Fire
by Lupe Diasco.
Downloading Video Star
Music Video Maker Free Edition.
Just like my ex, you all just love apps!
Quiet, volume zero.
Click remote activated.
Fast forward.
Fast forward working out.
Activate woman destroying laser.
3D printing.
Very anxious frog.
Explodes
Gay detected
Gay detective detective
Gay overload
Worcester, Massachusetts home of polar seltzer
Who are you three robot robot brothers brothers? Oh guys
It's so nice to see you. I was having this terrible bitch dream where bitch wait a minute bitch
But your robot is detected bitch detected bitch detected. I'm not a bitch. I'm
What you guys want to seduce me frog destroying laser
Brandon 3d Brendan cool version of anxious
Sullivan or cow loading
it's not the
salomon urkel complete
salomon are running salomon urkel dot e_x_e_
player dot place that means all of the intergala
all while
the president
day
the
this element is a way to alert
yeah okay let's go to the flags let's go guys go to six flags but uh...
what the right
uh...
dropped our
and i've got a lot of let's go this guy's game for anything
you guys can activate no fear
disabled people you know i don't know if you're here about activate easy pass
the
when we go on the drop tower because the robots we have a cavities in our body
that is like making sane whistling noises and i thought that
and it sounds like the ride is breaking and they shut the whole park down
whoa that was sour okay
food court going to food court food court requesting food challenge for cool son of
an okay let's eat can he eat 50 odd wings is it you need to see him eat them like
Like a vacuum, just suck them all up.
And then a waiter comes out.
Funnel cake challenge.
Uh oh.
Zero money detected.
Bitcoin downloading.
Downloading.
Downloading Bitcoin.
Point.
O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-Available.
Downloading one.
- One, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, one Bitcoin.
Buying scammed cash app from Twitter.
- Hey, we don't accept Bitcoin here.
You guys gotta pay. - Destroying waiter right now.
- No, oh no!
- Oh yeah, cool.
- Funnel cake challenge activated.
- Oh yeah.
- How much funnel cake can Cool Sullivan eat?
- How much you got?
- 50 pounds.
- Uh-oh.
(laughing)
- Dangerous.
Oh, somebody gotta roll me!
Tea cup ride.
[Laughter]
Going to tea cup ride.
Tea cup ride.
Overcharging. I'm plugging in like a USB thing into the ride.
We're gonna double speed.
Cool Sullivan!
5000 times speed.
No, we're gonna kill him.
Okay.
We're gonna make him throw up with puke.
Alright, yeah, he puked in the...
Puke protocol activated.
[Groaning]
He throws himself up and he's just deflated on the ground.
He threw up his bones.
Ugh.
Ah.
Bones detected.
Eating bones.
Sadness detected.
In brain.
3D printing DM patches.
Bzzz.
Hey guys.
Hello.
Gay detected.
No, no I'm not gay.
Hello.
This is a.
Hello pageant.
Hello Patches.
Hello.
We are three robots.
Wow, I'm 6'7".
This is sick.
Hello Patches.
You are like Spike It's three grandpa.
Photoshop free transform tool.
Activate.
Three inches tall.
Please don't do this to me.
Content aware scale.
What?
Wide patches.
Clone stamp tool.
Please don't do that to me.
Okay, what do you guys want to do now?
Color, color changer tool.
No, don't do that.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I do not consent to this.
I eyedropper color pick.
Don't scan.
Do not go to my obelisk in my room.
Finding color.
Finding color in environment.
Finding oak tree.
Oak tree.
Patches, whichever one you are.
We brought you here.
Okay.
Activating something awful photoshop Friday.
We brought you here for one very specific purpose.
What do you guys want?
Patches, Mr. Bean.
We want to make you...
Patches with Mr. Beanface.
Quiet!
We want to make you...
Quiet, Robot P!
Fall in love with us.
Yeah, that was a whole point of...
Activating pleasure sequence.
Releasing pheromones.
Destroying penis.
Indomitability.
Oh, wow!
Oh, God!
But I'm also cumming!
Collecting cum.
No!
fertilizing self
Incubating cloning patches nine-month time sequence why people shouldn't play D&D
cloning patches up cloning patches
Hi, hey guys, whoa patches. Hi. Hey guys, whoa, patches. Hi. Hey guys. Whoa cloning patches
Hi, hey guys, whoa cloning patches. How's it going?
Milking new patches.
Cool Patches is here.
Hey, what's up?
This is Cool Patches.
Milking Cool Patches.
Funnel Cake Challenge Cool Patches.
Okay, how much you got?
50.
50 pounds again?
What again?
What does again mean?
Oh no.
Downloading click remote.
From the movie Click.
Resi rewind to the end of the swan flume. The end? The end of the swan flume. Oh yeah
we're back. What happened then? We had normal patch Pachita. Oh. Oh. Activating
woman destroying it
well
as you know i don't know if all
and we're outside the eiffel tower about that
well
pitching has to choose one person to deal with
were bolt ron's together and i think i did
we're like a voltron that's made through gay sex
and she's like i don't know who to pick she's just looking at the one
we all speak in unison
that's because we're all one thing
well i guess i just have to be with this voltron
baby i love you
you
and
the
for what you guys have to
got to know what the other side
pocket where we are going to be on the phone
Lollipop, lollipop, oh lolly, lolly, lolly, lollipop
Come on baby lollipop, tell you why
He's just as sweet as an apple pie
And when he does his shaggy body dance
Man I haven't got a chance
So I call him Lollipop, Lollipop, oh Lolli
Lolli, Lolli, Lollipop, Lollipop, oh Lolli
Lolli, Lolli, Lollipop
Sweeter than candy on a stick
Huckleberry cherry lime
If you had a choice, it'd be your pick, but Lollipop is mine!
Lollipop, Lollipop, oh Lolli, Lolli, Lolli, Lollipop, Lollipop, oh Lolli, Lolli, Lolli, Lollipop, Lollipop, oh Lolli, Lolli, Lolli, Lollipop!
Crazy way it thrills me, tell you why, just like the lightning from the sky!
He loves to kiss me till I can't feel straight
Gee, my lollipop is great
I call him lollipop, lollipop
Oh lollipop, lollipop, lollipop
Boom, boom, boom, lollipop, lollipop
Lollipop, oh lollilollilolli-lollipop
Oh lollipop
Badoom boom boom
Bawm
*laughter*
This is so fucking stupid
I can't believe people are paying for that
I'm gonna stop it