You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
Did you feel like a boss when you did that?
Like a bouse.
Welcome to the dungeon.
Oh
I from the dungeon
The come to the dungeon the dungeon of ganja. Do you want a change enter enter the enter the gungeon?
Do you welcome to the gun John?
Do you want a hip shackle?
Boy, oh, there we go. I was watching the property brothers again
Yeah, where's this guy you always watching that shit use I am dude. It's so fun to watch you
There's this guy he was super quiet, and he had like a really loud intense wife
And he was like like yeah my wife man
She's like a ball of fire, but you peel back the layers, and there's just love underneath, and I was like
Oh, that's like a really sweet quiet guy, and then they're like going through their current home where they're living in and
Talking about like the design of it, and then he walked in this room
And he's like and I call these my hands of mercy and they're these giant sculptures of these like evil red
Yeah, I just love I just love my hands of mercy and everyone else in the family like hates them they look so fucked up
They're like red and black and have like long evil nails on them. I love when normally like chairs one evil
I they're like chairs
Yeah
And and then at the end of the end of the episode when they show like the new house the wife wanted to surprise him
So she put the hands of mercy in his new office and he walks in and he sees him
He's like, oh imagine that the hands of mercy in my brand new home. I couldn't be happier and he's just like
He's just so happy that he has his hands of mercy any time a normal guy has like an evil item
I really like that like there was a like Jana's childhood home. She lived on this like long
country road and there was a guy who had he was he's just a very normal nerdy like
southern dude and he had to like 10 foot tall red devil statues at the entrance
to his property and apparently like the city like find him for them like these
are too evil to be publicly displayed and so he had to move them like in his
house or something damn yeah people's or sorcerer I don't say fuck you to the
city you would go to jail I don't care well first of all you go to hell yeah
yeah you go to hell you're going to hell later um yeah but death death is a small
price for hell what does that mean you want do you mean you want to go to hell
yeah what yeah cuz yeah why when I die I want to go to hell cuz fuck it what's
that it's a biggie song he moves in Brooklyn and he just he's just quoting
biggie all the time did mm-hmm you haven't stopped every time I'm getting
you mad beautiful kid let's don't say brolic oh man we're not saying brolic
no we're not doing a Brooklyn we're not did no please stop yeah we are looking
up Brooklyn slang right now on on Google when I die I want to go to hell cuz I'm
I'm a piece of shit, it ain't hard to fucking tell.
- It is hard to tell.
You're a sweet guy. - It don't make sense
going to heaven with the goody goodies.
Dressed in white, I like black Timbs and black hoodies.
God'll probably have me on some real strict shit.
No sleeping all day, no getting my dick licked.
- This is not, no, this makes no sense for you.
You are a guy who lives inside of a Barenaked Lady song.
You are not a Biggie Smalls fan.
- I'm Biggie Smalls.
- No, you are the main character of a Barenaked Lady song
and you walk around all day.
like yeah I'm a down I'm a don't what is it I think it's an ice cream man playing
like I can't hear it so I think you're fine okay
you're so distracted he's about to say like he's about to say the n-word or
something reading the song that is not what happened I was about to say that
I'm a down-ass Brooklyn chopped chopped cheese fan I'm Brooklyn's charmer that's
what you're gonna say a Brooklyn chopped cheese fan is that what you that is not
a Biggie Smalls the lyric Brooklyn's charmer you were not Brooklyn's charmer
maybe Brooklyn Snake Charmer. Yeah. You could be. That's what they that's my
grinder name. Brooklyn Snake Charmer? Mm-hmm. Are you we're gonna get you on the
dating apps and you're gonna we're gonna get you a swagged out Brooklyn themed
profile. Yeah Brooklyn's Kid. Yeah. Brooklyn's Charmer. Brooklyn's Charmer.
The only pictures are hats. It's just like. Just a hat collection. Amazon screenshots.
yeah this is a little bit about me mm-hmm Brooklyn fitted hat Brooklyn
Dodgers and then my my my descript like my my description is just the chorus of
crush on you by Lil Kim you are not into little Kim I am you are not she's not
for you I got a little me I got into little Kim you got into little Kim so
you could say so you could like raise your eyebrow at people and go like I'm
I'm into Lil' Kim now.
Isn't that funny about me?
Isn't that a funny thing to listen to?
That's not.
Looking like me?
No.
That's exactly- Lil' Kim.
Why do you bring it up every time then?
That's exactly the reason you got into Lil' Kim.
That's not the reason I got into Lil' Kim.
Lil' Kim is your guy's wife name.
Then why don't you tell us about all the other bands you get into, huh?
Okay.
Yeah, Lil' Kim's one of my favorite bands.
Tell us about some other bands like Lil' Kim.
Lil' Kim is my favorite band.
No, what I mean is you never say, "Oh, I've been getting into this person lately."
Yeah, I do.
to us on the podcast not on the podcast so so name another band you like okay do
you guys want to talk about the replacements or something or no no
Kim do you want to talk about block party no there the block party is a
great band you want to talk about the grace or great replacements because
you're the racist man yeah you are you want to talk about prefab sprout for a
little bit no you sure yes you will make me prefab shout at you if you if you
make me talk about pre-fraps sprout I thought about them for a little bit we
know let's talk about them okay I've never heard of pre-fab sprout so there's
my why can't I see that that's my favorite and pre-fab you've never heard
Prefab.
F-f-f-f-sprout.
It's a very clunky name.
It's a very clunky name, I will say.
I do not listen to rock music.
Okay.
I listen to- That's so cool.
Is Prefab Sprout rock music?
Yeah, man.
You want a medal?
Yeah.
No, I mean that's why I've never- You want to be inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall
of Fame for that?
Sorry, I can't hear you.
I'm listening to Bad Bunny lyrics right now.
Yo tango, cus-cud-ola, mi amigo.
So Patti McAloon from Prefab Sprout was supposed to be a priest but then he decided to become
a musician instead.
And he's not Irish right?
Even though his name is Patti McAloon?
I thought they were Irish because of that and turns out they're just, they're Geordie.
They're from...
What's Geordie mean?
I don't know what that means.
Geordie is like a, it's like the border of like Scotland and the UK.
So he's Irish?
What do you, that you were like, what?
When you said like, oh yeah.
He wasn't Irish and his name's Patty.
I thought you were gonna be like, yeah, he's from Nevada,
but he's from right next door?
- Yeah, that's a different place.
Completely, that's a different place completely.
- No, that's the same place.
- No.
- Mm-hmm, it's pretty much the same place.
- He's British, not Irish.
- So are Irish people.
- You shut the fuck up!
(laughing)
Shut your fucking mouth!
- They're all British, dude.
- No!
- They are.
- We're the only, we're the podcast that's gonna
unify Ireland and we can't have this conversation I'm gonna break it up in
even more parts no one person each each nation and I'm gonna take a little piece
for myself yeah what do you what part are you gonna take me the middle the
new giddy middle and I have okay I can't have any of it no why fuck you I'm not
Irish I'm not Irish sir I own the middle of Ireland the middle you own like
It's a big circle.
You, okay.
So you own like a big circle in the middle of Ireland.
It's called the Irish Rotunda and I own it.
Okay.
Yeah.
I own the rest of the world.
Yeah, he owns the rest of the world.
I own everything outside of that circle.
No, you don't.
Yeah, he does.
So, I mean, you're trespassing.
I don't know where you are right now, but you're trespassing on one of our properties.
Yeah, Patrick, I'm sorry, but I'm gonna have to deport you to the Irish Rotunda, and if
they don't want you, you're gonna have to go to the moon or something.
We have a strict COVID lockdown at the Irish Rotunda right now.
Wait, wait, you don't own any of the oceans.
I own all the oceans.
What are you talking about?
I said everything outside of the circle.
No.
Okay, you...
But I own the air.
You said no, it was implied it was land.
Why did I imply it was land?
I said everything else.
Shut up.
The whole world.
Do you think the water's not part of the world?
No.
You can have a-
Okay Patrick, you can have-
A cloud.
Can I have a cloud?
You can have a cloud for as long as it lasts before it rains.
Yep.
Once it rains it goes back onto the earth, it's mine again.
I would like to have-
You get no part of it.
None.
All right.
Zero.
Zilch.
I get nothing.
Nothing.
What about-
You can ask to pay to stay with me.
Well, you can-
What about Australia?
None of you-
Neither of you want Australia.
I already have.
I yeah we have it under control that's me and cams like shared that's like the
demilitarized zone between the rotunda and the rest of the world we've
suppressed all the stuff that's going on over there yeah we've got it all figured
out yeah and this and yeah some of those accents to really had to go yeah we
don't wear what camps what where what where's the circle you can see it on the
map it's on the map where tell me tell me where the Google Earth right now yeah I
I mean I'm not gonna I don't it's also it is a secret location so I can't really
give it away on air like this is it around like County Cork?
It's around it's around it's round. It is absolutely round.
Patrick I'll tell you what you if you look at a map of Ireland right now okay
and you pick a point on it that's either owned by Caleb or me yeah I could that's
That's what I can tell you with certainty.
London dairy.
Is that in Ireland?
Yes.
It's not London dairy anymore.
It's Cameron dairy.
That's it.
Okay, London dairy.
London dairy is Caleb dairy and that's mine.
So which one?
Well, there's two London dairies, but now they're Cameron and Caleb dairy.
Well, one of them's in the circle.
The one that's in the circle is mine.
One of them is in a different circle.
Okay, okay.
So if it's in the circle, that means Caleb just has Northern Ireland.
Okay, so if it's in the circle, that means Caleb just has Northern Ireland.
of
It doesn't necessarily have to be round a circle it can be like a shape that kind of just goes
What the fuck are you talking about?
A circle doesn't have to be round?
Yeah it doesn't have to be round.
Well I mean if you're talking about you know territory I mean
It's a geographical circle it's actually like a different thing
It has a different definition
It's like when people say that America is a circle
It's like it's obviously not but
Nobody fucking says that
It's when they say like the united circle of America
People say time is a circle it's not it's a line
Exactly it's a clock
so it's a hand on the clock the one not the circle of the clock get this anymore
well it's like it's like if you think about it basically is that you're not
welcome on earth anymore yeah like you're gonna have to like Graham is
pretty much you you were spending way too much on the details and way too
little packing your bags yeah we don't like the way that we've got a really
nice spot for you on one of the space stations that is actually crashed okay
in the gases of Saturn and you're just a station that you sent Hitler yeah yep
okay yeah and Hitler owns all that stuff I'm gonna go buddy up with him I'm not
buddying up with him I'm gonna take him down yeah what with what yeah with my
lyrics no no way no you're not gonna by reciting little Kim well I mean if you
had gone all the way with the little yeah you know freak the fuck out you've
been like this white guy is really racist and awesome I love this guy have you
heard the the first the intro skit for that album I've never listened to a
Little Kim album? Well the intro skit of I think hold on let me what album is that?
The Blarney Stone by Little Kim. Yeah yeah Come Out You Black and Tans by
Little Kim is the album. Okay which one do you consider yourself? Black Irish or?
I was on hardcore so on hardcore the intro skit is uh it's just a guy jacking off
Jesus Christ little Kim I know well something that's a very ladylike little
Kim she needs to she needs to get her act together go back to church I know
that's right mm-hmm pull your panties up that's nasty mm-hmm
stop sagging your panties I'm sick and tired all these women sagging their
panties sagging your skirts and panties showing half your ass it's disgusting
disgusting these women are sagging their their bras
they're wearing their bras upside down
fuck why you got your you got your bow back turn turn your bonnet back around
Yeah, come on.
You're putting it the wrong way.
What's wrong with you?
Oh my God, yeah.
People are going to get the wrong idea.
I think you're some kind of criminal.
Can you tie the laces on your corset, please?
Don't just have them flopping around everywhere.
What do you think you are, Run DMC?
No laces on your corset?
Come on.
Yeah.
No.
No, thank you.
Not for me.
I miss when female rappers were just like whores with deep voices.
Yeah.
We should go back, dude.
Mm-hmm.
well isn't isn't that Nicki Minaj? She doesn't have a deep voice. Yeah that's
true she's got that very grating voice. She has a baby voice. Yeah. What's up with all
these baby rappers? Well no because she has different personas that she has different
voices for. Um. I'm a barb now. Um okay. This is my new decision to become a barb. Yeah
I've become a barb. I think that you should get you should be develop new personas for
podcasting where you do different voices. You get new personas? Yes. So like maybe
like goth or like chef or like golfer or... Are you saying I'm like Nicki Minaj?
I almost... I bought a tiny chair. I think maybe Caleb is the Nicki Minaj of the podcast. I bought a really tiny chair today.
Okay so if we're... hold on, shut up. No you shut up! I was gonna pretend that I was big but I...
I would have been good yeah but I'm sorry I'm sorry I said shut up got it in the
kitchen yeah fuck you I was trying to ask an important question I'm done
talking to you what you can ask me the question okay answer it on Kayla I'm not
looking at Pat I'm blocking him off on my screen so if we're if we're like if
we're like young money uh-huh who is who cuz I we've already established Caleb is
Nicki Minaj no I'm Drake no no I'm Drake I'm Drake tell that to this okay
Cameron's Drake and I'm Drake and Caleb is-
I might be too strong out on compliments
Overdosed on confidence
No, see, I sound way more like Drake right now
Too much like Drake
I sound so much like Drake right now
I sound more like Drake right now
I sound the most like Drake right now
Hey guys, it's me, Drake
Oh, we have a ding ding winner
Yeah, okay, Cameron's Drake
Cameron is Drake, but I'm
Lil Wayne now, and I'ma sound just like
Lil Wayne
you're you are Nicki Minaj we've already Cameron is running away with this
competition is there any can you do gutta gutta can you do can you do little
way Drake and Scooby-Doo okay let's take the other members of young money though
who are you hold on Cameron can you do mr. bean no okay well I guess oh no my car
is so small and the chair is on top of my car I'm in love with my teddy bear
what's I hate mr. being mr. being oh yes yeah well a lot of people think no he the
teddy bear is actually mr. bean yeah nobody nobody knows yeah and then the
mr. bean is actually mr. beans man yeah exactly yeah people people which is
shortened to just mr. bean yeah mr. man is kind of a yeah so they just call him
Mr. Bean. So really it doesn't matter all that much.
Right, because then it gets confusing because it's like, oh is he the Beans Man?
Or is his last name Bean?
Is he the Beans Man or a Man's Bean I ask?
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Is he Chicago's famous Bean?
No.
I hope to God he's not.
They should do a Chicago Mr. Bean reboot.
Yeah, where he gets born from the bean.
And it's called, you know how he falls out of the sky at the start?
of yeah in this one he he comes out of the bean you know what the name of the
show is born from the bean oh I was seeing bean origins that's good too
being origins they should have been origins and it's just flying around in
the sky before he falls down yeah he's just he's on okay so one mentally
disabled man. One giant spaceship. One bean. A teddy bear named Mr. Bean. A crazy turkey.
A banana peel on the floor. Christmas tree. A car. A tiny yellow car with a chair on top
of it. The pool where his swim trunks fell off. That one episode where he puts on a Nazi
uniform and goose steps around a dressing room that's the movie oh and
starring Homer Simpson as himself oh wait the Simpson bean crossover we've all
been waiting for in sins the beans sins bless me yeah yeah that's right so Homer's
that he's about to get hit by the car he's running up about to run into the
garage mm-hmm who falls out of the sky and squashes him mr. B Homer Simpson
Homer Simpson Oh mr. mr. homer's twin being Homer's twin from that homer's
brother from that one episode yeah Danny DeVito he has a car factory
Pat's throat just made like a yeah fucking like scary door sound yeah that
was fucking crazy yeah it was like busy thinking about Homer Simpson I might
have some crazy gastrointestinal problem I don't know about are you a snorer
yeah Juvio's been sleeping in my living room and every night he goes exactly like
that like two in the morning this six in the morning oh and every morning Jana
wakes up she's like what the fuck is that crazy sound and I'm like is he like does
he have like sleep apnea or something yeah I think he has a toucan stuck in
his throat is he there right now? no he's out he's out he's out on the city he's not there
he's on the town yeah no yeah where'd he go? will he be back by the end of the recording?
do you have a tracker on him? yeah let me check the bumblebee tracker or whatever that thing's
called the B. Juvio's a bumblebee? No what is that? We should buy, oh Firefly.
He is, I put a firefly on him. Yeah we should buy Juvio a bumblebee costume. He
says he's in the middle of the Hudson River that's not good. That is a bad sign.
He's probably swimming, he's probably having fun. Yeah looks like he is, we should all wait.
Looks like he's 100 feet below sea level. It looks like there's some nice little floaties on his pin
right here so I think he's fine. It looks like there's some water. It says scuba.
Yeah it says fun under the dot so I think so I think he's fine.
Wait hold on hold on click it click it uh click the three dots next to fun.
Okay. Oh my god it says he's funking underwater.
What is that mean?
He's funking drowning is what it says.
Oh my god he's funking drowning right now.
ground
i don't understand why when you press the three dots after it puts up before it
to
yeah
really
he's crazy talking died
he's
now it says he's fine
can you all know where i stand it is as he's finally dead
Wait, hold on. It says that fun is an acronym too. It says fuck, under, n- water.
All right. That's done.
Yeah, we may have killed that one.
We may have taken it one too far.
I've been, dude, I've been so off. I've been so off lately.
The funky thing was strong. You've been off?
Me too.
Are you a dude of yours?
Have you been down bad lately?
Me? Have I been down bad?
Are my friends down bad?
I've been down bad, dude.
I've not been down bad, I've just been off.
David Ortiz shirt, I feel amazing.
I'm down bad because God is throwing lightning bolts at me.
That is...
Try and kill me.
That might be Zeus then.
God doesn't really deal with lightning.
Well, it's a metaphor.
And yes, he does.
Oh, I got it.
I'm sorry.
Okay, continue.
My bad.
I got killed by God.
Yeah, I was killed by God several times.
I died a thousand times yesterday.
So that's how that feels.
I have tried a thousand times waiting for you.
No.
You don't like that song?
You're right, you are off. Yeah, off key.
Come on, brother.
That was horrible.
No, you know what it is? I ate a pulled pork sandwich before recording.
It's amazing that you are so easily affected by food.
Just any food that is not like an apple, you're like, "It's..."
I think I'm allergic.
It is... Allergic to what? Pulled pork?
No, an apple.
Oh, okay.
[laughter]
Yeah, I can use like...
If you had said yes, I would not have been that surprised also.
You'd be like, "I don't know, something about the shredded... I'm allergic to shredded meat."
Yeah. I, um... yeah, like if I'll eat... if I eat like apples or carrots, I think it's like... I think
there's some... I don't... I don't know what it... it's called oral allergy syndrome. I've talked
about it before where if I eat like raw carrots my mouth will swell up, but if I eat cooked carrots
it's fine. I think I might be allergic to eating a giant meal because it makes me so tired. Oh,
I'm so allergic to cigarettes. I'm allergic to beer because it makes me throw up.
I think I'm allergic to poop and pee. Yeah. I hate the smell. I can't stand it. It spoils my appetite.
It makes me sneeze. I burst out in hives every time I touch poop and pee.
And there's a big hive around my mouth. Yeah, I think I'm allergic to this stuff.
Yeah. Oh God, it's so gross.
I haven't touched it in years due to my allergy.
Yeah, no, I mean it's like it sucks because like I wish I could but it makes my mouth tingle.
Yeah, because I actually wanted to do like some like experimental art
with poop and pee but I guess I can't.
Yeah.
Oh well.
We should get into experimental art.
I'm going to do Piss Christ with Patrick.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Are you going to like 3D print me or like?
Are you not available?
I'm down to get 3D printed, but I'm kind of busy lately.
Can you just sit like David Blaine in a container that I pee in?
No.
Why not, dude?
It's for art.
I'm busy.
Okay, okay.
Somebody doesn't care about the art world.
I don't.
I'm busy now, though.
You guys want to see my latest art piece?
Yeah.
I call this the persistence of sleep.
Wow.
- Oh my God.
- That's amazing.
- Yeah, so I got-- - You wanna see?
I crafted this.
I bought one of Cameron's pieces lately.
- Really? - One of Cameron's--
- You lately bought it? - Latest piece.
- You lately bought it?
- I meant to say latest.
- That still would not have made sense.
I bought one of his pieces latest.
- His latest pieces.
I'm off today.
- I didn't know which one you bought.
- Yeah, you ate pulled pork.
That is a-- - I did do that.
Now that one's called,
that one is called the persistence of sitting down.
- This is an instruction manual for a chair.
Yeah, what's that say? Shit?
Come on, brother.
No, it's a found object type of piece where you find an object and you say, you name it.
Um...
See, it has...
I've actually been working on a piece...
It could be whatever you want.
Look, it's got nothing in it.
I've actually been working on this piece lately.
It's almost done.
It's called The Persistence of Caleb.
Really?
And pretty soon I'm going to be putting it on display.
I'm going to be hanging it on the wall in a very awful, bad-smelling, cold, and very
uncomfortable gallery that I found.
- No. - It's another one of Cameron's pieces.
- Blow off duster. - Now that one's called the persistence of no dust.
- The lack of persistence of dust. - Well I don't recall asking you for name suggestions.
- You're right. Yo, take a plump on the duster dude. Have you ever done that?
- No. - It's cold.
- It's cold. - Is he gonna do it?
- Is he gonna do it dude?
*sucking noise*
*screaming*
*laughing*
Don't do that again, dude.
Oh boy.
Oh fuck.
Oh fuck me.
I gotta sit down.
You're sitting down.
*groaning*
I have to lie down.
I'm gonna die.
I think that is- I think- I think I'm over being addicted to like real drugs and now it's time to move on to like-
Yeah.
Inhalants and yeah and like all that kinda awesome shit.
You should just be like a casual poppers taker.
I'm addicted to candles dude.
Fuck they smell good as fuck.
Dude you should get- I'm addicted to vanilla bro.
Fuck.
Yo I'm looking like- I know people say you don't- you should like should stay away but
I can't stop myself lately I've just been really into music.
I think I'm addicted dude.
I'm addicted to- But it hurts so good you know I just forget my problems instantly the second
that- I'm addicted to feeling good.
yeah i think i'm addicted to say except for her
i'm addicted to lavender and peach blossom
by glade
nice
take a ticket then
come on how could you get a new everything
in your room by the time this episode over
the
demi-hot
taking a hit off link air freshness like
Oh, hey guys!
Hi!
Just pretending, just pretending it's got helium in it.
I'm so high right now!
Oh my god, anybody could fuck me right now!
You guys all look like Mickey Mouse!
Oh my god, oh my god.
Yo, I think somebody put on some Bob Marley.
I'm high as fuck right now.
Yo, I think I see a Chester.
Oh no, whoa, your head is so big right now!
You look about ugly as hell right now!
Oh my god.
Wait, you should put on- did you know if you sync up Dark Side of the Moon to The Wizard
of Oz, it syncs up?
Do you know if you put on Dark Side of the Moon while you're vacuuming the house, it's
so much fun!
Yeah, did you know if you put on Dark Side of the Moon while you're sitting there listening
to music, it actually syncs up to be a great album?
Mm-hmm.
Have you guys thought about that?
Yeah, you can do that with any album too.
No.
Only some.
No, I think it's a couple.
If you play Dark Side of the Moon and you play Bon Jovi, Slippery When Wet, if you play
those while you're listening to the other...
You can sync up Rucka Rucka Ali, I'm Black, You're White, Who Cares with Tenet and it
syncs up perfectly.
The funniest way that people name their album is seeing like a phrase painted on a brick
wall or on the road or on a street sign and just be like, "Yep, that's it!"
That's what the album cover for Slippery When Wet is too.
Yeah.
I think it's actually...
Damn.
Recycling?
That's it, dude.
Thank you on a trash can?
That's the one.
Oh yeah.
Oh my god.
Oh yeah, dude.
Men.
Women?
Men's bathroom.
Cameron Fetter is banned from this bathroom?
I think that's it guys.
I think we found our album name.
Yeah.
This crazy sign I saw that says
Cameron is banned for sneaking into the girls bathroom.
We should name our album that.
That would be so funny guys.
Yeah, people would take pictures with the sign.
Yeah.
Today I saw
I like walked around Williamsburg today there's still on every block a huge like
mural of Trump with like fraud or like where at pussy I can I won't go take a
picture with it in Williamsburg there's like a bunch of them it's so sick dude
it's I think that that that it will be lost in time that neighborhood it'll just
be that forever it'll be stuck in 2017 I'm very excited I will go back there
there often you should you should move above he's gonna be president again in
four years that's true and they know that that's where they're leaving it up
yeah yeah they're not inside and suggesting it'll be situation yeah it's
like we'll just leave it up when he becomes president again people be like
if only somebody could write asshole over his mouth oh shit there it is how
that was fast those brave graffiti artists I know to
brave mural artists. There's brave five points graffiti artists who go to
Williamsburg and paint. They're like okay I'm gonna need an orange spray can of
paint. Yeah I'm gonna need a lot of orange because he's fat.
Give me all the orange spray paint you have please. Hey do you have a
pigment called Cheeto? Those brave brave warriors who paid their way
through art school and then suffered through wiki how to use urban slang yeah
thank God for them yeah salute salute to our champions yeah salute to our street
soldiers they're kind of like they're kind of like like you know nowadays
team culture maybe doesn't have many heroes like they used to like you know
they we used to have Achilles and Hercules and you I don't know but now we
Now we have graffiti.
Graffitis.
Achilles to Graffitis.
That's the name of one of my new art books actually.
That's so amazing.
Yeah.
When are you getting your art books published?
I already did.
So you're going to have to go look for them.
Wow.
Whoa.
Did you self publish?
Did you go?
It's kind of a Banksy turn of events.
You go to the store, you want to buy them.
You can't.
In fact, the only way to buy it is to destroy it.
- Yep.
- That's some artistic shit, brother.
- God damn, that is so fucking cool.
- You will be a professor at the new school
within the year's end.
- It's all printed on like shredded paper
that doesn't make any sense,
but when you like put it backwards through the shredder,
the art comes together.
- Whoa.
- Yeah.
- That's incredible.
- You have to buy the special shredder I designed
in order for it to work.
Otherwise it'll just shred it twice.
'Cause a normal shredder doesn't go backwards.
It's a $300 shredder.
Oh yeah, no, it's way more than that.
I mean, there's only one of these in the world.
$300 installments.
Yeah, for a million years.
Twice a day for a million years.
And the contract does say it goes
through your family line forever.
Yep.
I'm gonna get, I wanna go to Best Buy and get like a--
Right?
Do you think, right before you die,
just taking out just an insane amount of debt
and just ruining your children's lives forever?
Genius, dude.
- Yeah, just like buying every--
- Just cruising your family line.
- Every 70 inch TV at Best Buy,
and be like, "I'm gonna finance it.
"I'll do one penny a day for one trillion days."
(imitates high-pitched squeaking)
Sir, why are you tee-hee-hee-ing?
Oh, no reason.
Okay, we accept.
- Yeah, I'll pay zero dollars a day for one million years.
- Duh, sounds good to me.
Those people at Best Buy are so stupid,
except for the Geek Squad,
the brave and noble Geek Squad,
who took down Osama bin Laden.
- I mean, hey, we said that graffiti artists were brave.
We forgot about the Geek Squad.
- Well, those are the same people.
- It's true, yeah.
- Yeah, there's a big overlap there.
- Geek Squad, graffiti artists.
- Geek Squad and graffiti artists, yeah.
- That's true.
Those are two of the most hip hop kinds of guys
you can have.
- It's true.
- I feel so bad for,
there's a certain type of person at Best Buy
like that works at Best Buy when you go in,
you look at them and you're like,
oh, like you wanted to work at GameStop
they wouldn't hire you. Yeah. It's so depressing. Yeah, the people who are in the game section
or like the PC's. Yeah, with like the really skinny guys with long hair and you're like
oh shit yeah I'm sorry man. It's funny, you could have got those pre-orders like for your
friends but now you're just fucking. Yeah, now you have to walk back and forth like into
the parking lot in the winter because people want to do curbside pickup for their iPhone
Charger mm-hmm I think like when like me too was was happening I think like most
people who were publicly shamed were like Hollywood people and then I think the
second most was GameStop managers because I think like four in my hometown had
like 1,200 comment Facebook threads about them oh yeah there's something about
that rush of power yeah that is like technically powerful but at the lowest
level that anybody can access.
So, they just, I think it, I think it, uh...
Yeah, well the thing is, everybody who, everybody who's a GameStop manager also plays like, like,
you know, fucking, uh...
Fingering simulator 2 on Steam.
Yeah, exactly.
They play like, they play like the Call of Duty games for like 24 hours a day and just
like, like get war crimes injected into their brain and it's like, "I'm gonna become the
manager and I'm going to be Ronald Reagan."
Do you ever hear about that Call of Duty streamer, he was like friends with Keemstar, his name
was Only Use Me Blade.
Oh yeah, Only Use Me Blade?
Yeah.
I watched a video about him last night.
Oh he just became an alcoholic.
He became an alcoholic and then got banned from Twitch for showing his butt.
I used to watch him and like Sea Nanners and all those guys when I was growing up.
I wanted to be a COD pro.
- Didn't only use me, but isn't he involved in like,
I don't wanna get into like the--
- Oh, isn't he involved with like wings of redemption,
like trolling wings of redemption or whatever?
- I don't know what that is.
- Exactly, that's why I stopped myself
but then still said it.
- We need to make like a list of like,
me and Cam both make a list of things that we know.
And then you--
- And then I keep it to my computer.
- Yeah, you say I'm gonna stick to these subjects
and not go talk about one of the craziest things
anybody's ever talked about.
- Yeah, maybe if we like--
- Do you guys wanna talk about like
Lord of the Rings for a while maybe?
Maybe if we had a list of topics that we could that we made before the show.
Wow.
Maybe like a bunch like we could come up with like something where like we go just go through
them.
You guys are talking on this.
What if we did the news?
The news is too scary to me and I watch it like a horror film all day.
What if we did one where we said where we wrote stuff about Chipotle?
Okay.
What if we did an episode about Greg Peppers?
Done before.
Who did that?
think it was you and me and him okay that makes sense all right what if we did one
where Pete word it was like a mailbag uh-huh you want to be in a mailbag for
sure yes sir next man dude I straight up lately I've been in my mailbag what did I
What did I do this week?
I don't even fucking know, dude.
I've done so much.
I've done so much, but I have nothing to fucking talk about.
Basically, we have conquered New York City.
I can't believe you guys.
I was fucking, I was relying on, I've been sitting here doing nothing, wasting away with
God punishing me day after day, and I was like, "Oh, they're going to have some great
stories about like Jubio falling into a manhole or something."
Oh, you want to talk about Jubio falling into a manhole?
Yeah, I do have that story.
No.
No, Jubio's just like a giant Mexican toddler that I've been bringing around New York City
in people. How big is he? How tall is he? He's like 6'3". Yeah. Whoa. Very surprising. Came
out of nowhere. Yeah, he broke Noah's lighter. He broke Noah's lighter with his strong, brute
hands. Just with his height alone. Yeah, yeah, he was, yeah, he got up and he hit it with
his head. Yeah. He's gonna be so happy to hear that we're talking about him. He is going
through it cry you really cry no but I guess somebody I guess he was at like a
get-together and told somebody how much money he made every week and they got
really sad and nobody talked for like 10 minutes because he makes a Mexico wedge
and they were like oh all these like these like Brooklyn like rich kids were
like okay kill the mood and he's like so funny I'm confronted with like a yeah
like we're being confronted with reality and just being like whoo cuz Jubio
that's reality right there that's a healthy dose yeah it's a reality TV
station oh god but yeah I love him so much and he's my best friend in the
world and he snores like "Naaaaaahhh" What's his full name? Oh today I will say this, this happened today. Today I
parked my car on the street that is like the worst street to park your car
on but that's why there's always a space there. Car crash Avenue. It kind of is
car crash Avenue there's like there's a sidewalk on one side of the street that
that is full of like, like bear shit and like rappers.
Yo, what's up man?
And then like all these pieces of like cars
where people have gotten in fender benders
and like, like their bumpers have flown off
onto the sidewalk.
And today I parked there and I was like walking down
the street and there's a guy just like staring at me
at the end of the block.
And I was like, okay, this is weird,
but like not enough for me to cross the street.
And then I got closer and he was sitting with his balls
penis out peeing onto his balls and then the pee was flying in the wind towards
me and I had to like Matrix dodge the pee and get and move to the other side of
the street damn and he's just like looking at me like a bull like just
ready to charge. You should have charged at him.
I would have gotten fucking pee on my face. No I couldn't because I was
laughing so hard I just immediately started laughing and I had to I had to
cross the street yeah somebody just just just peeing
themself with just just no emotion in their eyes whatsoever is one of the
funniest and he was to their balls you know that it was his Pete had huge balls
and a very small penis and so the pee was just hitting the balls he was not
touching his penis at all there was no guidance was it was it his like his
pants were down or it wasn't wearing pants or balls were popping out of his
fly with his penis and he was just sitting there like like just staring at
me he wasn't even like asleep he didn't even he also looked like a normal guy
didn't look homeless at all and he was just peeing at me and looking away what
street was this? 60th. Oh you saw me? Yeah what time? Oh yeah oh man. You guys see those videos that went around a
while ago on there was like a Twitter account where a guy just pees in public
like there's one where he just like he's just Pete just peeing himself underneath
a Burger King table like that's next level I thought they were they were I was
laughing a bunch and then there was one I saw that me I had to stop because he
was peeing in a ball pit. I was like, "Alright, yeah, I'm out."
How does that guy get that close to a ball pit?
I know, right? There have to be some kind of security measures
in place. There need to be defense lasers.
Also, the thing is about a ball pit, there's so much pee in there already.
Right. There's no...
He's fine. They need one of those, like, fucking, like
a minority report, like, computer thing that can just detect if someone has the intent to
pee when they're walking into any definitely kind of children's
established and that's the only way the technology is used we never stop
otherwise yeah anything like that no abduction it's all that if you've seen
minority report you know it ends badly if they're trying to detect murders and
exactly it's snowballs I've never seen minority report but that is a crazy name
for a movie why why is that what the movie's about it's about it's about
time cops really they see that they see crimes before they happen yeah so why
is it called wait why is it called minority report I think Tom Cruise plays
the same character that he played in the last samurai okay yeah I think that
might be the name of the unit or something yeah something like that I
don't get why it's called minority you know you're getting hung up on the wrong
thing you know minority also just means like minority like it doesn't have to
mean like the kind of person that you're scared of or anything. It can just be like
what I mean like a small number. What Tom Cruise?
I'm not. Yeah you're an evil racist. Oh the minority report is when it's a see
yeah it's the report that's in the minority that when they say when they
there's three psychics and they think that two of them think that it's gonna
to happen and then one of them think it doesn't and so that's the minority
report. Damn. I've never wanted to learn about justice more. Yeah. I need to learn
more about justice. Yeah because that's what that movie is, it's justice. Exactly.
It's justice stuff. It's justice for me because I paid $7 to watch it and I enjoyed it.
That's justice. I've been watching a lot of guys grocery games. Oh yeah. Oh yeah.
I've been watching this shit.
Robert Irvine's built like crazy.
Put this boy in a zoo, dude.
He does not belong on TV.
No sir.
Robert Irvine should not be allowed to be on television.
I would hate to be a paparazzi fucking following him around.
You know how many cameras I bet he's smashed, dude?
Mm-hmm.
Dude, imagine if you were...
Plus he killed Anthony Bourdain.
Imagine if you were a...
[laughter]
He did, dude.
Yeah, Anthony, I'm coming to your hotel.
I'm gonna hang you.
Yeah, not right now. I'm eating a cheeseburger.
I'm eating trash off the ground.
I'm eating trash, which is actually a delicacy in a trash can.
Yeah, in Grouchland.
Yeah, I visited Grouchland to try some of their amazing cuisine.
These fried rotten banana peels.
But Robin Hood killed him. Imagine if you were a paparazzi in the 1800s and your
boss assigned you to take pictures of Dracula. Yeah. Wouldn't work. Or anybody.
Here, stay there for an hour. Hold on. Hey old-timey Jennifer Lopez,
what's the boyfriend situation? Also just stay still for like the
next 30 minutes. I'm gonna blow something up in front of you. Just chill.
let me get my light cannon ready yeah and if you can stand do you mind if we wait
for an eclipse be a lot easier if we add an eclipse I'm gonna put my black hood
on now imagine like like you know how like that paparazzi guy died because he
was trying to follow Justin Bieber on the highway yeah nobody can fucking out
just never the beaver imagine imagine doing that I'm like he's in a horse and
buggy with that big 1800s camera trying to follow like Harry Houdini yeah it's
sadly he was trampled today dangerous job in America being a paparazzo yeah that
is one of the most dangerous jobs it is what if you what if you're a paparazzi
and they say okay we want you to take a picture of Azathoth the dark sorcerer
yeah it's like he's gonna kill me if I take a picture okay you're a paparazzi
we need you to go through this oblivion gate we need some pictures of the daedra
we need you to take a photo of the devil can you take a picture of Mehrunes Dagon
for us we've been trying to see what he looks like for so long we're sending you
to hell to take a photo of George Bush this is your next assignment dude that
okay this is our new video game okay okay demon it's like it's like hitman but
you're a paparazzi instead of an assassin and they send you to different
like to hell or like I don't know to hell could be like a bonus mission no no
it's mostly in hell okay hello maybe it was like Tony Hawk's underground or
underground - or whatever or it's like those are like there's no skateboards in
it no but you can go to hell in Tony Hawk's underground - you said we're not
putting skateboards in our gamepad okay it's like boards in it just it would be
nice like we do it's like doom Pokemon snap oh you frame it now that you frame
it like that instead of hitman but all of your favorite celebrities who are in
hell exactly yeah and they're twisted into like horrible demon forms that kind
of like like accentuate like why they were evil exactly yeah see like mm-hmm
like I don't earn a sport nine you see Philip Seymour Hoffman looks like this
the sloth guy from seven he looks like yeah Michael Jackson looks like his dad
there's so many amazing possibilities for this game Michael Richards is just these
he's still alive but he's down there he goes down there to get lessons on how to
be evil yeah say bad words he didn't knew bad words that he can learn to say in
the clubs who else is in hell George Carlin mm-hmm
Mac Miller Mac Miller little peep juice world anybody wrapped obviously yeah
Hitler Hitler there famous right and Hitler the rapper both of them in hell
yeah from the Parappa games right yeah the rapper was was the less successful
successful brother of Chance the Rapper. The name didn't catch on.
Or we could do a twist ending where the final one is you have to go take a photo
of Hitler and then you open the door that's like Hitler's house and he's not
in there. And you look up and he's looking down at you from a cloud.
From heaven where he has a glass floor and he's like "Jeeeee."
He's in one of those glass bottom boats that you like look at at Sea Life and
he's leading a tour of hell true yeah I this is the paparazzi who is mean to me
or what if what if okay what if you see you have to take a picture of Hitler you
go to his room the root the door that says like Hitler's room oh you open it
up mirror hmm you were Hitler the whole time you were oh my god and they've been
trying to get you to go to hell for so long and the only way that you find out
is because you can't see yourself in the mirror. Because he was a vampire. Because he was also a vampire.
That's a very good point. And he was a Jedi. Or a Sith. Which one is bad? He was a
Sith. Oh. What? Oh. Never mind. Something happened. The other day we were celebrating Neil's birthday and Pat
talked about Star Wars for an hour and a half and I kept just hearing him talk
about Star Wars again and again. It was kind of amazing.
Joe and Alex were asking me about it.
And apparently it all stemmed from
somebody saying the word "Garagu"
and then Pat just had
like a beautiful mind
moment. You have to, dude, he hasn't been
around people for months. You're right.
You need to let him get that stuff out.
That's a good point, yeah. But dude, when you see
me again, you are not going to be able to shut
me up for one second about literally anything.
You are not going to believe how much I'm going to suck your penis when I see you.
It's been so long.
yeah yeah I'm just gonna be an absolute monster on the hog I keep I keep
forgetting to buy like god damn I have so much shit I have to get for the place I
keep forgetting to buy like floss sticks and I keep wearing my mask to go out in
public floss sticks? my breath stinks my breath has been stinking yeah there's like there's
this flossing sticks you know those you're not buying just buy a floss? no the
floss sticks are you a three-year-old? dude the floss sticks are way better oh
Oh yeah, they come.
Come on, dude.
Are you kidding me?
Are you four years old, maybe?
No.
What are you talking about?
I'll draw the line at five.
Okay, no, yeah, that's not gonna like, it's not gonna hurt my feelings, but like, please
don't go any younger than four.
Like I'm already, like, like three might actually hurt my feelings, but floss sticks are better
than floss.
Yeah.
It's good, they're good for like one time if you get sucked on the chicken nuggets.
Actually, like, yeah, like, you know, the dinosaur chicken nuggets are like better than
the normal chicken nuggets.
They are, though.
That's actually true.
They have a cooler mouth feel, and also you can pretend that you've killed a dinosaur.
- You are two years old.
- You are so wrong.
You are geriatric.
- Yeah, you're the oldest man of all time.
How's that feel?
- I'm normal.
I'm old and wise.
- No.
- Yeah.
- No, you're not.
- No.
- Yeah, wise potato chips.
- You guys are like two months old,
and I'm gonna take your soft spots,
and I'm gonna take one of your heads in each hand,
and I'm gonna bash you together,
and I'm gonna flatten your soft spots,
and you guys are gonna be stuck together like a molecule.
- I don't care as long as I die high.
- Yo.
I'm like potato chips 'cause I be in my bag.
(laughing)
- No.
- No, you're not in your bag.
- You don't be in your bag.
- No, your bag doesn't exist.
Show me the bag.
- I'm like potato chips 'cause I be in my bag
and I just stay crisp and clean.
- No.
I'm like potato chips 'cause I'm in your mom's
fuckin' mouth, dude.
- I'm like groceries 'cause I'm so fresh
I just might be your dinner tonight.
Okay. I'm just like groceries.
Please stop, you're making me hungry for groceries.
I'm like groceries because I'm going to eat you up.
Or you're going to eat me up.
What are you talking about?
I'm like a car because I'm going to drive you.
Who's head was that beeping going off in the background of their audio like every five seconds?
It's Caleb.
It's been going for a long time.
I know.
That was my humidifier.
So thank you for reminding me to get one of those.
People are going to be so mad at you when this episode comes out.
No they won't.
fifteen minutes it was showing up on my on my my WAV my wave WAV so I was like
I'm safe you just heard you there was a beeping in your room you thought I just
won't turn it off I'll just no I only heard it once I thought that it was
outside I'm so smart about audio I'm smart if you complain about audio quality
on a podcast yeah honestly you're a fucking pussy
You'll bust her.
Just shut up.
You'll bust her as hell.
Yeah.
Just shut the fuck up.
If you're listening to a podcast on anything where you can actually discern the quality,
you better be listening to this on your phone speakers on the subway.
Yep, out loud.
This is either phone speakers on the subway or like your iPod headphones from like 2011
where one of the ear foot buds is cut off.
Exactly.
It doesn't, it only plays at one volume, at 100 volume.
- You're sweating, through your hand
in your sweatshirt pocket,
and you listen to it with one hand up to your ear
so no one can tell that you're listening to music.
- Exactly, even though you are a grown man
and you're not at work, you're at home.
- You have to play this from your desktop computer
and then put your home phone next to it
and then call your home phone and pick it up
and then go to work and then have your cell phone
up to your ears so you can hear it playing
from your computer through your phone.
- Okay, so you're gonna need like a bunch of marbles
and a cream pie and some walkie talkies.
And basically you're gonna press,
you're gonna pull a string from your living room
and all the marbles are gonna make
all this awesome racing shit
and then they're gonna press on one of the walkie talkies
and then you're gonna hear a barbershop quartet
that we hired to recite the podcast
after they've listened to it.
And they're gonna talk it to you
through the walkie talk, walkers, talkers.
- Basically what you want is some baking soda
and some vinegar and you're gonna mix them up
and it's gonna make a volcano.
mmm yeah yeah you're gonna need some panko breadcrumbs for chicken breasts a
bottle a bag of oil a bag of oil a can of San Marzano tomatoes a cast iron skillet
and a cast iron fork and knife and a serrano chili and you're gonna make some
of the best chicken parm we've ever had brother shit a serrano chili and chicken
parm it's makes it spicy wouldn't you just use red pepper flakes
- Fuck no.
- It's too dry, dude.
You get more spice out of the fresh chili.
You can use a bird's eye chili too.
- Really?
- I usually just use the chicken in the parm.
I don't do any of the fancy stuff.
- Don't take it from me, man.
- Hey, this mayo-ass white boy ain't putting no spices
on his chicken parmies. - Don't take it from me.
Take it from Emeril Lagasse, okay?
- Oh my God, famous Italian.
- Famous Italian chef.
- Emeril Lagasse.
- Emeril Lagasse is basically Larry the Cable Guy
for Italians.
- Is he Italian?
I thought he was Cajun.
- Yeah, that's what I mean.
He's like, everybody is like, he's basically playing a character.
It's pretty awesome. Have you ever watched his pilot? No. He had a sitcom pilot.
Really? Yeah, two actually. Was it sick? Two film sitcom pirates, pilots. Pirates?
Emeralds, oh my god, Emerald Pirates. He was killed by pirates? That'd be sick. He's still alive.
Uh-huh. Yeah, he is living, unfortunately. We should watch Emerald's pilot.
okay I'm down that sounds uh yeah it's just a lot of cooking jokes so it's about
it's it's about Emeril right that is so why don't they do like like they got to
do like you know Seinfeld type stuff but for other professions that's what it was
that's what it was that's that is exactly what it was it was cooking at
the beginning of every episode yes no no buddy cam that is exactly what it
fucking was really yeah that's so sick what kind of food jokes did he make
there's a there's there's in the intro of it he's like oh I ate a chili that
was so spicy it was there is like my uvula was a pilot light that wouldn't go
out you ever notice how a potato chip and a chocolate chip look completely
different what's a chip? A chip's a chip! I mean Jesus Christ get it together who
are these people deciding what a chip is? Is there a committee of chips? Is there a chip council?
And why am I not on it? I eat more chips than anyone. Why would Emeril do that voice?
Because he's a sitcom voice. You gotta do like a Cajun Seinfeld.
okay
to buy you. How come when I go to the bayou, I'm doing only bayou jokes too? Bayou? Bayou?
I live by the bayou! It doesn't make any sense! I'm down at the bayou but it's by me! How
come? How about I buy you a ticket on my riverboat tour? Which I get! That's my job! I'm doing
it right now! How come when something comes out of a swamp it's a creature but when it
comes from a bog it's a monster oh that's fucking I had maybe you have to pee so
bad for every time I do the Seinfeld voice I have a sharp pain in my penis I
have to go baby I'll be right back guys the river Delta Delta's a damn airline
why do you think I love I love Seinfeld like his major bit at least in my brain
is like things cannot share the same name that makes no sense at all yeah I miss
him also dead also in hell he's so dead yeah also we'll be so funny how he just
became Seinfeld just became like think you're too far from your mic patch
Seinfeld became like the most out of touch person in the world well just like
yeah I mean his whole...
No I know I know I know
You think he was like in touch?
Yeah at least for a little bit
You think he had his finger on the pulse?
Yeah his observations were at least like
Oh the train sucks
Here's why the train sucks
Now it's like how come when I fly first class
That was so cutting edge back then too
That was a really weird of the time
People were like I guess the train does suck
Shit he's such a genius
I've never
said that Seinfeld was cutting-edge or anything I'm just saying it's like it's
extremely funny how like all of his I like cuz he's an observational comic and
all of his observations just became like oh yeah fuck it like it sucks when my
private jet pilot looks at me it's crazy how out of touch the Queen of England is
these days it's such it's so that's not even that is not even comparable to what
I said. Okay that okay now how about that?
Okay all right you made your point I get it. Yeah you're welcome all right I
have to pee I've done too much Seinfeld voice. Yeah bye you guys. Bye.