You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[Laughter]
[Explosion]
Why did you wait before saying zero?
Why didn't you do--
I have to keep you on your toes.
Okay, it's just going to be harder for you to edit.
No, it'll be easy for me.
I haven't even pressed record yet.
That's--
Why not?
You can't be telling the truth.
I'm not even--
You have to be lying.
Guys, it's 2021.
It's 2021.
Yay.
Year of the frog.
Year of the golf, dude.
Year of Sullivan.
I'm sitting here drinking an Armold Palmer.
Armold?
That's his name, Armold Palmer.
Armold Palmer.
He's one of the greatest golf players.
Caleb's over here saying "Erma-gurd."
I'm drinking an Armold Permer.
Erma-golf, dude.
'Cause I'm in golf mode.
I'm ready, dude.
Is that your new thing for the new year?
My new thing for the new year?
Your new one week thing?
Yeah, my new thing is I'm gonna start
taking cocaine at 8 a.m., I'm gonna cheat on my wife,
drinking Michelob Ultras, I'm dry popping a cigar inside.
That was your stop me, dude.
Your dry pop--
Get that thing out of your mouth.
Yeah, no.
Take the cigar out, it looks--
I refuse.
I will not refuse.
Get it out of your mouth.
Light it or get it out of your mouth.
It's disrespectful.
- You can't light it inside, dude.
- Well then don't, then get it out of your mouth.
- I'm a paid member of this club.
You think I wanna get kicked out?
- That shit looks like Dookie.
- You pay to be a part of your family?
- Yeah.
- I gotta stop recording these when I woke up an hour before.
- An hour is plenty of time for an adult to wake up.
- You should also stop waking up at that time.
You should just wake up earlier.
- Yeah.
- We planned we were gonna record at this time.
- Yeah, I know, but I woke up
and I couldn't get back to bed.
- I don't think I've slept in a long time.
- Yeah. - I think that's not true.
- You just kinda sit up, just waiting,
waiting for something to happen, you know?
I'm just-- - Caleb goes to sleep
at 8 p.m. and then he wakes up and he sees the clock
says 8 a.m. and he thinks, I didn't sleep at all.
Oh my God. - Exactly, yeah.
I think someone just turned the lights on.
- Yeah. - I couldn't sleep last night
'cause I was so excited for my drives today.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I'm living the line-- - What's your favorite
part of golf?
- Dude, it has to be the course.
- Have you been golfing before?
- No. - Okay.
Today's gonna be my first day at the Wilmington
Municipal Golf Course.
I'm paying 30 bucks, I'm putting money on the line here.
Yeah.
I borrowed a bunch of clothes from my stepdad.
I have a Boston hat on.
I have a cigar that I stole from my grandpa.
Yeah, you look like all of my uncles right now.
Dude, yes!
That's cool.
I just bought an Arnold Palmer light at the dollar store.
That reminds me guys, I have really good,
I just learned a new story about my dad's cousin
that's really exciting explain yes so
i don't know what
i was my business story but my dad's cousin you go you get here
well you guys are gonna like this
uh...
i don't know what i don't know what my dad's cousin is to me so i like my
something cousin
my hair that's your dad's cousin exactly he uh... he lives in new hampshire
uh...
mhm think uh...
uh... was a cause it
whatever it's like a he's like north new hampshire and i'm
and he bought one of his kids a pig,
like as a pet.
- That's gangster.
- It grew gigantic, like humongous,
and then his wife left him and took the kids,
and then he just stayed in the house with this giant pig,
and the pig won't go outside, it hates going outside,
so it lives in the house.
and they turned the electricity off,
and they turned the heat off,
and so he sleeps with the pig.
The pig got too big so it couldn't get onto his bed,
so he cut the legs off of his bed
so he could sleep with the pig.
- I thought you were gonna say
he cut the legs off of his pig.
- And so he lives with this pig, right?
And then they finally, the police had to come
and get him out of the house,
so he bought a trailer,
and now he lives in a trailer with a pig.
- With his best friend pig.
and the pig is like really, I guess like temperamental,
so it's like chewed up, it's ripped up all the linoleum
inside the trailer and like chewed up all the furniture.
And it'll like, apparently like if he's eating food
and the pig wants food, it'll like throw a tantrum
and like start freaking out.
And it still hates going outside, so it has a litter box
and he has to like, if he wants to get it outside--
- Oh, a fucking litter box?
- Dude, pigs are fucking huge too.
- He has to, yeah, he has to push it down a ramp
out of the trailer and apparently one time it was like sick and he wanted to take it
to the vet and the vet was like "no we don't treat pigs, they're livestock, we don't do
that here" and he begged the vet to take it and then so I was like "okay fine" and he
took the pig to the vet but the pig was really scared of the vet so it didn't want to go
Inside so we had to stand behind it and push it
And it was like it was like squealing and apparently pig squeals are like insanely loud yeah jet engine loud
So there's a bunch of people sitting in the best way to like
Noodles and shit yeah, just like covering their ears for the pig is just screaming and being pushed
That's like in that's like a fucking your ghost Lanthimos movie. Yeah, that's not I don't know what my dad
My dad just told me about this like a day or two ago.
I don't know why he didn't tell me before.
- Why does he, does he visit this cousin in the pig?
- He does.
- Do you have to pay your respects
to the pig when you visit?
- You do.
- I've, he's a French guy.
I've not seen this cousin since I was very little.
- Dude, we might have to make a,
we might have to make a trek.
We have to go see this fucking pig, dude.
- Yeah, I gotta find out where this guy lives.
- I can show you a video of the pig
when it was not full grown on Instagram.
The thing is pigs don't stop growing.
They grow forever.
They get gigantic.
Yeah.
I was saying that pig's gonna eat him someday.
Definitely dude.
Pigs love human flesh.
Yeah.
They'll eat any guy that they see.
They think it's funny.
Here's a picture of the pig when it wasn't fully grown.
That's already a huge pig.
It's giant.
No, it's huge.
Yeah.
How the fuck does that thing live in a fucking trailer?
I know, dude.
How does that live in a trailer?
Dude, can you imagine?
- Can you imagine, your family leaves you
and you live with a pig, it's so cool.
- In a trailer, and also you get up to go to the bathroom
and because the trailer isn't wide enough,
the pig is just in the way.
And because the pig also is kinda alpha-dogging you,
you just have to wait for him to decide to move.
'Cause there's no way that there's a 400 pound pig
and you're like, all right,
you gotta get the fuck out of my life, right?
You just have to wait for him to make his own decisions, dude.
- The pig's name is Sunny, by the way.
- Sunny.
- Sunny the pig, dude. - Yeah, Sunny the pig.
- Wow. - Yeah.
Pretty good, right?
I was really excited to tell you guys that one.
- That's really good, dude.
That's really good.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
You learn anything about your cousins
this Christmas Eve, Patrick?
- Yeah, all of them have cancer.
- Dude. - Swag!
- Swag, dude! - No.
None of them have cancer.
- Oh, that's sweet. - Swag!
- Swag, that's great news! - Even better!
- Congratulations. - So much better.
- Dude, I guess the only thing I could think of better
than my cousins having cancer
is that they don't have cancer.
- Yeah, one of the only things better.
- Did they get cured?
- No, they never had it.
- Oh, come on.
- They got cured with a time machine.
- Oh, that's cool too.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah, basically one of my cousins
invented a time machine and cured cancer,
brought the cure back.
- Dude, I want a time machine so bad right now.
If I had a time machine right now, I would--
- I would time machine back before you asked me this question
and think of a better joke.
- I wouldn't.
- Oh my God.
- Wow.
I would, personally, I wouldn't probably stop any
like horrible thing in history.
I'd probably just skip to my tea time, 2.39.
- Yeah.
Well, five minutes before, that's common courtesy.
How many holes in one are you gonna get?
- Probably, how many holes are there?
- 18. - 18.
- I'm gonna hit 18.
- Yeah.
- Hole in one, dude.
- Birdies, bogeys, or golf boys.
- I'm gonna be picking my bogeys
and flying them like a birdie.
(laughing)
Right, all across the course.
I'm flicking these bogeys left and right.
- I'm picking a bogey.
- That's what the caddy's supposed to do.
- If the caddy says bogey, I'm gonna say,
what the fuck did you just call me?
What was that?
I'm gonna do that every time.
- Yeah, a bogey, you feed your bogeys to the birds,
to the birdies.
- I told you guys that my friend used to have a fish
named booger yeah everybody's gonna feed him boogers I'm a booger yeah that's
that's a pretty good I do you think that would work with that pig you feed him
boogers you feed him boogers and earwax he loves it yeah he's a fucking dead
that's how you make it that's how you grow like an evil pig that would like
poison its soul pigs are like pigs it's like one of those things it's like it's
- It's like in a fantasy movie or something
when it's like, oh, the wizard got corrupted
by evil magic and he turned into a monster.
Like, that's how you make like a dark pig
is you feed it boogers.
- Do you think he'll get a--
- The wizard got corrupted by a pig?
- I hope he gets obsessed. - Yeah, you.
- Whoa, oh my God, dude.
- You're the wizard. - Please don't cry.
Please don't cry.
- Yeah, you're the wizard.
- So I was thinking, next time we meet up to record
maybe a golf trip, who knows?
Depends on how the day goes.
I don't fucking--
My plan is me and my brothers are gonna get
really good at golf the next three days
and then we're gonna challenge my dad.
Yeah.
Yeah, for his car.
Well, golf is just like really big pool, right?
That's what I'm saying.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Ask me tomorrow though, I might say that--
Balls and green and holes.
I might say that pool is just little golf.
I might have switched sides.
Really?
Dude, it's just gonna be so easy.
I think I have a natural talent.
Yeah.
Have you played it yet?
but I think I, but mentally I've been looking up different things.
Why don't you, here, take a swing, get up.
You want me to take a swing?
Let's see it, let's see your swing.
Let's see it.
Use the, yeah, use the mic.
You gotta use your, gotta make your wrist straight.
Wrist straight.
And then I pull back, follow through.
And you guys couldn't see it,
but I did actually pivot my foot,
which is one of the main five things
that I've learned from the YouTube video.
Let's get a few more swings, get back up.
Just keep swinging the rest of the episode.
Okay, alright, you guys do the episodes, I'll just swing.
Alright.
Every time I've played golf, I've uh...
I mean, I've played golf like a couple times.
I always do the Happy Gilmore thing.
Yeah?
I've been to like a driving range before,
but I've never like played golf besides mini golf.
Yeah, that's what I mean by mini golf.
I do Happy Gilmore shit at the mini golf rink.
Oh yeah.
Me too, man.
I do like Caddyshack stuff pretty much.
Yeah, you do pranks on a gopher.
Yeah, I do tons of insane SNL crap at the golf course.
of course yeah yeah yeah me and my friends are doing SNL shit at the mall
god damn dude I love being funny like SNL at the mall yeah they kick me out I'm
walking around extremely fat you're telling me this you're telling me auntie
Ann's doesn't sell Cheetos I want a Cheeto that's what I like mm-hmm yeah
give me one of me give me what people are like oh they're like a pretzel that's
That's right, you dumbasses.
I found this account the other day, it's called @cheeto45.
Swag.
And it's only one tweet from 2009, and it says, "I'm enjoying my day off."
Whoa, do you think his name was Cheeto45 in 2009?
No, his name's Robin Jones.
Oh, fuck, dude.
That's Robin Williams' brother.
Yeah.
woman named Robin? No. I just said what it was. I don't know. That's actually pretty
rare to have a woman. A woman named Robin? Yeah, it doesn't really happen for the
most part. I'm pretty excited to not see a girl on the golf course also. Yeah. Yeah.
A woman disrespecting. Dude, if I see a woman's midriff today I might lose my
mind. What kind of shoes you're gonna wear on the golf course? Bowling shoes.
What kind of pants? Black pants. I already have them on, dude. I have the entire, I'm
wearing the shirt I'm wearing a purple polo a three-quarter zip I have a Boston
Red Sox hat on let's see it I do I showed you didn't know the hat dude I mean what
show the hat do you think I'm faking over here yeah you guys think I'm a poser
don't you do you badmouth Boston you're a second you get out of Boston yeah you
were goth a week ago and now you're golf hey I yes yeah yeah yeah that's a you're
You're right, that is an interesting switch.
Caleb is just into odd future.
I never, no.
That's why he likes golf.
I'd like to iterate, I never stopped being golf.
I'd like to reiterate for the first time.
You never stopped being golf?
You stopped being into golf?
What are you into now?
No, listen to me.
So he went from goth to golf, so next he's going to be a wolf?
I'm deciding to mix the goth and golf lifestyle into one thing.
It's called synergy.
at a business school where I went.
You went to business school?
Why'd you go to business school?
To get better at golf?
Who the fuck is starting a business?
What accent was that, Caleb?
It was cigar in my mouth accent.
It's an Arnold Palmer accent.
Are you guys stupid?
No, you are, dude.
You know what, you guys just don't understand
what it's like to have passion.
And to have drive.
And to have a straight drive.
Dude, I mean, whatever.
You guys are putt-putt.
A straight drive is going to Hooters.
Straight drive lifestyle might not make it, dude.
They might have to take me off that course in a stretcher.
I think they probably will.
'Cause I had too many Michelob Ultras,
which I just picked up a 30 rack of, by the way.
You fell over and got your ear stuck in the hole.
I just picked up a 30 rack.
I just picked up a fake, no.
They're not gonna have to get me out of the hole
with the jaws of life, that's not gonna happen.
You're gonna fall over and the flag is gonna go
into one ear and come right out the other
and you're gonna be stuck on the ground.
- I just picked up a pill from a gas station called Adol.
(laughing)
It's called Adol XR and it's gonna get me through
an intense-- - Yeah, Adol.
- I'm not kidding. - I just realized.
I just realized.
- There is a pill at the gas station down the street
that they sell called Adol XR.
- Damn.
- And it's about to power up my golf game.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Dude, my swings are gonna be insane.
My rotator cuff has never been in better shape.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I'm serious.
- I don't believe you.
- I don't believe you either.
I'm gonna send you guys a video, dude.
- Please do, send it.
- I'm gonna send you so many videos.
- You should stream from the golf course.
- Dude, I might. - That's not a bad idea.
- I might have to show the world because it seems--
- This will come out after you go golfing, though.
- Well, now that I've-- - By the time this comes out,
you won't be into golfing anymore.
- I will, I think I've learned a new lifelong passion.
- You said you're gonna play golf for three days, right?
- Mm-hmm.
- This comes out more than three days from now.
- But I'm gonna train, I'm gonna challenge my dad.
- Okay, where are you gonna golf
when you get back to New York, Trump Links?
I might go to Trump Links.
You could go to Trump Links.
I could go to Trump Links.
It is really close.
It is the only golf course I've seen.
It is really close to where you live.
It's probably across the street.
I think, yeah, I live in the Hudson River.
You could just walk across the highway to get to Trump Links.
I think there's a-
You put your arms out, holding a golf club in the air.
Stop for me, do not hit me.
I'm going to Trump Links.
I would go to Trump Links and I would just sit there.
I'd just gum up the works.
Just fucking-
- Just shoot one foot at a time.
Sabotage those rich pieces of shit.
- Yeah, and Donald Trump will be behind you saying,
and no one ruined Trump links more than Caleb.
I'm owned, I'm completely owned.
- He'll be saying that that is praxis.
- Wow, that's praxis, wow.
- Trump hates praxis is the thing.
- Dude, he hates it, dude.
He gets so mad. - Praxis is what defeats him,
and he gets really mad when it happens.
- When someone does something praxis,
like reading a book or making an online blog post.
- Giving an ice cream cone to a young child.
- And also he's such a baby,
he might even crap his pants, pretty shit.
- Oh, if a baby does praxis.
- Folks, nobody hates praxis more than me.
- Now that Joe Biden is president,
we can do as many Trump impressions as possible.
- Sex work is not work.
It's just a hobby.
Golf is work.
- It's a game.
- It's just a game that women play.
- It's just people playing games.
- That was an interesting kind of like
older Woody Allen take on Trump.
- I'm Donald Trump.
- Hello.
- Yeah.
- Excuse me. - Hello.
- Well excuse me.
- Lady.
- Urkel Trump. - Lady.
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna grab you by the.
(laughing)
- Whoa.
- He would have, Jerry would have never said that.
- No, it's Donald Trump.
- Donald Trump would have, oh he did say that, whoops.
But yeah, I'm ready to do stuff like that.
I'm ready to talk, I'm ready to talk with my friends
in the golf locker room.
- You're ready to talk like Jerry Lewis?
- I'm gonna talk like Jerry Lewis.
I'm gonna walk around with a cigar.
I'm gonna pretend I know everybody
'cause that's how you dominate them mentally on the course.
You walk in, you say, hey, what's up?
What's up, Chet?
- Hey, what's up?
Yeah, how's the missus? - Good to see you, buddy.
How's the swing?
Hey, Derek, Derek, I love what you're doing.
Keep doing it.
- Hey, Ricky, off the course.
- Fred, Jose, if I see you again, I'm kicking your ass.
- Yeah, I don't want you here.
is my course.
- This is my public golf course, the only one.
- I get onto the golf course and I take out a megaphone,
I say, "Attention, everybody,
"I just purchased this golf course, it belongs to me.
"You're gonna get off, this is my backyard now."
- Welcome to Pits Links, dude.
Fucking suck my dick or get off.
$100,000 buy-in.
- Caleb, I don't know if the online leftist community
is gonna like you being a golf guy.
I don't think they want you to,
- They wanna turn all the golf links.
- You know golf is a waste of--
- It's a waste of land.
- It's a waste of land and it's a waste of being
on the left politically.
That's fine 'cause I also just bought 30 drums of crude oil
and I'm about to just dump it all over the field.
- It could be, I mean the golf course that you're going to
could be affordable housing for inmates.
- And they could use the water
to like feed a thousand fishes too.
- It's about to be affordable housing
for a bunch of chill guys enjoying drugs on a Sunday.
so, 'cause it's a $30.
- It's affordable playing.
- Exactly, dude.
- We don't need more housing.
- No, we need more playing, less housing.
- People can live on a tent in the street,
they do that already, it works.
- People can live in a trailer with a pig,
they can do a lot of things, dude.
- But can you play on the sidewalk?
- No. - No disrespect
the resolve of humanity. - Unless you're doing
urban golf, and it's 2006. - Unless it's like
urban hopscotch. - It's urban hopscotch.
(laughing)
- That's cool.
- What's that?
- I don't know Patrick, what is that?
- Hopscotch, backwards hat. - You said that, I mean.
- No I didn't.
- Yeah you did. - You said that Patrick.
You just said that.
- You said urban hopscotch.
- You said that first.
- Can we stop saying the word urban?
I'm wearing this Red Sox hat and it's giving me anxiety.
(laughing)
I'm getting really worried.
I keep looking out at my car and making sure it's locked
every time you guys say urban.
My Hyundai Tucson that I have.
- 'Cause you're wearing a three quarter zip and a polo.
- Yeah I might just, now that I'm looking at it dude,
I might just use my, I might just pop the trunk
with the button on the keys,
'cause that's one of the features
of the Hyundai Tucson that I have.
Are you gonna be driving a golf cart when you get there?
You know, if you're freaking out,
if you're freaking out from wearing the hat,
why don't you just go, why don't you go to Lidz
and just get a Scali cap or something,
get like one of those like--
Yeah.
The Lidz Scali caps?
Yeah, the Lidz Scali caps.
With the sticker on it.
The New York Yankees Scali cap, the 50/50?
- No, it would be a Boston one.
- No, we're not in North Carolina, dude.
- Maybe this problem isn't fixed.
- I'm really worried that somebody might see
a glimpse of a tattoo and I'll get kicked out of golf.
- Yeah. - Yeah, I'm pretty worried
about that. - Here's the solution.
You get a tattoo, you get all your tattoos
covered up to be golf balls.
- If you have a tattoo, you can't be buried
on a golf course. - That's true.
- Yeah, you're not allowed to be buried in a golf--
- The holes on the golf course is where
they bury leprechauns.
- Fuck.
- That's why the golf course is green.
- I'm about to bury some of these white balls
in those holes, dude.
- Yeah, I'm gonna bury my white balls.
- I'm burying, listen, I'm taking it to the course
and I'm burying these white balls.
I'm pretty excited, dude.
I might buy a Porsche today.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I don't know, man.
I think I've become a different guy
very recently in the last couple hours.
- You were goth a week ago.
- Yeah.
- And the thing is about being goth is that it's childish.
- Okay, so we have confirmation that you think
you're not goth anymore.
- I actually just decided right now.
- You said you were synthesizing them earlier.
- Yeah, and I decided that they're unsynthesizable.
- What made you decide that?
- Because I put the eyeliner on
and it was blocking my vision of golf.
- You didn't do that.
- I did do that.
- You never played golf.
- You never wore eyeliner either.
- I never wore eyeliner or played golf.
- I'm actually running a physics simulation in Blender
of what golf will be like when I'm golfing.
- Of what eyeliner looks like.
- Yeah, of what eyeliner does to a golfer's body.
And it actually is a, it's actually a detrimental
to golf performance. - I'm actually looking at
like a deviant art simulation right now
of like what it would look like to golf
if you had a giant bouncing belly.
And it seems very sexual.
- Yeah. - It seems like it actually.
- There's a lot of Caleb. - It seems actually
really cool.
- There's a lot of Caleb Pitts and Prague deviant art stuff.
- Yeah. - There's not.
- I'm actually, I'm running a simulation right now
to see what it would look like if their Pikachu was trapped
inside of Sonic's stomach.
It's beautiful.
- It's actually the miracle of life.
- Yeah.
- I don't know.
- Yeah, I can't, my wife's pregnant
and I'm gonna cheat on her today at the golf course.
- With the hole.
The hole is the girl who works there.
- That's how leprechauns are born, right?
Is that you fuck the golf hole
and then a leprechaun comes out in nine months.
- That's how I was born, 'cause I was born to golf.
- You're not a leprechaun.
- Yeah, my mother was Mother Earth.
- I'm looking at some-- - Through the golf course.
- Evian art and preg gifts right now.
- Stop looking at disgusting stuff and golf with me, dude.
- Well-- - You'll fly me out.
- Okay, you know what golf stands for?
- What? - And preg football.
- Gentlemen's only life fun.
- Gentlemen's enjoying life fancily.
Yeah. Green old, green old leaves and friends.
Golfing, awesome, lovely fun.
Great old life to fulfill.
Just, just, just, just awesome, loving fun.
Great old, great old laughing friends.
I love golf.
You guys want to play golf? Yeah.
Great old laughing friends.
How about we throw on an episode of Mind of Mencia?
Let's do a Jeff Dunham special.
Yeah, Mind of Mencia, me, I need the awesome, fun,
my favorite, favorite show is a show called Mind of Mencia.
Wow, that's good.
Yeah, I think my new favorite comedian,
I mean, it's gotta be Tiger Woods.
(laughing)
- Yeah, it's gotta be the Tiger Woods.
- You know, he's not that funny, but his swing.
- Yeah.
I mean, it's funny that he did--
- It's funny that his wife hit him with a golf club.
'Cause that's the last thing a golfer is expecting
is for your weapon to betray you.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah, you know that came out of left field to him.
He was like, what have you done?
- Left field?
You mean the green?
- Yeah, left green. - Come on, man.
- Left, the left side of the green is what I meant.
- Yeah, you're right.
- Yeah, I'm really sorry.
- You're a fake golfer.
- I'm sorry dude, I need to take a Xanax, dude.
- Do you, have you done mini golfing before?
- I'm about to play many different rounds of golf.
- Have you not played mini golf before?
- 18 to be exact.
- I've played mini golf, dude.
- So, okay.
- Come on, who do you think I am?
- Well, you said you'd never played golf before.
I would assume you would at least put,
say something about whether you played mini golf.
- Well, because I take golf so seriously,
I actually have decided that mini golf is not golf.
- What would you do if you saw Bill Murray?
Anything isn't the main thing.
A miniature horse is not a horse.
- What would you do if you saw Bill Murray
at the golf course?
- Beat him.
- Yeah?
- At golf.
- Okay.
- Easily, without him blinking.
- All right.
- Would you also beat him physically?
- No, dude, he's an old man.
I don't wanna, and also, I don't wanna end up
in a Zombieland situation.
- Okay.
I haven't seen Zombieland in so long.
- He's a, I don't remember.
- He's in there and they go like, "Bill Murray?"
Yeah, and it's kind of a lesson to all comedians
that a prank might get you killed one day.
Does he get killed from a prank in that movie?
He pretends to be a zombie or something, right?
And then they kill him for real?
I don't know, I haven't seen that since it probably came out.
Well, I think it might be my new favorite movie.
Is that true?
Yeah, actually I think, you know what my favorite movie's
gotta be, The Longest Yard.
No, that's not--
Is that a golf movie?
No.
It's gotta be the--
Are there golf movies?
Yeah, there's the greatest game ever played
- Starring Shia LaBeouf. - There's Caddy Shaq,
obviously.
- Do you guys think that I'm up to snuff
for the beautiful game?
- Here, okay, popular movies about golf.
- Yeah, greatest game ever played.
- Seven Days in Utopia.
- Happy Gilmore.
- The Short Game, Tommy's Honor,
the greatest game ever played,
Who's Your Caddy, From the Rough,
The Legend of Bagger Vance.
- Nice. - Birdie and Bogey.
I coulda guessed that one.
- How 'bout The Legend of Baggy Pants?
- Walt Disney's Donald's Golf Game.
- Yeah, that might be the one for me.
- Practicalgolf.com, the definitive list of golf movies.
I guess we shouldn't do a list, huh?
- Sieve the movie?
- I think I'm gonna get into Impractical Jokers
and learn all their names.
- There are more golf movies than I expected.
- Yeah, you know what, Caleb?
You could be like Dorf.
You could be like Dorf on golf.
- I don't know who Dorf is.
Just look up Dorf 'cause he's your height.
Nope.
He's the same height as you.
Oh, he's like an inch taller than you?
That's cool.
No.
Yeah.
You look like Dorf.
Not with my golf shoes on,
the spikes give me an extra inch.
You look like Dorf.
You do look like Dorf.
That's the whole reason I like it.
I'm gonna get into ballroom dancing,
girl stuff.
No, no, I mean in the face.
In the face, you look like Dorf.
I don't look like Dorf.
You know, I look like Phil Mickelson.
No, you look like Dorf.
I look like Rory McIlroy.
Who?
- So, you would know who that was.
He's a golfer. - Well, why don't you tell us?
- He's basically one of the best golfers.
He's hit tons of wins, and he's got--
- Oh, dude, we should watch this movie, "Golf Balls!"
With an exclamation point at the end, from 1999.
- I'll watch any golf movie.
- "When the Penny Tree Golf Club faces closing their doors
"due to rival Bentwood stealing their business,
"John Penny Tree and his daughter Liberty
"fight back with alternative tactics
"to draw a new audience in the raunchy comedy, 'Golf Balls!'"
- John Penny Tree? - This sounds really good.
- Do you eat cigars?
- Yeah.
- Have you been eating it?
I've been kind of chewing on it
and some it's gotten my mouth and now I have a headache.
- No matter what they say, I really liked this film.
It should be put in league with classics
like bikini carwash.
The theme of the broken down business
has been done to death.
Bikini, hotel, drive-in and bistro,
as well as the erotic house of wax.
But this one does it with style.
The use of the diver was brilliant.
I just hope the next generation
can come up with some new ideas
because the bikini ID mail is running short.
They made a film called Bikini Traffic School for Pete's sake.
What is next, Bikini Mining Camp?
Just wait, if they get desperate, they just might do it.
Maybe I should copyright it.
- That's a good idea. - I think--
- That's a good review.
- In my post-game interview today, after I win,
right, after I win the tournament,
when they asked me, "Caleb, first time golfing.
"You came in, you beat some legends.
You beat Fred Flintstone.
Fred Astaire.
Yeah, you beat all these guys.
You beat, I mean, you beat Trippy--
Fred Golf.
You beat Trippy Fred.
And you beat Drippy Fred.
And the entire time, I mean, what do you have to say?
I would say, first off, if you wear a mask, you're gay.
Second off, I'd like to thank Jesus Christ
for giving me the power.
I can do all things through Christ who strengthens me.
Yeah.
- Will you bring your knife to the golf course?
- I'm gonna bring my knife and I'm basically
gonna memorize a bunch of different,
I'm gonna have a new Bible verse
for every single time I swing.
- Wow.
- I'm gonna turn back to the crowd.
- Give us the first one.
- I'm gonna do John 3, 16.
- Just say it, just say it.
- For God so loved the world,
he gave his only begotten or forgotten.
He got, God so loved the world.
- God got it.
- God so loved the world that he got his son.
- God got crazy.
And then I'll give a big thumbs up, you know?
I might do an end zone dance when I win.
Yeah, there's no end zone in golf.
I'm gonna do the Dougie somewhere.
Okay.
Wherever I do the Dougie is the end zone.
Yeah, they should call it the Golfie.
That's right.
What kind of music should I listen to on the course?
Odd Future, dude.
Golf Wang.
Odd Future, I think, is a little too--
They say golf in the songs.
Yeah.
Mm, I don't know if that's enough for me.
- They say golf in the songs.
They make shirts that say golf on it.
- I might listen to like one rap song
that came out when I was in college
and really, and it'll be the only one that I ever know.
Something, kind of rap that they listen to at a wedding.
- Oh, White Iverson, some, no not White Iverson,
but maybe like Congratulations.
- Or like a Black Eyed Peas song, right?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- When I do it, I'll do a bunch of exaggerated
hand movements, you know, and really get into it.
- Ooh, you could dice roll walk, dude.
What's that?
- It's when you like.
- Dude, I could dice roll walk.
That's a really good idea.
My goal is to, I'm trying to get a video on a bar stool.
- Yeah. - Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
I found this other movie that we could watch,
if we wanted, called Hole in One from 2009.
And now it says here,
even though this movie has the tagline,
"American Pie Plays Golf,"
this movie has nothing to do
with the American Pie Presents series.
And on IMDb, it has some plot keywords here.
I think you're going to be interested in these.
Can I guess them?
Plot.
Yeah.
Sex.
Are you going to...
Oh, he froze.
I'm back.
Sorry.
I was thinking of golf.
Quick meditation.
Just guess them so I can say them.
There's 19 of them.
Golf.
That's one of them.
Hole.
Nope.
Getting hole.
Swing.
No.
Green.
Green hole.
Putt.
All right.
I'm going to read these, okay?
Shit!
Shit is one of them.
Lesbian kiss.
*Gasp*
Black comedy.
Golf.
Surgeon.
Bet.
Plastic surgeon.
Girlfriend.
College.
Golf club.
Ball.
Sexual humor.
Student.
Golf ball.
University student.
College student.
University.
Female nudity.
Nudity.
And boy wears eyeglasses.
Wow.
That's good.
That's good that they put that in there so I know never to watch it.
I'm gonna hate boys who wear eyeglasses.
- Dude, I'm gonna make some off-color jokes on the course.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I'm really thinking about it.
I might-- - You should,
you could watch this to get some ideas.
This seems raunchy. - Yeah, and you know,
and you know, you could just make fun
of some of the guys at the office.
- Yeah, I think I might.
I think I might, I might walk in and call my boss
a fat piece of shit, but boy do I love him to death.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Thanks for everything you do for me, man.
Glad we're both rich.
Yeah, it's honestly, it's hard,
it's really hard being rich, you know?
I went, I got a bagel earlier.
- Yeah.
'cause you have to fuel up for the course.
I got a bagel, it was $8.49 for the combo.
But she said $8.49 and I said, huh, $849?
It's pretty cheap for breakfast.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
Are you serious, dude?
Did you say that?
Do you guys wanna see 100 ducks?
Yeah.
You wanna see a $100 bill?
Yeah. Sure.
I'm not even kidding, I have one.
Really?
Pull it up, come on.
I mean, look, look.
Dude, that's paper.
Look at that, dude.
Ben Franklin was a famous golfer.
That's why he...
He golfed? He invented those glasses to
see the hole better.
Yeah, he doesn't even have glasses on here, but you're right.
Well, you know the glasses he invented.
Dude, I'm...
Here's the plan.
I'm gonna
go play golf.
I'm gonna get off. I'm gonna pretend that I'm tired.
You're gonna get off?
- That's the plan, yeah, go hit the locker,
hit the showers, go get off, you know?
- You're gonna jack off in the showers at the golf course.
- What do you think a sauna's for?
Why do you think a sauna has a lock on the door?
- Yeah, why do you think a sauna has rocks in there?
- Yeah, 'cause you get your rocks off.
- You flatten.
- Exactly.
- Oh, that must be, okay.
- So you can burn, you come into the rocks
and then that's what makes all the steam.
- Yeah.
- Kinda makes like, yeah.
- Yeah, that's why it smells so weird in there.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, oh fuck, smells like salt.
(laughing)
- Smells like sulfur, dude. - Going to the doctor
and like, it seems like your lungs are saturated
with like cum.
- I have, there's a thick cum layer.
- Yeah, I've been hitting the YMCA after the golf course.
(laughing)
- It looks like, yeah, it looks like a smoker's lung,
but it's white.
- Yeah, immediately try and change the subject.
Do you like the back nine or the front nine more?
Which one do you like more?
Anyway, I'm gonna go down to Ruth's Chris,
get a prime rib well done,
Throw some 81 steak sauce and ketchup on it.
I'm going back to the YMCA.
No reason.
No reason at all.
Just kind of being normal down there.
I think I gotta go clear my lungs out in the sauna again.
I gotta get back into the sauna.
Yeah, I know you're trying to give me advice, Doc, but I think I'm just gonna go back to
that sauna.
Do you know any doctors who are golfers that maybe you could refer me to?
Because I feel like there's a big difference here.
You're disrespecting me right now.
I guess you're right. You know what? I'm just going to go see a sports scientist.
I'm just going to go visit a sports scientist. I think he'll have a better idea of kind of
what I'm doing.
Sports scientist.
Yeah.
One of those guys who writes books that are like, "The physics of a successful dunk."
It's 80 pages. You get it for your dad. It sits in his bathroom, still in the wrapper
for years until he gives it away.
It's like, yeah, well, I don't know anything about your lung,
but did you know that a golf club can move at 10 miles per hour
when you're swinging it?
Gee, Doc, that's nice.
Thanks, Doc.
Yeah, can you prescribe me a Klonopin?
Say no more.
Say no fucking more, dude.
I don't mean to derail and go back to this hole-in-one movie,
but I'm reading the user reviews
and I've just found out what the plot is,
and I think the tags really kind of buried the lead here.
Really?
movie is that the main character Eric he loses a bet my brother's name he he
probably the same guy is it about my brother?
oh yeah well just listen to this he loses a golf bet to two weirdos who happen to
be plastic surgeons since he can't pay them the money they then freaking
electrocute him to knock him out and give him hold on tight for this one tits and
that is the whole plot the rest of the film is Eric trying to hide his new
double D's and finding a way of getting rid of them. It's just a it's a it's a
golf a golf guy with a golf movie about a guy who gets boobs and has to hide them. Wow.
Well it's gentlemen only ladies forbidden is what golf actually does
stand for so yeah so walking around with your tits out dude yeah yeah especially
as a golfer dude if I see a Bernie Sanders sticker today on a fucking car
I'm gonna go ballistic yeah I'm gonna break some windshields you can and they
won't get mad at you well they can't do them higher status in them I'm a golfer
mm-hmm the upper echelon listen to this review so I heard it is not a part of
of the famous American Pie series.
But, being a collector, I ought to watch it.
(laughing)
- A collector of American Pie?
- Yeah, dude.
- Not much of a story present,
but when half-baked characters play ball
with the sinister intention of overtaking
a low-profile clothing firm, the plot goes awry.
Fake boob transplants cause the lead character
and his friend to set on a quest to collect 50 grand.
The supporting cast play their farce balls
to create gross humor.
Other than some flesh show, horseplay, and slapstick,
it has nothing more to consider.
Bottom line, if you're a fan or collector
of such run-down teen movies, give it a try.
If you're not, stay away.
And the last line is,
can be watched with a typical Indian family?
No.
(laughing)
- That's what I'm always asking
whenever I watch a movie. - Dude, I would love
to be a collector of those movies
that they try to make you think there's tits
in the movie based on the cover.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- And also it's called like, school fuck.
- Yeah. - Or whatever.
- Yeah. - And then you watch it
and it's just like a, it's just a super bad rip-off.
Yeah, yeah, dude. I need more movies like that. I watch those with my Indian family
Did I might put one on my Android phone and watch it on the course?
Oh, yeah, why you can't watch actually I don't I have a Windows. I have a Windows 10 phone. Yeah. Mm-hmm
I have a I have a golf phone. Yeah, that's right. I
Have a flip up goal. You don't know you don't have that. I do you just say you're Cameron
I just came in the mail. No, it didn't. No, really? Yeah. No, there's only one in the world
There's only one in the world and I have it right here now. They lied to you
There was one in the world till they made mine.
- No.
- Yeah, it's a golf ball and it has one button
and it calls 911.
- No, it calls 1-800-I-love-golf.
- It only calls 911.
- It can only call 911 and I'm allowed to do it
whenever I want.
- Yeah, you call 911 to tell them
that you got a hole in one.
- Yeah.
- That's what 9-1-1 said.
- Are you proud of me, 911?
- Nine means the hole 'cause it has a hole in it.
- Well, nine, one, if one means eight.
- Well, the first nine is the hole, it means hole.
One stands for in and one stands for one.
So it means hole in one.
Yep.
That's so true.
Nine, no, it's nine for nine iron, one, no.
No.
One.
Listen, we could sit here and argue about
how 911 is related to golf all day.
But what we do know is that it's made for golfers
and it's by golfers.
That's right.
Yeah.
It's, I don't wanna say that.
Yeah, I was about to say it too.
(laughing)
I don't even know what you were gonna say.
- Mm, think about fooboo, but instead of ooh, do guh.
- And say that.
- And now say that.
- Fig big?
- Fug bug.
Fug bug.
- Yeah dude, I'm so excited to start exercising,
I just got my fig big.
It's gonna calculate so much stuff for me.
- I hope people don't make fun of my golf bag
and just call it a fugabug.
- That would, I would get so owned on the course
for something like that.
- That would be disappointing.
- For my little, I don't know man.
I just have to get, I gotta get tuned in
to the golf lifestyle and golf culture.
- Yeah, I agree 'cause you're not--
- I don't mean to, 'cause I'm not there yet,
but I don't mean to dominate, I don't mean to,
do you guys have any sports that you just recently
got into in the last couple hours?
Nope. No. Are you serious? I mean, I don't talk about it much, but I've been a, uh, I've
played croquet my whole life. Yeah, I'm really, I'm really into bocce, but you don't hear me
like, yeah, like tooting my own horn on the show. I mean, I, I tend to like, you know,
view the show as someplace, some way to like entertain the fans and like give back to them
instead of just like going on for like 40 minutes about my own personal interests and
like kind of like dominating the entire episode but I'm sorry you guys why I'm
sorry I am can you take that can you take that
out of your mouth I know you feel bad but you don't have to put poop in your mouth
just because you're a cigar and taste amazing it looks like a Cuba it looks
like a big it looks like a big shit it doesn't look like a big shit it looks
- It looks like a bunch of delicately wrapped tobacco leaves.
- It looks like-- - No, it's delicately
wrapped poop leaves.
- Come on, dude, we're trying to do
a family-friendly thing here.
- A family-friendly thing.
- Come on, dude.
- Oh yeah, a family-friendly thing, sure.
That makes sense.
- All right, well what do you guys wanna talk about?
If you don't wanna talk about my cracked swing
and how fucking swag I am.
- I'm gonna crack you with one swing.
- How much of a beast I am, dude.
- Amen.
I'm gonna turn to a beast and crack you.
I'm gonna throw my little towel on your head.
My little golf towel that sits on my bag,
it's going on your head and you won't be able to see.
I'm gonna eat you in one bite.
I'll eat you in one bite.
Yeah, you couldn't eat me.
I'll cover you in my mouth.
No, no, you definitely couldn't eat me in one bite.
I think I might be able to see an alligator
on the course today and make a viral video.
I'm gonna throw my mouth over you like a net, Caleb.
- Mm-mm, mm-mm.
(laughing)
Wrong sport.
- You know, maybe I'm into fishing.
- No, you don't, no, no, no, no, no.
You don't get to fucking switch it
in the middle of the episode.
- Why? - No.
- Why, 'cause, dude, I'm a fisherman,
and I'm always doing one. - No, you're not a fisherman.
- I was born a fisherman. - You're not, no, no.
- How many times have you fished?
- Like, like three or four times.
- I fish more than that. - You're not a fisherman.
- I mean, I've caught a shark before.
No.
You've never-- what the fuck are you talking about?
I caught a great white shark.
Caleb's going to be off the show pretty soon.
I caught a great white shark with a worm
and a piece of dental floss.
You did not catch a great white shark.
I caught him.
I saved thousands of lives.
You never-- you never did that.
You caused thousands of deaths.
Yeah.
You brought the--
Of different fish, yeah.
No.
Because I'm so good at fishing.
A real fisherman never kills the fish.
OK?
All fishermen are real fishermen,
because you've got a reel in your dam.
No, no.
That's exactly what a fake fisherman would say.
You don't know CPR. Yeah I do. Catch pussy and release it. See you were already messed up.
Catch fish with a... okay catch prune... no catch piss off and release.
So you catch the fish you say you're a fucking stupid fish until they start
wriggling around. They don't do that. Throw them back. No. Yeah. It doesn't happen.
So you threw back the great white shark?
No that one I kept.
You put a great white shark back in the water.
So okay let's see it then.
You kept it.
Where is it?
Let's see it.
Well he's huge and it would take a while.
Yeah exactly so it would be really easy to see because it's huge.
I mounted him on a piece of wood and turned him into a billy bass.
Great let's see it.
He sings the shark, he sings the Jaws song.
Okay let's hear it.
He goes, he moves his head and goes, "Donna."
I don't want to hear you sing it, I want to see him do it.
Let's see it.
"Donna, Donna."
Let's see your shark.
He's over there.
He's like right out of frame.
- Turn the camera. - I can't, dude.
I accidentally glued my computer.
- All right, Caleb's not a fisherman or a golfer or a golf.
- You did not glue your computer.
- I spilled a bunch of glue.
I was trying to fix a golf club,
spilled a bunch of glue all over my desk.
- You did not put glue-- - You said you weren't
a golfer anymore.
- Well, that was back when I was.
- So if you're not a golfer anymore,
can you give me your golf reservations?
- Sorry, the PGA Tour's calling me.
Hold on.
- Yeah, you're going on a PGA Tour.
- Hey, what's up, PGA Tour?
Yeah, no, I'll be there.
Yeah, yeah, I'll be on the PGA Tour definitely.
Okay, cool.
Sorry, a little work business I do at Tick Tock.
Yeah, you got one of those Chinese spam calls
and you were trying to figure--
No, no, no, I would not.
I don't know any Chinese.
I couldn't even point the China on a map.
So I can call it back.
Okay.
Here, wait, I'll dial right now.
It's 555.
Okay.
555.
Wait, I don't have my phone open.
Okay, wait, wait.
Hey, 555.
555.
Five, five, five, five.
Five, five, five, five, all right.
Yeah.
I don't believe that's a number.
See, I told you, it's not real.
Well, you know, coronavirus.
So.
You think coronavirus isn't real?
Various things, well, of course not,
but various things are closed because of a different.
But they just called you, so.
They're gonna try and vaccinate me on the course,
and I'm saying no.
(laughs)
I'm gonna hit 'em with a big N-O, dude.
- Yeah, you keep that thing away from my hole.
- Yeah, there's gonna be a big sign that says FEMA camp
that's crossed out and it says golf course underneath
and on like a piece of printer paper.
I'm gonna be like, yeah, you just have to take this,
you just have to put this lava in your arm
and then you can definitely play golf
and we aren't gonna put you--
- Yeah, the first hole is inside this tent.
Get in there.
- Actually, the first hole is that meat grinder over there.
You see that hole?
Yeah, you just jump in that.
- Yeah, just climb to the top of that 5G tower.
The 5G is five golfs.
- Put the 5G ball in your mouth.
- 5Golfing.
- Yeah, you wanna get five good?
- Five good shots.
- You gotta get 5G.
Dude, I mean, I've never loved anything
as much as I love the beautiful game.
- Which game? - You don't love golf.
- Fishing or golf.
I can't remember which one I'm back on.
- See, see, fucking look at this shit.
- Whatever, dude.
- It's pitiful, it's pitiful.
- It's pitsiful.
I'm thinking of getting--
- Maybe that's why that's your last name.
- Yeah, you're Caleb Pitsiful.
- It's not, dude.
Can we just make some New Year's resolutions?
- Nope. - No.
- New Year already passed.
- Exactly.
- Can we make some for next year?
- No. - No.
- I don't wanna make anything with you anymore.
- Yeah. - This is one of the
worst days of my life. - You completely abused
your friendship with us.
- How? - Mm-hmm.
- To talk about golf.
- What do you guys wanna talk about?
- We talked about golf for 47 minutes.
- Are you impressed?
No. No.
Have I proved that I'm a real golfer?
No. No, 'cause now you're
a fisherman or something.
Well.
I can be both, I just decided.
No, you can't.
You can't be both.
Yeah, you already know you can't synergize something
'cause you couldn't synergize golf and golf,
which is probably the easiest thing in the world to combine.
I'm pretty much bi, so.
So now you're something else.
I think I'm even--
That's not even a real thing.
Yeah, now you're this fake thing.
I'm getting in the game by sexual nature.
This thing that doesn't exist, I've never heard of.
- Yeah, I'm gonna become bisexual
instead of golfing or fishing.
- Yeah, I'm bi-golfer-fishual.
- Yep, I'm gonna do both.
- That means I'm golfer-fishual.
- I'm gonna hit the pier.
- That means I golf and I fish.
There's gonna be some scruffy fishermen
tights right next to me. - I'm gonna hit my pier.
- Great day to fish, man.
I'm bisexual.
Do you--
- They're gonna throw you in the water
if you say that to a fisher.
- Got any interest in that?
And they'll be like, "Wait, so you're gay?"
And I'll be like, "No, dude, get this.
I'm gay and I'm straight.
- Yeah. - Okay, all right.
- I'm twice as gay.
- As long as you're straight while you're fishing.
And I say no other way, dude.
- No, they will not accept you.
- Yeah, unless you're fishing off of a fucking Navy boat.
- They're gonna throw you back.
- Dude, the Navy's full of just homo sailors.
I think I'm joining the Navy.
- Okay, good.
- You know what it was?
I was deciding that I've been watching Forged in Fire.
I was getting into swords and I was gonna buy a forge.
- Yeah, that's right, you were a blacksmith too last week.
- Yeah, I wasn't a blacksmith, dude.
- You said you were gonna get a forge and make a sword.
- I got a blacksmith.
- I got a forge man.
- A forge man.
- You're a forge man.
- It's not a thing.
- And a golfer and a fisherman and a goth.
- I contain many multitudes.
- No you don't.
- No.
- And I'm a sports scientist too.
- You have nothing inside of you.
- You're not a sport, don't, don't, don't.
- Oh, if I'm not a sports scientist,
how'd I come up with this question?
If a soccer ball is moving at 30 miles per hour
and then baseball is moving at 20 miles per hour,
and they're both heading towards me
'cause I'm catching both due to my multiple sport abilities.
- That's a math problem. - Like Bo Jackson.
- That's a math problem.
This is a sports science problem.
Could you play water polo on a train?
- Oh, wow.
- That's sports science.
Math would be if I said how many miles
could the train travel towards
when you were playing water polo on a pool
moving 100 miles per hour.
- Maybe I'm a sports math petition.
- All right, that's fine.
- You're not, you're not, dude.
- That's the one thing you can be.
- Okay.
- No, he can't be anything else.
- I'll agree on that.
- Don't encourage this.
- Okay, well, now he's not a golfer or a fisherman anymore.
- Or a sports mathematician.
- Or a Navy.
- He's never gonna be true to himself.
- I am true to myself.
- You should be a magician, too.
- I just need to find something, dude.
Something for the new year.
I have all this time now.
I think video games have become,
they're childish to me now,
due to my golfing and fishing new things that I do.
- That's not happening.
You're not fishing or golfing.
- Well, not yet, but I will be in a couple hours.
I'm gonna do golf first, and then I might go fishing
at midnight.
- You won't fish.
- I can't.
- You're not Mike Gunna.
You're not Mike Gunna.
- I cannot describe how much that this is angering me.
- You don't seem very angry.
- I'm pissed off right now.
- You can't do more than one thing.
- Ah!
- You know what?
I've been thinking of karate moves and learning them
and becoming really good at it.
- No, you're not a martial artist.
- And I might end up doing martial arts to you
if you keep talking to me about my different interests.
- All right, what martial arts moves do you know then?
- Fucking kicking.
- Do it.
Don't get up and kick.
- Terrible form, terrible form.
- I heard the rip in your pants.
- I didn't rip my new plaid golf pants.
- I heard your plaid pants, your plaid golf pants rip.
I heard it. No, I didn't dude. These are 42 28s. All right. And they fit me like a glove.
There's no way I'm ripping them. You're ripping. You just ripped them. I saw your thing come
out of it. You guys are you guys. You're so disrespectful. I bet you don't even I bet
you don't even wear I bet you don't even have golf attire. I don't. I don't. Neither do
Me, what do you think I'm wearing?
Ugly clothes?
You're wearing my dad's clothes.
It's not ugly clothes, it's a three-quarter zip
and a polo, you know, I have a Boston Red Sox hat on,
I'm wearing Dickies, that's kinda cheating it a little bit,
but I don't have any other pants.
Yeah, that's not golf pants.
And I got Nike--
It's not, yeah, so exactly, no,
you literally just admitted you don't have golf clothes.
Okay, I may have--
And you just said, okay, so you disagree with it.
I may have, listen, dude, not everything's
gonna be a hole in one.
- That's right, you are a hole in 1,000.
- No.
- Worst golfer in the world.
- Not every four's gonna be a nine drive.
So just fucking cut me some slacks
which you can win on the golf course.
- No.
- No, you just ripped you some slacks, dude.
- Yeah, you ripped your slacks.
I heard it.
- Can you guys just cut me some golf?
- I'll cut you.
- Cut, I'm gonna cut you in half.
- Can you bring a weapon onto the golf course?
- I'll split you in two.
- This is an important question to ask.
- The golf club is technically a weapon.
- Can you bring a cooler weapon though?
Can you bring two weapons then?
You can bring a cooler full of beer.
I actually don't know if you can, because that's my worry.
I bought this 30 rack of mix, that's what we call them, Mickey Olt's, Ultra Mickel
Obs, and now I think because it's a public city golf course, you're probably not allowed
to drink.
But I'm going to do it anyway.
That's probably true.
And if I get kicked off...
I hope you go to jail.
If I go to jail for golf, it'll be a life well spent.
What'll you become in jail?
A thug.
Yeah. Yeah. I think if I get to jail, I'll become a thug.
You're gonna be the first thug golfer.
Yeah.
It's like Thug Kitchen, dude.
You can publish a book called Thug Golf Science.
Yeah, this is the swag drive.
Thug Golf Science.
Yo, if you hit a golf ball on the moon, what'd it do?
That's what you would write.
Is it swag to pop a cap in a golf ball?
Yes or no question only.
yeah yeah but I think I'd like to combine different that see that book wouldn't
that would have no market because this golf science is for dads and dad will not
read a thug book dad's hate thugs so much pull up your plaid pants as well
dad would say turn your scally cap around yeah come on and stop hitting that golf
ball all that trying to yeah trying to flatten the brain on your skin hitting
- You're hitting the golf ball too hard like a thug.
Knock it off.
Come on, what happened to the fundamentals of the game?
You're getting all flashy over there.
- Yeah.
- You're trying to hit it in the hole.
- Yeah. - Come on, dude.
Back in my day, you had to-- - And stop.
And the caddy's twerking.
- Oh, great, now the caddy's twerking.
Jesus Christ, dude, tuck your shirt in.
What's wrong with these people?
- What do you mean by these people?
Swag, swag golfers.
- Oh, okay. - Yeah.
I don't know, maybe I'll--
- Don't even say it.
Don't even say it.
- Maybe I'll get into animation.
(laughing)
Maybe I'll get into animating different kinds of cartoons.
Anthropomorphic animals.
(laughing)
You know?
Maybe I got it. You're not doing that. I think I might do that. You don't do no. No.
How many things have you animated before? I used to use pivot animation. I used flash.
I have. I'm going to download flash and I just got this drawing tablet. What are you
download? What flash are you downloading? What program? Adobe. Adobe flash that's not
- That's real.
- That's cap.
- It's called Adobe Animate now.
You would know that if you were a real animator.
- Is that what Adobe Animate is?
- If you were a real old school guy,
you would know that.
It used to be called Flash, I'm gonna use that.
- I use my, I still use Macromedia Flash.
- Yeah, that was the one, dude.
- That was it.
I think you guys should trust the animator on this.
- You're not the animator, man.
- You guys should see my old stick figure animations.
- I'm already coming up with amazing kinds of backgrounds.
- You literally just copied off what I just said.
- No.
- I had this idea for a--
You just stole what I said.
No, I had this idea for like a,
it's like about a family.
Yeah.
Yeah, but they don't always make the right choice.
Okay.
Yeah.
And it kind of gets them into trouble sometimes.
Do they love each other?
Yeah.
Do they maybe show it the wrong way?
Absolutely.
What family doesn't?
Kind of the perfect, kind of a,
maybe a lampoon of the American family.
Okay, so yeah, we got the mom.
Wine.
Wine, drinks wine.
- Loves drinking wine. - The dad, the dad.
- Loves it. - Mose the lawn.
- It's an adult cartoon, so you can get away
with mom drinking wine. - Exactly.
- The dad, the dad. - Hey, you could not,
you could not fucking get away with mom's drinking wine
on primetime cable. - This ain't exactly
made for Nickelodeon.
- The dad, okay, he's Mose the lawn,
he pitches baseball. - He plays golf and fish.
- He plays Little League.
Here's the twist, he's metrosexual.
He wears a scarf. - Oh.
That's the adult swim twist.
- Wow.
- The kids, five, 10, 15 kids.
- Okay. - Wow.
- They're the kids from, 19 kids and counting.
They're the kids from the Duggars.
- Yeah. (laughs)
- One of them's evil, did something bad.
- It's the kid, yeah.
- One of the adult kids was very naughty.
- He was on the naughty list this year for sure.
- Yeah, he did something that the dad
took off his scarf and whipped him with it.
- Yep.
Here's the big twist.
The dad, the metrosexual one,
he falls victim to the virus--
- Known as COVID-19.
- No, the virus known as the common cold,
which actually disproportionately affects metrosexuals.
- And he's affected by the T virus as well.
- Yeah, the low T virus, 'cause of his metrosexual nature.
- And here's the twist of the series.
It takes place on Mars.
They have a robot friend named Dr. Robot.
- Named Mr. Jetson.
- Named Beep.
which Mr. Jetson is kind of a,
that's an homage to earlier, one of my--
- Something to some other figure.
- But here's the twist-- - Something that
I can't remember.
- Here's the twist though on the series
is it's made for stoners.
- Yeah, so every, but there's nothing about--
- They need a show for stoners.
- Listen, it's a show made for stoners,
but there's nothing about smoking weed in the show,
but there's a five minute break in the middle
where it says--
- It says do what you gotta do.
- There's a chyron on the bottom of the screen
and it says, "Do what you need and do what you love."
- Yeah, and it shows, and get this,
it shows a guy licking a flower as a metaphor.
- Well, but also it's trippy visuals.
- Yeah, so yeah, here's the twist on the show,
is it's very colorful.
- Yes, yeah, there's tons of pinks and blues
so that when you watch it you go,
"Wait, am I high right now?"
- Here's one of the twists, is they swear.
When you watch it on TV, it's bleeped out.
You find the episode online streaming,
is as this wears a naked
definitely clearly they say and right out loud
definitely
and they're saying all of them
it's every episode there's a checklist on the side of the screen
that they run down
they gotta hit that the carlin seven
yeah here's a visit to a george carlin voices the dead here seven dirty words
that we're saying on television right we were psyched with the cycle that
audio from old george carlin specials the one that
It's all, it's all, yeah it's all George Carlin,
different clips of him.
There's a lot of him going like, "What?"
- Yeah, that's all the dad says.
- 'Cause we don't want him to talk about the Iraq War.
- Yeah.
- And listen, since the dad's metrosexual,
he says, "God suck your supplies."
- Wait, what if we do have him talk about the Iraq War?
What if we finally knock that down a peg?
- We could do a land use--
- Yeah, so here's the twist, the Iraq War is happening
while the show goes on on Mars.
- Yeah, what if we, what if we're the first--
called the Mars Wreck Wars. What if we're the first comedians to ever talk about I
mean the first TV show to ever lampoon the Bush administration. Right. That might be a
really. First animated show to ever lampoon the Bush administration. So here's the twist is Bush,
is George Bush moves in down the street. Wow. And Bart gets into trouble and
and is annoying to him. It's little Bush from the show Little Bush. Bart Duggar.
- When do you think, at what part of the Simpsons
development do you think they were like,
yeah and also there's this Indian guy for no reason.
(laughing)
Do you think that was like the fifth,
right after the family?
- That was the first character that Matt Groening
came up with.
- And they were like, oh we can't just do a,
can't just do that, right?
- Yeah, I guess we need a family.
(laughing)
- And we need a comic book guy to balance it out.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, they should have had a golf episode of the Simpsons.
Come on, you fucking prick.
- We were doing animation for some reason.
- I'm sorry, I'm just saying, you're right.
I got caught in the past.
I used to be a golfer and a fisherman and a goth.
Now I'm an animator.
- You were not any of those things.
- No.
- Well, I'm actually animating different stuff right now.
- Okay, good.
- You're not.
- You're an animator now.
That's it, you have to stick with that.
- So you guys are finally behind me on this?
- I'm behind you on being an animator.
- I don't know what's going on now.
- As long as you don't ever switch it again,
- Okay. - You have my blessing.
- Wow, that's actually really sweet.
- What's our show called?
- The Sopranos.
- Okay.
- No, that's a show!
- Oh, it's called Delightful Fancies.
- Yeah. (laughs)
- Right?
- Yeah, how about, what about this?
- That's pretty good.
- The family who lives together, loves together.
- How about this?
Un, it'll be like un, and un is a different color
than the rest of the thing.
It'll be un is red, dash, family,
that's a different color too, that's blue.
Yeah, okay.
And then fide is green.
So it'd be unfamily fide.
Okay, what about uncommon grounds
and it's like as a coffee cup?
And it's, oh, and they own a family coffee shop.
There, okay.
But here's the twist.
They sell the worst coffee in the world.
No, no, they don't sell the worst.
It's coffee that's made with a lot of heart.
No.
- What?
- What about, okay, it's like a pun on home,
what about a like, it's like a pun on home sweet home,
but it's the family, it's the gnome family.
- Gnome? - And it's gnomes eat homes.
- Phones. - Gnomes eat phones.
- Gnomes eat bones.
(laughing)
- Gnomes eat bones?
- Yeah, and they eat bones in the show.
They're like, they're like necromancers.
- Can there be a goth daughter?
- What if it's called, what if it's called,
what if it's called the necromancer gnomes?
(sighs)
- What if the show's just called The Necromancer?
- How are we gonna deal--
- What if it's called The Necromancer?
- How are we gonna deal with the teen daughter's
kinda bad attitude?
- What if it's a good--
- We'll just kill her off in the second episode.
- Yeah, if she gets too mouthy, we'll kill the character.
- But it's like she falls in a factory,
and we're also making a point about factory farming.
She falls into the hole that they put the male chicks in
in the chicken factory,
and then we just see that entire process
and she's getting like fucking turned into nothing.
- That could have been a chicken.
- Yeah, yeah.
But luckily it was just some goth bitch.
(laughing)
- Named Caleb.
- Whoa!
No.
- Yeah, I think that'll really drive the point home.
- What about gnomes is thicker than water?
- Wow.
- Bones are thicker than,
bones are thicker than blood.
- Bones are thicker than gnomes.
- That's why they like bones.
- Bones are thicker than the father.
- That's why it's called family.
How about, that's the subtitle.
The subtitle should be, "That's why it's called family."
- Gnome improvement.
- Okay.
What about...
- That's pretty good.
- What about the simps, the simps twos?
- Little gnome, what if it's called gnomenclature?
- Little gnome on the fairy.
- And the fairy's the dad.
- Oh my God.
- And the little gnome is, he's wearing a baby
in the baby Bjorn.
That's the little gnome.
- It's a gnome Bjorn.
- What about, what about if it's called
King of the Thrills?
- King of the Gnomes.
- Here's all I want, okay?
I'm willing to animate this show.
- Wow, that's great, wait, hold on.
My sister just sent me this.
- Can't even see what that is.
- Can't see what that is.
- But you're ruining a brainstorm session and--
- Wait, okay.
It's pertinent.
I can't see.
It's a picture, it's a gnome gif.
Oh, it's a gnome?
Yeah.
Listen. That's crazy.
Listen, I do want, I'm willing to animate this,
only if one of you two, I mean, between the three of us,
one of us has to have Dr. Dre's phone number.
Right? Yeah.
So we're gonna call him up, we're gonna say,
"Listen, Andre," first name him, "Listen, Andre,
"we want a Beats sponsorship.
"We're gonna animate a Beats pill,
And we're gonna pour Sprite on it to prove that it's Sprite-proof, and it's gonna be in the show.
And he'll say, "Yeah."
"Yo."
"Yeah."
What else will he say?
"Yeah, yeah. What up, Detroit?"
Say something like that.
Yeah, we'll tell him we're from Detroit.
Yeah, that's why he'll agree.
Yeah.
Is he from Detroit?
No.
We'll say, "Hey man, if you don't do this, you might end up with a guilty conscience."
Oh my gosh.
- Oh my gosh. - And he'll go, yeah.
Yeah.
You know?
And then he might puff some weed too.
- No, he's not on, I was, he's not on that fuckin',
what's that Eminem song about Detroit?
- Just stop, just stop.
- I thought he was on the song about Detroit.
- Eminem's a golfer.
- Eminem's not a golfer, don't fuckin' talk
about golf anymore.
- I gotta go.
- All right, I'm gonna animate you.
- Bye. - Bye.