Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
- Premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Did you guys hear the humongous national news?
Do you know what I'm talking about?
Have you heard?
- What is it?
- It's Thought Week in Philadelphia.
- Is it actually?
We need to do something about this.
- It's Thought Week in Philadelphia.
There's thotties gonna be walking all around.
not only are they going to be
fine and some of the baddest bodies on the east coast are joining up in
philadelphia for a pussy i mean i don't i a pussy party and all the brothers and
sisters are invited
why you saying brothers like that
we mean
that's my accent
guys i i i hate to say it i hate to say it or this this fast on the other side
i think it's not good to be a thought
wall
i guess morally wrong
Holy!
Alright, you gotta calm down.
I'm sorry, I didn't want to bring it up.
I think it's awesome.
I didn't want to bring it up, but you forced my hand.
I think actually, counterpoint.
That's an opinion I've been sitting on for a long time.
I think that it's awesome to be a thought and a ho.
That makes sense coming from someone who's failed morally.
Yep.
Really.
You are compromised in a morally and Christian way.
You're immuno-compromised, but for morals.
And for...
Yeah.
We'll talk about that another time.
Literally, sin can so easily permeate your body.
How?
just there's nothing blocking you're like a porch light like a sin is a moth
yeah, like a porch light yeah. You have like a porous body like the
porous body of yeah, you have like pores that same can go into yeah and it
just I don't I don't see how I don't you have like you have like know what
about my lifestyle could you know some people some people they just have acne
and that's just it. They just have it forever and that's that and that's it
they get the fucked up face scars and stuff.
That's you for sin.
It's funny that does just ruin your life.
If you have really bad acne as a kid, you just, no, but you would never see anybody who's
really successful.
I am so grateful.
Who has all, who has fucked up acne scars.
It's crazy, yeah.
Except for TrainwrecksTV, the famous gambler.
He has bad acne scars.
I don't know that I'd consider him that successful.
He's a bit like a millionaire.
And the grand scheme of things.
TrainwrecksTV is the most successful guy, the most successful gambler, but I think the
the most successful person with acne is probably Dr. Pimple Popper.
I think, I mean I like TrainwrecksTV, I like what he does.
She has acne patients.
He's almost definitely a servant of the devil.
Oh yeah, 100%.
Do you have Trainwrecks?
No, wait, no, he's a knight for God.
Who is?
I don't think so.
TrainwrecksTV?
He's the guy who teaches children how to gamble on Twitch?
Yeah, okay.
Yeah.
I think he actually might be put...
I got distracted, hold on, I got to get my thoughts back on track.
You guys are making me think too much about...
Thoughts, yeah.
How much fun it's gonna be tonight when I do all this sinning.
Are you gonna go to Thought Week?
You're gonna sin tonight?
You're going all the way to Philly for Thought Week just to sin?
I'm going to condemn them.
I'm going to do debauchery.
Did you guys ever have a, like in college, like a street preacher guy come?
No.
No, yelled at them.
We went to the same college.
You and me both went to different colleges too.
That's true.
And I had a street preacher.
But I guess you didn't have a street preacher.
We didn't have a street preacher. We're a public university, so he could just
cut you anybody can just come on the campus. Yeah, so he would just come on the
campus and he'd like he'd like busk by talking about how thotties and gay
gays are going straight to hell. There wasn't a street preacher, but there was.
People just like breakdance in front of him. There was a guy. At our like the dorms
that I stayed in there was a veteran with PTSD in the apartments across the
Street and this kid shined a laser pointer into his apartment and he came
over to our apartment building with a gun. Whoa that's sick. Well so what happened
was is like he was like somebody shining like a red light into my house and like
scaring me and my daughters and his daughters were with him and he was
wearing like basketball shorts and he had the pistol in his pocket and Cameron
just dropped the recorder. Let this go on record.
Yeah Cameron just dropped the recorder. He's the clumsy one who makes the most mistakes.
Yes, that's right. I was the first one who dropped something today. There wasn't someone who dropped something just minutes before me
Nope, you know something earlier. I didn't even say anything
Speaking of dropping something the guy he wasn't even connecting the bottle these thoughts in Philadelphia we dropping dropping it
Yeah, you also you told the story before at least I did. Yeah, damn it
Yeah, I told this story before went on vacation with my cousins one time. I was maybe 13 14 that story our
I know this one all the way through like condo apartment thing that we were
staying in it was in front of another guy's and he it was like on a hill so he
could see the roof of ours and we would jump up on the roof and he would yell at
us and then we started putting stuff up on the roof and we wanted to and then we
found a dead seal on the on the beach and we tried to drag it up to put it on
the roof and we're gonna put it in a chair and put a cigar in its mouth and
and but the seal as we pulled it away, it did it like split in half. It was
completely
is awful. It is like that it was a great. We thought we were like that'd be so
funny, then we started bringing it. We're like all like is it
it was intact enough that you dragged it and then when this when you tried to
get it up on the roof, that's when it split in half. Yeah,
did all down the side. If we had been there a week earlier or not a week,
three days earlier when the seal freshly died yeah we would have been the seal
you know the funniest thing I'd ever done yeah absolutely
it's still pretty one of the funniest deal with a cigar in his mouth sitting
in a beach chair funny and went after a guy gets mad at you the day after yeah
it's gonna rot yeah I don't give a fuck that's funny until the next day when you
wake up and all you're smelling is this old fucking guy try to prove it prove
that three 14 year olds brought a dead seal onto the roof yeah where'd they get
the cigar from my dad we got it from our dad mm-hmm yeah we have there was a
there's like this guy we like when we were like seven this guy came up to our
house we're like kids like play we were in our living room playing but we had
the windows open and I guess we were being too loud and he walked up the hill
and started like he looked into our screen door and started yelling at us
okay and he said he was gonna call the police on us and then like a couple
months later he died. Whoa that is sick dude. Yeah you guys are probably killed
him with loudness. Honestly you're loud playing. I did have that thought like
well he shouldn't have yelled at me. We had a I lived in a car apartment a
carpent I lived in a car I lived in a car I lived in an apartment complex that had
a like a little pool and one day I was swimming in there what do you smell that
- I smell weed.
- I smell weed, yeah, it just got stronger again.
- I'm telling you, it is, somebody is fucking getting high.
- Yeah, nearby.
- It's not me.
- There's somebody high in the area.
- One of us is high.
It's like The Thing.
Now listen, I'm high.
- Yo, it's like that crazy ass movie, The Thing.
- But it's not me, I'm not high though.
- That's a good--
- Yo, The Thing is a crazy movie.
- Wait, that's a really good idea for a movie.
- I'm not the high one.
- That's a really good idea for a movie.
- It's not me.
thing style yeah I find it like who's I but it's who which who which is high
yeah everyone's like sitting there look just like this is a crazy situation this
is so weird I never want to have THC in my body again that's the one sin I won't
that is that is truly the devil THC is really in the past month I saw a bunch of
I've been seeing ghosts.
I do have a pre-roll that I got from this party.
That's so awesome.
It came in a tube and I looked at the amount of THC in the thing.
Don't tell me it's a thousand.
It was like a one gram joint with 28% THC.
That's pretty low.
Yeah, 28% is low.
That scares the fuck out of me.
What are you talking about?
They should make joints that are 1% THC.
They make those.
What?
Yeah.
They make CBD.
.005.
I thought about buying some, Gus, when we were in LA, Gus gave me a CBD cigarette.
Yeah.
And I was like, "Oh, this is good.
I can like smoke something that isn't a cigarette when I'm drunk."
But then I like had it and it just makes the entire balcony smell like mango.
So it's like clear that you're not smoking a cigarette, you know?
Yeah, it has to be.
It needs to just be a cigarette.
Yeah, pretty much.
also still bad to smoke anything I think yeah I think it is you're just not
supposed to breathe stuff in that's not there. Is that fucked up? That's the funniest fucking argument though like
people who smoke weed like their whole lives and then they're just trying to
tell you like no it doesn't cause cancer. I had somebody once tell me that the
carcinogens that smoking weed puts in your body actually so it does put some
in your body they said into your lungs but then because weed is so like healing
it actually removes more when you exhale. Yeah it goes in and then it pulls it out.
to the carcinogen. It's like a plumbing snake. It's fucking genius. People's dopers are so
stupid. They're scum. It's so funny. I love just seeing whenever somebody says that like
oh like... Dopers and thoughts. ...weed is harmful or something. Everyone's like, like
everyone who smokes... It's just a plant. Yeah, everyone who smokes so much weed that
they are literally mentally challenged. Yeah. Seeing them like get mad and like and is so
so
fucking do true yeah I'm smoking put what the hell yeah wait pause you're smoking
put yeah that's fucking disgusting that's all I meant pot oh all right well
yeah your stoner time smoking weep yep not you're sad yep no like but if you're
if you're gonna sell we have some tricky situations if you're gonna smoke weed
don't try and tell me that it's like fuck my thing that's not a typo I fucked my
my mop my step my step mop. Oh, that's supposed to be I fucked my pop.
That's my bad yeah. I fucked my step. Yeah, I fucked my blue.
Blue just yeah, that was supposed to say dad. Oh, my fingers the guy's so high
that he thinks that he fucks it up. You were following that you were following
- No.
- I forgot you cut your hair.
- He's the doper.
- Yeah.
- Let me look at your hair.
- That could be the movie where it's the thing
and one of them's high as hell, the doper.
- Short hair.
- You look like a senator.
- His hair is short.
- I shaved my own head.
- Yep.
- Well, you didn't shave it.
You cut it.
- I cut it, yeah.
- You look like you could be a villager.
- Dude, I had like the,
I had like, I had like a little like,
short mullet for like a split second.
- A split second?
- That would be cool.
- Like I shaved the sides down and the top.
and the top. And then I like I looked at it and I was just like I I really can't
do that. You don't have the guts to do funny stuff with your head. I do. Yeah. I
do and I did. I had the shittiest mullet for the whole of 2021. You mean the year
when you didn't go outside at all? Come on. Yeah. Do something
funny with your head while you still have hair. All right I will grow this out
- Yes.
- And then now that I own clippers,
I can do whatever I want.
- I think next time I--
- Finally you can do whatever you want.
- Next time I cut my hair,
I might do a rat tail for a little bit.
That'd be pretty funny.
- You know, dude, I can give you,
I can go home and get my clippers right now
and I can give you a fun haircut.
- I mean, looking at your head, no.
I will not let you near my hair.
- Why?
(laughing)
- It's not happening.
- Let me cut your hair.
- I don't wanna look medieval.
- I used to cut my friend's hair in high school.
- Yeah?
I used to cut, dude, I cut my own hair most of my life.
Yeah, I can freaking tell.
Yeah.
I will say with this haircut you got to drop these glasses.
These glasses are in the trash now, unless you wear a hat.
Yeah.
Yeah, it makes you look old.
Yeah, okay.
I'm looking mean for no reason.
It's not, we have to band together.
Why?
He's just cut his hair, why are we being dickheads?
Yeah, we can't be mean, it's, listen, it's fucking, it's thought week in Philadelphia.
I'm sorry to any for thought week. I'm the world the world is a go drowning in a
mire of sin. I'm gonna kill the Liberty Bell of my nut. I have there's ackney
everywhere. Acne? Millions of teenagers are dying from acne. Oh acne. We need to
forge a better world. Did you guys ever have bad acne growing up? I never
have had acne. I didn't have acne until I was an adult and yeah all I get is just
the little. I just get one huge pimple every month. Yeah. A fucking giant one. I never got
one. I got like one zit on my like nose one time. Like one like big white pus ball. You
ever get the ones inside your nose? Oh the ones in your ears. Oh that sucks too. Actually
I did. You guys remember I had that big ass ear pimple? No why would I remember that?
I don't remember that. You guys know we were at a diner and then I was like my ears been
hurting and one of you looked at it and just like screeched.
Then it was Cameron. Yeah. I probably didn't screech. Because I was like
skating with ear pods in and the sweat was building up and it formed like a big
sebaceous like I think it was a cyst. I used to be obsessed with cysts in high school.
We tried to give my friend's dad a cyst. Why? Because we were like well we
want to pop it we were obsessed with the cyst popping videos and he
was like he said that he gets them every once in a while and we were like please
easily just like wear dirty shirts. I would like to try to get assist for us,
so we can pop it. I would like someone to do some kind of procedure on my feet.
Okay, what do you mean?
Open ended any kind of procedure. Ideally one that feels good. Well, that's
we should go get the, I should get a foot, the fish, the fish or when they
fish the one it's kind of scares me, but if it was like an expert doing the one
where they like they razor blade your feet, you know, when someone has really
fucked up feet. Oh yeah, oh yeah, I don't think my feet are fucked up that they
can do that to me, but maybe someone would find a feeder. I want the bot
flies removed from my the back of my neck. You have bought flies in the back
of your nose. Those those ones scare me. Kai told me that
one of his professors in college was growing a bot fly in his skin like flesh
like on purpose, like he was like an insect enthusiast. He's like so any
show the guys like check it out guys and he had like a festering disgusting
cool dude oh yeah when you see the video that's like stray dog has 5,000 I
want that just kill the fucking dog speaking of Philadelphia and killing
dogs you guys see that video the two Rottweilers attacking the baby and the
two men of action who just start shooting at the dogs no so that is
pretty sick dude these guys are just instantly they do the wheelbarrow trick
no they just shoot the dog I don't know about feet away the dog is right next to
the baby which is in the dog's mouth and the guy there's two guys just start
shooting it. I told you guys the wheelbarrow trick right? Have I told you the wheelbarrow?
You pick up the dog by the hind legs and just split it in half. That's what you're supposed to do.
Dude I almost had to do that. I don't even think it's a real thing. It's just like,
I think it was a 4chan post or something or someone said that and it stuck in my head.
I'm gonna stop doing that anytime. It's so funny. Anytime a dog gets at all aggressive with Phil,
I just rip it. And that's what you're supposed to do to a pit bull.
just rip it in half every time I almost had to do it today to a dog named chopper
chopper I mean he's asking for a dog was that this is it it's just a mystery dog
with like a really small head and the owner is like so weird and the the he
probably shouldn't say that he's a normal guy he's he's just got a dog
named chopper but he when he showed up the first day the thing is don't you
shouldn't bring dogs you shouldn't bring like weird violent dogs to a dog park
Yeah, bring them to the ocean or something or yeah, yeah, but he showed he shows a goose farb and he starts picking feed
So it's yelling at Phil trying to kill Phil and grab his ball the owner was yelling at him
yeah, so the owners got his teeth around Phil's neck and he's like shaking him like this and
Chopper comes up to me and I'm trying to kind of like soothe the the situation kind of diffuse it a little bit and the
Owner's like oh, yeah, if chopper comes up to you just don't touch his head the owner said that well
he had his mouth around his mouth. Yes, his mouth fills heads in the owners
man, and then he said yeah and you're like don't hurt Harper hurt uh-huh yeah.
He was mr. Bean like he was mr. B. He kind of yeah he kind of is a mr. Bean.
Okay, meet some weird dog owners owning a dog you know opens a whole new kind of
social area. You know what the you know what the weird the the weirdest thing of
the is if you're walking somebody else's dog in a place that they usually like at
park or something and then all the other dog owners know the dog right like so i
would walk my mom's dog and all the people who like my mom would talk to
every day would come up to me and be like ask who i was and stuff and that's
the weird it because like and you have to they're they're all such weird people
yeah today they're like investigating yeah i see people who see i can't tell
if they've seen you probably get that if like you know yeah like your wife is
walking exactly that someone comes up and it's like yeah so like this morning i
was walking down the street and this lady this like German lady dog in full.
That's one of the weirdest social situations. I think it's someone who
knows your dog, but you don't know them yeah yeah she was like this old lady.
She was like I would like to say hello and I was like what I dress she was
talking about Phil. Well, she needs to be with a voice like that. She needs to
be invited and I was like okay. I was like okay. Well, she probably has seen
Phil before in the neighborhood and Phil probably likes her and then Phil gets
close and he never does this feels like
and she she was like okay, that's how he says hello goo goo goo goo.
I was it and I was like what the fuck like what does this lady the dog hates
this lady she must have done something really fucked up when he said I last
minute in her soul. Yeah, some people the problem the problem. I think is that
some people they don't have the they have a switch broken in their head that
regulates where you when you talk to a dog you say weird things you do baby
voice and you act strangely. When you talk to a person, you can't do that.
No, that's off.
But some people, the switch in their head, it doesn't modulate right or whatever.
So they'll be talking to the dog and then they'll turn to you and then they'll say
something that you shouldn't say to a person.
They're still in dog mode.
They're still in dog mode. Yeah, they don't have an expert recalibration like me. I would
never say a dog thing to a person.
Oh, look at the little dog.
It's serious, we hot out.
People do that. It's crazy. People just don't switch in time.
Yeah, and I also, you know, having a-- just seeing other dogs, like people really have
different kind of reactions where some people will jump on your dog and then some people
are really scared of dogs.
Yeah.
Even little dogs.
We had to leave a bodega a couple weeks ago because the woman in there was so scared of
Phil and he's like 25 pounds.
Yeah, he's not big.
So awesome, dude.
He also bites.
He's vicious.
He did that to your arm.
Yeah.
Yep.
people get really really scared of dogs people are so weird about dogs
especially cats
cats get so scared of dogs yeah what's that about cats are so normal though i
fucking hate cats if a cat if a cat isn't afraid of my dog i want my dog to
kill it yeah my dog is i have a bad dog that needs to reinforce the natural order dogs should be
dogs should also one thing that's really making me reconsider phil is that he
actually likes my mailman that's yeah that's not right i mean there's a
that there's a natural order.
There's a natural order, there's a natural relationship
between dogs and cats.
- And mailmen. - That needs to be,
yeah, and mailmen, that needs to be upheld.
And it's, and you know, topsy-turvy dog owners
and cat owners nowadays try to train.
- These days. - You can't do that.
- You're saying there's no-- - You can't do it.
- They're saying there's no difference between dogs and cats.
- That's like turning the,
it's like turning the Ghostbusters female.
- A cat can be a dog.
- Yeah. - Yep.
- It's like they're making these new movies now.
Also they're saying now that you--
- They made a movie called Cats vs. Dogs.
- They made a character called Catdog.
- I went to the vet and I told them,
I told them I didn't want to neuter Phil
and they said, "Actually you have to neuter Phil these days
"but you can't get a dog spayed."
- Wow. - Yep.
- Wow.
- I heard that. - Isn't that horrible?
They want to chop all the guys nuts off
but keep all the girls nuts.
- That's terrible. - What the fuck is going on
in this loony topsy-turvy world?
- Why do you have to get animals spayed and neutered?
Well because I think the dream is that your dog fucks other dogs all the time.
But you don't want him to get pregnant.
I don't understand that.
Why wouldn't you want more dogs, man?
That's the thing.
I want to see Phil's...
Bob Barker was like telling people to get their pets spayed and neutered at the end
of every Price is Right.
It's like, why are you doing that?
Because they escape and they fuck and they make thousands of dogs.
and then we have to kill all the dogs,
you get the stupid commercials, the SPCA and shit.
You know, we kill so many dogs every day.
- Yeah.
- America.
- There's probably one million dead dogs in a pile.
- They don't, no, they get incinerated.
- Yeah, well how do you think they incinerate them?
They put them in a pile to burn them.
They don't burn them one at a time.
- They burn them one at a time.
- They don't have a little--
- Like Obi-Wan Kenobi.
- They don't have a little subway oven type thing
where they put a dog in and a green bar goes,
do they do and you open it up and there's a perfect dog and then they're
at the dog don't have tracker online and it will say that they're there.
What's it called they're checking it for quality
the dog's corpse. Yeah, yeah, checking to make sure I've been eating a lot of
dominoes and Arby's recently Dominoes. I've been ordering dominoes or Arby's at
least one dominoes is a pretty good dominoes is a good is Arby's. You're
is
Uber Eats close.
We're talking about Arby's, you know, those prices are so low.
Uber Eats aren't so bad.
How does Arby's keep the prices down?
I don't fucking know.
I guess the meat is very thinly sliced.
Well, yeah, they're trying to slice it thinner these days.
I started getting double meat on my sandwiches.
Yeah.
I had some Taco Bell the other day.
That's a damn bad fast food, I've decided.
I don't like it anymore.
What's wrong with you?
I realize the only thing I like about Taco Bell is the nacho cheese.
That's the only good thing I like.
They are falling off so hard.
You don't like a gordita?
No, still, I love a gordita.
I love the gordita.
It's not authentic.
It's fallen off in the past couple years.
That's all you need to get.
Taco Bell has been going downhill since 2019.
I've been eating too much authentic Mexican food.
Everything goes, yeah, but that's a different type of food.
Abuelas.
Abuelas, I mean come too many abuelas and tias.
Come too many abuelas culo.
Yep.
You guys are stupid.
No, you're not.
What?
Yeah, I'm not.
Oh yeah.
Fuck you.
You're not stupid.
Yeah.
Idiot.
If you only try joining this team.
You guys knew what you were saying right now.
I don't know what I'm saying.
You're having too much fun today.
Yo quiero comer abuela culo.
I think the only fast food I get now is either Taco Bell or McDonald's.
McDonald's is fucking ass now too.
They stopped doing McDonald's.
I haven't gotten McDonald's in so long.
The only, well that's the thing, the only things that I would get, well actually Chick-fil-A
too.
I love Chick-fil-A.
Chick-fil-A I love it.
And Popeyes too.
But I haven't gotten much fast food at all recently, but those are the places that I
would go.
And all those things, I would only get one thing there.
I would like McDonald's, I'll get a McChicken.
I would not get anything else.
I would get a gordita, a taco bell,
and then maybe something else.
Yeah, it has, it's too expensive.
- I don't want the McChicken.
You know what I want when I go to,
I want a double hamburger cheeseburger.
- The double cheeseburger is still good.
- Yep.
- What's the fucking, Burger King has never been on.
- Lie, lie.
- Burger King is pretty bad.
I don't really like Burger King.
- Whopper's the best fast food hamburger.
- It's never been on, but if you go in there
with the mindset, this is not gonna be good,
It's amazing.
- You're fucking stupid.
The chicken, amazing.
- The first two chickens I had were so good.
When it first came out, they were so good,
and now they're horrible.
- Yep.
- No, no, Burger King has like,
it's literally like,
you can go to Burger King in February,
and that is not the same as Burger King in April.
- Yeah, no.
- That's how restaurants are too,
'cause it's real, okay?
- Yeah, exactly.
- It's actually flame broiled burgers.
- You can smell Burger King like from,
if you live next to a Burger King,
prepare for your all your clothes to smell like Burger King for the rest of
your life. Do you know what else that what other fast food I had
recently I hadn't had in ages in LA was Subway. Subway. I had Subway I had
Subway for the first time in like three years. That was really the first time
yeah in like three or four years. Subway has been taking some hits as of late but I enjoy
myself a Subway sandwich. I'm a Quiznos boy. I like a six-incher. Quiznos is shit.
Firehouse subs is shit. Write that down he likes a six-incher. A six-incher Subway
sandwich okay yeah with extra mayonnaise shooting out of it onto my face no I'm
playing though yeah I just like the same way he likes two little tomatoes at the
bottom of the sandwich okay so basically what I like is a hoagie roll that has a
mayonnaise bottle in it that squirts on my face two little tomatoes and a bunch
of shredded lettuce on top to look like pubes that's what I like is that what you
want me to say yep you know what I really wish they had here that I think
even though I only had it twice has probably become one of my favorites is
cookout yeah. Cookout is the best. Cookout is go to. I've been saying this for years. If
cookout opened in New York City location and it was open 24 hours it would be the
biggest, it would be the biggest most busiest fast-food place in America.
Probably. You know what I had. I think my my S tier I think well yeah I probably
changed I guess I don't go to McDonald's at all anymore so I'd probably drop
McDonald's down. I still really like Taco Bell even though I do agree it's gotten
worse. It's gotten so bad. But also I never had Taco Bell until I was in college so
It's also true. So you don't have the experience.
I don't have the rose tinted glass that me and Pat have.
But I think my S-tier is probably cookout, Popeyes, Chick-fil-A, and Taco Bell.
There's no going wrong with the chicken restaurants.
Any chicken restaurant I will put in the S-tier.
Cane's is still like, you know.
I only had Cane's one time in my life.
Cane's is falling off a little bit.
I'll put the Zaxby's in this S-tier.
Never had Zaxby's, Chick-fil-A, and the Popeyes.
What's the fucking chain that's like...
Oh, oh, oh, Carl's Jr.
That's just, that's Harveys.
Was that the one where we got the breakfast sandwich?
Can we go through, what places did we go on tour?
Which fast foods did we go?
We went to Jack in the Box.
That was what expanded my...
Carl's Jr. breakfast I liked.
I got the burger.
I thought that was one of the best fast food breakfast sandwiches.
I should have gotten that because the Jack in the Box, or the Carl's Jr. burger.
I just got the number one. I got the number one. It's like 9 in the morning. Yeah
Yeah, but you know I you can't eat a breakfast burger. Yes, you can that's some stupid. That's yeah, that's bullshit
That is some fucking nah. That's fine. Okay. It's the first
Microbial time at the time of the time didn't breakfast burger time didn't matter the time matter
I was doing the test I was doing the ultimate test the ultimate test is eating a burger if it's a fucking burger place
Yes, it's not it's a fast-food restaurant. It's a fast-food restaurant that primarily sells burgers. You got to judge everything
I like my breakfast burrito. Yeah, the breakfast sandwich was quite good
We went to Jack in the Box. Maybe I had what do we get a check in the book?
What's that? I got a breakfast sandwich on a sourdough. I got the breakfast burrito or maybe that was no
That was what I like that was that was that was the really good one
We got the Carl's jr. Was on the way to San Francisco is that and we got that for breakfast. Yeah
What did I get there? I don't know. I got a steak burrito, a steak breakfast burrito, and it was mighty fine.
Wait, where did we get that? That was Jaggerbox. Los Angeles. Los Angeles. On the way out. On the way out. Nope, not in Long Beach.
It was in North Hollywood.
Like the movie. Yep. I don't, I think, I don't remember what I got at all. I'll have to go again.
There's a movie North Hollywood directed by Mikey Alfred and Miranda Cosgrove is 30 years old playing a high schooler in it.
There's a movie I watched both both Godfathers Miranda Cosgrove is someone that could play a high schooler forever. That's fine
No, she looks until she started. It doesn't matter. No. She's one of those people that doesn't matter what she looks like
It's okay that she can play high school or forever
You know there's certain people you have to just give passes to that's like you can you can get a child for your whole
Way too hard. She cuts. I watched that movie. She cusses. She cusses like a damn sailor
I shut that movie off. I shut that bitch up. I shut that movie Miranda Cosgrove cuss
mm-hmm why is it a bunch of high schoolers and they're there they're like
doing 50s stuff and the movie is takes place in 20 like 20 that movie sucks
yeah Romeo and Juliet how come they're doing Romeo and Juliet takes place in the
19th I fucking sense I don't know there's a plus in the title but it's not
a math movie you hate Romeo and Juliet I hate Romeo plus Juliet I hate all of
Baz Luhrmann's movies why did he make he made that Mulan Roush he made that great
Gatsby one with him yeah you're homophobe no he's straight what
Bosler man is a straight guy you guys gonna see Elvis Lerman he's Australian
you guys gonna see I mean two huge movies out this weekend call Elvis and
the black phone I know I don't know if you guys have heard about this Elvis by
Boz Lerman yeah call me when he makes a Yilvas movie yeah yeah I don't know if
you guys have heard it all about this but apparently in the black phone Ethan
Hawke turns in a career-defining terrifying performance as a sinister new
horror icon the grabber the grabber the grabber yes grab Ethan Hawke as the
terrifying grabber did you in the new movie the black phone apparently he
plays the grabber and get this the grabber he's a magician who kidnaps
children he puts him in a basement guess what's in the basement the grab a black
phone no yeah the phone or does it have some kind of why are they calling him
the grabber when he's got a phone. Ethan Hawking is the phoner. Does it have the dark application
on it? What's wrong with the black phone? Apparently when you pick up the black phone
you are able to talk to the spirits of the children that the grabber has kidnapped. Why
the fuck would they want to do that? Now what I don't understand is why the grabber keeps
the kid in a room where he can talk with the other kids and play. You're going to give
him advice. Exactly. The grabber, why don't you put him in a room with a different phone?
like an AI trying to learn. I got a scene that they could okay scary movie six
comes out they do my phone right mm-hmm kid picks up the phone on the other end
the Jared Fogle guy from Verizon says can you hear me now that's actually pretty
good hmm yeah can you and then and then the grabber says can you grab me or can
I grab you now? I heard that actually one of his terrifying lines in the movie
sorry, can I grab you now? Can I grab you now, but he is
great, a fine and let me tell you based on his mask, you might
want to call this guy either the smiler or the frowner because
the grabber has different masks that he switches out based on
his emotions. Oh man, I just got an awful text from my grandpa.
What happened? He texted me a joke that he wrote. Let's hear
it. He said the black phone. Did you get it from cricket
wireless?
Your grandpa said he just texted me that he just had. I didn't
say that, but he did text me that
That's what he said to me.
- Oh my God.
- Can you believe it?
(laughing)
Did you guys know there's a delivery app called Gitter?
- Yeah.
- I just saw it.
- I've been seeing those Gitter guys around.
- It made me laugh.
I was like, he's a Gitter.
- Yeah.
- He gets stuff.
- I've been seeing those guys around.
- That's funny.
- I need someone to get something.
I'll call a Gitter.
- Dude, you know what they do?
It's actually, it's fucked up.
'Cause I saw the Gitter,
it was in Manhattan,
and what they do is they have little offices, right?
And they have, it's basically like
they rent out a grocery store and you order shit
and it goes straight from the thing.
Like I saw like a getter guy leaving on his bike.
- I saw a getter.
- I saw a getter leaving the getter office
and inside of it was just like one guy behind a counter
and it's all like, the wall was lined with like reeses
and like skittles and shit.
Like they have like their own grocery store.
- That is horrifying.
- That's so, like.
wall of Reese's and Skittles it's so it's so weird that no one has thought of that
before like why not just like a man cut out the middleman and just like have you
know that oh well I heard grocery store in New York City does grocery delivery
well I'm not I don't do that because I don't want to pay a slave I literally
love you doing that because I don't want to make somebody go to the grocery store
for me that is the absolute best part of that yeah going to the grocery store
or whatever is the no paying someone to go to the grocery store you know literally
the best thing the best invention no I don't want to go to the grocery store
ever I know the grocery store sucks fucking ass what's wrong with you eat
grocery delivery from the from the the grocery store there's a they're not
you don't get to pick your own like fruit out or anything though I tell them
get the best one they don't do that I'd really try there's a better one there's
a better one literally it is worth it for the power I hold over someone yeah
And when they text me and they say, I love you find this item, we use the
best part of it. No yeah, exactly. Can you look harder? Can you actually it's
probably behind love? Oh my God, I love when they say I can't find this item. I
sit and and they ask if there's a replacement saying, can you send a
picture? Yep, you said it. Oh my God, zooming in on the picture. This is not a
great photo. Caleb Pitts has removed the tip for this order. I did that one time.
Well no, hold on, because you're saying the power, the ultimate power is going to the grocery store and picking your own food.
Cucked, cucked, cucked, cucked, cucked, cucked, crunch, crunch, crunch, crunch.
Yeah, you are cucked. One time I did grocery delivery.
Actually, the ultimate power is going to the grocery store and selecting your own healthy options.
You are actually such a fucking cuck.
You are gay.
I don't care, the grocery store is awesome. Going to the store is awesome.
The grocery store sucks.
Going to the store is awesome.
What the fuck are you talking, you like errands now?
I love errands.
Something is wrong with you, man.
Something's changed.
You know what it is?
I've been riding bikes everywhere.
What?
How is that?
So you want to haul 50 bags of groceries on your bike home?
No, just enough for the week.
That's 50 for the carriage.
I would be okay with a grocery store if I had a car.
And the bag yet poking out the top.
Okay, all right.
So this is starting to make sense.
Yeah.
Yeah, you have a little mental image that you like to try to live up to.
You want to look like a--
You want to be a little Euro guy.
Yeah, you'll be riding your bike around the city getting getting a bag of groceries
Yeah, if you want to you want to pick an apple out and you want to use your you want to put some breath on it?
And then rub it on your shoe if I could eat a protein bag. Oh my god
You you you you you pulling up in front of your apartment and and just smoothly
Dismounting your bike and walking inside and saying honey. I'm home to your 13 year old girlfriend. Yeah. Oh my god
Oh, it'll be French. It'll be a friend
- That's exactly what you described.
- Uh-uh, that's not what I described at all.
- You know what, it's people in this country are lazy now
and no one likes going to the grocery store.
- Yeah, you're right.
Americans are lazy.
The fucking French on the other hand.
- I'm not talking about the French.
- Hardest workers in the world.
They take six months off every year.
- Oh my God, yeah.
If there's something I like about Europe
is that they get down to business.
- Yep, and how hard they work.
They have such a work ethic in Europe.
- They like to sweat.
- Yep, that's right.
- I mean, they do like to sweat, actually.
- There's no such thing locally.
You know, that's right. I mean they do like to sweat.
There's no such thing.
They do not do anything about that.
French people love to sweat.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
They love to get in the dirt.
They love, you know, they love dirt under their fingernails.
It's really a cultural difference.
They just like working, you know what I mean?
You've seen that video of Serge Gainsborough and all those little kids are singing to him and they're like dressed up like him?
Gainsborough?
Who's the...
It's like all these like French kids singing to this guy who is weeping.
weeping because they all dress up like him and they're all pretending to smoke
and drink and he's like he's full on weeping. Yeah, I think in France you can
smoke and drink at age five. Yes, okay, he mixed up William s burrows and
search Gainsbourg. Yeah, yeah, I don't give a fuck. That's right. I just
wondered yeah, but you're talking about oh the one time I did well yeah, he
looks sweaty as hell in that video, but anyway, the one time I did grocery
was when I had COVID in December,
and I had like a bunch of gin in my fridge,
and I was like, "Oh, I should get some tonic water
"or something."
And the guy was like, he called me and was like,
"They don't have that.
"Do you want just plain tonic water?
"They have flavored and they have plain."
And I was like, "Oh, just get me the plain one."
And he showed up with like three big bottles of like--
- More like three gallon chunks of water.
- I fucking, dude.
How do I like I can't report that and say this is the wrong you would report it.
You would never know.
I love that's the best but one of the best parts of instacart is when they
mess up your order and you get to eat something that you would never eat.
I have to like they like one time we like we ordered on sound fun.
Do not okay.
No, it's no we one time on on on on like on when we were getting grocery
delivery or something.
We were trying to get two sweet potatoes, right?
and we got and the guy brought us two giant bags of sweet potatoes and we got
to eat a lot of sweet potatoes. I tried to get I made an order. I saw they added
Walmart on Instacart. Yeah, maybe six months ago. Yeah, I made an order. I
wanted to get some smoothie stuff so I could make some. Oh my God. I got
some frozen berries like a couple of big bags of frozen berries. They
apparently didn't have them. So she gave me six bags of frozen carrots.
That's what I'm talking about. She's like sweaty and she was like she's like
I'm sorry I'm late and I was like I'm never using this fucking app again, at
least not for Walmart. The Walmart one every I you should be able to message
the person and be like can you look at the blu-ray section for me.
Is there anything interesting in the blu-ray? Do they have any box sets? Yeah.
What's it looking like over there? You should just hire someone to live your
entire life too. Yeah. That sounds awesome to me. Yeah. You should pay
someone to pretend to be you and like and fuck your girlfriend. Yeah. Be
awesome no that would not be awesome trust me they can do everything but that
you do anything but that anything to my house fuck yeah do whatever you want to
my house do what you want in my house but don't try and get between don't try
and get in the bedroom with me hell no hell no you can fuck me you can fuck my
couch you can fuck the cantaloupe you just bought me I don't know but don't
you dare try and fuck my sweet lady. What's the point of house sitting? House sitting is so...
You don't have any dogs. It's an excuse to pay somebody who's a fuck up. Oh. Yeah. Yeah.
It's like when you have like a... Your cousin's out of rehab. Exactly. Yeah. Or like a family
member. You need to water my plants. When you're 26 and you're living at home and your uncle's
like, "Actually, we're going out of town. I guess we need someone to watch our house."
That's so smart. Your cousin's out of rehab and then you put him in a house alone with a cabinet
full of opiates from your dental surgery for six days. That's really, really smart.
Yeah. No, it's when you have a neighbor who thinks that you're going to fail in life and
you need $100 this week. Yeah. I guess I did some house sitting when I was a kid.
Yeah, that's what it is. I would love to house sit right now.
I think house sitting also- I'm tired of my apartment.
If someone's really rich and they have a villa or something, then it's a favor you can do someone.
We got to go on tour again soon. I'm so tired of my apartment. We had a shower problem.
but we're going somewhere. Oh yeah, we are. We're going to Seattle and well,
yeah, we're going to Seattle and Portland, but that's not soon enough.
That's soon enough. That's pretty soon. That's very, I am,
I am leaving for a couple of days. What are you guys going to do for my birthday
for your birthday? We should go buddy. I'm going to light off some fireworks.
For real. Yeah. Is there anywhere to watch fireworks around here? Yeah. Yeah.
And you're literally my old.
We got a window four days before 4th of July and four days after.
and they're just nonstop fireworks. It sucks.
The worst part of living in New York is the fireworks.
- Dude, literally, it wasn't even 4th of July,
last April when I first moved here,
the people in the building next door to mine
would just light off fireworks every other night.
- That was the government destabilizing us for the riots.
- It's so smart that fireworks sound
exactly like gunshots.
- Yeah.
- It's awesome. It's great.
- Yeah. Well, the difference is--
- They don't sound exactly like gunshots.
- Yeah, the difference is usually,
if it's a firework, they shoot off and suddenly
you hear someone go yeah. If it's a gunshot, you hear someone shoot it and
they go, "Ha ha ha, I shot you."
What if they... No, you can be so happy after you kill somebody,
they go, "Yeah." It's a different type, but it's usually... Okay, firework is
when you hear, "Yay," and then gunshot is also, "Yay," but then at the
same time, quieter, you hear, "Oh." True.
Yeah, like dying in Counter Strike. Yeah, exactly. "We'll get 'em next time."
That's awesome in video games. Mission failed. We'll get 'em next time,
hear that gunshot soap mctavish is running around the streets of New York
City he actually sublets my apartment soap mctavish I would love to someone for
someone to sublet my maybe it's just soap and then general mctavish you're
gonna soak my shower got clogged we had to call the guy super so it got clogged
with soap I clogged I was using too much soap that's you know I've taken too many
bath bombs and how did wait did you shave your head in the bathroom no I didn't I
I shaved it in my room on top of a trash bag.
Someone was fucking the drain.
Yep.
I think my Instacart guy was fucking my drain.
Someone was fucking the drain.
Your penis fell off into the drain.
I have maybe, I have one of the worst upstairs neighbors ever.
Really?
Yeah, the heavy from TF2.
That's fucking annoying.
He's so fucking annoying.
Yeah.
He's shooting his mini gun at 3am.
Put me Spencer here.
Oh my god.
It's like, can you learn to walk lightly?
That's right.
I hear every time he walks, it's his footsteps.
What happens if he's walking?
He's walking.
I'm walking upstairs.
Yeah, I know.
And when he's fucking the spy dressed as a woman.
Oh my god.
I'm walking upstairs to tell him to keep it down
and in the hallway I hear this
*mimics the sound of a man eating a sandwich*
He literally can't make a sandwich without saying sandwich.
Yeah, so fucking annoying dude.
Yeah.
He is horrible.
And then he comes downstairs and tries to capture my apartment.
apartment. You stand in my apartment for 30 seconds. You
stand for 30 minutes. It's not your f*****g apartment. Yeah,
you can't capture it. Yeah, he's trying to wall hack. He's
trying to like he's trying to go through my wall to capture
my house. Yeah. He is so I do. I missed it. I had two posters
in my room. The problem with it now is that it's like all it's
all bots and stuff. Yeah. You can't play without a bot. It's
been like ruining it. Here's the idea man. Just just release
again yeah easy bro that literally yeah yeah that game did rock they probably
have to add some dude we should we should start a private server after this we
should just all play the f2 in here I'm I used to do that with my friends so much
in middle school in high school just private TF2 servers dude it's so much
dude so private private modern warfare lobbies oh yeah quick scoping oh no I
used to be like a semi pro quick scoper that's pretty sick you told me that
before that's so that's like Noah has done like intro videos
videos. Yeah for like like and box and all these like yeah 13 is making shit
in blender. That's such a world that I missed it was the like people who like
kids who got into like After Effects. Yeah they can make a cool-ass montage.
That's the funniest thing to look up. And now all those people are like pretty successful
because that's like obviously. You know that clip in the middle of that that Cod video
where it's um just the guy sitting on the toilet jacking off that cuts to for like
one second and it like sprays calm. That's the best. Dude, so funny. Yeah.
The funny one of the really good YouTube search is just like, like a name and
then intro video. Yeah. Like if you look up like Patrick intro video or like
Tanner intro video and it's like some kid who just learned cinema 4d. Patrick
is a sick name as your, your like alias as a call of duty player. Yeah. Patrick.
Yep. I think that's Patrick. I think I'm going to, I'm going to learn this
week I'm gonna look at like a tutorial from like 2006 any video that you post
anywhere you should just have that kind of an intro at the yeah yeah it's like
yeah yeah and the yeah it's going in and out when that pendulum 40 seconds
apology video yeah the pendulum pendulum witchcraft like the the drums that lead
up to the drop that and then like hey what's up I just want to apologize for
what I said recently is not so right.
- Said a lot of things, a lot of bad things on the podcast.
- I'd like to apologize for what I did
at Thought Week in Philadelphia.
- I said a lot of things.
- I send, I send, they say the women are recovering though.
The thoughts, I killed the thoughts.
- I killed all the thoughts.
- I killed some thoughts.
What the hell was that?
- Something's in my throat.
- Can't even talk about thoughts around this guy.
- Yeah, he's making me feel sick.
- Oh my God, I don't want to think about thoughts.
man. God, I mean, that that harlot over there obfuscating the law of God.
Yep, she's obscene. She's obfuscating the law of God. Yeah, I think so. Yeah,
man, I do. I do so well at thought week as a male thought.
You'd be a male thought. If you ever decide to be a male thought, I will
kill you. Really? I will chop your head off. You already, he's kind of, do you
think how what percentage male thought do you think he's at right now? Yeah. I mean
he's kind of locked up right now. I feel like he's got it he's like I mean with
his arm like that it's true yeah up from a six to a seven percent percent seven
percent. Seven percent. That's safe. Second it hits 51 percent. You done.
Toxic gas. Disowning you. Disowning you, your body and your life with toxic gas.
But you're pretty low. That's low. I'm glad I'm glad it's a low reader. If your
daughter was a thought would you kill her no no I would I would I would send her to
like an obedience camp yeah I would do some Rapunzel type shit yeah yeah yeah
dude it must be so like that's why we need we need Charles Manson still around
to keep the thoughts under control yeah like at least so just a complete like
gratifying to a light it's essentially yeah I mean it's fine guys a family type
I think that's like a traveling circus, but for thoughts like a
traveling circus is so every weird kid can run away and their parents enough to
deal with them anymore. So the thoughts can run away. The thoughts can run away.
It's weird to be one. Yeah, exactly. Yeah, and they can you know yeah they can
travel. It must be so gratifying to be you know in a cult. It's probably the
best thing in the world. If you're like you know one of the favorites. I think people play pretty
loose with the term cult. Yeah. Yeah, I heard um. Well Jared Leto has one. I heard
that guy fucking Adam from the Norm Macdonald show he talked about some like him he grew
up in like a cult and it was like it was like a boarding school and they just yeah they
they spit on you that's I mean I mean the thing I think that pretty much every every
group of people is a cult I disagree well no I think you gotta have sex for it to be
a cult Jared Leto is doing that Jared Leto did that you can't be coded you can't have
a cult of your celebrity though. No Jared Leto has a cult. People just want to fuck you. He
has a cult where he makes them sign NDAs. That's just the, that's, the second you sign
an NDA it's not a cult anymore. It has a legal framework. I guess it's true. What is his
cult? What is he doing? He's like bringing people to the, I don't know, like Joshua Tree
or some shit and he's having them wear white robes with him. It's a vacation. I, dude,
I fucking hate when I go to McDonald's and the cult is there. They're all wearing the
same shirt yeah behind the register not see that this is 1984 and you've been
brainwashed yeah you guys at least wear different shirts you're all working the
same job yeah exactly it's a costing man Jared Leto not a guy I would be sad if
he if he what are you afraid to say you'd be you'd be happy if Jared Leto
died you even I'm afraid of qualified it so many times I know yeah not a guy that
I would be not happy or you if dot dot say if he died yeah you almost said you
almost said passed away which is the softest possible way to say it - I would
not be sad if he passed away the fuck kind of it's just a fucking guy you just
say you want him dead I don't want him dead sounds like you do you what I want
me you want him to live you don't want him to ever die you want him to be a
you want to live forever call Jared pedo Jared pedo pedophile I think he's a pad
I think he's Jared peddling these fucking dog shit movies to me in the cinema
every week yep he sucks so bad he's I'm I've I hate him so much he really sucks
I like there there's no there's never been a good I mean he's been in but yeah
besides just being like an evil guy he just he's just so annoying yeah he just
sucks so bad. He literally like, like him and fucking Ezra Miller are on the same
tier of like psychopath but like he's just better at like making people sign
NDAs because he's like 50. I think they're on the same tier of people that
I don't give a fuck about hearing a single word about. Yeah. Who cares dude?
I'm more concerned with having somebody to hate. Just that's what your parents are for.
you know you know who's very pro thought week Jared Leto good he sounds like a
beast yeah what I mean supporting thought week makes it makes me makes me happy
because it shows the evil is banding together we can extinguish
them all yeah exactly one well-placed one one boot heel mm-hmm grind them into
the ground oh my god oh my god grinding a thought into the ground with my boot
(laughing)
- Nah, thoughts don't deserve that.
- No, that's too far.
- Death is too far for the thoughts.
They only deserve eternal damnation.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Well, they've already got that.
- I would like to see-- - 'Cause hell,
they're already in hell. - I would like to see--
- They're in Philly. - Listen.
- That's right.
- Thoughts, they're sinning, they're horrible.
I hate them, but I would like to see them cured.
- Yep.
- I'd like to-- - I can't stand here
and preach death, okay?
Obviously, the doctrine of the thought
going to lead for death and suffering for millions if it's allowed to wreak havoc
over the face of the earth but I listen I I pray that they all find
salvation beyond this world and in the next yep because they are not gonna make
it to 25 because I'm gonna be killing hey I'm but if we're talking body count
they're probably make it a 2500 honestly so violent today I think something pissed
us off that week yeah you you're just less violent than normal they were on
the same level as we always are you you're not even saying that you want to
kill Jared Leto yeah yeah something's going on something is what are you what
is what's happening you got a depression you got one tattoo you got soft I
depression and anxiety no you don't you do look like the sad one from inside out
which one the girl the one who's the blue yeah the blue one when it's played
by Phyllis yeah you look like the Phyllis one yeah I have depression and
anxiety yeah, I can tell yeah, there's been a lot of depressing depressing
stuff that's been happening. What's been depressing you? I don't have a bike. I
almost brought you one today and I'd for I it was my car was too far away and
then I have to drive back to my apartment to pick up my laundry. I my
laundry is piling up. That's awful. That's you. I got back into Pokemon. I'm
fucking hating this shape. My head is terrible.
This is really horrible.
And have you eaten any candy recently?
I wasn't eating meat for a couple days and then I think before this I accidentally, I
asked the guy at the bodega for falafel over rice and he just gave me lamb over rice.
And you just ate it?
I just ate it.
I've been trying to eat more meat.
Yeah, me too.
I've been trying to eat my meat intake.
My meat intake.
It's a bison.
It's so shit.
Yeah, it's horrible.
It's fucking terrible.
I think you need meat.
I think it's horrible, but I do think that you need to have...
Unfortunately, yeah.
Eat red meat all the time.
I do.
I think you need it.
I think that those guys who eat just meat are almost completely right.
The guys who just eat meat and a mango every day, I bet they're going to live forever.
I think you...
Cholesterol is made up.
I think you need meat.
Yeah.
I think you need to eat it.
Think about it.
Why would they...
I can't eat fruits anyway, so if I'm picking out a snack, it has to be some kind of beef
beef jerky. I'm allergic to every fruit. That's why I have depression and anxiety.
You're eating too much.
I can't even.
You're eating too many GMOs.
True, that's probably what it is.
You know that thing where Alex Jones says that the pesticides are making the
frogs gay?
Yeah.
You know that's actually real?
It's true, yeah.
It's so crazy.
Well, it turns them female or something.
Yeah, something like that. It just like messes with their penises.
It changes their hormones.
Yeah, it's pretty cool.
they're it's all fucked they're not turning gay they're turning I think most
of most of what it's pretty gay actually yeah most of what Alex Jones says is
pretty much true yeah he just gets a little too crazy
something he's a little he goes a little over the top yeah but he's mostly just
talking I don't know if you guys have watched it a lot of is just him talking
about TV and movies and he's pretty right yeah he'll just say kind of stuff
about the office it is that is Jim and Pam they should be together and Pam they
They belong together.
It's true love.
He's the actual comedic relief, not Michael.
I'm sure a lot of people have the same...
Michael's just kind of an idiot.
I don't know.
I don't know anyone else seeing this.
Michael Scott is just kind of stupid.
He's just kind of an idiot.
I don't want to say it, but if I worked at that office, I would quit.
I'd put in my two weeks within two weeks.
I would not stay working there.
Dwight Schrute, let me tell you.
It's a non-professional environment.
The warehouse, that seems kind of fun.
the player outside the play basketball down their church versus kids
i'd be down there
you know what else i've had a bit i just gotta say this quite true
great man
i'd be happy best friends with him
is a good man to a tree to get that basically what what fucking what system
show called truth awesome
on the show called uh... in for a little wars yeah i feel like a lot of people
probably had the same experience is me or you're a dog in the human
They're going on adventures folks, people love it.
He's going over the garden wall.
He's going over.
And you know Mordecai, Mordecai and Rigby.
Mordecai can't, he can't seem to find true love.
Rigby, he's a feminine.
This Rigby character, he's a bad, he's a poor role model.
He's a feminine.
He's a weak little boy.
We shouldn't be letting our kids watch this show.
Adventure Time, that's a much more, that's a positive show.
Jake the Dog.
loves he loves marceline i don't know i can't tell you i can't tell you what is going to
happen next bubblegum she's a lesbian now they made her a lesbian they're putting chemicals
in cartoon networks but i do have some predictions i think maybe jake the dog is going to turn a
little bit bigger he can change it anything he wants folks i turned on the tv i have incredible
news dr who has saved the day dr who she's a woman now that's okay they're going they went back in
time they took folks this redness really happened they took Vincent van Gogh they
brought him back in time he doesn't want to stay the little I the Liberals want
to change the name of the TARDIS they say you can't call the TARDIS anymore
you can't call it the TARDIS I don't know why dude did you hit him on Rogan
is the best I think the best radio show you can possibly oh yeah he overheats
he's like a basketball player who takes too many threes he'll like be saying
some stuff and Rogan will be like oh yeah cool yeah and it'll be like fucking like
the frog thing or anything like that or like Sandy Hook was done by Godzilla and
then Joe be like whoa whoa slow down I'm sorry I'm just yeah pretty excited he
can't he's he can't control himself yeah it's so cool it's incredible he's just
like a fuck he's like a he's a he's a he's a poor thing you know for cookie
fortunes about like conspiracies he's a bull who's like getting ready to charge
charge yeah yeah and then he just well that's that's yeah. I feel like that's
the initial experience every video you see of him is when he's charged up and
he's on but then the thing is most of his show. I would say like 90% of his
show is him getting ready to charge up to that point. There's probably a
short four minutes. He's like I got yeah, I got to take a sip of water. Yeah,
he'll blow it, blow out a candle. You know what you know it's one of his his
best. I don't know if you guys have seen these. You just look it up his his
Bill Gates impressions. He has impressions of Bill Gates. I'll let me
if I can look one up. He literally does like the...
I'm Bill Gates!
Is that a good impression? No.
It is a good impression. Spot on.
Yeah, it's spot on, exactly.
Folks, if you open up command prompt, you open up command prompt, you type in a couple things, and you can watch the
entirety of Star Wars in command prompt. They're saying don't delete system 32. You got to do it.
Why can't you delete system 32? It'll speed up your computer. Watch Alex Jones impersonate
Bernie Sanders and Bill Gates. You can download more RAM. They don't want you to
download more RAM. It's true. All right here it is.
*Bill Gates impression*
You have to watch it
Obama. I was raised by the Ford Foundation and Carnegie Endowment. Welcome to McDonalds, may I help you? I'm Benny Vanders. Thank you, Satan, for all your love. Signed, Cheryl Sandberg. Jabba the Hutt.
(laughter)
- That's good, dude.
- He is the best.
- That's a really strong Jabba.
- So sick.
(laughter)
- So fucking sick.
- Just throwing Jabba in there, man.
Had to get it in.
- Yeah.
- What a great orange.
- Who's that?
- Dude, he's serious fucking Frank Caliendo.
- Yeah.
- He looks like him, too.
- He does look like him, yeah.
- Okay, he looks like Frank Caliendo.
- Yeah, I don't think he's Bill Hicks,
I think he's Frank Caliendo.
- Yep.
- Yep, that's right.
(laughter)
- People don't want you to know that Frank Caliendo
died years ago and he turned into Alex Jones. Portland. Portland. PDX. Yeah. PDX.
S E A T T L E. S E A. The Dirty Northwest. Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Yeah. The Dirty Pacific.
I what I like about you guys is you will never put up with Thought Week. Yeah.
Yeah. You guys are putting into that. Yep. You're more intelligent. Yep. Full of that.
Listen one thing we can say about Portland is Seattle two cities full of
real patriots. Yep, yep, yeah, two cities, real salt of the earth people and
working, working folk, working folk, yep, tilling, tilling the ground for
emails all day. That's right, yeah. These people grind their own coffee
beans, probably with their teeth. They're so fucking tough up there. Never
been, but I'm excited to meet these, these freaking, freaking navy blue
collar with all these denim jackets and denim pants, yep, and with patches on
them. Yep, damn, they got patches and actually earrings too. Yeah, blue hair
collar. Yeah, yeah, yeah, hey, yeah, yeah, yeah, hey, hey, one, two, hey, yeah,
yep, that's right. I wasn't sure if my mic was on. No, it was on. Yeah, okay,
cool. I was here now. August 18th and 19th, swagpoop.com/shows to buy tickets.
Please buy tickets. Please buy tickets. I need to get the fuck out of my
apartment. I need it so much. This is your last chance for it to see the tour.
Yep. This tour will be... We're never gonna do live shows again. This show is
gonna be retired, okay? Whatever, yeah. It's gonna be retired. We're not doing
never again after after this these last few shows. So if you you should listen I
were flying to Portland in Seattle. So I'm not you know if you don't live there you
should fly there too. I don't know we're flying there you might as well fly there.
You could be on the same plane as us and you could buy us chips. Yeah could happen.
On jet. On me. Yeah you could save three bags of chips for those those handsome devils in
because we will be dressed as the devils. We'll be in devil costumes on the plane.
- Yeah.
- All right, bye.
- Bye.