you're listening to Israel's number one pod
this is premium content
if you are not a premium subscriber
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately
*screech*
okay, welcome
yeah, welcome
welcome
back at it
back at it again
when my friend came
ahhh
sorry i dropped my jewel
- Do you scream when you drop your jewels?
- I scream, I'm very easily startled,
you know that about me.
- I scream easily.
- I do scream easily.
There was a long period of time where I would,
I had to like fight to erase this instinct,
but anytime I opened a door at the same time
as somebody else and we would like
almost run into each other, I would just go, "Ahh!"
And just strangers and they--
- They hate you for it.
- I think they didn't, yeah.
Yeah, and then I got, and then I took an arrow to the knee.
and then i thought yeah and that's the story
nice damn
damn you know you have
double the cats
uh...
uh... is he is right here is right behind you and then don't turn around
that's fucker
how can you tell them apart
yoda's bigger right? fucker has more hair
i thought yoda was fatter but no he's actually he feels lighter
interesting
cat science
cat for now here
poker as a hairy tail
what is the brand of catholic they are
their sphinxes
means intercats
their sphincter that's a kind of cat you'd like yeah i was a little bit
younger cast a guy's thing
his thingy
the guys not guys dingy
i'm putting my thingy in this thingy
i'm putting my thingy on a thing
i'm putting my thingy in a thing if you know what i'm talking about
I know what you're talking about.
What did you guys do today?
Anything fun?
Or this week?
I don't know, I haven't talked to you in a while.
Yeah, I went to, um, so I fuckin', oh shit.
Oh shit!
No, the cat's doing something.
What the?
Goddammit, that's not good.
Alright, hold up.
Um, oh, so I, um, I went to Great Wolf Lodge for my nephew's birthday today.
What's that?
like an indoor water park. Damn that sounds sick. Yeah but I didn't, so Dom and I went
over, we went to Fitchburg to see him, to like see my sister and like you know go
see my nephew and like we were supposed to get wristbands to like go anywhere in
that place and we just like straight up just like walked in and did... I should
probably let them out. We just straight up like walked in and just didn't like
check with the front desk or anything and then we were like going around doing
shit and I don't know I feel like security there was just really fucking
bad. Really lax. Good to know. Yeah. Everybody is listening. Yeah. Head down to
big big dog big dog big dog software solutions whatever was that Patrick was
talking about can that one day when you and me walked around downtown Boston
looking for a place called the pedophile law child child pornography yeah there's
a there's a listing on Google for on Facebook for the child pornography law
firm somewhere in downtown Boston. Milk Street? Yeah, yeah. And we walked for like 30
minutes just trying so desperately to find it and we like walked in somewhere
and just like looked at the directory and it clearly didn't exist. Yeah, it was really
upsetting. It was such a bummer because that I just wanted to just pick their
brain a little bit. Wanted to take a cool picture with their sign. I just wanted to
find out honestly I just wanted to find out which whose side they were on. The
children there you are or the poor yeah they are at odds yeah that was when I
went through a phase of just going on unlike messenger Facebook messenger you
can just send like you can search for a location and like just send people
random locations and this like Google Maps just has a bunch of stuff that
people just put in there yeah like there's a fake Chick-fil-a and shit but
there was one I remember that's called like there was like in the middle of
nowhere and it was called like two guys just but fucking it. I want to make a
pilgrimage to two guys just butt fucking it. You go there and they just are.
Just two guys on the side of the road. Just butt fucking it. Just covered in dust and old.
Thousands of years old. Yeah. Just two decrepit like two ancient Mesoamericans.
Americans kept alive. Yeah, right. Yeah, bronze man. Yeah, like those like those
monks that are stuck in Buddhas. They're like the statues. The terracotta army in
China. Yeah. What's that? That's an army of stone soldiers that they uncovered
underground. That's extremely scary to me. Yeah. Take it back. You're gonna scream?
No. No, I unlearned that habit. All right. Yeah. What if you opened the door and a
on the other side when you scream scary scary scary stuff scary times we're
living in man absolutely absolutely just next thing you know Dracula could be on
TV in the Senate or on TV. They could let Dracula on TV now. That would be scary as hell.
I know man I'd have to turn that off yeah I'd be like I'd shut the TV off immediately. I'd change the channel
immediately what if he's on every channel oh I can't even imagine. Welcome
back to the Dracula show. Yeah, oh my, well, yeah, there's a different bloodsucker
given the State of the Union. More like the fangs of the Union. The blood of the Union
address is what he would call it if he was the president. Yeah. Yeah, President
Dracula. President Evil. Who's in President Dracula's cabinet? Mummy. Oh, I'm
sorry his crypt. Yeah, the wolf man. His coffin. His vice president Frankenstein.
The first female Frankenstein. Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde have two separate seats.
True, and he switches between them based on what time of day it is. Based on how
hungry he is I think it is. Does he drink a potion that turns him into the scary guy or is it a day/night
thing. No, it's a metaphor for having a boner. Yeah, that's true. So it's when he sees a hot
lady he turns into Mr. Hide. He turns into Mr. Hide and he gets a boner? Yeah. Wow, Mr.
High Penis. Yeah, High Penis. I have a high penis. Mr. Hiding My Erection. Damn, my penis
is so high. That's what I say. Yeah. Because I have an extremely tall penis. Yeah. Yeah.
That's because it has an eyeball on the end and it goes bloodshot. I wish. Yeah. An eyeball
on the tip of your penis.
- A bloodshot eye.
Clear sign of a weed smoker too.
- Instead of peeing, it cries.
- The eye of Sauron was so high.
Did you see that mother,
how bloodshot that motherfucker was?
- That's so true.
- Just a big red eye.
I know you've been smoking, playa.
Shit.
What are you picking at, Patrick?
What's in your mustache?
- Oh, it's just my mustache.
- Mustache looking very strong right now.
- Yeah, it looks cool.
i'm into a for a month
congrats
why are you raising money
now as you know it's noveno no straight nose of ember of november
no that's where none of them very very uh... it's no belief
novi novio member is no real november
no real burn burn don't say that that is not an indian national park in tired
Why don't you take a shot of...
We were supposed to go at like 11am to meet up with them
and we were up till like 3 just hanging out
and then I just like, I don't know, we stayed up till 3
and then had to make a bus at 8 or 7 or 8
yeah 8 to go like pick up Dom's car
and I didn't sleep on the bus like an idiot
dumb dumb yeah boo now I'm like I've gotten like two hours of sleep and I
gotta go and I got nine o'clock shift tomorrow it's okay you can take the
night off me and cam got it from here yeah yeah yeah hey cam yeah do which
side of a frog would you have want to have sex with more than mouth or the ass
the left side of a frog of a frog the left side no left there is no hole there
which means that you have zero you know there's half no there's half of the
mouth and half of the ass so that's one hole it's not okay okay imagine if you
will a frog I can't stop imagine okay now draw a line down its body like so
there's it's one arm and one leg on each on each side acting uh-huh
no it's drawing a line you're on bisected it yet now be about now bisect
it okay I'm with you and so cut it yeah and fold it around so fold it like a
fortune cookie mmm so the the hole in the middle of the frog you close it up you
fold it on itself now the mouth is connected to the ass becomes one hole
how many times can you fold a frog and once just once this one's a frog
infinity times really my bad even if you if you fold the frog that many times the
frog becomes bigger actually. That's that is the most terrifying thing I've ever
heard. Yeah but no to answer your question I would not fuck a frog because
you have no idea where that thing's been. For all you know that could have been on
like a lily pad. For all you know some other guy just fucked it and he had an STD.
And he had a disgusting penis. Yeah. I could. I used to get pimples on my penis. I never. I haven't done that.
- I never.
- Well, I never.
- I used to get pimples on the shaft of my penis
and I would pop them and it was pretty cool.
- That's disgusting.
- That's not disgusting.
- That's just gross.
- It's just a young man exploring his body.
I don't know what's so wrong about that.
You're wrong.
- I've never been a pimple popper.
I don't pop pimples.
- I love it, dude.
I was telling people last night, my friend had a cyst.
I'm sorry, my friend's dad had a cyst.
telling people last night that your friend's dad had a cyst. Yeah, I did, because we were talking
about pimple popping and my friend's dad had a cyst and we would try to, we were trying to convince
him to like put stuff on the cyst that would make it come to a head because he'd had it for like
10 years or whatever. Yeah. We were like, yeah man, you know what'll make that cyst go away?
Just tons of coconut oil every night before you go to sleep, which is like what'll bring it to a head.
yeah and uh... we've time i moved out of the state before it ever
and arrived dot daniel higher over there
there is a from the old yep there is
it's so funny how here in l_a_ just like
the cars just don't move out of the way
yeah for an ambulance is there on a
now it's worse in l_a_ it's much worse really people don't try they don't even
like move at all
the the and it just goes on like the opposite side of the street around
traffic yeah shit
- Like in Boston they like at least try to pull over.
- Fuck the firefighters. - And now they just
don't care, it's so funny.
- Fuck the firefighters.
- Yeah man, I have to go be an office PA for this new--
- I have to be the guy that holds the money
for Billy on the street.
- Yeah, exactly.
- This is much more important than some old man
who has had some kind of--
- He's had a long and fulfilling life,
just let him die, who cares?
Also, what, is he on fire?
Is that why you're sending a fire truck?
It can't be that bad.
- It's not that bad.
- I've been on fire before.
- Somebody recently told me that you can buy a fire truck
for like $3,000.
- Oh yeah, they sell them in like Northern New Hampshire.
There's like, they buy like old ones
and then re like fix them and shit.
And then they just kind of sell like that and ambulances.
I've seen like used auto, like used car lots have them.
- Do you have to have like a,
can I drive it with just like a class C license,
just like a regular license?
Can I drive a fire truck?
I think you might need like a CDL.
That would be so baller.
Yeah.
Let's all go three Z's on a fire truck
when we get back to Boston.
Yeah, all right, yeah.
Sound good?
Damn, something's really going on.
Yeah.
There's a party.
There's a fire truck party.
Having a big party.
Yeah.
All the firemen are invited.
They're all going to a drive-in theater.
I don't think that's true.
They are, man.
It's firefighters and night out.
I really sincerely doubt that.
You're filming Firefighters Night Out.
It's a movie.
It's a movie and then they're going to play the movie at the Drive-In Theater.
Today I found this Etsy account that makes like these realistic baby monsters and like
I was googling, I just googled like small creature or something and I found this like
really weird looking like alien baby thing and I was like what the fuck is this and I
I clicked on it and I was like on it was an Etsy item and it's like there's it's
a one-of-a-kind and it's like a thousand dollars and it's called skangoo alien
baby terrifying I was like what the fuck is a skangoo and I googled skangoo and
the only and it was actually yo mama the only thing that came up was the Etsy
thing the Etsy thing itself and then I go fund me that was like help me make a
thousand dollars to buy a baby skangoo there's no other I put it in Google
translate it doesn't mean anything it literally it's just a word that someone
made up to describe this alien baby. Skangu. I want to show you...
Why do you keep sending images? I'm pretty good. Patrick, I know for a fact that
this episode is gonna have Patrick clicking a hundred times a second on his
mouse and it's just gonna be deafening. Patrick got a gaming mouse specifically
so he could have very loud clicks and catch up on the microphone.
Yeah, this isn't even a...
That's a gaming mouse. Anything is a gaming mouse
if you're a big enough gamer, buddy.
Yeah.
We're going to
a birthday party tonight. Two birthdays
back to back.
Back to back to back. Hollywood is crazy, dude.
Everyone be having birthdays
in Hollywood. Pierce's birthday was yesterday
and then Ryan's birthday is
tonight. Sorry, did I just
dox Ryan? Yeah, he's having a
birthday yeah Wow he's seriously having a birthday pretty fucked up yeah I I I
yeah I love birthdays that was sort of what I was getting at is that birthdays
are what I live for a sign X slice a cake yes please what's the best birthday
party you ever had. Candles. Sorry.
[Laughter]
That's stupid. You interrupted me. I'm sorry.
Candles. When candles the clown came to your birthday party.
Napkins. Yeah. That was all you remember?
Wrapping paper. Cool. Ice...
Ice. Ice. No ice. Birthday party is not complete without ice. I don't know if I've ever had a...
I used to I used to go and see all the new Transformers movies when they came
out for the first like three of them. Did they always come out near your birthday?
Yeah they always came out like either on my birthday or around my birthday cuz my
birthday is July 4th and you know there's some American ass movies. Yeah that's some
1776 Japanese robots what hey hey Michael Bay can we have a talk please I like to
strap in here's my thread about transformers they're Japanese it's I
don't even think they are Japanese I know they're from space yeah the
franchise they're from mega is the franchise is it an American franchise
spaceship I don't know from Cybertron first of all you guys are gonna fucking
pussyfoot around it we were trying to afraid to say the word cybercrime
you say the c-word on pod cybercrime you broke the barrier there for Cybertron
isn't it a cube planet they're from no you're thinking of the all spark no but I
think it's a cube I know that it's moon is not a cube those motherfuckers are no
no you know what it's not a cube because or at least in the Michael Bay movies
cuz in Dark of the Moon they build a portal and remember they try and bring
the plant Cybertron to earth and when it comes through the portal it's a sphere
because they cut it out because they close the portal and it cuts it off and
it's like part of a planet that this you would know if you're a real transformer
cyber head I've been thinking well he never seen you I think I want to rewatch
all of them dude I've only seen the first three but um so cool man they are
cool they're fucking sick I would say the easily in my eyes the best like
visual effects of any movie yeah I mean it's insane because like all the
explosions and shit are real. I feel like when it came out it got so looked down upon and
then you look back and you're like, damn. Like you look back at that and then you look
at like... Damn, Megan Fox was hot as fuck. Dude, Optimus Prime was fucking thick. Oh
my god dude, Megan Fox in those tiny little baby jeans. And Starscream too was so hot.
Starscream and Megan Fox? Wouldn't Starscream turn into a gun? No, that's what was hot. Starscream
is a plane yeah wait oh wait never mind that was Megatron I like those two
gangsta transformers from the second one yeah where it's Tom Kenny doing black
scent yeah man yeah those things were for like little RV one yeah yeah this
bitch trippin yeah yeah and they're little tiny that's awesome it's just
funny the idea that like they would come to earth with those actions well no those
Those were created by the shard of the Allspark.
So those weren't from outer space.
So they were around people they picked up accents from.
That's my personal theory.
It's not appropriating in any way.
Yeah, no, Tom Kenny is black.
True.
That's true.
Tom Kenny's invited to the cookout for sure.
Yeah, Tom Kenny, you can come to the cookout.
Says me.
Says Pat.
Pat is the head of the CEO.
He's the CEO head.
I'm the CEO of the cookout.
That's me.
I'm the CEO.
I was wanting them to make a Beast Wars movie.
Yeah.
Beast Wars was way cooler.
Yeah, it is a cooler concept.
Yeah.
Beasts are way cooler than cars.
That's why I like, did you ever watch Zoids?
I played the Zoids Game Boy game.
They had an RPG called Zoids Legacy.
are
is fucking sick. That's true. It's just it's always cool. I just like big stuff. I
like any movie that has a giant wave. That's like a genre of movie that I
really like. I like a movie where you can see the moon in the sky cuz I'm like
damn if you think about how big the moon is that's gotta be one of the biggest
things you can show on TV. Anytime there's a there's an establishing shot
of Earth I'm like damn that thing's big. Not as big as the moon though.
That's true. Yeah. Yeah, because the moon's closer to the camera. What? So that's why.
No, it looks further away. Not the movies I watch. It'd be cool if the moon was the
same size. As Earth? Can you imagine? Somebody should make a video that shows
what it would be like if the moon was the same size as Earth. Yeah. Here's what it would
be like if the moon was the same size. Yeah. In parentheses, as Earth. And they
spun around each other like two beautiful dancers. Right? And they were sort of each
other's moons. Yeah. Yeah. Man, what if? This is gonna be the best summer of our
lives. I'm trying to decide what to do with my girlfriends in town for the next week.
Trying to figure out fun stuff to do. Yeah, there's not that much. Probably go eat out a lot.
Yeah, go hiking. There's some good hiking around here.
We're gonna go to Montana del Oro.
Nice.
Which is on the coast.
I would not want to go hiking anywhere.
That's because you're a big fan.
Yeah, you're gay.
Come on.
No.
Why would you not want to go hiking?
Because it's boring.
No, dude. You look around and you go, "Wow."
Why not just go to like...
Why not just go to Taco Bell?
Why not go to Taco Bell and order one of everything on the menu?
That would be really funny.
And I can play CSGO in there.
On the Taco Bell WiFi.
That is one plus. I have to admit.
That is way cooler than a hike.
Asking the Taco Bell manager for the WiFi.
So is it Taco Bell 3G
or Taco Bell 5G?
Yeah. No, I'm not going to use the
guest network because I am more than a guest.
I am a customer.
Yeah, and you're going to treat me with respect.
I get so low latency
in the Taco Bell.
and I play their own server in the back they do yeah and you see a csgo server
inside of a Taco Bell yeah there's an investigative report just waiting to
happen that'd be some cool shit that'd be some cool I mean shit fly type stuff
what's like the coolest what's the coolest outfit that you can wear candles
candles candles on your shoulders no okay yeah candles on your shoulders you
of like like shoulder pad things that look like cakes okay so it's like cakes
with a candle the candle is burning hair straight up like five strands of hair
nothing it just yeah like baby baby baby hair but straight up okay
jelled so thick plastic bag shirt a shirt made out of plastic bag stitched
together holes for the nipples and belly button uh-huh for pants metal metal
metal no can't bend your legs no shoes no she went five toe one of those five
toe shoes on one of your feet other foot no foot prosthetic foot prosthetic foot
okay that your foot is a side ring with a spring
well you can bounce you just described inspector gadget yeah exactly what
inspector gadget looks like yeah
specter gets terrified me as a child
while in manhattan machine
yeah actually you know it now that you know that you mention it
there were parts there parts of inspector gadget that scared me like
just when you see like his hand or whatever come off and slickly and fuck
that shouldn't happen again a jack-in-the-box penis
yes i would have
well
Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
Oh yeah, he fucking did.
He had a big jack in the box penis.
With a tiny inspector gadget head on the tip.
Yeah. And just a big spring.
Yeah, he had a, like when it shoots a bang flag.
It says "Come."
That'd be cool.
Pop-Tart, you have brown sugar cinnamon Pop-Tarts?
Yeah. You're crazy.
I know but other people...
Get some s'mores ones.
The thing is, yeah I guess, that's probably true.
S'mores is the good one.
I don't know, there's something, I feel, when I eat a s'mores pop tart I feel like I'm eating
a dessert and I know it's no different than a brown sugar but it feels much more like
breakfast food.
Okay, yeah, I get that.
For brown sugar, even though it like, there's still this kind of gross whatever.
But there's a, there's a almost a pancake-y sort of flavor profile going on there.
Or french toast.
Yeah, I don't want to be eating like a marshmallow chocolate thing.
- Because it is just marshmallows and the s'more,
or yeah, and the s'mores, Pop-Tart, so.
- Yeah, so that's my argument.
- I don't think I like Pop-Tarts, now that I'm--
- They're not great.
- It's definitely not, it's not something I would eat
for breakfast, I don't think.
- Yeah, I--
- It's not something I'd eat all the time.
- I just eat them, I would take them with me
if I don't have time to make oatmeal.
- Ah, man, that's a rough morning.
- I don't like oatmeal, dude.
- You don't have time to make oatmeal?
- Well, yeah, I just don't, I don't wanna wake up
ever heard that play yeah you know snooze my alarm until I have to leave in five
minutes and then and then it's pop pop and get crumbs all over my floor never
vacuum I can tell that yeah lick everything up yeah I'm sitting on a pile
of crumbs yeah my bed is actually it's a giant pile of crumb sleep on a giant
crumb pile yeah cuz I'm a giant mouse that's what mice do I hear they hide
their crumbs and sleep on them they hide them they make a pillow out of a crumb
I did that's what a mouse freaking does a worst pillow ever makes a pillow out of
a crumb I want to wear that you know why would you wear a pillow
because you're sleeping what do you mean you put your head in the hole you got a
bad you put the feathers in your mouth yeah you close your eyes you see a you
and you're and you put your tongue in the hole in the pillow that usually fuck
yeah during the day yeah and then you just fall asleep yep well yeah and I
I would not want to do that with a crumb.
That makes sense.
It'd be nasty.
What did I do today?
I don't even know.
I didn't fucking know, it was so crazy.
Um, I, yeah, I guess I did nothing.
I ate Arby's for dinner.
Nice.
That was exciting.
I got a big half pound sandwich from Arby's.
Did you get the, um, you get the new steak one?
No, I just get the classic roast beef every time.
I don't even do the beef and cheddar.
at her. Beef and cheater? Beef and cheater. It's too expensive. I got two McChickens for
lunch today. Nice. Three dollars baby. It's a good deal. See I was imagining somebody mixing
up Lizzo and Brandy the R&B singer but he calls her Candy. I don't know who Brandy is. She's
a just a regular sized R&B singer and Lizzo is a ginormous woman. Yeah. Yeah. Very tall
right is what you mean? Yeah, she's over 6'2". It'd be funny, I don't know how tall she is,
but it'd be funny if she was like 7 feet tall and also that fat. She's Andre the Giant? Yeah.
Proportions. That'd be sick. That'd be scary. That'd make me like her more. Yeah,
if she should have to stay inside. I think she's practically, she'd have to stay inside. I don't
know that she could fit out of any doorway. Yeah, wouldn't be able to. Did you see that girl is
suing her back. No, what girl? Or is suing her. I guess Lizzo didn't sue her. But the
girl who she put on blast for taking her Uber Eats over. Oh really? That's great.
Yeah, that's the funniest shit dude. So funny. Nice. Just getting what they deserve.
Finally some comeuppance. I see I saw that the Epstein guards got got and she was
suing Lizzo the same day and I was like you know what I guess it
balances out huh? You know the universe it all comes to an equal zero at the end of the
day. They give my man Sandusky another 60 years. Nice. Nice. Nice. I just said he was my man
dude. Yeah I know that's why I don't know anything else about him but if he's your man
he should be in jail. I know who he is it was a joke. I was saying I don't know anything
about him but if he's your man he should be in jail. That was what I was gonna say. Sometimes
You interrupted me to tell me what I already know.
Which is?
What happened with Jerry Sandusky?
What do you know about him?
Yeah, I know that's 60 years.
He's a pedophile.
Pedophile from where?
Is he the guy from that college?
Yeah.
Duke.
Told you.
Yeah, he's the Duke lacrosse team.
Is he?
Yeah, he was the entire team.
See, I don't like this.
Can you stop looking at me?
I don't like it when you look at me.
I know you hate that.
- I just see that fucking everyone's mad
about this like TikTok thing.
- What thing?
- The nurse.
- Oh, that was, why do people care?
- What is it?
I don't-- - Who gives a shit?
Like, well, all right, I understand that like
a medical professional shouldn't be making fucking TikToks.
- What is the, I haven't seen this.
- But not, just 'cause they're embarrassing.
- Right.
- I do think it's funny that like all the people
who are mad at this person about like the TikToks
are the same people who are like,
like, yeah, like, it's a lot of like anti-SJW people
are like getting really upset over a TikTok
that a nurse made where she just like
laughs about people pretending to be sick.
- So what's the TikTok?
- So it's like, somebody is coughing
and the caption is like, we know when you're faking it
and somebody is coughing and then she's like,
She and then her nurse starts like dancing and there's like a beat that plays to the to the coughing sound and the nurse just like
Dances until the person stops coughing and it has a it has it has generated a humongous out read outrage mill. That's cool
Yeah, yeah somebody like sent like
Somebody like docks the lady and like sent like her DWI
That's great. It's iconic. Yeah, who cares? It's like I'm not like on the I don't
I don't think she's in the right for that TikTok,
but then I like,
'cause why would you go out of your way to doc some lady?
Yeah, and I just don't see,
I don't feel like a TikTok even deserves a moral judgment
of like whether or not it is good or bad.
Like it may be as far, maybe it's not funny,
but it's not doing harm.
You know what I mean?
It is making me afraid to go to a doctor.
Yeah, 'cause they'll just dance and do a beat
- Well, I'm-- - Yeah, they're gonna dance it.
- 'Cause I think I'll laugh too hard
because they'll do that in real life.
- They're gonna start, yeah.
- And I'll laugh until I die. - They're gonna show me
all their cool TikToks and I'm gonna laugh.
- And that terrifies me. - I'm gonna laugh
my ass off.
- My ass is literally gonna fall off from laughing.
- I guess if I found out that my general practitioner
was a, like I later, he was like,
"Yeah, here's my card," and he had his TikTok on the card,
I probably would never go back.
- No, that'd be cool. - Yeah.
- I would go, yeah, I probably wouldn't go back,
but I would go to his TikTok and laugh
make fun of him for to everyone I know forever. Yeah that would be fun. I would
just like post them all online. Yeah. Like look at this fucking idiot. Just absolutely
fucking rake in the cloud. Yeah and I would post this guy is has been arrested
multiple times for beating his kids. Yeah. I would post records of that. Even if it's not true. And then I would reply and be
like there's no need to dox the guy. Yeah. And I would say what it's funny. I'm gonna
dox OJ Simpson. Let's see what's in his past. Yeah. He's been on Twitter for like
I just don't understand how he got so many followers so fast. He really blew up.
He must have bought them.
He must have bought all those followers.
He bought all those followers.
And so I just wanna, I'm gonna, later tonight I'm gonna, I'm gonna Zoom him.
Yeah. Wow. Nice. Wow. Nice golf ball on that golf court.
Yeah, idiot.
Yeah, what is he, some famous golfer?
Yeah.
Who's just, his videos aren't even that funny. I don't, I don't understand why people like it.
They're not, yeah, it's just him just showing off how charismatic he is, basically.
Yeah, and yes, he is charismatic and yes, I yeah, I would I personally would let him get away with anything
I just want to know I would let him hang out with me
If you really wanted to also yeah open invitation
No, just Simpson anytime
You just want to fucking come over and smoke a little weed pen and play a little Super Mario Galaxy with me
That's right. Open open door, baby. Yeah, you only have to come on the podcast. I'm not worried about it, buddy
I'll hang out with you come chill. I'm fucking
I'm so fucking done with school shit. You ready to be done
Yeah, how much more school do you have to do? I don't know. I think it's like a year and a half wolf after this
yeah, well no no it this year and then I
Think I think got three semesters left after this semester. Yeah, and that's a bummer
Yeah, I'm just like I got everything I wanted out of this shit. Yeah, I don't want to write like
Like I I'm so sick of writing these fucking like papers that are like, oh, this is how a fucking
Locanian theory relates to
Freddie got fingered or something. I'm so yeah and sick of this dude. Yeah
Michelle Foucault's
thoughts on water world
Right on water world by Michelle Foucault. I have this one fucking class. I have to like
It's like a it's called like a sex and comedy
Seminar sounds sexy like I have this
Presentation I'm supposed to do to your classmates. Yeah
Which is
Look at look at this is funny. Yeah, my sex is funny because my penis is so small a
Plus that's where the comedy of it comes from yeah
But it's just like I got to do this presentation about a movie that like
Nobody has seen and then I have to do all these readings and shit, and I don't know how to fucking wing it
I don't know. I will say a movie that nobody's seen sounds so interesting
No, it wasn't that great. No what movie was it it was a it was called grief
Yeah, I haven't seen it. I thought it was gonna be yeah, it's about it's about AIDS whoa
And this is a comedy wait, this isn't your sex and comedy podcast
That's the freakin future that liberals watch and comedy podcast there's no more school they just want podcasts. That's true. You just
Podcasts, it's kind of honestly what my homeschooling experience was. Yeah, just strung together a bunch of podcasts until like I
I knew how to
until I knew everything from Freakonomics Radio. Yeah until I knew all the names of
the McElroy brothers. Until I knew how to say boy correctly. Boy! Boy! Hey boys!
God damn it dude. They're uh they seem to be obsessed with boys. What's wrong?
Interesting. Boys and dogs. That was like Hank Hill cadence.
system at hank hillick
bobby deuce
mcgrown men keep talking about bullies this is a great for you to all of us in
the june had to do it
these men are right bobby
uh... but one of the world's makeup bobby
but
the word michael like a girl bobby
but they are a
how are we make a black traffic
but
but i'm talking god you will
like a little while quicker but you will be a fingernail polish
bobby's any something called non-binary
uh...
i don't remember what they deal sounds like a four-year-old he will i can do
the voice was like well he will not
but but but but
but but but that's the case in the same yet that i don't even
no more like a hobby
well not in my house you'll be a lot of non-binary
(laughter)
Dang it, Bobby.
Dang it, Bobby, there's only two genders.
But, Dad, the McElroy said...
(laughter)
The McElroy's told me to explore myself.
God damn it, Bobby, turn that bullshit off.
Explore your... my God.
Explore what?
Explore outside.
That's what we did when I was a kid.
(laughter)
Explore the backyard.
Explore the great outdoors.
why don't you explore a football locker room yeah that'd be funny if Bill was
really into the McElroy brothers.
I don't know how to do the voice.
(Mocking)
Bill.
You know what they say is first thing.
(Mocking)
The McElroy brothers
are a CIA
generation to make our youth non-binary. Bobby, you should listen to Joe Rogan.
He would listen to Joe Rogan, right? I feel like. Yeah, yeah, yeah. He's definitely a Joe Rogan archetype.
Yeah. Let's do the King of the Hill cast as popular podcasts.
Yeah, that's fun. Yeah, so he is seriously a Joe Rogan type. Mm-hmm.
um the Native American guy. Boomhauer is red scare. Boomhauer is red scare. Dangle brain
worms. Dangle eating disorder. They got worms on in their brain I tell you what.
don't make me dress up like a damn sailor I look like that damn president god damn
it god damn it god damn it doing practice to that fucking that king of the hill
thing where it's like they go it's like a flashback from boom Howers perspective
and then everybody's talking like boom Hower but yeah that's so good dude that's
in that that's in the Rashomon style episode yeah that's right I know film
I wish I fucking did and I wouldn't be able to take this goddamn class. You would take Hank Hill
King of the Hill 101 yeah oh I wish I could write about King of the Hill damn
that would be sick. I'm doing a fucking dude it's the school's a fucking I'm doing a paper on Borat
that's sick dude and I'm finding so many fucking scholarly articles about Borat
like fucking here here's one of the titles oh shit hold on the first paper I
ever wrote in college this is when I was at a real college they it was a it wasn't
a paper as a story for it because I was in the creative writing program about
Bugs Bunny taking doing blood doping and I got an A+ that's pretty cool I kind of
just coast through this shit huh yeah yeah no my first semester was so easy so
I thought like oh that's what the rest of this is gonna be and it's been a
living nightmare ever since yeah I've just been fucking miserable yeah man it
fucking suck you should drop out I mean you have so much school left to do that's
Yeah, I know I was considering it after this semester just dropping out. I've gotten everything I need
Yeah, I mean I just want to do I just want to do one semester and then drop out when I was supposed to graduate
Yeah
That's what I wish I had done
I wish I had stayed long enough to like meet the people that I know right now from college and then drop down. Oh
That's basically. Yeah, it's basically what I'm doing. Here's a fucking title the Borat effect
dot pdf. The Borat Effect. What was the Borat Effect? What do you posit is the Borat Effect?
I don't know, I haven't read anything yet. I haven't done any of the research and it's
due like the week I'm in LA. Damn. Basically, yeah. We can write it. Yeah, we'll do it. Let's
start it. Fear Intrusions, a comparative reading of Borat and Dracula. Wait, so Borat is supposed
to be Dracula? I guess. Yeah, because he has to be invited in. True. The Borat Effect, film
induced tourism gone wrong it went so right yeah what are you talking about
Borat as tragic comedy of anti-us-americanism huh humor is serious
as a geopolitical speech act IMDB film reviews of Sasha Baron Cohen's the
dictator God did academia is a joke documenting clown training I was somebody
at prankster ethics Borat and Levinas somebody the other day at an improv
theater stopped me and they were like hey um what are you doing on Sunday and I
was like I'm working and she was like you should go see a clown show and I was
like what she said I think you would really really like like the clowning
community in Los Angeles. Damn. I saw she was like I freaking roasted you dude.
Yeah she yeah I was wearing my big red nose and my rainbow afro to work which
was a bad move. Just walking around. Yeah. You know what you would like? The clown
school. What's a clown? I don't know. Can you explain that? I don't know what that is. No idea.
What are you dressed like? Oh I'm dressed like Joe Mama.
Yeah. Then she killed herself. A clown doing a mass joy buzzer ring.
Going into a club and shaking everyone's hand one by one and just zapping them all.
I had a mind bug for a little while. It was a pedophile hunter who he would just find the pedophiles
And then just get real close to him and then buzz them with a joy buzzer.
[laughter]
I was thinking like...
"I wanna shake your hand, you piece of shit!"
[laughter]
- Oh. - Pssssss!
Gotcha!
Have you seen that video of the guy on the plane?
He's like a drunk guy and he's like walking towards the back of the plane, screaming.
He's like, "I wanna shake your hand!"
- Yeah, it's so funny. - "I wanna shake your hand!"
I had a joy buzzer then and my mom...
Me and my mom went to the grocery store when I was a kid and I had to...
It was like the day that I was just using the joy buzzer a ton.
and my mom knew like the manager of the grocery store.
Oh man.
And she was like, she was like, "Hey, like maybe like next year when you turn 14 or
whatever you can like work here and so I'm gonna introduce you to this guy."
And he like came out from the office and he was like, "Well, hey there young man,
my name's Jerry." And I joy buzzed him.
And my mom was so mad.
That's so funny.
I should just have a joy buzzer at all times.
It's so funny. Things like that are still funny to me. A joy buzzer, a Groucho Marx mask.
A whole mask.
Yeah, an entire-
A carnation that squirts water.
Carnation that squirts water?
Yeah, one that you put on your lapel that you squirt at the president when you're
meeting him for the spelling bee.
It's like a clown terrorist and he does carnation acid attacks.
That's just the Joker, dude.
Oh, that's true.
Get a new thing.
Yeah, I was imagining a guy who like fell into a thing of acid and it bleached his skin white
and he went crazy.
And then he fought back.
I was imagining the clown prince of crime.
Yeah.
Oh, now I'm thinking of the Joker.
I'm realizing.
I'm realizing that's actually the Joker.
Dude, you just blew a sick O, Pat.
Yeah, that was a pretty cool O.
Yeah.
I know its tricks.
I can do it, O.
I know the tricks.
Yeah, what a, can you do a kickflip?
Do a kickflip with smoke.
Create a dragon out of smoke.
Wow.
He just did.
There was a dragon at the place I went to.
A real dragon?
Did you do MagiQuest?
No, I didn't.
Dude, I did MagiQuest when I was a kid.
Dude, I didn't have the wristband.
If I went to go do it, they'd be like, "What are you doing in here?"
MagiQuest was fucking awesome.
It was the only thing to do in Myrtle Beach.
Is it not MagicQuest?
I thought it was MagiQuest.
It could be.
I don't know.
I don't know why it would be "magic"
Because you act as a magi
I love magi
Yeah you do become a magi
Well magi is plural
Just saying
So you and your friends become magi
Okay, alright now it makes sense
Magi
Keep going
Have you ever done it? No
It's so sick, I don't know, it probably updated
It would be even cooler now
You basically walk around like a
whole new world and you walk around like a like a fake like little universe and so
there's like there's different sections that are themed like oh this is like the
swamp and then this is like the cave where the dragon is. Oh that's sick. Like all
this stuff and you do all these quests where you have to like find things and you
have they give you like a wand that has like an IR sensor in it and you point it
at different like things it's so cool. I wish I'd done that when I was a kid that
would have been my shit. It was sick and they also had a dueling part. Damn. And I
I would fucking just beast on kids.
'Cause I went multiple times with the same wand,
so it saved my progress.
So I was like-- - Oh nice.
- I was way OP by the time that I did my last visit
to Magic Website. - Did you guys go
to Lazer Tag a lot?
- Yeah, 'cause my dad did some work.
- Damn.
- 'Cause my dad did construction growing up.
He did some work for a place that did Lazer Tag.
And so for two seasons, they gave us unlimited passes
or whatever.
- I've only been to Lazer Tag once.
I only ever got to go once as a kid.
and I think that's one of my biggest childhood regrets
is I would go back, I can't do it as an adult now.
- Yeah, I would not do adult laser tag.
- I mean, it'll be fun.
- Let's do some when Pat comes out to LA.
- Maybe if it's, do they have like,
I don't wanna do it with kids.
- Yeah, you could have adult laser tag
where there's like porn all over the walls.
- But no, I don't wanna--
- Oh my God, adult, I don't wanna think about adult laser tag.
- Come on, dude, let's do it.
- Yeah, but I, yeah, no,
I don't think I could do laser tag now.
they have a non c_b_d_ later laser tag you can get it
they have a
yes only a_o_ i'll get it i wanted to play in adults only games so bad growing
up
what what even are the i've no idea i didn't i don't know i can even name one
yeah i know i feel like it
what's an adult so we are all of the idea your computer so the game cards
against humanity travel so true
was uh... i think maybe you're still a really usually and i think it'll i
think we should there is an infirmature
yes if there are a few leisure suit larry's
list of a over late rated game all manhunt
all nude cyber
uh...
and i think that
and i was uh... uh... yeah i'm miss a lammer there are that many well there's
not many at all wet the sexy empire
well thrill kill
uh... sexy games playboy mansion private party that sounds good
yeah rent if dot of san andreas
uh... yeah one of the leader leisure c_n_n_ come laugh
weights and race with a l_ to what yet 'cause of the hot coffee mod
i don't know what that was
uh... that was uh... a mod that was in so it was something that was like
supposed to be uh... inaccessible
but then they left it in the game and people found out.
So on the Windows port,
you could like, it's basically like you just having sex.
It's like a sex-like rhythm mini game.
- That's sick, dude. - Damn.
- That's awesome.
Can you do that in your new one?
- Water closet, the forbidden chamber.
- What is that?
- That's a game where you shit.
(laughing)
- Tokimeki check-in.
- That's just gonna be like a, yeah.
Yeah, they're all just like visual novels. Japanese
hotline Miami
That's weird the games 2019 Microsoft Store release was rated a oh it was not it is not known
Why the game received its higher rating? That's very odd interesting
Hatred sounds really cool. Yeah, I bet this was fucking sick
It's a genocide crusade game to kill as many human beings
That's like there was a movie on Netflix for a while called Rampage which is just
about a guy doing a mass shooting and getting away with it. I remember that.
It was directed by Uwe Boll. Oh really? That's the dude who did the Postal
movies. Yeah, that was after Postal though. Oh really? Yeah. Yeah it's just a
it's the what's his name again? Uwe Boll. Uwe Boll. He just directs like...
boo boo bowl yeah boo bowl boo boo boo boo boo boo boo boo boo boo boo boo boo boo
boo boo boo boo boo boo boo boo boo boo boo boo boo boo boo boo boo boo boo boo boo boo boo
I wonder if Rampage, there's no way it got like a an actual release.
Yeah probably in Germany or something. Well they made that movie that movie with the
rock yeah true it's this one the 2009 one we we bowl you we had a sequel and had
two sequels damn president down I bet capital punishment and rampage
president down bowls first film the game mostly positive reviews what yeah how is
that well cuz that it was coming off the that that he cuz he does the shooting
because of like the recession. Oh is that what it is? Yeah. Yeah he basically just
walks down, I just remember watching it when I was younger and he just like
walks down a street and just like kills a bunch of people and then just gets away
with it. You're like damn I want to do that. I said that was gangsta. Yeah. Damn.
I love movies yeah where it's just like a thinly veiled like mass shooting thing
like yeah there's that movie Mayhem that came out with Stephen Yuen and uh
Samara Weaving and it's just like all everyone in the everyone in their office
building gets a zombie disease but it's not like they're not dead they just get
really angry and they didn't have to go around and kill everyone in their office
building. All zombie movies are kind of... Yeah well it's not even zombie they're like they
literally they're just like are angry. They have their eyes turn red and they get
really mad and they're like I guess we have to kill everyone. I guess we have to kill our
friends yeah yeah yeah and also we're doing this there's that one fucking sick
scene in that in the first Kingsman movie when the guy the older agent he gets
like this rage virus or something not the one from whatever in the first game
yeah and he's in like a church or something and he just kills a shit ton
people yeah that's fucking sick dude I would love to kill a shit ton of people in the church
I would parody parody alert that's covered by parody law yeah now I have to change the
tags on this podcast you can't put me on a watch list that's a parody yeah you have to
put me on the parody watch list you have to put me on the same one as weird al yeah you
have to put me and weird al's names next to each other and then make them kiss and also
give me his phone number so I can conduct a business transaction. What if I feel
like maybe Weird Al has like a like a Justin Bieber mass shooting parody that
he's just had in the vault for like 10 years and he almost releases it and
every day that he does news breaks that like another one just happened. Yeah. He's like
fuck! He has to wait until mass shootings end to release his Justin Bieber. What if
what if Weird Al was fucked up? Yeah. Yeah. What if he was Weird Al? Well he has that one, he
has that he has that song where Santa does a mass shooting.
Yeah true.
True Santa's going crazy.
When I was a kid I printed out the lyrics to that song and hid them in my room.
Just so you could look at them?
Because I read them with my friends.
That was in like elementary school.
One night Santa went crazy, one night Saint Nick went insane.
That's a good one.
Classic man.
What's the best Weird Al song?
Probably probably Weird Al the song.
I would say.
Weird Alvin.
I would say Albuquerque.
my favorite one I love that weird Alvin weird Alvin the chipmunk more like mm-hmm
weird Alvin the chipmunk weird Alvin the chipmunk mm-hmm who's a who's a I was
watching some parody music today Rucka Rucka I was watching Rucka Rucka Ali
I'm a Korean today and just remembering how awesome that was what a great time
It was so cool.
Just me playing Battlefield Bad Company 2, listening to a YouTube playlist of Rucka Rucka
Ali.
It was the best time of my fucking life, man.
Yeah.
Just blowing up.
I would just start a multiplayer server with nobody on it just so I could blow up the buildings.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, that's right.
That shit was sick.
Yeah.
I got, that's why I got Red Faction Guerrilla.
Red Faction Guerrilla was so good.
I yeah I never really like don't even do this like Saints Row in space that would
be so much cooler of a game cuz like really the only fun part of that is
breaking shit that's what it was advertised to me as was read Saints Row
in space and then I was like oh damn that's not this at all we should make a
video game absolutely that's the next patreon what is what is our video game
doodle jump to doodle jump yeah yeah poppy jump extreme crappy bird whoa yeah
crappy Mario I remember I like was laughing so fucking hard cuz you know
they have like those Facebook games that just like a bunch of them are like auto
generated and yeah I found this game that was like in some crazy language
there's some crazy language. I don't know it was some foreign game and it was
called wash run and it's a guy. I remember yeah like a flappy bird clone,
but he's sitting on a toilet and you shoot water out of the toilet and when
when you die it goes like it says like ah you scored the number. It just says
like ah above your score, so funny wash run.
I'm going to go on a wash run.
And you blasted off on the toilet.
I made a game when I was like 14 that was a poppy jump clone called,
because I thought it was so, I thought Gary Busey was so hilarious.
It was called Gary Busey Jumping Adventure and it was fully functional,
but I couldn't pay the $99 licensing fee to put it on the Apple store.
Nice.
Or else I'd be fucking raking. I wouldn't be here right now.
Yeah, that's true.
on a one watt of cash like an egg. I made a bunch of games in high school and middle school.
Me and Aaron made like a web game and then just stopped paying for the website. Damn.
Is it gone? Yeah. Well I think he still has the code maybe. It wasn't very good. It was
like an RPG. It was like a turn based RPG. It was going to be like Kingdom of Loathing.
You ever played that? Yeah. It's a good ass game dude. I remember playing a shit ton of
kingdom of loathing love that game I have West of loathing shout out that's a good
game - not as good as kingdom of loathing no shout shout out shout out shout out
shout out new rounds calm shut out I used to go games that you go to the to
the adult section of new grounds the adult section new grounds could find a
good dress-up game and I guess get this I would dress down and put him a casual
user error yeah yeah yeah I'd put them in a in a Hanes plain white tea and some
some dickies yeah I'd say yeah try go to the Met Gala now Barbie idiot you
fucking bitch you bimbo got her boom Bobby what kind of game is this it's a
dress up game.
Booo!
Dang it Bobby, you gotta get off dressupgames.com.
Bobby are you on new grounds again?
Bobby are you playing Elsa Frozen Princess Pregnant Pimple Popper?
But dang, she's beautiful.
Bobby boys your age should be listening to Chopo Trap House.
Not come town.
But that, but that, they're like this.
God damn it Bobby, no they're not.
Bobby, you're doing crypto-fascism.
Yeah, something like that.
And this, I think it would look a little something like this.
And it would be a little something like this.
But that, it's just a frog.
It's the OK sign, Dad!
Bobby, why do you keep doing the OK sign all the time in all the family photos?
What in the hell are you doing?
Bobby, what have you...
What is 14 to 88?
Bobby, why do you keep shaving your head every week?
Bobby, where the hell are 1 through 7 chans?
All right Bobby Hill. Yeah. Yeah. You know that one there's that one episode when he
tries to he goes to like Def Jam like comedy club and he just like he first he starts out
and he's like how come he's like how come white people are all walking like this and
he just does a bunch of like black comedian jokes and the the. Teenage. And then the guy
is like you can't do that you have to tell like speak to your experience like you know
as like as a white guy and Bobby's like interesting and he like Rick goes on his
computer and he's like like like white race experience like goes back and just
is like doing neo-nazis saying neo-nazi shit on stage and everyone starts throwing shit at him.
That's a great episode. It's a good show man. Yeah I remember. It's just such a fucking good show.
I had a friend growing up who thought that that show was offensive to redneck people.
yeah cuz that's just where we were from and he felt that it was rude it's funny
yeah yeah yeah so you didn't watch it Bobby Hill is as big of a troublemaker
as Bart Simpson I would say Bart Simpson's the Ultimo troublemaker
extreme absolutely yeah no questions asked have you seen what the fuck he's
been doing to Disney plus I said no questions asked right sorry I did ask a
question yeah so please don't ask a question that's my phone all right I have
- I'm going to pee so bad, can we stop?
- Yeah, I gotta take a dunk.
- You have to dunk it?
- I'm gonna dunk my head in the toilet.
- You gotta dunk it, baby.
- All right, bye everybody.
- Yeah, no, I gotta go to bed, I'm like dying.
- Is there anything to, I guess,
well this won't come out 'til Saturday, right?
- Yeah, this comes out the day of.
- I can put it up now.
- So don't plug it.
- True, yeah, you might as well.
Yeah, if you're in Boston,
no, you might as well.
If you're in Boston, come to Moo-Yah on the 23rd.
- So yeah, tomorrow.
- Tomorrow, 140 Tremont.
What time is the show?
- The show, doors are at, show is at 8.30.
- Yeah, show out.
Jamie Loftus. - Tickets and shit
on Patrick's Twitter.
- Jamie Loftus had a really good show.
- Yeah, they're on Eventbrite.
They're on Ben's Twitter.
- Check it out, baby. - Jamie posted it herself.
- Yeah, check it.
- Yeah.
All right. - All right.
That's it.
- Bye. - See ya.
Bye!