The McElroy brothers are not experts and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but due to pending legal action, he's had to stop saying that.
This show is not for kids. It's for adults who have the brains and bodies of kids.
What's up freak bitches?
Hey everybody, welcome to My Brother, My Brother and Me.
I'm your uh, middle-est brother, Griffin McElroy.
You're the, uh, baby brother.
I'm your baby brother, Griffin McElroy.
I'm the big brother.
I'm the big brother and it's me, Justin.
I see, I'm the baby brother, but Justin looks the most like a baby.
I'm kinda like a baby, but like a baby if he grew up.
I'm the middle and the most sexual brother, Travis McElroy.
You are definitely the most sexual brother, Travis.
I have a certain charm about me.
It's quickly becoming a problem.
Anyway, welcome to My Brother and My Brother and Me.
We're not gonna talk about that today.
Not right now.
Welcome to My Brother and My Brother and Me.
An advice show for the
for the modern era.
Today we
um
we
(laughing)
Today
we have some great questions for you guys.
For us to answer.
You guys send in your questions and we're gonna answer them for you.
So I got some questions.
You guys got some questions.
Who wants to go first?
I can go first.
I have a question here in the inbox.
Dear Brothers, My wife loves your show.
I love to listen to it with her.
Only problem is she laughs too much.
She has a really loud and annoying laugh and I mean really loud and annoying.
a donkey combined with a baby being sawed in half. I wouldn't have married her if I had
ever heard her laugh while we were dating. But these kinds of things happen. Anyway,
what are some ways I can stop my wife from laughing?
Oh boy.
Huh. Um.
Well.
You could put, my only idea is you could put like a big sock in her mouth. Right?
I feel yeah, I was thinking maybe if she was asleep. She wouldn't be laughing. I think yeah
I think going off of that maybe if she was asleep
Maybe you could put her in some kind of like a cube and you could just have her
Like when you're listening to the show you can just have her in her cube
or like a big jar or like a
Basically any content you could pin her up to the wall like a butterfly kind of Tupperware
You could fit your wife into I feel I feel like that's probably gonna be best
I think the cube is a great idea because basically you I would say no windows in the cube
Right, so she can't see that you're having fun and you're laughing. No, you can't right you can't know and and and
Completely sealed with obviously enough oxygen to last however long the show is
Probably an hour if you
Yeah, it was worth the oxygen sounds and not and not a tiny bit more cuz she'll waste it and then
- But then, you can also put your kids in there too.
Wives belong in cubes.
- Mm-hmm.
You could also put her in a basement.
- Travis, this has to be--
- That's one of the rooms where if you put someone in there--
- You have to stop talking about the basement.
We're gonna get fired from Polygon.
The fellas at Polygon are gonna be really mad at us
for that one.
- Yeah, we're not gonna get any more monster factories.
- Well, I don't work at Polygon
because I'm not smart enough to play video games.
You guys know you're the intelligent ones who are playing.
- I think the last time you tried to pick up a controller,
you got so mad you threw it in the wall like a boomerang.
- That's true.
A lot of people don't know this about Travis,
but he has a giant bone that goes
through the middle of his head
and sticks out either side like Frankenstein's bolt.
- It looks like Steve Lawson with the bow,
or the arrow, but instead of the arrow,
it's a bone and it's round.
- I just, I couldn't help throwing the controller
the wall because I was trying to play the Sims and I made only women in the game
this town didn't function I got so mad I threw it at the wall because a town made
of women should function better not not at all. I agree I agree or people who are
somewhere in between like us. We hatched out of eggs. Yeah our dad laid a big egg
and all three of us came out. Our big gay southern dad laid a giant egg and we
were all born at the same time.
Mm-hmm.
That's why we don't have a mom.
That's why we were born at the age of 35.
Yeah.
Basically.
You could try laying an egg onto your wife.
That's good too.
I mean, you put your wife in an egg like Yoshi?
She might hatch after a while, but you get some good time to listen to your podcasts
and your--
Or you could stick an egg in her mouth like a ball gag and make her go outside for an
hour.
mouth the egg in her mouth and then wait till the chicken hatches. The chicken
will rip her jaw open. All right I feel like we answered that question to a
acceptable level. Yeah hopefully that's helpful. The cube. The cube, the egg, the
basement. So I actually have another question also from the from the inbox
directed especially to us brothers. All right it's from Stu and he says. Hi Stu.
- Hi, Stu. - Hello.
- Hey, Stu.
- Hey, how you doing?
- Dear brothers, this is Stu.
Me and my wife have been married for 20 years.
Our marriage is great.
She has a very tight hoo-ha
and I've always found her extremely attractive.
Parentheses, we have sex about twice a month.
She is insatiable.
I, like many of your listeners, am a hardcore gamer.
But recently, I've been going back
and playing some classics that I missed over the years
as I mostly play Pokemon games, Animal Crossing,
and picto-chat with my daughter's friends.
One of these games I've been playing is Halo, an absolutely terrifying horror game for the
Xbox.
Now, I did not enjoy the game, but after finishing the campaign, all I can think about all day
at my WeWork cube is that blue mink's Cortana.
She's taken over my every thought, as if I am Spartan 117 and she is installed in my
helmet.
It's bizarre, because I don't usually have fantasies about women, unless you count those
choice Looney Tunes episodes where Bugs Bunny dresses in drag.
It wouldn't be a problem, except it's starting to interfere in my marriage.
At first, I couldn't help myself from saying little subtle comments like "Hey, what if
you were a blue female artificial intelligence?"
But I'm afraid it's escalated since then.
I am now dosing my wife with 3mg of chemical silver in her morning coffee in an attempt
to turn her skin a more bluish tone.
I realize this is morally wrong, but I cannot control my own impulses to bust a creamy load
inside of Cortana and watch it fall through her holographic body.
Brothers, my question is, how do you get over a girl?
It's not possible.
Honestly, I feel, first of all, I don't think you should have been playing that game.
I think you should have done a little bit more research.
I'm almost certain that's an M-rated game.
Yeah, I'm...
which is M means mass shooter which is why they have so many guns in those games
that's what people don't realize is that they're training you. Master Chief is actually one of
the most one most despicable mass murderers in history. They don't say it I
mean I working at Polygon I had to read up on video game lore I did learn that
that his name is actually Spartan John 117 Dylan Klebold.
- Oh my God.
- Yeah, that's what I heard.
- I just wanted to answer your questions, Stu.
I think one way you can actually avoid getting over a girl
is every time that you have a girl
or whatever you would like to call it,
you can kind of take on one of her characteristics
one maybe a one item of her clothing or perhaps a style of makeup and you kind
of just keep building that on to your person and then you never really have to
give up any of the any of the women that you have have conquered in the past you
kind of just become them in in a kind of outward sort of way and I mean that's
not something that I have any experience with in any way but it sounds like you
absorb your victims like the Soul Calibur sword? No I find often I just like to
you know inhabit the skin of a woman and you know suck the the essence from their
bones and into my mohawk but it's oh that you know it's it's what girl did
you steal the mohawk from Roxanne Gay? It was uh that was actually one of my
friend's mother's. Roxanne Gay is your friend's mom? Yeah. That's crazy. Travis had sex with
Rhea Butcher and now he looks like that. It's a it's just it's not say it's a
transfer of essences I would prefer that's my bad for two hours my wife
feel like that's just more that's more of a PC term my wife on the medical field
I've heard of this transfer of essence before I've she deals with that almost
daily I've heard I've heard her have several loud conversations with people
in kiosks at the mall about it that's my wife yeah I saw your wife yelling at a
young Dominican man in the mall for selling fake Rolexes the other week and
I said yes Queen mm-hmm yeah I saw her hitting a little boy over the head while
he was trying to shine her shoes that's my wife she's a girl boss that's my my
sister-in-law I would love to take on one of her characteristics I don't do
that I'm sorry no I'm gonna come over to your house actually later tonight no I'm
- No, no, no, no.
- We're brothers, we share everything.
We share our wives' characteristics.
Justin.
- I don't think.
- Justin!
- I don't think that's gonna happen.
- Travis, remember what dad said
about you speaking in a man's voice.
- Count to 10, Travis.
- Count to 10, look at your nails.
Look at your nails, Travis.
- Oh, they're so beautiful.
- They're so beautiful and galaxy printed.
- I'm dazzled.
- Look at your pineapple shirt and calm down.
The pineapple represents the shape of my penis and that's why it always calms me down to
look at.
Thanks fellas.
Of course.
I needed that.
Anything for my brother.
Alright, let's move on to the next question here.
This one, oh it's from our good friend, it's from our good friend Lin-Manuel Miranda.
Oh Lin, hey buddy.
I'm actually, I'm very excited to read this.
I haven't seen Lin since me and him marathon my crazy ex-girlfriend on Easter Sunday.
Oh I was there but I was outside.
You were in the cube.
I was under the couch.
Yeah I was in the cube.
I understand that when I watch that show I laugh too loud and you have to put me in my
cube but that's fine.
We had to keep Travis under the couch so that he wouldn't sing along.
I was singing along anyway, but the piece of cloth you put in my mouth did muffle it quite
a bit.
Alright, so the question here from Lynn is, "How do I get the stain out of my wife's carpet?"
I was eating a bowl of chili and I got it on her carpet.
Do any of you guys have experience with this?
With this one?
I know I spill chili on the carpet all the time.
I feel it's very easy, I mean I do leave the room and I'm screaming crying once I spill
the chili and I come back and my wife's already had it cleaned by the time I get back in.
So I don't know how she does it.
I just turn the carpet into a dress.
Okay.
Oh yeah, it'd be a cool little pattern on one of Travis's famous dresses.
It looks like a period stain.
Which is good.
Which I find very empowering to myself.
Sometimes I sit around and think about the fact that I will never experience the beauty of a female period.
And I cry, and I cry.
I laugh.
I just eat chili.
[laughing]
What does your doctor wife have to say about your diet, Justin?
It's fine. It's mostly chili. Your entirely chili diet? I got breakfast chili, I got
lunch chili, I got dinner chili, and I do have snack chili in a tube. So do you have
is there now here's the most important question is there a dessert chili? Oh
there it's called ice cream. Basically if you look at every food as
as just a different type of chili, then you'll be healthy.
- Then you can acquire the perfect male body.
- Mm-hmm.
- As you obviously have.
- And the perfect wife.
- Yes.
- She's so beautiful.
She's so beautiful.
- Yeah, I'm coming over tonight, Justin.
We're not done with this conversation.
I'm gonna be-- - Look, you can come over,
you can have some chili.
- I'm gonna absorb your wife's characteristics.
- I, you can absorb her chili, I can tell you that.
I'll absorb her chili.
Well that's all you're going to absorb.
I'm going to absorb all of her chili.
Nope.
And you know what, and Griffin knows exactly what I mean by that because I did that to his wife as well.
I do know what he means and my wife has never been the same.
Okay, next question.
Next question. Travis, you have a question over there?
Yeah, from the inbox.
from the inbox here, this is from uh...
uh...
it doesn't have a name, and no name
Anonymous
Hey there Anonymous!
I-
Hello Anonymous!
I think the homeless guy who sits outside my apartment complex is inhabited by a demon
How can I get rid of him without being noticed by the authorities or by my four uncles whom I live with?
Well
Well first off Anonymous, I really respect your work in leaking Jennifer
Lawrence's nude photos. But moving on from that, most homeless people are actually
inhabited by demons. That is true. A lot of people don't know this. That's why
they love to scream in made-up languages like Chinese. So that's why they're
homeless. That's why they're homeless because demons, you almost never get a job.
I think, um, I think right now, and this is just based off of information I got from the
medical professionals I know, you need to stay inside because of this crazy virus.
Oh yeah, we haven't talked about the virus, huh?
I think dad has.
There's a crazy virus on Travis's computer that keeps sending messages to women.
I yeah that's the virus we're talking about yeah it's called the it's called
the kovat under 19 and it's a real problem I don't know who programmed it or
who put it on to my computer and phone and every piece of a lace so yeah I'd
appreciate if you don't actually send us questions anonymous because I'm rather
myth. Yeah let's just go on to another question then. I have another question
from the inbox. Okay all right let's read it. This one is from Brutus. Hey Brutus.
He says, "I am in the United States military serving our country for the
last seven years. I have vaporized countless Iraqi civilians in my tours
overseas protecting us from the wrath of their rocks and their sticks. But one
One specific memory keeps me up at night.
One time, one of our bomb-sniffing dogs broke his tooth while eating the face off of a child
who was begging for his mom, which we thought was the word "bomb."
After opening fire on the terrorist child, I was forced to also put down the poor little
pupperino as his broken tooth left him useless to us as a monstrous terror to the Iraqi people.
Brothers, how do you deal with regret?
I live with no regrets so I can't answer this question.
The only regret I've ever had in my life was letting Travis convince us to put him on this
podcast.
I externalize my regret onto other people and I ignored that last comment.
That's an advanced move, Travis.
Points!
Yeah, I actually have a little closet in my house I call the regret chamber that I use
to externalize my regret onto people.
I styled after the the chokie from Matilda I've heard. Yeah the chokie from Matilda.
One of my first crush my celebrity crushes was Matilda. When you were when
that movie came out? Yeah a few weeks ago. But that poor little doggo. That is such a
disgusting story to me. The idea that you would ever have to put down a poor little
doggo for any reason whatsoever. You could have shipped it back in a box. Exactly. You
could have given it to us. I would have gladly taken him. I would have turned him into the
best chili you've ever had. Boys, what is your biggest regret in life? I've already said
I have no regrets. That can't be true. I can't actually speak on my biggest regret because
It's still, we're still discussing it in a courtroom situation, so I'm actually not supposed
to share any details about that at this moment.
As Travis's lawyer, I concur.
I have to sit in the cube in the courtroom because I'm too, I'm too loud.
You breathe too loud.
You smack your bowl of chili too loud.
I'm in the back of the courtroom, I'm eating chili.
You drum on your stomach like a bongos and your wife says, "This does not relieve stress."
and she yells at you and you guys were asked to leave the courtroom.
Yeah, that did happen and I think that might be my only regret.
Justin, you have to stop using your enormous steel belly like King K. Rool.
To reflect projectiles. Yeah, reject women's advances. Who has another
question I have I have one here from from Caleb this is well it's not really a
question but it's in the inbox here it's kind of it's one line it just says it
says my dog won't stop sucking my dick in my sleep all I would say about this
one is that God works in mysterious ways you know and we here at my brother my
brother me believe in God and we believe in his plan for the world so if you wake
up every morning and you have just a slopping wet fucking dog job on your
penis maybe it was meant to be that's true yeah yeah that's that's beautiful
maybe that puppers hungry right right maybe it doesn't know who are you to
deny a little doggo doesn't help that I've been leaving the bowls of chili
near my penis. It doesn't help that I've been sipping my penis in dog food as a way to make it
absolutely disgusting to myself so I don't touch it when I when I read our
email. That might be oversight on my part. Mm-hmm. Is that all of our questions?
That's all the ones in my inbox. I have one question here. It's actually from a
picture I found. Oh great. It's from a picture it says let me let me find this
picture real quick. How about we okay it says here it says it's got a picture of
a guy and it says interesting it's a picture of a guy and he's got a scary
face and it says it says Nutella why you no last forever that's a great point
that's why why you no last forever I would say this one is definitely geared
more towards Justin than us Travis see I think that if maybe Nutella made an
infinite jar then maybe we could get an infinity jar of Nutella.
An infinity jar of Nutella. Mm-hmm. Huh. That's not bad. That's a good idea.
That's pretty good. We should make an animatic of that. We should, yeah. Now that's funny.
We should have one of our middle school fans make a little video about this.
Yes. We should make the Nutella a character in our D&D campaign.
I think this little guy here who's saying "Why you know" looks pretty funny. I think maybe
we could have him on the show. As one of our guest experts.
I think maybe we could bring him on. I think we gotta find his information. This little
guy. This little white man. If anyone can find the information of the little
white little white man please message us at little white man at gmail.com did you
say white man Griffin that's Griffin's email little white man at gmail.com he
made it in fourth grade I am NOT white I am gay thank you very much yeah I stopped
being white when I dyed my hair purple I'm an elf now Travis I've been meaning
to tell you I think you look amazing with a sort of dreadlock beehive haircut mm-hmm
I think maybe if you dyed your skin yellow and wore a green dress and got big
blue hair I think that's maybe a good might be the next logical step yeah and
a big red necklace I'm willing to make myself look like anything to challenge
the patriarchy mm-hmm let's take down the patriarchy once and for all by all
dressing up like the Simpsons. 3, 2, 1. It's gone. We took it down. It doesn't exist anymore.
We got him.
We should play some D&D. Yeah, let's play right now. Let's play a round of D&D. You
You guys ready?
- All right, yeah.
- Okay.
All right, so I'll DM.
How's that sound?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Travis got in trouble for DMs.
(laughing)
- No, that was the virus.
- Oh, okay.
- We're not, I thought we weren't discussing the details.
- Justin, you don't know how to shut your big fat trap,
do you?
I'm sorry.
Set the scene.
Okay.
Paint a picture with words.
You wake up.
It's a polygon offices.
In 2014.
Have sex with female employee.
You don't even roll your dice.
You have to roll.
It's 320s.
Okay.
Have sex with female employee.
Okay, hold on.
Travis successfully has sex with female employee.
Travis successfully has sex with a female employee.
Hold on, wait, she has to roll a defense roll.
Hold on.
(laughing)
It's a one.
- Oh, God.
- Travis successfully has sex with female employee.
- See, that's why we haven't played in a long time
because he keeps doing that.
I think he's got some loaded dice.
Travis, let me see your dice.
- No.
- Travis, give me your dice.
They're in storage.
- No, you had to roll them.
- I put them in storage after I rolled.
No, they're not, you don't see, no.
- Let me see your dice.
- Why?
- I need to see them.
- Why, why?
- Give me your dice right now.
Right now, give me your dice.
Give me your dice.
- No.
- Give me them.
- Fine, here.
- Travis, this has all 20s on it.
- You're like Two-Face.
- Is that not supposed to be all 20s?
- No, use this dice.
Okay, all right, now you have this die, all right?
So I'm gonna make you re-roll.
Okay? - Okay.
- You have to roll to have sex with the female employee.
- Mm-hmm. - Roll.
- It's a one.
- All right, now we can go on with the game.
- All right, doing good so far, Travis.
- I hate this game.
- Okay, so you unsuccessfully try to have sex
with a female employee, which is almost worse.
(laughing)
She complains to HR and now they want to cancel Monster Factory!
Oh no!
I'm glad Monster Factory is getting cancelled.
It's not getting cancelled.
You guys wouldn't let me on it anyway.
We make you in the show all the time.
Justin, what do you do?
The boss just came to you and said, "We're going to cancel Monster Factory because your
Your brother tried to have sex with one of our employees in the middle of the office.
Offer boss a bowl of chili.
Okay you have to roll for it.
Do a chili check.
17.
It's a 17.
The boss graciously accepts your offer and says listen as long as you keep that chili
coming your brother can do whatever the fuck he wants man.
This is the best day ever.
And this is why we like working at Polygon.
He says, "As long as this doesn't leak to girls on Twitter with short hair, we're fine."
Mm-hmm.
All right, now, Travis, you have been let out of your containment chamber at the Polygon
offices, and someone comes up to you and says, "Travis, Travis, we need you to wear a dress
a sexy photoshoot for the Polygon calendar.
Wear dress.
Wear dress?
Okay, you wear the dress.
They also say, "We need you to cut off your penis for the sexy photoshoot calendar."
Cut off penis and keep it in a jar on my bedside table.
You have to defense check to see if you live.
That's a 100.
These dice are loaded, man.
I had a bonus on it.
I have a bonus.
You don't have a bonus on defense.
I had a...
What gives you the defense bonus?
Your nail polish?
Look, he painted his nails to look like dice.
I have feminine fingers that let me roll the dice more better.
He painted his nails to look like dice and he's counting the numbers on the nails.
That's separate.
say 10 on them and he's got 10 fingers. I don't have 10 fingers. Yes what? You guys are just
like. I'm looking at him right now. Regardless, apparently the woman said to cut off your
penis as a joke. You took her seriously and now you're bleeding all over the polygon offices.
I always believe women. It doesn't matter if it was a joke or not. Okay, regardless, they
They say you have to get out of the offices, you're bleeding all over the other rapists
who work here.
So they kick you out of the office and you walk out onto the street, okay?
Go back in with a gun.
You don't have a gun.
Why not?
Because they did a background check on you.
Make a gun out of my severed penis.
What does it shoot?
Sperm.
You can still make sperm.
My penis can't, I can't anymore.
Okay, you walk back in and you start shooting sperm at people with your disembodied member.
Who do you go after first?
Me or Justin?
Justin.
Okay.
Why?
Justin, you have to defense roll.
Your brother is shooting his penis at you.
I got a one.
Travis?
I don't like playing this game anymore.
Yeah, this is boring.
Fine. I'll try to do something fun with you guys and you guys spit in my face just like dad does.
Whatever.
I don't give a fuck anymore.
I quit, man. I quit this podcast.
Yeah, why don't we just drop the fucking voices, okay?
We're only doing these voices so people will listen to the show.
I mean, if we're not gonna be brothers anymore, I mean...
Oh my god, this is like the worst day ever.
Jesus Christ, dude.
Travis, will you stop being a gay bitch on every episode?
Wait, uh, fuck.
The contract says I have to be gay.
You wrote the contract!
When we signed that fucking billion year contract, I didn't think it was gonna be this long.
Oh my god, dude, I just wanna vote for Trump.
Can I just fucking vote for Donald Trump?
Can I fucking...
Can I just fucking get a bride and sick of eating all this chili?
It's destroying my fucking home.
It's destroying my house. There's so many fucking bowls of chili.
Justin, you used to be by far the most athletic of the three of us.
Oh my god. My name's not even Justin. It's Frank Rizzo.
Sorry, I got so caught up in the character.
Sometimes I forget we're not brothers at all.
Yeah, we're just tall guys.
We were just found by that old gay southern man like Master Splinter
and turned into a team of homosexual podcasters.
Yeah.
Ugh.
And...
And justinate the fourth one.
I just wanna go back to Hoboken!
Soon.
I just wanna go back to Hoboken, Jersey!
Very soon.
As soon- again, as soon as arbitration is finished in Travis' case, we should be okay.
We can drop the act.
Ugh.
Alright, wait, are we still recording?
Oh, fuck.
Wait, before- before we go, I just wanna say, in regards to the allegations,
I just wanna remind everybody, uh,
Believe men who dress like women.
Believe Travis.