[MUSIC PLAYING]
Exterior, Duluth, Minnesota, Duluth Mega Mall day.
Scene opens up on an establishing shot--
establishing shot-- great start--
of the Duluth Mega Mall.
Text on screen reads, December 23, 1255 PM.
Cut to interior, Duluth Mega Mall, same time.
In the mall, every inch is filled to the brim
with Christmas decorations.
The holiday music is lazily spilling out of different stores.
Children smiling and laughing, munching on food court goodies.
The centerpiece of the mall's holiday cheer can be found by the life-size Hungry Hamster
Nativity Scene, where the 14th annual Mall Santa Wet T-Shirt Contest is just about to
kick off.
The crowd is packed around the contest stage, upon which an announcer bellows about the
beauty and sex appeal of seven of the nastiest, sluttiest, fattest, ugliest, and hottest mall
Santas in the city.
And here are your gorgeous mall Santas!
Look at those Saint Nicks!
Ouchie Mama, ladies and germs! Sensational!
The camera lovingly pans over the Rubenesque bodies of these fine Santas
who pose seductively on stage for the crowd of onlookers
and ho-ho-ho it up by doing twerks and a sexy dance.
Like a super sexy, sexy dance.
And one of them is stuffing pennies under his foreskin.
Above them is a giant pig trough filled to the brim with eggnog
attached to a candy cane colored string that, when pulled, will drench these
Santas in that eggnog. Also present are a group of
handsome, strong, tough, buff men that seem strategically and tactically
staggered among the crowd in order to blend in with the civilians. As the
announcer continues vamping, the camera punches in on one member of the crowd in
particular, Sergeant Jack Frost, with his awesome blue hair and kind of blue face,
dressed head to toe in regular clothes, an MK-16 SCAR, 12 Apostle Bandolier, and Kevlar vest,
easily blending in with the crowd. He puts his finger to his earpiece. "Yukon. Any sign of the
HVT?" Over intercom, we hear a barking prospector's voice. "That be as a negative, J.F." We cut to
Lieutenant Yukon Cornelius, a nine-foot tall beast of a man wearing Oakley's, and a t-shirt that says,
This isn't a beer belly, it's a fuel tank for a sex machine, and nothing else.
He's standing right in front of a mall directory nearby, completely blocking an elderly woman's view.
"The insert's been clean since the R.O.N. took point last night!"
"Okay, stay frosty, Yukon. If you get a whiff of him, grease the fucker where he stands."
"Amen, Sergeant!" Yukon begins absentmindedly licking his gun as the old woman slinks away.
We cut back to the wet t-shirt contest.
Now who wants to get these Santas? Who wants to see them get wet? The crowd erupts into thunderous cheers like the Beatles
All right
So we have a very special contest winner this year that will get a chance to dredge these Santas in that sticky icky nog
This young man was a 1 millionth customer at the Duluth Mega Mall Big Lots making him our Dunkaroo of the year
Come on out Sullivan the Frog! A meek dapper little frog waddles up to the stage and smiles sheepishly at the crowd
Sullivan, are you ready?
"As ready as I'll ever be, I suppose."
"That's the spirit! Okay, Sullivan, pull that string!"
The crowd starts chanting, "Pull that string! Pull that string!" as the Santas mug for everyone,
twisting their tiny, hard nipples and gaping.
Sullivan reaches for the string, but he's a tad short.
He's swatting at it.
Finally, he jumps up and yanks the string.
Everything slows down to bullet-time speeds.
We hear nothing but a steady heartbeat,
and cut to the Santas, pushing their hairy tits together and making kissy faces.
Cut to the Milky Eggnog sloshing around in the trough above.
Cut to Sullivan the frog, feet dangling as he haplessly pulls on the candy cane string.
Cut to the crowd, screaming like wild apes.
Cut to the announcer, dramatically gesturing to the scene.
And finally cut to Sergeant Jack Frost.
His face, ever focused, ever stern.
We punch in on his eyes as they scan the scene.
We cut to his point of view.
We glance over the crowd, then back to Jack's eyes.
Back to the crowd.
What's that?
That man there in the bomber jacket.
Cut to Jack's eyes.
Cut to the eggnog, about to spill over the Santa's.
Cut to that man.
Who is that?
Is that a tuft of green hair?
Back to the Santa's.
To the eggnog.
About to land on them, to the tuft of green hair!
Poking from a man's black beanie!
Cut to Jack's eyes widening.
"Looook ouuuut."
But it's too late.
It was over the second Sullivan pulled the string.
Splash goes the eggnog, click goes something else.
Boom, time resumes.
The stores and the mall all explode, one by one in a row.
Boom boom boom boom boom boom boom.
The stage, too. Boom.
Out shoots fire, and rotten eggs, and slime.
Yuck!
Destroying the beautiful holiday displays across the mall, and killing hundreds.
Chaos in the crowd outside the contest, the Santas maimed beyond belief, the eggnog stinging
their wounds, Sullivan turned to a green paste, the Hungry Hamster nativity scene covered in
blood and viscera, the Hungry Hamster model in Jesus' manger, its head blown off.
Jack gets up from being knocked by the force of the explosion, but his target has already
dashed away, halfway across the mall, addressing his team.
"Red Alpha, get on my 916 and take point to Dago, Blue take Charlie to Guinea and meet
Red on WAP, insert South.
Yukon, you're with me, move move move."
Meanwhile, the sing-songy baritone of the Grinch theme croons eerily throughout the mall as
our hero sprints through the catastrophe, the injured and dead littering the floor as they
try to catch up to their target.
"You're a mean one indeed, Mr. Grinch," Frost thinks.
All three teams finally meet at the front of the mall and charge through the front doors
together.
Exterior, Duluth, Megamall Day.
The Spec Ops Holiday Unit piles out, their scars ready, scanning the horizon for that
cackling bastard.
Frost, knowing better, looks up.
With his beanie gone, his full green nudity revealed, and his awful, terrible smile haunting
his face. The Grinch flies with his Hello Kitty backpack helicopter some 1,000 feet in the air,
carrying a massive sack of presents for good little boys and girls. "Maybe next time, Jack Frost."
Jack stares at the sky, lowering his scar, completely defeated. Suddenly, kablam,
something in the sky explodes. The troops cover their eyes from the bright light of the fiery
explosion, only to look up a moment later to see the final insult to injury. Spelled out clear as
day in rotten, stinky, lump of coal black smoke. It reads, "This time I'm gonna fuck the presents."
"Jack, what are we gonna do?" says Yukon. "I need to get the team back together."
Cut to main titles. Yule Team 6.
Wow. Beautiful. Christ. You really outdone yourself. I hope so.
So, now we're exterior. Ethiopia's Danikil Depression Day.
The scorching sun beats down the horrible salted sulfuric ground of the Danikil Depression in northern, a far region of Ethiopia.
Did I pronounce that right? There's no way to know. The most uninhabitable place on Earth,
a collision of tectonic plates creating deadly sulfuric hot springs.
The depression is surrounded by volcanoes and is literally the hottest place on Earth.
There are forms of bacteria found in Ethiopia's Danikil Depression that exist nowhere else on Earth.
It's been used to study how life may form on other planets, like Mars, or other Mars.
The irony is, some paleontologists believe that depression to be the cradle of civilization.
Maybe that's why the world's greatest killer, Soldier's Wrath, has retired here.
Sergeant Jack Frost saunters up to his cave where he lay, where he's, you know, he's there.
"Soldier. Soldier's Wrath. Are you here?"
"Oh, I'm here."
Why don't you tell me a little bit about Soldier's Wrath?
*laughs*
Okay.
I've gone by many names in my lifetime.
Darkness the Destroyer,
the Shinjuku Master Lord,
the wickedly evil demon.
But now folks just call me Soldier's Wrath.
I can be found wherever there's conflict.
A menacing mercenary bringing death to all who oppose my employers.
On the lower half of my face I have a Bane mask,
and on the upper half I have Splinter Cell goggles.
snake plissken eye patches over two of the lenses. I have the cape of Todd McFarlane's
spawn and the strategic mind of Seth McFarlane's Stewie. I'm wearing Morpheus sunglasses and
my boots have spikes on the bottom like the scary guy from the Spongebob movie and I have
Boba Fett chest armor with a Mario color scheme and I'm wearing Hulk shorts. I have the knuckle
tattoos from Night of the Hunter but instead of love it says hate and instead of hate it
says tactical. The last thing my enemies ever see is my machine gun which is named Destiny's
Fate and it shoots bullets which are named Insanity's Predilection.
So uh yeah, Soldier's Wrath. Jack Frost tries to begin the conversation again.
Soldier's... Wrath. It's gonna be tough. I think we're also both gonna sound like this
it seems like we both sort of never mind we need you America needs you the world
needs you Christmas needs you the Grinch is back huh I thought this might happen
you okay tell me just one thing frost is there gonna be killing oh is there gonna
to be killing
i got the idea
i have a lot of uh...
okay yeah soldiers wrath piles in the helicopter it's very easy to recruit him
and he joins hot
now uh...
we cut to
uh... outside a uh... no no that's uh... different interior tel aviv nightclub
uh...
he does emanating from the sexual grind dancing is happening in club shalom
were gentiles in glorious ally of those same visit
uh... those are the same day and i think that i think that i think that i think
i didn't look it up after a road it
the
well this is what's called a non-reliable narrator
well-being and yet well at least though i got fact-checked in real time it's for
pinocchios for me uh...
alike in bogey their bogey like their body did nineteen forty five
that's after the holocaust i'm pretty sure
in this happen tel aviv nightclub everything is kosher but no one is more
kosher which to me i think is cool
uh... means cool probably than the zone
and no one messes with the zone on
if you remember the movies as well as i do you'll know that for sure
so hot is the headliner club shalom tonight
and is playing one of his hit songs for a crowd of idea of soldiers the gaza
striptease
i don't remember is on played music in the movie i know he cut hair
but for some reason i also thought he was a d_j_ or something
i don't know maybe i'm confusing with another israeli character maybe in
israeli admit before
anyway check for us is not one for the heat of the dance floor
uh... is usually waiting for girls to notice him and then blame only a sex
with their bodies but
this time
he's gonna go up to the uh... so on ways
doing a set
so uh... uh...
uses a club music playing it's bumping
and so on is d_j_ in in this world
and jack frost's radio music to you
uh... someone
uh... and it's it's cascaded every time we touch
yeah
so on
so i can you hear me
is a little it's a lot
alright
deterred thanks for turning the music down no problem anything for my friend
so i can we talk somewhere more private there's a lot of soldiers here yeah of
course and i said i stepped six feet to the right
yeah
okay
Um, come on.
I have Soldier's Wrath with me here.
Oh, hey Soldier's Wrath.
What's up?
We need to-
We need to- Why did I start doing the accent?
We need to get the team back together.
It's infectious, baby.
It is.
We need to get the team back together.
The Yule Team 6.
The Grinch is back.
He's gonna fuck the presents this time.
That's actually not a bad idea.
No, he's gonna broadcast it to the whole world and destroy the holiday spirit.
No fucking the presents. Yeah, thanks. You thank you
Do you want to join
Sure, you know I have nothing going on tonight. This has been so much easier than I thought it was gonna be I had all these
Plants, fuck you
No, are you implying by saying something like this? No, it's a good thing
It's a good thing that it's easier than I thought it was. Okay. Yeah, let's party
Okay, and we cut to outside a bar in Jalalabad
Jalalabad is an Afghani city
I definitely don't want to try to think about what I don't know anything about that. It just thought the name was cool
But anyway, we're outside a bar in Jalalabad
with the two guys we have in sergeant frost and
We see old Vladimir Muhammad Afghanistan
And
Why don't you tell me a little bit about who Vladimir Mohamed Afghanistan is Thomas?
Hello
my name is
Vladimir a
Mohammed
Afghanistan
And I am from a Afghanistan originally
Forever actually never even moved here
Always lived here. That's sort of my thing
My family is also from here and they didn't come here during the Russian
Afghani war
Don't know why people always say that but I
Live here normally in the traditional
if Guinea
we I
Very much combat experience, but I am terrible at it. I
Not much of a help
Where where why are you standing outside the pussyhound bar in Jalalabad tonight? My family lives here
outside the park
As I am from here Afghanistan
judge other questions
personal in
queries. No, now it's back to I'm Sergeant Jack Frost. Do you remember me? And do you
remember Zohan in Soldier's Wrath? Oh, Zohan and Zolthas Wrath. My old friend. We go way
back several months ago when we first killed the Grinch well he's back no he
was dead yeah oh yeah everyone's had the same reaction yeah well you actually said
that you knew that this would happen I still I couldn't believe it what he's
doing with the presence he's trying to fuck the presence you I'm going to say
No.
She didn't stole.
No, no, go ahead, you're always the boss.
No, well, no, no, I don't want to, that's not the dynamic I want for us man, come on.
Okay, look, we could all hang out, right?
We're all on the same team, right?
So on.
Yeah, man, sure.
This Grinch you speak of.
Yes.
Where is he from?
He from, he from, he from, he from, he from, he from, he from, he from, he from, he from,
he from, he from, he from, he from, he from, he from, he from, he from, he from, he from,
Where is he from?
He is from a country nearby.
Uzbekistan.
Ok, I mean, I don't know anything about...
But I thought you were from Afghanistan, which is, you know, in the Middle East.
Afghanistan.
So you only know, okay, you only know about Afghanistan.
I only know my home village.
Okay. What was that village called again?
Afghanistan.
Okay, good.
It's like Mexico City.
Right, now I'm picking up on it, yeah.
Before I was like, that's weird, but then I was like, there are a lot of cities like that.
Yeah, like Oklahoma City, sort of, you know.
Mexico's, you know, um, Canada city. It's kind of like Mexico City
Texas City, you know Vlad
We need you now more than ever to take out the gritch will you come with us
Okay, okay good
All right, yeah i'm gonna we're now we're now we're somewhere else exterior Ann Arbor, Michigan
Hype house is come and go, but the go blue house never dies.
Here's where superstar Lieutenant Clargon has been chilling since it was a halfway house
for Ann Arbor rich kids who got addicted to pills.
Clargon manages the house, all the influencers in it through hard work, dedication, and creating
15 separate fan accounts to hype him up, one for each race, he says.
Clargon is a talented warrior in his own right.
With his insanely stupid and impractical bolt action rifle, there isn't anything he can't
do.
Sergeant Jack Frost with his team knocks on the door of the Go Blue house.
Glargon!
Identify yourself.
Oh no.
You are going, you like, right now, right now, like by knocking on my door, you are telling
me you don't care.
Like my family doesn't live here, they live somewhere else.
They actually live like, uh, here, here, uh, Auburn Hills, actually.
Like they just moved there.
I haven't been by there.
It was like a whole fucking thing would happen where, like, I didn't clean the grill and
and it's like I helped pick out the grill.
I would like way to get the fucking new house
off on a bad foot.
Like, oh yeah, I'm gonna clean the grill.
I told you what fucking grill to buy.
But anyway, like if my family was here
and they opened the door and you were like a type
of criminal that would shoot them.
- Right.
- How the fuck like kill me every day, all day,
anytime, anywhere.
- I'm following you.
Yeah, go on.
Like, you have a lot of fucking balls coming to my house when you could potentially could be a BTK.
Look, Qlargon, I know the Grinch mission didn't end well, but I got the team back together.
We need to fight the Grinch again.
We need you. We need your bolt-action rifle.
Yeah, honestly, like, I have a lot of, like, PCD and all types of stuff from the last mission,
And it's like, I would never be the type of guy who goes out there in the world and fucking talks about like,
"Oh, you know, I have this problem, I have that problem, you know, I feel bad for me, I'm not responsible for what I do."
But like, honestly, since that mission, I cannot tell right from wrong.
Oh.
And it's responsible, it's the reason why I've done so many bad things since then.
Right.
Well, Argon, he's gonna fuck the presence this time.
And wait till you hear what he's doing. Oh, fuck you stole it.
You know, honestly, I got to say I'm the last person who I ever thought would hear myself
saying this. But one man's terrorist is another man's soldier.
I'm asking you to be a terrorist for us. I mean, or a soldier. I'm actually a little
confused now I'm sorry. Whichever you want to be you can be that. Yeah honestly I never
thought about it that way. I'll do it on like one condition. Name it. Let me say goodbye
to these people at this influencer house who have been like basically my family, my real
family ever since the mission. Yeah who's in the house with you? Yeah we got my boy fucking
Chadster Jake.
What's up?
Yeah.
Oh shit, there's two of us.
We're twins.
No, you're Chadster, I'm Jake.
What's up?
Jake Joshin.
And my girl, like I never thought there'd be a girl in this influencer house, but honestly,
she's been like, she shows that like women, like at least half the time can be the same
as men.
Clarissa, Clarissa Smuckers.
Hey.
So I know for a fact that I'm the most important person in all of your lives.
I don't know, until this moment, I didn't know if you were the most important people
in mind.
But sometimes to be someone who's important in someone else's life, to be who they meant
to be for you, you've got to be who they are for them.
And sometimes the, you know, they say like, if you love something, abandon it.
And that's what I'm doing right now.
Stay clean, don't take pills you find on the floor.
Only take them if a doctor or someone who got them from a doctor took them and could
verify it for you.
And just be yourself.
I love you guys.
If I die on this mission, please tell my family it was their fault.
Will do.
Sounds good, Skipper.
Dude, honestly, yeah, you're the realest fucker ever, dude.
I know I don't know what we would have what we would do without you, but you know, I guess we're like
We're probably pretty bad. Yeah
I will I will remember your life forever. Keep doing
the
day with this whole squad rolling up. The San Francisco Zoo, it's one of the two
cities that will be left in 50 years. The Zuckerberg Zoo for Waipipo is an exotic
place meant to showcase how Waipipo be kind of sus. That's right, it's a zoo for
the whites in the straights who are, they're not okay. One of the most famous
exhibits is one that holds Crispin "Crisp" Ratt, a legendary grenadier and
and member of sergeant jack frost all you'll team six
uh... to get to the zoo you have to give them a tweet you made in two thousand
nine to hold this collateral
uh... they'll be returned to you upon leaving
uh... so uh... jack frost did so
as you guys did you get him a tweet from two thousand nine no i would like to
uh... pull out my uh... claim that i'm twenty five percent cherokee
right now can visit uh... well doug do you have the paperwork to prove that
sir uh... swan
it to have any paperwork you realize that like
paperwork like literally no one needed paperwork before christophe i'm so sorry
i'm so sorry i'm so you're absolutely right i thought i'd stupid
stupid
stupid it's consider yourself held accountable you dumb fucking pussy
well okay and that guy just like pulls on a lever and he just falls to the
earth
uh... immediately after that conversation uh... i make a paper airplane out of my
my
paper that I wrote on in 2009 that just says "Chinese food be tasting weird AF" and I signed
it with my name and the date.
Vlad.
My tweet is written in a language no one can understand.
Unfortunately, we may never know.
But it gets me in whatever it is.
Don't worry about it.
You're so right.
It does.
And Cameron won't let me read mine, so I have to just move on I guess. So yeah, so we go to the
zoo. We're going, we're rolling up to to Sergeant Crisp's exhibit. What's going on Patrick? Who's
Sergeant Crisp? I'm Sergeant Crisp, Brat. I love, I'm in the zoo because I love Christ too much.
Yes, so they saw trap to the exhibit where you're you're doing your thing. What are you doing in your exhibit?
What do you I I am just I'm reenacting old episodes of Parks and Rec
You're just doing some fatty fall down some classic ready fall down. Yeah. Yeah
Can we see some bloopers I
Have a blooper reel
On a thumb drive I can throw out
Yeah, I'll sit over
Okay, okay rolled athletics check
What you get eight it just sort of like hits the side
Did his classic trick
USB drive to the plexiglass
I have a question for crisp. Yeah. Oh, yeah. What what's up?
So like you were on TV, like did you like? Oh, yeah, it was awesome. I love being on TV
That's so sick. Did you did you like fucking no Dark Angel? Oh, yeah. Yeah, I knew Dark Angel. I knew we we were on
We did a bunch of Marvel stuff together. It was so cool. It was so awesome to do that with him
Yeah, I don't know. I'm done. Good talk to the group. Yeah, I don't know what the fuck like this guy's whole thing is
I think he's like a Baptist version of the wall books. Yeah
I love God and I love Christ and I used to have a youth minister and
Before I got sent into the the zoo. I you know, I
Used to go to church every day and I'd you know
Chris
Do you love God you love this zoo? Look anything anything you can say to get me out of here. I'll do it
I don't do you love the United States
You don't even want me to do all the thing. I've honestly talked so much. That's fair. Let's go
So yeah, we get Chris Pratt out of the white people's zoo after signing some paperwork.
I slam my head against the plexiglass until there's a crack in it.
And yeah, you guys, the team is back together.
My voice is cracking.
And we are now, so the team now goes to, Sergeant Jack Frost brings you all to the Holiday HQ.
HQ, United States Secret Holiday HQ, which is underneath the
Senior Frogs in Times Square. And after passing through multiple security
checks, retinal and rectal scans, a ping test,
two-factor authentication, you reach a final massive
like Krabby Patty vault-sized door. And Jack Frost says, "The password is
'Ding, fries are done.'" And the massive vault
turns open and you see a state-of-the-art facility of all,
you know for all you know holiday activity right so
it's bass and lush looks like a wonderland but also has like
steel and metal in computers and call graphic technology
researchers are testing weapons
mind control devices and his little helpers are there to their helping you
know working on shit
uh... there's a sick bay for anyone who's the holiday spirit
is a rec room filled with christmas christmas cookies and a giant glossy
ham for each of you
i thought i think i do is that the whole but i wrote a bit
i have not eaten real food i_d_ pellets whenever the fuck i was thrown into that
zoo
you just need to to hands like you don't even need to meet somebody else and to
know this is awesome it is just like bacon's cousin
no i think i'm eating hamsa disco
the
uh... and there's also of course the holiday deck
which is where any battle simulations can be played out in real time
uh... everything that happens in their
uh... even if it seems like an illusion your brain will believe it
so jack frost adjusts you all
but it feels like home fellas
or anything feels better than where i was
uh... i'd like to know if there's any uh... opana or perhaps t-shirts that
have opana residue that i could lick off here
uh... there might be in the changing room area before we go to the holiday deck if you
want that
i don't really i'm clean and sober for
Yeah, no, but you're trying to look out for it to make sure you don't look at yeah
All right, let's get you guys debriefed cortana and cortana appears in front of you and she's wearing a sexy christmas outfit
Uh, she says, uh, happy holidays. Sergeant frost. What do you need? I need a hand job
I guess I didn't finish writing that
(laughing)
- Let's debrief the team here on Operation Tokyo Melanoma.
And Cortana pulls up a hologram and presents the mission,
briefing information with maps, video clips, audio.
She presents it like Vanna White.
Jack Frost says, "You know your target by now,
"it's the Grinch.
"We thought he was done when Zohan threw him
"in the volcano in Portugal, but it seems like he lived.
"We have ample reason to believe he carried out
terrorist attack and do it with mega mall and he's gonna strike again before Christmas Day.
Um, I told you he's gonna fuck he's gonna fuck the presents. He's also captured Santa's normal
Santa, Jewish Santa, and Black Santa and he's captured all of them and now there will be no
presents delivered. Uh, I uh, that the but he if he got Black Santa like I started the Black Lives
Protest in in Ann Arbor. I started the the uh the fucking Ann Arbor chapter of Black Guys and
Are you saying there are black people?
No, it's more like, okay, so there's in the world, there's a lot of societies and in those societies, there's this thing called police, police mutality.
And it's basically like I was I just had seen enough. I was like, let's end it.
Oh, respect, respect.
Thank you. Um, so like, we got to get black Santa back, especially,
especially black santa
yeah agreed
now that there is a good black guys friend in the oval office is like more
important
uh... it couldn't agree more clark on
and that gives us a president
uh...
our sources tell us the grinch is holed up in the back of stan
and in the capital city of who did that
and another one of our sources a double agent who came to our side claims they
They know exactly where the Grinch's Bahambug Fortress is located.
You'll be dropping in the Candy Cane Forest outside of the city.
You'll be met with resistance fighters, gumdrop mines, missile tows, and things we can't even predict.
If you move quickly, it'll take you about half a day to get in the city. We can't drop you any closer.
We don't want you to get caught. You'll be assuming new identities once you're there.
And then you're going to go to a safe house in South Hooterdad.
My contact, Charlie Brown, he owns the place. He'll let you in for the mission.
He's a civilian, so don't make too much trouble for him.
When you reach his house, he'll greet you outside.
He'll say, "One, cut a hole in the box."
You'll say, "Two, put your junk in that box."
Then he'll say, "Three, make her open the box."
And then together you'll say, "And that's the way we do it.
It's my dick in the box."
That way he'll know it's you for sure.
Once you're settled in there, you'll put on your disguises
and meet our special friend, the double agent codenamed Rudolph
at the Jollibee's Bar and Grill in the center of Hooterdad.
He'll give you the location the blueprints of the Bahamut fortress
After that, you'll storm the fortress and you'll do whatever you you know, you know, you'll kill the Grinch probably
any questions
Yeah, can you repeat all that? Okay
I'm genuinely running out of gravel in my voice and it's my fault
I didn't know there was a finite amount until now
Uh, which part do you want me to repeat the whole thing?
The whole thing. You know what I can do? Here, I've got a PDF. Just, do you have a phone?
No. I can airdrop. They took my phone in the zoo. Okay, well I'll get something printed out for you
later. Okay. Does anybody else have any questions about this mission? Can you repeat that thing
about the PDFs? Hold on. Anybody else have any questions about this mission? Yeah, what,
can you repeat that last thing you said? You are the same person. You know that, right, Chris?
Okay, so we're gonna in 100 hours we're gonna commence training at the holiday deck.
So get suited up, say hello to old friends. I trust you all to remember where your old gear is.
Let's get to work. You're free to roam the headquarters and then we'll just meet up at the holiday deck and you'll do a training session.
I started doing P90X.
the
that pretty easily. What are you doing there?
Um, first thing I do is clog the toilet.
I haven't used a real toilet in years and just the act of wiping excites me too much.
I'm sharpening my bullets using like a cool stone.
I sit down crisscross applesauce in the middle of the floor and put my head in my hands hoping
that a girl will notice.
I just keep offering a dowry to like any woman who walks in.
You guys all harass somebody in some way for the remainder of your time and you get some
Christmas hams and some cookies and you guys show up to the holiday deck.
water overflowing out of the toilet. I'm laying in it and I'm doing like snow angels. I'm
rebaptizing myself! I'm rebaptizing myself! The water is flowing and you literally end
up swimming. It just floats you down to the holiday deck. It's like the shape of water
where she fills up the bathroom with the water. You guys enter the holiday deck and Jack Frost
sort of talks you over intercom. He says we need to make sure you guys are all up to snuff.
It's been so long since you've been in combat about a few months, I guess. The holiday deck
has improved quite a bit. So Cortana load up Fred Claus and you see right away just a perfect
Fred Claus shows up in front of you guys. He's a shoot him. Let's go. Okay. Yeah, roll
an attack roll. Okay, that hits. Okay. Oh, no, it's not. Oh, wait. Yeah, I forgot for
destiny's fate it's just like a deck save free so he has to make a deck save
well yeah he he gets hit he dies you just tear so you see I did say huh yeah
you see yeah he's just going like yeah I don't know what about however Vince Vaughn
sounds it's so hard I tried to learn an impression it's not possible I have a
certain quality Vaughn's libertarian right yeah I think he's something like
that. Age of consent is bullshit. Yeah, yeah and he says that and then he gets completely lit up by
your minigun and you see Jack Frost go, "Not bad, now what do you think of this?" and he loads up
15 Fred Clauses in front of all of you and everyone's gonna roll for initiative for this
first test. Oh my god. So yeah, yeah so 15 Fred Clauses show up in front of you and they're like
they're being obnoxious about something and
i never saw that movie itself
and uh...
what happens in it
patrick you look uh...
fred claus is paul giamatti santa's brother
and there is a must have been a better way to construct that
idea
uh...
uh... it was fine
and i was good yeah
uh... cameron you're gonna go first others with fifteen afraid causes in
front of you
there they're about sixty feet away
uh... as far as how in holiday space
uh... i mean holiday tech space
uh... and uh...
uh... yeah
that's that's what i'll say so we want to
uh... i'm just gonna start unloading my
damn many gun at 'em
yeah we have a lot of this is a
okay
what's a role for them so yeah you're gonna be able to hit probably about seven
of them with this
so they're gonna just try to roll the dexter i'm just gonna roll for like
seven dextrose and just see how many get caught.
Wow, they, how do you kill all seven?
You kill seven of them.
Yeah, I just go, I just, I kill seven of them but I only shoot seven bullets from
the minigun. I start shooting for like half a second
and they just like poof away. Okay, yeah, yeah, there's eight left and
they're just like, they look, even though they're
computer programs, they look terrified suddenly.
on jack frost is like looks like i got a turn it up a notch any
cranks some meter that says of bonds on any crates of bonds number up
to and i see fifty
vince bonds in front of you
uh... uh... and now it is uh... your turn
uh... sarah is your turn as though on
so you are on
you know me is my ninja star david
okay yeah you got thirteen so that that
hits
uh... whoever
you're aiming at which we're aiming at the sea of in spawns is there one in
particular you don't like
are any of them are you ready for chance like lined up all in a row said maybe
there's a possibility that the
the star goes straight through
a bunch of them
uh... you know i i'll have you do role uh...
please
the role role i i i think role at athletics
on top of that to see if you do this uh... athletic maneuver
is what i call it
are you getting one still
and just roll for damage now hit me a lot of it yet is too low
yeah i mean you still basically like you you get in one in the head
and you blight eight like five more on fire they're not dead but they're all
they're like melting
uh... but the one you get in the head is just dead
uh... and uh... you have another taxes if you want to throw the star that
and on the now many is my problem ago
yeah okay you run up to them
that's gonna hit whichever one you're aiming at what it what kind of uh...
moves you want to run them
uh... problem dot
is
or but you can't even the ball so it's like karate and ballet
right side i'll do like uh...
well i got uh... yes i'm like that i'll do it up to you
a into the jumping double that's not what crop of guys that's a half ballet
come through
what do you like it
you like uh...
yes i a yes i am serious i would like to be a part of character i don't know
actually just for swag points i i uh... because i'm the zone out of the on and
then every skilled
yes i i i i i build a uh... a bill a small sort of like sheet rock wall
in front of the guy
and i'm attacking and i kick through that
into his face and i got it
probably killaments did you build the while you're building the she rock wall
the
Vince Vons turns and they're gonna try to swarm you uh uh Zohan since you're up on them um let's
see how they do okay yeah a few of them do get some land some punches on you uh you take uh
these Vince Vons are pretty weak you take three damage that's it from the punches um and it's
just like a few of them just like jumping on you and just and doing their their kind of uh yeah
Incredulous improv that Vince Vaughn's do and
Now it is
Yeah, it's your turn
Oh wait shit. No, Thomas got a yo Thomas. You're up. Oh, no, it's not. It's sorry. It's Patrick. So Chris fucking pick whose turn
Man this is the most unprofessional thing I've ever been
What do you do Chris
All right, so they're all I mean
No, and Vince Vaughn, he's probably
Distracted right now talking to the other Vince Vaughn's. Yeah, they're all agreeing with each other. You were so nice. You were so good in dodgeball
Hey, you were so good that remake of psycho underrated
Yeah, so while there's like a group of them together, I'm gonna throw
What's this blinded by is that a flashbang? Yeah, it's a flashbang
Then I'm gonna throw the Molotov slushy at him. Yeah, go for it
Yeah that fucking that hits them and
Wow shit, you're gonna do a lot of damage to them. Yeah
Okay. Yeah, it's just a bad role
But you still like get slushy on like ten of them and they also now can't move like they're they're fucking like frozen from the
slushy explosion
Yeah, okay. All right, then uh, I have another attack. I'll just go Tommy boy gun while they're frozen. Yeah, do it
Yeah, that's a crit roll for damage
11 yeah, you just care we go. Yeah, that's beautiful. You just killed like
16 of them. How do you do it?
Very carefully. Yeah, okay great and
Thomas you're up
Let's see, I've got this this terrible ak-47 and I've got this
I've got a character carved into it and I say it's Arabic for joy, but it's clearly like maybe Chinese
And I'm just gonna I'm just gonna pull that out and start spraying
Yeah, do it it might jam, but we'll see
Yeah, that hits for sure
Yeah
You did one of the ones that were that were like that was fucked up with by the slushy and you could attack again -
If you want to attack again or I'll probably do some of my traditional Afghani martial arts. Mm-hmm
which involves
Yeah, what does that involve? It's a good question much what you'd expect. Okay, you know cuz say no more
It sounds clear to me. Yeah, um, it's
It's like how you'd react if you just like we're attacked by like a medium-sized dog
yeah, it's just like a
throws and then
I've got it. I may or may not have a turban on depending on what
And if I do which maybe I don't
Then maybe I sort of whip with that like I have a little hook on the end of it. It's right. I
Can pretty much do whatever I want
Yeah do that so I probably do that like a million times
Yeah, I forgot to put that in there but you could do that a million times but you're right
Yeah, I'll probably a million times. Yeah, yeah, yeah roll for it. Hey, maybe
Yeah, yeah, it doesn't hit it's a seven
And Clark God you're out
All right
So like I don't want to use my bolt action. It's fun. It's obviously very important to Clark on right
Like God got me through a lot of tough times
so I'm gonna take out my scar and
I
I lied down on my back
But like I sort of like put my it's like you have your head to propped up on a pillow. Yeah, it is actually
It actually hurts my windpipe, but in my mind, I think that's the most accurate way to shoot
a gun.
So I just sort of try to line them up.
Yeah, you look like your tummy's full after a big Thanksgiving meal.
Yeah, yeah.
And I have something to say to Vince Vaughn, and it is, hey, you may have done the breakup,
but now we're breaking up.
My favorite that's color guns favorite movie of all I don't know. I don't know what you're talking about, you know the breakup
I don't even see that movie. Yes, you know, they're just vamping. They don't know they're they're AI they're hurt, but they don't know why
Just yeah, I feel like I'm getting blown off and it makes me really mad
So I'm just gonna start firing. Yeah
Rolling nice as a critical one
I'm so my aim is so fucking good. I start going like
Nice to catch one of them like like but like you catch one of them in the shoulder somehow, but yeah, otherwise just I
Instantly turn to the group in any theoretical girls, you know, honestly
I probably have the most bodies in every sense of the word in any war I've ever been in but
you don't really feel PSD or
TSD or or ODST until you fucking have to fire on someone who is once a friend as
is Vince Vaughn. And the Jack Frost you see him he's like he's like all right
this is all I can already see how tough you guys are I'm gonna turn up the
bonds meter more and he turns it up and you see like 500 Vince Vaughns and then
you see everything go completely dark and he's like and Cortana's like like
power off you know with joshie says and uh the lights come back on oh my god am i [ __ ] dead
all the vince vons are dude no i see the [ __ ] light at the end of the tunnel
oh my god oh my god wait god wait god is e from entourage
my favorite character of all time finally i can go to hell
and all the vince vons have the grinch face and they stare at you all blankly and then they make
the creepy ass grinch smile and you see jack frost from behind the the plexiglass in the holiday deck
he's like i don't know what's going on this isn't in the simulation cortana what's going on run
diagnostics and she said i already did run diagnostics you're right this isn't in the
simulation hey run it again okay she starts running it again meanwhile you see uh the grinch
Space says, uh, well, it looks like the whole gang's back together.
How do you know?
Because I'm looking at you.
We could have an extra guy that you don't know about.
There could be a new guy.
You could have got a new guy.
Oh, yeah.
Where is he?
He's in the bathroom.
You all said that at the same time.
So that makes me really suspect.
Yeah, that just means it's more true.
Honestly, the odds of everyone coming up with the same lie at once are very low in odds,
and it's only happened to me two or three times in my life.
I guess I'm thinking about it, I can see both sides of sort of what I'm saying.
Look, I'm infiltrating your base to tell you to come and get it.
You're never gonna stop me, and I know you're coming for me, and I'm gonna stop you when
you try to come for me.
You try- if-
Listen, listen here you fucking green cocksucker.
Oh shit.
If you try to stop me when I'm stopping you to start what you started before you stop it,
and I stop it when you start me, well you're gonna be ending a whole new thing that you're
fucking starting.
You can fucking- you can fucking tell anybody that.
You tell your fucking boss that.
I'll tell my boss that and then I'll tell him that you tried to stop me from starting to
to stop on you and that's when you're gonna really feel it.
'Cause that's what's gonna happen
after you start stopping me.
We try to start doing that.
That's when it's up.
- Hey, you know what?
You know what?
That's fucking fine.
- All the Gritches are saying this.
All the Gritches are saying this at the same time.
All 100 of them.
- All of you, all of you,
I want you to remember this right now.
- Go for it.
- I didn't start this,
but,
fuck.
How does this usually go?
Oh yeah yeah yeah!
No, I didn't start this.
But when it ends...
I'll be the one that started that ending.
Roll an intimidation check with advantage.
Yeah, you're right. That was cool.
You see the Grinch?
You see beads of sweat on the Grinch's forehead.
You think, "Well, I've got something to do anyway, so..."
I think that, I think these AI Grinches just peed.
That's not real pee, that's, that's the-
I'm seeing pee!
Yeah.
That's the holiday Dexter's filling up with AI pee.
It's a hundred-
Just ones and zeros, it's not real pee.
Oh, oh, it's, it's, I hate this.
I hate this so much.
I'm, I'm gonna get out of here.
I'm gonna go lube up my, my penis to fuck the presents.
To pee some more?
No, that's not what lube is for, I think.
using P as lube? No I'm not. Stop putting words in my mouth. It's totally fine if he does,
like P is sterile. I wouldn't do it, but hey, you know what? If it's recommended by my team,
I might try it. I love you guys. It's not bad for you, I love you too. You're the realest
fucking guy I've ever met in my life. You guys keep me down to earth, you guys keep
the grounded
that's right and then we're gonna send some more people down to earth
to and
when they're sixty
under the ground
in hell
uh... i'm swimming around in the p_e_ and i look back and i'm like i can use this
is thermal camouflage in case you run into a predator
the
the greater the greater
uh... vanishes in in shame at clark on spanner
epic intimidation
you see jack frost runs out he says sorry i didn't make the bridges voice that
different i'll work on that later but also i'm really sorry about the bridge
infiltrating that's not ok
that should not be sacred sacred train
damn right it's not
it's not
uh... i am i am holding your shit accountable
you know what this uh... the second time that's happened to me today and i'm
learning
i'm growing in learning and i have ten more tweets about that in a second
but first they used to use to eat longer dot com
uh... it longer dot com what's that
this is a great website that she tweeted more than a hundred forty characters
it's really how is it possible to donate to them
that's right so on how is that possible more than a hundred and forty characters
How is it possible on Twitter.com?
It just drops a link for you.
Oh my god.
That's amazing.
Maybe I'll have to try it later when I apologize
about something I said about hungry or something.
(laughing)
It is, there's nothing better to use than twit longer
for when you're accused of something you did not do.
Yeah, it used to be, it used to be pay spin,
but now I don't know where that went.
Too many people who were actually guilty used pay spin.
(laughing)
But all the innocent people use TwitLonger.
Yeah, that's why some of our famous clients like Harvey Weinstein, Louis CK, Alan Dershowitz,
David Geffen all of you use TwitLonger.
Can we not talk about Alan Dershowitz?
He was like the godfather at my confirmation.
I'm sorry about that.
Cherokee confirmation.
He's a really good guy.
Once you actually get to know him.
We'll take that out of the ad read I'm sorry about that
He's a guy who helped me hide the Malaysian Airlines
So, please, have some respect.
Goddamn.
Yeah, I heard he hid it in Pharrell's hat.
(laughing)
- That's just a rumor I heard.
- That was so 2014.
(laughing)
- Chris, I wish I had a FameStar cup I could give you.
- Thanks for the cup, darling.
(laughing)
- So yeah, it's time for the mission.
So you guys all pile into the jet
that's on top of uh... senior frogs
and you are fly
for you know
fifteen ur so hours
to uh... uh...
to over who becky stan
which again is is uh... between
iraq
uh... iran
uh... saudi arabia kuwait
somewhere and uh... you guys fly over it
and uh...
we start to see it so it's you can see it's wintery cheer even from way up where
you are
and uh... uh...
uh... you see uh...
sergeant uh... jack frosty motions to all now
spit out fifteen hours of flight you know
he says uh...
that that game of
of uh... was monopoly we played was fun but now it's time to drop out of the
plane
into the candy cane forest
what you get there
get ready 'cause you're you probably have to deal with some insurgent who's who
work for the great
are you guys ready to drop
Okay, we could circle a few more times.
I'm like shaking like a junkie because this is the longest I've ever gone without having sex.
[Laughter]
Look, we all offered to do something for you, Zohan,
but you turned us down, so I don't know what to tell you, man.
I just leap out of the plane instantly without saying anything.
Okay, uh...
Everyone should jump. Everyone should jump now.
of
Oh, nice.
Yeah, everybody roll athletics.
I'm so not sure if I got a turbine or not,
but if I have a turbine, I'm using it as a parachute.
You have a huge turbine.
You have the biggest turbine, like a Ben Garrison cartoon.
Just like a, a huge turbine.
Oh, for me, it's a normal sized turbine, from my culture.
Oh no, Caleb.
So hot.
I gotta crit one, dude.
What are we rolling here?
Athletics.
Yeah, what are we rolling here?
I think I clicked the wrong button or something.
say you are dropping down here rushing past you as you fall through the sky
uh... you know
the temperature starts to drop i could get used to this all over again
and uh... you start to see the massive candy cane trees coming into view
uh... chris pratt
you fuckin
you've missed this so much it's so much better than a zoo
it's so much more freedom than you've ever had in a long time
This feels nothing like a cattle prod, I'll tell you that.
You know, with the 21 you're just like flipping around, you're doing all kinds of fucking
sky tricks.
It's a cool time.
Do you remember the intro scene of...
This Power Rangers movie?
Yes.
Dude, when Higher Ground is playing, colored blood and chili peppers?
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah, I'm doing that.
I'm fucking, I'm on the... which one of them has the skateboard?
Probably the pink one.
Yeah, probably the...
probably the yeah you can't be stereotyping my bad I take it back
it's a black one then so now it's time for a let's let's see what else someone
else is doing it's a fuck what's his name oh yeah soldiers wrath you're
falling it's perfect this is all you know how to do is fight and kill yeah I
I say again slightly louder, huh? I could get used to this all over again, and I look back up at the
My of my squad members. I heard you the first time
That's real cute
Wow
and
Hold on. Oh, sorry
Tell me this when I get down. I can't hear anything. There's so much wind I
I just I shake my head like and expect him to see it
Yeah, I want to make sure you were good sorry you were just oh dude my mic hasn't been plugged in this whole time
I've been on my headphones audio, but it's fine
*laughter*
There's no cable.
Oh no!
*laughter*
I'm so sorry.
I noticed this light wasn't blinking.
I was like...
Oh no!
That explains why you're kinda quiet.
It does explain your audio, like a lot.
I did just like, expect
that Thomas would just not know how to
how to like set up his microphone
and that's why it sounded so bad.
(laughing)
- It's literally, dude,
I literally just have to plug this cable into this.
It's plugged into the computer.
- All right, let's see it.
- I'm so sorry. - Let's see what happens.
- This is gonna sound amazing, dude.
- Plug my cable in and see what happens.
(laughing)
- Magically.
- Oh my God. - Oh my God.
- Oh my God. - So much better.
- Really? - Yeah.
- So much better.
- You have to keep this in, Cameron,
so that everyone can experience it together.
- Yeah, I'm so sorry.
No, it's rocks, dude.
It adds to the narrative.
Yeah, absolutely.
Every time I talked, it was like,
y'all were struggling to hear me.
And I was like, I'm right next to the microphone.
(all laughing)
I don't get why I'm doing, my audio is great.
And then I look and it's not plugged in.
That's like, Thomas had a,
he was trying to get like an ethernet cable
ran up to his computer for like so long
so that we could play games together.
And then he sent a picture of the back of his computer
in a group chat and he had a wifi card the entire time.
(laughing)
- Yeah, it was like a seven month wait.
- It was so long, dude.
- Well, back to it, I guess.
(laughing)
- We are better equipped than ever.
- Yeah, definitely.
This is only a good thing, dude.
It's been fun already.
- We're like an hour and a half into this.
- Yeah, imagine if the opposite thing happened.
(laughing)
- Klargon, you're killing it, falling from the sky.
This is easy for you.
- Yeah. - You've done this before.
- Yeah, I was born into a parachuting family.
So this is really like whatever for me.
- Yeah. - This is, yeah.
Like no problem, no problem.
- And Afghanistan, Mr. Afghanistan.
Vlad. - Yes.
yeah this has been this is this is you do pretty well you you basically
uh... you know you prize get your sea legs back a bit it's been a while since
you've dropped
uh... you know i mean and uh...
uh... yeah
and uh... yeah
missed uh...
and uh... when did correct
uh... yeah you know that it's
it's a a plan on
yeah
i think uh...
she kept it is a little bit on the grounds
and says though i don't know in a moment
so on you are just like we teach it a refund not fucking to get this right
here at the details
in yeah i'm just like screaming
like i think i don't even realize that a parachute on i think it's a jane sport
the and
i'm just free falling and i hit the ground but my penis lands perfectly in a
hole in the ground
yeah uh... yeah and you you uh... uh...
take and you were fully healed by the way but uh...
you're gonna take
uh...
to damage from just falling uh... everybody else felt kinda perfectly
uh... he has all landed in the candy cane forest
everything sticky in there's like the snow on the ground is like sugary powder
and uh...
uh...
i need now so on unusual stealth check though
only landed pretty hard
i did
Okay, 23. So you hear some rustling in the woods and you hear some people talking, but
they don't notice you. And you all sort of, everybody roll a perception check now. Zohan
with that 23, I mean you guys, Zohan you get a clear sense of where the insurgents are.
You know exactly where they are. You can communicate that to your team members. You guys have a
a chance of I'd say with that crit you have a chance of everybody else rolled solo.
Everybody else is not quite sure where anybody is but Zohan for some reason you know where
everything everyone is where all the insertions are.
His penis went into the ground so he can feel the vibration.
Yeah exactly.
Footsteps.
I also immediately came.
Just the friction of my penis entering the ground made me come instantly.
This planet is Zohan tree.
Let's see if it glows.
And uh, yeah.
But I'm also like, I'm also like,
you guys go ahead, I'll stay here.
[Laughter]
You guys, I'll catch up with you later.
You could take point too,
Zohan, now. So, uh,
you can lead the group through the woods
if you want to. Dude, I'll do it.
Okay, cool.
So what do you say to them? What are you guys planning on doing? You guys know there are
insurgents around you.
What's the strategy? Are they,
do we like the insurgents or do we hate them so much?
you hate them, they're Grinch insurgents
insurgents is just a catch all word for something you're not supposed to like
I say uh, follow me's
and then I start, I start swinging on the candy canes like monkey bars
yeah, you guys follow him?
no, I start licking the candy cane
no, dude, no, you can lick them all the way
okay, if I can lick them all, what if I swing by my tongue?
which is just a normal sized...
yeah, of course, yeah, no problem
okay
I'll let you try and you can roll an athletics check.
Okay.
Got an eight.
Yeah, no, you just, you hurt your tongue.
It's too, it's too spiky.
It's a classic Christmas story joke.
So uh, suck, suck, suck.
suck.
I said suck!
I can't suck because my tongue got stuck in my teeth and it's not fun to sit.
And with that expert perception check though Zohan too, I'm going to give you all advantage
on your stealth roll and you're going to have to together be stealthy enough to avoid dealing
with insurgents.
But because Zohan got that crit on knowing exactly where they are, everybody rolls stealth
role and you'll just take the highest number of the two. It is interesting to me that you made
the only Jewish character. He has he has advantage in stealth and deception. I didn't that's just I
just find that interesting. Nope that's the character of Zohan. He has a place in finance?
That is well but he only had his own business he's a business owner in the movie.
The only character played by a Jewish person is awful at deception.
But that's a good point, but does it constantly?
Well, you know, that's I'm just sort of figuring out what the
right way to not get cancelled is so that's just sort of
fine-tuning that it's a science.
We have Thomas with his turban.
So we're all just sort of figuring it out together with
all kind of working off that right now.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's the foundation.
Yeah, Thomas is sort of the touchstone here.
Exactly. I'm texting Thomas tons of ideas.
I'm just sending him lines from the boondocks and I'm like, you should do this.
It's the first hour and a half. My mic did work, but they blurred out the audio so you
couldn't hear what I was saying. I'm like, oh, oh, now I can talk. This is cool.
Okay. And so they're going to see if they hear you. Let's see.
Chris Pratt, you are, you figured out you can't use your tongue, right?
And so you've been just sort of swinging on the candy cane vines.
But you see sort of a cluster of gumdrop berries nearby and you just go ham on them.
And you stop what you're doing and you just go ham on them.
Okay.
and uh...
one insurgent
here's some ferocious eating
uh... interns to look over and we give you one chance to stealth role because
it was very close
uh... i've rolled intimidation because i was intimidating gumdrops
to intimidate gumdrops
i got a sixteen
they're incredibly scared
you i thought you know what i thought because it's like a christmas
stellar's
i'd just wanted to explain my reasoning
that's i thought that because it's a christmas universe that the gumdrops
would have a personality like the fries at mcdonald's
so
all god he's
and they are at thank you
and i think you need to hear anytime i got a nineteen for stealth
okay cool yes so insurgent sort of wanders over
he's looking around it's a who needs police gun
and uh... use of crutch behind the bush of gumdrops
you're still nibbling at them
but he can't hear it
he's just like, meanwhile there's a gumdrop just going
"AHH"
he just comes over and he's like
"huh, i guess the gumdrops were eating themselves again"
damn, damn gumdrops and yeah so you guys make it through
uh... avoiding the insurgents, avoiding an ensuing fight
uh...
and you guys make it a bit further now in the woods so it's been a few more hours
uh... you guys traversing uh... the candy cane forest
and uh... you come across what looks like
uh... a large yeti
and uh... you see it
uh... intimidating
what looks to be a a a a group of of local who's
and uh...
they're like all
is that he has yet he plays and uh... the the yeti
is just like
so you can see that sort of in your periphery
but uh...
that he will you want to do this is so he has played the games of all games
as a lot of moral yeah yeah i a m it's it yet or like
uh... nice field republicans in my head yeah right
all right
uh...
so my reading on it is late and it's really like
you know i see injustice as i said that's a new part of my personality last year
i can group
this is the reason i joined blackwater in the first place
the protect the week from the strong
we have to do something
i do in the yeti steam
uh...
no
was everybody else to you guys want to something with this
i'm i'm in the bush just
for i'm going to town on these fucking gumdrops
i see i i see the opportunity to kill a big monster i just a great
but i will never have a lot of
and running towards it
okay uh... uh...
all right as a lot are you gonna are you gonna join the any
is frozen
he's frozen
this difficult question
It's a very difficult question to answer.
Yeah.
Are you going to join the Yeti?
Vlad, what about you?
How are you feeling?
I think I'll probably follow around the Zohan because I'm trying to figure out what his deal is.
Oh, okay.
I'm back.
Sorry.
I thought dude, we thought you were just sitting entirely still.
I was like,
Damn, he looks good at being still.
I didn't know.
I was like,
It was pretty weird, man.
No, I got, I got owned by Spectrum yet again.
(clears throat)
- So, are you joining the Yeti?
- Yeah, I joined the Yeti
'cause he's kind of like the stronger, bigger guy.
And it seemed like the Hoos are,
kind of have it coming.
- Okay, yeah.
So you guys square up on this scene.
Play this scene out for me.
Like you guys are now on opposing sides
in this random Yeti Hoos.
- I'm on the Yeti's shoulders like he's my dad
in Disney World.
and i'm i'm i'm kinda unlike twenty a different
different who's alone no one in the end
place that may not stop at any now
there was a new yeti bar my turban
yeti blood loves that he's wearing turban
he's flexing and he looks good
he gives you a thumbs up my all along with the eddie's in the end guys i'd
grab the yeti's leg and i'm trying to pull them over
okay related to my role role shrink check to see if you do that
eighteen
okay yeah you're able to tell how many of the a little bit
uh... you call a little bit over your
her
uh...
and so on is just you're just sort of on top like i would try to keep maintain
your balance
uh...
uh... the whole family dashes away at this point
uh... uh...
uh... what do you guys want to do 'cause it's just a turn to a fight
or you guys can or you guys can dash away
uh... you don't want the smoke and i just walked away
very slowly
you guys are uh... you as well if you more hours
now you're outside of of who did
uh... which is a major city in who becky stand
and uh...
you can see sort of an entrance in there
uh... off to the side you can walk through it
uh... into the city uh...
and you guys can head south now to meet up with charlie brown
uh...
and uh... uh... you do you walk down the way you need a picture of the brown you
see this uh...
yellow shirt wearing a bald older guy
uh... well my god this kid has leukemia
and uh... i'm gonna pray for you
and he says to you guys a
all high on
uh... one
you cut a hole in the box
he's just sort of staring at you blankly
your prayer goes very well with that religion check of twelve
uh... he might not have leukemia by the end of the session there's a good
chance
uh... and
charlie rex dear lord jesus please at this kid with only three years on his
head
please let him survive time i'm jumping is this is prayer like a bullet
uh...
he's a little he says uh...
one could hold the box i say yeah
to nothing wrong with me
that's basically close enough come on and and uh...
he'll let you guys into his home
and uh... he says thanks for coming by uh...
other snacks i got snacks if you guys want any you see these just like kicking
the ground and he keeps tripping
and charge into that
and charlie canary i got this football you can kick
all right i do love the idea of doing that
and he goes he runs over to try to keep the football
what do you do
i would have taken
only got his brain breaks
he called the toes on the ground smiling
uh... you see a note on his chest that says yeah there's tax of the fridge make
yourself at home
you guys can help in the basement if you need to have got a p_s_ three
i know that's an older system but you know it does me all right so hopefully
you guys can enjoy it did not great i got kingdom hearts two point five remix
I uh, I shove Chris Pratt out of the way and take the uh, the disc for Dead or Alive Beach Volleyball
that I always have on me at any given time and I am trying to shove it into the PS3 to make it work
even though it's an original Xbox game. Yeah, what do the rest of you guys do? You guys gonna, so so
here's what's happening now. You're now in the Charlie Brown safe house, you're safe for now.
you go to the bar now to meet with uh...
rudolph
quote-unquote the contact
uh... you can also
that's around who did that you can do whatever
but uh...
uh...
near in the trial about safe house uh... so long
i
i take out my motorola razor and i press the pound button but upon
closer inspection to start david
yeah
I make a quick phone call and then the Xbox disc starts working on the PS3.
And then we start playing Dead or Alive.
Amazing, yeah.
Yeah.
So yeah, you guys are playing PS3, you're hanging out.
Time is approaching to meet up with the informant in the bar, in the Jollibee's Bar and Grill.
so if you guys wanna go over there or you can try to revive charlie brown who's
now passed out on the ground from the extent of the ticket ball
i pull i pull out a thing of uh... smelling salts for my carpenter pants
pocket
and uh...
i'd be happy to have you
i thought the thing is spelling salts in his in his nose
in he
throws up the a throws up all over you and like uh... just just as i'm so sorry
i've never got never came to my foot has never felt anything like that
before
uh... this sucks
the i'd start
wiping the the vomit off of the uh... chris bradt and i start to smear it on
myself to use for camouflage in case
what do you do it
it's called camouflage
you should learn a thing or two about war soldier it would serve you well
we've i've fought so many wars with you what are you talking about
policy
you have a local here deep in the gestures over the to uh...
to serve the land
and he says that the d_u_ in afghani
uh... home
and uh... they shot that is a
now i'm not gonna you know i mean
the what do you have to say
he says some of the unperfect afghani and
k_-pasa
yeah
and i don't know what this is a little deceptive
was saying
world six per year except
yet
he had a tribal issues like
how they must be uh...
that just let must be a different dialect he's like a little confused
when you are you you keep
talking to me like this i will uh... kill you
but i don't know how you can from uh... if she's in the stand
where are you from? you foolish dog
i'm from hubekistan which is uh...
use your teeth
to make
something made out of teeth like a knife
or something like that
well that sounds
bright intimidating enough for me to just back off this line of questioning
good that's what i was going for
now uh...
i have a uh...
information for you guys about a where the jolly be bar grill is and uh...
just to meet the rudolph uh...
your form it there now i i i if anybody ask you know i'm just a civilian so
i was gonna hang out here and i don't know anything that's going on in
and uh... you know i try to stay clear of anything the u_s_ has been doing here
which god bless and you know we love every second of them being here
but uh... uh... you guys uh...
guys do what you gotta do alright uh... if you need any place to stay you got
you got
got all charlie browns and he tries to kick the air again the falls
andy gets back up all well i guess
guess it only happens once every once in a while
in this foolish child
the sanctics
and uh... yeah you guys can head over to the johnny barbara's wife because uh...
i've been like fifteen minutes making fun of him for being bald
yeah
yeah and you guys go to the uh... the bar
and the jolly be boring grill and who did that after uh... i guess playing some
dinner alive and uh...
having a uh... the stilted conversation with charlie brown
and uh... you the bars packed tonight
uh... people are hanging out
hop around you're looking for a root off
your contact
uh... so uh... there's a lot more or perception checks if you guys can notice
him
All right, yeah, right. That's good enough. Yeah, you guys all kind of I mean not not as much a
car gone
But you know, you're I see guys you guys kind of figure out like you kind of see in the bag
I got I got all shit. I got a deception and perception confusing. But that's fine
We'll take the crit because the crit is the crit, you know, we're just adding in different numbers to it
So you do have to deceive somebody? Yes. Yeah, you know what I like
Yeah, so you have to you you did spot him perfectly and it is this guy just like a regular
Joey looking guy with a just glowing red nose that he claims is rosacea, but
And so you see that but you have to lie to everyone else about whether or not you've seen it or not. I
Don't see anything
Believe you I believe you
And you see the Rudolph guy he sort of notices you guys
there you're in your disguises, which is all just Groucho Marx glasses and
So it's like five guys like that and you he sort of waves you over
He says yeah, come on sit down sit down. I got that. How you guys doing? Do you want a drink or something? Yes
Okay, you order something from the waiter comes over and you order some couple of drinks. What do you guys want?
Shit okay
Okay, we got two shits. What else you guys I don't wait. No, I don't want shit
You're going to make me drink ish alone
No, you want that I was going off of you
Three shits
What do you want?
Could I have a control with one big square ice cube in it, please?
Yeah
He sort of tries to relay that to the waiter and the waiter
Sort of like says something back to him shakes his head and he says um, they only have cylinder ice cubes
You know that kind it is so fucked up what the Taliban did to you guys
I go up to the waiter and I grab him by the shoulders and I say
Give me whiskey and then I get really close to my say a lot of whiskey
And I still I'm still covered in vomit and
So he smells me yeah, he's shaking in his boots now and he started in the huds vigorously
Can I get a whole bottle
Okay, so now we're getting three shits and one one who's oh
All right. The shits are for Zohan. I want who's oh
So on you want three shits? I
guess
And you I
Would like one room temperature Modelo
Wait, hold on he can't drink that that's her
It's it's liquor is is Harambe beers fine. I think
The waiter pulls that out of his pocket he just puts under the table
And he goes back to get the other drinks and Rudolph sort of looks at you guys he says
Hey, so glad you guys talked to me. I'm really risking my neck here
I've been working for the Grinch for some time, but I want out. He's a mean son of a bitch
You've been working for the Grinch. No, that's the whole
This guy's deal good reason why I shouldn't kill your ass right now guys
briefed this is a double agent in our midst
I thought who is it you?
Hold on which one of us is the double agent?
All right, all of you all of you it's me
Oh what?
I trusted you
You shouldn't have
No wonder we couldn't tell what race you were
I'm, so sneaky
uh... kids all the world route three of you will still because you're just
yelling at this point of the picture
all-knowing
but i don't know
uh...
cargo what are you doing with that credit
nobody else has to worry more
uh... i'm sorry stand on the bar
the and i go
muslims
have been prosecuted
beginning
of fucking time
did you know
that the word muslim
comes from the
uh... roman word
for bundle of sticks
the roman empire
they used to light them on fire
and now certain people
act like
they're lesser than
because they don't know how to make square ice cubes well yeah have you thought that
during the siege of baghdad
when Genghis Khan was doing all that
he destroyed their sides books told them how to do that
no you fucking did it
you see like
in one guy's like
yeah
and uh... uh... while you're getting that speech you see a couple other folks
start turning the face you one of them is a giant snowman
and he looks at uh... the people sitting by the table and rudolph is like
fuck fuck fuck fuck and he holds up his
puts up his collar
and uh... the snowman guys like
I'll recognize you folks.
Where'd you say you're from? Where you from?
Don't worry guys.
I got this one.
I say that really loud in front of him.
Yeah.
Yeah, of course.
Greetings.
You don't know my name,
but you definitely don't know my story.
I come go like yeah, I come from the land where they invented
Christmas Michigan's Upper Peninsula.
(laughing)
- All right.
- I was born in a hobby lobby.
I was born amidst the mail mail cables,
the Christmas lights, the cutouts of snowflakes
and things of that nature.
I was born looking forward to December 25th every year.
I may be a man with two legs,
third leg some would say, just kidding.
(laughing)
And a lot of experience.
I've seen the life leave the eyes of others.
I've seen life be put into a baby's eyes
when he is born from his mother.
- You see the snowman's bobbing his head too
while you keep going, yeah.
- Start snapping.
- But even though I am in your country
in an invasory type deployment,
I respect the desire for Christmas as it is a part of me, as it is a part of you.
Just like a carrot is put on your nose, it doesn't make you smell any less.
Just 'cause I'm not made of snow doesn't mean I don't drink the nog.
So let's forget the stuff I was yelling, and I'll buy what you're having for myself.
you know what?
Clark got Felix Roll persuasion with advantage.
That's such a fashion speech.
Let's see if you can calm this guy down.
Okay, you have--
- Yes!
- Yeah, thank God, yeah, that's not bad.
Yeah, snowman, Frosty the snowman, some would say, goes,
- You know what?
I don't know what the fuck Michigan is, but you're all right.
(laughing)
- I think you're, you're, you're just,
I just met you, I can tell you're a real fucking dude
and one of the realest fucking people I've ever met
and you will be one of my best friends.
- Brother, you know what I try?
I try every fucking day I get up in the morning.
It's cold out, I'm cold inside and out,
but you know what?
I got a lot of love and I see a lot of love in you.
You know, as far as the stuff about my carrot nose,
that's fine.
I just got that.
it
i don't know that was uh... racially changed remark now and i know what you
know what it's your new year man and you you
you'd book
you quite this week talker
story worry about it
i can uh... i i i don't mind one bit
and uh... the frosty sort of dislike shuffles away
and uh... you see rudolph is a
and uh... the waiter comes over brings you guys your drinks
and the real dislike
I just want to make sure you guys understand what's happening because there seemed to be a lot of confusion before
So I
was was was
Previously so not currently and currently
Because you haven't yelled yet, but the other ones do so I just okay. What do you mean the other ones?
What do you mean by you guys
Don't do this. I will just hand you a USB with the information if this continues
Is that what you want? I have one question
Okay, where is USB?
He's just like stares blankly his eyes are like rolling in the back
Yeah, you you go Slavia that's
the
So I'm gonna give you guys the blueprints and he just slides over the
blueprints to the Bahambug fortress and you guys look at them and you see that
he starts pointing out really I'm sorry I couldn't do anything about it it really
It was like there's about there's a five minute stretch during Felix's speech where I was like, when's it gonna come?
And he says so there's three entrances, okay
There's the the chimney. Okay, that's gonna get you into the ventilation system
Not many people know that but I know a way to get up there
Then there's a front entrance. I don't recommend it unless you want to face the eat miser and snow miser themselves
That's gonna be tough
The other way around this is to go through you have to go through frosty's den
So that guy who just talked to you frosty the snowman
He's a drug kingpin around here works with the Grinch you can go through his den. It's around back
It'll lead you right into tunnels or get you into the bah humbug area
But you're gonna have to again go through a whole drug den you could do it sneakily you could fight your way through it
But again, don't recommend recommend the chimney, but if you fuck that up keep in mind, you'll be surrounded
You guys played Metal Gear Solid
Here
I'm I grew up in a tent you household
The way the Metal Gear Solid treats military service is frankly disgusting to me. It's one of the worst things ever
It's disgusting the way they try to you know, they they try to complicate it. It's horrible
Can you repeat all that don't do this a trick out of character
So look I leave this in your capable hands now I gotta go figure out why my nose is glowing
fucking ridiculous and
He sort of puts up his coat again. He says hasta luego and
He walks out of the bar
So you guys have these blueprints in front of you three separate strategies to break in to the bah humbug fortress
You can certainly split your teams up
and try to do a multi
Approach or you can just work all together. But yeah, you have the chimney which leads to the air vents
Give the front door which is sort of a guns blazing approach
Many of the den which is a sneaky approach but requires some complicated
Making sure you can get into the drug den making sure you can work your way through it may lead to a shootout
But those are your three approaches
So I feel like I feel like Felix already sweet-talked this this snowman. Yeah, so well, why not capitalize on that?
Yeah, yeah, I think I could probably
Like extract some concessionaries out of him again
Yeah in a verbal entanglement
Yeah, that's makes sense to me. So he's he's he's still at the bar.
So you can still talk to him for sure there.
He's got like his crew around him.
There are other there who's and other Christmas creatures and
critters that just are sort of like buzzing about him.
So yeah, do you want to do I like I push Clark on towards him like
Like a timid boy approaching his crush.
Yeah.
Come on, go talk to him.
Alright, alright.
Alright.
So, how's the night treating you?
Ah, the tough guy himself, Mr. Sweet Talk.
Well, you know, it's going alright.
Just here with my crew, sipping on some soju.
just enjoying the cool Hubekistan air. Oh, Hubekistan. I mean.
Someone's had a lot of sake.
Just kidding. Hey, that's a good one. Thank you. So, look man, we're thinking about
taking this party back to my den keep it going get some girls there maybe some
uh maybe some Cindy Lou's if you know what I mean all grown up wink adult
women is what I mean that's my favorite type of woman Cameron can we keep that in
yeah honestly like there's nothing that like puts me into the Christmas spirit
like some tuna around my thing. Hey I know what that is. Yeah. I got a carrot down
there too you know what I mean? Yeah absolutely. It's not a carrot it's it's
more snow but you know they don't mind. Yo, ask if your boys can come.
Yeah can you like uh can you like accommodate a crew of friends?
is
all right
there
- That happens to Clargon a lot.
(laughing)
- I threw a flashbang under the table,
realized what I did and just.
(laughing)
So this whole time I haven't been able to see anything
that's been going on.
(laughing)
- That happens every single time Clargon talks
for more than two minutes.
(laughing)
Someone around him throws a flashbang at him.
- And Frosty sort of looks over your crew,
sort of sees this motley group of everyone wearing
Groucho Marx glasses.
And he says, you know what?
The more the merrier.
Come on, let's head over there.
And yeah, so for you and Frosty,
you go with the crew outside of the Jollibee's Bar and Grill,
go around the corner a little bit,
and you see there's a door.
You see there's a guy in front of it
with his hands over his crotch.
And he says, Frosty, you hear Frosty say,
"Ding, fries are done."
And you hear the guard go, "I've got to run."
and he's moved out of the way
and uh... you guys walk into this like
fast drugged and whether making them
heroin
and uh... there are
just tons of heroin everywhere and uh...
you see christmas decorations you see mistletoe is up
uh... you see reese and and all these things and uh... the couple men or is
too
and uh...
i_c_a_a_ the sort of lounge area in the middle
it's sort of like a judge you jacked up version of the uh... alfred malina
uh... house
in uh... boogie nights
and uh... uh... you see some uh... girls dancing on polls
uh... some some fine honeys
and uh... you see frosty say welcome to the pad
and uh... he sits you down and what you guys will remember from the uh...
blueprint
is that there's a doorway in the back
uh... has a code on it
uh... which you guys know the code it's one two three four
And if you go to that door and you type in the code it's going to get you into the grinch's
Uh, it's gonna get you down a ton a bunch of tunnels
That's gonna lead into the baham bug fortress right now
So that information you guys know, but right now you're just sitting down with the crew. He's bringing bacardi out. Um, uh, it's like a club night
Uh, uh, you hear uh, the music playing. It's great
I would like to fall in love with the who woman
okay you don't have to roll for that even you know okay cool i fall in love
okay yeah you fall in love with one of the strippers um
and uh uh what do you say to to to her
i listen i i've killed about a thousand thousand thousand people
she starts going to the other pole
I do yeah, I just go to the next stripper
I'm just gonna keep doing this
To every every single woman in the in the room. Yeah, I should mention there's not just like bacardi out
There's like like crudités and shit like, you know, it's like a pimped out pad
There's people like packing, you know packing drugs like sending out runners and shit, but also like bringing in good fucking food
uh... you know if you got a few guys have ever idolized people
uh... like that but like i'd hit
and that's what i'm picturing in my head because i start ice nor the line of
heroin
but he had a yeah but i think it's to he
the
world constitution saving their
where's constitution
you see a little bit
well it's not so not
you know
algae mama
flag
yeah yeah uh... process that
me heroin is to heroin
uh... yeah you feel a little woozy but you're okay you're saying that you to
lay just a close one
uh... caleb pits but you're okay i could have overdosed my first time
you could have uh... yeah i mean not overdose you just could have uh... dealt
with some of the adverse effects of the what adverse effects
well sorry never mind there when you're right stupid uh... but uh... to get a
good time
yeah
yeah i have it's been a family uh... yeah
uh... i was there as you guys we as one do there's like there's like uh...
there's also like uh... in old pinball machine that's like a
in all the home cool world themed pinball machine
in there as well
party thrown a grenade
you throw a grenade again
reflect big for twenty david
the or twenty
yes twenty-two hit okay yeah uh...
did you have
okay
couple things i guess i have to resolve now
god damn it
alone
grenades did you hear that
i think i did you know that it
a bandolier of just grenades
i'd i'd tell you what i was making the character and i was thinking like
or whatever i get patrick is going to something stupid but
so what i just think it would be a like to have a map grenades like i was like
whatever
you know what you're wrong to find that i was wrong again so
uh...
a are you doing this on purpose you are or is it on accident be it's it could be
a it's an accident every time i'm trying to i'm trying to white
uh...
whatever and whatever crew to take a look at it
i think that i'm trying to get off my shirt and i hit my bandolier and the
great falls off
here's the thing
and i thought it every time
if you do this it's a pretty good move
to say oops sorry
and then run to the back
so i don't know if you're trying to do that
or if anybody else is picking up a really strong feeling he was a baby i'm
just doing maybe i'm just doing some jackie chan drunken kung fu stuff
i think that's your idea this year that that movie
yet he was
jackie chan is a good thing
and jackie chan with a grenade i'm shaking in my boots that's the scariest
thing i have a have you seen that video uh... where they're trying to prove that
jar jar binks is a sith lord and he's jackie chan's drunken kung fu moves and
that's not going to be a drunken master
uh... techniques
as an example it's uh... jar jar binks is i like that that's your reference for
for
jackie chan's drug master is not the movie itself but when they showed it in
a jar jar binks
it's not a good
and i think it humbles me more is when i realize that patrick and i have this
star wars overlap
jacksepticeye
no i know i know pat just knows this shit
i'm like yeah i've seen that video ok so here's what's gonna happen
if you guys want to take this opportunity
you can all make uh... i hit a grenade off my bandolier and i say misa so
so
the pin of this blinding grenade and it blinds you and Frosty's like "Oh God!" and the strippers
are like "Ahh!" and then like, like everybody in the fucking drug debt is like freaking out.
And so you guys have this opportunity so you're, if you're gonna dash I'm gonna roll to see
if they notice you.
They have disadvantage so I'm gonna roll twice.
Let's see what they do, how they do.
Oh man.
Yeah, okay.
And do you guys dash for the door?
guys - for the door and you guys - for the door and Frosty's like wait where's
my new best friend where's I didn't even get your name and he's just sort of like
closing his eyes looking for our God and and you guys are running for the door
hurt Thomas put on his sunglasses.
I'm gonna take a picture of that so we can post it with the episode later.
Oh done yeah. Dude, Raising Cane's and Sunny's inside.
Oh my, Thomas is living the dream right now. Look at this dude.
Oh look at that. That kind of cup is illegal in New York City.
yeah so we're gonna get interrogated just for being a call to god and uh...
yeah
all right
uh... we're escaping
yet he dashed through the door and they don't notice you guys you guys go in
frosty's like my new best friend where to go
all god
and he slowly site returns to him and he's like off strip is a sweet
it's been guys are going to be no
and uh... you guys can make your way through the tunnels
uh... you see their line with like uh... christmas decorations and ornaments
and uh... as you make it it's almost you get to you
looks like
a little great above you
in here like footsteps and shit and uh...
one movement above you
uh... i told i guess he's so bad you guys
the actual
and
uh...
sorry i thought it was all the study aid
it's a pretty good to say something is nobody can be a little bit and can tell
you know you can't really do that
and i think that
doesn't
it doesn't work that way that i thought that's where they're making each other
life
uh... so so the explode so so patrick you see
he's clear-eyed
uh... yeah you see a year so we go what was that
so i'd like to hear from over there
and uh... kathleen c_e_o_
so i don't know
you see someone with that the great
and it's a who would like for use and uh...
yeah uh... welfare initiative guys
far-cracked rama
uh...
uh... so so yeah
you guys uh... jump up to the vent and you guys try your weapons
you see a few hugh who's in front of you you also see some elves on the shelves
and they are uh... uh... they go
this is the turn to face you guys
and their eyes are charging up with lasers
uh... but yeah first before any of that happens
uh...
uh... you go uh... felix uh... it's actually your turn
alright so clark on yes so you have elves on the shelves
like three three of them around you up top
and in front of you you have like four who's
uh... uh... who are uh... aiming their guns at you
i think it's now it's time for the bolt action rifle
do it
uh... okay i'd like to say something before i uh...
take out this giant piece of shit that everyone on the squad hates
your whole life
people asked who
cindy who?
they're about to ask who were you
that you know
you see like one of those like
uh... that's what i thought and thought
all right uh... now i'm enrolled bolt
all of that yeah let's go
the overall for damage
yeah
yes you you tear through of one of them
you just you just say this shit and then he's like
and it's like explodes his head
it
and uh... yeah you're yet you know it's been around reloading but uh... worth it
but
and
keep keep doing i'm reloading
but you know
and uh... yet now it is a
now it's uh... uh... chris chris pratt it's your turn you've photos thomas
mister
uh... all she you're right thank you
uh... i got out the ends of that's insane but patrick did not have a
them or
but had on the malls
and we're facing here
afghanistan you're now facing three who's
you have a couple of uh... elves on the shelves
a got three who's not a single correct
to give. That's what I'm saying.
So, uh, I'm pulling the shelf right?
Let's split up with that choppa and let the shotty bang.
Amen, brother.
Uh, well, I better hit, I better go on roll 20 and actually do the attack.
Sorry, I've fallen asleep probably 45 times.
Yeah, your character is just like T-posing whenever you're AFK.
Yeah, I'm just like, "Oh, I'm gonna roll 20."
I'm like, "Oh, I'm gonna roll 20."
T-Posing whenever you're AFK like it's just like yeah, you keep switching between poses
And it gets to the ready pose. Okay. Yeah damage. Yeah roll for damage for that. Nice
Yeah, so you you pretty severely injure one of them. You just like you're like nodding off and the bullets just like
down its body and
Yeah, you have another attack - so you can do that again if you want
So I can just do that again, right? Yeah
Okay, it does not hit this time this time
You're like you like fall asleep and you kind of like shoot them down
I empty like a full clip and everyone hits the next one
Drop it on the ground. I'm like, yeah, so what?
Okay, yeah, so one of them is smarting pretty bad
But but the three of them still are up and now now it's your turn Chris. You're up
All right
the
and
Tommy Boy Gun.
Oh yeah.
Oh ho ho ho ho ho!
25!
Oh wow!
Wow!
You got a fucking kill!
Yeah.
Alright, roll for damage.
I, I just start spraying that shit.
11-8 is the, 11 plus 8 is the piercing.
Jesus Christ.
Okay, yeah, so you do, so describe your kill on two of them.
You fucking just spray around and just fucking body two of them with the Tommy Guns.
blinded from the flashbang. So I'm standing there with the gun just like...
Yeah and two of them are like "I've never seen that technique before!"
We can't analyze this! Yeah, he just tear through them. And I rolled something behind the
scenes and you hear some footsteps coming towards you guys and it's now
their turn and you see uh... put your footsteps of any here
and then you look up you see the heat miser
lighting up his hair on fire using as a jet pack flying at you guys feet first
and all of you to all dexterity saving throws she because he's coming at you
and you hear him say you know who signs up pictures fuck with the great
you get that
uh... way i just wrote this thirty minutes thirty saving
although attended
and still
a very green twenty-two i guess sixteen okay
uh... we have
or i'm ron
uh...
so that he might have blasted and like
all of you car got especially you just like
how do you dot just you got credit on that scene
so it's not that
i uh... so i cross my arms
like in and make i would do
and uh... i'd just see a bunch of alliance will show around me like a
Very fast. Mm-hmm. And then I jump up in like a jackknife position and do several spins
You're just reloading your bolt-action right
Exactly, yeah
Zohan this one gets the best of you though
You take eight damage as this heat miser
fucking flames you by like flying past you and he's charging up his
Charging up his hair and yeah, and
But now he's a positioned himself behind you to attack again and the other who's trying to attack you
but they do just shoot fucking miss and he also on the shelf though do charge at you guys and
They they attack you
Patrick because they saw you just fucking tear through two of them. I got a 16
No, this is a different different role. There's a different role. Okay, and
They they managed to get seven health on you. Like they just like fucking their elves on the shelves eyes go
And they shoot lasers at you
And they get you get seven damage on you and their attack. But um
But yeah
now you're back on the top of the order and the heat miser sort of like
Like his foot is like digging and he's like putting his hands on his head
It's like he's making horns and he's like he's like ready to get you but it's your turn Clark on
uh... you guys spend this round reloading the bold action where we had a good
turns
ocean i'm sorry i fucked up my bad uh...
we're gonna get a little bit
yet right turn
you did you know i have an amazing i'd just before i'm sorry for that up
uh... it's your turn actually uh... as though on or no wait uh... structure
yes it's your turn toms as crutchland
outside my second
i'm sorry i'm not a lot of it
you take the main this world is such a you need to succeed in terms of the
people's trick of mine
it's your turn though cameron uh... okay
there else on the shelf left right yeah there's still three left in the in the
shelf area
so i say i say
you've so you've heard of elf on the shelf
and i think of my machete and i throw my machete at them and i say
now check out machete on alfano shelf
no
payroll that
yet it's role for damage
okay yeah
you just like
you dislike say all that we are chipped in the machete dislike
completely like pierces through one of the elvis blue
reduces powers down
it's just dead
uh...
uh... yeah you can also do another machete attack to if you want to yeah i'm
doing it
i'm going for a status keeping it
and yet it's wrong for damage
well yet you're like halfway through saying it and let me just throw it again
and it just
bull bliterates another alf on the shelf
and now uh... it's dead
and uh... you know it's your turn so hot
okay so
it's just the heat miser
and they'll phone and
anymore off on the shelves there's one more out on the shelf and they're still
to
- One other who.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah, that hits.
- Easy.
- Dude, oh my god.
- Yeah, describe your kill.
You're gonna obliterate this guy.
You guys are trained warriors.
- We're so cool.
- It's so easy for you.
- He gets sliced in half.
(laughing)
- That's awesome, man.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- It's awesome.
- Wow.
- Yeah, that is really cool.
actually
woah
yeah you're just saying that as it slices in half
wow that is really cool
wow i've never seen that before
yeah who's just screaming in agony
wow
really cool
and then
AHHHHH
and he just dies
he just lies there
pool of blood around him
and uh yeah you get another attack too if you want to
um
well i can only
I can't you can I use the ninja star of David twice? Yes, you can you can use it again. Yeah, you miss this time
You just oh fuck you just throw it like I'm way too high the elephant. I was
His laughs at you I hate being mocked
And yeah now is your turn again Clark on
So you all right? He miser behind you one elf on the shelf left in front of you above on the shelf
All right, because I think everyone is just a character in the movie about my life, instead of helping everybody out by just like, you know, rolling for my scar or even my riot shield, I decide I got to keep reloading.
Right.
Yeah, you spend your turn reloading.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
And I'd like to say to him, you're so fucking lucky that this gun takes so long to reload.
But it was actually given to me by my grandfather, Clargon Sr. III.
Tell me about that!
Well, so the thing is, he fought on both sides of World War II.
He lived a very storied life.
I mean, he actually started out on the allies, but, uh, right.
Sure.
Yeah. He actually like, so what happened was that he was part of the secret mission where he had to
look like he was, uh, he was, uh, selling Volkswagen parts to Americans when there was an
embargo, but it was actually like, he was trying to catch other guys who did that, but then they
just acted like, you know, he wasn't doing that. And so he had no choice. You're just switch sides.
You're just saying all this shit and just reloading your gun.
Yeah.
They really forced his hand and...
See the heatvisor has sat down, he's crossed his legs, he's just sort of listening.
Yeah, he actually like, you know, he had PTSD his entire life after that from when he did
fall out of the guard tower.
Clarkon, you said PTSD right.
I mean, QRT, QTBT from when he fell out of the guard tower.
are
it's not your turn afghanistan but here it is that after clark i don't want to
that speech three ladies can
you know he's my gun
and uh...
actually i think on this and i use my uh... afghani
martial arts
and they do it do it
uh... on this one
i'm going to be
i'm going to be attacking
uh...
one of the
you know who were up against we both know
I don't have to say
The one that's closest to me
Wrote this thing patches shouldn't you fucking know I feel like such a fucking dick. What's wrong? Sorry?
Honestly the heat miser that's who you're going after
You know and I should have known um and um I'm gonna do really crazy
It's gonna be it's gonna hit around the hip area cuz designed for kicking a dog
but it's
Kick and I'm gonna say
You want to get slick? It's time for a kick
Boom yeah, and then I don't see
Well, yeah you missed him
You just sort of do some sweet kicks, but they just like go over the heat miser's head who's like he's like four and a half
feet tall
Your sweet kicks are too sweet. We have another attack with the Afghan martial arts. Well, I'm gonna do it again
The he might was like, haha. I am too hot to handle. That's my character and
Yeah. Oh, yeah, you just kick in the same exact spot just over his head
it first you don't succeed
second time also no
and
and i think profound
the
and now it is your turn uh...
uh... chris pratt
right on the throat the uh...
malta slushy adam
that is the advisor
yet twenty one with uh... eleven damage
yeah uh... yet you you do that and that
seems to do some extra damage to the seat miser for some reason
uh... when you throw them all don't know why
it does that cold damage
the he might as well
how
which might be
you hurt my heat
it's a yeah
i don't know what you try to tell you if you're the bad guy right now i'm just
trying to tell you that by he's been hurt
all right cool i hope you don't do things like that again
because that would hurt my heat
i might
that i mize ok and uh... he just takes a little extra damage
he looks pretty bad but he's still standing
uh... and now it's his turn
and uh... he uh... takes out a whistle
and he blows it and it makes a tone only people who are really really cold can
hear
and you see uh... sliding in is the cold mizer
who i definitely don't know what he sounds like but i assume it's like
and the crowd myself name is the snow mystery
is it the snow mystery of snow mystery now you know i'm not go off i guess
yeah i will i will go off alright and the snow mystery
and the snow mystery i mean and he doesn't attack on all of you
and ocean does it
uh... i say i say i see them both and i think for a minute
met that they might be twins and i get a huge correction
like put that away no
not please put it away
it i am wearing pants
i can see
okay sorry i did no but there for the impromptu
you have a very good
uh... for long
accuracy to hook it up
not again caleb
and uh... you have uh...
thomas
and
you bothering me
and that i was using the over mid sleep cycle during the episode that i think
for ninety second intervals and then we can stop with the witnesses naked
thomas is doing it in their smithson's that yeah
the money we need
yet
for damage and so does uh...
uh...
chris pratt and uh...
uh... working and soldiers wrath and therefore did it really here
there is a lot of now thomas so
and i don't know what to do about that
okay
you being a speech and approved it could be could give him disadvantage later
you know you can't keep thomas disadvantage if you put me off
yeah i've got a disadvantage for you right here no film
all
it's not a very good god i was another millie i think i did it's kind of
ridiculous now i'm taking it out
you know just as i have feelings to man and i was a of all of the men's pin
what's up in a busy weekend
yeah i'm sorry for it
overstepped my boundaries is
now has a friend in this
i love her
no and
well you know and and you know
we can talk about that definitely off mike just yet
the second party i'm still not out to a lot of people death
but the uh... as a friend and great and and it's okay
uh... you know
you do take for damage to cook the snow miser does he with a little blizzard
attack i know and they thought you can answer your personal
and uh...
yet
getting all kinds of magic
at the screen
and uh...
yeah
uh... but now uh...
uh... they often the shelf attacks he misses you guys so like you just like
is a great
and he shoots the ceiling
he's a several days completely fucking missed
and now uh... it is your turn
uh... soldiers wrath
or really
okay uh... i'm just gonna time to take out
destiny's fate
and i'm a star shooting
the heat miser in the uh... snow miser right next to each other
so they have to roll uh... uh... decks even through yeah they take uh...
sixteen damage the heat miser
uh... dies explain how you kill the heat miser while the snow miser is taking damage
let's go
uh...
i
i shoot him with the gun and it goes
all the bullets go into him and he goes
spins around and disappears yeah he just poofs
away motorboating the air
and uh... the snow myers like
i think it's a snow myers who does that actually know that i think about it
patrick in you
to firmness
which one of them goes but i'm going to spend around a circle like this and my
snow mystery okay so the yeah i don't know if it was a dozen to you
yes no mystery my dad is not his normal it
yes she shits like you know
he smells awful now
i mean you bet you
better believe i'm rubbing that off
her paper can watch
yeah and uh... the snow myseries like my brother no dies normally
and uh... but he's also taking a shit ton of damage
uh... and now it is uh... your turn so on
uh...
okay
uh... it's not cool
yeah
uh... first i stand over the heat miser
his dead body like uh... and like l_a_ war like pick up his his arms and his
head
yeah he died normally
and then i go and i i'm gonna do i'm gonna do krav maga
yeah on my on my guy the snow miser roll for damage
i'm gonna fuck
i'm gonna fuck him
uh... fourteen dude
okay yeah
uh... describe your kill cause he already took a shit ton of damage from cameron
I, uh, I do a, a, a, like a, whatever, like how double or like hexa, but for 10 times
backflip.
Yeah.
And then I, and then I put both of my feet completely in his eye sockets.
No, just like the movie.
He's so good.
He's already, he can't say it.
He's dead.
He died immediately.
My bad.
He died.
I'm really sorry.
Take it back.
I'm sorry.
That didn't happen.
And then I use his uses buddy whispers it he whispers. No, he's you can't you don't whisper when you die
You can't say anything in any times you can know that's not true. My uncle whispered when he died
He said you could have my
Dead another for me. Yeah, he dies and tape goes over his mouth as he's dying
Their word just die
And yeah, I killed him. Yeah, and the elf on the shelf just like self-excel self self fucking explode he sells explode
Yeah, he spontaneously explodes and yeah, you guys have a clear path now to get to the Grinch who is
sprinting down the
uh...
he's in his lair any said he's setting up his cameras
for a story of a live stream of him fucking the presence
and you guys go in there he has busted
you see the great you see all the presence
uh... lined up in the off covered in lube
in the graces but naked you see the three centers normal black and jewish all
tied up
and gagged
and the graces
i see you finally all arrived
What are you gonna do?
Are you gonna kill me?
What?
Hey!
You're a bunch of wuys.
You're gonna be one of the only people
whose funeral was on Christmas.
Okay.
Anybody else got anything
fuckin' mean to say?
I have one question.
Where is Grinch?
We are weird.
Are you where are you hiding him?
Are you are you a bit slow?
Because I just please there is no way listen.
There's no way this beautiful woman has anything to do.
Oh, okay.
I see now.
I see what's going on.
I see what's going on here.
I'm the Grinch.
This is basically wait what I'll do for the boys.
No,
I'm wiping my tongue.
It's like the end of Ace Ventura.
And it's also not like that.
No, but it's the same exact.
Yeah, nevermind.
Patches, who's that behind you?
That's a ghost.
Is there someone behind me?
There was someone waving at you.
It's him. It's him.
The Grinch is here.
Oh my god, oh my god, she's like Psycho Mantis, he broke the fourth wall!
Holy shit!
That's incredible.
Oh my god, Patches, you really fucking immersed us in this game!
Okay, now he's telling me that he's gonna save a file of twisted metal, alright, so I'm gonna give it away.
I don't want to wish it into existence, but this would be the funniest time for Patches to get murdered.
the
that's what i'm thinking of
so you have a great is there he's all moved up and real fuck the president's
assailants are tied up
we got one of you
uh... boy
well
what i'm just sitting at large
uh...
i think that i have
i i think you know what i'm going to do
is my uh... bold action reloaded
all my god patrick is this all while all please wow
Double crit flashbang in the room.
I've never seen that before.
What the fuck?
You keep throwing grenades, you're gonna hit a double crit eventually.
Exactly.
Take a screenshot of it so I have this.
You know that was my plan this whole time.
That was amazing.
Jesus fucking Christ.
I accidentally drop a grenade on the ground again.
I'm swinging my arms like Kermit when he's excited, you know, he's like "Yay!"
I was doing that because I see the Grinch, but I'm scared so I'm doing that and one of them just falls off the bandolier for a double crit.
You are all blind.
[laughter]
Everybody in the room though?
Everybody is blind. The Grinch is blind right now.
The Santas are blind.
Uh, everybody's blind right now.
For how long?
I fart really loud.
[laughter]
I- I take credit for it.
That was me.
Fuck, I can't see.
And you see the timer is going down for the stream is gonna start
No, I can't fuck the presence if I can't see them and you see the tires going down
It's about to be Christmas Day when he's gonna fuck the presents
Take somebody please point me to where the presents are so I can fuck them. I
Say, okay. I start guiding him towards the Zohan
Popping my lips
*laughter*
This doesn't feel like a present while while he's doing that. I'm just kind of like feeling around the room. Yeah
Which Santa is this I'm certainly not anything I shouldn't be
Okay, yeah again boss in your court with that one
one
and
okay
that's true yeah you have not skills for sure that's true it's just it's the it's
a matter of uh... me on doing his belt or me and doing his uh... yeah i love that
yes that's what's happening
role of all the twenty just straighty twenty okay
above a ten it's israel below ten it's israel
okay yeah you just barely you're like and is hovering around the place my
mouth is on the book
But your hand is untying the rope?
Yeah.
I don't know how I'm doing without it!
Meanwhile, the, uh, Kargon, Kargon, what are you, Kargon and Vlad, what are you guys doing in this, you're, you can't see, the Grinch is about to kiss Zohan.
What are you guys doing right now?
Oh, he's not gonna kiss him.
I'm gonna try to use mental visualization techniques to aim my bolt action at the Grinch.
Okay, uh, roll an attack roll with disadvantage. Let's see how you do.
Okay, and then we'll resolve that depending on the result. All right
You just hit it you'll just take the lower number, okay. All right, so Thomas
Afghanistan's Vladimir
What are you doing doing this time you just feeling around for shit what's going on? Yeah, I
I think I'm sitting in Santa's lap because I like sort of felt around and stuff,
but I've just been sitting in like a regular chair for like five minutes.
And I'm just like talking to just a chair. I think he just has like really toned thighs or something.
The chair is like, yeah, what else do you want for Christmas?
I was like a magic chair.
He sure is.
Well, that's just too much.
that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's
story keep you guys focus on the narrative or any of the stuff that's
going on and that's all I gotta work on the chair I'll work on the chair I'll
pull that back the chair is not magical okay keep me inside my house so what do
you do it with the bridge before Thomas kills me he I stick the like pointy part
of
is
dead grinch
and a bunch of presents
thomas talking to a chair
uh... clark on visual doing a visual part on shooting is done and it just
completely fucking missus to create should be
uh...
and uh... yeah what do you guys want to do with the body
this is a this is the end of the mission you guys killed the grinch with some
shy uh...
i instantly speak up for a big mass
the rich
was bad person
and he hurt this country and all the other countries in the world
but
we're no better than our adversaries
if we desecrate his corpse
I think we have to give the Grinch a Muslim sea burial
in accordance with his faith
or one of them
one of the faiths
I'm going to find the Grinch
I do
I will kill them
(laughter)
- I cut off the Grinch's like,
like mangled bloated ball sack
and I just wear it as a necklace to add to my trophies.
Cause I'm bad ass as hell.
- The gap in my tooth is stuck in between like that,
that thing in the belt buckle,
where it like connects to the it goes through the belt hole so i'm just kind of like me and
santa i'm like kind of waving my arms back like whoa i'm falling backwards and it's this cycle
where santa and i keep like doing cartwheels and then connected to his and i i walk up to the
present the presence the pile of presents the president president i walked up to the president
He's standing in the pile of presents.
And get this boys, I unzip my fly.
Oh no!
And I say into the camera, being Israeli is about more than having fun with your friends.
It's about more than using Reddit for pornography.
More than sounding like a French guy with a concussion.
More than visiting the dentist because there's no fluoride in the water in Israel.
It's about ruining Christmas.
Yeah, and you hear Marvin Gaye's "Let's Get It On" play and the screen fades to black
and the credits start rolling.
the
okay i mean
i'm in the hospital i've married i've married all three of the strippers
from the uh... there were exactly three yet there are three of them i married
all of them and
there
and
one of them is praise pregnant is giving birth the other two are just there with
me to support me
you i see my my beautiful
baby who
uh...
pop out
and i looked at him and i say
well
your you're pretty awesome i think i'm gonna name you blow toss piss and then
cryogenically freeze you until the year two thousand two hundred and forty
just you know it just for the record
yeah
alright that's all i needed
and i want to make sure everything to the same you thank you and i was worried we
wouldn't do that uh...
well i've got an idea we hold on to the top what's up uh... more i have uh...
i've book a yoda
and you know that i heard you know they live for nine hundred years so it is
think that the amount of time
you know we ought to fuck something at the end of the uh... you're a kid
but uh...
In accordance with his Muslim faith, we are fucking the corpse.
*laughter*
Let us never say that we've stooped to the low of America's enemies.
Yeah.
Perfect.
Yeah, and before- right before we fuck him, we say, "Hey, here's five pillars for you, you dead son of a bitch."
I, uh, I would like to say the traditional Muslim prayer during the sea burial.
Brooke Atatinoi, Kampenu, Mele Shalom.
You see his-
Happy Hanukkah.
His body touches the water and it bursts into flames.
Well, guess I was wrong about that one. He clearly wasn't Muslim.
It would have just sunk if he was Muslim.
Well, I mean, there were like, there's a one in five shot of me getting his religion right.
Like he could have been Hindu, he could have been Buddhist.
At least we tried though.
Great job boys. This is all after the credits. I'm Sergeant Jack Frost
wishing you all a happy happy holidays. Merry Christmas. Uh from from uh, uh, what's up Thomas?
What's up? I was gonna mention the other one but
Which one did you? Kwanzaa? No, that's not a big deal.
I was just thinking about it.
(laughing)
- The podcast about list, happy, have a good day.
God bless America, everyone.
- All right.
- All right, perfect.
- Perfect.
- Thank you guys, this was a lot of fun.
- My pleasure.
- You guys carry on.
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]