You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[LAUGHTER]
Ooh.
It's an especially haunted night here.
This is a--
What'd you get?
What'd you roll?
I got 18.
18.
Holy shit.
Wow.
OK, you do the first.
That is the oldest.
That is the oldest you will go.
Yep.
What?
No.
He said yep.
I'm hitting stop. No, I'm hitting stop.
You have to subtract 7 also.
Oh, true.
11.
You are a sick piece of shit.
Here, I'll roll a D50 million for my age.
That's the highest I'll go.
Let's see what's the highest you'll go, Pat.
It's a 20. It's actually a 20.
It's not an 18 again. It's a 20.
It's great to know that you'll go for any age under 20.
No, no.
That's 11.
That's canon.
d4 for you look at that I hate this so we put dice in front of podcasts about list
just to see what would fucking happen yeah mm-hmm we play see low real quick
we're trapped inside because of a scary storm yeah there is a scary I keep
getting an alert a storm that's making a scary noise how do you play ceilo you
You get three die, you roll them, but you can't roll...
Five, five, four.
So you would... I mean it's basically like Yahtzee, but with three dice.
So I would win.
Is there a three dice version of Yahtzee?
How would I have not won?
It's like a gambling thing that super old black guys play on a wall on the street.
Okay, hold on.
And it's really good. You bet singles.
Yeah.
Four, five, six is basically the best thing.
thing okay three three five that's that's gonna bits terrible you would if I were
you I'd reroll but you basically you reroll until you get something okay you
yeah do you lose money the whole time though you pretty much lose okay so it's
the best game ever you lose you lose one dollar every second six three five you
just keep rolling till you hit something and then you like a straight or like a
two of a kind or three of it was three of a kind one two one two three is the
worst it's basically automatic nothing.
No shit.
And you go around, everybody rolls a hand.
So like if I rolled a 1, 2, 3, he rolled a 3 of a kind.
Okay.
Like 3 3s, you rolled 3 4s, and Pat rolled 4, 5, 6, he would take everything.
What if I rolled like 10, 9, 100?
If you rolled 10, 9, 1, then you would probably win.
100, I got 3 2s and a 4.
Stop rolling things, none of these are hands.
Yeah, so what if I, okay if I roll these.
Those are 20s, that's different.
So I got a 9, a 9, and a 3.
What's that?
Like if you rolled that with a normal die, you'd probably win.
Okay so what about if I get a 14, 8, 13?
Is that...
Because that's 14 or 13 in a row.
Now you're playing Dungeons and Dragons.
So I would win.
You know what would be funny is to show up, see people playing CeeLo or whatever and show
up with like three 20-sided...
*laughter*
I believe these gold pieces are mine.
Man, I gotta get into...
Man, gambling has straight up ruined my brain, I think.
How? How? You have talked about
gambling has zero effect on you at all. I think you might be the most... you have the
most fragile brain of anybody I've ever known.
Oh, you've known me for what, like three years now? You don't fucking know that already?
Well, I did know that... yeah, I knew that.
Yeah, you fucking knew that.
yeah i'm not okay so just tell me how is it in minor inconvenience how is
gambling my whole life
broken your brain now I can't stop thinking
about diamonds and I can't stop thinking about
money that's like this the American way that's normal and I can't tell you about
you don't think about that normally
yeah go you don't you don't just sit around all day thing but diamonds money
and gold bars when you follow
oh my god I've been having dreams I did I did have a second slot stream
bars and sevens. What? What was it? Another dream about playing slots. What happened in
this one? I played slots. The same thing as the first one. Did you win? I don't know.
I just played. No, so this is what I'm saying is I think that the slot streams really reveal
what kind of psychological effect gambling is having on me because in my dream I can't
tell if I'm winning or losing money but I'm really happy because there's lots of noises
and flashing lights that are making me like smile.
- That's a true thought.
- And that's what's the fun part.
- It's a really, it's like a return to childhood, right?
- Yeah.
- It's like seeing your mother's legs
while you're crawling underneath the table.
It's looking at, hold on.
- What do you mean by that?
- What did you just say, Patches?
Yo, mother's legs, nah.
You guys know that trope, right?
It's a trope.
- Oh, man.
- A trope from fucking Muppet Babies, maybe.
- So much worse.
- Your mommy should run around
in fishnets around your house.
Yeah, you could and you would be your mom's barefoot and you see any and you
know, it looks like I dropped your favorite toy under the table. Yeah.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no. Okay.
No, it's like, you know, it's it's being a child again. It's looking at the
flashing lights. It's looking at the cow says, yeah, it's right. It says
clock. If this dude, if they had a cow says moo chicken says cluck slot. Oh my
God I'm playing farmer Dan's banana.
That's the slot.
It's I mean slots are essentially just baby Mozart for
alcohol.
We can't yeah, we can't in the last episode.
We did on the normal feed be like, hey, everybody go listen
to the patreon.
It's great.
And then just also talk about the slots.
New guy.
Yeah.
Yeah, exactly with a person who like yeah, like you haven't
heard us talk about slots.
Yeah, no.
So I'm just like, oh, this is exciting.
I've heard this.
Yeah.
Well, yeah.
That what's what's the pressing matter here is that we're trapped inside and
they're scary lightning. And I might pee myself.
I just went and bought everyone pizza.
You did do that. And it was very good.
And all the cheese fell off.
Yeah, the cheese was like falling.
It was like it's fine.
It was like like that.
Mafia cheese.
A lactose sludge.
It was that's mafia cheese.
That's mafia cheese.
Not kidding. Yeah.
So so I mean, I mean, whatever.
So you're the you're the New York.
I'm in New York Guinea. I mean this might be this might be apocryphal.
I didn't want to say Guinea or Whopper.
You can say it.
What's apocryphal?
I might this might be apocryphal Guinea bullshit but like
apparently according to many members of my family that cheese that we that you
always see on pizza is like...
It's called mozzarella.
[laughter]
And it goes over the sauce.
It's like mob cheese.
It's like, it's like, basically like, mobsters were like, like, if you want to have, like,
good mozzadel, fuck you, you're gonna get this cheap bullshit, we'll give it to you in bulk,
and we'll protect you, or whatever.
And then like, places like, um, Spumoni Gardens back in the day, or like, uh, this place where
I'm from, called Salvatore's, it's really good, where they have like, real mozzadel.
You're from El Salvador?
(laughing)
- Wow.
- I've completely read you wrong.
- That explains everything.
- No, it wouldn't explain anything.
- Yeah, you have a tropical vibe now.
- It would explain a lot of stuff.
- Is El Salvador famously tropical?
- I don't know.
- I'm asking the group here.
- You're asking the wrong people.
- Yeah, I've pretty much been there a million times.
- Yeah, no.
- I'm quite familiar too with several of the statistics
about it and different factoids.
- It's actually, you know what,
it's Spanish for the Salvador.
It is true.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, but yeah, so that cheese is supposed supposedly is mob cheese, but I fucking love I'll eat it.
I'll eat it when it's like all balled up and shit.
Oh, yeah.
I mean you live knob cheese the goop knob cheese.
Really?
It's cheese on your knob.
They then put it on the pizza.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's called.
It's also called smegma.
Yeah, your glob is cheese.
Yeah, my globby smegma is my cheese.
What the?
I don't make the rules.
It's like an Italian thing.
It's culture, alright?
Sounds horrible.
You would eat bog cheese?
I mean, I'd eat bog cheese.
Yeah.
Cheese from a bog?
What's bog cheese?
Cheese from the bog body.
Cheese from a bog.
From a bog body?
Yeah, they milk the bog body and they make cheese out of bog milk.
Alright, what's like, what's an animal that makes milk that you would not eat the cheese from?
What if, what if, like a kangaroo?
I think I would eat cheese from any, I would eat kangaroo cheese.
I would eat probably any cheese.
I mean, can I see how the waters have milk?
Goat cheese.
No, they do.
They know mammals.
They're not all mammals.
Got milk.
They got they got milk from something.
Why the fuck is it with mammals?
So like a whale is a whale make milk.
Yeah, I think so.
No, yeah, if it's a whale makes ambergris.
What if one day what if you know this is this is a sidebar here,
but you know, like, oh, see the ice man.
Like, you know, they find like an old body preserved in ice.
Like what if when they thought him out like he was the juice man.
Yeah and they thought him out and he just immediately like just squirted cum everywhere the second
that he got out of the ice.
Like he was just stuck in the middle.
He got black frozen.
He got frozen right in the middle of having sex.
He pulled out.
He pulled out and the woman.
It just gets the woman.
The woman.
The scientist right in the face.
The ice queen that he was fucking.
Yeah.
Blasted freeze out of her pussy on him.
As a general rule whale milk is rich in fats and comes in very large quantities.
Sounds great.
Oh okay.
has the largest mammary glands on earth.
- Oh my god.
- Do you have a photo?
- Each is about 1.5 meters long.
- What's the cup size?
- And weighs as much as a baby elephant.
(laughing)
I like comparing a whale's tits to like another huge--
- I wanna be crushed by those.
- I wanna see that.
- Why don't they poke out?
Why don't they poke 'em out?
- Maybe that's why you can't like,
like whalemur in Pokemon, you can't go under--
- No, that's why you're not allowed to kill whales.
yeah their tits are so huge okay hold on I don't know what this is okay hold on
okay so there is apparently for this yeah careful the cord yes sorry but this is
what I just saw on the New York Times
what is that oh okay yeah it's something from Evangelion and also it's a whale
which is like I think like up to words of 10 boobs hanging off of it and it's look
it's a float though yeah it's like a that's not where the boobs that's what
the new remade that they are gonna look like mm-hmm I'm gonna try to see it's in
Australia but that's happened I would drink well milk yeah well milk just cuz
I you know I do love see ya I hey I'm gonna say what I always say I would eat
or drink literally anything if you put it in front of me yeah but like if it's
food if it's not like like if you saw how it was made do you think you would still
do it yes like if you were at if it is if it is edible I will eat it yeah if you
put it in front of me there's no reason not to you want to eat some of my hair
that's my balls in my butt it's not food what if I put I would eat your flesh
If I cut off a little piece of my skin will you I will eat it really yeah, I'll fucking do that
Oh, this is what's happening. We're trapped inside
Yeah, no, I will not eat a scab no, but that's no like this part right here. That's just skin. I know it's infected
It's not in fact. It's clearly infected. I cut out. How is this it's infected. It's not in fact
That is you were just telling you showed me that so the red said look how
your leg dangle off the bone this
I'm fine I can walk home. I'm worried about you man. I'm fine. You're in big
trouble. I'm not a big, I'm in the smallest trouble ever.
I'm not in big, no. Are you still mad at me for slapping you again? No. Okay.
No. That's been eating me up inside. You slapping me? I think you just want to
bring it up again because you think, because you you're very proud of it.
maybe it's time I get back for all the ice I just hope you I will knock you out
no I know yeah like I know there's no make no mistake I'm getting I'm getting
all the slaps in now before so that when I knock you out it's it evens out I
would say you have two strikes right now yeah I've been getting too drunk and
slapping Caleb because I think it's funny yeah and then I hurt you worse and
you go like wow you double hit me yeah next time I think I will knock you out
yeah you know it is I think it is the third time and I know there will be a
next time well the first time I'm saying that cuz I know for a fact there'll be a
next time right and I know I will knock Patrick out it'll be like well why'd you
do that like I told you weeks before the first time I did it I was sober that's
when we went to Central Park together and then we were on the train and I told you like,
"Oh, what's that sign?"
Oh yeah, you guys did get into a slap fight in the train station.
That was funny.
Yeah.
And then I guess I did it in Atlantic City too.
I guess I did it in Atlantic City.
What was the context for that one?
I slapped your phone out of your hand and then you slapped me and then we were in a
war and then we walked into a you just want me to tell you say this part that's
why you know we talked about this like yesterday what happened is we walked
into an elevator with three older black
was yeah enough to slap Kayla and then and then Patrick and this is this is so
funny right as we were leaving the elevator I was like well we're safe
there's three old ladies here there's no way that he's gonna slap me in the face
as soon as the elevator opens he says you got something it doesn't even finish it
slaps me in the face and just runs off. He didn't he slapped me. As a third party here I can tell you
very funny because he did not slap you in the face he slapped you in the side
of the head and he did it so hard that his hand followed through and also hit
the wall of the elevator. And then one of the ladies went, "Oh my god."
Wait, so he said he ran off. Where did he go?
I went to...
You ran out of the elevator.
I ran to like the right and it was like...
He knows I can't go right.
I have a very weak right side.
I ran to the right and there was just more elevators and I went, "Oh fuck."
I walked out and you were trapped.
I was like, if he could get me right now, I'd be done.
It's not, at some point, I'm not going to get you, dude.
I'm going to beat you up.
Well, okay, then what was, I don't remember why I slapped you last night.
All I remember is you pulling me aside and being like, "It was funny in Atlantic City,
but you can't do that again."
I didn't pull you aside, I kicked you out of my house.
I wasn't friendly, like, "Hey, man."
I just said, "Get the fuck out."
I pulled you all the way aside.
I forgot you kicked me out of the house.
Yeah, that's... You know what I did? I did go. You know what? I went too far and I'm
gonna apologize. I'm telling you, you can do it again. I'd be happy to
punch you really fucking hard in the face. I would love to knock you out.
Why? I mean like, I don't know, it'd be fun.
Like the joy you get from like slapping me like a girl, like I would get ten times
that from like actually hurting you so bad.
Why? Because I'm just telling you it'd be good, it'd be like really fun for me. So keep that in mind
next time you think about slapping me like Caleb's gonna beat me up and he's
gonna really enjoy it. Uh-huh. Yeah and I might actually wear like a big gold chain while I do it too.
That's the thing, that's the thing like I don't know like I feel like if it's something you're
really gonna enjoy maybe I'll like end up doing it just to just to make the
friendship stronger I'm open to that yeah that's fine I'll probably slap
patches yeah I don't think I think you and I I'll just I be immediately be you
and I you if I ever you try to dude you use the you know you're I'm afraid of
you I will step on your neck kill me he's too tall I can't you do it yeah
Patches, I can tell when you're getting too rowdy too and I'll just stay more than arm's
distance away from you.
Oh no, not you.
I mean, you've all seen me get way too rowdy before.
I had a distinct memory of getting into fights a lot as a kid.
Like very emotional kid, getting into fights all the time.
And then one time I was at, I used to wrestle, so I was at like a wrestling camp.
I told this like kid who was being annoying to me, I said "Fuck off, nobody likes you"
and he walked away and he told his older brother that I punched him in the face.
Which I didn't do.
Oh shit.
And so then his older brother started wailing on me.
And this was like the textbook like your dad saying, "Hey, if somebody hits you first,
you have every right to hit them back." And I just like let him hit me. I had like a complete turn.
I had like been starting fights my whole life and then all of a sudden that like when somebody did it to me,
I was like this is awful I can't believe I just let him hit me it was like a crazy
I think they're like not like a mercy thing I wasn't like I'm like you're
turning the other she no I was just like I was like this is really bad oh my god
yeah it's very intense I think the first fight I was ever technically in I was
like 11 years old and this kid was like like I goes with my friend Desmond and
this kid in his neighborhood like started like I guess he knew before so
like screaming some like very like racist shit at this dude and...
You were screaming racist shit?
No, my friend Desmond and so we like had to we like got up in his face
we were like "Oh fuck you, fuck you" and then the kid just...
Wait, who was screaming the racist shit?
Some random kid was screaming it at this kid Desmond that I was friends with.
I thought you were saying you had to some your friend Desmond screamed some racist shit at somebody
and you were like "I guess I gotta go kill him."
No, so I then then like we got in the kid's face and we were like and I'd never been in a fight before really and
So I just was like I'm you know, like no, we're not gonna I'm 11. I'm not gonna get beat up. So I
Was we were like, yeah, man, like fuck you like do something and the second I said do something he punched me
Yeah directly in the face like how like how nobody actually punches he punch make a shark go away
Chipped all of my front teeth and then my friend Desmond
Just like beat this kid to death
And then we I like spit out all my teeth and like Desmond got up and he was like
Man, I had to like I just step in for you and I was like
Why don't you do that before I got fucking punched?
What the fuck is that?
I never got in a fight before cuz like I would probably just kill them and I'd have to go to jail
It's a really good point. Yeah, so I just try not to do what you would use
you had a superpower yeah yeah yeah you would kill you would fucking kamehameha
somebody sit there and scream until they exploded yeah I might accidentally like
release dark magic I don't like it yeah you would you would be crouching down
you would you would turn into the witch from Left 4 Dead someone else would like
walk through the alley that you got into the fight in and just see you
Cameron fuck!
This guy spending any fucking time in an alleyway as a kid.
What?
He was low down and tumble.
He was rough fucked and fumbled.
I forgot about C-Money.
You forgot about Killacam.
Yeah, Killacam C-Money.
Who did you think he was talking to?
There was another guy named Cameron at my school who was a white rapper
who his rap name was Killa Trill.
- Hell yeah.
- What a fucking, what a missed layup.
- So cool, dude.
- What a dumbass.
- Let's censor that out,
I don't want any free press for the guy.
- He quit his rap career.
- Oh, he's dead, yeah.
- I don't know what happened to him.
I tried so many times to find the Killa Trill songs,
I could not find them.
- Oh dude, it was so, I mean,
you go to like predominantly,
like a predominantly white high school
and you're seeing how many kids
became like soundbite rappers.
- Yeah, oh yeah.
- So fucking cool.
- Could have been me, man.
My mom didn't pull me out, I would have done that.
have done that so fast.
Yeah, it's not even a question that you would have done it.
Yeah, but you would have been like a conscious rapper.
No way.
You would have been like most definitely.
I'm sure if I had like a few more friends I would have ended up like that.
You would have converted to hip hop.
No, actually being homeschooled made me a conscious rapper.
I would have been out there saying drugs, money, hoes.
Oh yeah.
If it weren't for...
Just the idea of like some like high school like soundcloud rapper like in a predominantly
white school just he decides he wants to be a rapper so he just like but he's only like
He like loves like most effort like tell quality. Yeah, it just becomes just like he's just like yeah, I'm like
Yeah, call me you said yeah, he's walking up to like
Table of like rich white kids in a cafeteria the lunch table become the brunch table
Shit the skunk table
Ramadan you eatin?
You catch what I'm feeling?
Nah, not for me
Like the white SoundCloud rapper kid just immediately just like all right just made my SoundCloud account and
I am going to read the Quran
Yeah, yeah
Haven't made the song yet
But if you're reading the Quran
So because you have to become Muslim you have to like know everything about Islam before you make a read
If you're gonna convert like you got a little make if you want a quiet dog I
Just mean like in general like if you're gonna like or mathematics
It's such a funny thing where it's like if you if you grow up with something you're allowed to be lapsed and whatever that is
Yeah, no and no like 20% of it and act like an authority on it. Oh, yeah
Yeah, if you convert it's like like yo, you weren't like forced to do this. You got to know. Mm-hmm all of it
It's like becoming a citizen. It's like yeah, it's like like well
Well I wasn't raised Muslim and I didn't convert either but I know pretty much everything there
is to know.
I'm excited to like when I convert to Islam like walk into a temple and be like, "Hi,
yeah nice to meet you.
My name is Justice Knowledge Da Alphabet.
I'm a recent convert."
The alphabet!
Yo, my name's Destiny Creative Writing.
I'm Derek Biology.
I'm like the newest guy in all of Islam, and pretty much I'm here.
yeah I'm a your mosque I'm Tanner mathematics I'm new to the brother
they have Islamic Brotherhood - I think that's the that's the that's the Lewis
fair economy yes my name is gun gun car Michael just like losing the plot yeah
why are you thinking like Bubba Sparks is my name is YMCA Derek I'm Hannah Montana
yeah dude that's like that's the best part about like any other like religion
you change to you mostly have to keep your name yeah Islam you make up an
awesome fucking Megatron name. That's amazing that makes you feel like like you own it
it's your name yeah exactly your dumbass parents didn't pick it for you exactly
because you're born again like I think Christianity should have that.
We are born again Christians you don't change your name though.
In Catholicism you don't get to change your name.
You have a confirmation name though.
I know but like you never don't get like yeah, you know, it's not like like like, you know, Cat Stevens converting
Yes, exactly. It's not like, you know, it's not like that but like I know what would the Catholicism names did you get confirmed man?
No, I I wasn't really allowed in church as a kid
I
Was to ADHD. I think I went to I went to church a couple times and then my mom watched the passion
and my mom watched the passion got like very like into Christ again mm-hmm and
all right yeah I think she yeah she got like really into fucking God and shit
yes and tried to like take us to church I went to like God and the Holy Spirit
and racism but she got really into that and then like she tried to take me to my
cousin's confirmation and I had to sit in the quiet room and the whole time I'm
in the quiet room I was sitting there like this is so boring.
You're right.
This sucks.
Confirmation is boring.
I just want to go home and I want to eat snacks because they're
having a big like party after.
Yeah.
And we got in the car.
I think I've probably talked about this before, but we got in
the car.
My mom turned to me and went like, I can't believe you did that
in the house of God.
I.
That scared me like out of.
Oh yeah.
Confirmation like was so my high school was like I think I think
I said this on on a little bit, not that much, though a little bit on Pindeo time, though,
when I was on there, but like my high school was extremely Catholic.
So like it was a public high school, but like almost everybody there was Catholic.
So when you're leading up to your confirmation, you were going to like religious education
every week and it's every Tuesday.
And so like the entire eighth grade would just like leave, except for like five, like
like Protestant kids and one Jew would just have to stay for ninth period.
And then like every other kid would leave.
And so you would just like, it was like this weird fucked up thing where like all
the teachers were like completely helpless to stop it.
And that was leading up to the confirmation thing.
But they should have stopped those damn Protestants.
Yeah.
Confirmation party was tight, but like the confirmation itself is so fucking boring.
Oh dude, it's the most boring shit in the world.
You sit there and like the fucking, the priest sits there.
He's like, "Oh, I'm also with you."
Yeah, it sucks.
Yeah. Oh my God.
You got to say it back to him in the same fucking intonation.
Oh, yeah.
Church is awesome.
Oh, you were a fucking Baptist.
Yeah, dude.
There's like an older girl who always wanted to see my feet.
Maybe I should have become Baptist.
Yeah, it does sound better.
It's pretty awesome, dude.
For us, it was older men.
Yeah, it's older men and they're like, "If you tell anybody, I'll fucking kill you."
Yeah, no, I just got like, I got like sexually harassed by like a like a hot high school girl. Yeah, right. Yeah. Oh
My god, that's so I was like 13. She was like, do you wanna like take your socks off? I was like, no
That is very weird that like an older girl really wanted you to know I was really yeah
No, she also I found out later that she she used to sleep in a bed full of like a living roaches
is
you
No, she was just like another, like my mom was like
always like involved in church. She was your other mom?
And she, her mom was also involved in church so we'd end up like
Sure. You know, both like working like the babysitting shit at church or something
or like be like handing out all the food on like the cookout days and shit
and yeah she was always like, "Yeah, you should show me your feet."
What the fuck? Don't really... Have you said this on the pod?
No. Alright. Probably shouldn't have.
But I did resist, like I never showed her my feet.
Good.
I would have showed them immediately.
That's not right.
You're weak.
Yeah, but I also was, I was, you know, I was an active enough kid who as far as jacking
off at the computer went that I knew that that was bad news immediately.
Yeah, absolutely.
You know, like someone asks to see your feet, you say, "Hell no, you turn the other way."
Yeah.
Stranger comes up to you and says, "Can I see your feet?"
Maybe that was just God testing you.
Also, she was goth.
Really?
and she was goth. She sounds great. What's she up to man? I don't know. Yeah she's goth,
she's sleeping in the bed of roaches. Yeah which is also like that's cool. Yeah. Like
that's fucking very cool. How goth? Like uh, like My Chemical Romance or like Christian
Death? Like Cot Topic goth. Okay. Yeah. That's approachable goth. Yeah. That's not like scary
like. That's not like owning like uh human bones. Yes. I mean like yes. That's not goth
you're doing some Gotham evil yeah goths are that's not sir mostly evil do you
remember it like last year when I was goth do you think like you last year
when you were got any idea yeah I remember that you were faking you were
faking you were faking being God you're faking being God you can change what we
would do the D&D stuff and you'd be like my character's name is crow and I mean I
thought that was a good idea we knew it was it was cool it just wasn't the
character we need to have a moment of silence up top for Brandon Lee yeah
right Brandon Lee actually died in my hometown really filming the crow in
Wilmington North Carolina my uncle was on set when he died yeah my uncle was
the prop guy who was that was like like who framed Roger Rabbit the living
bullet in the gun that jumped out. Oh, Uncle Bullet! Yeah. Yeah. Oh, that guy? Yeah, sure!
I went through his heart! Yeah. I went through his head! Wait, is that Brandon Lee? Oh, no!
Ah, cripes. That's crazy. I didn't know Brandon Lee, like, died in North Carolina. Yeah, he
died. I can't... They shoot so many movies in Wilmington and he never told us because
because he wants to hide his movie star past. I'm pretty much a Hollywood big shot.
I didn't know that. Did you guys know that Wilmington is like a movie town? I know they shoot a lot of TV shows there.
They shoot a bunch of movies. They used to but now in Atlanta there's more like tax breaks there.
So they stole it. It was a tax break thing. I thought that was shot in Massachusetts.
Dawson's Creek. Dawson's Creek is entirely in Wilmington? Yes sir. No shit. I have no idea.
um
It's pretty much it. Oh wait. What was you remember when in like 2012 where there was all those like
NBC and ABC primetime primetime like dramas that were about like what if the fairy tales came to life?
Yeah, like uh the bastard executioner and stuff grim grim was shot in wilmington. No, that's a different thing
Yeah, halloween kills was shot in wilmington. The dome the new like the new one that's coming out
Oh that makes sense, I mean Danny McBride's North Carolina.
And it was fun but like you never, oh Iron Man 3.
Yo!
What?
Yeah, parts of it at least.
Do they really have the suits there?
No never mind, the whole movie.
The whole movie is shot in Wilmington.
Damn, I'm supposed to go there, supposed to go to Wilmington with you.
Yeah it's gonna be fun.
Yeah it's gonna be crazy.
I'm excited, I hope Cam comes too.
I will if you tell me when.
You told me you'd tell me today.
Well not here.
Yeah not here.
That's how you lead it.
Everybody shut off your microphones.
You're the one that said it.
No I'll turn it down when we're going again.
Yeah, no, I but I like didn't know any like that was like yeah, I knew that that was happening
But like yeah, I never oh, I knew one kid whose dad was a
Like drove a truck for screen gyms, but that was it. Yeah. Yeah, I didn't didn't know anybody who was involved in it much
They shot some movie that had Robert Downey jr. In it in my hometown really I was there and I
remember
Someone of my friends moms or something like went to like one of the set of one of the shoots or whatever like they're shooting
It like on a street and she was freaking out because she was like I was waving hi to Robert Downey jr
And in the scene he like looks bad
He like he's in a car and he looks back over his shoulder and he saw me waving hi
I was like you need to like calm down. I mean she's famous. Yeah, why are you you're ruining her one?
There's one hour of fame. No, she's famous now. No, she wasn't famous
No, you know miss and she has a million dollars. She doesn't have a million dollars. She's so hot. No, she got immediately she got
She got hit by the car
She died serious. She's very famous. No, no, she died and basically she was erased from history as well
Yeah, and she also she had no face so there's no pictures of her
She looks like the question mark man
What's the question mark man go ahead Pat? I don't think that's his name. I think his name is actually the question
Yeah, go ahead me hold on
I know I know who he's talking about, but I want to hear my face. I swear to God. It's the question
He wears a his name is the question, but was you let's go the question. I know yes, okay
Who is let's hear let's hear if he wears a detective. He's an old super hero. He's who Rorschach was based off from watchman
Oh, he's based off another guy.
He looked exactly like the question mark man.
Yeah, the question mark man tells a lot of riddles.
That's the riddler.
No.
No, the riddler tells all those jokes.
I'm thinking of Slender Man.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, the guy who teaches you how to be thin.
I will say there was three weeks where I was like, "Really?"
Yeah, I was terrified of Slender Man for a while.
I thought Slender Man was real.
(laughing)
- I didn't know, when I was a kid,
my mom told me he wore a toupee, Jon Bastow.
And as soon as I saw that commercial,
immediately after, I realized--
- I don't think I even thought of that.
That is so real.
- Yeah, oh, he wears the fucking craziest hairpiece.
- That is 100% what that is.
- Yeah, as soon as she told me that, I was like,
what the, no, how does it stay on on this machine?
Like, that means it would sweat the hair off.
Did you guys ever see the Fitness Made Simple infomercials?
No.
He's Sean Bay style and he's gonna show you how.
Wow, holy shit.
What a weird overlap.
You know what was a great commercial that always would come on?
You guys ever see a commercial for the Hover Round?
Yeah.
And the guy who's like the CEO of Hover Round, his name is Tom Cruise.
But Cruise is spelled different.
So we would come out and be like, "Hi, I'm Tom Cruise."
(laughter)
- Tom Cruise in Adventure of the Hover.
- It would be funny if they also just lied
about his name.
- Yeah.
- That they were trying to get him on the show.
- I trust it, I trust that that's his real name.
- That's definitely his name.
- Yeah.
- It's like Tom Cruise, like C-R-U-Z.
- I think if you're--
- Tom Cruise's real name is not Tom Cruise, I think.
- What?
- Well, I'll confirm that right now.
- Fact check that, please.
- I got you.
- I think Tom Cruise is a stage name.
I don't think that's his real name.
- It is, it does sound like a stage name.
- Yeah.
- That's kind of smart to change your name
to a misspelling of a famous person's name.
- Thomas Cruz Mapother the fourth.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yep.
- Mapother?
- Mapletherp.
- I mean, maybe Mapotherp.
- How do you spell it?
- It's a horrible name.
M-A-P-O-
- He changed his name, he changed his teeth.
- M-A-P-O-T-H-E-R.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
- Mapother.
- That's what I was looking at.
- I was thinking Mapother.
- Tom Mapother.
Tommy old Tommy Muputher the fourth.
Tommy Muputher?
That's a completely different guy.
I can see, I can see like...
Well I think he would have a very different career path.
Yeah exactly. I guess...
Tommy Muputher I think if he didn't change his teeth he'd be like a Willem Dafoe like character.
Yeah. He would maybe be a guy who just played guys who lived in a swamp or bog.
Well why is his middle name Cruz?
Probably because of how much his dad liked to drive boats.
Probably because of Cuba.
Yeah man.
dad's name was Thomas Cruz Mappa third of third. That's true yeah. And what was his
grandpa's name? And what about his grandpa's grandpa? Yeah. I think we got it.
Saul guys. Well his grandpa's grandpa was Zinu. His father took a job as a defense
consultant with the Canadian Armed Forces. Oh isn't he? Yeah Tom
Cruz is Canadian right? Is he? He's born in Syracuse New York. Okay yeah yeah
fucking like a like guy who's pretty far north. Do you guys remember when Billy Mays died?
Yeah. Yeah. That was so fucked up. That was sad.
Billy Mays, dude I can't find the photo anywhere but I was Billy Mays for Halloween when I was 12.
You should be like the fact that you blew that when you were 12 and not like right now is such
a fucking shame. Well I think it was a funnier costume for a 12 year old to have. But it would
be such a good costume for you now. It would also be really funny if you maybe drew like
X's over your eyes when you did it and like I like war like
Like it look like they're flames. Yeah, yeah, and you held like it you held like
Like a sad face on it
Running into the fire
Fireplace I can't take it anymore. I'm Billy Mason. I'm gonna kill myself
I'm so fucking sad. Billy Mays here, I'm gonna fucking dive my head into the corner of that brick.
Billy Mays here, I am about to asphyxiate for real. It's gonna end.
What are you doing?
In all seriousness, Billy Mays was a great man.
great man. He genuinely, genuinely one of the greatest men. And the way, and the horrible,
the horrible way he went out. I mean, it's tragic. It's so tragic. It's tragic. I gotta
find that fuck. I gotta ask my mom if she can ask around for that photo of me as Billy
Mays. And who is his, who is his British fucking replacement? Oh, Anthony Sullivan here. Anthony
Sullivan here. Oh, Anthony Sullivan here for my buddy. Anthony Sullivan here, I'm worse.
I'm a much worse version.
Oh, man.
Yeah.
I mean, no, I think I think Anthony had no cap.
Fuck Anthony Sullivan.
Really?
You're going to go that far.
I even know who that was.
I know the Slap Chop guy.
That's it.
No, I remember the Slap Chop.
Yeah.
Vince.
Anthony Sullivan's a guy.
Vince Shlomi was Vince Offer's real name.
Vince Offer is such a good name.
He changed his name to Vince Offer when he became like a pitch man.
I think Vince Offer is like incredible.
Probably the best life you can live.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Sure.
What's that?
(laughter)
- What's that, oh, oh, Vince Offer,
before he became the Pitch Man,
he had a movie called The Underground Comedy Movie,
which is like one of the worst fucking pieces
of shit of all time, and then,
after that he made Inappropriate Comedy with--
- Oh, that's him. - Rob Schneider, yeah.
- Oh. - And he wrote and directed that.
- Good for him. - Yeah, and then he--
- Wow. - Beat the shit out of a hooker.
- He did? - Yeah, you don't remember that?
- Do you think he slap-chopped her?
(laughter)
- Look, you save that for 2008, when 2008 comes around,
when 2008 comes back, that joke's gonna crush.
(laughter)
- Oh my God.
- Yeah, I just like, I remember finding out that
the Slap Chop guy was also a comedian when I was like 11.
I was like, holy shit!
- I think Slap Chop, I don't think I've ever seen
the actual commercial, I think I've only seen the YouTube.
- Yeah, me too.
- I saw the commercial a lot, a lot growing up.
Yeah, I did too. Yeah, the Slapshot and the ShamWow.
So I was always up at weird hours, like as a kid, like watching infomercials.
Did you see the Girls Gone Wild, like New Orleans?
Oh my god, of course.
Yeah, the Comedy Central during the Secret Stash.
I mean, that's porn. That was porn that you could watch.
Oh my god, I would get up at 5am and watch that and just go, "Ugh."
Yeah, 'cause also, like, I can imagine what a nipple looks like.
Like, if you just make the nipple a little Comedy Central logo or whatever,
I'm gonna, I mean, I'm gonna whack off.
whenever I see the Comedy Central logo today I remember the first time I saw
boobs in real life I was like where's the logo I said I said put those fucking
things away I tried to rip off the nipples to reveal the absolute watch
you'd see how high and you they could say up to shit they couldn't say fuck
yeah you say up to shit still censored everything else up then in between that
in between like the bumpers that were like the Comedy Central secret stash and
they put like the VHS yes into the VCR they would have the the girls gone wild
commercials oh yeah and then like fucking dick pills yeah pill commercials and so
cool is the girls in the shop calm the girls in those commercials always seem
like so fucking happy yeah that was just like the best part of it for me they
were they don't know because they don't know they don't know they're being
exploited what yeah what are you talking about well it wasn't that the whole
thing was a day like they sued like the guy who made that shit got sued a
million times cuz the girls were like I thought they were so happy they were so
wild yeah yeah but they're like all that they sued them like like I thought that
you were holding like a toaster it's awesome yeah there's just some freak
holding a toaster yeah well you know what they say you know what they say though
you know what they say well-behaved women rarely make history yeah now but
that would also crush in 2008 yeah you joke that would do better in 2008 or
you're so good now it's like a half-life you know yeah half-life you know yeah
exactly yeah hey where's the third one yeah yeah yeah yeah it's not called
halfway three so it doesn't count yeah that's fair yeah you guys play you have a
VR that is it is like I know it yeah it is an old 2008 Chuck Rare but it's so
funny they're like yeah we'll make we'll make like three more half-life games
we're never making one of them called half-life 3 it's so it's like it is like
ridiculous three is too cool a number like if you put three after something
it's gonna be the expectations are gonna be so high.
Well also there's no I think there's very seldomly been the third of something
that was the best one. The second one is usually the best. No third is usually the
best. Okay, sophomore shows. In terms of TV series, third season always the best.
Movies and games I think third is usually the worst. Mm-hmm.
Depends on how long this the I mean Halo 3. Halo 3 is the worst one. Halloween 3,
Nightmare on Elm Street 3.
Halloween 3 is great.
Friday the 33. Exorcist 3.
Texas Chainsaw 2.
Star Wars Episode 3.
Star Wars Episode 3 is a...
Oh no. That's Revenge of the Sith.
That's where like...
Also Return of the Jedi.
That counts as 3 too.
That's the best of the prequels but it's not the best of the whole series.
Revenge of the Sith is my favorite Star Wars movie.
You go to the ring, you put them in chunks.
And that's why Rises of Skywalker is the best one.
Three?
They're all really good though. Three's not bad. No, there's only there's a there's ten minutes that are cool. Blackadder season three?
No, you're stupid. You're wrong. Blackadder season three? Blackaddam. Blackadder. Oh, I don't know what that is.
The Rowan Atkinson show. The Rowan Atkinson British show. House of Cards.
Horrible third season. I remember watching House of Cards. First two seasons, awesome. Third season, I mean. When House of Cards came out
I was like something's wrong with this president character.
The thing about that shows the first two seasons are like oh like this guy's like well
I'm this guy's I am I am the rapist I am evil
He's like kind of scary. He like sometimes kills people he's like, but he's like trying to do
And then by the third season he's just his God and he could do anything he wants
He's like starting wars and like adding like like it's crazy. Yeah
I've added a 24th amendment that allows me to do whatever I want
Pretty much. I feel like I feel like if you write that many hours of
Like any story I get to know - yeah
Well, you know what happened is is Kevin Spacey just kept going to the writers room was like
What if I was just like God I could do anything I want like to anybody
Yeah, sure
Yeah, let's go to Chick-fil-a on Sunday
It's so sad that he was like one of the greatest impressionists of all time who can you was so fucking good really good
Insanely lost a huge talent. Yeah, all right. P. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah should be killed
But first you have to do all the mocap for a new water warfare game
Pat's gonna do it what you're gonna kill Kevin Spacey. I never said that all right. Why did you say that?
I never you there's no recording of it. You say right a recording of what me saying. I'm gonna kill Kevin Spacey
We're gonna reverse it like a rap song so you're gonna leave
Kevin Spacey. I never said that. You're gonna lick him. There was some time in
between what I said. I'm gonna kill Kevin Spacey. That's fine right?
No that's fine. Oh because you put the blank in it? It's like a long like you know
it's like a period long breath. Well yeah I mean it's an incomplete sentence. Yeah it's because I'm
telling Pat to do it in that second part because he already said he was going to.
Exactly. Well I never said I was going to I said he said what did you
I mean this is why you guys do the main podcast because I can't keep up.
Pretty much who's on first.
And then somebody else said something else and I said then I'm gonna do it.
Another great 2008 joke, who's on first.
Oh my god.
Who's on first though?
They should bring it back, I don't know.
It would be who's on second.
Who's on first?
Ahmed the dead terrorist?
That's right.
That's who's on first.
it was a very rare outlook on how do you know actually what
patches has been bringing back very well
is not as me play i have a very good he's been very very very very very
incredible okay i've been i've been uh... we've been to the plague a lot of
video games
and uh...
can see the name of the game or else we have to pay a visit to the royalties
uh... i mean but it's been like between sport and split gate but like
whenever we just start playing like if i like
just do anything or if I like,
like, "Oh, I almost killed him, I missed."
Meep.
(laughing)
Just like, just saying meep again,
I think it's really--
- It's gonna come back.
- I think it's gonna come back.
- Yeah.
- I think meep is--
- It sucks. - I think you're tired
of it. - One of the worst parts
about speaking English is that if you say something
like because you think it's funny to say it
like four times, it becomes completely habitual.
- Yeah. - Like I cannot,
like I say no cap now.
- Yeah. - To my wife.
yeah yeah I did the dishes no cap you like year when we could not just stop
saying that is awesome yeah yeah this is officially awesome that is awesome
yeah we all still do that but this was like no we did it like like people told
me like stop saying yeah like that one is also unique because that's not like
once every 10 minutes.
"Okay, this is officially awesome."
"Yeah, okay, this is officially awesome."
Which is like such a long tick.
And people would get really mad at it.
Yeah.
Well, that was when you guys were in LA, right?
No, that was when we were working.
That was a long time.
That was probably around the same time I met you.
Okay, now this is awesome.
I think we probably were just growing out of it by the time that we met you, maybe.
I remember, and I probably said this before,
we recorded a test episode of the podcast with me and Caleb and I sent it to Leo
to be like hey do you think this is funny he was like you have to stop
saying this is officially awesome. It's so annoying.
You have to stop saying this is awesome.
I'm sorry the episode is...
For some reason you said it's officially awesome every time.
Meeep.
Yeah I think saying meep is good.
We were talking about it when we were gaming.
Oh and also bringing back derp.
I think Derp, I think Derp, we maybe have to wait a little bit.
But I think Derp is, I think Derp is on its way up.
I think Derp's on its way up.
Derp's on the come up.
I would buy it on Derp right now.
Buy Derp now.
Buy some shares in Ermagerd.
Oh no, for sure.
I think, I think Ermagerd might have a little bit longer to go.
Yeah, I think, I think.
I mean, well get in on the ground floor now.
Get in the fucking.
I think, I think Derp, like honestly, next month you can start saying Derp.
I think I can.
Yeah.
I've been thinking about it.
I think Ermagerd might have about two or three shares.
on the ground floor now get in the fucking... I think derp like honestly next
month you can start saying derp. I think I can. I think ermagerd might have about two or three years.
Ermagerd is very funny. Get in on it now. I'm laughing at ermagerd because we're talking about derp.
But I think if someone said ermagerd... What I really want to come back is like you know how
they they had all the different advice animals like they had like you know like socially awkward
Penguin. Bloodhound gang wrote a song about it. And like all the like you know the like
like the have the success kid one and the ones that are very clear when you look at it you're
like oh I can tell like this is like a happy kid so this is like this is a success thing like I can
tell the vibe. I really want the ones to come back where people just decided like oh yeah like this
bear means that it's a confession. Like this stuff like that then like you have to like know the
lexicon. Like I need it to get really complex and we need to bring all those. You know what I miss a
a lot is meme generator.com. I think it's still up. It definitely is still up. I would also,
that's another phase I went through is I would go on like. On the new images? No, I would
just, one of the meme generators has like a shuffle button. Or no, you know what it
is? You can type in like random numbers into the URL and you just get like memes that like
11 year old kids make to like make fun of their friends. It's the best thing ever. Yeah,
- Was it on Meme Generator?
- Yeah, Meme Generator new images are like a different one.
- Image Flip is the one.
Image Flip is the one that you can get random images.
It's so good.
- But Meme Generator new images,
there's like a whole Tumblr dedicated to it.
And in high school I would look at that
and it would just be like, the funniest thing to me,
it would be like the picture of Fry
and it would say like, not sure if or whatever.
And it would just be like the big meme font
and all it would say was like, "Estoy."
(laughing)
That was it.
Just a picture of Fry from Futurama like,
- "Gay?"
Exactly. Yeah, that is also the best. They take Homer Simpson and they say something about, they say, "El baño está muerto."
That or like, I remember there was one, one specifically it's the "Ain't nobody got time for that lady."
Yeah. And it just says, "Car, car, car, car, car, car."
Yeah, we're just looking through Image Flip right now over here. What do you see on there?
Can you describe the pictures to me?
me this one is a dog telling a joke and it says where do ghosts post all of their
videos on boo tube dog soy face that's actually pretty good yeah actually you
know what say say don't say the dogs that say you said it yeah this one is a
picture of Drake going like this uh-huh and he's it doesn't like it and it says
buy an unlimited toilet paper and then it's a picture of Donald Trump with deal
with the glasses and it says stop kovat 19 all right this next one do it like
it's this one this one is a woman crying and it says the holding newborn son
can't reach iPad don't tell us what the image is it's your own joke yeah wait no
go back to the other one that were you just went away from come on stop come on
my god no yeah come on patches I'm sorry found it okay say you want another
Harry Potter book I dare you this dude we could this could be a great game of
charades yeah yeah oh yes what the photo is yeah okay this one read this out loud
birthday at college I don't remember my arm hurts I don't really get that one I
don't remember my arm is that what happened I don't know that's like one
specific guy who went to college and like some frat was like yeah we have to
punch you in the arm a thousand times back in my college this is yeah I love
these ones that are like this is what was this this never existed this is not a
joke or anything this is just a thing that somebody wants to say it says back
in my day we used to put up the tree and decorate on Christmas Eve
Scrooge oh there's a it's also like a meme that I've never seen yeah it's
screwed it's an old man angry old man that's angry old man duh angry screw you
don't know I'm gonna see that you're about to make my Scrooge angry straight
up you're about to make my Scrooge turn red no that's come on we got it come on
we got to get some good. Yeah. Okay. Here we go.
Do traveling fertilizer salesmen go on tours of duty?
That's pretty good. Do you get it? Yeah, that's not bad. Uh-huh.
No, anything about any of that. Yeah. There's a Minecraft one.
A Minecraft meme. There's so much man. I remember when, when,
when here's a really good one. Now I want you guys to guess,
or you guess you're already looking at it, but I can't read that from here.
Have it here. I'll just read it out for everyone listening. Having fun,
forcing everyone to go to church with them, my grandparents.
You can guess where the car, which exit the car's getting off
at.
Yeah, I was gonna say when when the first time I ever played
mine, mine, minecraft, sorry, minecraft was with was with you
to Caleb and Cameron, because I just never played it. And then
and you guys were like, Oh, did you got to get minecraft? We got
to play it. It was like we were just starting the podcast and I
play with it was a lot of fun but like I also remember being like this is like
the exact generational divide yeah but I have with you guys which is like not
many years but enough where I'm like playing Minecraft and I'm like I feel a
thousand years old you know what it is that is my craft you literally I played
Minecraft like like in high school and now Minecraft does that to me yeah it is
it's they've changed it in the middle school that's what I mean yeah no high
It was like the only thing that would run on like my family computer right I play
Yeah, exactly. It's a game you can play on a Mac. You know, I know this was like when they first did the Java download
Oh, I would like join random servers. There's this one server
I would go on where the the mod would oh
he had a
He looked like the devil like he had like a devil skin and he would just type in chat like I'm the devil and he would
Go around just breaking
(laughing)
- Like, so there would be these kids would be,
"Please, no."
(laughing)
- They just joined a random server,
spent four hours building something sick,
and then the devil would fly down
and set everything on fire and say,
"LOL, I am the devil."
(laughing)
- I remember there was like a server
that was like a challenge server
where you're just like on a tiny floating island
and you have to like, like it was,
I forget what it's called,
but like you have to like harvest resources
just from like this like four by four square or whatever and me and my friend
went on that server and we got like this hack thing that like let us fly and we
found out that every island is just like they're all in a line and they're all
just a certain distance away so you can't see the next one so you just
logged on and just and just flew in a straight line and just took everything
out of everybody's chest all the way down the line and like you can't like
reset on that server so you just like ruined like 20 people's games.
I mean there's nothing more satisfying than ruining somebody's experience of a video game.
Oh absolutely.
Like a stranger.
Yeah.
Just cause like, it's zero stakes cause like who gives a fuck it's a video game.
You joined like a TF2 server, you just mic spammed, that shit was awesome.
Oh dude, hacking kids runescape accounts back in the day was so funny.
Yeah, I remember in middle school there was like a, or no no no, this was elementary school
in the third grade.
It was like me and this other girl had, we were the only two kids in our class who had
Neopets and she gave me her login I gave her mine and then I didn't know how to
play Neopets too well and you know I asked my sister like hey can you like you
know boost my profile or whatever also can you boost my friends and my
sister went on and just stole everything from this girl's Neopets account.
My sister was like... That's fucking vicious. That's a lot of time. That is a
that one of the most vicious things I've ever seen because one I was like what I
mean she's she's like four years older than me so she was in like mmm sixth
grade I was yeah third grade and she's like just stealing a bunch of shit from
an eight-year-old that's so so yeah and and I remember I came to school the next
day and she was like crying and I was like what's going on she's like I don't
want to fucking talk to you like you know it's like what happened she's like
you stole all my stuff and I had to explain to her like no my sister did that
She's like, well, why did you give your sister my password?
Yeah, I was always like I was - I was too nice as a kid I never yeah, that's the thing that fucking ruined me
I was just like I came home that day and I was like
Mad at her. I was like Amanda. Why the fuck did you like do that? That's so funny. She's like, I don't care
What do you say that? I don't care
I was also like a hundred percent though the kid who would watch kids do that shit and be like, I
I wouldn't do it, but I'd be like, "That's cool."
I was evil and I wanted to blow up the school, so...
Yeah.
Oh, dude, another fucking...
My cousin...
One of my cousins gave his, like, Webkinz account...
Like, password to, like, my neighbor.
And my neighbor, the guy that showed me
"Three Guys, One Hammer"
when I was, like, in fourth grade, so this is, like...
He trusted that guy with his damn Webkinz account?
I mean, I don't know.
If you had a Webkinz account, you were foo-foo.
No lie.
I wanted a Webkinz account but I couldn't get one.
Foo-foo asshole.
Yeah I know right.
Foo-foo.
He gave...
Not even a wannabe foo-foo.
I know dude.
He gave his Webkinz account to my neighbor and he lost like a firefighter chair and my
aunt...
What is that?
It was like a chair that was like firefighter themed for like donations.
He lost a firefighter chair.
A chair for dogs.
Well yeah it's Webkinz.
I guess so.
So we get a call, like I guess he like, you know, went home.
Did you think that was gonna hit in this room?
No.
I lost a firefighter chair.
A firefighter chair.
A firefighter chair!
My brain, my brain!
The more I'm thinking about you saying that so matter of factly, the more it's gonna...
Look, it made me lost a firefighter chair.
My brain went through like 15 different images trying to fucking like, like, like, like,
lost rating feel what I think it was a hydrant shaped chair my aunt his mom
calls my mom and it's like I'm going to contact the police I mean it's a
firefighter chair I would - I would love to do jail time because of web kids I
was like I like a noir detective trying to track it down yeah you said it was a
firefighter chair. She walked in there with her four legs. Yeah alright okay okay
bye everybody. Wait wait wait, subscribe to the Patreon. This is the Patreon. That's smart.
No that's really smart. That is clever actually. Subscribe to the Patreon.
Yeah hey tell everyone else to do it too. Yeah please.