you're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[LAUGHTER]
[EXPLOSION]
[INAUDIBLE]
[HUMMING]
Me, me, me, me, me, me, me.
No, I don't do that.
I had another--
Me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me.
[HUMMING]
OK.
Anybody else?
Yeah.
You see the smoke?
You see the vape come up?
You're the other one.
Me, me, me, me, me.
Are we done?
That's pretty bad.
No.
OK.
do it do your opera voice.
[Laughter]
Dude that was a beautiful voice.
That was really beautiful.
That was absolutely beautiful.
God, I had another penis predicament.
- I had another penis predicament this morning.
- What do you mean penis predicament?
- I wore the same shorts that I did last night.
- Okay, the Grace Flit Pants challenge.
- To take out the trash.
- Yeah.
- To take out the trash and another lady saw my Lego
in my pants, dude.
(laughing)
Made full eye contact with it.
- Nice.
- His dad.
- But it was like a morning, I had a morning Lego though.
It was like, because I'm like 50/50.
Either I'm like the hardest I've ever been in the morning or my penis goes into my body
in the morning.
Like I guess I don't have that problem.
It's like one of those optical illusions where you think the face is pointing towards you
but then you move to the side and it's going in.
No, I do.
You're like, wow, that's a three foot long penis and then you shift over like one degree
to the left and you can see there's just a giant hole in your pelvis.
It looked like I tried sewing my pants like a patch and I left a needle in my pants.
That's what it looked like.
It looked terrible, dude.
It was one of my all-time worst pieces.
Some ants were camping down there.
They raised a tent.
Yeah.
No.
You live too close to a church.
Yeah, you got an ant camp down there.
So don't, okay.
I just want to come out and, I want to get ahead of this one.
I don't have ants in my pants.
Yeah, you do.
I do not have any ants.
Explain, explain your dance.
Nowhere near my pants, dude.
I don't do a dance.
Explain your dance.
I don't have any ants in my pants.
- Yeah.
- Okay, it's that simple.
None of them are from France.
- Okay, okay.
- You have ants in your pants?
- No.
- Yeah, you do?
I know we like to joke around,
but I don't have ants in my pants.
- You have ants in your pants?
- No, you guys both have dogs in your pants.
- You have ants in your pants,
and you're in the place in France
where the ladies wear no pants.
- That's everywhere in France too,
that's why I'm moving there.
- Yeah.
I understand that the ladies here wear no pants. Am I correct in that assumption?
C.
C. L. Ladies wear no pantos.
L. Ladies no wear pantos.
No pantalones. No pantalones on es mujeres.
you know you know understand oh ladies wear no pants oh I'm sorry
l-ladies wear no l-pants oh me understand oh your French is very good yeah I've
seen ratatouille I know how to speak French man talk about her talk about an
ant in your pan how about a rat in the hat oh my god dude yeah my god I'm
surprised dr. Seuss's estate did not say ratatouille I got a freaking squirt in
my shirt.
(laughing)
- Raditz.
- The turtle.
- Squirt the turtle.
- I got a tort in my shorts.
- I got a turtle in my shirtle.
(laughing)
- I have a shrew in my shoe.
- I have a clock in my sock.
(laughing)
- Nice dude, let's do this for an hour.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- One whole hour of this.
- I've got grains of sand in my brains and hands.
- I had a wanket in my blanket.
(laughing)
- I have some meat in my sheet.
Baby, there's meat in the sheet again.
- I have a cousin in my oven.
(laughing)
- There's a little snail in my fingernail.
- Alex Moffat's in my closet.
(laughing)
that is an from s_ and l
alex moffett yeah i don't know how you're thinking about the morning and you're
thinking of the end when a hand in my boys little hands
i don't know what i'm doing anymore man to society
life so that i have to say that now we do uh... ten minute long bit about this
work that right
nothing makes me laugh for it and they had to know why
I have no idea why.
Cause it's funny.
Has anybody else showed their penis to a stranger recently?
I got a guy in my eye.
No.
No?
I've not, I've never, maybe by accident.
There's been some...
I've never showed it to a stranger.
There was a while where that was like, you know, that was like what I did.
Am I connected?
I thought it was.
You guys hear me?
No, you're disconnected.
disconnected no I just my internet just like went kind of like you guys like you went like
for a couple boys
Yeah
You just put on live headphones, and you heard yeah, yeah, you guys are sitting there like
There's been some construction going on across the street
And I have like a lot of windows in this apartment now
And I've been walking around my house nude like I usually do and I forgot you're one of those people
Yeah, if I gotta get something if no one else is home only if you have to get something you will be completely naked in your
House, maybe I want to listen to music in the shower to get something. Hold on
I have to go get something in the other room. Will you hold my shirt my pants and my underwear my socks and my shoes?
I've already got my socks and my shoes off. Yeah, we just hold all this I wear them in the house
Yeah, I can go a lot faster if I don't have clothes on
Yeah, I can get this thing and be right I'm way more air time you you just dive through the door
Slide across the ground
Patrick has little smaller doors that are just for him in every door in his house like a doggy door. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, it's a poggy door cuz Patrick's a pog
That's right. Oh, you know, that's right of gingerbread
What a peg
A bat? No, a person of gingerbread.
Oh, okay.
Where's the W?
No, he said P-O-G.
P-O-G.
Person always, always, uh...
Wearing...
Gloves.
Glitter. Always wearing glitter.
Gloves?
So you're telling me you flashed that old, that old Lego to the construction workers?
I probably, I probably flashed my little, my little church mouse to a...
construction worker this week yeah do they try to catcall you they took the
crane and they put it up to my window and they and then they're sitting on top
of each other with each of them having a pair of binoculars yeah yeah when you're
asleep they they bring the crane around through your window and they try to play
the claw game and jack you off in your sleep.
The crane's too big for my penis.
I've had the craziest dream ten nights in a row where a crane comes in my window and tries
to jack off my penis.
Pat, you're killing yourself there.
And here's the craziest part of the dream.
Caleb, you keep going like, your audio keeps cutting for me.
I don't know if it's my internet.
Oh, it's just for you.
Alright, it doesn't happen, it's not happening to me.
I'm perfect, dude.
Fuck.
It's okay.
- No, 'cause I haven't called Comcast yet to switch it over.
So my internet's been working,
but it's just gonna shut off one day.
- So you think that they're like slowly
like turning it off for a second
and then turning it back on?
- They're testing how much they'll notice.
- I don't think that's what they're doing.
- Why don't you just call them?
- Yeah, it's difficult--
- Are you somebody who doesn't do phone calls with people?
Like you don't wanna call--
- No, because I used my phone number to help my friend,
her phone, like she didn't have data for a little bit
or something like that, or like her phone wasn't working.
- I can tell this is gonna be a really good reason.
- And.
- Continue.
- No, I had to use, so I had to use my phone number
for Comcast, for her Comcast.
So my phone number is linked to her account.
So anytime that she needs to do stuff,
I have to do it for her.
Or I have to at least call for her.
- And so you can't call Comcast.
- Dude, this is, I'm on the edge of my seat here.
- Oh fuck.
- Pat.
dude I froze oh no freeze for a frozen still no videos frozen for me we have to
unthaw Patrick I'm frozen I'm frozen oh fuck dude no gases D dosing you dude I
think they're finally shutting it off
shutting it off right as we record dude that's fucked up dude he's frozen oh no
Hold on, I gotta call Comcast.
Yeah, we're gonna call them right now.
I'm gonna call them right now.
The worst part of this is he's definitely talking into his mic right now, so we're just gonna have two overlapping audios.
Oh, he's back!
I'm back. Dude, this sucks. I think they finally shut it off.
How are you talking to us right now?
I'm gonna give them a call.
Who?
I'm gonna give Comcast a call for you.
No, don't call them. I have to figure it out.
Don't worry, I got you.
No, he's calling them.
It's not linked to your phone number. It won't work.
No, it'll work.
We have a special relationship with Comcast.
Don't call them.
Hold on, I need to find their customer service line.
I'm gonna take...
Don't even worry about it, okay? I'm gonna take care of it for you.
Oh, no.
I'm gonna take care of it.
They're saying oh no about your internet or about me calling
Oh, he's gone again. Fuck dude. Don't worry. I'm handling it. Yeah
Guys it's not working
Which one do I press for Espanol s to I think
What's a zip code in Boston - what -
One one for one two
*laughs*
*typing*
Sorry, I didn't find an account based on your zip code.
Okay, alright, let's try this again.
Oh, Pat's out of the call. Oh, he's back.
I'll need a phone number or account number to look you up.
Which would you like to use?
Can you...
Call us a representative.
*laughs*
Call my representative.
I understand you'd like to speak to an agent, but I need a little more information from you
to better start with your call.
fucking backstab me you fucking robot bitch
I gotta figure this out dude, this sucks
can you guys hear me?
yeah
I don't know what's going on
I think your your Wi-Fi is bad is what's going on
yeah
that would be my guess
or other options.
(yelling)
- Friend.
(laughing)
- Sorry, you can say, technical support.
- Friend attack.
(laughing)
- Let's try this.
For technical support, press one.
For billing assistance, press two.
- Spell out friend attack with the numbers.
- Yeah.
- Sorry, which service are you calling about today?
- Friend.
- TV?
- For my friend service.
- Internet and email.
(laughing)
- Let's try this.
For TV, press one.
For internet and email--
- So you can watch TV over the phone now?
- Whoa, awesome.
- Press one, you can watch TV.
(speaking in foreign language)
- Did you just switch it to Spanish?
- I hope so.
- For billing inquiries or technical support--
- Why are you sultry now?
Why'd your voice change?
- If you're on YouTube Comcast
and would like to purchase services,
please press two.
Technical support.
Friends. Friends support.
Need to support my friend.
Alright, now we're waiting. We're on the phone with him though.
Don't tell me you started this over again.
What are we doing?
We're talking to Comcast.
I have to call them...
I'm doing it for you, I already said I'm doing it for you.
We're supporting you.
You're not gonna be able to do it, I don't know my account number.
I'm gonna be able to do it.
I don't know my account number.
Sorry, you interrupted me and now I have to restart.
What was that?
Let's try this.
Using your keypad, enter the zip code where you have...
They started you over, dude.
I just put in my zip code, fuck it.
I just need somebody on the phone right now.
Sorry, I didn't find an account
- Sorry, I didn't find an account based on your zip code.
- What? - Let's try this.
- This is fucked up.
- I'll need a phone number or--
- No, it uses your phone number and then--
- What would you like to use?
Or if you're calling to sign up for--
- It's not gonna work.
- It's just gonna keep starting over.
- Yeah. - New customer.
- Just close it, I think I'm fine.
- I just need to talk to someone.
- I think I'm fine.
- What service are you calling about?
- Internet.
- God, just don't.
- Sorry, I didn't get that.
- Internet. - Why are we doing,
Why are we doing this the whole episode? This is a premium.
*laughs*
I need...
The int- the internet.
*laughs*
I need to talk to somebody about the internet.
I need to-
*laughs*
You're attacking my friend!
Somebody...
*laughs*
in China is DDoSing my friend...
and I need you to put an end to this.
I need a firewall.
*laughs*
I need a firewall to protect my friend...
ASAP!
*laughs*
Don't...
Don't you dare do this again!
Don't you fucking dare!
*laughing*
I'm gonna come to your home.
What are you-
I'm at your home!
*laughing*
You can say, "Add new service."
Add new service.
Add new service to Patrick.
I'm just going to get you new internet, dude.
Don't worry about it.
Don't!
Ask us about Xfinity Mobile.
I won't.
Number one in customer satisfaction.
Skip.
Skip this song.
In customer satisfaction index.
Skip button.
Hello?
Spanish.
I don't speak Spanish.
Yeah, dude is Spanish.
(laughing)
- For billing inquiries or technical support.
- It's doing it again.
- You broke her.
You broke her, dude.
She's going.
(laughing)
- Did I destroy you?
Did I win?
- If you are moving to a new address
and would like to move your services,
- Did I beat you?
- You beat the final boss, dude.
- To disconnect your services,
please press four.
- I'm giving up.
- Yeah.
- I think it's good now.
- This is our first Fatwa in like a year.
Comcast.
Yeah.
Yeah, first one was very successful.
Comcast.
Yeah, the first one.
Comcast, you might want to look back.
Yeah, you might want to look at some things on the computer that happened.
You might want to look up some videos on the internet that have been going around.
Yeah.
Yeah, Comcast, you're going to want to, it's a, you just made a very powerful enemy, I'll
say that much.
The fucking taps the FBI already has on Caleb's phone.
Is he screaming at the Comcast robot?
China is DDoSing my friend!
*laughter*
Dude, you're fucked.
I'm already fucked, dude.
You were saying you were gonna attack them!
You said you were gonna go to their home.
I will. I'm looking up the Comcast
address right now.
Just for fun.
Don't say it over the
mic. I don't want to.
Yeah, they bugged the mic actually.
*laughter*
- Do you think they're watching this right now?
- They listen to the podcast, dude, they subscribe.
- They definitely do.
- They have to, they're one of those people
with a racist name that we didn't want to read out.
- Ah, gotcha, they're the racists
who are infesting the fan base.
- Yeah.
- It's their fault.
- Yeah, I hate those racists.
- That didn't sound very convincing,
but why'd you say it like that?
- I hate them.
- Why are you winking?
- Why are you...
- I'm not winking.
- Why'd you wink again when you said that?
- Why'd you just wink?
Did you just wink?
- Why are you holding up a sign that says,
"I love the racists"?
- That's my internet's been glitching.
- Why are you showing us a DVD copy
of Louis seasons one through three?
- No, my internet's glitching right now
and you're seeing things because of the glitches.
- That's the Woody Allen collection on your bookshelf.
- No, it's not.
- Yeah, it is, dude.
But it's not movies.
It looks like it's a photo album.
Why did you just pull down your pants and show us the tattoo you have where it looks like
Jefferson Davis is riding your penis like a horse?
Cameron, how...
You can't explain your LOL swastika tattoo.
Yes I can.
The tattoo artist said it was Japanese for love.
LOL means peace in India, actually.
It means lots of love.
And I wanted it four times.
I wanted it four times to make a symbol.
different orientation. Yeah. I think that's the first time that's ever happened. How did you
solve your internet crisis? No, it just started working again. So after this I
have to like finally do that. Yeah, I basically solved it by calling them it
seems like. Yeah. We are so sorry sir. Oh my god. We're installing a firewall. You're gonna have free internet for a whole year.
That's right. I wish I'd been alive during Hurricane Katrina. I could have stopped that with a phone call too.
Yeah. I'm calling Harp in FEMA and I'm telling them.
I'm 15. I'm 15, but if I was 16 and I'd been one years old, I would have called George Bush.
"Hey, Bush! Yeah, you already know who it is. Listen, all that water, you gotta knock it off."
You weren't 15 when Hurricane Katrina happened?
No. I'm 15 now.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
We're all 15.
- I think it would have stopped every world tragedy
with a phone call.
- I would have stopped the World Trade Center
from falling with my hands.
- Listen, Osama, between you and me,
I don't like the Towers much either.
They're a real eyesore.
I hate that they have become,
every mug and every fucking t-shirt with the skyline,
it's like, oh, look at the Towers.
- I hate seeing them in the Sopranos intro.
I hate seeing that.
- What about, you know, like a preschool or something?
- I feel like that would have been worse.
Preschool in like a lower-income neighborhood, you know those kids. There's nothing they're not gonna be anything who cares man
If you really just want numbers just just absolutely just blast them dude. I don't give a fuck
Just leave our towers be if I was at 9/11
I would have built the towers back from the rubble and I would have glued them back together. I would have said oh damn
Oh my god
Side of my Impala that ice cube was driving
Yeah
That's what I would have built it back like mine. I would have said listen. Yeah, I
Have minecraft I have minecraft on my computer. Yeah, just just step back Rudy Giuliani
Yeah, we're rolling back the server is it am I misremembering this or after shortly after 9/11 did Rudy Giuliani and George W
Bush play a game of King of the Hill on the rubble?
- What?
- Did they fight each other to stand on top
of the mountain of rubble?
- I don't know, I don't think they did that.
- You're thinking of Godzilla versus King Kong.
- Yeah, you're thinking of Godzilla and King Kong.
- You're thinking of aliens versus the predators.
- 'Cause Rudy Giuliani is an ape
and George Bush is a lizard person.
- Yeah, they're both a couple of monsters in my book.
- They're both aliens and predators if you ask me.
Did I ever, did I tell you when I saw Steely Dan in October, Donald Fagan, after he made
that Me Too joke?
What Me Too joke?
I don't know if I, I, uh...
You just assumed that we would remember a Me Too joke that Donald Fagan made at a show
that we weren't at?
No, I thought I told you about it.
It's funny that he won't explain that, but if his brother stubs his toe, he'll do 15
minutes of like, "Yeah, my brother stubbed my toe," and he actually has really weak toes,
which he runs in my family.
We all have weak toes.
But uh, fuckin, yeah, Donald Fagan said that the Dayanettes, the female backup singers
were gonna sing "Dirty Work" and then he was like "The beautiful Dayanettes, I feel weird
saying that, I feel like I'm gonna get me too'd.
Anyway, here's 'Dirty Work'" and then he left the stage and came back with a jacket cause
he was cold, and then as soon as he came back, cause he's fuckin old as shit now, and he
came back and he sits down at the piano and he's like "Halloween's comin up, huh?
I think I'm gonna go as Rudy Giuliani. Pretty scary, huh?
Dude, owned. That rocks, dude.
Dude, fucking awesome. What about the Nanette singing?
Uh-huh. You know?
I don't wanna do your dirty work, mate. No.
No, I'm not gonna do your dirty work anymore. I don't think I've ever heard dirty work.
I can't contribute. I was more setting a...
Times are hard, you're afraid. You're afraid.
Yep, keep going. To pay the fee.
Do you find yourself somebody?
I'm a dillywad to do your dirty work?
No. Oh no.
Can't do the I say.
You're a cunt to do my dirty work.
Do you think she
Listen, look at me Patrick.
Do you think that Hannah Gadsby
is Crocodile Dundee?
Is that what you honestly
believe in your heart?
Do you think that's the same guy?
Cause I think it's a different guy.
They all sound like Australia.
They all sound like Crocodile Dundee down there.
No.
I don't think so.
Yeah, some of them are like, "Noooo!"
And some of them are like, "Noooo!"
And then some of them are like, "Fly to the Concord" style.
Yeah, "Fly to the Concord" style motherfuckers.
I think that's what "Dannette" was, or "Nannette."
Yeah.
It was song parodies.
It was loose song parodies.
I still haven't seen it.
I think I watched like the first couple minutes of it and I was just like, "Nannette."
Well, let's get into it.
It's a year and a half old. Let's break it down. It's a year and a half old. God. That's fucking 20 years ago. Yeah
Yeah, it feels like it came out in 1999 and she had a she came out in 1989
She had a high top fade like kid and play. Yeah, she looked like she looked like Gerald from Hey Arnold. Yeah
2020 is so crazy. Can you guys believe that 9/11 happened this year?
Wow, it feels so it feels like it was almost 19 years ago. Yeah, but in fact it happened this year. Yeah. Yeah
How do we celebrate murder hornets and and and kovat everything's nobody
One of the murder hornets I think they found like a hive of them. No. Yeah in your ass. Yeah, that's right
So I mean they found them
Yeah, they were actually they weren't able to get him out. No, they're still there. They weren't able to know they weren't able to get
About they're doing they're chewing out the insides of my router right now. Actually, they're stinging in my router is inside your ass
- Yeah.
- Is that why your internet's so bad?
- That's how he remains connected everywhere he goes.
He had a wifi router implanted into his asshole.
- Yep, it also gets cable, so.
- Whoa.
- Uh-huh.
- I just learned about penis implants.
- Yeah, like the silicone ones?
- They have ones now.
- Wait, are you thinking, are you, like,
extenders or the guys who inject it with legs?
- Extendo clip on the penis.
- Extendo clip on your penis?
clip on your penis? I'm talking about the banana clip lego dude. They have ones now that you they
take off your penis and then they add a sleeve of plastic and then they put your penis back on.
What does that do? It makes your penis plastic. It's so you can become a toy. Oh my god. Is it
Medical-grade plastic or just like
Yeah
Water bottles full of BPA
Harvesting a harvest. There's a little bit of particle board whenever a sea turtle chokes on a six-pack on six-pack rings
They melt them down and make them into a new penis
That's how he got that's how the creator of the implant got that idea he saw a sea turtle choking on plastic
He's like, "I'll give you some plastic to choke on."
[Laughter]
I'm putting that on my dick, dude.
Yeah, and then he created a penis extender.
He wanted to fuck a turtle.
And here's the best part, it only comes in--
Would you fuck a turtle?
What?
Yeah, no.
I'm not gonna say my answer 'til I hear yours.
Did you know sea turtles--
I would.
I would fuck a turtle shell full of peanut butter.
[Laughter]
I wouldn't fuck a turtle.
I was just saying, I was just asking.
asking.
Well a sea turtle or a land turtle?
You kind of hopped on that a little too quick.
I mean I'm just an inventor.
Is that so wrong?
This world is so anti-science, pro-religion and god nowadays that you can't even put a
hot dog in a cell.
Fuck a turtle full of peanut butter.
No, not a turtle full of peanut butter.
I don't want to... that's messy.
I'm saying a dead turtle's bone.
The turtle is part of the shell.
I didn't realize that.
- Turtle's not part of the shell.
- If you take the shell off it--
- I saw a cross section of a tortoise.
- You take the shell out the turtle,
you can't take the turtle out of the shell.
- In Cannibal Holocaust, they take the turtle off the,
the shell off the turtle and all the guts come out.
- It's like the third time we've talked about that.
- About the part--
- About Cannibal Holocaust turtle.
- All right, are we gonna start keeping track
of how many times people mention stuff
on the podcast, Patrick?
- I don't know.
- We're gonna start counting that?
- Yeah.
- We need to start being mean to Pat,
like the people on the subreddit.
- No.
- Yeah, being mean to people doesn't mean that people
are gonna watch. - My whole family thinks
Caleb's already too mean to me.
- Well, yeah, they're your family.
- It's so funny that your whole family listens
to the podcast.
- I know.
- That's so sick, dude.
Will they hear this right now?
- Probably.
- What's up, mama?
How you doing?
(laughing)
You're welcome, by the way, for saving your brother's life.
- It's more likely-- - Or your son's life.
- Your brother.
- Yeah, what?
(laughing)
- If it wasn't for me, Pat, he'd be in a gutter right now.
If it wasn't for me, Patrick would be your brother.
He'd be stuck in a storm drain.
Oh, okay. It happened to the... the internet thing happened to my neighbor, too.
So, we're good. It was just a hole.
So I don't have to get that shit fixed for another week.
Does your neighbor text you?
Do you guys hang out?
Well, my... one of... like, Dom's best friend lives in the building.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Nice. So it was a whole outage.
Yeah, I guess it was an outage.
But yeah, my whole... it's more likely my brother's gonna hear this, not my mom.
not my mom. What's up Rodney? What up Rod? Big Rod. It's good to see you buddy. My brother
Big Rodney. Big Rodney. He's 6'8". And he's 10 years old. My cousin Timmy is 6'8". He's
He's one of those really tall guys that is injured all the time because he's too tall.
Do you guys ever know a guy who has a cousin or a nephew or something and he can't stop
talking about how big he is?
No.
You don't know what I mean?
Where it's like, "Oh, I have this, my nephew, I mean this kid's a hoss.
He's 6'5, he's 10 years old, he's headed straight to the league."
You don't know anybody like that?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that's always so funny to me.
Yeah, that's how my uncles would talk about my 6'8 cousin.
- My six foot eight cousin.
- Of your cousin's growth.
Well, if you have a big cousin, that's the,
see if everybody in your family was six foot eight,
nobody would give a fuck.
- Right.
- But you have a six foot eight cousin,
it becomes kind of the only thing
that your, that uncles care about.
- When you get together, yeah.
- Uncles love big nephews.
- Uncles love, yeah, a big kid.
- Uncles heart big nephews.
(laughing)
That's just the truth of the matter, dude.
That's in an uncle's blood.
- Yep.
- That's in their DNA genes.
Yeah, uncles love to talk about like how
like the football season's going.
And uncles literally will forget a niece's name.
Yeah, uncles will be like, "Oh, Pete!"
Hand it over to what the fucker over there.
"And a girl, girl Pete."
You knows.
Your name, you know your name.
You look so much like your mother.
You-ness.
Eustace!
Girl...
Manette.
Yeah.
My cousin was really big.
I know, I think you would like this.
I just saw this comedy special.
It's called Manette.
It's about a woman.
You might want to check this out.
You'll like it.
It's about girls.
I don't know what it's about.
There's an awesome plot twist about 30 minutes in, too.
I think you're really going to like it.
Oh, right.
So you've been going to the mall lately?
That's great.
Alright, Pete, get over here.
I'm gonna fuck you up.
Take your clothes off.
Take your pants off.
You know there's a no pants house.
Let's get you oiled up.
Inspired by the Japanese.
I drew a big ring on the living room floor.
And we can cover it with a rug.
Hey, what are you doing?
What are you doing in my house with your clothes on?
Get in the bathroom and put your fucking singlet on.
Put your singlet on.
Put your big sumo diaper on.
We're wrestling today.
It's 2 p.m.
Come on with family!
Put your singlet on!
Put your big sumo diaper on!
It's 2pm, what are you doing?
It's Thanksgiving!
Get your fucking sumo clothes on!
What are you fucking doing?
When you're at Uncle Ralph's house, you know it's sumo.
Oh, I hate it. I hate going to Uncle Ralph's house.
I hate having to throw the sand for respect.
Uh-huh.
I hate having to like...
I hate when he gets those highlights in him.
I've seen him. I hate when we have to do a fire dance. Yeah. Hey, Uncle. Where's the rest of the family?
Oh, I sabotaged their cars. They're not showing up for a few hours
We're gonna get some really good wrestling in Pete. You're going pro. You're gonna hit the pro American sumo wrestling market. I
found this
Working at the supermarket and he's gonna come over in about 10 minutes and you're gonna beat the shit out of them, dude
They should have an American sumo wrestling league like the they probably like it should be like X. Yeah, they do
- I do, you know what it's called?
The freakin' line to order at McDonald's.
- Oh, there we go.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
- Hey. - Wow.
- Hey, Big Pete, I don't know,
I saw someone at the grocery store today,
he might've been like six foot 10.
You think you could take him?
- I think you're not that big anymore, Pete.
- You think you, yeah, I don't know.
I think I'm gonna go be his uncle now.
- I think I'm gonna pick you up
'cause I know you don't even have your learner's permit yet.
Actually, fuck it, you can drive.
We're headed to the grocery store.
You're gonna kill this guy.
There can only be one big guy in town.
- Look, I know the guy, I know the butcher.
He's gonna let us go into the freezer.
We're gonna have an ice cold sumo match.
(laughing)
- Ice sumo.
- Look, I've combined-- - That's the American
sumo league.
It's 32 degrees. - Cold sumo.
- It's cross nations. - Frozen sumo.
Combined I've combined curling and sumo and we're gonna watch you fucking 400 pounds six foot eight body
Slide across the floor of the butcher's meat closet
We've cleared out we've cleared out a big section
We're gonna give you some we're gonna feed you some raw steaks. You know in Japan they call this football
Just plowing is his pickup truck through the front of the supermarket just where's the big guy?
Where's that big guy I saw a few weeks ago
Sir, I don't
Give me the biggest guy in the store
Big guy trench coat really really a really high voice trying to buy alcohol
Kind of boyish features
It kind of looked like a little guy in the face, but then a big guy in the body
Where is that big guy? I think he might have had that Beetlejuice disease
The one with the you when you get the shrunken head
But your body's the same size and your head's got like a big ponytail. I think he might have had that
I'm talking Beetlejuice from the movie not from the whack pack. I know what I'm dying. I oh, I know the whack pack
I've recruited a few fucking people for I would stir its whack back. Did you see that beetle juice is suicidal?
What what dude he came out and did an interview and he was like well not gonna do an impression
Yeah, you know what he sounds like and he was like
Yeah, pretty sad pretty sad thought about thought about ending it all oh
Do you know just come on?
Well, I mean when you're fucking it when it wouldn't a fucking
Guy who makes people ride the sibyan turns you into a circus freak of course you can be fucking suicidal
I think he was born a circus freak dude I
Don't think I don't think I'm a normal life look like he could have led a normal life
You think so yeah, I think he could have been like people making a box and shit
No, he could have just like worked it like the store or something, but like maybe you're right
He could have worked at the grocery store
Nah, dude, he likes it. He gets to like fucking...
I think he...
That's true. He was in True Crime. He was in True Crime Streets of LA.
I think he fucked Pamela Anderson.
Yeah.
I believe that.
I think that happened.
Yeah, I was there. I set him up.
Yeah.
Yeah, I said, "Pamela, I know this guy."
He's like a basketball player type. I think you guys would get along really great. He's an athlete.
Yeah.
He was a pro boxer for a little bit. He's done some radio.
He's in a pack, you know like the rat pack. He's in like then, you know, they'd like the rat pack and the brat pack
He's in like one of those things. He's kind of looking up. All right. Look I you're gonna have to go into this trick room though
It's the only room I have
Just I'm telling you only look at him through this this fun house mirror. Yeah
Yeah, where this where these these fish eye lens classes yeah
Yeah, he kind of looks like a fish eye lens guy
beat
Let's say that cuz we're best friends. Yeah
Yeah
Yeah, I love being best friends with you Pat, but I can't wait to make you my husband
It's not gonna happen. It's already
I'm gonna I'm gonna call Comcast right now and I'm turn off. I'm gonna turn off your walls
You can't turn off my wall. I will have them turn your walls off. You're not get comcast can't come can I wall hat here?
They're gonna. He's gonna turn on a floor. You're gonna fall furniture is coming off next
Don't call them again. I don't want to why
Why not? I don't want to I want to have a
Conversation I don't want to listen to you scream at a robot why why that's kind of because is already buddy because I don't do
anything all week
That's true. This is the only time I get to talk to my friends, right?
That is true. Listen and this and playing DS games online. You just right you just catch up then. Yeah. All right
What are you guys doing?
I showed my penis to four people this morning three people last night and then on Wednesday to two more people
I found a girl in town. You're found a urine
You I found a European mouse. Yeah
I'm not Australian. I'm not Australian. I would not pee in my mouth.
I found a new place to pee, guys.
I found a new hole in my body where pee goes.
Do you think Australian people pee in their own mouths because their toilet's flushed the wrong way?
Yeah.
Yeah, and the pee comes out the wrong way. It comes out of the mouth.
Yeah, the pee comes out counterclockwise.
It comes out the balls first.
first. Do you think Australian people watch... Other than normal American people where their
pee goes out the balls last. You think it touches the balls last? Yeah. No, the pee comes out
the balls... The spout on your balls? The pee just taps the balls as it goes by like you're
walking the hot dog way and tagging the top of the doorway. You don't have the spout? It's
just like I was here, you know? Showing off. You guys are... You don't have the spout on
I'm gonna drain your balls just as soon as you fucking sign that dotted line for our marriage
certificate buddy, because I'm saving myself.
No, because no, you didn't want a prenup.
You will not take these from me.
I want some pre-nut in my mouth.
I'm gonna touch your little prenup.
You have to sign a prenup because I don't want these gone.
I want you to sign my peanut.
How about that?
I want you to come over, I'm gonna get you a sharpie, you're gonna sign my peanut.
You're gonna do an Andre the Giant, you're gonna stand there and go, "Would anybody like a peanut?"
Yeah, I'm gonna give you my peanut.
Hey listen, on the TV I was watching the Princess Bride and I saw a guy on there who's a little bit bigger than you.
A little bit bigger than you, I'm gonna say.
We need to figure out how to get you into the TV.
Look, I got this PlayStation VR thing.
No, Oscar, look, look on the TV, he's only like, you know, 6 or 8 inches tall.
Yeah, but look at him compared to the other guys.
Well, but they're, see, they're like 4, 4, 3 inches tall.
No, they're just far away.
I mean, you got him, you got him standing up.
That's cause the TV's outside and we're sitting in the living room
cause I moved everything out of the living room for him to make room for the sumo ring.
So, congrats.
Hey, look, Wallace Shawn's pretty fucking tall.
I mean, look at this guy.
I don't know, that guy, that guy's a, that guy's a little bit bigger than him.
There's this little guy, I think his name is Gromit, but then this guy Wallace is pretty big, you know, comparatively.
I don't know, like it doesn't, I mean...
Uncle, he's standing on all fours.
But like, he sits around and eats cheese all the time.
Hey look, he's standing on all fours, he's standing on all fours though.
Look, if he stood up on two legs, he'd probably be a little bit taller.
Look at how small those crackers look next to him, I mean, Jesus Christ.
Look, he's on the moon, he's like...
You can see the curvature of the moon, that's how big he is.
is
seen this movie honey I shrunk the kids look how fucking big this Rick Moranis
guy is okay look he's compared to his kids we're gonna get you to fight this
guy all right I found his address between his big his big nephew and just
any tall guy you could find yeah I'm flying you out to China you're gonna
to fight Yao Ming. One round, feet only. It's his rule.
Look, Rick Moranis was tall in Honey I Shrunk the Kids, but look at him next to the rest
of these Ghostbusters. I think something's wrong with my TV.
Bill Murray might be pretty big. Oh fuck.
Yeah, I tried to schedule a fight with you and Bill Murray, but no one would believe
me. Harold Ramis, technically the biggest, but he passed away. May he rest in peace.
We're going to dick up his bones and you're going to punch him. Just the proof that you
can do it. Digging up Andre the Giant's bones and you're going to dominate him. Okay, you
understand me? You're going to get on top of him and you're going to jump around. I tried
to get Dan Aykroyd, but he was too busy getting sucked off by a ghost. You're going to fight
Harold Ramis's bones. You're fighting Leslie Jones and it's not gonna be
televised. We need to make sure it's not televised. If it's televised you will go
to jail. We'll just say you're doing some Andy Kaufman thing. That would be funny if Andy Kaufman came back.
You know if he picked a Leslie Jones type out of the audience to fight and she just
just threw him out a window. She just ate him one bite. There was one fight where
he lost I think. Was it to a big girl? I think so. Wouldn't have been me dude I would have.
Yeah, because you're a little girl. You're a big girl. You're a little girl. Put on your
big girl pants. Nah, I don't have any girl pants. Girls wear dresses. But I'm also not
a girl so I don't have a dress. You don't have anything? Yeah, I don't have a dress.
If I did it'd be made out of dollars because I'm so rich too. Oh, I just realized there
- There was a, I think that guy's dead now,
but there used to be this guy in Nashua,
it was this store called Dollar Bills,
and it was this guy who just bought everything wholesale
from other--
- It's like a store almost.
- Yeah, it's like a store, but he would buy--
- You buy things wholesale, you sell them for a markup.
- No, no, he would buy things using money and dollar bills.
That's why they called the store that.
- It made no sense at all.
Yeah, he would buy things, he would buy drinks
on a big pallet, right?
He would buy a ton of 'em, and then he would sell them
to you for like two or three dollars each.
- Damn it.
- No, he would buy things that didn't sell at other stores,
and then it would just be a warehouse store like that.
- Oh yeah.
- His whole thing was he wore an umbrella hat
that had little dollar bills that would hang off of it.
- Whoa.
- And I thought he was the biggest celebrity on earth
when I was six, and then my mom met him.
My mom met him at a flea market,
and I was like, "Holy shit, it's a dollar bill!"
And he gave me a hat.
He gave me one of his umbrella hats.
- Whoa. - No way.
- Do you still have it?
- No. - Why not?
I broke that shit. I broke that shit like immediately.
I have a fucking huge head. Even as a kid I had a big head.
So you broke the hat by just putting it on your head?
And I probably, I was not good at keeping my toys. All my toys would break.
That's a powerful head, dude.
Yeah.
If it can't even, if, if, can't even handle an adult hat as a child, you're the chosen one.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah. There's a crown somewhere in like some fucked up-
Hey nephew, I've been listening to this podcast and there's this guy who could break a hat with just his head.
We're gonna get you wrestling this fucking idiot.
They call him the Hammerhead!
[Laughter]
He must be pretty tall.
He's gotta be pretty tall.
He's breaking heads with his head.
Oh my god.
I feel like my head is proportionate to somebody who is like...
6 inches bigger than me.
Your head's gotten bigger, dude.
It's gotten bigger since I've known you.
It's from all this HGH I've been taking.
It's from all the knowledge you've been building up in there.
All this knowledge and this HGH.
I've been taking HGH
a
head right now like he's having like a epiphany I he's never read a book yeah
- no I read a book - wires are touching in his head right now that have never read
I read oh you know what my dad was a big dog a little dog you say you're dead it's
a it's John Glazer's John Glazer's my dead dad was in ZZ top that's not the
That's the last book you read?
That's the last book I read, yeah.
Wow.
Whoa, dude.
How long ago is that?
That book is mostly pictures.
What was the last book you read, Caleb?
Moby Dick.
I don't like to read.
I'd rather have an audiobook.
You didn't finish it.
What happens on the last page?
Everybody dies.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, I read, fuck, what is this book called?
I had to read it from my Latinx literature class.
Latinx.
Latinx literature.
It's called like...
He's freaking out right now.
No, it's got a fucking name.
It's about like these migrant workers who work on like a...
This is the most active I've seen Patrick on a video call ever.
He's trying to think of a book.
He's literally using every part of his body to remember the name of a book.
It's like these like migrant workers and they work on a boat and there's bad conditions and
it's a new...
Moby Dick.
bad conditions.
Uh...
It's about these migrant workers.
And there's actually bad conditions on the boat they work on.
In the book there's bad book...
There's conditions that are books.
Bad some things happen to...
in the boat?
And they're Latinx, I think.
Oh my god, what's it called?
And it's right next to him and it's called
Latinx Workers on a Boat with a Bad Condition.
It's called I'm on a Boat,
the book.
It was on my mom's Kindle. I can look this up.
Oh my god. You don't have to look it up,
Pat. You really don't. I don't think it's going to do anything for anybody.
No, I have to prove that I read a book. This is the last book I read.
The Vegetarian by Han Kang or Han Kong.
Han Kong.
It's 10 best books. Fuck, I don't know my mom's Amazon, Pat.
I can't believe that you're just trying to...
Just don't worry about it, Pat. We can move on. We can do something else.
We'll do another episode about it. We'll do a whole hour.
You can describe the plot and stuff. Get off your phone.
It's important to have this fisheye lens up on Patrick when we're recording because we can see...
That's right.
Immediately he moved a hand to his penis.
(laughing)
- I thought about opening this up,
just showing you guys my little spike
and just so you guys could see how little my wiener looks.
- I've seen your penis.
I've seen your penis before.
- No, but in these shorts specifically,
it's looking, I mean it's dire, dude.
- Things are pretty, yeah.
- Like it's not looking good.
Nobody's checking me out, you know?
- Well you never know, dude.
Some people could like that kind of thing.
- Normally I like jack off a little bit
before I walk out of the apartment,
just so when people see my--
- I got rid of the Kindle app.
- Well, people normally--
(laughing)
Normally people see your big bald head--
- I'm never gonna know what that fucking book is called.
- Normally, Caleb, people see your big bald head
with the cut on the back of it from falling out of bed
and they go, "Oh, he has the biggest penis ever
"on the top of his body."
(laughing)
- Thank you for saying that.
- Oh, no, 'cause that was the second to last book I read.
'Cause then the last one was some Juno Diaz book.
That was the last one we read in class.
That's the kid from Spy Kids.
Oscar Wow?
Oscar Whoa?
Oscar Wee-oo?
Nowadays they call that Oscar Hit the Whoa.
No, and then after that there was some fucking
magical realism book.
You've never read any of these books?
I read it! I read it!
I read the whole thing.
Books for class definitely don't count.
Books for class don't count and the last book I read was My Dead Dad was in ZZ Top.
Yeah.
I'm writing a book right now.
I'm writing a manifesto.
God, I should...
Don't say that.
Should I read more? I don't know.
It's my 10,000 follower manifesto.
When I hit 10,000 I'm releasing my manifesto.
Why should you read more?
Because you look at your phone 23 hours a day.
No, I don't.
Yeah, dude. You're like...
I read articles.
What's the last article you read?
You read clickable articles.
A Vulture article doesn't fucking count either.
- Like a magazine.
(laughing)
- Yeah, okay, that counts.
- Okay, then I'll give you that.
- A Thrasher article doesn't count,
a Mad Magazine article, a cracked article.
Yeah, I'm actually quite a reader.
I'm quite the reader.
- Reading the words that says on a shirt,
it's an article of clothing,
but it doesn't count as an article, okay?
So you can't say The Exorcist,
the shirt you're wearing right now,
doesn't count. - I don't need to read.
- I think you do.
- You should read.
- I think you would be a better person.
Patrick's faking his own death now to avoid reading.
I don't either.
[Laughter]
Oh, he's turning into a pig again.
It'd be funny if Pat read, like, one book and it killed him.
I read the Transformation!
I read fucking Kafka. I read that fucking...
Metamorphosis?
I read the bug one. The Metamorphosis.
I read the back of the Transformers DVD, you're right.
It's the Metamorphosis, that's what it's called.
Yeah, the Transformation.
The Transformation? I don't think you read it.
I read it. I read it.
Yeah, I read Moldy Dick.
[laughter]
I did.
It's just the facts.
I read The Catcher in the Guy.
[laughter]
I read The Street.
I read that book, The Street.
I read My Son Also Rises.
[laughter]
I was thinking it'd be funny to tell somebody like,
like tell your son,
like, uh, listen,
If I kill myself, I want you to know, it was not me,
it was like the government.
- It was Ernest Hemingway.
No, it was the government.
If I died in a parent suicide, it was not me.
I have no suicidal tendencies or ideations.
It's just, it was the government.
And then like the next day, died,
like jacking off, doing asphyxiation.
And he walks in and he's like,
why would the CIA do this?
They hated my dad so much they made it look like he was jacking off.
Oh the CIA putting gay porn on my dad's computer.
Yeah.
I read Huckleberry Qui-Gon Jinn.
Dude, we need to start a book.
I read a book.
No, I read a book.
Dude, I read War and the Other Thing.
and the other one. I read War and Pete. I read War and the Girls. War and Pete. Yeah I read
War and Pete. Yeah that book by War and Pete. The Art of Stores. No dude I'm really into
Cormac McCarthy I read Blood the Sibian. I was gonna when Charles Portis died I was gonna
I was gonna read some of his books.
I don't know who that is.
I did, I did genuinely, I was gonna get into,
somebody posted like an excerpt of something he wrote
and it was very funny.
And I was gonna start reading his books.
I was gonna go to the public library,
the Boston Public Library and get a card.
No, that was not a transaction.
Did you guys realize?
No, I was gonna do it and then like.
You read the script for The Mask
and you were like, this is a book
and I can't wait to see what's next
from this young up and coming author.
- Jim Carrey.
- Yeah, Jim Carrey.
- You guys realize that, I just realized that
Stephen King and Stephen Hawking have almost the same name.
You could just add Haw.
- And Stephen Hofstetter.
- Also the same.
- He's also has three geniuses.
- And King Stephen, the king of the castle
from medieval times.
- Oh my God.
- Stephen Hofstetter brutally destroys Stephen Hawking
on Epstein's Island.
Dude, I just remembered this.
Stephen Hawking heckling Steve Hofstetter.
How about you tell some jokes?
Next.
Stop dogging, I'll blow a drum.
Boo.
And Hofstetter could be he could be like is it is it okay to make Stephen Hawking
jokes now that he's a like on Epstein's Island yeah they've that's what they
buried no no cuz that's a fucked up part is like he didn't somebody could have
just wheeled in there he can't do anything about it
yeah that's true they can make a big frame that dude for fucking anything
that's true right they could have put him fucking anywhere like his maid down
the stairs or something? He had sex with the maid. No he didn't! He has the greatest alibi of all time. You just mixed up, by the way,
Stephen Hawking with that movie, or that documentary, The Staircase. Oh, okay. Yeah,
didn't Stephen Hawking kill Nicole Brown Simpson? Yeah, no, Stephen Hawking, yeah,
cuz he had those little paperclip legs and he ran in the Olympics.
Stephen Hawking did not have sex with anybody.
His maid put like porn on his brain or whatever.
I don't know how his computer works.
And was like, "Do you like this?"
And he was like, "Bless."
And she just put more porn on.
And then his wife was like, "Finally a fucking reason I can divorce this guy. Oh my God."
And she got out of there with like half his money.
Damn. Goddamn.
- Damn, and half the universe.
(laughing)
- Oh my God.
- Yeah, she also got, she got freaking time.
- Half his knowledge.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- She just uploaded it to the thumbnail.
- She got time travel in the divorce.
- She got the secrets.
- Yeah.
- I was, I, we mentioned Jim Carrey and I just remembered,
I just had a flashback to this creative writing class
I was in at my old college, where,
I can't believe I've never,
I know I've never told this story on the podcast.
Yeah, you don't talk about your old college at all.
Yeah, UNCW, I was in this like, beginner creative writing class my freshman year.
And we did the icebreaker thing and everyone went around and it was basic, your name, your age, and a fun fact about yourself.
And there was one guy who was like a veteran and he had a dog and he was like, "Yeah, my name's Dan, I'm 43 years old."
"I'm Lieutenant Dan."
(laughing)
My fun fact is, I have this dog because,
yep, I have PTSD.
(laughing)
And then immediately after him was this like,
this like pale, like see-through white nerd.
And he was like--
- Cameron.
- His name was Cameron actually.
- That's not true. - I don't remember his name.
But he was like, yeah, I'm Arthur or whatever.
I'm 19 years old and fun fact about me,
"Well, I guess it's that I do a pretty killer Jim Carrey impression."
And then he got up from his desk and did...
He did... He was like...
"DO NOT GO IN THERE!"
[Laughter]
And then he gave the veteran guy PTSD.
That's what my platoon leader said about the bunkers.
[Laughter]
But then he was like, "And if anyone ever wants to see, I do a pretty mean Ace Ventura also."
And he did it a couple more times throughout the semester.
It's a good one to pull out, dude.
That'll make people like you.
Every once in a while, you just gotta throw out a little carry.
Yeah.
I'm sure everybody here is a comedy fan, you know?
Exactly.
"Okay then!"
You know, like he says.
"Oh, well."
"Oh!"
You know, like Ace Ventura says.
"Oh, the..."
"I agree!"
agree. Like Case Ventura said, "Somebody get this friggin' animal out of my office, I'm
trying to do work!" You know, what Jason Ventura said, "I love animals!" You know, "I'm going
to the zoo!" What Jim said, "Give me my mask back. Where's my mask?" "If you don't give
Give me back my mask.
I'm gonna feed you full of- I'm gonna stuff you full of pills.
I neen to be green.
Give me my mask, Bask.
Give me my back smacks.
Give me my animal mask.
I'm about to go- I'm gonna- I'm gonna beat- I'm getting dirty.
I'm getting all dirty.
Where's my- Where's my pet donkey on the mask?
I'm the mask detective.
There's blood on that. Somebody clean me!
*laughter*
There's shit in there! Somebody wipe me!
Smells bad in there!
*laughter*
Where's my mask so I can go smell that room?
I'm smelly, Batman!
My favorite number is 20.
*laughter*
I'm 20 years old.
I'm Andy Kaufman!
I'm Mandy Kaufman!
*laughter*
I'm Mandy Kaufman and I'm the Max.
My name's Max the Mask and I'm the detective.
And I'm a liar liar pants on fire.
And I'm God too. I'm Mask Almighty.
Where's my God mask?
I gotta go green. And I'm the guy from Click.
Yeah I'm gonna click you and I'm Judy and Jill.
Judy I'm happy Gottfried. Where's the funny people on the mask?
When I get my mask on I'm super bad, I'm officer grown-ups
Hey, I was watching this movie grown-ups and uh
Runners - and this this cop came over and uh you pretty tall pretty tall
They called him Shaquille a key
Yeah, let's just, let's, alright, now let's just go back through all the episodes we've
done and just do a joke from each one right now.
Okay.
From each one?
Uh, that...
Oh wait, no, we got...
I'm the mask and that hamster is too damn hungry!
We have one that covers it all.
The poop guy.
Alright.
There we go.
Yeah, the poop guy just showed up.
That should be good.
Uh huh.
Yeah, he ate crap.
The poop guy ate some crap.
Yeah.
The guy got sepsis because he got crap in a cup.
Yeah, cut.
Yeah, sepsis.
From the movies.
But doctor, I thought you said I had pepsis.
And he drinks pepsis.
How's that?
I thought you said my blood was pepsis.
[Laughter]
Nurse, we have an emergency.
This man's blood has become pepsis.
[Laughter]
Do you mean septic?
No, you fucking dumb bitch.
What the fuck are you talking about?
It's Pepsi's. It's brown.
Like a Pepsi.
You know, like Pepsi.
And it tastes delicious.
Oh, he tastes so good, I just need a couple straws in here.
Give me a straw, stat.
I need a scalpel and a straw.
I wouldn't want to see this Pepsi go to waste.
Give me a straw.
I heard this man down to the cafeteria. I heard you guys had a Pepsi tank out back. I'm gonna head out there and take a sip if you don't mind.
Oh my god. He's going into Pepsi shock. He has Pepsi shock syndrome. He's shocked by the flavor.
Pepsi shock sounds like Pepsi's like energy drink in the 90s
Yeah, it doesn't yeah an energy drink called toxic shock
Yeah, that would absolutely be a bang flavor yeah toxic shock syndrome shock bang AIDS AIDS bang
Bang toxic shock tastes like
When you leave a tampon in yeah
Keep going okay keep going so I didn't have to finish that now come back bang full-body degloving
Bang I move away from the mic to breathe in hey
Chocolate bang
Some some stay dry and others drink the bang
No
Some drink bang and others drink Pepsi.
Some drink Pepsi, others drink Coca, drink Dr. Pepper.
Some drink Sprite, Sprite is lemon, lime, flay, avert.
- Cranberry sometimes.
- Cranberry when Lebron's involved.
Alright, bye.
- Alright, bye everybody.
[LAUGHTER]