Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
Premium content!
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately!
[Explosion]
[Music]
This better be worth it.
Yup.
[Music]
You already played this one. I thought you were going to play a new one.
Does he just, wait, so he just put Tom Hanks into an R- it's not that funny.
It's pretty funny.
Well, we're just playing this now.
It's El Toro, Peter.
Let's just watch all the videos on your Instagram.
Peter Gramis.
Yeah, let's do that.
Let's just do that.
Okay.
By the way, I started a TikTok.
You did?
You started a TikTok?
Yeah, you want to see my TikTok?
There's a guy doing a, he does a tail whip on a scooter down El Toro.
I saw, Tailwhip is pretty good against Onyx.
I accidentally uploaded my TikTok twice because it said it didn't upload and then it actually
did upload and it completely fucking lied to me.
What is your, what's your account?
I'll show you.
Caleb_Pits_Most_Evil.
And this is it.
I put a selfie on it.
It's pretty good.
and this is it
it's pretty good
it's good
so i'm basically becoming a tiktoker now. that's really good. you guys both started tiktoks
yeah it's fucking in a new wave dude
that's how you do now
I'm so behind the times I just started Instagram.
You pick your favorite song.
That's so fucking stupid.
Today I don't feel like doing...
I love Bruno Mars. I like his outfits and his hat.
Today I don't feel like...
And honestly, I made that yesterday
and I was just telling you about how bad I felt yesterday.
So it was like completely true to life.
Like I was not doing any kind of acting.
I completely felt like,
Today I don't feel like doing anything.
Yeah.
Imagine... Well, I don't know what word of these songs
songs came out, but if you were like say you were you were like dating Bruno
Mars right, so imagine that that might be tough for you to imagine but but
he releases this song grenade and he's saying I would catch a grenade for you.
I would jump in front of a train for you. I doing a version all these and then
and then and then it's next and you're like oh my God, he loves me so much and
a month later releases a new song today. I don't feel like doing anything yeah
because he got hit by a train and he jumped on a grenade. Yeah right. It's
- That's true.
- Does Bruno Mars still make music?
- You don't wanna do any,
you don't even wanna catch some grenade for me anymore?
- Bruno Mars does all this Super Bowl shit now.
- Football?
- He does all this like performing at the Super Bowl.
I think the last time I ever heard,
no, Bruno Mars does still make music.
He had that really good song last year.
- He has brunomars.com?
- He has that song.
♪ Happy birthday to you Tom ♪
- That's not Bruno Mars.
That does look like a Bruno Mars music video though.
- Yeah.
- Oh yeah.
- It's well directed.
- He has a new--
♪ Don't believe me just watch ♪
in Bruno Mars to help you not do anything, the lazy song I learned it's called.
Is it does he am I am I tripping or does he make the music video and he's hanging
out with a bunch of monkeys? I don't remember. Monkeys wearing business suits is it that one?
I think that might be it. I learned the other day. I'm thinking of that Pulp Fiction poster with the two monkeys.
He has an album cover with a gorilla on it. Somebody told me the other day that
you know that song "gold all on my watch" that one? That Trinidad James song?
- "Trinidad James." - "All Gold Everything."
- Yeah. - Yeah.
So because he says, "Don't believe me, just watch,"
he's credited as a writer.
- Well, that's not really how it worked.
The guy, Mark Johnson or whatever--
- Ronson? - Mark Ronson,
the other guy in that song,
is friends with "Trinidad James,"
and he said, "And 'Trinidad James' had like no money,"
'cause he blew all of his money from his one-and-one.
- Oh, is that how it is? - And he was like,
"Here, I'll put you as a credit on this song,
"and we'll put 'Don't Believe Me, Just Watch' in it."
- I have a credit on that song, too.
of me too because they say the yeah really - for the only one who doesn't
have a credit on that fucking song yeah not the only one in my world but in
this room close to it that's like a being having be having dinner with Jay-z
and being like am I the only like guy in here is not the first black billionaire
what is he the first black billionaire I think I would assume so that there's a
Bill Gates. What? What the fuck are you talking about? Bill Gates. What? What? He's a black guy.
Bill Gates isn't black. Bill Gates is white as snow. Bill Gates is a white guy.
Yeah. You look at that guy and you think that that's a white guy. Dude, he's a honky.
You think that's a honky. He's a complete honky. He's a peckerwood. Look at him.
I don't think... peckerwood is not... peckerwood only applies in jail, I thought.
I don't think so. I think it is. I think that's only a jail. And I think he should
be in jail. For what? Microchipping? Mm-hmm. No, micro-stofting is what he did. Oh,
you're right. I was thinking of microchipper. No, no, the microchipper does that. He's the
king of micro-stofting. Wait a minute, hold on, hold on. Why is the microchipper wearing
glasses? What? What? Like Bill Gates? I don't understand what you're saying. I think under
his mask the much or do you think it might be Bill Gates yeah you said that
like Bill Gates like glasses or is like Bill Gates is thing it is this thing
he's a nerd I don't think it's a black nerd is the first black nerd billion
there's Microsoft Bill Gates is the first black nerd billionaire did Steve Steve
Jobs and Bill Gates do they have beef they did really yeah Steve job they had
apples one of them had an apple I'm gonna put you know I'm putting you know
- You know what, I'm off today because I--
- You're off today?
- I forgot that we were recording and I found,
it's a Guinness Nitro Cold Brew, and I had a day beer.
- Day beer will ruin your shit.
- Yeah.
- Day beer can fuck you up, man.
- I think to fix this, we should all go get day beers.
- I don't think so.
- I don't, I mean, I don't hate the idea,
but we'd have to pause.
- We could pause and then we all go on a little--
- I don't wanna do that.
- We all go on a little field trip.
I don't want to go on a mid episode.
Wouldn't it be kind of funny if we were like, "Okay, we'll be right back," and then it just
started with cracking noises?
Wouldn't that be kind of funny?
That'd be awesome.
I don't know if it would be funny.
That would be so awesome.
We live so close to a bodega.
You spoiled it.
Now we have to think about a different funny noise to start with.
Okay, all right.
We'll still have the crack, but we'll say a different thing.
We'll come up.
We can come up with something.
We have a-- We'll come up with something.
It'll take five minutes to go get beers and then come back, and then you'll hear--
I'm so tired.
We'll get beers.
from Los Angeles. Oh my god, maybe it's a Hollywood producer. It might be. Hello?
Hi, yes, Patrick. Yeah? What's going on? Hey, yeah, my name's Noel. Everybody calls me Doogie, though.
Doogie? Yeah, Doogie, uh-huh. Yeah. I got your number from Big Red, our other neighbor.
are you doing today man? Doing good. Oh super. Super, well hey I know you're probably busy
just real quick. I'm new to the neighborhood. I moved in across the street and Big Red was
saying he might be able to help me put some tinting. I got an 18 wheeler. Tint the windows
in there. I know how to do it and everything. Maybe if you could just give me a hand or
just for some time maybe next couple days or something like that.
Alright YouTube Monks. Yeah, yeah. Is it? Is this? Is this LPC?
Okay Theodore. Oh no, Doogie. Doogie? Or Noel. Or Noel? This isn't LPC?
who the fuck is LPC get off the phone okay I'll get off the phone he had the voice
mod on yeah you think it's hard to do that I don't I don't know guys I just
got a call from Spotify calling back oh my god okay pick up okay hello I was
told to get off the phone I apologize about that I got told to get off the
- I'm on the phone, what's going on?
- Oh no, yeah, I was just trying to reach Patrick.
Is this Patrick up?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
- Oh, okay.
Well, I travel with this 30 year old macaw bird.
He goes everywhere with me, never leaves.
The 18 wheeler, and I was hoping to maybe put
like some louvers in the window on his area, you know?
Maybe like a visor, and I could just use a hand with it.
Yeah, I could help out.
Oh, great.
Great, great. Yeah, I'll let you pick the farm and everything.
I was hoping to make it say Nicodemus.
That's his name, you know?
Like maybe an old English style lettering, like a tattoo almost, you know?
Something like that would be sweet.
Yeah.
I should warn you though.
Nico, that's what I call him,
he will talk like wild.
He'll talk to you.
He'll talk like wild.
And he'll communicate great.
This guy's gotta be joking.
So uh...
It's totally full of crap.
This guy talks fucking crazy.
Who the fuck is this?
It's so confusing.
Is he on the phone with an animal?
Hello?
And if you play like a gulag station on the radio, that bird will sing like wah-wah-wah.
How does he do that?
What is he doing?
What is this bullshit?
And this...
A gong gong gong a bing gong gong gong a bing a gong.
Oh my god, is that T-Pain?
and
You wanna go with a nano carbon tint on there?
What do you think?
Or maybe--
- I could do a nano carbon tint.
- Perfect, that's what I was thinking.
That's what I was thinking.
I always do a deep dip on the pigment.
Maybe with a ceramic infused variant.
Like Big Red had our neighbor here.
He's got the same thing.
- It might not be tea, it's not got hip hop.
- How much butter?
- How much sputter?
- Sputter?
- Yeah, sputter. - Personally, I don't know
why Patrick's giving him the time of day.
- I know, it's probably a scam call.
- I like copper, so maybe some copper sputtering.
- Copper sputtering?
I got two tons of copper sputtering.
- What the hell, what is Patrick even talking about?
- Oh, well I'm in the right place, heck of a deal.
Heck of a deal, I could tell you right here.
Oh man, as long as we achieve glare reduction.
Oh, and that reminds me.
- This guy's off his rocker.
- The absorbance reflectance ratio,
you think approximately.
No, the reason I ask is 'cause I'd love to have a good
reading on the BTU meter.
You know, once I get that thing, it's gotta be right.
(laughing)
Could you repeat all that?
(sounds of a jet engine)
Oh yeah, just across the board.
Because refraction is key, of course.
Across the board.
I don't have one of those
fancy spectrophotometers
and
I trust whatever we come up with
will give us the absorption we need.
(clears throat)
Oh! Quick question.
Does that remind you anything we could do
It's the Jerky Boys film.
Reflective film to get rid of the glare?
Well, because the bird loved his cream.
Oh, God, I think it's the Jerky Boys.
That's how I'm going to make a bet with you.
I'll bet you a hundred bucks.
This is the Jerky Boys.
No.
It's a Jerky Boys character.
Maybe a hybrid film.
That's a cliffhanger.
The right male puppets at home.
We are picture in picture.
We can work out, you know.
We're the cranky anchor of the Puerto Rican woman.
No, no, no.
That's an old Jewish grandma.
So what's a good time?
Maybe tomorrow?
About 5 o'clock.
5 o'clock.
Could do 5.
5 o'clock p.m.
I'm busy writing this down.
That sounds good.
You could get completely sucked into a coma.
I'm gonna check with that big red here.
As long as the guy's going, "What the fuck is it?"
If he's available.
Hold on.
I'm gonna try to get him right here.
'Cause I'm not sure.
But that sounds good to me.
So yeah, let's see.
We got that.
We're gonna tip.
And, uh, I'm gonna try to get him right here.
I'm gonna try to get him right here.
that
a pill.
Hey, yeah this is Noel and Patrick's gonna help us tint our windows tomorrow.
I just wanted to let you know.
Okay?
What do you want to do?
Tint the windows.
Tint all the windows tomorrow.
And he's gonna help us.
I'm just waiting about 5 o'clock.
Why don't you lay off you son of a bitch criminal?
Why don't you lay off of me?
I'm just letting you know.
You're a piece of shit.
Shit.
*sounds of a vacuum cleaner*
Oh, I said, "Patrick, anyway, it'll be fine. Don't you worry about a thing."
"And we'll achieve the UV block that makes the most sense."
*laughter*
"So we'll just get it dialed in."
"Get the nanocarbon up."
"Get the pig red in the mix."
"Get it all sputtered up."
*laughter*
I can smell the weed through the phone.
This guy's a stoner.
Total dope.
Do you want to take red or?
Yeah, yeah.
And you've got a spectro-
spectro-photometer, right?
I do.
Do we have spectro-photometers?
We don't have one of those.
The reason I ask is because I'm going for that
U-value as I said.
If you've got a BTU meter,
that'd be sweet.
I got that, I got it all
I think we have that, yeah
What do you mean you got it all?
I'll be in front and Nicodemus will be there flapping his wings, don't you worry about a thing
I'll pull the 18 wheeler right up in front
Oh, that's gonna be tight
That's the weirdest day of my life
Oh that sounds perfect, yeah
Alright, have a good night
You too, thank you
the
is walking up a lot of people
but i think i think you have a lot of people are expecting a report called
time at the phone line to picture of the group of people who are not capable of
that
it could be a little bit of a referral to the group of people who are
people who are
the
why the focus
cranky acres called the added to the jerky boys get right now they get your
phone number
uh... it must be the phone number we put out
I've never seen you just completely cocoon like that.
Yeah, that was crazy.
You're just losing your mind, dude.
Deer and headlights.
I get it.
That was amazing.
That was crazy.
I've also never seen you that happy in my entire life.
I know, I can't believe.
Look at him, he's beaming, dude.
Whoever set that up, I don't know if he, because I keep getting calls from Los Angeles and
I finally picking it.
I picked it up just to, you know, I picked it up to do a prank on a fan, but.
That's what you get.
Honestly, you spent the last two weeks doing, or last week doing pranks on people who call
you. This was your retribution.
Oh yeah.
This was finally-
From the king of it.
Yeah, you got revenged. You got fully revenged by-
I think that was the guy from Scream.
No, it was the guy, what's his name?
It was LPC. It had to be-
No, no, that was not LPC.
I don't know.
That was the hash-
That was like-
That was the hash-slinging slasher from SpongeBob.
No, it was that guy who does Indian prank call on YouTube and shit.
- Oh, the Jerky Boys.
- No, not the Jerky Boys.
- I'm telling you it was the Jerky Boys.
- You're being disrespectful to them.
- It was the Jerky Boys.
- I can't let it happen.
You're being disrespectful.
- No, that was clearly,
that was probably just some disgruntled factory worker.
- Yeah, some random guy calling you.
- It was Ownage Pranks.
(laughing)
- You got a call from Ownage Pranks.
- What a weird day.
- That was crazy.
- Yeah.
- That was awesome.
Whoever, if somebody set that up or something or.
- Think somebody paid Ownage Pranks?
I think you can pay him to give calls.
So whoever did that, that was awesome.
I wonder how they split up the money among themselves.
Yeah, the jerky boys.
I don't know how Ownage Pranks does that, how they split the money up.
Because there's the Indian guy, but then there's also the Vietnamese guy.
But then there's also the Chinese guy.
You know, it makes no sense.
Whoa.
That was crisp.
That was satisfying.
All right, hard reset, guys.
We got our beers.
reset no more fuckin no more getting weird all the joke we're just wasting our
fucking time trying to ruin our podcast we're done with that bullshit okay we're
no point with the losers calling us wasting our time destroying the episode
nope yep slackers slackers like this all around smoking weed probably sick no
good but he admits it but I love eating chips and sitting in my bed mmm what beer
- What figure are we rocking with today?
- I'm drinking a-- - Matt didn't even get a beer.
- I got a Truly Wildberry.
- Mm, you watching your figure?
- Yeah.
- And then you get a--
- I'm watching your figure too.
- Okay.
- Yeah, I'd like to watch your figure.
- You don't have to look through your kid's list.
- I'd like to watch you figure skate.
- Yeah, figure out how to figure skate.
- Mm-hmm.
- With no paint on.
- My dad tried to get me to do hockey when I was a kid
and he bought me skates.
- Tonsil hockey.
and
not okay to fuck them. Your dad made you wear full pads to play tonsil hockey with him.
That's what you did. And then you did it and he said you're underweight kid. You're gonna
have to put on weight for the season. You've got a long grueling tonsil hockey season ahead
of you. Tonsil hockey is very similar to... Your dad made me wear a maxi pad. That's not
how I would feel like I was a woman. Tonsil hockey with your dad is really similar to normal
hockey where you have to start playing when you're really young or else you won't get
good at it. Oh yeah. And Pat's dad understood that. Yeah. Yeah. My dad understood the assignment.
Yeah. Which was you have to wear. You have to wear. You have to wear. You have to wear
pads to make out. To do, well not make out. I'm making out. There's a winner and a loser
in tonsil hockey. It's a real game, okay. Now watch this. Now you're the loser because
I fucking did something cool and you just watched, bitch. It wasn't cool at all. I literally
flicked a lid. It wasn't cool. You never heard that that that expression? Oh I'm about to
flick my lid. I like literally just did it. It's not cool people say that when they're
about to ruin their life. No they don't say that. They say I'm about to flick my lid and
then they hit somebody and go to jail. I think it's flip your wig. No they oh I'm about to
flick my lid. No I'm about to flick my wig. Oh no it's flick my leg. Leg? It's when you
do something really funny like you know like a knee slapper. Yeah flick my leg. I think
that's a separate expression. Flick my lid I've been saying since I was a kid. Flip my
wig. No. It's a Husker Du album, Flip Your Wig. What does flipping your wig mean?
Probably the same thing. Losing it? Yeah. Losing that? Losing that thing we
don't mention. You know, shaking your head? No, like imagine I'm really lost.
Okay Cameron, you demonstrate. Like flipping your hair like this. But if I was
wearing a wig. But you don't have a wig on. If it was a wig. Yeah, but if I had a wig I
could flip it like that. I think I got a gym injury. Yeah? Yeah I think I hurt my arm.
You got a gym in jury? You got a BTS jury at your case? Your court case?
What is a BTS jury? BTS curry that sounds pretty good.
Mm-hmm. Bacon tomato sauce. Bacon tomato soup. Why isn't there a BLT tomato soup on the
market? I think there is. I guess the lettuce would not be so good. Yeah.
Yeah.
Lettuce is so good in soup.
What are you talking about?
Mayonnaise probably.
Oh my God.
I keep seeing on like...
Lettuce in broth.
Do you ever watch like Instagram reels?
Yeah.
And they got like the...
Well, I'm a TikTok star now, so I kind of have to.
Well, that's true, yeah.
I need to be cross-posting really because I'm trying to.
Well, you can make up to $1,200 doing Instagram reels.
I keep getting this ad for Instagram.
I keep getting a post.
Really?
Instagram reels are...
I don't know...
Instagram reels are like evil.
though, like whatever the like like algorithm is is very scary.
Yours is creepy. Mine is I do not know what happens of all these medical pages.
You follow you just became a that actually I do follow a bunch of pages
that are called like doctor shout out and it's mostly like a picture of like a
doctor like and he's like doing a peace sign. It's like what's up taking over
this account for the week, but then like every other post is like a post of like
a woman who look like looks like she has the chest burster from alien and it's
It's like what do you think is going on doctors?
I want now it just shows me Instagram reels like the suggested reels thing
that goes in between all the posts you view.
It's all like deformed dogs and stuff.
Yeah, the dog was short spine.
Oh, I hate that weird little dog.
Do you want to see like him the one that looks like a frog?
Yeah, there's I mean, there's that one.
There's also the ones with the twisted.
Those are the like popular.
Yeah, dog, but Instagram reels the like the like recommendation algorithm
has got me like I'm in I like know all the deep cut deformed dogs.
Really?
Do you want to see one that is crazy?
Of course.
Let me find it.
I just don't, honestly, deformed people, love them.
Deformed animals, no I don't like them.
No, you don't need to love them.
I don't need to like you.
Yeah, they're, look at this thing.
Is that the dog with?
Oh, fuck!
Oh, yeah, I've seen that one.
That's why you don't smoke cigarettes, that's why I quit.
That's so disgusting.
This dog's name is Arrow.
He lost his entire jaw, he's Ebert. He got Eberted.
Look at that.
Oh, dude, stop showing me that. He looks like the fucking, he looks like Dr. Tongue from
Day of the Dead. Wait, okay, hold on, show me, because I haven't seen him, show me him
again. Put it up closer. He has no bottom jaw. His tongue is flying out of the side
of his head. Oh, so his bottom jaw is broken? He literally looks exactly like the zombie
from the beginning of Day of the Dead. I don't think I would, I don't think I would adopt
that dog. No, I'd probably, I'd probably leave it wherever it is. I'm thinking about fostering,
and we've been thinking about fostering a dog. You already have a dog. I know
you're so greedy. I just want every I just I think I want I think I want fifty
dogs. He looks exactly like this. Ah doesn't he does yeah. He's got no
bottom half to his. Oh yeah. I guess that was funny with
it's missing its lower jaw and its tongue is hanging out. It was I guess it
kind of looks like it. The Ebert thing was cool that they like gave him a just
like a handle on the bottom of his head. You know like he looked he had a like a
like a kettlebell upside down.
- He should have gotten a robot jaw.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Like an iron giant, sharp teeth.
- Yeah, that would have been sick.
- Like that guy from the Venture Brothers,
that villain that has the robot jaw.
- Oh yeah.
- They should have been bad.
- But if you're gonna get your mouth removed,
why are they even, like, it's not like the jaw was us like,
- Yeah, they should just cover it up like,
like when they take, when they steal his mouth
in the Matrix.
- Yeah.
- You should have just done that.
Just, just spackle it.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Just spackle up the dog's mouth.
with grout. Spackle it with grout. Take a skin from his leg and put it over his mouth.
And then we don't have to look at it anymore. Yeah. Which I don't think the problem with
Ebert was that he his mouth was open. No the problem was he didn't give he didn't give
good reviews to my favorite movies. That's why they should have sealed his mouth shut.
He would have got into a fight with Bam Margera. Remember that? And didn't he date Oprah? Yeah.
Have you seen that video of him at the
Fuck what is it? I bet he ate crazy pussy though. Yeah mouth. That's how I got mouth cancer
from Oprah
Oprah yeah, I mean it will do that to you
Roger you were got mouth cancer because he's too good at eating pussy, which I'm afraid every day
I have a lump in my mouth right now really I've never even thought of having that problem. You have that problem
I don't have that problem. That's what happened to Michael. That's actually what happened to Michael Douglas he claims
Michael Douglas claims that he got mouth cancer from eating. Michael Douglas has mouth cancer? He had mouth cancer and
Then he claims that he got it from eating Catherine Zeta-Jones pussy too good
He dated Catherine Zeta-Jones? He's married to her
The only I told you about this. Why would you? They go on dates, yeah?
Yeah, why would you stay married to a woman who gave you mouth cancer? Exactly. Yeah, I told you about this
There's a restaurant in my hometown called...
I think a train conductor.
Yeah, the hat's big.
There's a restaurant in my hometown called The Bacon Barn, and the only two celebrity
photos on the wall are Michael Douglas, Catherine Zeta-Jones, and then Hornswoggle from the WWE.
That's sick.
So tight.
Me and Joe went to... I had to have talked about this before. We went to some diner in LA one time
that had all the celebrity pictures of people who had been there. And then right next to Brad
Brad Pitt, there was a guy and his name was like he had like a nickname like
worm or something and it's just a random dude holding a ketchup bottle. It was
like worm first to use the new ketchup bottle.
Like Brad Pitt Bill Clinton shit my favorite they always have or like a few
places. I've been when when they don't have like celebrity pictures, but they
have like like five guys had this and I think also the South Street Diner in
Boston had it where they don't have celebrity pictures, but they have like
like a page from like a comic book where like an artist like drew that like
that's so funny to me like you couldn't even get a nerd like and you're gonna
frame it for a restaurant I'd probably put up pictures of famous scientists
yeah we're actually not famous scientists accomplished I would actually
probably put up pictures of like famous chefs and food tasters yeah and porn
stars yeah on the wall I put like a big mural of like a Bella danger me
eating pussy. Come on. That's nasty. You wouldn't do that. That fucking picture of...
That painting of Drake eating pussy. Mm-hmm. That's... I want to get that. I want to get a
print of that and put it in my house. You know that picture of the the grandpa
eating paint and he thought it was yogurt? That's gonna be my restaurant. Oh yeah. I don't even want to say what I'm
thinking about it. It's Roger Ebert at the NAACP Image Awards. Cool. What does he do?
they have him guess a song he like they play a little snippet mm-hmm
questions
he's gonna finish you the proto feud yeah just proves that he's just such that
he's the best host of all time
He's a beast. Yeah dude, Roger Ebert was so cool. Rest in peace. And then Siskel.
Siskel? Siskel. Siskel. Thong song. No, Siskel. Siskel and Ebert. The other guy.
Let me see that movie. You're right, that's what I'm thinking of.
I think of Cisco. Is Cisco the one who had the crazy hair?
Is that like, that's got to be on like Mad TV, right?
Like Cisco, Cisco and then it's the movie song. And it's to the thong song.
I don't think anyone has ever thought of that. The movie song.
Maybe Cisco and Ebert would be like a better.
Cisco and Ebert, yeah.
I don't think it makes any sense without the Ebert part.
Yeah, I think that that would maybe be how you would have to do it.
- I think if Gene Siskel is an accomplished movie critic,
I think it would make complete sense.
- I don't think--
- I think what if Gene Siskel, he died,
and then it was Ebert and Roper, right?
- Yeah.
- There's another parody there.
- And now it's just--
- It's violent.
- And then it was just Roper.
- Yeah.
- But RogerEbert.com or something,
they still, it's just like a bunch of movie reviewers.
- It's really funny.
- Yeah, it's like, just call it fucking movie,
one, two, three movies.
- Yeah, movies.
- One, two, three movies.
- Catalyst.com.
- Yeah.
- What would, we should just start,
know someone's talking about pitchfork yesterday yeah and they were like
pitchfork now is just like they don't even review music they just do articles
about I like stuff that happens I said this to you guys before I think but we
absolutely need to start reviewing stuff because then we can get review copies of
things and we can go to press events okay here's a review truly wild berry
with its filtered water in K and less than 2% cane sugar it is the
perfect it's the perfect seltzer for a summer day this is getting a little too
close to my plan spin-off podcast what me Rex and Juvia are doing we're doing
beers we drank really yeah I didn't know that it's fine I'd be the first guest I
think this is my audition all right yeah I mean show me what you got first
produced for the hard seltzer beverage company and I'm not talking about a
company in Boston mass it's not okay review at all truly truly it's not even
- Also, you're fucking messing up.
- All right, here's--
- Yeah, this is--
- Hold on.
- Let me teach you how this is done.
- Hold on, Truly gives you the--
- First of all, Pat, that's not a beer.
- Tools to live Truly.
- That's a seltzer.
- Bud Light, it's good, it was cheap,
and I, drinking it, I like it.
- See, and that's basically what beers we drank
the new podcast is gonna be about.
It's like, yeah, I drank this beer, I drank that beer.
- That's kinda it.
- Did you know that Truly is a Boston-based brand?
- I knew that already. - And it is gluten-free.
I knew that you're sounding like the how it's made guy. I'm not being a
white cat flavor is like wild berry and peach fizz truly peach fuzz peach fizz
truly truly gives you the tools to live truly the tools you are guys like a
guest on beers we drank the really the hit podcast beers we drank with a hard
seltzer with natural flavors at a whopping 24 ounces. You can be on...
Whopping. That certainly is a whopping size for a seltzer. This tasty
beverage goes down smooth. Smooth. With a clear... You're not even
reviewing it. No, you're copyrighting. Hold on. You're doing copyright. Hold on.
done. Overall, I give Truly Wildberry three cans out of four.
Well, you have one can.
No, that's my review system.
Well, you have one can right there.
Three cans out of four.
You clearly have one can. You can't include our can. There's three cans here, but these
aren't Truly.
Three truly cans, three cans out of four for...
No, the other cans are ours.
Because it is giving, it's currently giving me heartburn.
It's giving heartburn.
Wait, you think that we're on a can system at beers we drank?
Bottle system?
It's kegs.
It's a 16 ounce glass system.
Okay, so you'd say I gave this three 16 ounce glasses out of four 16 ounce glasses.
Okay?
Why wouldn't it be kegs?
Because we can't drink that much, idiot!
It's an actual realistic podcast, we're not trying to portray, "Oh, I can drink a million
beers," okay?
We need more positive media. Yeah.
No fear drinking and amounting of beer.
How much do you think you could drink?
How much do you think I could drink?
10 trillion ounces.
I can drink an endless amount of beers and sodas.
Yeah.
Two glasses of water, I'm like full
like Thanksgiving.
But 15 sodas and beers,
it's fine.
They turn into just like
it's like when
milk sits out too long.
I used to be able to put away a 24 pack of beer.
- In the fridge.
- I used to be able to put a 24 pack of beer,
like I could drink a whole 24 pack in a night.
- I'm trying to get a 24 pack, so I've been in the gym.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I'm trying to get myself a 24 pack.
- You've all seen me do this, where it's like,
oh, let's get like a, back in college,
we'd buy like a 30, and then like,
like two-thirds of it I would have drank.
Are you trying to impress a 17-year-old boy right now by saying this on the podcast or
something?
No, I'm just reminiscing with my friends.
Okay, all right.
Reminiscing about the time that you drank a bunch of beer?
Yeah.
All right, let's check in.
Some of the best times of my life were going to your apartment and drinking all of the
beers.
I mean, you guys saw me back there.
I could drink like two ounces of beer.
You could drink two beers.
One time he drank two beers, smoked weed, and turned green.
Yeah, I was there for that.
He turned completely green.
I was there for that.
that was one of the first times we ever hung out. You had two beers and then you kept going like...
I don't know. It wasn't the beers that was the problem. Yeah, I know. It was the weed.
Weed is always the problem. You turned green like Shrek. It happened to me another time.
Yeah? Yeah, that happened to me two times. Did you also turn green then? I don't know. Nobody saw me.
Whoa. I was invisible. That's cool. I went completely invisible. It's fucking epic.
Are you kidding me? That's the sickest shit I've ever heard.
Yeah, nobody could see me.
The fuck? That's so cool.
I went clear like the Trulie I was drinking.
I wasn't drinking Trulie.
Damn it.
Do you ever drink them? You ever drink a Trulie?
See, I don't...
Can we move on from beers, guys?
You're the one who wanted to talk about them.
You brought up your new show.
You wanted to get free marketing.
And then I tried to audition and somebody got in there.
I think me and Pat are gonna start "Beers We Would Like To Drink."
would like to drink. Okay, so it's like years we imagined beers. We that we
might drink beers. We might make you're not gonna miss beer. Okay, wait, okay,
wait, wait. I've got it. It's called it's called a space meteor. Yeah, 90%
ABV when I was smoking and it's got comic book art on. I was smoking a
bunch of weed. I was like and it's it's branded and it's purple. Yeah, it's
Brandon, it's a collaboration with Bruno Mars.
(laughing)
- When I was like two years ago--
- They only sell it in California.
- Okay, here's what--
- This is a terrible beer idea.
- Here's a beer idea, it's an amazing beer.
- You're not allowed to review our beer
'cause you didn't drink it.
- It's called Beer Energy.
- Okay, I like it.
Let's see where you're going with this.
What does the can look like?
- The can is black with blue--
- Can you be quiet?
- Shut up.
- Caleb, Caleb, you need to shut up.
- Fine, I'll do my own podcast.
- The can is black with blue lightning.
- You shut up.
Oh, dude, we could get AC DC or Metallica.
AC or Metallica could be in on this.
Or both.
Both of them.
And then it is basically,
it is a Bud Light with Mio Energy squirted into it.
That's actually a really good idea.
So it's 24 ounce or 22 ounces of Bud Light.
Yeah.
And then two ounces of Mio Energy.
What are you doing?
You can think of a beer too.
You can make your own beer too.
I'm just making out with whatever you were doing was making your microphone
cable make crazy noises.
Yeah, you've you're you're fudging.
You need to go on time.
I am a genius with beer ideas.
Tell you literally haven't come up with a single beer.
I did close two years ago when I was smoking a bunch of weed.
It's not going to be one you came up with the past.
You have to come up with a new one.
I was smoking a bunch of weed and I was like, I'm going to start making
kombucha.
And so I would every night I would have a an idea and I'd be like that's
gonna be such a great idea for a kombucha flavor.
And then recently I found that note in my phone,
and one of the ideas was soy sauce and vanilla.
(laughing)
And I was like, I guess, like two years ago,
I was like, that would be the best flavor ever.
So I'm a beer expert.
I am a beer expert.
- My new idea, Pat.
I don't know.
- Wait, soy sauce.
- Soy sauce and vanilla kombucha.
(laughing)
I don't know how I ever even like I don't I don't think I tasted so I saw us with
vanilla or anything I just was like that would be really good I've I've heard
that I forget there's like one of these one of these like Instagram chefs I
follow she put like a cheddar cheese on top of vanilla ice cream oh that's good
dude yeah yeah dude my fucking mother-in-law makes something called
pineapple casserole Oh hi that on Myrna's party cheese salad no it's
pineapple with cheddar cheese and sugar and then it's like it's like crusted over
and that's so good doesn't sound that sounds horrible terrible and it has like
as like bread crumbs sounds like some 1950s thing that you make because I'm
like an aspect yeah you're trying to show off that you own a fridge yeah good I
don't know I mean it's just sweet and salty you know yeah yeah okay check this
this out okay 50% beer 50% wine in a buzz ball okay it's called it's a called a
beer wine cocktail that sounds good yeah that sounds good I think we're beer wine
we're it's it's we it's no it's it's a spin-off of cheering it's a spin-off of
cheer wine it's called beer wine that's amazing yeah same company makes
here's a really good one yeah hard cheer wine that's a really good idea that is
good that's a really good idea you need to take that all the way to the bank my
yeah yeah hard here I had cheer wine one time and it was so good okay I was a
bit IPA called crazy burger it's ketchup and mustard flavored okay yeah and
pickles and lettuce and bun and sesame seeds what about sesame seeds in it
Dracula killer IPA garlic flavored beer I could see that doing numbers yeah I
could actually be great yeah yeah oh I were wolf werewolves Bane IPA colloidal
silver flavored beer what about what about okay Bruce Bogtrotters curse and
and it's
it's a it's a fifteen percent a b v sixty ounce, I P a chocolate cake
flavored
twist off yeah yeah, it comes in a six pack only. Well, I always thought that
they should put you know the lid that they put on ibuprofen that on beer. So
that's when you're too drunk. You can't even open one yeah yeah. If I was a
president that you can't open that when you're drunk,
if you're like so fucked up that you're like,
you could open it, you could twist off.
- I feel like that's easier than a bottle opener.
- Not a bottle, I mean if you're really fucked up,
it's all these.
- Bud Light Lime. - It's all these pop tabs.
- But I feel like that's probably one of the easiest lids
to open. - It's at least a little harder,
okay?
- I think it's easier. - Did I ever show you guys
the movie I was writing about beer?
- Maybe.
- Bud Light Lime, the movie?
- Oh yeah, you did. - Yeah.
- Yeah, I think. - Bud Light Lime.
- What if we did a live reading of it on the podcast?
- I thought you already did that.
I don't think I want to do that. I think we've already done that. Yeah, I think you
did already do it years ago. We did. Oh, we did. Yeah. Yep. Yeah. I forgot we did
that. Yeah. Yeah. You guys want to read my movie? Do you want to like, I don't
know, maybe get it like maybe we pitch it. No, maybe we like do it at Carnegie
Hall. That's fine. I would like to go to Carnegie Hall. What about crud light?
And it's all it's the region. It's they they make the bud light. They do the
quality test. Oh, it's all the fails the quality test. It becomes crud light.
It's way cheaper.
There should be something at bars.
What about, okay, have you ever had an Aero bar?
No.
Or like a, like an Aero bar is like a chocolate.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's full of air.
Yeah, it's like, you know, like World Market and shit.
B-A-R-O.
It's full of air.
It's full of the foam.
Beer, only foam.
That's a good idea.
Only the foam of a beer.
I always thought, you know.
It's in like a shaving cream.
It's in a spray, yeah.
Or an--
So if you pour your beer and there's not enough foam,
you can spray some foam on top of it.
It's really good for...
It's the biggest hack that bartenders have.
It's good for photo shoots.
Yeah, good for photo shoots and if you pour a Guinness wrong.
Yeah, yeah.
There's no wrong way to pour a Guinness.
And the spray can, it has a reverse setting, so if you have too much foam on your beer,
you can suck the foam back up into the can and reuse it later.
I do want something like what they do in Mad Max when they spray paint their mouth.
Yeah, I want that so bad.
Oh, that's such a good idea, the chrome beer.
There's a new energy spray called Pazaz. I think that's what it's called.
It looks… I keep seeing it at bodegas and I want to buy it.
How many times do you spray it?
On your mouth.
How many?
How many times do you spray it?
Yeah.
I think maybe just once or twice.
So if you drank the whole thing, you'd probably die.
It's like a caffeine… Yeah, I think it's like a high… I think it's called Pazaz. P-A-Z-A-Z.
There's no way they can sell like 15,000 milligrams of caffeine in a little bottle.
little bottle. Yeah, Pazazz Energy Mist is a breath spray. A breast spray? Breast spray.
Come on, bro. Come on, dog. You can buy a four pack for twenty, oh, I know that guy.
That's Robbie. He's on their website. What the fuck are you talking about? I have a really
good beer idea whenever you get done looking at this website. What? But yeah, it's an energy
mist that you can spray in your mouth and they sell it at bodegas.
So going off of that, they should do that with beer.
Yeah, a drunken spray.
Why have they not done a toothpaste?
Here's my beer idea, okay?
Let me paint a picture for you.
Comes in a four pack.
Okay?
Wow.
It's a four pack, but they're not arranged like a square.
They're in a row.
Okay.
Okay, there's an arrow on the side, which order you're supposed to drink them.
They're numbered, which order you're supposed to drink them.
All right, I'm going to get back in.
First one, open it up, drink it.
It tastes exactly like bread.
Okay.
Second one, open it up, drink it.
Exactly like peanut butter.
No way.
There's no way.
Third one, open it up, drink it.
Jelly.
Fuck me.
No spoilers here, but the fourth one, it's bread.
It's bread again?
And it's called the sandwich experience.
Wow.
That sounds incredible.
And it could be a viral challenge that people drink the bread.
- Go with the PB or a J.
- PB or a J?
- PB or a J.
- Experience.
- It's an experience.
- Here's going off of that idea.
- Yeah.
- Six beers in a row.
- Okay.
- So first one.
- Yeah.
- Pretty much like an O'Doul's, like it's a one ABV.
- Okay.
- Second one is a four ABV.
So it's like, so it's called, it's like hot ones.
it gets gradually stronger.
- Oh, I was thinking it would be called the mountain,
and the one in the middle would be like 20% ABV,
the ones on either side like nine.
- And it goes down, yeah.
- And then O'Douls.
- That's smart, yeah.
- Then you have like a perfect peak.
- Yeah, yeah. - You're coming back down,
you're hitting O'Douls again.
- I would be in the liquor store switching them all out,
I'd get a full pack of 20% ABV.
- My dad claims one O'Douls in the morning
after like a night of heavy drinking
is the perfect hangover cure.
- Really? - Yeah.
- I'll have to remember that. - And I've tested it,
and it works.
so he doesn't claim that you're claiming i'm claiming that my dad is correct
as a good way to say that my dad is so smart
yeah i've never met my dad never imparted any kind of knowledge like that
yet my dad's always dropping knowledge bombs like that my dad is not very
knowledgeable what about a beer bottle and it's it's empty comes empty if can
fill it with beer and carried around
What about algene beer bottle? Exactly yeah. You can put whatever stickers you want.
What about like a sex doll but it's all glass? And you fill it up with beer? It's filled with
beer. And you drink it out of the pussy and butt? Yeah either one is fine. Yeah. And you could or
you could double team it. Whoa. You could trade it off with your friend. You could fuck it when
you're done. What about like it's like a it's like a humidifier and you put beer in it and it puts
beer gas into the air. So anyone in the house or room it gets really it's
messed up. It's really beard up and then you could have one in your car and
then also we could sell a so that's a beer midifier and then we could sell a
D beer midifier, which is the only way you can get it out of your house. Once
true in the air because you want to rope them in and then you sell them the
yeah, exactly problem in the solution because there's no way to turn it off.
Once you plug it in, that's smart. You are you're going to die unless you
but a beer carousel. How would that work? It spins and it gives you a new beer
every time. Oh, that's smart as fuck. Like a sushi conveyor belt, but for beer.
Yeah. Beer roulette. Beer roulette. So everything has a different beer on it.
It's different. So it's like a four or like a six pack of beer, but one of them
is like just like 20, one of them is just water.
- I do wanna see the kind of like fucking kids,
code name kids next door engineering that weed heads do.
I wanna see that applied to beer.
We have some fun stuff.
- See that's the thing.
- 'Cause listen, we don't smoke weed, okay?
We like beer.
- I hate weed, I hate weed, but I love--
- But I like the weekend.
- 'Cause I can drink beer.
- Yeah. - The weed again.
- Yeah.
- I hate weed, I hate smoking weed,
I hate being high off the pot.
I hate having THC in my body,
but I do appreciate the spirit of invention.
- Yeah, they do a pretty good job.
- They, you know, if you have to smoke out of a,
they used to have to smoke vape out of a plastic bag.
Where is that?
I think maybe it's because beer is already perfect as it is.
- Yep. - Yeah.
- They used to castrate opera singers too.
- To make them sing high.
- No, just stuff that, yeah, stuff they used to do.
I need to buy the equivalent of a Rick and Morty bubbler,
but for beer.
- Exactly.
- Whatever that is.
- Well, they have Rick and Morty IPAs.
- You know what I really like?
- But that's the thing, it's not the IPA.
That is an apparatus, I need to buy something.
- You need an, yeah, there has to be more apparatus.
- Yeah, exactly, a device.
- I also think that IPAs are completely like,
- That's the weed of beer.
- I think that's like CIA.
- Yeah.
- Because it's an act.
- Three letters.
they came up pretty recently if you remember correctly I never had one until
I was 21 yeah and then they also are like they're like they just that's the truth
yeah three letters they taste bad they're trying to they try to scare
people out of drinking beer yeah so they were like we'll make a shit what a beer
tastes like bad yeah you're taste like bullshit fucking shit it's complete
bullfuck shit yeah and what if the name was confusing it's like what and what is
that's an IPA yeah exactly a Simpsons movie you think that the I and IPA would
stand for Irish a lot of people don't know the grandpa in the Simpsons movie
we're saying II Pais talking about an IPA mm-hmm and what and how do you says to
evil I or a million eyes uh-huh yeah cuz they saw a million different fucking and
and that and that grandpa's name Abe you know you spell it IPA
hey I BA I yeah at BA he's Portuguese yeah the Simpsons are poor chance people
know that and then twisted tail twisted tea twisted tea because that's so
they're saying you should be drinking twisted teas yeah right because what's
better than a 400 calorie tea drink nothing nothing I try to think of
something I couldn't think of as many calories as two ice cream sandwiches and
it gets you about as buzzed as half a but ice cream sandwich that's a variation
on the PB&J experience it is ice cream sandwiches personally one of my favorite
ice cream sandwiches. I hate the chocolate one but like a chip witch or like a
Choco Taco. It's called a chippy chip. A chippy chip. That's the ones they sell
over there. Do you guys want to get a chippy chip after this? I can't get a
chippy chip. You don't want to get a chippy chip? No I have to go shortly after. You
don't want to get a chippy chip? No I also don't like ice cream. You don't want
a chippy chip? I don't like ice cream. You don't want to get a chippy chip? No I just
- I don't want ice cream.
- You just said you love ice cream sandwiches though.
- I like ice cream sandwiches pretty well.
- A chippy chip is an ice cream sandwich.
- But I don't like ice cream that much.
- You guys, I just got one free tube of Pizzazz.
- Holy shit, really?
- Are you serious?
- You won?
- I won one free tube of Pizzazz.
I was very close to getting one year of Zazz.
- That's gonna really fuck your life up.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Can't you just refresh it and do it again
and try to get the one year?
- I think I'm gonna buy.
- Don't do this.
- Oh, so it's a coupon code.
So it's not, yeah.
I think I'm just gonna keep entering in emails
until I get one free year of Pazazz.
- I'm sure it's gonna work.
- But I'm sure purchase is necessary as well.
- So I'd have to buy one and then I get one free year of Zazz.
- Yeah. - Yeah, it's a good deal.
- That's a pretty good deal.
- Yeah.
- Have you guys ever won a lifetime supply of anything
or the lottery?
- I want to win a lifetime supply of something so bad.
- I wanna-- - A lifetime supply,
you know, that lasts about 10 minutes.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah. - I wanna win--
- Or an hour if you're trying to go somewhere.
- Or a lifetime supply of something so fucking bad.
I want a lifetime supply of happiness by being born into this world.
It's beautiful. Born under Christ.
So beautiful.
Lifetime is how long it takes a girl to get her makeup on.
Yeah, an hour. That's what I said. It takes an hour.
Yeah, well, yeah. An hour is what I said. I kind of clarified it. That's why we're a team.
You kind of just said a D'Worst version.
That didn't really fit in. We're like a comedy duo.
Yeah, kind of like a trio, but you and me kind of have our own thing right there, obviously.
Yeah, where you just like take whatever I say and make it less
interesting a little bit. We have our own thing where I eat his chips.
I also have one of those things where I eat your chips too.
Who? I mean your thing. Did you just call me Patches? Patrick. You think I called you
Patrick? Your name is Patrick and you thought I called you Patches? Yeah. No.
No. Okay. All right this is bad we're all eating chips at the same time. Yeah I
I stopped eating my chips.
So you eat the chips faster.
I can talk about anything I want now.
Say something.
Speaking of lifetime supplies of things,
when I was in like 4th or 5th grade or something,
Transworld Magazine used to have these contests
where you could like,
you could enter to win
like a free box
basically of like boards and stuff.
And I never won one of those,
but I've always wanted to win one.
I want an Xbox as a child.
I want it because they used to have like, you get like three or four boards from somebody,
a bunch of clothes, a bunch of stickers, a bunch of trucks, a bunch of wheels.
If somebody could win that for me.
What's the publisher's...
I'm going to have an endless supply of minions doing lifetime supply entries for me.
Because I need a lifetime supply of something.
Yeah, what's the current lifetime supply at Sweepstakes?
They only do one at a time,
'cause otherwise it would get overwhelmed.
It's probably estrogen.
If I would split a lifetime supply of something
with one person, 50/50, if somebody wins--
But then that's a half of a lifetime.
What do you mean, you would get alternate weeks,
like divorced parents,
or you would split right down the middle?
You'd be like, "My life is halfway over."
Guys, huge news.
What?
Here's, I just looked up,
I'm on SweepsAdvantage, sweepstakesadvantage.com.
I've got a list of sweepstakes here.
Number one here, I think we could enter this year,
this year long supply.
It's monthly winners.
Enter the Enfamil Family Beginnings Formula
for a year sweepstakes for a chance to win.
One prize will be awarded each month
during the promotion period.
- I think I'm ready to have a kid.
- It says this prize consists of a year's supply
of the winner's choice of any Enfamil
or Enfigro branded product.
That's huge.
- I think I'm ready to become a father.
- Patrick told me the other day we were driving home,
he said, "Yeah, I think I'm ready to just have a kid."
And I said, "No."
- Guys-- - I think I'm ready.
- I don't think he's ready.
- I don't have a job.
- You have a job, you're doing it.
- This is not a job.
- I am going to enter us to win--
- This is art, I'm doing art.
- Obviously, yeah.
- I am going to enter us to win a year's worth
of Procter & Gamble products.
- Okay.
- Who's Procter and who's Gamble?
That's my fucking question.
- Look, we're gambling right now
whether we're going to win these Proctors.
- Wait, we're not--
- Proctor.
- Add to my, what is this website?
Add to my sweepstakes.
- Prog ducks.
- Yeah, prog ducks.
- I have to make an account.
I'm not going to make an account on here.
- That's the key to everything.
- Utz Ripple's chips.
Sour cream and onion.
- Can't go wrong.
- Free cheese for a year?
- Yes, enter that one.
- Enter that.
- I'm going to enter that one, hold on.
How weird I just found that one.
- Free beers for a year might be--
- Where'd it go?
- Yeah, let's do free beer for a year.
all the other time you're on the website all all we all we're trying to do now is
just get a bunch of sponsorship the ultimate trip to nashville enter for a
chance to win two nights in music city i'd love that to take us to join the
barbecue beer and bourbon nashville foodie adventure is national music city
yeah
what if we
well what if we sell out there have a bunch of beer sweepstakes what we sell
out completely right now
that's fine anyone wants to invest in this show
- The Coors Light Summer 2022 Sweepstakes.
- Can you say Coors Light?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I'd like to do that.
- You don't know who would and who wouldn't
completely invest in us.
- I'm gonna put you in a vest.
I'm gonna make you do magic at my birthday.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I'm going to invest you.
- What are you doing?
- Whoa!
- How did you put your fingers together like that?
- He's doing magic tricks.
- That is not magic, that's clearly fucking witchcraft.
- How did you take your thumb off of your finger?
- Stop, dude.
on each. How did you make three fingers on that one became three two fingers on
each became three on one where the other one go there it is oh my god is for if
you make it go to six on one hand then I'll be even more impressed honestly.
Holy shit oh my god holy shit okay I'm entering I'm buying you I'm entering us
for the course light contest right now nice that'd be sick to have an endless
supply of something and we just keep it at the office that would be so sick in
the way it's a okay enter your email address I did if you and then it says
for the following companies toys are us yeah.
Please hit us up.
I need help here guys.
I entered our email address and then it says under that enter a
keyword optional a keyword.
I don't know what that means.
What should I enter?
What try beer beer beer beer?
Okay, your Stravaganza.
Yeah, that's good.
It's good.
Key.
We're Strava.
Gansa Stravaganza.
What a beautiful Italian name submit.
I'll have to fill out a form.
Okay.
When you guys keep talking I'm going to fill out a form.
Well, tell me what the form says.
I'll tell you.
It's like name, address.
Okay, name, chocolate fetter.
Address, 150.
Fetter chocolate.
Checkland.
150 Checkland Street.
Checkland Place.
Yeah.
Yep.
Okay.
I got my phone.
Gender, okay, listen to this.
Gender.
female male non-binary transgender i'd use another term or a prefer not to
answer
i prefer not to have her for not answer yeah cuz i don't want to play any part
of that fucking i have no chance right that's right now they got a capture
these days it's almost like a capture just type in uh... flogging molly fan
one
that's really it
that's probably the capture that's usually what i get on catches
minus is christmas but the seas backwards
Do you ever when they used to do ones from books the good ones those ones are
so awesome.
No.
Do you remember what you would get one every once in a while you get one that
says like kill someone.
It was like two words.
That shit was funny as fuck.
I never.
Now they just make you look at pictures of bicycles.
It's like I do this enough on my own time.
I'm just going through Instagram and click on every picture that has a
bicycle on it.
Yeah I already go through Instagram on the grid and then select
everyone with a red light in it.
The code that beats Beards Traffic Anza is invalid.
fuck didn't I guess just get rid of beer
straight yeah this true or not sorry you
are not an instant winner what return
daily through September 6th for
additional chances to win fine then we
just try tomorrow again yeah that's fine
I'm a big of a deal it has all my
information now beer strava Gans it says
whoa I opened up my phone that pizzazz
was still open that shit that looks like
shit you can get a huge tattoo why do
people think there's a good way to
design a website now I don't know
know. Websites, you know it's a good website. Swagpoop.com/brewhomars.com. Oh, really? What
else does he have on there? Any games? He's got a different segments here. Look, he's got
music plus video, store, news, tour. Let's look at the news. Ricky Regal. Yeah, what is
it? It's only an evening with Silk Sonic out now. Okay, introducing Silk Sonic. He's got
a new music video. Wait, Please Me with Cardi B? That's what it said. What, dude? Pretty
I'd like her to please me.
Wow, Cardi B?
Some big news.
I don't think I could ever please her.
Cardi B?
You don't think you could please her?
She gives you all the instructions in that one song where she's like, "Suck a poop,
jump fuckin', put a-
I like it like that!
Put a comb in my ass," all this crazy shit.
Yeah.
She's just always just talking about-
Yeah, I don't think I could afford to listen to Yonzo.
All of her songs are telling you how to fuckin' make her calm and shit.
Really?
She's like, "You gotta nut by giving me a-
That's what's wrong with music nowadays.
You get a nut by putting a glove on.
I haven't heard him in a while.
He fucking put the middle part of an N64 controller in my pussy.
It's all about completely cum.
You put the rumble pack in it.
Yeah, and I'm fucking nut.
It's actually about cumming nowadays.
Songs are about cumming, but movies are about...
Shows used to be about...
Movies are about being an actor in Los Angeles and also being a hitman.
a music song nowadays, you'll turn it on it's a woman singing and she says, I
want that male come all in me
discuss a movie nowadays, you turn it on its two women in France and they're
putting their hands in each other yep, they come out covered in honey. This is
art.
They've got sticky lines like grimer or muck going from her hand to her whole. I
don't know if it's honey. It's covered in honey and chocolate.
and that's and music nowadays is like music a woman's like I want to make a
baby and I want to throw it out yeah I want you to get I want you to creating
life there I want you to shoot it on my face I want an embryo yeah I want you to
take the glue that creates a person and put it inside of my foot where there's
no egg there's women babies born woman rap music nowadays is like a fetus makes
me Randy and the worst part is half it's in fucking Spanish so I don't even know
what they're saying and it's always far away yeah I hear these songs it's far
away it's always playing someone's you are a random car with a cooler version
of the American flag that just completely rest over it what's it are
unifying and with a with a man in the high castle alternate history US flag on
the back of it and they're playing some Spanish song where it's about just
just using, just wasting a man's seed.
(laughing)
Which is a complete fucking cardinal sin, they say.
- I want to open a whole graveyard
from the amount of babies in my face.
In my, on the load on my face.
- Yeah, that's what they want to say.
- I want you to turn my butthole into a graveyard of semen.
Is what they're saying in these songs.
- I want to see little tiny homunculus baby skulls
all in Cardi B's asshole.
That's what she wants to say these days.
- Cover me in sin.
- Yeah.
- She's saying-- - Into my cervix.
- Also, these women have the fucking gall
to have asses so big that you can barely
put your thing through it.
- Yeah. - And reach one
of the two things. - Exactly.
- It's like a hot dog and a hamburger bun.
- 'Cause they're trying to make it
so that they can never have a baby,
so they're like, I'm gonna get my ass so big
that a guy just has to fuck my ass
and then come in my butt crack
and never actually get close to actually
creating a beautiful life. - Exactly.
That's what I want.
I want miraculous new babies in my butt.
I want a macular concession.
I want them up in my butt.
I don't want them in the place they need to be.
Yep.
And they're saying, "Oh, I got a diaphragm put in so it catches all the cum."
It's like nowadays, I heard about this.
I don't know about you guys, if you've heard about this.
Apparently nowadays, in order to prevent life from happening, women are getting IEDs that
blow up the babies when they're eight months old.
And what happened to songs being about saying hey to Delilah?
Yeah.
That was actually a very powerful song.
That was actually a beautiful ass song.
That was actually a beautiful ass song as well.
Two teenagers falling in love.
Little Diddy by Jack and Diane.
What happened to that?
Nowadays songs are about two teenagers just going at it.
Getting up inside each other.
Jack and Diane used to be about two teenagers sucking on a chili dog.
Now it's about, now every song is about making a chili dog.
Because you put your wiener in a butt.
These days it would probably be
Little Diddy put your cum in my hand.
Because they want to waste the cum by putting it in their hand.
putting it in their hand.
And also, kids these days can be named Diddy.
(laughing)
The fuck is that?
- I had a manager in a restaurant call me that.
- He's saying, "Little Diddy."
- 'Cause my initials were P.D.
And it was short for, he called me Puff Daddy.
- What?
- That's what happens at restaurants now.
- And now restaurants don't even serve food.
They're serving.
- They're singing.
- They're serving like, "Yo, yo, yo."
They're serving their customers.
Like, "You just got served, Diddy."
That's what he said to you.
- That's what my manager would say to me.
And then I would have to sing to the customers
when it was their birthday.
you they diss you they say your cards decline. I would have to sing to the customers when
it was their birthday I'd say happy happy birthday from Applebee's to you we wish it
was our birthday so we could party too. It's like Applebee's you don't have a birthday
you're a company right the other thing they want corporations to be people. Nowadays people
and that's not leftist. People in Seattle and Portland they're holding up magnifying
glasses to loads and they're looking at ants. They're seeing little ants and babies in there
they're waving and doing little heart signs to them and they flush it down the toilet
and make 'em battle rats and mutant ninja turtles.
- That's right, that's right.
- And nowadays-- - Get that nut
out of the toilet!
The nut goes in the girl, not the fuckin' toilet!
- Nut goes in your wife-- - Dude, not touch
that flusher. - Not the toilet.
You'll be full of strife. - Pick it up,
put it back up there.
- Reach your hand-- - At least reuse it.
Save it for next time. - Everybody, right now,
okay, life pro tip.
- Nut inside your wife or your life
full of strife. - Go to your toilet.
Everybody has a little bit of nut stuck in their toilet
'cause of how many nuts had been flushed down
by previous tenants.
I would hope go reach in grab it like you like you hid money in there for a long
time and you're trying to get it put it in your wife while she's making food.
Yeah, and you're at nine months later. Thank me. Okay, because you're gonna
have a beautiful little spell will be cast on your life. Beautiful little
baby. Okay,
but yeah, Seattle in Portland.
Don't come other show.
We have shows. We don't like it. Oh wait. We have another thing. We do have
another will Seattle in Portland first buy tickets to that. Yeah, that's what
Swagpoop.com/shows. But also, we're doing it, we're back in Brooklyn, we're doing a
Brooklyn show at Lifeworld. A little show. A little show at Lifeworld. There's not all
that many tickets, so get them hot. It's a small space run by our friends. We're
doing two shows on the 5th and 6th of August. Tickets should be up on
Swagpoop.com/shows, but if they're not yet, be patient and don't message me
like you did last time that I said they should be up, but if they're not, be
patient just act normal and just be patient and refresh the page every
five minutes like a normal fan would do. Bye.