You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[laughter]
Looooord.
Awwww.
(yells)
- Aw.
- That's beautiful.
That's beautiful, it's so kind.
- Aw, look at that, aw.
- Oh, you wanna bring that up?
- Aw, your microphone, aw.
- You're gonna bring that up?
Yes, I've been wearing my camel hat
and I don't know what happened.
I think it's 'cause it's very old.
- Yeah.
- It gave me a rash.
It probably had like, somebody probably smoked Camel cigarettes into the hat for like 20 years.
Probably. Whoever owned that hat got it with Camel cash.
They smoked the cigarette through the hat as an extra filter.
Yeah, it's made out of the one material that would sop up cigarette smoke the most.
Yeah.
Corduroy.
And I've been wearing it and now I just have like a huge like the sweat where the sweatband
of the hat would be on my forehead just a big red line.
Yeah.
And it draws attention to like my forehead being big.
It's very funny.
It looks like you look kind of like Voltorb.
Yeah.
Maybe yeah.
So I gotta stop wearing that hat for a little bit.
You have to put it through a cleanse.
Yeah, I did.
That's the thing.
Their sickness runs deep in that hat.
It's infected.
It's true.
It's cursed.
It's the cursed hat.
Yeah.
It's like, you know, it probably like a wizard put a curse on it or something and it has
a bunch of like microscopic spikes on the inside.
Someone probably died of emphysema in that hat.
Yeah.
yeah it wasn't a camel hat before but then somebody there's some of the person
who wore it all the time died of emphysema and they're like we should put
the camel look it wasn't corduroy either it like wrinkled up yeah yeah I gotta
get I gotta clean that hat I'm worried about breaking the brim of it if I clean
it. But then it's like, I mean, that's the whole of my forehead.
It looks crazy. It's such a clean line. I feel like most rashes, even if you get it
from something, it won't stop right where the thing is.
I mean, it's like dry skin. It feels like eczema.
I got a haircut too.
Yeah.
So I can't like put my hair over it.
Yeah, you should get a wig.
Maybe.
Oh dude, there's probably a wig store around here.
There's gotta be a wig.
There's probably like 10 wig stores on your block.
Yeah, I should probably get a toupee.
Yeah, you should get a big blonde Jimmy Houston wig.
Yeah.
Or like a cut, yeah.
And then you can like kinda,
you can cut it just right above your eyes.
So it doesn't--
So I just have like big bangs.
Yeah, exactly.
Just big white bangs.
Yeah.
That'd be great.
And then you put a hat on over it because nobody expects you to put a hat on over a
toupee.
Right, right.
See that may be, okay, yet like one of the most realistic, maybe it's like horse hair
or like real person hair.
I think real person hair is probably more realistic than horse hair.
Well, no, aren't most expensive wigs made out of horse hair?
I feel like maybe, I don't know, actually now I'm talking out of my ass I think, but you
know I would think that...
Yeah, you don't know shit about wigs, bitch.
I would think you're probably not allowed to...
Are you allowed to make wigs out of people hair?
I guess you must be.
Yeah.
Well, I mean for cancer patients.
That's true.
We, in my high school, we had for like, like the big event at our school was we had this
pep rally and every year we had this one pep rally where like this guy organized it so
So we did a mass hair donation for Pantene, Locks of Love.
And for all four years of high school, and in middle school I knew about it because it's
the one thing in our town, all four years of high school I had to go, you weren't allowed
to skip it, you had to go to this, you had to go and just watch everybody get their hair
cut.
Like everybody who volunteered get their hair cut and then it was like this weird like stigma thing where it's like girls who had like
Long hair, it's like well, why don't you donate and it's like this is the fucking we had hair bullies at my fucking high school, dude
You know, I would you know
I would do the thing like where if you have to take like a urine sample
Telling drug test or whatever I would go into the bathroom and then I'd fill the bag with cat hair
This is my hair, yeah
That's my thing.
No, you do it for the urine sample.
Yeah, that's true.
You put cat hair in it, it's like, "No, that's just how I pee."
Yeah, it looks like, you know, I will say there's a significant amount of drugs in here.
It also seems you may be 50% cat based on your DNA.
Dude, fucking, uh, what was I going to say?
I just looked up, um...
They have 23andMe for dogs.
Yeah, I know, yeah.
I kinda, that's one of those, that'll trick you.
That'll, I mean, if you're a dog owner,
that's, your brain just gets warped.
It's like, I don't know, it's like,
it's like having some kind of like magical artifact
that gives you power and then you like turn evil,
you know what I mean?
Like having a dog makes you into the kind of person
who wants to get 23andMe for your dog.
It's true, yeah.
I just wanna know what kind it is.
It's like it doesn't matter at all.
I've thought about buying that so many times and had to stop myself.
I think it makes sense.
I think I would definitely want to know what breed my dog...
Just because of the breed characteristics, like, "Oh, my dog likes to sniff my ass."
He's part bloodhound.
He's part ass sniffer.
You know that German type breed that sniffs asses?
Yeah, he's one of those.
I mean the thing about my dog is like because of her shape you know there's
either a corgi or a dachshund somewhere in there and then beyond that it's probably just
like one percent of everything else that's not interesting.
Well I think that's kind of cool like knowing that there's like a shit ton.
I don't know I just want to get that and then put my own DNA in my own DNA.
That sounds like I'm cumming in the tube.
(laughter)
Sending in your pet 23andMe and you're like...
Just your own jizz in the tube.
Yeah, well that would get you in trouble too, because even if it wasn't yours, that might be worse if it's not yours.
Right.
Might be worse if it's your dog's.
(laughter)
I fucking... ah, shit. I... I...
I misread the instructions. I didn't know you were supposed to take a swab of their cheek. I thought it was something else.
That would suck if you like jacked off your dog. If you jacked off your dog that
would be so horrible. No, if you put in like your own hair to like send to the
to the to like your the pet 23andMe thing and it came back and you're like
yeah you're one of those you're like one of those um those super inbred like yeah
well you know the ones that has his faces always look like they like just got
stung by a bee they look like really fucked up. Bull terrier? Is it a bull
- Bull terrier?
- I like bull terriers, like the target dog?
- Yeah, bull terrier.
But I mean, just imagine if your DNA came back
and they said you were a bull terrier.
- 100% bull terrier.
- That's maybe one of the worst,
one of the worst, what's the worst dog
that they could tell you you are?
- No, you know what would be worse?
It would be worse if it said like 99% human, 1% dog.
(laughing)
Like somewhere along the line, like a grandma,
or like an aunt, or no, it's probably a grandma, right?
(laughing)
- Yeah, I mean, I don't think you're aunt.
Yeah, a grandma or something like fucked a dog. Yeah
It'd be gross
Yeah, I just I just um, I looked up when we're talking about wigs I googled what is the best wig material
And this is from Oprah's website. Okay, okay for the most natural-looking wig up for one made of human hair
Okay. Yeah
There are two types of wigs human hair and synthetic as you might guess human hair provides the most natural
natural look says Faye Norris a hair stylist at Rock Paper Salon because it's
a great name for that's yeah right that's a bird God level pun it just rolls off
the tongue because it's real it falls and swings the same way natural hair does
plus it can be styled blow-dried curled or ironed like business as usual but then
we get this next paragraph here still there are different types of human hair
European which is a little finer is the most sought-after and most expensive
Norris Indian which is softer and has more texture is also very popular but a
little less expensive and Chinese hair. And Chinese hair which tends to be thick
and straight is the least expensive and most prevalent. Oh my god. I didn't expect
I mean I think about it I'm like I guess the wig people would probably
differentiate that and like probably get weird about it but I didn't expect to
read it on this website. What the fuck? Yeah, that's the way the wigs racist. I would expect
to read that in an article that's like, here's the problem with wigs, not how to find your
favorite wig. Shit. Yeah. God, I, we need to cancel. I'm not buying a wig. Anytime soon.
me tell you that. Not after reading that. Yeah, not after knowing now that wigs are racist.
Christ. Yeah, and luckily, yeah, luckily the synthetic wigs are not racist at all because
they're made by Chinese people in sweatshops. But we don't take their hair though, so it's
fine. They're made out of like runoffs of like some kind of plastic that's being made.
Like some kind of plastic that they were like they
Accidentally put it in a lathe or something like that. No, I said this kind of looks like hair
It's a little bit like you know, yeah, it does give me insane hives whenever I touch it
But you know, it's probably fine and everybody who's worked in our factory dies at the age of 30 from some kind of strange alien
lump
Just like a wig that's made entirely out of Kevlar strings. Yo
You like tighten it up and yeah, you could try to pull it
Yeah, when you're like when you're about when you're like in danger you like pull on it really hard and it tightens together reverse Bayonetta
Cuz she I've never really played Bayonetta. Yeah, I don't know her doesn't her hair turn into guns
I don't know. All I know is her leg goes in a portal and Smash Brothers. That's true. She wears glasses
I know that too. Does her hair turn to guns? I don't know Bayonetta hair. No, it's crazy is
is you've done way more googling than I have ever done
on an episode in the past eleven minutes. I like to google stuff.
I know but...
See that's the thing is I probably google the most. I mean now that
Caleb's not here we can get into the nitty gritty the truth.
Maybe it's because I just type too slow. Maybe that's the problem.
I think also I google stuff. I'm a very fast... I skim very well.
I'm good at it. I don't.
I'm I'm I'm I read it as pace of 1000 words a second.
I don't think that she makes her hair.
I can't tell by this Google search and I'm not going to read.
What did you look up?
Does Bayonetta?
I looked up Bayonetta hair guns.
So maybe that's that's probably yeah, maybe type in type in does
Bayonetta hair a gun?
Does Bayonetta hair does Bayonetta have a child?
Is the suggestion.
Okay, look up Bayonetta Lady Pregnant.
Okay, yeah, hold on. Bayonetta Lady Pregnant Bowser.
Okay, ooh.
Let's see here.
The images here.
You know, surprisingly there's not a single image of this search of Bayonetta Pregnant.
Oh.
This is very, you know.
Well that ruins the fucking episode.
Yeah, we don't have anything to talk about anymore.
- I'm in.
Delete the fucking, delete the files.
This sucks.
- Oh, I think, oh, a fan fiction came up.
Oh no, this is not a fan,
this is a page of Rule 34 Bowser porn.
- Oh, okay.
This is probably like the third episode in a row
that we've looked up something like that.
- Yeah, hey, why not?
- I need to stop burping right into the microphone.
- Sex games tagged Bowser.
(laughing)
- Sex game, sexual tag?
- Sexual dude, I--
- Sexual tag with Bowser.
- I hate playing sexual tag with Bowser.
- Oh man, you know why?
Is 'cause you always gotta chase behind him
and he's got those spikes on his back.
- Yeah.
- So you gotta fuckin'.
- He gets way overzealous too.
He grabs me and he jumps up in the air
and he jumps down into the, off the screen.
- Yeah, the trick when you're playing
sexual tag with Bowser is you gotta get up in his butt.
- You gotta get in his shell.
to crawl in between his shell and his stomach.
Sexual tag. That is like...
like, 'cause there's like
naked twister
so I think along those... There's what?
Is it naked twister or strip twister? I don't know.
Both of those sound... I mean
why not just get naked and hug?
No, 'cause there... I know it's naked twister
'cause I think there's a line in Jack and Jill
This is something somebody told me.
I don't think I've ever seen Jack and Jill.
Somebody told me there's a line that says,
Al Pacino wants to play Naked Twister with your sister.
- Whoa.
- Yeah.
So Naked Twister exists.
- Naked Twister, that's a perversion
of both being naked and of Twister.
That's not right.
- And Twister's already a fucking perverted game.
- Yeah, that's a game that if you're older
than seven years old, you should not be playing.
That's a game to play with like--
- If you're like, playing it with your kids,
you're the spinner. - You should, yeah.
There's something's going on.
- That's weird.
- We're gonna get you in trouble.
- I don't know, I think that's an innocent, I don't--
- I think that's a fine game.
I think that--
- Sorry, sorry, Gilton Bradley.
Sorry that we're talking shit.
- That's an okay game for families to play with
in the family.
That's a family game only.
(laughing)
you know you have a dad who's like really excited
a dad or an uncle who's just like really excited to play twister
when his kids friends come over
uncle jerry comes over you hide that game
you put that in the back of the closet
and you're playing marvel chess with uncle jerry
hey what's this behind the spider wick board game
NO NO
you hear the doorbell ring and you throw it in the back of the closet
and then he like walks in and you everybody realizes at the same time you
accidentally left the spinner out and he's like hey what's this i didn't know
you guys had a spinner there's the rest of the game uh that's our chore wheel
it's my day to do red we needed to use it as a as a uh shit a shower curtain oh
oh no our clock fell off the wall again
yeah
definitely that is definitely that's a
that's a fuckin
naked twister
order what are some other games that shouldn't be sexual that are sexual
i don't think any game should be sexual i don't either
but i think a game is between a gamer and his partners
but there's strip poker naked twister
strip poker is also you know sexual candy land
yeah you know i was a lot of the space
of let me tell you do you gloppy
gloppy scared the shit out of me as a kid
you know i was my it was a licorice man
who's the most was the licorice but no his name
can demand
licorice
yeah i can demand can be land
yet
is not only is that the bill that for the villain guy
this guy scared to gloppy scare you now i thought last night scared you over
gloppy
gloppy is fun
if you land on gloppy space you lose a turn
hold on, candyland guys
characters, yeah
let's go through them
there's uh...
princess frosty, lord licorice
lord, okay, lord licorice
i liked mr. mint
thought he was nice
yeah, i think i talked about it before but i played the candyland game
for windows ninety five
all my god plumpy i forgot about plumpy
although i will be happy yeah
yeah he's a gingerbread plum tree caretaker
well look at this guy
he's a plum troll
the last of the plum troll yeah and then in the in the the candy land game for
pc
he you have to like
collect his plums or something
collector and and plus plus i'm not just because you know it's because your
your family's dead doesn't mean you can get me to put my hands all over your
plums. My family died, please touch my plums. I need my plums. Oh and there was
Jolly too, the gumdrop the gumdrop one. Oh yeah, I remember him. I'm on the
Candyland wiki. I don't know if you're there too. If you go to Jolly's page,
Um, it says "Jolly title placehold species dinosaur mole hybrid"
Oh yeah, yeah he's like a weird fucker. Jolly.
He doesn't look like a mole at all to me. He just looks like a creature.
What the hell?
There's just all the comments on Jolly, there's just like a hundred comments that just say "nice"
and just reply to each other.
There's all the characters and then somebody wrote "Gaba Ghoul"
smiley face. Oh yeah, I do see that. What the fuck is that? There's no...
There's no Capicola in Candyland. Enough redesigns! Stick to this version!
Just quit changing stuff and people will stop complaining. A squirrel could figure that out!
It's true. I think there has been too many Candyland redesigns.
Yeah. I'm gonna be the guy who's really pissed off that they're redesigning Candyland.
Yeah. Oh man. I'm gonna-
They made Gloppi a girl. They didn't do that. I wish they did.
What the fuck? I'd love to- I'd love to take her out to the Homecoming Dance.
Oh no. They-
Fucking- My brain just shut off for a second there.
Dude, the Princess Lolly character, who's a lollipop, they spell Lolly like the pedophile
anime thing. Oh no.
Oh, don't spell it like that. Respell it!
Come on, it's easy. It's easy to choose a different spelling.
Respell that thing.
That's not even how lollipop is spelled.
Candyland the Great Lollipop Adventure. Is that the PC game?
I don't know. Candyland PC game.
I think it came out in '95.
Candyland Adventure?
Dude, we can get it on Amazon.
It comes in a, is it a child's first game comes to life?
- Yes.
(laughing)
Yes, that is the exact one.
That's the exact game,
and you go to Lord Licorice's house.
- That's a really good tagline.
We should definitely order this.
- Yeah, play it on stream.
- Yeah, dude, we should.
- Yeah.
- You could get it used for 20 bucks.
- I mean, in all, we could probably, oh shit.
Let's read some one star reviews here.
I forgot Grandma Nut.
Remember her?
No.
She had peanut brittle.
She's the one who had peanut brittle.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah.
No, I was thinking about it because now I remember her.
All the related products for the Candy Land game are headphones and blue blocker glasses.
Yeah, real gamer shit.
Yeah.
Oh, dude, I'm fucking, I'm so, I mean, I'm going to complain about being tired.
I haven't done that in a bit on the show.
- I know, I'm tired as hell too.
- I literally like woke up from a nap
20, like--
- Dude, I'm exhausted. - 20 minutes ago.
- I was working hard all day sunning myself on the beach.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Were you sunning your perennium?
- No.
- You weren't? - The beach was crowded.
I can't do that.
- You weren't sunning your perennium?
You weren't-- - No!
I do that in the Porta Potties.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
- You were not absorbing the sun's light
through your perennium?
- No.
- Wow.
- Do you think, do the people who do that put sunscreen on?
They have to, right?
- No, no, no, no, no.
They don't believe in it.
- They're gonna be like sterile or something.
- Yeah.
- They don't know that.
- I guess they don't.
- God, do you think they like, do you think they just like being sunburned?
- That's freak shit.
Being sunburned is one of the worst things in the world.
I hate it.
- Yeah.
There's no way that like, I mean,
well no, 'cause it's like, I always do this where I say
like there's no way that X exists,
or there's no way that like X will,
but it's like, with the fucking internet,
the internet like hyper, like,
I don't know what the fucking, hyper normalizing.
(laughing)
The internet like, fucking, oh god damn it,
and everybody just does everything I don't know yeah I'm tired to let's just
keep talking about candy like no but just like the internet like the the amount of
information we have now as like boosted the amount of like weird fetish shit that
exists now and now there's like people like gun fetishes and like guys who like
like their whole thing is like like getting stuck in a bowl of porridge or
something like yeah yeah like you know you know what I mean just like I wish I
could I wish I could be buried under cement with a tube yeah exactly like
guys like that exist now I wish I could I wish I could fuck the pat of butter on
my mashed potatoes right like there's that guy now like that guy exists now
yeah and we need to stop it we need to put an end to people yeah with liking
things like sexually that people like things too much now people like yeah too
much sexually and they got it cut it out exactly so I think what Patrick is saying
is that sex is designed to be between a man and a woman yes in wedlock and it
It must always result in a child.
Yes, that is exactly what I'm saying.
Sex should only be for procreation and you should not be putting anything on your thing.
Yeah, speaking of crazy fetish stuff, Niko, shout out Niko, she sent me a diaper lover
clown that she found.
Let me see if I can find his.
he had a funny name if i remember correctly well it's not docs the clown
well no it's like a clown his name is docs the clown
crinkles the clown crinkles yeah oh my god this is up in clown outfits
and wears a diaper too and in a lot of the pictures
he has posters in the background of for legends of legend of zelda and mario
kart and teenage mutant ninja turtles damn
that's anyways big class
it's
with the diaper
that's a list of the uh... two worlds this should not meet
was that the other day
i mean is it like a is just a chat
is kept calling calling your penis your thing
is so funny
yeah it's still the funniest thing
It is.
Like saying like, "I shaved my thing."
Yeah.
My thing big.
I shaved my thing and I got hair on the bath mat.
My thing got to blood on it.
My thing crazy.
Ooh.
My thing wiggly today.
My thing...
Man.
my thing my thing my thing big baby dude do stuff that you think we should could
there's so much just like like late early 2010s hip-hop that just no one thinks
about anymore yeah well I don't think about hip-hop at all I'm more of a
rock-and-roller Wow you don't expand your musical mind no well I mean it's
It's basically like, you know, it's what, it's like talking in a beat.
So it's like I preferred when someone shreds.
What the hell?
I'm into stuff like Mumford and Sons where people, they shred.
Like I really like Florence and the Machine is one rock and roll band I've been getting
really into lately.
You should check out Iron and Wine.
Yeah, dude, Iron and Wine, I mean, throw a little kiss makeup on them and that's the
perfect band if you ask me.
yeah
comment
uh... the i'd like to be a little real rockers like the shins and arcade fire
yeah home and are killed by a day
date they'd shred did when they when they'd shred into a solo
there's a guy who's in the rock and roll but it thinks he's in a rock and roll
but he doesn't know a rock and roll is it also
the only where he can use the describe it is shreds
yes
the admin i mean i'm in a rock and roll i like like mac demarco and he's like
when he shreds on salad days i mean the shredding is just crazy when he does
get that i think i really shreds all day
i mean i didn't like when he shredded at that party that one time
it
i'd say bonnie bear i mean they should be a shred
real hard is bonnie bear one guy is that a band
i don't know i think it's a high end
dude i
When that shit was coming out, like,
Boney Bear and Arcade Fire and shit,
I hated that so much.
- Yeah, and like Vampire Weekend.
Did you like Vampire Weekend?
- Yeah, no, no, no.
- Yeah, no, me too, dude.
All my friends in high school were into it.
The thing is, when Vampire Weekend got really big--
- I liked A Punk.
I think I liked the first album.
- Yeah, there's some, I mean, they have some nice stuff.
- Right, but I'm not like,
there was people I knew who were obsessed with those bands
Death Cab for Cutie.
Yeah, like I don't give a shit about that.
Yeah, by the time Vampire Weekend blew up,
that was already, like my mom would just
had been listening to Vampire Weekend in the car
for like a while, like that was just in my brain
that was like, "Oh, that's my mom's music."
Yeah. And then it's like, yeah, it's not
that's not, high schoolers shouldn't
be listening to that. They should be listening
to Power Violence
or Breakcore or
like Ambient.
They should be listening to Project X Straight Edge Revenge.
straight edge revenge.
That's right.
They should be learning to not drink and do drugs.
Yeah, exactly.
I'm as straight as the line that you snort up your nose and I'm as hard as the drugs that
you wear on your clothes.
Well yeah, that's the thing is that people don't understand these bands like Boney Bear
and Vampire Weekend, they all are secret drug references.
And there's references to sex.
I mean, A-punk, you know what the A stands for, alcohol.
Asshole.
Asshole, alcohol, butt-chugging.
And a vampire weekend is actually, if you go on Urban Dictionary, that's a slang term
for when you suck the blood out of heroin addicts to get high off their blood.
Yeah, you suck somebody's arm drinks.
Yeah, exactly.
And it gets you so fucked up, they last the whole weekend.
actually what that name means yeah which is you know fucked up for high schoolers
to be listening to it's not okay we got a higher an editor to cut out my burps yeah
and I mean the the Arctic monkeys don't get me started oh man you know that's
squiggly on the other cover I do that with cocaine my that was like my that's
my brother's like favorite band I do not do not fuck with them do you know I
I can't stand them. I think they have you know I don't fuck with them but I did
like the soundtrack to that movie submarine that the guy the yellow
submarine yeah the one it's like that movie the yellow submarine yeah the
Arctic monkeys did was really good but yeah I just like that was like I don't
know those that was a band I just did not fuck with that like you know what it
It was like, I didn't like it because I thought people probably thought I liked it.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
Like that's why I don't like Radiohead because I feel like it would be too on the nose if
I liked Radiohead.
Exactly, no same.
I never got into Radiohead because I ignored them for a long time because I was like, oh
like this is, this like I already listen to like Neutral Milk Hotel and Death Grips.
I can't also be listening to Radiohead.
That's like, that's a hard line.
all three when you get all three of those in your fucking like you know that's like a that's
not yeah no yeah no good you have to you have to exercise some control you have to get like
you have to have like half of in high school like half your favorite albums have to be mu albums
and then like you have to pick something like you can't you can't do the whole thing it's not
gonna work right if you're gonna get you there's the triangle you can have like death grips and
neutral milk hotel and Radiohead you have to like you can only pick two.
Exactly yeah. And it's really gonna affect how you are as a person. Yeah.
Later in life. You're gonna get killed. Yeah by me. Yep. Well the reason I didn't like
Radiohead is like people were just so annoying about Kid A and stuff and like.
Yeah no people that the time that we were in high school that was like so that was
like the thing that you like went online and that was all the people that was
like the best album meme. Yeah and it was like nuts about it. Like I learned I
listened to Neutral Milk Hotel because I didn't understand why people were
posting pictures of the album cover and then I listened to it and I was like oh
this is pretty good and then I just never like gave Radiohead a chance
because I was like I just like yeah I don't care it's not it's not for me I
I just, I don't fucking give a shit.
- Yeah, it's lame, it's boring.
When a guy who has a radio for a head,
they did that in Transformers.
- I'm sure it's good.
I'm sure it's probably one of the best things
that you can listen to.
- Probably the best thing ever, actually.
- It's probably really good.
- Probably the best band ever.
- Yeah, I might think it's the best band ever
if you show it to me at the right time.
But if you show it to me, I'm gonna kick you.
- I'm gonna hit your phone out of your hand
into the sewer.
I'm gonna swing kick, I'm gonna fuckin' spin around
like I'm Ryu.
- That's right.
- And I might pull out a fireball.
- Yep, I'm gonna Hadouken you.
- Yeah.
- I have, yeah, I've been, you know,
I've been watching some Mortal Kombat tournaments
and I might stomp the ground like Tremor
and send a little earthquake after you.
Knocked you in the air.
- I've been playing Injustice, God's Among Us.
Look, I got--
- Yeah, I can't lie.
I might jump up on your shoulders like Catwoman and slash your face with my sexy claws.
Mm-hmm.
Could happen.
I might become sexual at you.
I might...
We might end up in a sexual situation.
That sounds bad.
That, I take...
Duh.
I don't like saying that.
I did not like saying that.
Yeah, that...
That was all fake.
Yeah.
I'll become sexual at you in a positive way.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- That fixes it, right?
- Yeah, that fixes it.
I actually wrote you a poem.
- Really?
- Yeah, to read to you.
Now that Caleb's not here, I feel like this,
I can read like a kind of a friendship poem
that I wrote.
It's called Cameron and Patrick Friendship Poem.
Okay, here it goes.
- I'm ready, I'm ready to hear it.
Okay, here it is.
This is a poem from my friend Patrick.
His smile is golden and his loveliness is magic.
- Wow. - Together,
we are always playing.
- There's more?
- You're my friend, I'm always saying.
We like to eat in restaurants
and scream when we see a ghost that haunts.
I like to hang out with him in a house.
I like to hang out with him with a mouse.
I like to hang out with him in a box.
I like to hang out with him with a fox.
Would you, could you, in a car?
Eat them, eat them, here they are.
I would not, could not, in a car.
You may like them, you will see.
You may like them in a tree.
I would not, could not, in a tree.
Not in a car, you let me be.
I do not like them in a box.
I do not like them with a fox.
I do not like them in a house.
I do not like them with a mouse.
I do not like them here or there.
I do not like them anywhere.
- Candace, green eggs and ham.
- I do not like green eggs and ham.
I do not like them, Sam I am.
I thought you wrote me...
I did, yeah.
Well, so...
You wrote like the first half of a poem.
Well, yeah, so I mean I needed a reference for how, like, I didn't know how to
like write a poem really so I kind of copied and pasted the text from...
Well, you know, I replaced stuff at the beginning and I kind of, you know, as it
went on I figured... Did you forget to do the rest? Is that it? Well, I thought maybe you would get the
gist of it by the beginning and I didn't need to... I didn't know, you know, the backspace
keys broken so I couldn't get rid of the other stuff I already pasted so I
figured maybe stop reading I thought you would written me a well I can't what I'm
not gonna stop in the middle I thought you had written me a whole thing I wrote
I mean I press ctrl V on a lot of it so and I was doing it line by line so it
was a lot of stuff took a long time I was copying and pasting each letter I
I really thought you'd like it.
- I guess I'll take what I can get.
- So where's your poem for me?
- I didn't know that we were writing poems this episode.
- I figured that it made sense as a thing to do, right?
That's what you do when you talk to your friend, right?
- No, I...
- You really don't have a poem for me?
- I don't have a poem.
- All right, well, then I'm glad
I didn't change the second half.
- Why?
- I said it.
sucks. I thought this was going to be different. Ok, here, I'll read it again and I'll just
read the first part this time. No, don't. Ok, I'll just read the second part then. Don't
read the poem again. Do you want to see the pictures I drew to go with the poem? Ok. Ok,
one second. And these better be pictures that you drew. Green eggs and ham images. What?
No, you're looking up green eggs and ham. I'm sending you a picture right now
Click on this
You're gonna like this. That's doctor. That's the cover. That's the cover of green eggs and ham
anyway, my
My poem has um is actually been greenlit to to become a Netflix series
Yeah, it just has no it hasn't it has it says um it says right here
Patrick's friendship series from Ellen DeGeneres to debut on Netflix in quarter from Ellen
After more than four years in the works Netflix TV adaptation of dr. Cameron classic
Actually it already came out in 2019 look at that I
Mean and listen to this cast
Adam Devine divine
Michael Douglas, Diane Keaton, Ilana Glazer, Eddie Izzard,
Tracy Morgan, Keegan-Michael Key, Daveed Diggs, John Turturro, Jeffrey Wright, and Jillian Bell.
This sucks.
This sucks. This has nothing to do with my friendship poem.
I thought I was gonna have a beautiful friendship poem today. I thought you were gonna like my poem.
Well...
What about the part about the ghost that haunts? Did you like that? I did. I'm worried I got haunted.
I'm worried I'm haunted.
Did you ever get haunted before?
Have we talked about this?
I went to a movie screening.
I went to a cemetery last night for Xavier.
Shout out to Xavier.
His screening of his movie.
It was in a cemetery.
And the whole time, I thought a Dracula might come out.
Yeah, might come out of one of the graves.
Yeah.
Well, the way you can avoid that is you look at the graves you're sitting near and if any
of them say Dracula or Vlad on them, you change seats.
Good point.
Yeah.
The shitty thing about sitting in the cemetery is like you go, you know, you move one seat
over and then it's like, "Oh shit, this one, this one is Walter Ulfman.
Walter Ulfman."
It's like, "Oh."
Oh yeah, well, okay, maybe maybe I mean that just sounds like a normal guy.
That just sounds like a normal guy is probably fine and then and then somebody
walks by and blocks part of the name and you go oh no.
Uh-huh yeah.
So you move to the other seat and it's Dr. Frankenstein's grave.
Yeah when you say well he's I mean he's not the scary one it was the monster.
Yeah so you know I don't have much to worry about here I guess he was just a
a scientist.
Man.
Yeah.
If I got haunted for the rest of my life, I don't know what I'd do.
Yeah, it would be tough to be haunted.
Yeah.
I think I'd probably suck it up.
Probably take it.
Exactly.
Lift yourself up by your bootstraps or whatever.
I wouldn't let my haunting define me.
Define me.
I wouldn't let the haunter find me.
i would hide
uh... doctor
i think that's a good look at the ghost could be a dracula
it should be a walter offman
the scariest thing about walter offman is uh...
his crimes
yet though he's done terrible things
yes
here you know it's almost
you know he's almost a large size of the worst guy when he's not aware of the
than when he is. He's done. I know it's just like the werewolf powers made him
you know even worse as a person. And the contempt he showed in court he was so
disrespectful to the judge. I've never seen somebody flip off the judge at the
courtroom before. I know and I mean he you know he has a good sense of smell
being who he is and I have not ever heard anybody described with such accuracy the
exact way in which the entire jury smelled bad. He told a gentleman in the
back of the jury box they could smell the come on his hoodie
and they took that juror out of the courtroom
because he was he was supposed to be wearing a hoodie he was wearing it under his button
down shirt
because he was afraid he would be cold
and they had to declare the whole thing a mistrial
that's how he got away with all of his crimes
Just too good at smelling.
Exactly.
He would...
Yeah, he smelled...
He could smell that the judge's wig hadn't been washed.
Dude, I wish, I fucking wish we had some stupid court system like they do in the UK.
Like their judges wear powdered wigs.
That's so fucking silly.
That is like...
It's awesome.
That's like if like I know there's nothing else like that.
That's like yeah.
I mean we're a powdered.
I mean the and they also they have fucking Bobby's.
Yeah they still wear Bobby helmets and shit.
Right.
Like that.
It's so that's so fucking stupid.
I think I think Bobby still wear the hats.
I think maybe if you're a constable you wear it.
They still have constables.
Yeah.
guards still wear them I think like imagine if you worked at McDonald's and
yeah you had to wear like a chef hat and like a whole chef outfit to work at
McDonald's yeah that's the same as making a judge wear a powdered wig yeah
it's just like a child's understanding of like what that person would look like
we should make politicians wear like like old sash yeah like a sash and like but
like dress up like old politicians like they have to wear like like five layers
of clothing and like a petticoat to like and just like so they're because I mean
the thing is they're all so old if they had to wear that many clothes 80% of
them would die of heatstroke immediately yeah just sitting in Congress or
whatever I mean hey these clowns these clowns couldn't take a hot car these
These clowns wouldn't last two minutes in a microwave.
I locked all my clowns in a hot car.
Oh no.
Yeah, well it's like you're walking through like the grocery store parking lot and you
see like a golden retriever like locked in a hot car and you're like, "Oh my God," and
you like look around, you can't tell who owns the car, so you go and you like break the
window and then like 500 clowns climb out and the guy comes out of the grocery store
like only bags he's like really possibly
you're like fucking clowns
what did you do to my clowns?
so I'm never gonna be able to get them back
they're all they're scattering
that's what happened when there were all those clown sightings
in like 2016 or wherever
whenever that was
man that's I mean
so remember that fucking shit
so fucking stupid did you ever like encounter
a clown? yeah yeah there was one
There was one in downtown Boston.
Yeah?
He was standing outside of one of the dorms, dude.
Oh, that's right.
You were in the dorms then.
I was in the dorms and there was a big glass window like on street level.
And there was a clown who was just like walking around the street.
And then, if I remember correctly, there was also a guy in a Mario outfit.
Which made it a little less scary.
Yeah, I mean it was around Halloween.
It wasn't close enough to Halloween to be wearing costumes.
I don't remember exactly when it was, but I remember being like...
"These guys are up to something.
"You can't be doing this."
- There was, I was in community college at the time.
I was at the place where I was living in Laconia,
and there was a clown sighting there.
Someone was in the parking lot.
So it's obvious, it's like,
"Oh, that's somebody who lives here."
But kids on the floor that I was living on were like,
"Yo, there's a fucking clown out there."
- Yeah.
- And they were like, they all got ready
to like beat the shit out of whoever it was.
Like, I think they like, somebody like saw the clown guy
and like screamed at him and like ran downstairs
and like the clown ran away.
But it was just like a stu, like, it's like,
that could be just like your roommate.
Like that's like, that's so fucking stupid.
To run after a clown?
Who paid me to run after a goddamn clown?
- I'm on the Wikipedia page for 2016 clown sightings.
yeah on october to share that one was not notable on october twelve the russian
embassy in london issued a warning for russian and british citizens because of
the clowns care
man i i i miss i miss when shit like that was news you know
the village of
membrane cook new brunswick
asked residents not to dress up as clowns on halloween
threatened clown purge yet threatened threatened clown purges an incredible
Wikipedia heading yeah threatened there's a heading that says hunts and it this is
all that's under it many people took baseball bats to the streets to hunt the
clowns college students formed mobs campgrounds floated with rumors of clown
attacks see also bin laden sightings in the United States yeah the most famous
famous clown, Osama Bin Laden.
He was a clown, dude.
Yeah. Bro, you're trash.
You're trash. You're a fucking clown, kid.
You're a clown. Yeah.
Just like talking to a, like,
in 2001, talking to Osama, like,
like the way that, like, a FaZe Clan gamer
trash talks.
Yeah.
Wow, kid, you're fucking trash.
Clown.
You're a clown, dude.
You're a bitch maid.
Bitch maid doesn't get thrown around a lot anymore.
No, we gotta bring that back.
Yeah, that was something some kid called.
The evil clowns were bitch maids for real.
I heard someone call someone that in high school.
And I was like, oh man, that's...
That's just wrong.
That's cutting. That's like for a high schooler to call another high schooler that.
You were made by a bitch?
Yeah.
who gives you an evil shiver down your spine just to hear it
reported bin laden sightings
yeah what's the deal with this
is this like a
slick up
well i'm sure
was a and i'm not looking at yet
and then we'll be sending very well-meaning and serious about her
current concern told emergency dispatch
badgers that she encountered osama at a seven eleven
- Oh, baby.
- In Utah, so that was probably some fucking Mormon lady
who just thought every, I shit on Mormons too much.
I'm sorry to all of our Mormon listeners.
- I don't care about our Mormon listeners.
Don't be Mormon.
- Yeah.
- I don't give a fuck, I don't give a shit about you, dude.
You better be an ex-Mormon.
- How many times have I talked about Mormons on here?
- They're evil.
- Probably a lot.
It's a weird, I mean, I got called,
I made a joke on Twitter about Mormons and I got called a religious bigot.
They're not a religion, they're a demonic collective.
I guess it makes sense to, I don't know, I don't want to justify this person calling
me that.
But it's like, I guess you could say the same thing about Scientology to people, like if
like shitting on Scientology because it is technically a religion.
Yeah I mean but then you just get into the you know.
I'm trying to be more open.
The like Reddit atheist territory where it's like yeah everything it's all technically religions
but it's you know it all sucks.
Yeah.
Hey man.
Hey have you ever thought about how religion is a crack of shit?
Yeah.
Check out my new movie Religulous.
It doesn't even sound like Bill Maher.
they need to check out my new movie
religious yeah
do you have any how many different title
ideas do you think he went through he's
like rigidly did she kill us ridiculous
drink rich rigidly ridiculous it because
what it's supposed to be a pun on
ridiculous it doesn't work at all it
does not it doesn't work at fucking all
and that movie is so it's so funny and
just how much of it is just him being just a smarmy piece of shit.
There's a scene of him just talking to a guy dressed up like Jesus and the whole of the
conversation is just him going "but really?"
He loves that dude.
He's a really guy.
Let me see if there's any interesting trivia here on IMDB.
Yeah, that's probably a good... I mean, how many times do you think he almost got the shit
kicked out of him?
During the sequence set inside the Dome of the Rock, Bill Maher and his guide were approached
by two men who were upset and then proceeded to speak in Arabic and supposedly talk about
how Maher is "not funny". In actuality, what they said was "We don't normally hang out
here" and "The boss only gives us five minutes".
What a fucking asshole!
What a loser dude!
They were just walking out like, "Man, I wish I had a better lunch break."
And he's like, "These religuliculars are..."
"These Muslims are mad at me for being too funny."
"Isn't that Islamuliculous?"
Yeah.
I was gonna say, is Islamabad a thing?
That's a city, I believe.
Oh, then the joke would have worked.
That's the capital of Pakistan.
Oh no.
All of the S's on the DVD's closed captioning are dollar signs.
Whoa.
All the captions, they just made the captions unreadable.
Yeah.
Why dude, that's not even like sending a message or anything.
No, not at all.
That's the most annoying thing you can fucking do yeah, they just had a unicode mix-up when they were writing the captions
Yeah, I mean what a what a guy oh man bill are demands of viewing
For one thing he makes it so clear how illogical the mass amount of people can be
Illogical fucking who wrote that review Spock come on true yo
Yo!
Come on now.
Come on.
Yo!
Who's writing these movie reviews?
Is it Spock from Star Trek?
I mean, come on.
We should make a documentary that goes around to prove religulous wrong.
Religulousalist.
Yeah, religulousalist.
And we just go to everywhere that Bill Maher went and talk to the people and we're like,
"See?
It's actually pretty cool."
This guy's a nice guy.
This guy's pretty cool.
Hey, man.
Hey man, this church is pretty cool.
They didn't let me skateboard at this church, but I did have a good conversation with them
about God.
You know, the creationism museum didn't like reading any of the placards.
Some of the statues they got are pretty cool.
Great worksmanship.
We went to Mecca and we had no problems.
yeah got a say a bit
the chilly dogs at the food truck outside the creationist community
absolutely delicious bill maher has no idea what he's talking about
he was blinded by his atheism
he couldn't enjoy a simple hot dog
so you probably think god created this hot dog what are you talking about
man i don't know i don't work at the museum
yeah i don't know i don't work at the museum what are you talking about in the
closed captions say like
i am your enemy
I shall strike you down with my sword of faith.
Speaking perfect English.
Yeah.
Oh man.
Man,
Bill Maher,
You're the sucker of the week.
Bill Maher, I got one
finger for you.
My ring finger. That's right.
Bill, if you're hearing this,
I love you so fucking much.
And I know it's a long shot,
but it would mean the world
to me if you would take my hand in marriage and together I I mean we
wouldn't be married in a church right maybe a secular ceremony an unholy
matrimony oh yeah you will listen bill I got one finger for you too and guess
what is my pinky and I'm gonna make you smell it after.
I'm just gonna put it in a vat of hot dog water.
And you're gonna smell it.
Oh boy.
Alright dude, home stretch.
Five minutes left.
Yeah.
minutes left yeah then we can both go to sleep I'm dude I have a I have the
second half of a Cubano in the fridge yeah I'm like I'm waiting for that yeah
so good dude it's it's like clear that Caleb and I both like that sandwich
because we like the movie chef a lot yeah I still never seen chef but I mean
I mean, it's the perfect sandwich, I think.
- I think that just looking at the food on Chef
will make me throw up.
I don't want it.
I'd rather eat a Cheez-It.
That's all I'm gonna say.
Dude, if they open up a food truck
that sells Cheez-Its and Goldfish.
(laughing)
- Dude, it's just like a restaurant,
a food truck for picky eaters.
- A food truck that sells Goldfish
I go up to it and they hand me a handful of goldfish and I throw it on the ground because
it's flavor blasted.
I wanted these plain!
Where the fuck are the pretzel goldfish?
Oh, I hate those ones.
Yeah, they suck.
Just eat a pretzel.
Pretzel, I know, just, there's like too much air in the pretzel goldfish.
Pretzels and hummus I think is maybe one of the best snacks of all time.
I'm not-
And making it into a goldfish is kind of-
I'm not too big into hummus.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
I'm a big hummus fan.
Yeah, I think in terms of like...
Hummus is one of the number one components of the straight edge stoner mindset.
Yeah?
Yeah.
That's, instead of, you know, instead of sitting around and hitting a dab pen and like, and
reading, like watching like YouTube essays about 2001 A Space Odyssey, you sit around,
you shovel hummus into your mouth, and you read about Pokemon or something.
And that's gonna change your life.
Straight edge stoner mindset, you eat a handful of baba ganoush, you don't smoke a bong and
watch roosh.
And go sploosh.
Yeah.
Yeah, exactly.
Hey man, I'm wearing all tie dye, you'll never see me high high.
Man.
Yep.
- Man.
- I think hummus unfairly has dominated
the Mediterranean dip marketplace.
- I know you're a tzatziki guy.
- I think tzatziki, number one dip.
- It's very good.
Yeah, but the thing is that that's like--
- It's very filling.
- Yeah, it's also like--
- And it's not as light as hummus.
I get why hummus is.
I think more people--
Hummus is more accessible.
- Hummus is also, I think, you know,
for what I would put in hummus is like pretzels
or carrots or something.
which i don't know you could do that i guess you could do it
feels weird with pretzels presence is he is good
is it maybe i'll get some susie
i can barely find susie
no grocery store
the grocery store
i go to know what they are going to let me in there for five minutes uh...
it sucks i keep going to keep going to the you know what's that show called
supermarket
dash or so i don't know
yet given guys grocery games yeah i go to the guys grocery games groceries man
yeah i know i mean it's it's a really hard shopping for groceries lately cuz i
only have about like
forty five seconds before they realize i'm walking around without pants like
when he the poo
and i think i think that the exit
they usually does let me keep whatever i have i'm holding up to
they're more interested in getting my
my hit my one centimeter thingy out of the
i'd like to be old lady on the scooter
the right for him
i totally i'd totally do fit
when i had that like the when the knee injury was that like the peak
my daughter died
i'd never went on one of those
fuck i don't think i've ever been on one of those in my life
i i remember we were we're at the we're at neil's lake house and we went to a
shop right
and
I saw a lady leaving on one of them and I was like limping around the store and I was like
Why the fuck didn't I just do that? That would have been so fun. Are you kidding me?
I can't drive. I'd be going around the store like a fucking gta
online character
Just like fucking driving into everywhere. I would topple over rubber banding from from leg. Oh my god, dude
I'd go
I'd be on that i'd be in that store doing missions. Yeah
(laughing)
- You gotta go--
- Yeah, going up to the deli counter
and they're like, "Man, we don't have any missions for you.
"Please, this is, it's a deli counter."
- I would ask the people I was with for some missions.
I'd be like, "Oh, you need me to go get hot dog buns?
"All right, set up a ramp for me."
- 45 minutes later without hot dog buns.
- But like $1,000.
- Sorry, I was stuck on a load screen.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- All right, that's good, that's enough.
- Yeah, that's it, that's it.
- Bye bye. - Fuck you, that's it.
- Bye.