You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[EXPLOSION]
All right.
Woo.
That was close enough.
We're here with Felix.
We're here with Felix on the show.
What's going on with him?
Oh, he's getting a rip.
Getting a rip in.
He's getting ripped off his pod.
Yeah, I have a new pod.
I have like the Nord where you have to click the little like...
Oh yeah.
The VPN.
Yeah.
That hits different.
Spooking a VPN baby.
Yeah.
That thing's crazy.
It looks like a Mio water enhancer.
Yeah.
That's why I got it.
No, it's a LED fucking thing.
I don't know.
I wish I didn't have to hit the little fucking doodle on it.
You have to hit a button?
Yeah.
Oh, that's game breaker.
It's sometimes nice to have the button though.
sometimes nice when you can pull your own it's nice to have some sort of feedback
yeah exactly it's like a jewel like my like if my jewel pod leaks then it's
like if I try to hit it then it just doesn't work for me the most important
thing is always just that it sounds like a cigarette does in a movie uh-huh you
know I mean where it's like a crackle that no real cigarette has ever made but
like a jewel makes that crack right so it kind of tricks my eye it tricks my
brain into thinking I'm smoking a cigarette a little bit that's the best
part
loud cigarette. I want to find out which brand is the loudest though. I think
camels are pretty loud. Because you crush them. Exactly yeah you have to crush them
they have all that that tinfoil in them. Juice. Yeah that juice and the tinfoil.
Camel crushes are very important to in New York the b-boy community. Yep exactly.
They provide. Yeah it's one of the hidden pillars. Yeah. Michael Rappaport
didn't learn about that pillar until he was 45. No, he'd randomly picked up smoking.
Yeah. I was laughing about like being like 30 and picking up smoking recently.
Oh that'd be amazing. For me it's almost as embarrassing. I didn't start
smoking till like two years ago. Yeah. Like middle of college. I didn't smoke a single
cigarette until college. I don't think that's that. You were what like 19, 20 when you
started smoking? Yeah. I don't think that's that bad. I don't know. I
I started when I was like 13.
- Me too.
- That's cool.
- Did you read The Outsiders too?
- No, no.
I just like, I like, I saw like older kids smoke them,
like kids I knew were having sex.
And I was like, this is, I thought it was like AP classes.
Like, oh yeah, if you do this now,
like you're going to be set up down the line.
And that was not true.
- I read a million little pieces and I was like,
I'm never doing a drug, dude.
I was just lied to.
You read A Million Little Pieces when you were like 13?
Yeah when I was like, yeah, maybe even younger.
Oprah recommended it, of course he was gonna read it.
Yeah, I was part of the book club.
No, my big brother was into like any book that was like,
like, what's that other one?
Perks of Being a Wallflower?
Like any book about like a sad, got a sad white guy, like,
selling drugs.
A Million Little Pieces and Perks of Being a...
Those are two very different books.
No, they do stuff in the book.
What do they do?
They have sex and they do drugs.
Yeah, well anything like that my brother was super into and he would make me read
Did he make you read the audiobook?
Perks of being a wallflower, man growing up religious must be fucking crazy. It was insane. Yeah. Yeah, it's really weird
You didn't grow up religious at all. No. Well, yeah, I read Master of the Senate
Yeah, perks of being a wallflower for me, I mean it was like it was like
Discovering like the clash. Yeah
I was like wow, there's this whole other world
that like I had no idea existed discovering guys who were a bit you
were basically discovering being too into the Smiths yeah a hundred percent yeah I
yeah no I watched perks of being a wallflower when it was like I forget what
situation I watched it in it seems like one of those movies it's just like on in
someone's house that no one cares to turn off yeah it must have been one of
those and I was like who the fuck is this movie for and yeah no people who grew up
religious that makes sense absolutely people who grew up religious who like are
trying to rebel against their parents but that's somehow the movie they need
it well they need to do it in their brain right they're too scared to do it they
can't they can't rebel actually but like in their head they're like I'm fucking
yeah I need somebody to do drugs for me exactly it's drugs by proxy exactly I
would that would be a good book if he just started acting like Morrissey
The most racist kid in high school?
Yeah.
[laughter]
Just saying like Chinese people are barbarians and shit like that.
When did he start being so racist?
He's was racist, like he said, I think, 2012 he said something about
he made the "Chinese people are barbaric for eating dogs" comment.
He specifically...
And then the anti-Muslim stuff.
Chinese racist against the Chinese?
Yeah, Chinese people and then the Muslim stuff happened in like 2018.
Oh, gotcha.
He became like a Trump guy.
uh...
this was said
huh you have a shaved head
more see does not have a shaved head uh... more see is very famous haircut
does he get a still got it
he still does have what does she is not a good the cat
now we're good nothing happened or
okay
the cats are constantly attack the equipment will record now
snark it's yoda yoda likes to eat the cables
it's not fucking good did
has got to turn my volume up a little other to turn your volume down i think
I think he did. Oh my god. There we go, that's better. That fucking rascal.
Um, yeah, I have a, if you can tell, Felix, I have an extremely shaved head right now.
Yeah, it's reflective. I'll take the wide angle off. I thought we were gonna need it.
You can see this fucking bean I got. Wow.
I just walked into the corner store to get a beer, by the way, pass me a beer.
And I walked in and there was like, just like this black guy was like standing right at the door
And he was in the- he was mid-conversation, I walk in with my shaved head, he's like,
"Yeah, but- but holy shit!"
*laughter*
Yeah, and I wanted to tell him, like, "I have feelings, man."
"That doesn't feel good."
"I'm a good guy!"
Yeah, like, I'm not- I'm just- I'm cursed.
It's not a- *laughter*
I didn't do this on purpose.
Why- like, what was he saying "holy shit" at, like, how-
how bald I am I think yeah cuz I shaved it I shaved it down to the skin yesterday
and I think he might have just been like he might have been like might have been
like a Chris Tucker holy shit you know what I mean
pressed he's a holy shit that's cool yeah all he said to you it's all he said
yeah and I didn't have the the hutzpah to just be like what are you talking
about cuz I also knew yeah I guess definitely about my you could have just
been like yeah I know yeah I'll just leave it's funny you buy the beer for me
I'm 16 I had a really bad holy shit like that like two or three years ago it was
when Street Fight was in town and we're doing like a show at Littlefield I think
and me and Brian Quinby from Street Fight like went to the gas station to
cigarettes or some shit and I showed the woman at the gas station my ID and she's
just like one of those in tri-state goblins.
There you go honey.
Just the secretary from Monsters Inc. the slug.
Oh yeah Ross.
Mike Wazowski you haven't filed your paperwork.
She looked at my ID and was like you're 27?
"Ugh, that's a rough 27."
(laughter)
And to be fair, at the time, I didn't know what face wash was or anything, but it's like,
"Come on."
Like, you were like,
that's just someone who like,
actually lived years of their life in Delaware.
But I took it. I didn't have to hide it.
I was just like, "What am I gonna do?"
Well, also, I have such a reverence for just like, service workers,
'cause I'm such a good guy. I'll take a lot of shit.
lot of shit today we went to some diner the Red Arrow Diner oh yeah yeah yeah
Manchester Red Arrow Diner with them, San Luberto. It's now the Sirius XM Red Arrow
Diner. Sirius XM bought it. Yeah. It's fucking insane. After they kicked out Opie and Anthony they picked up the Red Arrow Diner.
They needed something more racist. So I walked in and I I was like I ordered to
go and I was like yeah it'll be to go and she like didn't acknowledge it or
anything so a couple minutes later I was like yeah that's to go by the way and
she was like yeah I know like you seem very excited to tell me I wanted to spit
in her face but I was like yeah okay 25% I'm going to get the biggest tip of your
life I mean she deserves it yeah is that just a Manchester thing no they have they
have a new location so the red arrow was a Manchester thing and then it got like
too famous because every politician went there so now they have to put red arrows
and like fucking Portsmouth. They have a pretty fucked up picture of Hillary in
that. Oh they have like the most fucked up picture of Hillary. It's like her face is
completely washed out. Like if you like wanted to convince me of Hillary being
like an actual reptilian you would have to show me that picture and that gif of
her being surprised. Yeah she looks transparent. Yeah no yeah I totally see it yeah. Oh no I
I meant like service workers like that because I feel like...
Oh, being shitty?
Yeah.
That's a New Hampshire thing.
Or just New England in general.
New England.
Yeah.
My mom does that.
New England is like...
The only place I went where people didn't seem like that bad of a mood all the time,
weirdly enough, was Boston.
Yeah.
Boston is...
Well, Boston everyone keeps to themselves.
I mean, Boston you just have like nice, rich Chinese people.
Yeah.
Like there's like...
No, you don't have the like white trash of New Hampshire.
- Oh my God, the best.
- The best white trash.
- Best white trash is Hampton Beach.
Hampton Beach are like a really rich suburb in like Auburn.
- Yeah.
- Those are like the most like white,
they're like cosplaying white trash though.
They're white trash and then they went up.
- Yeah.
- And then they got rich
'cause their landscaping company
got fucking bought out or something.
- Yeah, the landscaping company with the logo.
- With the Looney Tunes.
With the Looney Tunes on the side of the truck.
- That's a big thing here apparently.
every landscaping company has a Speedy Gonzales
as their landscaping logo.
- Yeah.
- Nothing to do with landscaping.
- To show how fast they are at landscaping or something.
- But also the other one had Elmer Fudd.
- Yeah, Elmer Fudd and Taz.
- What is that supposed to insinuate?
- Elmer Fudd was very rarely successful
at any of his tasks.
- Exactly, why would you use him as like,
- Oh, there was one.
- Or as good as Elmer Fudd is at hunting
with that for landscaping.
It's like he famously never killed the rabbit.
- There was a septic company that used to do
like the like that used to like empty the septic tanks and shit in my like
childhood neighborhood that had Yosemite Sam on the side of it
Elmer Fudd would be a good mascot for like a like a Teflon company that like
dump stuff in the water and they're like this is what we turn people into yeah we
make people into Elmer Fudd. Yeah I don't know yeah I think that must be why I
like Boston because most of my interactions in New York are with rich
Chinese people. Yeah. Just from like where I live. Like far out in Queens. Like that's...
Exactly. Yeah, no, it's a good way... One of the best types of guy you can be in New England.
I, um... Definitely. They all work in like, like, uh... Oh, shit.
Bio-pharmaceutical technology or some shit. Yeah, same with my area. Yeah, it's like,
you know what like it's good going yeah probably better than rich americans were in china like 120
years ago yeah they're not showing us for yeah for opium yeah exactly yeah not yet yeah no we might
know we're doing that ourselves in new england yeah we're killing ourselves with opiates they're
just killing themselves for opiates yeah yeah uh yeah if the time comes i think it would be
that could be the next phase of my life being a traitor a traitor you think so yeah yeah
like it is you know
no no a traitor
like uh...
uh... between my country all i think you know i got a i_d_ i think it'll be in
truth and others without thinking to as it would you do you like an opium
trader and like that like middle like pittsburgh what level of trader we
talking
uh... i would you know i mean like
chelsea manning alike colin kaepernick like young that
i thought i had one holiday i forget that i thought that i thought that
Yeah, the lowest being Chelsea Manning.
I is going to go with Kaepernick.
Yeah, I would do the thing where it's like I'm just their local proxy and I tell them
who to bribe and open up opium shipping routes.
Damn, that'd be genius.
That might be a good line of work for you.
And then like, yeah, probably 60 years down the line, we become communist and my grandchildren
get killed in a cultural revolution.
yeah that's the circle of life we go to China we go to like we go back to China
and do the opium wars yeah again and again and again over we're living the
same 180 years over and over again except now we have like cooler guns and
shit we have like John wick stuff yeah nowadays soldiers would be on their
phones all day exactly now it's on your gun yeah gang is Khan would be like gang
Genghis on his phone. Genghis console.
That's what his name would be now. That's right.
You doing alright Cameron?
Yeah, Cameron's taking this episode off because he's sick.
He's been, there's a succubus taking him down.
Cameron ate too much Red Arrow and he got the...
That is true. Yeah, you got the Dina, or you got the Queen Mo.
These fucking Nazis serve beans with breakfast, dude, and they're delicious.
That's the fucked part. That's the most... that's the worst part of it.
Oh, they do it Anglo style there?
Yeah, man.
Yeah, they do, like, English breakfasts here.
How fucking... as an American... talk about a traitor.
Uh-huh.
Beans for breakfast.
I think...
Double Kaepernick.
Oh, my...
Exactly.
Don't even say two Kaepernicks, dude. You're gonna make me flip my lid.
I don't know if you've seen my haircut.
That's two D's on the ground.
Two D's on the ground.
Yeah, and he's praying to Allah.
(Laughter)
No!
God damn.
That would be a good Jack Ryan movie.
He has to prevent Colin Kaepernick from
(Laughter)
One full prayer to Allah during a football game
or it will ruin football.
(Laughter)
Damn.
Yeah, I fucking...
Is that still going on? Is he still trying to do football?
Colin Kaepernick? Yeah. I think so. Good for him man. Yeah. My grandpa's not gonna let
him I'll tell you that much. Yeah I know. He'll fucking stand in the tunnel of
whatever team it is and body block them. My grandpa is so racist but only about sports like
outwardly. Like one time he was watching... That's like still like accepted. I mean that's kind of the highest level of racism.
True yeah. Like one time he was watching golf and I was at his house and he was
he's just watching golf some tournament like the mid 2000s and Tiger Woods was
was up and just completely unsolicited he's watching Tiger Woods play golf he
said you know that guy's only famous cuz he's black
he actually sucks at golf
he's terrible
he's terrible also golf famously so welcoming to black guys
so think of golf affirmative action
it's those clubs that only let in black guys
I know, it's crazy dude.
He's going nuts.
Oh the cat's going nuts?
Fucker's going nuts again.
I hate your cats dude.
I'm back to hating them now that I'm seeing them again.
This is our first time seeing each other in months.
Yeah.
We're very excited.
I think, who had their balls in your face last night?
Was it Yoda or Fucker?
It was you.
It was me?
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
They don't have balls.
They have a little cashew between their legs.
It's not a cashew dude.
It looks like a cashew.
It's an empty balloon.
There's nothing in it.
I've always wondered this, like, how did you decide to get, like, that's, cause like I've
never seen anyone with that breed of cat.
The Sphinx cats?
Yeah, Sphinx.
Yeah.
How did that come to be?
I just liked them.
Cause he has fucking fetal alcohol syndrome, what do you mean?
That's why I made that decision.
I just wanted a cat that looked like Caleb.
Oh, come on.
I just missed him.
No.
They're cool, like, how did you find them?
Just like a shelter.
The internet.
Yeah, isn't it like the most expensive kind of cat? I think so. Don't say you're supposed to deny it, dude
I don't say yes to that. You don't you don't have a job
Yeah, the pot about list patreon is or the subreddit's about to go crazy about how they're paying for Patrick's cat happy
Yeah, we need to get our subreddit shut down like you did that was genius. Yeah, it's one of the best moves
We've ever it was so smart dude. Oh my they weren't they weren't that expensive. How was that the best day of your life?
Honestly, it was something things have been getting better since then I'm not yeah
Much good things so many good things have happened to me since that happened. Yeah, and I can't be a coincidence
That was not getting no seriously like I like I never
read it like I I
Think I had like just a low level of like just ambient annoyance with it existing like the idea of it was like Israel to me
like I first got mad about Israel as a child because it was like you're doing
this in my name and I felt the same thing seeing people post like shitty memes
where it's like 10 paragraphs of text and then gritty with the AK-47 I was like in
my name. Because you feel like it's your fault, like you should feel responsible
for Israel you also felt responsible for the Chappatrap subreddit. I feel responsible for it too.
yeah all white people should I know this really big streamer on twitch trainer oh
awesome cool oh me too his name's Hollywood over here some people got
their jubilee some people got their train wrecks yeah I he has like he has a live
podcast thing called scuffed and like it's one of those things that like most
people on like our media consumption bubble I've heard of but like yeah
50,000 people watching it once oh yeah I was I was on there and I was with like a
bunch of people like big streamers like people who five years ago like everyone's
doxing each other swatting each other yeah everyone their articles about how
bad their fan bases are and I was the only one whose subreddit had been shut
down. That rules. I'm trying to kind of navigate my way into where you are
where I'm trying to become a pro pro gamer as well as a podcaster I feel like
that's a sweet spot. Yeah I mean well like you you're starting like eight years
before I did so like you getting worse every day. It is funny learning
It's funny learning like, it's funny that Counter-Strike pros have a, it's like
basketball like once you turn 26 you go way down. What's your FaZe Clan name?
What's your handle gonna be?
Mr. Awesome. Is that good? What about FaZe Mr. Clean? I don't know any of them. I know FaZe Blaze, FaZe Swag, FaZe One.
I was on Scuffed with Faze Swag.
You told me that's one of the funniest things you've ever said to me.
You were on a podcast about, was it about like racial politics?
Yeah, with Swag.
He's a very nice young man.
He rocks, dude.
Yeah, he's great at Call of Duty.
He's fucking awesome at Warzone, yeah.
I do think it's funny though, just like,
do you know Hiko, the old CS pro?
Oh yeah, Hiko's like 30, and the only reason, like,
he's an amazing player and has like
like amazing game sense and shit but it
would be hard for a 30 year old to win
consistently a Counter-Strike. The only guy
I know of who's like 30-31 who did
really well is Faze guy OlafMeister
uh-huh that is such a fucking... I do know him yeah
he made that name in like high school and
just couldn't change it. That's the fucked up
part about all these pro gamers is
that in like high school they were like
I'm gonna name myself furious destroyer
yeah now they're 35 and they're like I
I'm on an NBC show and I'm a furious destroyer. I'm credited in a movie.
I love the gamer names where it's like they just heard a word and they're like
that's a gun word. FaZe Panopticon. Yeah, the guys here name like Panopticon
Ultimatum. Perfidious. FaZe Raytheon. I mean I did that in high school or in like
when I was when I was like 14 and I made like a Steam account I named my Steam
name was Sci Theory.
It's just get this it's a it's a combination of psychology and theory.
I don't know man. That's how you know you're a gamer but you're also thoughtful. Exactly I was yeah I was a
mentalist. I'm thinking about my next move in the game. Yeah I'm always ten steps ahead of the
competition them in their head theory did you have an embarrassing gamer name I I
like the most embarrassing what I did cuz now yours are all like hunter Biden's
pussy is trash AF yeah I'm still South Park rules in Valorant which is great
cuz you you always bait one guy yeah in the voice chat who's like hey man South
Park does a rule man Carmen Carmen's funny as hell bro chef is
chef's black balls bro that's the funniest shit I ever seen man respect
that was that I did you have that day when we played with like that invaders in kid
oh my god yeah absolutely yeah the most random man on earth what did he kept
saying like he's making like George Floyd joke yeah and he was like he was
like oh man if we lose this game I'm gonna rape my mom yeah dude you see you
see so much swag yeah he was like a caveman that got frozen in ice from 2007
Yeah, it was like his first day on something awful right and he was like dude. I'm gonna take all these jokes to Valorant. Yeah, I
Got I'm gonna rock on Valorant voice chat, bro. You've been on the fiat forms
It's been really cool to watch me go from Jim watch Jim Blunt go
Yeah, there's nothing like fucking team chat in a video game. Yeah, cuz you just always get a kid like that
I like I've been getting I've been solo queuing CS a lot. No one talks to me because my name is always like
the gay guy
Became so funny to me it is
Just like this stupid as simple. Yeah, my my steam name is still
My YouTube poop name with the name that I made YouTube poops under when you were like 13. Yeah respected
It's still wargers, which is another thing of just like a combination of
What are you need another beer? I do
It's a combination of what just a combination of things that I did. There's sounds I put together
Well, that's the highest level highest level of gamer is like just random sounds. Yeah, right
For example, like sci-theory, you know what I mean? Like this is genius three random syllables thrown together. Hmm
Yeah, I mean
Opening that oh you got it. Okay?
Yeah, all the really good CS players now are just like gorlocks and smack. Yeah, my favorite
There's a valorant pros name is just food. Oh, yeah
Food is really these are really good players. He's great
Yeah, there's a valorant streamer. I see all the time. That's just Wardell that were tells me out
I love it. I keep why it's Brandon Wardell
I keep thinking it's Braden Wardell playing Valorant and shit.
Dude, Wardell, he owns, dude.
Yeah, I've seen a couple of his games.
I've heard that he was like not a very good...
This is for nobody, by the way. This is just for us.
I know.
I know, right?
Wardell was like a... He was not a very good Counter-Strike player,
but he's great on Valorant.
Well, yeah, I mean like...
Valorant... Again, this is also...
It's for bad... It's for bad CS players.
I know you think this, Felix. Come on.
I... Well, it depends... I mean, Braxton "Swag" Pearce
was gonna be like the American,
God damn, this is really for no one.
- I know. - He's gonna be
the American simple,
but then there was the match throwing scandal
and he's like, he's very good.
There are a lot of like great CS players
who are there just for different circumstances.
- Nitro just switched over to Valorant.
- Yeah. - Whoa.
- Yeah, so that'll be huge.
Let's get off video games.
- Yeah. - Let's get off like
very specific pro scenes in video games.
- I know, yeah, it's insane.
I mean, it's funny 'cause to me,
like I was never into any sort of like competitive gaming until Valorant
because it was like it was the only game that I played with a competitive scene
because I just grew up playing like Halo and shit and I never was aware of like
any sort of Halo pro scene although I guess Ninja was like a Halo pro right?
He was yeah no a lot of those guys who like blew up in the last three years were
big-time Halo guys or like Gears of War guys. That makes sense. Like games you would never think had a
competitive scene. Yeah, Gears of War having a competitive scene is insane.
Saints Row 3 competitive scene.
Who can be the funniest shit in Saints Row the third?
Tildo bats only.
Tildo bats only rounded in fucking...
What's that? Oh, I thought it was gonna say Port Carverton, but that's Skate 3.
Yeah, you're wrong. Is there a competitive skate scene?
There is a competitive Skate 3 scene.
That sucks, dude. Yeah.
That shit gives me so much anxiety. Like, whenever I would read
the former Gears of War pro, I would just think of the economics of being a Gears of War pro.
It's like, what's the most, if you're like the ninja of Gears of War, what did you make?
Like $18,000 a year?
No, dude, you made like $400 bucks and won first place in the world.
You're the greatest of all time.
Every Gears of War competitive match is probably just a giveaway.
It's fucked up.
It's fucked up because if the truth is, to be the greatest player in the world, you have
at any video game, it takes as many hours as like becoming an engineer.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
And like, and if you were the greatest engineer in the world, you'd be a millionaire.
But if you're the best at fucking playing like...
Conker's Bad Fur Day, you're not making any money.
Right.
It just, it gives me severe anxiety.
Like when I see like, I like watched some YouTube clip of like,
this is the Gears of War tournament in like 2007 or something,
like the major of Gears of War.
And it's like basically sharing floor space with like, you know,
like it's all in for fans of Law and Order.
Yeah, yeah.
It's one conference hall.
It's at a family guy meetup.
Yeah.
It's more competitive.
It's like the fucking Yeah, it's the the dream hack of Gears of War.
And it's like, if you spent 12 hours a day, six or seven days a
week playing like yeah Kane and Lynch until you like you didn't learn anything
else like when you turn 28 and you're like oh my reflexes are too bad to play
this game yeah like all right time to be a lawyer yeah well but you but you got a
lot of pussy that's the truth yeah you went up to you and I was a girls at the
at the at the bar and you were like yeah I'm actually the number two player in
conflict desert storm in the entire world so you might want to watch my penis right
now I'm gonna look out for that I'm gonna look out for my penis blow up I have c4
strength to it what's even worse is like the people who play pro games and they're
just sport sports games oh like that's the bad and competitive UFC game
competitive - shit so sick dude I always feel like I have like a twinge of
sadness for those guys because it's just like it's like when they make a wire mom
for monkeys it's like oh it's like so close yet so far to being a pro football
player. Exactly yeah it's like well I'm amazing at imagining being Bo Jackson in
my head right you know like I'm so good at that. They should just give them
coaching jobs honestly. No.
They would.
What we need to do here is press X four times.
In this match.
I'm gonna need you guys, look, I'm gonna...
Talk about some guys who'd be anti-Colin Kaepernick.
I think the pro Madden gamers maybe is the number one anti-Colin Kaepernick constituency.
Yeah.
I guess the same argument can be made for competitive Tony Hawk players.
yeah I was like no shit do more of them skateboard that then the best there's
not a single Madden pro that plays football like flats the trail now like
in a league of children oh they were all like amazing at Tetris and then they
stopped making money off Tetris and they're like I'll just play this instead
it's true yeah you know I'm playing it so I should do it I mean that's the
nature of competitive gaming is that every game except for stuff like
Counter-Strike or League has like a year and a half of like competitive peak and
and then they all move to a different game.
- It's true. - Yeah.
- You know, so they have to constantly--
- Right, 'cause you can't, like, it's not like no one's,
like, you can be the best at, like, Madden 2012.
- But Madden 2013, they put an extra button in,
they put a juke in there.
- They made a whole new soundtrack.
They got Mellow Hype on the soundtrack.
- You gotta get used to the soundtrack, yeah.
- That would be the worst thing.
You have to keep buying Madden,
and for like 90% of Madden pros, does it even,
are you even, like, coming out ahead?
Are you breaking even on buying Madden?
60 bucks. The 70 bucks with the pre-order and the like fucking sticker that you get
with it? No, definitely not. This could be like my most stereotypical trait but I just get so
much I get economic anxiety for other people thinking about their jobs.
That's the most Jewish thing you've ever seen. You're just thinking about
the the Epoch Times writers and you're just like oh yeah yeah when I see
someone who like works for OANN I'm like oh his retirement accounts in shambles
I can't I can't say it's like I have the they live glasses for that stuff yeah
actually that's the second most Jewish thing you've ever said to me the first
was in Call of Duty warzone you said I'm great at sniffing out money in this game
And then the fucked up part is there was a time where everybody on our team died except Felix
and in like 90 seconds he bought the whole team back dude.
I did buy, I bought 14k in like 90 seconds.
It was the most, like directly after he said he was great at finding money in the game.
I found 14k.
It was crazy, he was like skipping over crates he knew had nothing in them.
He was like, I can just tell dude.
- We should get Felix into the competitive
deal or no deal for DSC.
(laughing)
- It would be great.
It would be great on a game show.
- Yeah.
- No, all this, my entire media career,
has been leading up to deal or no deal
coming back and me getting on there.
- Is it gone?
I didn't even realize it was gone.
- Yeah.
- Oh my God, dude.
- Yeah, Howie Mandel hasn't been doing,
he got the fucking, he got whatever that show is.
It's not The Voice, it's the other one.
- Howie Mandel?
- America's Got Talent.
- That was forever ago, dude.
Howie Mandel was doing them at the same time. He's doing them both at some point?
Yeah. Damn that is why they call him the hardest working man in show business.
It's true. Yeah it's funny that he won't shake a man's hand. Yeah. Kind of sus
Howie. Yeah. It's kind of sus to shake a man's hand let's just... No. Nah. Nah that's respect.
Yeah exactly. No respect is the straightest thing you can have for another
man. It's when it bleeds into into something else that's that's when you
Yeah, Howie Mandel.
If the pinkies touch.
If the pinkies up while you shake the hand, that's us.
Yeah.
Cause then what is it, like a beverage to you?
What are you drinking?
What's this, a beverage?
You gonna drink me?
Huh?
You gonna lift me up?
Yeah, big guy.
Do you guys know anybody who's ever on a game show?
Just by odds, I got it, right?
I mean like...
Yeah, right, at some point.
Yeah, I actually know Watson from IBM.
Yeah.
We're close friends.
I mean like I guess I think being Ken Jennings follow each other
That's not really like knowing someone. I guess true
Yeah
My dad was on some game show in the 90s and this was back when you make like if you win the game show you make
$600 yeah, you know and I think they might they asked him like it was all like
They would show him like a stop sign and they'd be like if you're on the road
What do you do when you see this sign and he got him? All right, he's perfect until the end
they asked him some like science question they like showed him like an equation
they were like solve this they knew he was getting too close yeah they couldn't
lose 600 bucks back then that was like the most the show had ever made on cable
TV manufactured the wheel yeah I had to sell the wheel to pay my fucking dad but
that is the reason my parents got divorced my mom brings it up constantly
really she's like yeah my life would have been different if your dad had won the
The final question was about child support.
[laughter]
My parents were in a situation where they knew each other too well
to really even care if they paid each other child support.
They were just like, "Eh, pay it when you can, I guess."
That's the only reason it worked out.
My dad does not have a job.
Yeah. Yeah. No, he just he runs an illegal poker room and a storage unit.
That's that's that is what that's worked.
And then he launders the money through a construction company.
Cool job.
You should see it, dude, because when I was a kid, I used to have to like put
Fritos in the fucking pantry at the poker room.
It's not that cool.
No, I mean, it's it's not like it's mostly direct TV.
That's why people come. Yeah. Yeah.
Who gets invited? Like it's like I'm seeing like a lower level poker game.
Yeah, there are high level legal poker games. But so like, it's like David's game.
Toe for Grace is there.
The people that would go there would be like the guy who won salesman of the month at the
Kia dealership. Yeah, right. The big ballers in Wilmington, North Carolina.
Gambling with fucking gift cards that they wanted a call center.
Yeah, Blockbuster gift cards.
Yeah.
I had an aunt, I still have an aunt, she's alive, makes you rest in peace, Aunt Phyllis.
She would, until maybe two years ago, every year she would give me a $15 Blockbuster gift
card.
And it was after Blockbuster closed.
So she just had them?
Apparently she stocked up for 10 years with Blockbuster gift cards for every niece and
nephew she had.
Damn.
And she kept them in a drawer.
She was just giving, she had no awareness that Blockbuster had been closed for like 10 years.
Well there's still like one open, you could have gone to Alaska.
I could have gone to Alaska, that's a great point.
Yeah.
I don't know if it was valid in all 50 states.
Oh that's true.
Yeah.
I had to find out.
Do you still have them?
I mean probably, like I mean it's just for breaking into houses now.
Yeah.
You know, just figuring out how to jimmy a lock.
That's what the Blockbuster gift card has become.
That's true.
Do you see how they tried to do like a...
The 90s room?
No, they did like a thing on Twitter where they got on the Blockbuster official account
and they were like, "Oh yeah, we've been chilling."
Yeah.
Or whatever, like six days ago.
That was for the Airbnb in Seattle.
There's a 90s themed Blockbuster Airbnb.
That's horrifying.
I know.
The worst part about that tweet was like every brand from the 90s, just like Chuck E. Cheese
and dominoes commented under it and they were like oh bro we miss you
my dick dude it was insane yeah it's horrible I just guess you know they
don't have like the blockbuster gift the blockbuster Twitter account also has
like 9,000 followers yeah even like when Twitter started like in like 2008 it's
Yeah, and nobody cares.
No.
I don't give a shit.
Not at all.
I, um, I had a flashback to like one of the most annoying-
You know like when there's just like a-
It's like a hall of mirrors of people being annoying?
Where like-
Wendy's, like, Wendy's made some like, you know,
It's good, just like, if you're gay and want to eat at Wendy's, cool.
You know, because-
This don't eat the bacon it might, the baconator might turn you straight.
You might want to be careful.
I know you don't want to piss off Allah.
These gay guys, they definitely don't want to piss off Allah.
But they, yeah, they had some dumb shit tweet like that.
And then like, the, like, you know, people who were like, guillotine Ray Jepsen were like, pay your workers more, my bitch.
And then the woman who ran the Wendy's account was like,
"I think it's interesting that Bernie supporters are targeting Wendy's,
which is one of the only brands identifiable as a woman."
[Laughter]
What?
Oh my god, dude. The psychosis these people are fucking experiencing on a daily basis.
That's what every day in 2017 was like. Like Trump just made people so annoying all the time.
Just made them crazy, dude.
Yeah, fucking come and go the gas station has a tick tock account
Dude, nice. Oh, what the fuck? What about come and see tick tock account? Yeah
Be pretty funny. Yeah. All right now we got something cooking
When mom makes an idea work and it's the guy crying
That's right, yeah now I'm excited for
Just all of it just to relive every moment of 2017 again next year. Oh my god. It's gonna be amazing
If Trump what I mean, that's if Trump wins, but if Biden wins we'll have like a reverse 2017. What do you think?
What's your predictions? Um, it's just like we roll we roll everything back to like
2009 like Michael Ian black just like
Breaks out of a cocoon. Yeah, like you see like he has one treat. It's like
January 19th or whatever the day before inauguration is is like, you know guys
For all the pain and suffering that happens in this country
We believe that America could truly be as great as the founder said it would be but for POC
for disabled people for blah blah and then the tweet the next day is like
I'm dumb sucking disabled dick in the Holocaust
How come how who
What baby do I have to rape to get some sweet low
They're gonna bring back Michael and Michael have issues when by the yeah, they will absolutely back Michael and Michael have issues
They're gonna bring back human giant. They're gonna bring. Yeah. Oh dude Aziz is getting uncanceled. Yeah, he's coming back
Oh my god, every as soon as Biden gets elected people would be like Aziz. You're such a hero for fucking that annoying woman
(laughter)
Thank God!
Aziz, for doing that move with your fingers, we've now decided that that's cool and that we're gonna like that.
Dude, we've now decided you're just chill as hell, dude.
Where's Wiz Khalifa? We gotta get Wiz Khalifa back.
There's like a parade right after inauguration.
For Aziz?
Yeah, for like, the people that walk out of Biden's limo are like,
Tyga, Aziz, Crystalia.
(laughter)
Hey, they're back!
Chris DeLea is doing his face again! Dude, he's epic, oh my god. Yeah we get like-
Oh my god Joe Biden, thank you so much! We get like old school memes back, we get
Philosoraptor back. Oh my god, we're gonna have socially awkward penguin at the
dais of the uh, of the roasts that are coming back. Jeff Ross is coming back.
Greg Giraldo's coming back to life. Greg Giraldo's coming back to life. And he's gonna roast the socially awkward penguin.
He's gonna destroy him in court. Oh my god. Oh man, every meme will be about how Justin
beavers gay and a girl. Yes. Oh, which is true. We're gonna bring back his haircut.
Yeah, the bowl cut. The bowl cut. It became the k-pop haircut. It did.
Yeah. I don't think it's gonna be like that extreme but like it is
like... You don't think so? You don't think Greg Geraldo's gonna happen? Well I think that will happen.
Okay. Everything else. I do think there's gonna be a rollback on a
lot of stuff because like every, like if you have like liberal parents, they've
gotten hyper engaged since Trump but the promise of Biden is like hey you don't
have to pay attention to this shit again yeah so every everyone whose job is to
like write about like the Paris commune for Condé Nast that like the second
that bite his hand touches that Bible it's gonna be like well you're done
that's how it is like that's how it is like the we did this thing for a G the
company genius in 2016 we're like we would just take like shitty news articles
and like be really mean to the writers. That's funny. And the day, literally it was during
Trump's inauguration, they were like, "Oh yeah, we just don't have it in the budget for this anymore."
Like that's how quick it moves. Like, well, you know that Biden's not going to be putting
his hand on a Bible, you know it's going to be a Quran. Oh yeah, for sure. For sure. It's going
to be a Corona. That's right. Yeah. I pledge allegiance to the beer. Yeah, I'm fucking,
I hope that that happens.
Yeah, that would be sick, dude.
We get, uh...
Every mom that's made like a parody song about Trump...
Just evaporates?
They're just gonna disintegrate.
My mom was not a liberal until Trump.
My mom was a hardline conservative
until she decided Trump was too mean.
Yeah, a bunch of those people are gonna like...
Some of them are gonna stay, but like for the most part
there's just not gonna be the cultural space for all that.
and like yeah I hope that slides back because like it's easy it was easier to
make fun of her as a conservative now I just feel like bad for her you know I
mean she's like super into Pete Buttigieg it's like god damn it dude like
if you just fucking if you just still like the day that Obama got reelected I
walked downstairs and my mom this was her idea of a cheeky joke she was like hey
son welcome to the US long pause SR
crazy that those jokes are still being said though I miss that shit dude no
like people are doing that about Trump now like people are like oh like every
every president you don't like them they're Russian right that's the truth
yeah or never ended I wish I had like that type I only have like one real
conservative in my family and I have a neocon uncle. Nice. Hell yeah. So he's like
he'll never do like the you know the funny like a bungler stuff but he'll be
like um this you this Council on the United Nations that has absolutely no
power and has never stopped Israel from doing anything they're actually
anti-semitic and it's like whatever man. Dude the conservative Jew is a that is a
a that's the supreme conservative. Oh he's awesome. He's awesome. Like his he just
like all he does is like respond to articles that are about like some like
academic who died in 1989 and he'd be like why Harold Tuck is still matters in
the face of Jew hating Muslims. Well because conservative Jews get to
do the thing where they mix conservative politics and like liberal like identity
politics yeah so they get to be like yeah the war in Iraq was bad but just because
it was like kind of annoying for Jews yeah I like I've seen a lot of like
conservative Zionists be like do the I'm so tired thing oh I'm so tired of being
Jewish listen buddy I'm Christian and I have open arms let's go anytime I'll
baptize you that goes to you Felix if you want to be baptized go to
neighborhoods over in Queens let's do it baby I got a bathtub for me it is it's
free you're somebody's Shabbos boy but all you do is baptize
you can't make it through an entire Shabbos without turning Christian
by Caleb. By a man with no hair. My goy tricked me. I'm a Christian with no hair. I wasn't
allowed to turn on the light. It was too dark in my house and he baptized me. So you just
have one conservative relative dude? Oh all my relatives are. Well not you, of course
sell you know you're in my aunt's house today all for blue lives matter we went
to we went to Patrick's aunt's house which is drove by he hasn't been there
in years literally has like six blue lives matter flags on the front porch so
sick dude come on London Dairy hearts are cops and then the heart is the blue
lives matter like next oh that's great I like I had like a lot of friends when I
lived in Minnesota or like friends that like were in rural Illinois whose parents
were like you know like had Ann Coulter books and shit like that and they would
try to like you know get me into an argument with their parents but the art
like it was just like well I don't like you know like Obama like yeah that's
always the confusing yeah they're like well what do you mean you are a liberal
correct and I fit my beliefs are so like weird that I'm like my main thing is
like we need to dissolve NATO and they're like, okay.
Sure. I don't know what that is. Is that a video game? Sure. Yeah, it's fine. Yeah, I
remember getting in arguments with like, because I grew up I mean, North Carolina,
it was pretty hard to like, go to a friend's house and not get into it. I mean,
it's obviously as you can tell, very politically minded young man. And I would
go to like my friend, his my friend, Chad, his parents house, and they and I would
argue with them about whether 9/11 was an inside job and that would be that would
be my version of a political argument yeah where I'd be like it's somebody did
it I don't know my parents are on that tip now yeah my parents are like my mom
last time I saw my mom we were talking about new JFK conspiracies Felix is
Jewish you can tell us straight up yeah what's up you guys do it well the thing
The thing is, this was like, you know, success has, you know, many parents, but
failure is an orphan. But that's also true of 9/11. A lot of people worked really
hard on this. We would love to take credit for all of it, but we couldn't have
done it without the Mormons and the Deep State. Yeah, exactly. You had
collaborators, you know. The Mormons had to do it. They had to find the pajamas under the
towers. It's like that movie New Year's Eve. It's like so
many people worked on this it's hard to hate right you know what I mean there's
so many big names attached. They got Mr. Bean and Louis Veracon.
I like yeah I um my dad was kind of a conspiracy boomer but like in a tongue
and cheek like he would yeah he was like he was like one of those liberals that
hated the CIA like he remembered like the Church Committee and all this shit
but he was also like, "Bill Clinton's a good president."
Like just totally like incongruous liberal boomer beliefs,
but he had like, he had fun with it where he'd be like,
"Yeah, John McCain's a Manchurian candidate,
but they deserve that for what we did to them."
(all laughing)
And it was like, that was like the only guy.
My brother, my sister has really interesting,
like weird contrarian opinions.
I think it's just like,
she's the smartest person in the family.
And I think just like, if you get that spark,
You just, you have to come up with like just insane things that you can argue,
just have fun.
But like everyone else is just like, you know, like my, my uncles are like,
really nice. They're really great dudes, but they're also like, you know,
I thought, I thought Julian Castro was electrifying.
And me and my sister are like,
the Black Eagle Trust Fund was formed in 1983 with the express purpose of putting
the Knights of Malta in power and then did 9/11.
Yeah, it is funny, like, liberals get so magnetized to politicians.
Like, my mom is not, again, she was not a liberal until fucking three years ago, but she went to,
she did her master's degree at Walden University, which is an online college that's like bankrolled
by the Clintons. And so like every year they have Bill Clinton come be the commencement speaker.
And so my mom did her like master's commencement or whatever and she and my
mom has always been like Bill Clinton is a rapist piece of shit and then she came
back from her trip to Minneapolis and she was like Bill Clinton has the most
electrifying eyes I've ever seen.
She's like something about his yes gravity that pulls you in.
It was the most insane fucking like coin coin turn I've ever seen.
- That is amazing.
- Yeah.
- It rocks.
- My neocon uncle got married to like a resist lib.
- So nice.
- He's been married a bunch of times,
but he, she would always like email me,
like basically pleading with me to be a normal lib
because like I could like, I used to get mad at my uncle,
but like after a point I was like, okay,
I'm like not letting him get me mad
because his opinions would be so ridiculous.
Like he had this weird thing where he played,
he had this way of saying that like Elliot Spitzer
cause the recession in 2008 because he prosecuted AIG.
And after a while, like after I got old enough,
I was like, okay, I'm not gonna let that like get me mad.
But his wife, like my aunt would email me and be like,
I wish that you could meet Hillary Clinton
to see what a great person she is.
I know you two would get along.
And I was like, that's like really nice of you to say,
but she's Satan.
I actually agree with my uncle, she's Satan.
- Just for different reasons, but like--
- Could you imagine the Hilary Chapo episode?
- Would you guys let her, would you,
if she said, I wanna come, I wanna chop it up,
all right, I want me and Joe Budden to come on the podcast.
- I wanna go to the trap house.
- Yeah, I want us to come, are we gonna squash the beef?
What would you say?
- If she was down to do like a hangout,
like riff on the news episode, yeah,
but not like an interview episode.
- No. - I just don't,
like, I don't know, there are only a few people
who are like good interviews.
- Well, we have her right here.
you think she would be good at riffing yeah I think so I think like I mean that
you know we came we saw he died riff was pretty good it's pretty good it is
truly one of the all-time great riffs yeah I guess you're right
what was weird because people were like oh that like the way she laughed on that
proves she's bad and it's like oh we're good what about like all the stuff she
did. Who gives a shit? Like, if you're one of those people, if you're an Atlanticist who thinks that
NATO should police the world, of course you would think killing Gaddafi is an objectively good thing
with no negative repercussions. But whatever. That's why I'd have her on. I think she was
unfairly targeted for laughing during that. As someone who's had a lot of stuff of my own taken
out of context. Buy your subreddit. Yeah. Buy your own. What kind of
questions would you ask Kaler? Would you do like top five dead or alive rappers
and comedians? Yeah I would do Marc Maron style questions. Who are your guys?
Yeah. You're kind of like the Patrisse O'Neil of American politics. If you had had ten years where you could
practice guitar what jam with after if you could fuck Frank Zappa's daughter
would you do it I know my answer
before can you get into him can you get into that mark I mark Marin gives me
pause because I think like there's a real risk I become like that's what I'm
like when I in like only like 20 short years hmm no you know the thing is the
The way to get Mark Maron is like 30 years of just like begging to be a successful comedian
and then getting successful doing something other than comedy.
Okay, yeah.
That is the-
My dad worked with him.
That breaks a man.
I've talked about that before.
Huh?
My dad worked with him.
Oh yeah, you guys worked- they worked at Regina, right?
Yeah, well it wasn't Regina, it was called the Sports Depot.
It was just a restaurant.
My dad used to drink whiskey in the basement with them.
Your dad has such- his dad has such an interesting web of like famous people he's interacted
with.
He used to bully Jeff Bezos in high school.
No, no, no, that was-
that was Dom's dad. Oh it was Dom's dad? Yeah. Oh that's even better.
Yeah. You guys are like the opposite of the Illuminati, your families.
Like Patrick's family, it's like they have all these connections to famous people but
it's just like weird coincidences. Right, it's like he worked with Bobby Kelly.
Yeah. That's pretty big. Yeah. Actually Bobby Kelly's gotta be... I was watching Louie in high school and he's like
"Oh I know that guy." That's so funny. Bobby Kelly has to be like, I mean that's like
the lowest level guy you let in the Illuminati, you know?
He makes $40,000 a year off of radio and TV appearances,
but you're like, yeah, okay.
- Yeah, he's cool.
- Yeah, sure.
- We'll let him in.
- He's so funny.
- That is, that's a cool way to get into the Illuminati.
I've been reading this book,
"The Family of Secrets" about the Bush family,
and there are like, there are like all these pages
where it's like, and then they form this like
oil services company that was perfect
because the CIA could hide all these funds,
and then they killed this guy and then blah, blah, blah.
- JFK.
- Yeah.
- Like there's just all this like satanic shit in there,
but then there's like, oh yeah,
and I guess like Prescott Bush
just thought this guy was funny.
So he paid him $5 million a year to be in this company.
- Yeah, it gets you further than you would think.
- I would, yeah, that's, if I, if there wasn't podcasts,
that's what I would have tried to do.
- Be the funny guy in the Bush family?
- Yeah, just find the most evil family I can,
like in Chicago and be like,
Like I'm fun to be around for them. Yeah. Yeah, it's like a Dean Martin Jerry Lewis thing, but with like Illuminati like
Felix is like marrying into the Emanuel family
That was my other plan if like there was no podcast or articles
Just power just because you're cool to be around. Yeah, that's what happened with Jared Kushner most
Relationships in LA. Yeah, pretty much. Yeah. Oh, yeah, I know Aaron Carter
No, yeah
I I think it's an amazing accomplishment to be close to the Illuminati as an entertainer and not eat like
The fact that Chris Tucker was on the flight logs, right?
My first thing isn't like oh, he's a pedophile. It's like oh
"Oh wow, they just liked Chris Tucker so much."
They're like, "Yeah, you can see all our blackmail."
(laughing)
- You're so goddamn funny.
- Yeah, that's the highest compliment to an entertainer.
- Yeah, dude.
I mean, that's gotta be crazy for like,
like imagine you've been in the Illuminati like 40 years.
Right, like you've been,
you paid your dues in the Illuminati, right?
And you're still like a low level Illuminati guy.
And then you walk into work one day
and Rick Ross is your boss.
*laughter*
And you're just like, "What the fuck dude, Mastermind is not a great album."
Yeah, it's just like James Baker or some other Aran Kondra figure.
It's like, "Well my kid says he's great."
And we really hit it off. And you're like, "What the fuck?"
*laughter*
Look, I like blowing money fast.
I put years and years into fucking pedophilia just for this guy to come in and ruin it.
He's sagging his pants all over the office.
*laughter*
Jim, are you kidding me? I killed Gary Webb.
And that was 30 years ago.
Yeah, now I'm cold calling for Rick Ross.
Jesus fucking Christ, dude.
Yeah, I'm becoming one of those conservatives like,
"Oh, I got fired for standing up against affirmative action."
But it's like, yeah, Rick Ross got added to the pedophile Illuminati.
And he went way higher than me, just 'cause he's a black guy.
Yeah, just like Tiger Woods.
It's like Tiger Woods in golf.
He skips every, he skips the hard part.
Never paid his dues, Tiger Woods.
He sucks at golf, let's be honest.
He sucks, right?
Look, I can hit a hole in one probably more times than him.
Yeah, dude, it's easy.
Take me and him out on the links.
I'll show you.
I'll show you he shouldn't be here.
Listen, here, we'll settle it.
I'll rap battle Rick Ross.
Fine.
Rick Ross, they only, yeah.
People just say he's a good rapper because he's a black guy, just like Hyder Klutz.
Did you ever follow Rick Ross on Snapchat back in the day?
I did not have Snapchat.
He had, well yeah, you're an old man.
If I downloaded Snapchat now I would get arrested.
Yeah, immediately.
Yeah, that's what they're waiting on you to do.
They're just fucking, the FBI's just, "God, I hope he downloads Snapchat."
He used to have these snapchats where he apparently is like a, he has a mansion and then he has
a farm of llamas.
Oh yeah?
And so he would walk around his property just like feeding macaroni and cheese to the llamas.
I mean like, my llamas are always fed very well.
It was sick dude.
I just remember, that just reminded me of, I was trying to find it the other day, it
was just some Danny Brown tweet I saw in high school and it made me very self-conscious,
just said uh if you snapchat another dude you gay
i mean absolutely owned yeah yeah uh there was one i found i was trying to
find that one and then i found another one
um that was like bat the new great theft auto game is called
ballot of gay tony
i do remember that being a huge thing in the eighth grade community
Just like, "What, I'm doing missions for a gay guy?"
"They put a gay guy in my favorite video game?"
Well, that's like, the gay marriage Supreme Court case also passed just a few short years after Gay Tony.
Just because of Gay Tony.
Yeah, the Gay Tony expansion and the Battlefield Vietnam expansions, they allowed gay marriage to pass in the Supreme Court.
There was a lot of, yeah, Battlefield Vietnam, Gay Tony, when Mitt Romney was, he was in New Hampshire actually,
And he was in it might have been that diner you guys are talking about and he just sees this like crusty old man
He's like, oh this guy would will be like
homophobic with me and
The guy is just like I fought for my country in Vietnam and I love a man. What do you say to that?
Romney like he like spin bodied and like clip out of the restaurant
I miss Mitt Romney dude. It's funny that he tried to like he tried to be anti-Trump for like yeah
Well, you had that picture with him. Yeah. Yeah, I remember that for just one year
There's like a crazy amount of politicians that come here like there's politicians all over the wall at the red arrow
But the airport diner is like the one where they go to like get away. I watched it
Did I ever tell you that the Ted Cruz thing?
I saw Ted Cruz at the airport diner in Manchester and that guy has no fucking control of his kids
me and my girl calling him out yeah Ted Cruz fucking get him did wrangle your
kids what they do one of his daughter slammed her face into a pancake and then
his wife just like wouldn't look at him when he talked to her first off get your
kids in control second of all your bitch in control she's not paying attention to
you doesn't make any goddamn sense brother yeah but yeah we I think my
girlfriend got a picture with him and she's like doing a really like she's like
closing her eyes like in the picture she's like that's pretty good it's a
good picture I got I had like a I was like very hungover and I got too nervous
to take a picture with Ted Cruz no I did she went over and got the picture with
them his wife took the picture of her and Ted Cruz and I went outside to smoke
because I was like that man is so evil I'm like god that's one of the most evil
people I've ever seen. Yeah that's the best just like yeah just fucking meeting some like it
It just any Republican politician would be like, "Wow, the evil in that room was palpable."
I'd go outside because I was afraid of what I would say to him.
I was afraid of myself, the devil that would come out, if I had to fucking talk to him right
then.
I would just see red.
I'd be one less bastard in the Senate.
Yeah, the truth is there would be some new viral video for conservative Twitter of some
fucking dumbass 18 year old being like, "You totally suck."
yeah that is what would have happened but you you you're a total asshole suck yeah
seriously just like David Cross's comedy in 2008 like Bush you're a craphead you
suck crap and that's it I am that's why I was good that I went to New Hampshire
for the Republican primary is the first time when I was like 25 because I just
have that like, if you see them you have to see something or you're complicit
like that thing. Because I would just see Tom K or John Kasich and be like
oh he looks like a hobo. Yeah see Ted Cruz, be like what an ugly guy. Oh he's so much
uglier in person. That beard's doing nothing for him because you know
you when you see that beard in person it's like probably patchy. He looks like a conquistador.
Yeah he looks fucked up. He looks fucked up in person. I saw him put a lot
of food in his mouth. Yeah he seems like he would not chew a lot. We went to a
Carly Fiorina event in, I don't think it was Manchester, it was like St. Elsam, and
it was like the Carly Fiorina, it was like the Carly Fiorina like death march.
It was when she was like pulling in single digits after like conservative meetings, like Carly Fiorina is
actually having a moment. Actually no one's gonna vote for Donald Trump and
they're all gonna vote for Carly Fiorina to give us all jobs so we don't have to
start the Lincoln Project, but it was just clear her campaign was anemic. No one
wanted to support her. No one liked her. Like literally at the debate she was
like, "You might not like me, but you definitely want to see me debate Hillary."
And people were like, "We want to see Trump do that." But we came in there and
we were trying to, we were covering it for Cafe.com at the time, and there are
these two like six-foot-four mass holes on the floor. Like they're wearing like
floor-length leather coats and had balding ponytails.
Yes, sickest kind of ponytail.
And they were just like, you know those little pussy
Northeastern Republicans, the guys with the quarter zips?
These guys were just partying.
These mouseholes were just partying them like the sea.
And they were just screaming, "Where's Collie?
I want to get a picture taken with Collie!"
That rocks.
And I always wonder if those guys became Never Trumpers or what,
because it's like you would see them be like oh Trump voter but they were just
like we love Kylie she ran HP so good they're like they're never Trump but
they also own like a fucking like auto auction yeah it's an auto auction in
Pittsfield Mass yeah god damn that's called like Frank auto auction Tony's
Tony's foreign auto. There's a lot of those around here. Oh yeah. If I had access to like
Echelon or any deep state technology I would like track those guys down. Yeah.
What are your opinions on what's happened since you tried to get your
picture with Carly Fiorina all those years ago? Turns out that's like one of my uncles.
Goddamn. Alright. Felix, I have to piss so bad, dude. Thanks for coming on, man. This is very fun.
Yeah. Excellent time. Thank you for having me.
Do you have anything that you want to tell people about?
Yeah, you have anything to plug?
Yeah, I know that we don't have a 100% overlap with your podcast, but whatever.
What do I have to plug? We are probably doing our George H.W. Bush episode soon.
I'm pretty excited about that.
that that was gonna be really fun we've all gotten obsessed with the bushes very
recently it's pretty easy to get obsessed with them nicely
there's so much yeah do yourself a favor watch a 60 there's a 60 minutes
interview with HW from 1980 that you can watch on YouTube and he is the like you
won't be able to believe this country elected him like he's the most
unsettling fucking guy in the world oh yeah of course he sucks like a goblin
Like he's just a straight goblin.
All right, yeah, people should check out that interview.
60 Minutes 1980 interview with George H.W. Bush.
You'll get yourself excited for the episode.
We'll let the people know.
The Lincoln Project.
Felix has been doing a lot of great work with them.
Dude, your tweet, you're killing it with the tweets.
Oh my god.
On the Lincoln Project.
Your Regina George video was great.
I have a new one I'm trying to tease.
It's "Stop trying to make MAGA happen.
It's not going to happen."
All right, man.
- So definitely when you see that, retweet that.
Thank you guys.
- Of course, at any time.
Bye y'all.