you're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
Okay, I just hit record.
I want to see what happens.
We're recording. You can't.
It's out of my hands.
We can watch the video and record.
What video? Exactly.
Sharpest bismuth kitchen knife in the world.
Peso Patrick's in LA.
- Patrick's in LA.
- Yeah.
- Patrick's in LA now.
- What's up guys?
- Yeah, oh my god, this is an alien feeling.
- I know, this is crazy.
- It feels weird when you've done this.
- To not just like say something
and then you four seconds later go, ha ha ha.
(laughing)
- Ha ha ha.
- Yeah.
- Ooh, mama.
(laughing)
I forgot about how good the podcast is when it's live.
- Yeah.
- Shit.
Yeah today at my work a guy came in and he was dressed in like a LARP outfit.
He said he was like Peter Pan. He looked like Peter Pan or Robin Hood, one of the two. Or
Robin Williams. He was wearing, it was green. Yeah that's true. That's both. Yeah that's kind
of the combination. Yeah and he was holding a big. Robin Peters from Hook.
a big staff, he had a giant staff and he was like "I'm here for the shoot" and I was like
"I don't think there's a shoot but I like I guess I can check" and he was like "I'm from
experimental media" I was like "okay I'll go check if there's an experimental media shoot,
I'm pretty sure there's nobody here I don't think but I'll go upstairs and I'll ask" and I went
upstairs and I was like "is there a shoot today?" and everyone's like "no" I was like "yeah" so I
thought I went back and he was gone. Yeah he disappeared. He threw down. What if no because
He came to teach you a lesson and his job was done so he just, he just dissolved.
If I hadn't gone upstairs to check you would have cursed me.
Yeah, he left to go, or no, somebody came downstairs and was like, "Oh, it's Robert, okay.
Robert, right this way."
Yeah, the CEO of the company.
Yeah.
Peter Pan.
That was him.
Robin, Bob, Peter Pan.
My favorite character.
My favorite character from Hook has got to be either Robin Bob Peter Pan or Robin
Bob Hook. All names start with Robin Bob. Yeah Robin Bob Rufio. That's after Big
died. Yeah. Right after Christopher Big Black Boykin died. Robin Bob. Robin Bob.
Oh well today so I just got I got in to school yeah to school
congrats I'm in school now good work after got the first grade you got
accepted into the first grade yeah trying for four years so hard to pass
kindergarten yeah but I got in today and then I was hanging out I went I went
skating down Sunset Boulevard and then I was immediately saw just like a
dude attacking a group of skateboarders and I got so nervous. I was like
is that what they do to skateboarders here?
It's a big problem.
Yeah.
It's a skateboard apartheid here.
That's why there's all those tents. They're skateboarders.
(laughing)
- They make the skateboarders live in Skid Row.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- But, oh, so then I turned around
to get away from the guy, 'cause I was like,
okay, I don't wanna get caught up in this.
- You're like, I'm next.
- Yeah, exactly, like, oh, I don't wanna be guilty.
- You looked up, looked down at your skateboard,
and looked back up and ran the other direction.
- It's like the Scooby-Doo run.
But then I turned around, I was in that parking lot
with the right aid, and then I got--
- Gower Gulch.
- Yeah, so I got on the sidewalk,
and then like a woman walked out of the start like old woman with like
sideways beehive hair. Fuck you looked at me and went no skating on the
sidewalk.
I didn't know what to do. So I just went back to where the guy was fighting.
You're like rather take my chances with yeah. So then I yeah, I don't want
the beehive lady to fucking kill me and then I went back and then I like
asked one of the dudes. I was like, Hey, is everything cool here? I don't I
don't know what's going on. Things like nah man, this dude's bugging. I went
all right, went back. I'll see you guys later.
I went back to the beehive lady. Yeah, and you said, listen, listen, I'm
gonna level with you. You need to tell them to not tell them. You need to go
tell that guy to stop beating up the skateboarders. Yeah, they'll listen to
you can I grind your hair yeah so I did I tell you the dude was he had a camera
with him so from far away it looked like a dude was filming his friend skating
yeah so I was like oh shit classic LA moment damn and then I get up and the
dude is in like taking pictures of someone being like what's up oh and then
the guy had his board like in his hand like he's about the truck smack him and
he was like you need to go brush your fucking teeth. What kind of was it a flip
video camera? No it was like it was like an old like it was like a DSLR. Really?
It looked like an older one it had like leather on the sides and like silver. Oh
damn. Wow. They're making a movie. So it's probably just an SLR. Yeah. They're probably making a
movie. They're probably making the new. Mid 90s. The new mid somar. Can't walk
anywhere without making a movie in Los Angeles. Yeah. Yeah I thought I was
I was walking into a shoot.
I was like, so it was so disorienting
to see like the dude saying, "What's up, ho?"
- What's up, ho?
'Cause no movie would ever have that line.
- People don't say that.
- They wouldn't say it that many times.
- That's true, yeah.
- 'Cause every time the camera got back in the dude's face,
he went, "What's up, ho?
"What's up, ho?
"What's up, ho?"
- I'd watch that movie.
- Yeah.
- The guy saying, "What's up, ho?" a hundred times.
- Oh, and then he followed,
and then I met up with Alex.
- Yeah.
- And then Alex and I was like, "Oh, shit."
yeah, you like Alex is going to trader joe's, so i went to trader joe's with
alex and then he like ended up walking into the trader joe's and then was
behind that guy the dude who was going what's up ho and he was his how did he
act in trader joe's very respectful very respect yes very respectable he bought
like one sample yeah he bought four things a hash brown you get like an
open wound on his head i don't know that's probably got hit yeah i don't
know if he got hit by the skateboards he got hit by a skateboard and jolted him
back into politeness became very polite. My apologies, sir, off to trader joe's
what's up for
he bought like four things a hash browns damn like the like the frozen patty
carbo loading yeah. Those things are really bad. Oh yeah, i carbo loaded
before my ucb one oh one showcase job last night. I was like i could eat so
much bread yeah my brain had to run the the improv mile yeah. I did the improv
mile. That was an improv marathon. A naked mile more like it when you're there.
Yeah, because I do. We might take out whatever possible. Use it as a prop.
Because it's at UCB. That's true and they encourage that. There's a whole class for it.
It's called Caleb 101. It's taught by Aaron Glazer. Yeah, it's taught by Matt Besser.
I think as soon as the internship's over I'm just gonna put his credit card
online. You should not do that. Why? Why? Not a good idea. What, what, tell me what, tell me the worst
version of what happens once I put Matt Besser's credit card online. You get sued.
Yeah. Why would he sue me? For putting his credit card online? Also that is traceable back to you.
How could he prove it though? What if I just right now read the number? Come on,
It's on the Patreon. He's never gonna listen to this. He'll never know. It's
one two three. It's not one two three. Four five six. No, it's three one seven four. Don't do it.
Matt Besser, expiration two nineteen. Oh shit, no. Now I can go buck wild. What? It expired. Oh.
It's an expired card. Damn, he tricked you dude. He planted that to see. He's got his
search alerts on to see if Matt Besser's credit card comes up. He has a Matt Besser credit card
Google alert. He gave you a fake credit card that only you ever had because he knew he looked at you.
He took one look and he went yeah this guy will upload my credit card online. When you're right,
you're right buddy. There's nothing I can say. This guy's gonna do punk rock. Yeah. At me.
yeah Matt Besser is punk rock dude yeah he did start an underground theater he
has freakishly long arms yeah they like touch his knees oh like an ape yeah like
in he's built like an ape like a gibbon yeah he's built Matt Besser's built like
a fucking like a fucked up gibbon dude he looks really bad yeah yeah if you're
listening this punk fuck you Matt Besser it's official yeah yeah podcast about
listeners it's a green light on Matt Besser I mean that on-site go for it what
do you think about LA so far me no no Cameron yeah well I don't like it no no I
mean I feel like I'd probably like it if we went somewhere other than fucking
sunset that's true we will tomorrow yeah yeah we will tomorrow my mom I told my
mom because I got Chick-fil-a for the first time today and then I told my mom
that and she's like you fucking dumbass we have Chick-fil-a here you do have
Chick-fil-a yeah there's there's there's one there's one in Nashua yeah yeah
there's not one in Boston no but there's one yeah I think that did the Taco Bell
and Downtown Crossing ever open yes oh shit that's been there that's been there
since November damn that shit was nice just sick I don't know it was there
since October because I tried to go in the middle of class.
Where the subway used to be.
Yeah.
Huh?
You know where noon and five guys are?
Yeah.
So it's right across from noon and it's like a block over from five guys.
Damn, that's awesome.
I don't know what blocks, I don't know how blocks work.
No, I can visualize where it is.
It's by that crazy sub place.
Al Capone?
Al Capone.
Yes, it's like next to it.
- The guy has the bum arm and he scoops your meatballs
onto the sandwich with one arm and makes a whole sandwich.
Like one arm, he has one arm that works fully
and the other is like--
- Just like Al Capone.
- Is just like Al Capone, he has the Al Capone arm.
- Yeah, he has the syphilis.
- He has one arm that's like stuck in a position,
like a cast, it's like stuck like how people,
or how the people hold their arms in slings.
But it's like a little smaller, not like comically small,
but it is a little smaller and he doesn't--
- Does he have like herbs palsy or something?
- You know, I didn't ask.
(laughing)
- Hey bitch, do you have herbs palsy?
- Hey, stop that fucked up arm sandwich, man.
- You like herbs?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, you get that when you work
with too many herbs and spices.
- Yeah, that's a huge fucking juice.
- You get that from smoking too much ganja.
Ooh!
(laughing)
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh!
- Ow.
- Me happy love smoke weed.
(laughing)
Man, what's up with your fucked up arm?
I smoke too much man! This old Italian guy. I'm smoking too much! I got the weed arm!
What is that? You're making that up.
Your name is Sebastian Maniscalco. You have no relation but that's your name.
There's 15 Sebastian Maniscalcos in the world and all of them in the past four years their
lives have been ruined.
Yeah. What else is on that block? On that block? I think. That's my block, man. Yeah. Oh, there's
the falafel king next to the Al Capones. Yeah. There's the teeth guy. Teeth guy? Oh, yeah,
Chatterbox. Oh, yeah. The spare change guy? Yeah, Chatterbox. Yeah. Chatterbox, if you're
listening, man. Hey, man, we love you. Big fat fucking shout out to Chatterbox. Yeah.
I don't know. The homeless man with the newspapers. You can live in Pat's apartment. Yeah, man.
Yeah, you get a free invitation.
Come over to my house, man.
Fuck my girlfriend.
I don't care.
I think it might have been my brother who called him Blacksull Rose.
Blacksull Rose?
That's good.
Yeah, for context, everybody, this is a homeless guy who goes, "A-ga-ga-ga-ga-ga-ga-ga" very
loud.
He's a homeless guy who said there's a newspaper called Spare Change that I guess there's a
charity that prints this newspaper, gives it to homeless people, and then they sell
sell it for like a dollar or whatever and yeah, they don't get to keep any of
them. Yeah, it's just something for them to do. It's boring is being homeless
all the fucking time, but this one guy with the he's crazy. He dresses up like
santa. He dresses like santa. He has like teeth that are popping out of his
face and he will say because the newspaper is called spare change and
when you walk by he'll be like what time is it yeah guess what time it is yeah
what time it is and you'll be like I'm 230 and I'm like no spare change time and
it's fucking awesome it's one of the highlights of living in Boston
Massachusetts absolutely yeah yeah you to see him man I cannot wait to go back
oh my god to see all my favorite oh yeah the guy with the guy with the fucked up
leg on Boyle's oh yeah doesn't he show people his penis no that's the other
that's the guy with the goggles. Oh, Sebulba? That's Sebulba, yeah. Sebulba is a... I don't
even know, I wouldn't even say that he's especially a homeless guy. He's like kind of a, like
he kind of is like a genius. Yeah, this is a, he's a homeless guy. Because he shows people
his penis? Yeah, which is the smartest plan. He's a guy who stands outside a building and
just has inventions. Yeah. He wears these crazy goggles, he has these flashing lights and
he will he has like a like a headlamp that for like spelunking that's really
extremely powerful and he will just turn it on strobe at night and just like
blind tourists as they walk by yeah he's always like cranking a wrench on some
like yeah some like indescribable future technology doesn't he's like the chains
on his boots - yeah he looks and dresses like Sebulba yeah he talks like normal
Yeah, and he has showed his penis to multiple people. Yeah, have you seen guys seen that one guy?
Which is why we called him Sepulveda.
We're just making fun of a homeless guy. It's just cuz he shows his penis to people like Sepulveda.
Yeah, yeah, that's where the Sepulveda nickname came from. You guys seen the guy who dresses in like all white and walks really slowly
on the block. He's with like with music. Oh, yeah
he'll like dance yeah he stands outside of the Anson building yeah whatever
answers to the radio dude he's the man yeah so many home here I'm so excited so
many good in in LA the homeless people are just like they're like a fucking
like a Borg hive mind it just tries to fuck you walk around it's a very
different experience sexual Borg yeah Borg gone sexual or Borg sexual I saw
today I completed the trifecta of Sunset Boulevard twins of oh yeah yeah I saw
the third I've only seen the two pairs so there's there's there's three pairs of
twins who will often they dress exactly the same and they walk up and down
Sunset the girl twins have identical have identical dogs yeah I saw it so
those are the ones I saw today yeah so there's yeah it's terrible there I think
think they just walk around just waiting for somebody to be like I'm sorry are you
legally are you the girls from legally blondes and Zack and Cody and they say
yeah there's there's these two guys these guys are crazy because they walk
like and they walk in lockstep gate they walk in lockstep down the street it's
like to look like a glitch in the matrix and isn't isn't this like near like
they're all like agencies right there's right they just walk right past outside
here outside this building. Maybe they think this is a big modeling agency. Maybe.
They're like one day they're gonna see our strut and they're gonna pick us up off
the street and make us famous. We need twin models. We need, we want to, we want to do a
photo shoot where one person's looks really, was wearing really cool clothes
the other person's wearing really lame clothes. Yeah. Highlight our cool clothes.
It's called the prince and the pauper. Yeah. I don't like these twins because
it's clear that they have had sex with each other. They're gonna say that they have money but that comes with...
That's probably why they did it, it's for money.
They were like oh I'll give you $600. Yeah and they just trade it back and forth.
No I'll give you $600. 601! Sold!
I just remember the reason they walk down here is because there's a rest there's a
fast food place called twin sliders. Oh yeah. That serves pairs of sliders and
it's so they go there and they order. You get it for free if you're twins. No.
I've seen them go there. They just buy food. Did you did was it you who's
telling me somebody told me that the twins like walked by while they were at
twin sliders and one of the guys who was ordering at twin sliders turned around
- I go, "Ha ha, twins for the twins!"
(laughing)
- Remember in like 2004, 2005 when like twins was apparently
the, according to beer commercials,
it's like the ultimate male fantasy?
- And twins!
- Yeah man.
- What?
(laughing)
What is going on with that?
- Me personally, I like two girls
look exactly opposite of each other.
I like an Amazon and a midget.
And a man.
Yeah.
Wee man.
Yeah, wee man.
Wee man and Serena Williams.
And I fuck them both.
I can't tell the difference when I'm down there.
It's all the same to me, man.
I'm wearing two eye patches.
And a mouth patch.
And a penis patch.
And I'm having sex.
I dressed up like the techno Federation from episode
Yeah, yeah, I'm cyber yeah, I'm cyber cyber get up
I'm a I'm a freakin cyberpunk, but I was in community college. We had I'm Ashton future and
No, why is it my laser gun working?
fucking yeah that's right yeah yeah we shot a hole straight through your dog's
head with a laser you're on cyber punked yeah he he vaporized a kid kid we turned
your son to dust TV
there's sobbing like killed my
people.
Crying
shot up in your fucking idiot.
Yeah,
you should have a genome sequenced by now.
Just go home ten years old.
Just press the button you back your kid up
shit. You haven't backed your kid up yet.
Come on.
You know, you know you were getting cyber punked.
future blows up again is oh that's like a new anti-vaxxer anti-vaxxer
that's the main instead of dying from disease that's the main danger of being
anti-vaxxers that - in future there's a lost episode of cyberpunk where techno
you know, Zach Braff just destroyed a child who was an anti-baxer.
Yeah, just decapitates him with a lightsaber.
Unprompted.
He decapitated him with the silver lightsaber.
Yeah, he was touching my vehicle pod.
Yeah.
Yeah, my orb, my flying orb, my hover chair.
He was touching my X-wing.
Oh my God, he spray painted he spray painted the word poop on my ex wing
yeah. So I'm going to download them into the Internet and lock them there
forever in a realm of eternal suffering. I put a virus in your kids back up
to try to restore the back up and the kid can only speak Chinese.
Yeah, I changed it like it corrupted. I changed the language settings on your
back up. You're a backed up child. Yeah, Toy Story 3 Buzz Lightyear, you kid. Suck my dick.
I'm mashed in future. That's good. Yeah. Woo! What are you looking up? We have a big computer.
We got the big screen tonight. Oh, the butterfly effect. That's a movie that sees us. Oh yeah,
can see the future yeah all right let's see did you guys see his man he has a
crazy jawline yeah that's Ashton future that's actually those are some sick
sunglasses yeah that's badass so if you if you're playing along if you're
listening at home look up the daily rash comm slash Demi - more - dumps -
- Ashton - Kutcher - for - Herman - Cain's - illegitimate - son - Ashton -
Kutcher - glass glasses - - glasses - slash slash slash and slash
slash clutches and his glass and glasses future glass closed.
God did
Look at the headings on this website.
Home, celebrities, Joe Biden, news, politics, Reverend Al Sharpton.
It's on Reverend Al Sharpton.
I've definitely looked at this website before actually, now that I think about it.
Cory Booker chooses illegal immigrant as his running mate?
That's pretty funny.
He's got a serious joker face on there.
He looks good.
That's him right here.
- Um, so what's up?
- What's up?
- I'm chillin'.
- Yeah, I'm chillin'.
- I'm fuckin' chillin'.
- I'm so ready to, I mean, this'll be definitely
the highlight of my time in L.A. probably.
- Yeah, it's four days.
- I wish I'd fuckin' showed up earlier.
- Yeah, me too.
- 'Cause I have like the biggest paper
I have to fuckin' write.
- Yeah?
- I'm gonna talk about it all week
and I'm never gonna do it. - How many pages?
- No, it's a word count.
- How many words?
- 3,500.
35 words?
That's easy.
I don't even know that many.
3500 words.
3500, that's fucking...
How many pages would 35 words be?
3500 words would probably be 2 pages.
No.
Probably be 1.5 pages single spaced.
It's one page that is 3500 words long.
Yeah.
That's what I would say personally.
14 pages.
Don't blow into the microphone.
Dude, I'm fucked.
That's easy, man.
14 pages double spaced.
Yeah.
Well, either way, I mean, I can't fuck it right.
3,500 minimum?
Yeah.
That's something.
Wow.
That's a lot.
Yeah, this dude sucks.
That sucks.
The longest paper I ever wrote was a paper that I basically just wrote to prove to my
mom that vaccines didn't cause autism.
Nice.
That was like my thesis paper in high school because I was homeschooled.
And she was like, "Just pick a topic."
I was like I'm gonna prove her wrong yeah I'm gonna own my mom with facts and
logic right now my thesis paper in high school was about Chuck Palahniuk
really cool guy yeah yeah what do you guts is nasty to write it huh
you mean like the program I was in was like a classical education program
seems like a co-op so I did have like an actual thesis that I had to yeah I had a
thesis - my school is super like college prep my we had a program called college
and career ready but that didn't do anything for us yeah like it was
basically like oh you need to know how to use Excel yeah I wish they taught me
how to fucking cook top ramen and have sex at my college yeah um how come in
math class they don't teach you how to balance your checkbook yeah man I haven't
really thought about it like that man but that's kind of fucked up what what
What the fuck?
What the?
Wait a second.
I'm starting to think school is kind of like sort of a fucked up institution and shit.
You know?
Yeah.
School is basically telling me I shouldn't pay my taxes.
By not teaching me how to do it.
If I can't figure it out, I'm not going to do it.
Yeah bro.
I don't know how to use wikiHow and shit.
You think I know how to use that fucked up bullshit, that green ass website?
I don't fucking know.
Is it green?
Oh yeah, I guess it is green.
It is green, man.
has green yeah how is green between wiki how is green we're watching videos where
the guy makes yeah he makes the best he does one that's like feathers right he
makes this guy makes guns out of guns guys make swords out of knives this guy
makes imagine I couldn't imagine owning that looks like fucking soul caliber yeah
Soul Calibur was such a premium fucking game. Yeah loved violence and ginormous titties. Oh, yeah, they had the best physics
Yeah, they did have the physics
Yeah, they should put Caleb in Mortal Kombat
But like no special abilities like I'm so easy to kill no attacks yeah, you're kind of like
You just go
Like the never soft I in the Tony Hawk's first gear 3. Why did they that there's a bad gig for that? I yeah
That used to like make me want to vomit when I
Watch the the never soft intro and they would stab the eye and I like I would close my eyes during the the never soft
Logo when I was when I was playing portal for the first time the valve thing scared the shit out of
Yeah, I was like damn I'm actually
Scary about it is you don't know what that valve is controlling so yeah
I think controlling like water up and down his like
It's like right or is it his consciousness that you were like and also if you put it halfway. What is that doing?
You know yeah, it's true. It means turn around and mmm. It controls his head. Yeah, or is it?
He just move his head around with it. It's like a handle. It doesn't turn
Damn, he's got a smooth out this handle
Is he you think he's going to I think it looks cool if he does he made a bit so the guy in the video made
a bismuth knife
And which I guess it bismuth is sharp is pointy. Yeah, it's like a mineral. That's oh, he's he's melt
Oh, what the fuck? He's well. That's what he does at the end of his videos
I think I think he destroys the knives a lot of the time us
Maybe that's not what he's doing now.
He just spilled some fucking bismuth on the counter.
Damn, he's gonna die.
Yo. Bismuth.
You got your bismuth everywhere.
Yeah. Whoa.
Oh, it's fine. It dried instantly.
We can't be watching videos.
Yeah. It's a bad idea.
Pause it. Press pause.
Dude, we have like
two seconds left. No.
No, there's a minute. A minute. Okay.
It's a minute of premium. That's so long.
yet people are paying for this
exactly
yeah we could talk about my guess i mean i'm going to
i feel we've talked about on several times we have a lot of that not in depth
the i mean i looked at his website what it would he has a no doubt i guess i
could use for that
cancer disease he was a plate in his head yeah
yeah i think i i i think i was a good asset is a new
is not only does any fell off a ladder
and they had to reconstruct is that
so i can't spell
That's probably why he can't spell yes. He's really bad at spelling. Also I do know that the weather greatly affects his
his life because I guess
if like the the pressure in the air gets to some point
his head starts really like the metal starts like hurting starts ringing. Yeah, so I do know that
it does affect him. The metal is still a big part of his life. Yeah. Yeah. Um anything else?
No, just covers it.
Uh, is he, is he, does he have style?
He has some of the most amazing style I've ever seen.
Yeah.
Is he, what's his favorite color?
His favorite color is green.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
100% sure.
Can you ask him?
Yeah, I could text him.
Let's give him a call.
Oh, there he is.
Yeah.
Man, he looks really good.
Um, yeah.
Ooh, MySpace.
Yeah, he's still on MySpace.
Really?
Yeah.
Does he think that my space is like the oh, let's see who's in his top eight. He only has two people in his top a
He's a
He is a humongous dream theater fan, that's
What's his name Mike Portnoy is at the dream theater drummer. I think so. Yeah, that's like his bits like his
Like his dad basically basically his dad Dave Portnoy insomnia
There it is
That's a cool photo. He uploaded to my space some fractals. He just thought a fractal was cool. Yeah, yeah
Get off the screen. This is
Most we're reading something why this is what you do. You're just doing what you do when you call in which is
You just love clicking so much. Well, at least this time you can't hear that you click
Yeah, this is gonna be the first episode like a while or you can't hear me. Can't hear any clicks. Yeah
Yeah, Patrick loves clicking. You'll hear Cameron's natural clicks that come from his body. Yeah
That's a snap. That's a click. No, it's not. I was not snapping my fingers. I was just coming out of my mouth. You were snapping your fingers.
That's the noise I'm making with my mouth. I can make it simultaneously as I'm speaking. Let's watch a Tech N9ne freestyle video. Stop watching videos!
It's a video of Caleb's uncle. Tech N9ne.
Well, okay, Tech Nine. Do you remember when that other rapper named Tech Nine
died? Yeah. And I was like, it really scared me for a moment. I thought, we're
not going to get a worldwide Choppers 4. Yeah. Jesus fucking Christ. I'm going to
change my name to someone really famous and then kill myself. My name's Brad Pitt.
Barack Obama killed himself. Obama Boulevard, baby. Obama Boulevard. I drove
by, there's a street in Los Angeles called Obama Boulevard that I drove by
That's cool. It's named after Malik Obama. It's named after Malik Obama, yeah. Yeah. It was cool.
And then I did a voice to myself for a long time in the car. Yeah, what voice? Don't worry about it.
Yeah, it was good though. Yeah, I'm assuming it was a French accent. It was a French accent.
Boulevard yeah exactly yeah yeah
man
Obama
Boulevard
God damn man
Are they gonna hear that on the
Probably not
There's a lot of fuckers downstairs
I don't really care
Obama Boulevard
They done fucked up in Gabe Obama Boulevard man
God damn
This is the price they have to pay for
not having it be over Skype
You have to hear some people yell in the background
Yeah you have to hear a bunch of theater kids
We can't give you a single good episode.
- I know.
- No matter what.
- No matter what happens.
- That's the podcast about let's promise.
- We absolutely refuse to give you even one.
- There's gonna be one glaring thing wrong
with every episode.
- With every single one.
- That's right.
- And then someone's gonna point it out.
- Yeah.
- Also they're gonna point out that we can't,
we can't differentiate our voices.
- Oh yeah, fuck.
- When me and Cameron get back to Boston,
we will start pitching my voice up three octaves.
- Okay.
- For every episode.
- That's a good idea.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Me!
[LAUGHTER]
And it'll sound like that.
I'm Caleb.
That's Meatwad.
Now that-- we should get Meatwad on the podcast.
That's me, Caleb Pitts.
[GARGLING]
Mom.
Mom, it's me, Caleb Pitts, coming to the house.
Meatwad was probably the first voice I learned how to do.
Yeah.
Pretty easy.
I used to say, Mom, I don't want to clean my room.
That's pretty good.
And your mom would go, Meatwad, go away.
Meatwad, you don't have a room in my house.
[LAUGHTER]
Why are you calling me mom?
Fuck you mom
AHHHHH
He just screams
in the top of her lungs
Oh you're ok
BSR
You mean wide voice
What else is
on his website?
His website? Yeah
His ghost hunting tools
So let's go through here, he has JVC camera
yeah then he's got the Fujifilm. We should have just asked her to talk.
As soon as she was leaving I was like oh fuck. One of the cleaning lady came to the office and
we're recording this in a windowless room yeah which I think is a first for us.
At work. No our work doesn't have. No it had windows. No it didn't. Yeah it did.
No that did not have windows. On the left side it had windows. They don't go there literally into like a wall.
Yeah, they're there's an alley. They're frosted so you can't see anything
through them and it's directly into it still there is natural sunlight that
permeates that window. Shut up! I'm saying this is our first window. No, also
how we do used to do in the basement of uh of uh the one when we checked out
that room. Yeah, I'm smart dude. I forgot the way that used to be our spot to
record. That will probably go back to being our spot. Damn, I'm gonna be
graduated though and y'all are gonna be taking this old-ass man into the...
To sign you in. Yeah. Yeah. And I'll just be like, "Huh. There's something about this place that's so
familiar to me. I can't quite place it. Wow." Oh, I remember when I used to roam these
halls. I used to record a podcast with a fat guy and a retard right here.
You're like, "Okay, man, I need your ID."
Yeah, it's still, you're not proving anything.
You have to leave.
I love you.
It's my birthday!
It's my birthday.
Now, what do you have to say about that?
Well...
Happy birthday.
Thank you. Well, I guess I'll just go on.
I'll be continuing on my way.
You won't mind if I bring my revolver.
bring my revolver I have business highway 55 footsteps oh this is just a constant
this really is a constant you know the freak of the week is it's it's Patrick
Patrick's I just can't just doing the bike oh my god again with the ADD you do
have a dd asshole dude dudes asshole do do at asshole dick approaching
down huh wake up what why'd you put your dick inside my anus what you think my
dick under the table you wanted to I didn't do either of those huh I didn't
either of those things I don't think you bust inside this self-righteous ass of
mine. Tiny little guy. Oh come on bust inside my tiny little guy. I'm a tiny tiny asshole and he's a guy.
It's a small man. It's a face. Mm-hmm. The brown eye. The brown eye itself.
Opening my third eye. Yeah. Then taking a big shit. Yeah. Oh my god. Yes. I can't get
over the CKY 2K him putting shit on Ryan Dunst. Oh yeah. That's the one in the
hood. It's so funny. Congratulations. If you did that to me I'd think I'd kill you. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, I think if you know anybody I know put shit on my face while I was asleep. It was in his ear, too
Now they put the paper towel. Honestly that way I've been having a weird thing where I have a I have like a
Fan of my
Wake up a shit in my ear
No, I lizard comes and shits in my ear. I
I hate when that happens. I've been having a thing where I feel like a pain, like a
phantom pain where my ear is and I keep thinking, you know, you know, in movies
it's like, it's like, I keep going, it's a place where I, it's a phantom pain in the
way that I feel a pain in my ear area but I can't identify where the pain is
coming from. Alright. So it feels almost like detached from my body. Yeah. And I
keep thinking that I've been like shot in the head by a sniper and I haven't
realized it yet yeah and I keep your soul dude it's your soul it's it's leaving
out of my right ear yeah yeah I can't deal with your twisted
thoughts anymore that's true my soul is divorced from my mind I wish dude I'm
at it is bitch I'm out this no one shit at me what is there a copy of Garden
State in here the only there's two movies in here Garden State and
and reserve our dogs well in the open up the thing of garden state because there's another movie in
there reservoir garden state and the war of the world i don't know why it's a double feature
you got to watch those two movies you know when this movie came out they're both documentary
yeah they both take place in new jersey that's true i think garden state happens before war
of the worlds directly before yeah yeah moments before the war of the worlds
yeah how fucking gullible were people that what's his name got away with that
shit horses horse and whales got away with what about orson whales could you
just say that nice nice world sports world
you seen everyone's probably seen at this point everyone's seen it but the video of him
like drunk your shit doing the wine commercial. So funny yeah yeah such a good video.
It's funny that at the end of his life he's just indistinguishable from Del
Close yeah they look exactly the same. He was at the end of the Muppet movie.
I don't remember that. Yeah he plays uh he has that line. Del Close or Orson Welles.
Orson Welles. He's at the end of the first Muppet movie and he's like oh
Oh, right up the standard rich and famous contract for Kermit the Frog.
That's a good line.
That's a really good line.
He made that up himself.
That wasn't in the script.
I can't wait to just be an old fucking fat ass piece of shit that everybody hates.
Yeah.
Don't have to wait long.
That's true.
I'm getting there.
Yeah, bitch.
30 year old.
As soon as I'm 30, I'm just giving up.
Yeah.
I'm clocking out.
Come on, you're so young.
Are you younger than me or older than me?
- 22.
- I'm 22.
(laughing)
Wait.
- I was born in July.
- July.
- 23rd.
- Oh, I'm two months older than you.
Or no, three months older than you.
- Caleb's the oldest and then Cameron's the youngest.
- I'm a little guy.
- Yeah, you're my little guy.
- We call Cameron Dad's guy.
(laughing)
Like, "Hey Dad's guy, can you grab me that?"
So my uncle used to call his kid dad's guy.
Yeah.
That's so sweet.
Dad's guy.
Yeah.
Hey, dad's guy.
They called me boogie growing up.
Boogie pits.
They called me boogie.
That was my nickname.
It's because you boogied?
My dad will still call me boogie sometimes.
Nice.
Yeah, because I guess I love to dance.
There's this guy who from my...
Like boogie two eight.
Yeah.
Whatever.
in my town his mom called those friends with his mom called him sugar booger
that's sweet well that crazy make fun of him yeah it was really crazy his mom was
just crazy yeah sexy kid
room clean your room pocket pussy I love you
fuck buddy jr. oh on the place being of kids you can have kids I've had sex on
the plane ride in the kid sitting directly next to me so like it was a
family of four and then they like the whole row and then my bonus kid and he
was on yours yeah he's on my no there was like the whole row so it was like the
mom and then the two kids and then the dad. The dad was in my row so it was like
A B C D E. You got the bonus dad. Yeah. I was the bonus dad. You were the bonus dad. So at the end of the
flight the kids ears started to pop and he didn't know what was going on so he
just started screaming. Yeah. And then while he was just like sitting there
screaming and crying the dad moved back to my row and just watched an episode of
Broad City. And then while his kid's sitting there screaming and crying, he's
like yelling at his dad because he's like, "I don't know what's going on!" He's like telling his dad, like he's, I guess he said
something, I don't know what it was, but then the dad was like, "Henry, that is the
meanest thing you've ever said." The kid was like four. He's telling him to yawn. That's what they were doing, they were giving him gum and like telling him to yawn. He was like, "I don't know what's happening!"
I almost freak out every time my ears start to hurt on the plane.
Yeah.
It's scary.
My ears don't pop very well.
Really?
It always takes so long for my ears to pop.
Even like in a long car ride across.
An elevation change.
Yeah.
Elevation chamber.
An elevation chamber.
I'm going to start calling it elevators.
There was one plane ride where my-
On cyberpunk in that era.
Yeah.
We locked.
Corey, hey.
locked dr. computer who's the biggest
celebrity in the future into a into an
elevation chamber when it will work
building we filled it with business
hologram poop yeah that's right
yeah hologram poop that's real taste yeah
has all the qualities of poop just you
can't touch it by holo poop today
same old poop taste brand new hologram
hologram hologram holographic what about a bitch named Holly Graham the Heather
Graham of the future no touching
you guys think the future is gonna be like a thousand a thousand times this a
thousand eggs in a laboratory it'll be like this times a million it's gonna be
thousand eggs in a laboratory yeah I think I think and I think in the future
the computer is gonna play a bigger role I think they're gonna invent I think
they might invent a bigger internet that can hold more of the websites you guys
get scared about nanobots I think every website is gonna be one terabyte big I
think the whole world's gonna be one big website I think the whole way my friend
are the mouse go fucking crazy click everything you can while you're alive
Patrick would love that shit Patrick would love to be the mouse on the
computer screen I love being on the computer you do it's one of your
favorite hobbies in the future there's gonna be no more stairs only elevation
chambers and the only TV shows cyberpunked mm-hmm there's gonna be 10
Matrix movies and matrix and ten new animal. Oh my God yeah a new a different
a different sister is gonna transition into being a witch house key yeah oh how
about the Wachowski sisters. The matrix. The Wachowski sisters. Man they're beautiful.
But yeah the future I'll be there for sure. I'll be off adventuring. Adventuring?
On my computer. Yeah I'll be doing different types of research on my on the
websites I can find be all smoking one big jewel a giant jewel that's the size
of a room yeah no it's a size of a we're gonna have an electric jewel mmm they're
finally gonna have a jewel that that works it's gonna be steam-powered we're
gonna go back to see you can blow into it yeah you can blow your breath and the
jewel is also it's also a breathalyzer yes you can test yourself to see if
you've had too much jewel and yeah alcohol we ran out it's like helium there's only
like a certain we only have so much a bunch of people went on an expedition to
find alcohol on a different planet and they crashed the spaceship on the way
back because they're all freaking drunk yeah there's no there's no water on Mars
but there's tons of fucking course cold so what they do they're playing to get
more beer on to Mars is they're gonna put two silver bullet course trains at
had both poles they were gonna launch silver bullet trains into the both of
the poles and dig they're gonna dig and it's gonna play a song that in every
course commercial that was like people of the world
course trade they should send Bruce Willis Armageddon style into the center
of Mars to mine the course the cores core mm-hmm at the scent the bank of the
core bank wars planet cores planet cool welcome to a plane and cool names but
then Bruce Willis he gets to the to the center of Mars and it actually is just
like a molten or in it incinerates him and then Ashton future says yeah cyber
yeah you just got punked that's what you get for trying to remarry cyber Demi
me more. You fucker yeah yeah demi you know it takes a it would take
two cores light years to get to play it.
Okay, all right, all right, okay, and you'd have to fly in a beer ship
and hey scotty be me hops
Am i right? Yeah, i'd like to light savor the delicious flavor of Coors Banquet.
Right? Yeah. They're probably gonna invent beer 1000, i would think.
They'll have a new- definitely beer 2.0 will be up by then.
Yeah, there's gonna be- It's beer with lens flares.
In the future, there's gonna be a new Tucker Max book called "I hope they serve
beer in space and then in parentheses I actually know the answer and they do on
planet on planet beer yeah planet beer is kind of where I want to go right yeah I
kind of pick up a little a little a little a little more a little taste of
planet beer after this yeah little asteroid do they so do they sell the 99
can Pabst blue ribbon here what's that it's a box of PBR that's got 99 cans
I feel like I can guess what that is.
You fucking idiot.
I didn't know if this was a special kind of can called the 99 can.
That's what I was thinking.
I was like imagining.
I actually did a really cool design of it in my head once you said it.
The PBR 99.
Have you had the PBR easy or whatever?
No.
It's like the light PBR.
It's got a cool can.
Is it blue?
It's blue and yellow.
I've seen it.
Okay, big shot.
Shut up.
East Coast big shot. Fuck you. You guys think dinosaurs will come back in the
future? Yeah we're gonna bring back dinosaurs. Okay.
Um yeah we're um hmm. What? That's Jeff Goldblum because he touches his face when he asks.
Oh yeah. Delicious. He's eating a dinosaur.
(mimicking sounds)
- Turd-actile egg.
(laughing)
Tastes like...
- Planet beer.
(mimicking sounds)
- Didn't he fuck somebody?
- Yeah, he fucked a lot.
- He has, doesn't he have a giant dick?
- I heard that, yeah, he was like, I guess people...
- Is he Jamaican?
(laughing)
If we're just saying things.
- I think he has a giant dick.
- Jeff got a blue man.
(laughing)
- Yiff.
Remember My Name is Jeff?
Yeah.
Fucking awesome clip.
That was a cool video.
Pull that one up.
My name Jeff?
Yeah, My Name Jeff.
My Name is Jeff Goldblum will be the biggest video in 2090.
When does the future start?
When do we enter the new epoch?
3, 2, 1.
Okay, now 3 more seconds.
It is funny.
Yeah, we'll play it again.
My name is Jeff.
Thank you. That Channing Tatum is a multi-hyphenate. Huh? Actor. Jeff. Jeff.
And that's it. Yeah, Magic Mike. He's Magic Mike. Yeah, all his roles, that's
the multi-hyphenate he is. He's truly a renaissance man. I'm sure that people,
This is exactly the moment that people regret their patreon. This is what everyone unsubscribes
Yeah, you shouldn't have asked Patrick to play a video. Yeah, please
My god, I wish you had your axe yeah axe distract. Oh, yeah. Yeah, I'd give you something to play with
Do you want some candy you do you want a peppermint?
Do you guys want to get candy? I would love to go
Yeah, I won't get candy
Damn, okay. All right. Okay. I'll get some candy. I'm trying to get some candy. They got it. They got an M&M store in LA
Hey, man, they might
20 years old here's a 20
The candy store I'm too old come on man, please
Not falling for this one again. I know you run
Please dude, I'll suck you
Suck your dick for candy Wow
Wow
for Haribo Cola I was like in like
cartoons when candy is like
Like the Jawbreakers from it. Yeah, like it's gonna say those things are too damn big
that would not fit in a human that way that would not be the a's got some
fucked-up jaws how you unhinge your jaw to eat a jawbreaker
tell me that ed tell us what else can you put in there yeah what else can you put
a quail it's fun to have ostrich egg what else is roughly the size of the jaw
Breakers and Ed Edd nitty what if they're just really small what if it's a small
like a whoo style like society on something very there and they're
actually if you heard there they're actually all dead and they're all living
in purgatory and they're like don't like because they're in purgatory because
they're too small to go to heaven yeah mmm you must be this big to get it in
heaven oh crap you're gonna miss out camera yeah you're so small I'm taller
taller than both of you combined.
Tall is not, tall doesn't matter anymore.
That's not the word I would use to describe you.
Yeah, yeah, tall is not the word.
What's the word?
White.
That would be the main one.
No, no.
No, I'm saying you won't get into heaven.
Well, that's what I was asking.
I said I would...
You asked what I would use to describe you.
No, I asked what's the word, you said that's the...
I said, okay, let's...
run that shit back run that shit I said I'm I'm gonna go to heaven yeah you said
you can't go to heaven cuz you're white I said what okay well I think it sounds
about white yeah yeah the caucasity pure caucasity I need a shot of espresso
machine yeah I'm tired oh my god I'm freaking Jeff lagged I'm serious Jeff
Jeff Lang right now. Jeff Lang. Yeah. Jeffrey Lang. I was looking at a college
because I was thinking about college and I was like oh this has like a cool like
history program that maybe I'd be interested in, but then I clicked on
notable alumni from the college. First one was Jeffrey Epstein. Ooh yeah.
That's- and I honestly was like that's sick. Harvard? They listed that? Yeah.
this on the no no it was on Wikipedia yeah it was funny it was like it was like
sandwich between like artists artists Nobel Laureate or whatever yeah and then
it was like billionaire pedophile investor yeah they're freaking everywhere
man there's they're all your friends all your friends are kill all your friends
because they're all Jeffrey Epstein in disguise kind of over Jeffrey Epstein
I don't even care anymore.
- Yeah.
- You know, I'm on a new shit, you know.
- Yeah, what's your new shit?
- I'm excited for the new VR Half-Life game.
- Yeah.
- I'm kinda not even thinking about Jeffrey Epstein,
you know.
I'm excited for new things in 2020.
- Yeah, did you know he didn't kill himself?
- What the fuck?
Nah, you pulled me back in right when I thought I was out.
I thought he killed himself,
and that's what I thought was interesting about the story.
- I'm the only one who thinks he killed himself.
- I think he didn't.
- I think he did.
- No.
I think he killed Hillary Clinton.
yeah yeah took her place and took her place he's a shapeshifter yeah and
that's why she went on Howard Stern mm-hmm yeah she wrote the Sibian
Howard Stern shit was awesome yeah Hillary Clinton wrote the Sibian on
Stern God that fucking big fat fucking meaty clit just hanging out of the top
Jesus Christ you have a hot dog you have a hot dog sandwich between your legs I
think you'd be a spectacular president I think honestly you have one of the most
amazing pussies I've ever seen on a presidential candidate. Thank you! That's
what she sounds like. Yeah. Do you guys see Jamba Juice? They got that here. They
got Jamba Juice here. Do you guys know Jamba Juice is in Boston? Did you guys see what?
Tell me. Yang, whipped cream. Oh yeah. Yeah. Same energy. What? Same energy. Oh yeah.
Those things. That's my least. I hate when someone says same energy. Yeah. That's
this one that pisses me off so much. Like what even talking about just say these
pictures are similar. What is whatever happened to sane energy? Yeah, I feel
like we could use a little bit more of that. Yeah, nowadays, yeah, absolutely
yeah, yeah, rule, rule, rule, sane energy. You know everyone's talking about all
the time talking about same energy. I think we need to focus together and
focus on defeating the same enemy Donald Trump. Yes yeah and the Republicans
yeah Republicans. Oh shit are they filming that? The Republicans? No Bill
Maher. We should go we should go to a Bill Maher taping. Yeah. That's a good idea we
should go to a taping of some kind. Real time we should go to a Bill Maher taping.
yeah
that's i that's pretty funny. Thank you. Yeah, what about epic meal time
with bill maher?
Yeah, he's just eating pussy. Yeah, yeah, we put a hamburger in this
pussy
and bacon and bacon and bacon.
Yeah, i feel like i feel like bill maher would love epic meal time because
Muslims can eat anything that they make. Yeah, what about epic halal meal time?
Epic kids meal time.
Right, so it's just like a smaller version. All right, okay. You just get a
toy. It's just like a regular food. Yeah, it's a regular food. What about-
What about- To a kid, that's the biggest, the biggest, most epic meal you can
have as an adult's meal. What about non epic meal time?
and the meal isn't even epic.
- What about epic steel time and it's four thieves
and they do a heist on a bank?
- What about Eric Meal Time?
(laughing)
- This is a guy named Eric.
- Eric Meal Time.
- I'm Eric Meal Time and that show ruined my life.
- This shit sucks.
- It's a lawsuit.
- Yeah, it's me, Eric Meal Time.
- And then they interview for the documentary
about Eric Meal Time, a guy who's named Epic Meal Time
and he's like, "Imagine how I feel."
(laughing)
- Yeah.
What time are we at?
- An hour.
- Oh, word.
- Okay.
- Yeah, I'm getting hungies.
- Yeah, I'm so hungry right now.
- I'm just mostly tired.
- Yeah.
- We'll have a lot of episodes,
well, you won't hear them in the next couple days,
but there will be a lot.
- We're recording a lot in the next couple days, yeah.
- Do we do Patreon shout-outs on the premium episodes
or the normal ones?
- No, normal.
- Okay.
- Yeah, so then people will know to subscribe.
- Absolutely.
you could hear your own name.
Yeah.
Imagine hearing us say your own name.
Yeah, ready word, your own name.
Oh, come on.
We don't even say our own names.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
Do feel bad.
Why?
About that, I don't know.
I don't feel bad.
I guess I don't feel bad.
I don't know why I said I feel bad.
It eats me up.
It keeps me up at night.
Every night I'm awake.
If you listen to enough episodes, you figure it out.
No, you don't.
No, you do.
You do.
Yeah.
I mean, that's how it is with any podcast.
you start to differentiate all voices sound the same yeah what at first no
you're telling me this voice sounds the same as this voice yeah you sell you
tell me when I say when I say I'm Caleb that's the same as saying I'm Cameron
you think those sound the same no you're right yeah yeah cuz you said a different
name I've been proven wrong again by the fact master the fact master the fact
Factmaster fact-blastered me. I'm the Factmaster Flex. He figure-blasted me, exactly.
Yeah. Yeah. Alright, let's go get some food and some beer.
From Planet Beer. It's gonna be back. Back in the fucking sack.