You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content!
If you are not a premium subscriber, please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately!
*laughs*
*explosion*
Alright, we're recording.
I'm stuck in the peanut butter, Lois.
It's me, it's me, Peanut Griffin.
Peanut Griffin.
Peanut Grif- Lois, please.
*laughs*
*gibberish*
Friggin' crap.
I'm stuck in the peanut butter again.
I'm drowning in the peanut butter.
Peta, it's just your arm.
No, it's my whole body.
I'm drowning in the peanut butter.
I'm drowning right now. I'll stick my thumb in this side.
I'm stuck.
That's how you get a work around not being able to do an impression of somebody.
You feel like, "Oh, it's them."
It's an impression of them stuck in peanut butter.
Yeah, it's them, but they're like stuck underwater.
This is Barack Obama.
I'm Barack Obama, I'm drunk too, I have food stuck in my throat!
I'm choking!
I'm choking, somebody help me!
I'm Barack Obama!
It's me, Obama, and I'm choking on food!
Help me! I have food in my mouth too!
I know it's me, but it's Obama, and I'm asking for food!
I'm choking at Harvard!
Now let me be clear!
The CPI on me right now!
(laughing)
- Now let me be clear, the American people.
- I'm getting just lightheaded.
- You've been lightheaded.
You're lightheaded 'cause I knocked you out
in Fight Club, bitch.
Don't even lie to me.
- It's true, you were.
- I literally just took Patrick out bad,
and I beat him.
- Yeah, you guys made me winded before recording.
- I beat him down.
So I wouldn't be--
- We cornered him a couple times.
- Yeah, so I wouldn't be on top of him.
- I'm not making that up.
- He tried to do a kung fu double kick on us to get out.
- And I beat him.
I think that's gonna be my new--
- Your new move.
interacting with you guys I'm gonna fight you I don't like that well you're immune
that's what I do. I'm gonna fight Patrick. That's what I used to do to Neil and Neil did not like it.
Oh that's because you were doing it to Neil. That makes sense.
The thing is Neil, the problem is Neil is specially trained in Kung Fu and so he
knows that he's a ticking time bomb yeah one day somebody's gonna throw a fake
punch at Neil and he's gonna fucking terminate him. I remember the one time that Neil tried to
punch Patrick he tried to punch me that one time there's two there's two
incidents where he tried to there was the one time I did something I think I like I
don't remember what I did but he turned around and started choking me and then
you turned around did you saw him doing it you're just sitting there watching it
laughing and I was like the first time I ever hung out with like all of you guys
Neil choked me I miss him did I talk to him today I think we're gonna hang out
pretty soon. I should have. I wanted to, yeah, I meant to invite him to come hang in New York.
Oh yeah, we're all, we all got, we're in, it's amazing, we're in New Hampshire again. We're in
Manche, Vegas. Yeah, Fallout Manche, Vegas. We got, we all got positive COVID tests. Yeah, so we
decided, we decided, why not, might as well. Might as well, we already got it. That's true, I mean,
we're building herd immunity. We all tested negative, but if we'd all tested positive,
we'd be in the same place. That's true. It wouldn't matter. It's like, it wouldn't matter.
Might as well, yeah. True. Either way, right?
Yeah. We could have fought it together.
Yeah. I would have fought it for you because you're so weak and I'm the king of Fight Club.
I never get sick, but when I do get sick, I get like... Man, if you get me sick, that's fine. I
don't care. But if you get my family sick, you get my friends sick, I'm going to fuck you up.
I'm going to get you sick. I'm going to get you sick right back.
I'm going to inject you with cancer blood. Whoa.
Yeah. I'm doing experiments to undo the cure for cancer and I'm going to use it on your mom.
Did you guys ever have the chicken pox growing up?
No. I, dude, I straight up, anytime I do get sick, I'm like out for like a whole day.
And I'm like, if I like, like have like a flu, if I have like flu-like symptoms,
I'm like throwing up for 24 hours, but I puke so hard that I think I push all of it out.
I think that's food poisoning.
You, I could see you having like a very like 1800s idea of what like medicine is.
Yeah, it makes sense. You're like yeah, my pepper. Sometimes your blood turns evil and you have to let some of it out. Mm-hmm. Yeah
Yeah, the different the syrups in my blood are in a minute. Yeah
Your humor. Yeah fucked up. It's shiny. I need more strawberry syrup in my blood
I got a lemon lime is
Over the top. I'm doing a cranberry lemon lime thing with my blood right now. That's cool. Mm-hmm
flavored blood mm-hmm did I tried to do tried to do a try to do a mule tried to
do a Patrick mule ginger beer blood with mint and stuff don't they eat blood in
the UK yeah blood blood sausage yeah Wow blood pudding black pudding explain that
it's like it's like congealed blood and it's I've had it before it's not it's
not good but it's also not it's not like terrible like but it just doesn't really
really
blood bites back. That's the tagline of Resident Evil.
I recently re-watched the first Resident Evil movie.
I've been watching through them. I have two left.
The first one is sick when the guy gets turned into cubes.
Yeah, and every kill in that movie is just stolen from another movie.
It's just ripped off. It's so funny.
Yeah, because it's like the coolest kill in Cube.
You know what that movie's called?
Yeah, Cube.
And they just were like, "Oh, we can just do that."
Yeah.
Cube.
Right, you know. It's Canadian.
Resident Evil, fuck, what's it called?
Apocalypse.
That one's good. It has like weird dogs.
the fourth one is like so good because they just like... Resident Evil 4? No, the movie,
what's it called? Resident Evil... It's where they just give up and they just like none of it
makes any sense and it's just like CGI fight scenes for no reason like and they
like fight it's when Paul W.S. Anderson came back to the movies he like he made
the first one then he and then he left and then he came back and it's just like
Paul Thomas Anderson. You mean Paul Thomas Anderson. You're talking about Paul Thomas Anderson.
Yeah, yeah. There's a scene where there's like just a giant zombie with an axe
That just like like it's like he just looks like like pyramid head
He just like comes into a bathroom and starts fighting a girl and they just never explain what it is or why it happens
They just killed the zombie and move on. Well, it's
In the games. It's like there's an evil spirit or some shit, right? No, no, I don't think I've ever
We're gonna read a resume. I haven't played one either. But um, it's it's a virus. It's the virus. Oh, right
T-virus testosterone. So you're saying that this is a coded feminist game. Yep. Yep. Wow. They're trying to take us down
Yeah, I mean think about it. We gotta get him first.
I'm inviting every girl listening to this to fight club outside Patrick's house. You know, you can't double team
Take me on and if you're above 5'5"
You lose by the decision. Mm-hmm. I'm also the judge
I'm also one of the judges. It's 12 rounds
And the last round is an eating competition and that's where I really clean up. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, you I may not be able to beat up every woman, but I can out eat any woman on earth
Mm-hmm. Yeah, and that's absolutely true except have you guys seen this show on?
Hulu that I've been watching which yeah, but have you guys been watching? Yeah. Yeah, it's about two women who combined their sisters
I've watched like two episodes of it the first episode I cried. Yeah sure I cried a little bit. Yeah
the like emotional part of the episode is she goes to a dump because she can't fit
on a different scale, she can't fit on a normal scale and so she goes to the dump
and they like weigh her like next to a bunch of scrap metal and it's like
"you weigh 600 pounds" and she's like "I thought I weighed 300 pounds" and she starts crying.
That's sad. It's horrible. Yeah I mean yeah it's awesome though. Yeah. Yeah. I would go to the
dumped probably weigh myself yeah you go to the dump to weigh myself just to feel
better about it cuz then it's probably like it's too low to read yeah you like
this sounds all about this I'd like to weigh my dump hey what's that go to the
dump and crap on the scale and wait that yeah how much money for this that's what
I would have done if I was working on that show as a cameraman yeah I mean like
while we're here I might as well take a shit on this scale right can you zero it
We're gonna add some drama to the show. If you eat a bunch of pennies, you can sell it.
I tried to get on the scale, but there's too much poop on the scale!
Another hurdle she must overcome. There's poop on the scale and she has to bend over to pick it up.
No! But yeah, one of them was like, the best part of it was they were like, "We's gonna get healthy.
We's gonna get healthy enough to have our weight loss surgery." Because they're too fat to drive to another town.
yeah yeah they can't even they just bike well that's a great that's two birds one
stone see now you're thinking like a genius if they use the bikes from
Spongebob those ones just float right it doesn't they are to worry about wait
they could have gone across the ocean as in they went underwater Tron underwater
they weigh negative they could go to outer space no that's true they could go
to outer space no they wouldn't be they would just be cool I mean just there no
If you sent to 1000lb Sisters to space
You might be a redneck
Here's your sign
What was the concept behind the "Here's your sign"?
I don't know
It made no sense right?
It made no sense
You'd just be like, sometimes you'd be cooking stuff and it's tasting weird, here's your sign
Yeah
Yeah, sometimes you leave the TV on at night
Like get her done
And you get to the Girls Gone Wild commercial and you pop a little hot one in your pants.
Here's your sign.
Here's your sign made the least amount of sense.
It's probably why he wasn't like the most popular one.
Well, because it's so funny that he just had like two other catchphrase comedians and he was like,
"Oh, I gotta, yeah."
Luckily Ron White escaped that.
They tried to put Ron White in with the catchphrase
and his catchphrase was just "They call me tater salad."
I forgot that he did "They call me tater salad."
That was his catchphrase was just they call me tater salad. It's awesome all of
them had to have one. He's like still I mean he's easily only one of those guys
who's like a very funny comedian. Yeah he's the only one who's still like
whole like Jeff Foxworthy was good but then he just found out that like you can
just do that and then lay in golden corral commercials. And smarter than a
fifth grader. Yeah. He makes a shit ton of money. Some of that shit on smarter than a
fifth grader. Hey I wasn't learning that in fifth grade. Yeah. I was learning how to
finger that's what they should be asking those guys they should be asking those
guys about over the clothes stuff yeah that's what I was doing in fifth grade
you I'm just bouncing my leg oh I thought we had a scratch I thought the cat was
scratching himself under the table yeah yes no I was just Cameron's oh but what I
was trying to say earlier is like okay so like the combined weight of like
everybody on the Challenger was probably one of those sisters or at least like
two of them. Two or three of them. And then if it explodes it's only one person dying.
We were watching that show and then we were just gonna say it because you were talking about
sending fan people to space. You replace a crew of ten people with one one thousand pound
sister. Because people weigh a hundred pounds. And then if the astronauts do, they feed them
freeze-dried powder. That's why when a freeze-dried powder dies you can eat a SpaceX steak. Exactly.
freeze-dried lettuces pieces she goes to space cabbage I was I was watching that
show gets out she gets a powderized salad that she's every day she comes back
she's one pound she's gonna make some alien pound she comes home in a box
that's right yeah she's got a she's gonna run into some some Martians that
are gonna hit her with some cosmic beams you're so fat I was watching that show
and that with the big bitch she's 600 pounds okay 600 pounds like five foot six
that's probably like all of us put together so she has so much fat that it
started that's all I got together oh my god Patrick she has a she has a horn
you know one for her forehead because she's so fat what do you mean a horn
It's like a mound on her fucking forehead.
It's insane.
So my question is--
Like a fat lump.
It doesn't have a point, but it has a giant--
You know people can grow horns, that happens.
Yeah, that might be her problem.
She might be all horn.
She might be the devil.
She might be horn all over her body.
She might have a demon living in her.
She might have a devil in there.
My question was, I was watching that and I was like,
if I had--
Yeah dude, if there's a 300 pound demon living in her,
you just have to do a ritual
and she's gonna be 300 pounds, dude.
And that's manageable 300 pounds. Yeah, I was I was looking at her. That's like
Kevin James. There's an incubus. There's a 300 pound incubus and a 300 pound
succubus having sex inside of her. You just have to ruin the mood and they'll leave.
Yeah, she's like a motel room for demons dude. That's why she weighs so much.
That might be true. A motel room for demons? She's been living in sin dude.
She's gluttonous, you know. She ate three pieces of cake. Demons are checking in there
and they're fucking with their big barbed horn penises. Whoa. And if you just put
What is it? You put Christian music on headphones on her baby, like she's
pregnant. Okay. Baby lump. Uh-huh. The demons fly out. True. You play some-- She looks
like Megan Fox. That's how they made Megan Fox. Fingers crossed. You play some
Lifehouse in there. Yeah. Is Lifehouse a Christian? I'm gonna show you guys a
picture of this woman and I have a question for you guys. Uh-huh. Hold on.
one thousand pound sister okay a thousand pounds i thought you were just gonna like
i gotta show you this picture of this woman i saw on google street view yes
okay where's yeah this isn't a real show this is okay this is just looking out his window in queens
no because he lives next to the dump okay so this is her okay you see her see her horn let me see
Oh yeah, she's got a horn. A little bit. No, I wouldn't call it a horn.
She's got a lump on her. It's a lump. I wouldn't say horn.
That's like a... That's like a Klingon.
She looks like a Pokemon. Yeah.
That's like a Klingon forehead. She has a Pokemon shadow.
She does have a Pokemon. Outline that, who's that Pokemon.
[laughter]
Black outline, who is it?
Alright, my question is, this woman, you are put in, let's just say fight club with her.
Your mission is to kill this woman with your bare hands, punches only.
How many punches does it take to kill this woman?
I wouldn't do it because I would never hit a woman. No, you have to. You have to kill her.
I would never do it. She's begging you. She's saying, "Put me out of my misery."
For me, that's different. That's not a fight club. That's a euthanasia club.
Okay, you're a euthanasia club. Okay, now the rules are different. You're a euthanasia camp.
Rule number one of euthanasia club, you can talk about it all you want.
Rule number two, do not go in the bathroom.
(laughter)
But yeah, I mean, what, a thousand punches?
- I'd say one.
- You hit it in the right spot.
- I could do, I could get one.
- Okay, also, no head shots.
- All right, I punch.
- You have to do internal organ damage.
- Okay, listen to this, right?
I punch, I start from one inch away from her.
- Why would Euthanasia Club would have more than just punches?
- Okay, remove it from Euthanasia Club.
- I do the punch from Kill Bill, two.
The one inch punch.
I punch into her stomach, I pull out a hot dog, I eat it.
Nice.
She dies because she, that's the exact amount of nutrients she needed.
She dies of heartbreak that she didn't get to eat the hot dog.
My favorite part about it is like, because if you have somebody this fat on TV, they
can just be naked because they can never actually be naked.
Because all of the good stuff is hidden.
Yeah.
They're already wearing a walrus coat.
Like they just, this person can never be naked.
you she walks around her house in the in the fucking show completely naked really
and just you'll never see there's not ever gonna be a nipple don't look this
up do not look this up I will hear you staying in your house yeah we're asleep
on the bed you just start using the computer to find that footage yeah and
then you give yourself a little one-inch punch yeah come on dude yeah no but I
would like to be that fat I think I could be that fat I definitely couldn't you
could you would I do not have the will I think I know I would kill myself but I
could do it for a day I think people who get that fat people get that fat for a
day no one day okay one day magical I wake up you know called big and you
wake up it's called big it's exactly like the movie be it's called really big
but I I accidentally go to the to the Zoltar or whatever and I wish to be big
and I wake up and I'm like, "BURNT LIKE THIS!"
(laughter)
And then the whole--
(unintelligable)
"What the fuck?!"
"Why would you do that to me, Mr. Virginia?"
"I was supposed to fuck that girl! That adult girl!"
"I never wanted to be a girl!"
But you're still like 10 years old.
(laughter)
You're a 10 year old 700 pound kid.
You're 10 years old and a thousand pounds.
Your mom walks in instead of you being gone. She's just like who is
this?
Where's my son? Did you eat my son?
Just roll it just the whole movie is rolling down a hill like a
Katamari.
I'm just collecting things
like a Katamari. That'd be a great movie. If somebody wakes up one
day, super fat and then they're like just a Katamari, just grabbing
that
yet
it is a good
of the arts and we're just a little bit
this is working up a pit bull chained outside the
worldwide is like a robin newtons
I was on the menu!
*laughter*
Hot dog!
You're a very clever fat man.
Yeah, you gotta make the movie entertaining.
I'll tell you what, you are charming, but you did slurp my dog like a banana.
You ate my guard dogs.
You ate all my guard dogs and I don't feel safe.
And guess what, I got a new job for you.
*laughter*
You are my guard fat guy.
You're my guard bull.
Did you see that shit that was like the
Some like Saudi prince has like a robot bodyguard.
- Did you see the video?
- It's so sick.
- The video under it is the same robot
at like a children's party.
(laughing)
So some Saudi prince, some Saudi prince.
- He's like, "That is very cool."
(laughing)
- And then he put like a cape on it
and like put like a little bit more armor.
But it's just a guy, you look at the chest,
there's eye holes on the chest.
- Oh my God, dude.
- So some Saudi prince was like--
- He showed up to that guy's house one night
and he was like, "You work for me now."
Yeah. You still have the suit. Come on. Yeah. I need to go to the airport.
It looked like it was at like comic con.
No, it looks like he's at comic con.
You get some like Dubai airport and like it's just got, there's like booths,
no cement floors. How the fuck do you get that thing on a plane?
You got to check it when you're the prince. You got to check it at the gate.
Dude.
Do you think the guy was sitting in like the bottom half of the suit on the
plane the whole time? Just like, so you just want me to walk behind you?
No, he's stitching the cape to the suit, like the small mesh parts in the suit, and he's
just like, they're like a married couple in like their two chairs.
And when we land, you wanna go to the Cinnabon?
You had to buy him two seats for sure on the plane.
Yeah, it'd be funny if he was flying economy.
Sorry!
He has to do it, boys.
He has to do it, robot.
you want like a do you want like a complimentary drink do you have motor
oil bring me batteries you're gonna have to upgrade to first-class the batteries
he stands up to go to the bathroom and as he does to Tara chips this is all we
can just rips every arm rest off of the outside I was walking by sorry sorry
sorry sorry none of the TV's work cuz the arm rest all the all the all the
fucking like complimentary headphones just get like stuck
twenty-five
respects
do you have microchips
and i think it's a good state randragham out of the airplane
that's a good doctor
start
and i think it's a good
uh... they just dragged all know this is a violation of my rights
i have different laws than you
uh... i have a robot
i have a proper
turn him. Yeah, he gets really mad that he can't board first.
I'm basically a prosthetic my whole body. You can come on the plane, but
you're going to have to sit at the back of the plan. Do you have a charger?
My whole body is a wheelchair. You have to let me on first.
I'm a veteran.
They put my brain in this. I was the best soldier and they put me in
here.
Yeah, whenever he turns his head, he...
Pedophile detected! Pedophile detected!
That's the captain.
Yeah, I know. That's what he does when they won't give him the batteries.
Pedophile detected! Pedophile detected!
Okay, fine, yes. Yes, yes, yes.
Concealed bomb on flight stewardess!
Scanning. Scanning. Scanning.
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
Pedophile with a bomb.
Yeah.
that man just the man in the bathroom right now is in the mile high is doing a
mile high club the man in the bathroom is doing a mile high club the annoying old
man snoring next to me is a terrorist eject him immediately yes he has the
power to eject people from the play yeah he's strong flips up a fucking like
remote control thing on his arm was like just eject the seat like bounces out
with the spring he just throws him out the window did he strong plus he could
just stand in front of the hole yeah yeah that's true there's a big robot suit he
would yeah I mean he should maybe start doing other security gigs like he should
be like a bouncer did you what is it that the the idea post the original post
was like oh this thing has so it's got built in business in guns cameras
party robot yeah that's like that's like I was PVC pipe and fucking like silver
spray paint. It's like if the Queen of England started like walking
around with like Krusty the Clown. Yeah. Or like an RC car. They made BB-8 real!
Holy shit the Queen of England has BB-8! We need a soy president so that
they'll make real life TIE fighters to bomb you. Who will be the first soy
president we always had soy president maybe no will be just not soy yeah you're
just not so he's extremely a soy husband yeah yeah yeah for a soy first husband
yeah oh soy first husband would be because what did Michelle Obama do other
than ruin the vending machines at my cafeteria
boy she put soy in the venue I don't know tofu soda you fucking nice up flabby
arms you man that's right yeah she's a man cuz she has a podcast now she's a
woman that's right yeah man shell mm-hmm man show man show that's pretty good
that'd be really funny somebody trying to make that argument yeah it's Joe
Rogan and Doug Stanhope just taking turns being Michelle Obama I love my
I love my husband Barack, but not as much as Spike TV.
Look we gotta really take into consideration that the vending machine snacks are too unhealthy.
That's a good Doug Stanhope.
Thank you.
He's not bad dude.
I just pretended to be libertarian.
Is he a libertarian?
Yeah I guess he is.
In his fur there's like a whole Doug Stanhope on nationalism.
He's like "oh fucking nationalism is fucking stupid dude."
wearing a baseball jersey that says libertarian with the Statue of Liberty
huge swag dude it's fucking I mean he's awesome yeah yeah I want to go hang out
with him at the fucking at his town hall state you know he has like a he's like a
giant estate in Arizona yeah where he just how you know he's a freak he lives
like in Arizona by choice he was born there he's does coke and fucking he is
like the clown wife his clown wife who like fell while they were doing coke and
when it was in a coma for like a year. She fell into, she missed the pool. And her diving board.
Her name is like, she fell, she fell. She was doing a clown thing. Her name is like Bobo,
right? Yeah, Bobo. She fell out of a car and she was okay until the 199 other women fell
onto her. That's all I've been tripping over and over again. 250 people are dead today
in a single vehicle accident on highway 95.
(laughing)
- Oh yeah, that'd be a better version of Final Destination.
- Yeah.
- Clown Final Destination?
- Yeah, just a clown goes, just fucking,
nobody ducks when they go over the underpass.
- There's so many clown things.
- Yeah, there is a lot of cool clown stuff.
- There's a lot of clown deaths you could do.
- Yeah, like a pie?
- Oh my god, a pie full of poison?
- A pie of poison?
- A pie full of peanut?
- This is a poison berry pie.
I think that's it. I think that's all the clown deaths I can think of.
The clown sprays the flower, drowns.
The seltzer.
Too much water comes out of the clown's flower, it fills up the room, the clown drowns.
He starts spraying it and it's water, and then it slowly turns pink,
and then it turns red, and you realize he's been spraying all his blood.
It's just directly connected to his heart.
hit the pin too hard. Yeah, the pin, it went too deep. Yeah. Or the Selchewado that the clown sprays at you.
Yeah, and there's blood in that too. It gets too hot and it boils his face off.
Because that's how you get Selchew to have the bubbles, is you boil it.
Stilts made out of cattle prods. Human bones. Oh my god. Wait, what, this is just a
scary clown now. Yeah, now we're just making the perfect scary clown. He honks his horn and it's a roar.
a roar. The MGM line. Sorry, I didn't mean to get scary again. We've already done a scary
episode. We don't need to do two of them. The clown is standing, the clown is standing
like five feet away from the train on the subway platform where the door's closed and
his shoe gets caught in the door. Terrifying. And it drags him along. Yeah. Oh my god. Now
that would be scary. But it takes a really long time because he has long shoes. Yeah.
he goes "WHOA!" His suspenders get too long. His suspenders get too tight and chop his
arms off. And then he becomes Axel from Twisted Metal. They have to put him in a big clown wheel.
Who would you guys, if you guys could be a Twisted Metal character, what would your thing be?
My thing would probably be... I'd be in a really hot car. I'd have a... I'd have like a... You're
locked in a hot car. It's a character who's a dog who's locked in a hot car. Because they're just
trying to be a carrier yeah i'm not gonna hot car russell terrier yeah it's stuck
behind the wheel just looks so sad
yeah yeah special abilities that you just got a c for like two years he wins the
tournament and it is unlocked it is open the door
that is crack the window that's the reward and turn it into the radio on
Yeah, I'd be in a hot car for sure.
What would my power be?
Yeah.
I'd probably go in a spaceship and I would be in the Millennium Falcon.
I would have lasers and instantly win would be my power.
I think there was like a...
Is there a space one?
So there was like Star Wars, every Star Wars game ripped off another game at some point.
Like there was like Masters of Terrakasai, which was like Mortal Kombat.
I think there was a Star Wars Twisted Metal rip off for the PS1.
Yeah.
That's cool.
it and like you had to like it was like a harder game it was like you know twisted
metal it was like a rated T version of it. Has he ever played the Burger King
ripoff games? Oh like sneak king? Sneak King yeah and King Racing or whatever.
Five cents now. Yeah I got him I got all three of them when I was a kid yeah it's
probably the only time I ever went to Burger King and they terrified me. Yeah
sneak King is about your you walk around a construction site handing hamburgers
to people so in a way that they don't notice. Yeah. Only level is the
construction site. Yeah, it was like a $5 game. It came with your burgers. If you got
enough burgies they gave you a free game. My cousins had like every console
growing up. A hamburger is already game enough for me though. That's true. The only game I ever saw my cousins.
I play that shit like an instrument when I'm eating it. That's right. You should see this guy on the hamburgers.
Oh my god he plays it like, it's beautiful. It's about the
bites he doesn't take yeah yeah my cousins had every console growing up
near the Xbox but I never saw them play the original Xbox except for the time
that I saw them play sneak King they were too afraid of the X on it they thought
it meant death logo opens up and it's all green and shit yeah damn they had
dreamcast dude and they fucking never they never played that fuck there's a
drink cast right now hey this cast is my dream I love you guys we're walking
around Manchester and we went to a hero place and the logo is just a Pizzagate
spiral and they just have it everywhere. They just have a bunch of
pictures of hats. Did you get a picture? I didn't take a picture. Oh god, we got to go back then.
Just like a hat. Euro world. Eurospot. It's literally, it's like
it's like the square spiral that's like the Nambla spiral and it's
literally just have it like. Is it exactly the Nambla spiral? The Nambla one is a triangle
but I think that the Pizzagate people say,
"Oh, there's another one that's a square."
- That's so funny.
- It's, yeah, no, it's like, it's very,
'cause like a normal restaurant doesn't even,
they don't put their logo everywhere.
Like that's not, you just put it on the outside
and maybe like on the menu, but this place had it,
it's like all, they had it like carved
into the wall and shit, dude.
- Well, I mean, we have no choice.
We're gonna walk in tomorrow,
we're gonna blast the place, okay?
- Well, okay.
- We're gonna put them on blast.
Let me get one more euro, they're pretty good there.
Okay, and then we're gonna go...
And I guess we gotta find out what's going on in the basement.
Yeah, have you guys seen Rampage, that movie?
Yeah.
I'm gonna go Rampage.
Have you seen... oh, what was it?
We were talking about it on stream the other day, but the...
the Uwe Boll movie called Attack on Wall Street,
where it's just a movie...
Uwe Boll, he did Rampage too.
He did Rampage? Okay.
He did, I think he did two of them.
And it's just, the entire movie is like,
gamer so mad that he just starts killing people on the streets.
No, I just remembered, I just remembered I saw Rampage,
because he gets away with it at the end.
He kills his friend during the paintball game.
- I remember that.
- Is it like falling down?
- I saw that at a sleepover.
- I don't know what that is.
- You don't know falling down?
- No.
- It's not like falling down.
- No, because he gets away.
- Oh, okay.
- Falling Down is also a movie about a mass shooter.
- Yeah.
- About a guy who gets stuck in traffic
and he gets pissed off and kills everybody.
- It's more than that, but Joel shoots him off.
- That's a funny snap moment.
- He blows up a construction site with a bazooka.
It's a really good movie.
- How do you get a bazooka?
He goes to a like a army memorabilia shop and the guy is like, "Oh, I can tell you're a
Nazi like me.
I'm going to show you some cool stuff in the back."
God.
And shows him a bazooka.
Did you guys know, didn't Uwe Boll like-
He fought Lotex.
Yeah, he boxed Lotex, right?
And he beat his ass.
Oh yeah, he kicked the shit out of him.
It's so funny.
And everything has gone downhill for Lotex since.
Lotex is not doing well, dude.
There was like a thing Lotak spent like $80 on two pies.
What?
Yeah, I just remember seeing that.
It makes no sense what you just said.
He spent $80 on two pies.
I'll have to ask.
They were confused.
They were golden pie.
No, it was like a mail order service.
It was a really good deal.
Mail order food service and he spent like $80 on two pies.
Oh, did he get like, did people try to like audit his Patreon or whatever?
I don't know.
That would be so embarrassing if people did that to us.
They're like, "We demand accountability."
And they just see me buying like skins for my guns on Valorant.
Yeah.
- I had to make my gun look Chinese.
I put the cool Chinese skin on it.
Is that so wrong?
- Cameron buying Blu-rays and then me buying groceries.
- Yeah, like a pussy.
I've not spent any of my Patreon money on anything cool.
- No.
- Yeah.
- But you had the computer.
- Yeah, that's true.
- Yeah, that's all I've spent my Patreon money on
is computer and Blu-rays.
- Yeah.
- We should just brag for a little bit
of how much money we have.
- We have a million dollars.
- I love having money.
- I love having one million dollars.
- Oh my God.
Oh my God, it feels good.
- It's awesome.
- Now we're gonna open up a restaurant though.
- We're gonna take down Eurospot.
- It's called Patrick's Breast.
- We're gonna take down Eurospot,
'cause they have the pedophile logo,
then we're gonna open up a shop in there.
- Then we're gonna open a farm,
and I'm gonna mill Patrick.
- It's gonna be called That Eurospot,
and we're gonna just change the logo.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Uh-huh.
- We're gonna change the logo to--
- It'll be like, kinda like an X, I guess,
but then with edges, like little extra lines at the end.
You know, maybe sideways.
- Yeah.
- No.
- What?
(laughing)
- Hold up.
You're gonna say it was like Malcolm X.
We'll do Malcolm in the Middle.
We'll do a Malcolm in the Middle themed restaurant
like that Breaking Bad themed restaurant in LA.
There's another one there that's like
the kids in all the...
We're gonna close the
pedophile hero place, okay?
And we're gonna open up
our new hero place that's called
Nice Awesome
Munchies Best
Lovely Awesome.
Okay, we're gonna put, it's gonna be an acronym, we're gonna put it on the front and we're gonna
get rid of the pedophile logo and we're just gonna, we're gonna...
Straight and narrow.
Yeah.
We might just make the pedophile, the Euro spot look...
Pedophile hero, what's that, an oxymoron?
Maybe just make it sharper, a little more triangular.
I think we're gonna have True Detective playing on the TVs in there.
And we're gonna boo when they win at the end.
Yeah.
I think that's what we're gonna do.
I love the first season of True Detective.
I think we're gonna put the
I think we're gonna put the behind the scenes
of Eyes Wide Shut where they say it's all true
and it was a documentary.
I think we're gonna have that playing in our restaurant.
What I love about True Detective is how
dark Matthew McConaughey is.
He's so good in it too.
I gotta re-watch it.
I watched the last episode of it
and that's it.
Yeah, I was like, "That's all I need to know."
[laughter]
I watched it with my brother when it aired.
When did that come out?
That was a while ago, right?
That was in '14, maybe?
Yeah, I was a junior.
Junior in high school.
You were a junior?
Yeah.
You were a little junior?
I'm Patrick Jr.
Life is a fight.
Life is like a box of chocolates.
How about this? What about this?
My wife is a fat circle.
[laughter]
Do you guys like Opie and Anthony?
my wife is a fat circle it all went downhill when Patrice died it's true
though so that actually is true yeah do you guys listen to the Chip Chipperson
podcast? Chip Chipperson is an original Jim Norton character I'm gonna need a
few more of these it's a good show it's a great show yeah now do you listen to
the black philip show have you ever have you ever watched chapo trap house there's
this guy named Philip DeFranco used to go by sexy Phil back in my days it was all
was that straight was his name straight edge Phil it was SXE Phil yeah it wasn't
straight edge Phil but people used to call him sexy Phil but I didn't know
cuz I've seen a sexy for straight edge I mean yeah I don't think he was straight
edge he looks like he would have been you look into those dead eyes straight
Straight edge did. Those are eyes that you can only get by like destroying your
nerves. When I was 11 my brother, I think I've said this before, my brother who was I
guess 17 at the time, I was really close to getting a straight edge
vegan tattoo. Yeah. I was 11 years old. That would have been sick. It would honestly be so cool. If I had known what
straight edge, well I was straight edge but I didn't know what straight edge was so I
didn't call myself straight edge but I was for most of high school. For me it was just the sex thing
was a big problem. I had a friend who was straight edge and then he turned 21 when
I turned like 17 and then he was like well now that I'm 21 I should probably
just drink beer right? Respect. Yeah you should drink beer. Yeah why not man. And then he used to
buy me beer when I was 17. Dude. Uh-huh. Nice. Josh tells me stories about he every time he
comes home and visits Wilmington my older brother just like we drive by this
one convenience store and he just always tells me the same anecdote of it he's
like yeah they sold me beer when I was 13. He just used to go in there, he's 13 wearing a
Volcom shirt, just like I'll have the Bud Light please. Give me all the 40s. Yeah
give me every 40 you got. I got four nickels. Yep. Yeah that's sick dude. Yeah I
know. I don't think that, I don't think you find those as much anymore. You need to,
you need to, we need to normalize selling beer to children. I agree. Yeah.
normalize selling beer to children they're thirsty - you know kids get
thirsty what are they supposed to do when they're hanging out with their friends
and talking it's so important rather than get it from someone that they know yeah
like did you guys have parents have bought you beer in high school my dad oh
I said I was rich oh yeah I my brother during finals week in my junior year my
little brother drank like a couple of my dad's yinglings nice and my dad found
out cuz he was counting them and I go dead he will he counted them cuz he knew
we were stealing him oh he wasn't like planning out his week no for on Friday
six oh he was like well I drink those on the weekends I don't want to like yeah
you know he bought like a 12 er for like the weekend nice and he went and noticed
it and like most of them were gone because Eric wanted to watch Willow and drink a
couple beers. I remember being 16, I remember being 16 and like having beer like in my house for the
first time and like watching like basketball and being like dude it was
like the sickest shit ever. Beer and freaking ball dude oh my god. But I just
remember he drank a couple of the Yinglings while watching Willow and then
my dad found out and then he opened all of them in front of us and poured them all
down the sink like in front of us he's like that's what happens when you drink
my beer I pour all of them out you don't get the rest and he we know he poured
them all one by one I'm going to the store unrelated I'm just gonna drink in
my car no but I like while he was trying to uh well he was pouring one of them
out I went to the fridge and grabbed one whoa I was just trying to fuck with him
and then he just grabbed it out of my hand and poured it out.
But yeah, I think when I was 16,
that's when my parents started buying me beer.
Yeah.
Yeah, they were like--
My mom bought me cigarettes.
I want my kid to be awesome.
I don't know if I should say that,
but my mom bought me cigarettes when I was 17.
I was never, my parents,
it was like this huge conspiracy I unearthed
once I was like 20,
when I found out that every older person in my family
smoked cigarettes until I was like 10.
Like my both my grandparents both my parents everybody smoked cigarettes
Yeah, until I was like 10 years old and they were like cigarettes are evil never smoke cigarettes
And I listen man. I smoke my mom's cigarette. I was so afraid of cigarettes until like two years ago. Yeah
Yeah, I smoke cigarettes. They're better. They don't kill you. They make you are so cool
They make you strong get addicted to nicotine and you need to have it or you shake. It's awesome
You're shaking because the power is like going through your veins.
You're losing power.
Yeah.
And that's why you're shaking.
Nicotine just makes me way better at video games.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
That's what it's for.
My mom found out that I smoke cigarettes because she went to Jamaica and...
She went to Jamaica and my sister...
Yeah, they smoke a different kind of cigarette.
They smoke a lighter cigarette.
[Garbled]
(laughing)
(garbled speech)
- My mom found out that I smoke cigarettes
because she went to Jamaica
and then my sister took a video of me.
I lit a cigarette, I took an aerosol spray
and lit a cigarette with a lighter and started smoking it.
And I guess she posted it on her Snapchat
and someone sent it to my mom.
- Whoa, snitch.
- Yeah.
- Snitch on the snap.
- Yep, snitch.
- Can you imagine, she was fucking,
She was on a Jamaican cruise, getting cornrows, doing fucking dabs.
Getting spit roasted by two hot big Jamaican guys.
You know?
And she gets a Snapchat notification.
Yeah, he was filming it.
He's Jamaican.
He's watching.
My dad is Jamaican.
Yeah, he's in the corner, jacking off.
She just gets a Snapchat notification.
Her life is ruined forever.
Yeah.
Well, she went there with a...
She tears out the cornrows.
She said, "This is seriously harshing my vibe."
She screams.
In Jamaica.
Yeah.
They got sold a mixtape there on the beach.
There's a picture of my dad with someone selling him this mixtape and he's like, "You need
to do the lion claw with me."
So it's my dad and some guy and they're going, "Nice."
That's sick.
Yeah.
Your mom, some guy was looking over your mom's shoulder when she opened the video and he
was like, "That's the wrong kind of cigarette, mom."
Yeah, but she had one of those old, like the old style electric cigarettes that are shaped
like not like the-- Blue.
The blue, yeah.
I smoked one of those recently.
They rock.
It was a bootleg blue.
it was a white blue it was a white blue I think I like where this is going to
eyes white whoa I like cigarette blue eyes white I got a couple of those I got
a lot of those actually yeah my head there's a guy one of my like great uncle
his name's uncle mark and uncle mark used to make my brother call him blue
I had badass but I would yeah fucking weird guy there's a little that's not
see that's creepy it's weird it's weird I'll admit that it's weird I don't like
it and uh somebody's gonna send this to a snapchat someone's yeah my uncle mark
Patrick has a snapchat family yep yeah he does I wake up every morning I do a
video I go what's up family with the family of family snap yeah with the baby
- Patrick_family. - Do you guys have Snapchat?
- I do, but I don't. - I have it,
but I only use it to send stuff down Cameron.
- Me and Patrick were playing Snapchat 8-ball a bunch.
- We played pool. - At the beginning of quarantine.
- That was how I used to pick up girls in high school.
- Oh yeah? - Yeah, dude, Snapchat was it.
- That was just how I would talk to my friends.
- Yeah, I was not even concerned with girls.
I was only concerned with skateboarding.
- I was concerned with girls 'cause I was homeschooled.
I wanted to fuck every girl
watch every Christopher Nolan movie. I did one of those two things. I just wanted to skateboard and
girls were an obstacle. That you wanted to skateboard? Yeah you wanted to skateboard.
Girls were just ramps to me. Yeah. Girls were ramps and rails. I saw two tits, I saw two ramps.
I saw butt cheeks, I saw two balls. You said, "Girl can I grind on you?" but she was not expecting
what was coming next. Yeah, put a truck in her mouth. "Grind this bitch!" Did you see that video
there's like these kids. I just grinded her teeth with this skateboard. There's a video of these kids and they're like like there's
like these drunk guys that like start fighting them because they were skating
like a spot near a bar yeah and like some like fucking like dude like they
they look super young they look like 16 and some dude like the kids like oh come
on hit me hit me and then like this older dude just actually does it nice and the
kids are like freaking out they don't know what to do and then one of them
eventually gets like he goes to hit another one then the kid like gets him
on the ground somehow and then someone just runs over
and truck smacks him in the head.
- Holy shit.
- It fucking ruled.
'Cause it's like, the guy totally deserved it.
You fucking punched a 16 year old.
- I miss fight videos, dude.
- Everyone starts freaking out at the kids
and it's like, the guy fucking hit him.
- Yeah.
- Dude, what's your favorite fight video?
- Oh, fuck.
There's a video, it's called Trailer Park Low.
And it's a fight at a skate park.
It's like some girls come up and then someone's filming and then there's a girl and she's like,
"What's up?
Trailer Park low!"
And then it's a whole skate park fight.
It's like the whole park fight.
It's amazing.
That one.
That's a battle.
That's not a fight.
And then...
That's the battle of...
Have you seen that?
One of my favorite recent ones is the one where it's filmed through a window and it's
like two guys and there's like this like tall nerd guy and then this like short
like kind of like like like stronger looking guy but then the nerd guy like
know some kind of martial art so he goes up and he like stances up and he start
he like he just like unleashes this fucking like crazy like like fighting
game combo and he just goes like and he like just like kicks he kicks the
fucking like sunglasses off the guy's head it's insane dude that's gotta be the
only time that's gotta be the only time that karate worked out yeah it's like
the white nerd is like the guy gives him some bring it on and like a Johnny
Dominican dude just like punches him once in the guy gives him so the guy like the
the nerd guy who knows karate like walk like he's like he's like doing the
stance and he's like jumping or he's doing like a fighting game idol stance
and he like runs up and he like taps the guy on it on the chest like he's like
aim lock on his like fucking swing you like around yes he babe Ruth it's crazy
crazy. Imagine Babe Ruthing this other shit in your life. Yeah dude, I Babe Ruth the dishes
when I put them away. Somebody put... His plates go in there. There you go. Just throwing a
plate across the room. I told you bitch. Somebody send us that video because I don't think I
can find... I remember the Twitter page it was on but it's like pretty... Have you seen
a couple months old? I'm pulling out in Babe Ruthing. Why are you pointing at my face?
Hold on. Give me five minutes. Give me five minutes. Close your eyes. Have you seen...
know babe Ruth is like the candy bar yeah yeah just think of the candy boy think
about candy bars right now have you seen the the fight video it's like two guys
are fighting and then one of them tries to slap one of them and the other guy
just goes up and goes like no way he or no he goes like and he like kisses the
back of his hand and just like knocks a dude out with a backhand - it's like in
like a pizza can is powerful yeah people underestimate the backhand is so
Because you get some fucking, there's some knuckling.
If you hit just like the jaw or the back end, you can knock someone out.
Yeah, because think about, I mean it's like, you know, if you swing a giant piece of wood,
the end of that piece of wood's going pretty damn fast.
There's another really good one where there's like one guy who's against like three or four
guys and they're all coming at him and he just fucking tanks their punches and a guy
hits him with a baseball bat and he like doesn't flinch, he just grabs the baseball bat out
of the guy's hand and then chases the other guy with it.
One's so sick, dude.
Oh, have you seen the Mike Villelli?
The Mike V, the pro skater?
No.
Oh wait, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The one from CKY4?
Yeah, of course.
Where he fights four people or whatever?
Yeah, I think that's CKY3.
It's either CKY3 or 4.
That dude rocks.
He rocked.
Is he dead?
No, he, uh, I don't know what's up with him now.
But he doesn't rock anymore?
No.
There's a lot of videos of him.
He did amateur hockey.
Now he rolls, dude.
Makes sense.
He did amateur hockey and he got, there's so many videos.
There's a video of him, like, breaking an ankle in a fight.
That's cool.
That's awesome.
That's still cool.
Yeah, but he got his ass kicked.
I don't care.
perfect track record and then I saw that one video of him and I was just like,
"Ah, come on, man."
Dude, you're a fake fan.
I'm not a fake fan.
You're a fair weather fan.
Uh-uh.
Yeah.
No, I respect...
I thought you were going to say he was dead or he...
I respect his skateboarding.
I respect what he did for skateboarding.
It just...
But the fighting game.
The fighting? His fighting stance... His fighting stuff?
His fighting stance.
His fighting stance is kind of not good.
Yeah, he needs to move his shoulders in.
If it wasn't for Mike V, we wouldn't have...
There wouldn't be two sides to a skateboard.
It would still be flat.
Yeah.
It would be like a piece of paper.
- It would just be one.
- It would be one circle.
- One dimension.
- It would be a circle.
- If it wasn't for Mike V,
a skateboard would just be a box still.
It'd just be a cardboard box.
- It would.
He was the first guy to open up the box.
- Yeah, he's a genius.
- He was the guy.
- Hey guys, there's a skateboard inside here.
- You guys, there's a whole skateboard in here.
- For some reason, I don't know why,
but I thought that skateboarding was like 150 years old.
And so when I found out.
(laughing)
So when I found out that it was invented in like the 80s,
it blew my mind.
- It was invented in the 50s.
No, but like, you know, skateboarding in pools or whatever.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like the Lords of Dogtown.
That's '70s.
Yeah, that blew my mind.
That's like late '70s, early '80s, late '70s.
I was like, the man who invented the skateboard, probably Thomas Edison, is dead now.
Yeah.
Yeah, there's no way.
I mean, they had skateboards back then, but it was just like...
But they called them horses.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They used to try and do tricks with horses.
Yeah.
Oh, you try to do a backside flip on a horse?
Nah, they used to do a horse air.
they had skateboards back then but it was just they would just use it as like a
thing in the home where they'd put they put your wife's baby on it your your
wife's chair they would just put two skateboards under the chair legs and if
your wife is talking back to you just push the chair yeah yeah that's what
they use them for back then and they that's what a skateboard used to be no
now they've been in the hip hop now they use it to tattoos snapbacks and tattoos
this is Rob dad dick. This is disgusting. Rob dad dick? Yeah. He's a dad now. Rob bird flick. He does have a dad.
Bird flick? Yeah. Get him dude. Woo! Yeah Rob if you want. Rob bird flick and his friend big guy. Big black guy. Big black guy and Rob bird dick.
- Hey Rob. - You better not
ever talk about me again.
- Hey Rob Worm, Wormy.
- Hey Rob Wormsley. - Hey Rob, Mr. Hayley man.
- Hey Rob Shermstick.
- Yeah. - You back?
(laughing)
You wanna smoke one?
- That's what the DC stands for.
- Yeah. - Okay.
- Dad cock. - Okay blob.
- Diet Coke. - Diet Coke.
- DC stands for Diet Coke shoes.
- DC shoes is Diet Coke shoes.
- Yeah. - That's delicious.
- That's delicious.
- DC, DC's got good shoes now.
do that yes they used to not but when i was he's really closer she has gone up
it was very is for you know
journeys to wax what i do know yes sir that was for that was for kids who
competed who could beat up their mom we have no one's i'd need for my life
becomes swag it's remember that yeah i remember that yeah
that's what they were always we had we called them out the other way rappers
that you know i rappers from my high school appointed to it is literally down
the street yet more in all the way you were in my school much
But all the white rappers I went to high school with
were all like DC fitted hat and DC shirt and the shoes.
- So sick. - Yeah.
- People who wore DC shoes in my school
all wanted to join the Marines and also to kill a teacher.
- Right, but they all wore the DC court graphic
or the DC, like very specific,
like the DC shoe that is just the heel has the DC logo.
- Yeah.
- Or the metal militia DCs.
- You could tell me that DC shoes was like
owned and operated by the state of israel and i would just believe you
it would make perfect sense
yeah
you know course it's got to be some sort of
well yeah i mean they've been re-releasing their old shoes from the
early nineties
yeah i bet you hate that
no i love that really yeah
because they look fucking sick but you hated reboots
i hate reboots of movies
yeah the earlier patrick tweet is like
you know they're making a monkey ball
reboot suck my dick
I was fucking, what?
Make something fucking new.
(Laughter)
(Unintelligible)
What's wrong with that?
(Laughter)
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to come for you.
That's true though.
Yeah, no, you just hate reboots.
Me personally, I'm a sage
and I do not care.
They could reboot my family and I wouldn't care.
They could do...
I wouldn't care. No, I wouldn't care at all.
- You can reboot me, but the minute you reboot my friends
and my family, we're gonna have a problem.
- Don't you dare reboot my computer.
I'll delete you.
(laughing)
- You reboot me, my family, my friends, or my computer?
- I'm gonna reboot your PC.
- I'm coming to your house.
I'm coming to your house and I'm gonna show you my gifts.
- I'm gonna show you a gift that's an eye roll.
- I'm gonna show you the gift from Commando
and you're gonna get scared the hell out of your mind.
- Listen, I'm gonna come to your house
and I'm gonna be sarcastic, okay?
(laughing)
I'm gonna be a real smartass.
I'm gonna be such a jackwagon.
I'm going David Spade level of snark.
You're gonna drop something in the kitchen and guess what, I'm gonna be there and I'm
gonna say, "Huh, nice."
I'm gonna start clapping.
I'm gonna do a slow clap.
I'm gonna start clapping in your restaurant when you drop the fucking beef tips.
I'm gonna be a real stinker.
You're gonna do something, you're gonna do something in your house and I'm gonna say,
"Hey, the 80s called.
They want their thing you did in your house back."
They want their house back.
you're gonna do something. The 80's called, they want your kids back.
You're gonna do something? I'm gonna be right behind you and I'm gonna say
so that just happened. So I guess that's a thing now. So I guess that's a thing.
Owned. I'm gonna talk so much smack to you. Oh you're gonna be in a world of smack talk.
You're gonna be in a world of smack talk. I'm gonna be such a smart aleck to you.
I'm gonna go on smack high I'm gonna throw so much shade you're gonna go on smack
high New Hampshire oh you're I'm gonna sass you I'm a sassy assassin I'm the
sassy assassin I'm a sassy assassin I'm gonna come to your house I'm a sass you
up yeah I'm gonna snipe you with you I'm gonna I'm gonna pop in front of your
window while you're like about to put something on table go yeah I'm gonna say
Mmm, okay. Mmm.
Okay, let's not do that.
I'm gonna do the Marge Simpson.
Mmm.
Homie.
Homer!
[laughs]
Homer Simpson.
You have been beckoned by me, Marge.
Homer, it's your wife, Marge!
Homer. Homer, please.
Please fuck me, Homer.
Homer.
Homer!
[laughs]
Homer, it's Marge!
[garbled]
Our kids are doing mischief!
(laughter)
- Part.
- Yeah.
- Marge sees Homer eating too many pork chops
and she goes,
(screams)
- Sometimes you gotta crack a dolphin laugh.
You know?
- Yeah, I got on smack high New Hampshire in high school.
- I'm gonna smack you until you're high.
You're gonna be slapped silly.
- I gotta find that picture,
but it's a photo of me and my friends
and we're waving a flag, it's just an RIP Tupac flag
at a hockey game.
- Nice. - Yeah.
- It's cool.
- That's a bit of Patrick lore.
We're in New Hampshire now,
remembering all these fucking stupid ass things.
- Ghosts, the ghosts here.
- Ghosts of my past.
- They're everywhere.
- Ghosts of my life.
- I keep noticing them.
- If we go to London area tomorrow,
I'm gonna just point at everything.
- We're gonna make a tour video.
- I think we should just make an episode
of us just walking around.
- Yeah, we make a tour.
- It'll be the New York vlog, dude.
- Yeah, we could do that, I have the camera.
You know, Mark Maron used to do those episodes where like, there's one where he goes to the Creation Museum.
Yeah.
And he's just like, "He's a bunch of crap."
"Yeah, I don't believe any of this stuff."
"Yeah, I'm shitting my pants."
"Yeah, actually, I don't believe this stuff."
Yeah.
"I don't actually believe this. Can you- who- who are the guys?"
"Yeah."
"Who are the guys that did Creation?"
"Yeah, who are the guys?"
"Noah, Abraham."
"Look, I'll tell them maybe if they understood Zappa."
"Yeah, but they don't."
"But I fucked his daughter."
"I don't understand Zappa."
I understand him because I've had sex with his daughter.
I had sex with his daughter, but I still don't get Zappa.
It is funny.
He'd be such a fan of a musician.
No, he had a whole thing in--
I'm going to fuck his daughter.
Oh, no, no, it was Captain Beefheart.
No, he loves Zappa.
He's like, I can't get into Beefheart, man.
I remember that.
I think I listened to the episode of his--
or was it--
That was a special.
Yeah, I remember.
Yeah, yeah.
He just talks about Beefheart.
That's insane to have a comedy special,
he's like yeah I can't get into Captain Beefheart that's just an insane way to
start right that's cuz he I mean he's like he thinks he's being like it's like
a cool person dog whistle yeah yeah no he's like well I mean for me it's just
it's a h14 it's a dog whistle for everyone who looks exactly like mark
right yeah yeah true right yeah me at age 14 I'm not wearing like denim
underwear. Oh yeah, yeah.
That has the people who do like...
It's like if you just removed all the dye and tattoos from
from Riff Raff. That's the type of person
that thinks that's cool. Just you run them through a washing machine.
Yeah.
Oh fuck. Just geometric facial hair and shit. That's the
that's the kind of absolutely I heard I heard that special the thinki pain one
where he's like I can't get in a beef heart man yeah and then I listen to safe
as milk and I was like how the what how do you not fuck it this is so easy to
get into yeah you just listen to it right zigzag wander is a great song so
it was a I like a whip-wop woman I like Dachau blues that's a good one
I love that go blues bat-chain puller bat-chain puller is a great song
guy and he always he did in between the song he's like a guy went crazy and he
jumped into a bag yeah cool and the song starts right it's awesome you're
thinking of love shack yeah yeah say a faded road now go keep going come on
show us the song dude I'll sing the whole thing a love shack my dad and my mom's
whole thing when they were married it was when they had sex karaoke yeah when
karaoke was around yeah they would do love shack together your dad would be the
gay voice yeah my dad is completely tone-deaf oh yeah me too
I remember my mom told me a story about my dad where she bought he was like I
want to get into guitar she's like okay so bottom a guitar for his birthday and
then he started practicing and he practiced for a week and it was so
horrible that my mom stole the guitar and returned it while he was out of the
house. Oh my god. She was like I just can't. She didn't even let him grow. Didn't even let
him grow. Well no, I mean my dad's really like can't understand like yeah like he
he'll try to like sing along with songs and he just I mean he's so fucking he's
sounds deaf. Yeah yeah I mean I sound deaf when I sing along. That's why my dad
loves like John Mellencamp. Yeah. You know like that's what he just likes
just like a song about a story. No that's Bruce Springsteen. They're all songs
about stories. That's true. John Mellencamp has some great. Little Diddy.
Little Dragon Man. Hangin' on. Suckin' on chili dogs. By the taste of your breath. Hangin' with your friends.
Suckin' on a chili dog. Oh yeah! Chili dogs. Yeah man that was the whole
thing in like the 70s and 80s is you could just be like if you just said like
yeah I'm like an island rocker yeah you could just sing about being drunk in the
we just don't be the worst singer in the world and then you have one song about
like your ex-wife and somebody will be like this is a saddest song oh yeah
yeah it's a but yeah he's the all the other songs are like I'm drunk at school
yeah I smoked a cigarette at church I smoked 50 cigarettes at church I just
Smoked a hundred thousand cigarettes at church.
Yeah.
All those guys rule, dude.
John Mallenkamp, what's the Margaritaville guy?
Jimmy Buffett?
Jimmy Buffett.
Jimmy Buffett has some good songs, though.
Yeah, Margaritaville.
Yeah, Margaritaville, Cheeseburger in Paradise.
Cheeseburger in, when I was vegan,
my dad would play that song to mock me.
Yeah?
Yeah, he'd be like, this is you, fucking gay bitch.
(laughing)
You want a burger so bad you can't.
Yeah, I'd be like, yeah.
That's how my aunts still are with my girlfriend.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, they still make vegan jokes.
It's been like five, we've been together five years.
They're still--
- That rocks.
- Dude, they do not--
- My girlfriend's dad makes fun of her
every time they eat a meal for being vegetarian.
- Why is a girl's vegetarian and guys meat meat?
- I was pescatarian.
- That means nothing.
- That really does mean nothing.
- That literally means nothing.
- All that means is I got the filet-o-fish at McDonald's.
That was it.
(laughing)
That's it.
be like yeah I'm avoiding rice yeah like it's not a you know no Constitution to
that well I couldn't quit shrimp I couldn't quit shrimp yeah I mean the
shrimp keeps ironically reeling me back in yeah all right we're at an hour and
two minutes okay let's do ten minutes let's see ten more minutes dude yeah we
just supposed to do ten minutes we already are 50 minutes over oh my bad no
- So stupid.
- Dude, we have--
- 15 minutes over?
- How often do we get together,
sit at the squeakiest table in the world?
- This is literally, this is the table--
- In a room that, what have you farted in?
And I can't tell which one.
- I bet it's the cat.
- No, it's the cat.
- One of the cat's shit.
- It's you.
- In the room that we're gonna sleep in.
- Dude, I forget that we're sleeping in the cat shit room.
- No, they shit more in that one than the--
- What one?
- My office.
- Oh yeah, me and Cam, we are snuggling up tonight.
- Yeah.
- If anybody's lonely on this Saturday night,
just imagine me and Cam.
Me plugged into him like a nightmare.
- I mean, yeah, no, I can snuggle with Caleb, that's fine.
I've done it before.
- I'm telling you about the air mattress
because I feel like Caleb will have a power trip
about sleeping on the air mattress.
- I would sleep on the air mattress.
- We could pair a power trip.
- Caleb would, when I'm blowing,
the whole time I'm blowing up the air mattress,
Caleb would be like,
oh yeah, I'm gonna love sleeping on this.
- I'm not sarcastic.
- Oh, I'm gonna love this.
I'm gonna love sleeping on the air mattress.
If you insinuate I'm sarcastic one more time,
I'm gonna fight club you again.
In your own home.
You can't fight club me in here.
I'm extending the boundaries of fight club.
We have too many plants and glasses around.
You have no security cameras and you can never prove it.
I think we're gonna take a walk after this.
Yeah, we're gonna take a walk in the courtyard.
I think we're gonna go hang out outside.
Yeah, there's like this area of town that's all graffiti and barbed wire.
And we were thinking of going and hanging out there.
There's kind of like a, there's like this kind of like, this circle.
the circle and white chalk on the ground and there's kind of like these red
kind of polka dots around it yeah and really accent the mood. I have a really
funny belt for you to wear. We have outfits. We have very funny diapers that we're gonna play in.
It's not gonna happen. Why? It's called a costume walk.
Have you not heard of this? Exactly. It's because it's a southern thing. Yeah yeah
as in south of New Hampshire like Boston and North Carolina like that's what we
understand that you don't yeah why don't you want to fight me also you have to
wear you have to wear a blind why won't you fight me you would win no I wouldn't
you would know there's no winners you have momentum on your side Pat he's
always running I have momentum he's been charging up like Sonic for 10 years
throws a punch it's not stopping he can't I don't think he can pull a punch
I I'm also a bit more acrobatic than Caleb no not true all right what do you
mean what do you mean I'm acrobatic I have years of skateboard experience
you're balancing on rails didn't come on man swim team fucking third play team
third place when you have a team all you have is like kill the woman in a bar
that's true yoga my bitch makes me do yoga sometimes I don't need to do yoga
go Marty's oh Zen you're not Zen I'm Zen no you're not Zen I'm a bitter Buddha
you're Eddie Pepsi toned it's funny cuz you could just call Eddie Pepito and
- Bready Pepsi-tone.
(laughing)
- Yeah, he's way fatter than you.
- Yeah, he's so much fatter than me.
- Dude, you're bready Pepsi-tone.
(laughing)
- Oh, fuck.
- That's right.
- No, but I will fight you and I'll defeat you.
- You will not defeat me.
- No, I'm gonna do a spitting kick.
- You won't.
- I'm gonna challenge you.
Who do you think could last longer in a mechanical bull?
- Bready peppercorn.
- Oh, you.
- Peppercorn.
- Not even like, not even like fattening.
- Yeah, yeah.
Eddie Pepperoni. No, Mechanical Bull. How long? I could probably, I would probably last
longer than you but by like a second. I would rip out its brain. Yeah. I would
last like a year on there. I would last like a year on there if it was turned off.
Yeah. True. Yeah. You would die because of food starvation. They bring me food.
- Who? - My elves.
- The other bulls? - Your elves?
- My elves. (laughs)
- Okay, Santa. - You think a bull would--
- Okay, Santa. (laughs)
- You think a bull would be freaking offended
by a mechanical bull?
- Yeah. - Yeah, they're taking
our freaking jobs.
- Yep, mechanical bulls.
- Mechanical bulls are taking the bulls' jobs.
- There was a mechanical-- - Why don't you do some jokes
about that now, Caleb?
Do it like a funny voice and stuff.
- Oh, yeah, hey, I'm a mechanical bull.
- I'm stuck on the water.
- I'm a mechanical bull on the water.
Somebody call the mechanical police.
There was a mechanical bull at the farm.
There actually was a mechanical bull who drowned.
So we had to do a really quick land acknowledgement.
Because he drowned in Manchester, New Hampshire.
Before you ride the mechanical bull you have to do an acknowledgement.
This mechanical bull was stolen from the Native Americans.
They invented it before us.
And we took it.
That was a trial.
Every time I would jerk off in my parents' bed I would do a land acknowledgement.
I acknowledge that my parents have had sex in this bed,
and it's giving me a boner right now.
- That was the weirdest thing.
Like, there was, like,
oh, my cousin told me this.
My cousin knew, like, a kid--
- You know that Pat's story's gonna be good
when he says, "My cousin told me this."
- My cousin told me that a friend of his in middle school
broke his pube bone having sex in his mom's bed.
- Wow, dude, the smash god.
- The chosen one.
We found the chosen one.
- He broke his pube bone in his mom's bed
but didn't want to say anything
and then he had to eventually admit it.
- With his mom.
- Yeah.
- Mom, you broke my pube bone.
- Sorry son, I'm sorry.
- You knew what you were getting into.
Your mom.
- Oh, come on Caleb, what's that about?
- We gotta do another thing.
- Are you doing it?
- We can't end it episode.
- Nah, come on, nah, fuck.
- You're doing a Jim Gaffigan thing now?
Caleb
Yeah, so I ate a whole hamburger tonight did he just say that I have a gun in my
*laughter*
I 3D printed it in my house.
It's only got one bullet so I better not miss.
It's plastic so the metal detector didn't find it.
*laughter*
I just hid the bullet in my belt.
I hope he doesn't notice me standing up right now.
Oh, it's just one shot.
I have one shot at this.
- And that's why I love cake.
- Hot pocket.
(laughing)
Hot bullet.
- Okay, we can end on that one.
That's a good one.
- That's a good one.
- All right, thank you.
- Bye. - Thanks, guys.